Hello. Hi. How are you? Oh, hello. Want to start at 12, but it's 12.30. Whatever. It's a couple.
Ah, it's a half hour. It's all right. Bear with me for a second. I'm going to make everybody very upset,
okay? Well, actually, not really. Not really. I know that today I was going to stream yesterday
modded Skyrim. I was thinking about it. Some of the mods and some of the people in the community
have helped put together a list of a hundred something mods for Skyrim. I spent the better
half of the last day or so for getting them all. And I, some of them don't work. Some of them
fuck up the game. So it's going to take a little bit longer. And, and not only will there be a
shitload of mods on that Skyrim mod mayhem night, I think I'm actually going to get access to
Ghost Commander, or if you don't know Ghost Commander, Kraken. Kraken's extension for
Skyrim. So it's good that we're going to take a little bit longer because we'll get access
to that too, probably. Just going to let it sit for a little bit. I want to get some more mods,
make sure they all work. Because I, okay, I opened up the game and I had literally no idea
what was going on. It was just a mess. And I'm like, is this like, this is going to be funny
for five seconds. They need, they need a little bit more time in the oven. Okay. Let's just put
it that way. It's, it would have been funny for literally five seconds and we all would have gone,
oh, that's crazy. That's funny. All right. Well now what? So I'd rather have more elaborate things
going on and get some more, more time on it. So today, I don't have very much time today.
I've got a lot of things going on over the next few days into the weekend, but I did want to hang
out and we're going to do something called a comb stream. A lot of new viewers. Look at all these
new viewers that don't know what this is. When did you start watching? 2018? Please don't leave.
Like you've been incredible for the channel and the community's grown immensely. So like you guys
are awesome. Thanks for coming. A comb stream is, is this. Well, hold on. Let me tweet it first.
Hold on. Oh, give me a second. I'll be right back. What the fuck is this new Twitter shit?
I'm writing a tweet and it's like public or what do you mean public? What are you talking about?
This is freaking me out. I don't like this. This is a new feature on Twitter. What is this? Public
or my Twitter circle. What the fuck does that mean? I don't have a Twitter circle. What?
Okay. Anyways, uh, short hangout stream. Come say hi with a big smiley face.
It's so funny. All right. I'm so sorry, but listen, this is kind of funny. So if you've been
a few days ago, two or three days ago, right? When I last streamed, it's like, oh, mod night.
I'm going to get modded GTA, modded Elden Ring, modded Skyrim. It's going to be fucking crazy.
Mod night, hundreds of mods. It's going to be insane. And, and you don't, you know, you don't
pay any attention after that. And you see on Twitter here, short hangout stream. Come say hi.
Like what? What are you, what are you talking about? Where that's what you're doing today?
A short hangout stream, but I got a baseball update for you. So before we get started,
baseball, if you don't know baseball's seen a little bit of a rocky road here. Um, they had
some venue problems trying to still get the show paid for. It's been kind of rough with the show
creatively. This thing's ready to go. It's ready. It's been ready for a long fucking time.
But we keep running into problems, but I think I can safely say it's still happening in July.
We're really trying to really lock in the 24th, July 24th. And I think I mean it this time.
We just, behind the scenes is a lot going on and it's been pretty stressful. Nothing I really,
really speak of on stream. Uh, but we've had multiple different issues with trying to,
like I said, get the show paid for and get the right venue for it. And it's, we've gone back
and forth. It's been kind of a mess, but July 24th is the new day that we're trying to lock in.
And I've really, me and Community Jake obviously have been going back and forth. And with this
show, I need to get this show off the ground before August. I ain't, this show is, I'm not
canceling this show. There's no way I will do this show in my backyard. Okay. But no,
we're not going to worry about that. Uh, it's going to be a great show. I'm really looking
forward to it. I think it's going to be really, really fun. I think a lot of people are potentially
sleeping on this show. And some people are like, Oh, it's just a baseball show. Who cares? You'll
see. It's going to be a really fun time. But, uh, that's that update. Hopefully July 24th.
I just found that out today. I'm on calls, man. Cause I'm on phone calls. You understand? Like
it's like, it's every fucking 10 seconds. And I got to call my mother too. I'm not just not
going to call my mother. Oh shit. I forgot to tweet. Hold on. Give me a second. New noise.
Now that's the same noise repackaged like three times. Okay. It's a Skype call. No. All right.
So what we're going to do today. Hold on. Let me just clear my throat for a sec. I don't want
you to hear that. So today I don't really have a plan and I figured why not just hang out. I don't
have that much time today and I'm trying to get a lot of things off the ground over the next few
days as well. So let's just chill. Let's hang out. Let's do a comb stream. Comb streams are exactly
this. How are you? That's where I sit here and I put a comb in my hair and we, we sit her in
and do nothing. I'm not kidding. That's what this is. This is what it is. This is what the show is
today. I actually did just get a haircut recently. Your cam is skewed. Yeah. Why do I have like a
fucking hourglass head? What's happening? This isn't this, this camera. I don't like this new
camera. I don't like this new camera. It makes me look weird. I have a five head. It really does
look weird. I don't understand this camera and this thing was expensive. This was not cheap.
Did you have a wig on? No, I just, just got my haircut. What do you guys think? I'm a fucking
weird looking guy. You got the same comb. All right. I also shaved too. So that's why I just
look equally as different. 144 P Andy. This camera is not 144 P. This camera is very expensive and
it's very high quality. You look like 20. Well, good. Cause when I'm 50, I'll look 40 and that
makes me happy. When I'm 55 years old, I'll be, I'll be 30. You look strange and off putting,
but because I got fucking messed up hair, I just got, okay, let me ask you a question. Those of
you that get your hair cut every time I get my haircut, the first three days of the force,
the first like five days, I look horrible. I hate the way I look and I need my hair has to grow out
into the haircut for like a week before I look like a normal person. Does that make sense? So I
need to wait a week for this to grow up for me to look like a normal human being. Do you have lip
gloss on? Yes. Sure. It's coconut lip balm. Okay. Get the correct cut next time. There's no correct
haircut. Get the correct haircut next time. I got to get my haircut however I want. It also doesn't
help, right? Here's another thing. So it doesn't help that I have a new hairstylist every single
time I get a haircut and I get a card every time. So I go in to get my haircut because I last minute
Andy, right? I don't get my haircut for two or three months and I go, fuck man, I really need a
haircut. Okay. So let me get a haircut. I guess I'm going to see if I can do, can anybody do a walk
in today? And I do a walk in today every single time I need to get my haircut. I know. And I keep
saying I don't want to do that anymore. I go to, I go to a salon. I don't go to a barber. Just don't
do that. Just get a dedicated stylist. I say that every time, but it never happens because two months
will go by and I just, I don't care about my haircut anymore. So I just forget and I don't care. And
I go, oh, all right. So I need to get my haircut. Oh shit. I want to get my haircut today. Not like
three days from now, not a week from now. You get a bald spot. I mean, I got a, I got a bald head, dude.
Relax. What's on the shirt? Oh, that's a half shelves ago. Go big pancake. Your features are
too sharp. You look like Dennis Reynolds. No, I'll grow into it. I'll grow into it. And then I do,
I have a fresh shaved face. You're lucky I'm on camera like this. You're lucky I'm on camera
like this. I always have two days after I shave my face before I go on camera. And this webcam is
weird too. It's extra soft and weird contrast. This is, the camera is weird too. So that's the
problem. So what is a comb stream? We're just going to sit here and I'm going to just take your
questions. Not really. You get a weird head. Yeah, I know. I'm aware of that. It's really great. I
don't, I don't know why this thing was expensive too. What if I go like up this way? We're trying
a new hairstyle. It's just Donald Trump's hair on my head. You look like a conehead, maybe a little.
Is the camera, is the lens dirty? No, I need to grow into it. Fix the settings, please. There are
no, I can't fix the camera settings. There are no settings. The settings are so bare bones. I would
have to go get one of those third party programs that nobody wants to go download. Let me ask you
a question. Do you go get the third party, like let's say Logitech webcam software and install it
and use it? I don't know anybody that does that. How's that? Can we do a Reddit shelf tour? That's
actually a little bit better. Make it darker. What if I do this? It's the same color. Change the
sharpness. Drop it or increase it. That, okay, that way that looks way better. Raise it. No,
you don't want to raise the sharpness. That look like a fucking VHS tape. Does it like this weird
backlight compensation? You're at 985,000 Twitch followers. Holy shit, that's right, I am. Run it
through the hue cycle. It's grayed out. It's fine. Whatever. I don't care. I don't think I care about
the camera. It's a new, you know, it's a new haircut and I shaved my face literally last night.
I have a ring light up here. That thing doesn't really help, really at all. What have I got to
have for dinner? Porridge. I think a large porridge. I can't hide. Imagine me with a beard. You look
like from the 1930s. AI dungeon looking guy. You look 17. You look like, oh, what did you say?
Do you remember? Hey, me and the boys from our soap were wondering what kind of soap you use
to clean your body. Uh, I like Irish spring. What are you talking about? Is this person real? Um,
I use just slime soap. I use slime soap. It's just, you know what I mean? It's just the,
it doesn't even lather up either. I'm so, my brother used to give me shit for this all the time.
We would have this, you know, the gel, the slime soap, right? And he would get so pissed off
because I would go through it so quickly. And if you like, stop just sliming the soap all over your
body, that's what you're doing. I can tell. Cause it's almost empty every time. So he was, you get
mad at me because there was just like this in the shower, there was just the, the gel soap and he
could like tell each week how much I was using. Cause he would pick it up and be like lighter.
He's like, you're sli- you're sliming it all over your body, aren't you? And I'm like,
no, I use the loofah. And that was full of shit. I don't use the loofah. I just sli- I just literally
slime it all over me. Stop sliming. I know, but it's so much easier. You sli- you're a slime.
Yeah. I mean like whatever. Omega lol. There we go. I got an omega lol out of you. You look fake
today. I'm not going to go over this anymore. Okay. I had a haircut. I had a clean shaved face
and I have a camera that has a permanent soft filter in it and I can't turn it off.
I'm going to go get the Logitech controller software. Let's go get it right now. I'm going
to go get it right now. What, what, what, what, what, what, what do I need? Stream is derailed.
The stream is this, this is the stream. It's just complete derailed. That's the whole thing.
All right. What am I looking for? Logitech webcam software. Wait, is this even a logitech? Yeah,
it is. Logitech webcam software. Where's the real germo? All right. Logitech capture video
and record software. Okay. Here it is. Download from Mac OS is first before windows. What the
fuck? Why do you look so young? Cause you guys never see me with a clean tooth to the bone.
You know what I mean? Like to the skin shaved face. I never let it happen. You never see it
ever, ever except for today. Except today. This is when you're seeing it. You're seeing clean,
smooth shaved face. I've never do this ever. Do you shave your eyebrows? No, I'm just very pale.
Okay. It looks good. I don't like the way that it looked like this. I prefer having a little bit of
shade, like a gruff, whatever it is. What was shade? What am I thinking? What's shadow? Five
o'clock shadow. Right. Shade. Yeah. I like, I like having a stubble. Yeah. Right. Scruff. Shade.
That's fine. Should we try some new hairstyles? What are you guys saying?
Dude, should I try like going down with it? Yeah. Eat spaghetti on stream. Oh dude. I was just
thinking about eating spaghetti on stream last night. I swear. I was thinking about eating
spaghetti on stream. You look like Ace Ventura. That's fine. That's okay. I also have a ring
light here. That's, that's putting even more light in my face, but it has to be there because
all webcams have just horseshit awful chips in them. All of them. It's been
fucking 10 years and they all look like they're 480p. And I'm sorry. I don't want to, I don't
want to plug a DSLR in here and point it at me and have the room heat up another 10 degrees
that it already is. Turn it off and let's see. All right. This is without the ring light. This
is what it looks like in here. Better? You look like a ghost. This is not better. No way. That
makes you look unwell. Well, cause now the white balance is wrong. Do some muscle flexing. All
right. This is a 2008 vlog. It really does look like a 2008 vlog. You're right. Turn it on,
please. You're scaring my sister. Maybe I, wait, what if I do this? That's, that's much better.
Isn't it? That seems like it's better. That's more realistic looking. Yeah. I think that looks
better. Yeah. It's a granny ass camera. Whatever. Do you even lift? Uh, not in about seven or eight
years. What if I do this? Hold on. Is it like zoomed in? Maybe that's another reason why.
Maybe if I like, that's probably better. What if I go back to see like, this is, this,
this looks normal now, right? This is you having the webcam like zoomed in and shit. This is like,
not what a person looks like. They look, this is what you look like now. For real. You look real
now. It's like, Hey guys. Hi. It looks weird. It's like people don't have conversations with each
other with like the iPhone reverse camera, right? Well, I guess you do with FaceTime, but I'm saying
like when you just talking to somebody, I don't look like this in real life. I don't look like
this in real life. You guys know what I look like in real life. You've seen the videos of me from
every angle. You have American girl teeth. What are you, what does that, what does that mean?
Exactly. You have American girl teeth. You mean like an American girl doll is what you're describing.
They're fake. I'm just like pull out my front teeth. Yeah. I've heard it all, man. You got big
teeth. You got a long head. Your nose is too much. I've heard it all. Hey dude, you got a long ass
head. That means my fucking brain can fit in here more. It might be squished vertically, but it's in
here. You look like a handsome. I don't look like this in real life. I swear to you. I don't look
like this in real life. I've got to get the fuck away from this. What you, I got to get away from
this. It's how long have you been streaming for? Like 30 minutes and we're still talking about how
I look. I haven't got like, I got kind of a long head. Like, all right. New question, please. New
question, please. Will you play five nights at, I'm sorry, will you play long face? Will you play
five nights at Freddy's again? No, never. What's my favorite movie? Ghostbusters 2 and then Gremlins
2 or depending on the day, Gremlins 2. Dermot, do something crazy. Do you have long nostrils?
Maybe a little. What do I think about the rapid growth of the channel in the last year or two?
Um, it's cool. It's, I mean, it's cool that more people are here. I just hope I can keep it up.
But I'm trying, okay. I'm trying to not just do, to not do anything different, right? It's really
easy to kind of, all right, let's real talk for a minute. It's really, the more people that are here,
it's almost like I got to, oh, I got to fucking, the show is going to be great. It has to be good.
I've got to, everything's going to be super funny. I have to, I got to try as hard as I can.
Everything's got, I got to try so hard. But then I try to run into the wall there and I go, don't
just fucking do what you've been doing normally, right? Um, it is, it is like kind of hard though.
I really don't want to have it kind of get in there and screw around with how I think and how
I do. And then it's not, I mean, it's not like the channel was unpopular before a year or two ago.
I, they would, there's, there's been a lot of people here for a long time. So I think I've
got, you're kind of used to it. So yeah, I'm, I think I'm doing okay. I hope so. And that,
I mean, that's up to you. That's up to you guys. I could sit here and go, you know, I think I'm
doing a pretty good job, but that's not for me to decide. Um, like I said, all I hope is,
I, you guys still think it's fun and funny and that's at the end of the day, that's it. Like,
cool. What are you talking about? Um, did you just open the stream and hear the word like,
uh, I know, don't be mean, don't be mean to anybody. You do get, and that's also like,
my schedule is kind of all over the place too. And, and like, I'll be honest with you,
me having a really erratic schedule where I stream maybe a couple of times a week, two,
three times a week, it kind of, it's hard to, let's just put it this way. It's hard to lock
in a lot of things with a lot of different potential companies and stuff. When I stream
kind of erratically, sporadically, like twice a week. So I'm just going to give 50 subs.
What the fuck? 50 subs from pixel cat. Thanks. I don't, and by the way, I don't shout out subs
or bits anymore, but I just did right there. Well, yeah. Um, if I can keep going, I'm going
to keep going. And I think it's, it's, it's going well now, but could I like, could I broadcast
every single day and get on like the grind? But I was, I, I think a lot of people forget this.
I did that already. I did, I was on the grind already five years ago, six years ago, back in
the YouTube days, I was making a video every other day. Every two days, there'd be a new video,
even into kind of the lat, like a few years ago on Twitch. And then the whole medical shit caused
a bunch of problems, which it still does. That didn't go away. So yeah. Um, I, I already did all
that. I already, you know what? I'm going to be, I'm going to do this every single fucking day,
all day. Like I'm just going to do what I want to do now. What's the medical shit? Well, I don't
want to get this. I don't want it to be like the medical recap, but I have chest and back pain that
has never been solved. I've been to, I took like four months off in a row, uh, back a couple of
years ago to try to figure it out. And I was told it could be this, it could be this, it could be
this, it could be this, it could be this. And I ruled out a lot of really bad things. So that's
good. Uh, I'm, I'm doing fine though. Are you in a better chair? I am. Uh, yeah, it's good. You have
costochondritis. Okay. But you might not. Okay. There's a hernia that's in your, uh, in your
hiatal area. I don't, we don't think it's that though. Okay. You know, there's this little bone
right here that maybe it's called the xiphoid and it could be, do you think, oh, is that what's
causing it? Oh, I don't know. But no, I'm in, I'm in a new chair. This thing's great. This is the
Herman Miller. I know we make jokes about it, but seriously, that keeps me propped up. There's this
little wedge that's right here that just kind of is right there to make it so I can't slouch.
So it's great. It's good. What does it say? What do you say? What do you say? What do you say?
Yeah, just throw questions. I don't care. Whatever. Were you ever nervous streaming and how did you
get over it? Yes, I was incredibly. Um, the first, I'd say the first six months I started streaming,
I came from the YouTube world, which the YouTube world is you can mess up as many times as you
fucking want. You can mess up a hundred times in a row, a hundred times in a row, and you could
fix it. And it would be easy and nobody cares. And nobody knows on stream. You can't be in the
middle of a sentence and go, um, three, one, two, three. Okay. So that doesn't work. Um, so it's,
it took a little bit of getting used to that because I, for five or six years,
I was used to the whole YouTube thing where I could just screw up a hundred times.
What was the last time I streamed high? Hmm. That's a good question. The last time I streamed high
was I think saw two. It was just, I, that was it. It's not today. No, I told you I,
people think I'm high every stream and no, man, I can't do it. I can't. People will say, no,
it was definitely the hitman stream when you were walking around in the cement place and freaking
out. No, it wasn't. I made that up. So I didn't look like a fucking idiot. All right. Here you go.
Here you go. During the hitman stream where I was pissed off and talking so much shit about that
cement level. And everyone's like, dude, I remember reading in the chat, somebody was like, dude,
this guy, this is so stupid. This is hard to watch. There's no way he's not high. Otherwise
it's impossible. And I read that it was something I'm kind of paraphrasing it,
but I read that and I go, well, yeah, okay. I can, I can use that. And I think I actively said,
man, huh, this is what a bad time to be playing hitman right when the edible kicks in. And
everyone's like, Oh, yeah, of course. Of course. Of course. That's what happened. And everyone's
like, see, Oh, yeah, of course. I was stone stone cold sober that whole stream. Do you have any
kids? No. But now I've used that. I've done that too many times that people really do think I'm
high every single stream, which is bad because it's not true. What's my favorite soda flavor?
I think just, just straight up just standard Coca-Cola or a vanilla Coke or I've, you know,
I've really liked those San San Pellegrino San that right San Pellegrino. They have this blood
orange San Pellegrino and it's great. How long were you getting zero views on your videos until
you started getting more views? I actually, I don't, it's been so long. I really don't remember.
I just, I really don't. I remember TF2 had the big, I would try to get searched for because TF2
at the time was uploading, not uploading, but they were adding tons of new stuff to TF2.
And everyone was sort of looking for footage of that stuff. So when anytime, for instance,
oh, the medic got a new syringe gun that afternoon, the second that that update dropped,
the second that steam was downloading it. Boom. Okay. Let's go record, get footage of it,
talk about it, understand what it, what it, what it does and get it up as fast as I could.
While still having to be a video that I thought was like good because there were a lot of times
where I didn't do that. And I just kept fucking up the video over and over again. And I just
watched it back. And I was like, this video sucks. I'll just wait till tomorrow. And I would be,
I would get it out like a day or two later. Somebody said, have you ever read Animal Farm?
Wait, like the book Animal Farm? I've seen the cover a bunch of times. No. Have you ever read
Ender's Game? No, I don't read. I don't, I actually don't read it. I really don't. It's bad, but I
don't. Most of my reading is the back of cereal boxes to see how much iron is in it. Or it's to
read an ingredients list to see, does that have high fructose corn syrup in it? The heck. I've
read, oh, you know what turned me off reading forever? I read the Game of Thrones books and
I was super into them. And those are like 5 million pages each. And I was obsessed with them. And
then they just never came out ever again. So I was like, I fucking hate books. I'm never reading a
book again. What's my personal squat record, bro? I didn't do squats. I love that. That's, this is
like, this is such a, that's like, that's like the piano of, of the comb sounds, right? Do you guys
think that, um, the last Game of Thrones books will ever come out? I, I, I don't think they will.
I really don't. I've accepted at this point that I just don't. I'll, I'm okay. At this point in my
mind, after, at, at, in the middle of the last chapter of Dance of Dragons, in my brain, there
was this elaborate shit going on. Crazy story. Oh, Tyrion Lannister and, oh my God, Daenerys.
All this crazy cool stuff. And in my mind, what I do is I, I go to the middle of the last page of
that book and I pretend that a meteor hit earth in the middle of one of their sentences in the
last page. And that's it. And it's like, obviously they can't do any more of this story. A fucking
meteor hit earth and wiped out all of civilization. That's how I do it. As you had just a comet
strikes earth and kills everybody. So, wow. I, wow. What if, right? What if, I wonder what would
happen if that comet didn't strike earth? That's probably a real, that's probably the real ending.
That'd be funny. That would be so funny. At this point, I feel like he should do that. You know
what I mean? Does that the end of Winds of Winter or whatever? Does it have a meteor strike? The
book is, the book is like 60 pages long. I feel like people would forgive him for that. I feel
like it'd be like, that's actually really funny. That's such a horse shit. Yeah. And you know how
it's broken up by chapters by name. So for instance, if you don't, if you had never read
the song of ice and fire books, it's their chapters are broken up into the Tyrion one and then
Tyrion two comes three or four chapters later, right? Tyrion six. So the chapters are the names
of the characters and then like what chapter that character is on. So how fucking funny would it be
if you just turn the page and it was like meteor one and it was what the meteor was up to during
the, during a feast for crows and you've got meteor two, meteor three, meteor four, and meteor
four is when it hits. I mean, I don't have to give you all the answers, George, but
could be one of them. What's the shirt? It's hash house a go-go at the link. Best cheeseburger
I've ever had in my life. How do you feel? I feel all right. Are you going to Twitch con?
Probably not. Probably not. Way too much going on around that time period. That probably not.
We'll see though. I don't know. I don't think so. What Diablo two clash should I choose? Are you
kind of, are you a kind of person that likes to, you know, do spells or do you like spells and
summoning or do you like summoning? If you like to summon, I'm telling you the most fun you could
ever have in any game. No one's ever done it as good. No one's ever done it as good. Summoning in
all games sucks ass in every single game except for this one. I don't know what, okay, let me go
off on a little bit of a tangent here. What happened to summoning in video games? Because
summoning in video games became this, it was this cool thing that you could just summon a shit load
of things and have like a ton of different kinds of units and almost be like this commander to,
you get two and they're kind of strong, aren't they? I don't want two summons. I don't want to
like dump a bunch of points into one summon or like three summons. I want 30 things on the screen.
Oh man, I'm going to be, oh, there's a summoner in this. Oh shit. I wonder what it's like.
You get two skeletons or two specters. Isn't that fun? That's StarCraft, idiot. You're an idiot.
I don't like that game. I didn't like StarCraft. You know why? Because I played it when I was like
fucking 15 over like a telephone connection with somebody. And they did this thing where I went,
I was about to beat them. I was about to defeat them, right? I'm going to defeat them. And they
played this, whatever this character class was, wherever it was, where their building started to
float off the ground and I couldn't attack them. And I just couldn't do anything. He lowers all
the buildings and then he attacked me afterwards and I lost the game. So I was like, this game's
stupid. I'm never playing it ever again. Terran. Yeah, whatever. That was stupid. You got out Terran.
I was 14 and I, what do you want me to say? Out Terran. I don't have like 10,000 hours in StarCraft.
I was playing with my friends over a telephone line and I was like, this game's dumb.
I don't want to play it anymore. You said 15. I don't know. It was when I was younger. Wait,
talk. Wait, wait, what do you want to do? Can you look off screen when you talk? I don't want to
make eye contact with you. All right. I'm not, I'm talking, I'm talking like this. I'm talking like
this. I'm not looking at you. You ever played RuneScape? I never played RuneScape, but I really
feel like I should have. I feel like I would be a super RuneScape guy if I ever played it back in
the day. I don't think I could play it now. Can you say big Chungus? I just did. Oh shit. Am I even
on Twitch right now? Oh boy. Wait, what did I think I was streaming this to? Dude, am I even
on Twitch right now? No, you're not. Twitter spaces. Do I have any good other tweet, draft
tweets? Let's find out. Let me see if I have any, any, any good draft tweets. Okay. So,
all right. This is a pretty good one. So by the way, you guys, here's something you guys need to
know. Some of you new viewers potentially. I don't use Twitter, but I write a tweet and I put it into
drafts because I just don't want to post it. So I have like 30, I have like 50 draft tweets.
I'll read this one. I legit thought every show was filmed in front of a room full of overly
excited people until I was like 20. Knowing the truth was a Santa Claus 2 situation.
All right. I got to, I got to tell you this. This was from the 4th of July.
I was fucking, okay. This tweet is a bat just tried to fucking attack me,
is the tweet. I just didn't tweet it. I use Twitter drafts as like a journal.
Okay. So me and Holly, we're walking around. So I just like, Oh, let's go take a walk.
4th of July, whatever. Let's go take a walk. We just, Oh, well, it's like, Oh, cool. Like people
are out. Oh, this is interesting. Just taking a walk. We're on the way back, walking around
and going down around as we're through like the neighborhoods and everything. And we get close to,
we get close to the place, like my place. And maybe I would say a couple hundred yards away
from the house, like from my house. And I just saw from right here, it was just this like,
just floating right here. And I thought it was like a bug or something. So I didn't freak out.
And there were two other people walking and they noticed that I stopped and they noticed that I was
being weird because I was just like, what, what is, what's going on? Holly's right here next to me.
And she goes, she kind of screams and she dodges. And this fucking bat, dude, this huge bat, we're
talking like Batman type in the fucking silhouette with the light behind it. Huge bat was just like
flapping its wings, like trying to fucking kill me. It was like, it was about to kill me. It was
about to like start attacking me. And I was like, I freaked out. I screamed and I moved around. And
the people over there thought I was afraid of their dog. They were kind of walking with their dogs
and they thought I was like screaming at the dogs. And I'm like, no, no, did you see the bat?
I said, did you guys see the bat that flew over? And they're like, no, we didn't. Wow, a bat. And
I'm like, yeah, a bat. And I had Holly right there too. So I wasn't, I wasn't crazy. So,
because she was also freaking out too, but they thought, I think they originally thought I was
scared of the dogs that they had, but it was like, it was, it was crazy. And there are bats around,
right? And you see them from time to time. You look up and you see them kind of swoop around,
but never that close. What breed? I don't know what breed the dog was. It was just a nondescript
dog on a leash. I don't, I didn't, I don't know what breed the dog was. It was just a dog. It was
two, it was two dogs. They were just dogs. I, it was dark. It was 4th of July. What breed was the
bat? I don't know. It was big. This is a lie. This is not a lie. I'm, this happened to me
on the 4th of July. And it's not even that crazy of a story. A bat flew into my face.
And me and Holly were like, kind of laughing our asses off about it. Cause it's just like,
can you imagine if I had to cancel a stream? Like the reasoning. Oh, hey, sorry guys. I got
to cancel the stream. I got attacked by a bat. I got bit by a bat. I have to, I can't stream
tomorrow. What are your thoughts on the tectonic plates? I mean, I think we should stop fucking
with them. Vampire Andy. Jerma, I've spent so many points. I need an answer. Oh, it just got
deleted. It's gone. I don't know what it was. It was something about, have you ever eaten a bag of
warheads in one sitting? And the answer is no, because that's fucked up. Don't do that. That's
weird. I can't stream. There's a bee here. Are you going to release new shirts? You too, shirt Andy.
Yeah. All right. Well, I, but it's a surprise if it goes through. Yes. This things, this merchandise
that I've like, oh, that would be kind of fun. There's a lot of merchandise coming, a lot of
merchandise wearables, but it's cool. And I want to announce it when I, when I want to announce it
and it's going to be cool. You could probably guess what it is. If you could just, if you wanted to
guess of what merchandise could be coming in the next 30 to 45 days, what is happening in the next
30 to 45 days on this channel? What could possibly be tied in with that? What could you possibly tie
in with that? You know what I mean, Vern? I can't fucking hide and drink. I hate drinking on camera.
I always feel like nobody looks good drinking on camera. Nobody. Is it a bat shirt? It's just like
a big flapping bat. But that story is not even that big. It's not even like a crazy story.
I just forgot about it because I had a tweet that I didn't tweet. Why do you have the 2016
before Vegas camera? Make the, that one's gotten too. Mods are on point today. Mods are on point
today. Do you like hamsters or guinea pigs? Are they both cute and fun and interesting and fun?
I don't know. They're both, both of them are fine. I haven't combed in a while. You're right. Let's
fix that right now. This is too long. This is, this is like a little too long. I'll grow into it.
I'll grow into it. It's just a little too long. Once these come out a little and this comes down
a little, it'll look a lot better. Who's your favorite chat member? All of you. Nope. That's
a joke. Some of you guys are dicks. Would you ever be an actor in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?
I don't know. At this point, who would I even be? They've, they've like made every movie.
Well, who would I even be? The Joker. That's a different universe. You should be in a movie.
We make our own movies here. You still was, I didn't say it.
Oh, you could be young Green Goblin. I could be old. I could be regular Green Goblin. I'm 36.
I might look, you know what I mean? I think a lot. I might look a little younger, but I'm 40 in,
I've got to be regular. Why don't I be young Green Goblin? Young Green Goblin. How old was
Willem Dafoe in this first Spider-Man movie? 40 something. You don't look old. I don't want to,
I don't want to be young Green Goblin. Moisturized Green Goblin. He was 45. Okay.
So in 10 years, we'll talk. How come you look like so many different celebrities? I don't know.
I'm, what do you want me to say? I have brown hair. I have a, I'm default face Andy. I mean,
I'm just brown hair white guy. I mean, there's, what do you want me to say? I default face.
Give us a profile. Okay. My profiles are a little different because my nose is crooked.
So like, for instance, like this, ready? This is a little, and my hair is parted this way too.
So my nose goes this way. So my nose is more pronounced over here with my nostril because
my nose is crooked and my mouth is like upside down. I don't know. A lot of people don't,
don't know that about me, but take a look at my mouth. Half of my mouth is like normal. And then
the other half is like Joker mouth. Like I have like half Joker mouth. See what I mean? Like it
goes like kind of down and this way, but here it's, it's kind of flat. So I have like my lip
kind of goes down like that and my nose goes this way. So that's why I look a little different from
this angle because I've got kind of like the Joker mouth here and the nose going this way.
Whereas over here, it's a little less pronounced on the Joker mouth and the nose is going that
way. So my, and the eye is a little set a little differently because this one's set a little deeper
from head on. I mean, it's fine, but once you get an angle here, you kind of see the different
roads. My face has kind of like two-face guy kind of. Yeah. Cause my lip line goes like this
instead of like on this side, it goes like this. It's just like the way my lip goes.
And then this line goes a little bit further like that. So if I go like this, ready, I'm sure I,
whatever, I'm trying to move the nose and get rid of the lip line. You'd, you'd be a good rat man
instead of a Batman. I don't, I would want to, I would not want to be Batman. Have you seen the
new Minion movie? By the way, I have a question about the new Minion movie. Why do they keep
putting Gru in these movies? Minions, rise of Gru. Minions, Gru's in it as well. No, the kids
don't give a shit about Gru. Why do they have to keep tying it to Gru? The Minions is what
everybody cares about. Why not just, why does he have to be in the movie? Why can't it be like
the Minions? Uh, like the Minion, the great Minion caper, right? The great Muppet caper,
like they can't just have their own movie. He's the main character, not in the Minion movies.
This is the Minions movie. Minions. They already did that. There's a way there's already a Minions
movie with just the Minions movie. What was it? What did they do? Minions, the rise of Gru,
Minions film. Okay. Minions is a 2015 American computer animated comedy film produced by
illumination. Oh, there is a, this is a long time ago. The rise of Gru is Minions too. So wait,
did the Minions, they could, they couldn't hang on their own? So they needed Gru to come back
him up? What did people think about the first one? It sucked. Did it really? Oh shit, it has bad,
it doesn't have great reviews. No, you're right. Imagine not being invested in Minions lore. Hold
on. What, what did it actually have for ratings? Minions movie, like Rotten Tomatoes. I want to,
ooh, this is really, what was wrong with it? Okay. Let's, let's read it. Okay. I got tired
of this joke before the movie ended, but I appreciate the gusto with which the filmmakers,
particularly Coffin with his nimble vocalizations carried it out. Okay. Fittingly, because they're
pill shaped, the Minions work best in small doses. That's a line. That's why, that's why,
that's why they're a top critic. Top critic. What a fucking line. Seeing the Minions end up in your
happy meal would not have been a stretch in this absurd, tangential movie. Actually, it would have
been more to the point. Holy shit. These critics have some real bangers. This, these are fucking
great. Okay. Okay. Let's start with what Minions gets right. It's a mercifully short 93 minutes
long, but even at that length, it still feels padded. Merciful. It's, I just imagine this guy
sitting there just like fucking fidgeting in the chair, like, ah, it's like, you know, the last
40 minutes on an airplane when it's like a four or five hour airplane and you've made it all the
way through, but you only got like another 30 minutes left and you're just like, fucking get
me the fuck out of this chair. And then you hear like, we are now doing our final descent in Las
Vegas, whatever. And you're just like, thank God. But that last 30 minutes takes four hours. That's
how this guy felt watching the Minion movie. Calm down, dude. It's just a cartoon. Like right before,
okay, on an airplane, right before it's like time to, you got to sit down for the, you have to,
you have to be seated for that 40 straight minutes to an hour during the descent, right? So I know
that's coming. So she's like, all right, but right before we do the final descent, I try to time it
so I can just like get up, go to the bathroom, even if I don't have to piss or anything,
and just like, just like fucking get me out of here. And just like look in the mirror and like
wash my hands. Okay, fine. Okay, I'm good. And then sit down. And I'm ready for the hour that you
can't move. No, I'm not talking, I'm not, I'm just talking about, I'm not like going into the fucking,
the bathroom in the airplane and like making a bunch of weird sounds and stuff. I'm just saying
like you move around, you kind of crack your knuckles. I can't, I hate sitting there for an
hour. I would never ever, and this is why people are like, oh, hey man, you ever gonna go to like
Europe for anything? No, I could never do it. I can never do people, oh yeah, man, it's not bad.
Yeah, the flight to London's not bad. It's like 11 hours. Huh? No, no, no, no. I keep, I hear about
people that take these long trips across the whole world. Well, yeah, it's 12 hours. And then you get
off at, you know, whatever in, in like France. And then after an hour, you lay over for an hour,
you get another 14 hour plane. I think, no, I'll do, can I do it through Zoom? Just sleep,
I can't sleep on airplanes. It's, it's, I just can't do it. I've tried, I just can't do it.
One of the number one reasons I cannot sleep on an airplane is nothing to do with like being
able to actually, you know, drift off and go to bed. It's, I don't know what I look like sleeping
on an airplane. It freaks me out. Cause I, cause people walk up and down that aisle and I just know
that, you know, if I'm sitting there like, it's just like people are walking by going like, oh,
that guy's sleeping. Like, no, don't, I don't want, I don't want to, like, I always have a hat.
So I go like, put the hat down like this, but then you're like, and then it's like, okay,
put a mask on. You're such a diva. You know, I remember one time you want to diva moment.
I remember one time, you know, this movie's on airplanes. It's like, okay, it's going to be,
so for instance, I'll give you a perfect example. Bohemian Rhapsody, the movie. It's like, oh, hey,
by the way, there's movies on your TV in front of you. Right. So, and everyone goes, oh, okay.
Am I going to watch the movie or what is on long planes, by the way, at least like three, four or
five hours. So there was, there was one time when I was taking a plane and I loaded up Bohemian
Rhapsody. I was like, all right, Bohemian Rhapsody, let's go. I want to watch Bohemian Rhapsody.
And I, maybe I didn't start it fast enough, but there was a guy over there who also was watching
Bohemian Rhapsody and I was in the aisle and he was in the aisle. And out of the corner of my eye,
he was 10 seconds in front of me in the movie. And I'm just sitting there being like,
shit, I could see this. There's a stream delay. I'm getting the stream delay version. So I just
sat there and I was like, I can't watch this movie because I'm literally, I literally am seeing this.
I have this in like my peripheral, like right there. Somebody else is watching the exact same
fucking movie 10 seconds in front of me. So I contemplate, I didn't do this, but I contemplated,
I contemplated walking up to him and saying, Steve from Davidson high school. So he had
to pause his movie. And so he'd be like, oh no, I'd be like, oh shit, sorry about that.
So they're like, all right, I'll get back to my seat so I can watch the fucking movie now.
I didn't do it. I just didn't watch. But you know what I mean? Like the thought for one second was
like, I was going to wait for him to go to the bathroom. Like, okay, when he go, I can like,
can I catch, is he going to pause the movie? Fast forward. You can't fast forward. You're such a
bad liar. This is a real story. Like I'm not, why would I, what a dumb thing to make up. This is a
stupid thing to make up. This is a dumb thing to make up. I didn't do it. I didn't do that. I
thought about it. Like, is there like, how do I like, because I'm not, I can't get over that.
It's right there. ADHD makes you a genius in the wrong ways, but you would have to have paused your
movie as well. So that's why I said, all right, fuck it. I can't, I'm not going to watch this
movie and I'm not going to bother somebody because that's like, I don't want to do that.
That's stupid. I wouldn't want somebody to bother me. Like you're just trying to relax on a plane.
Like I'm not going to do that. So I just like, try to go to bed and whatever. But now if I want
to watch a movie, if I ever want to watch a fucking movie ever, it's like, oh, and the movies are on,
what is it? Stuart Little, Stuart Little, go, go, go, Stuart Little. I'm watching Stuart Little
first. Fuck off. I got it first. I'm watching Stuart Little. So, and then I just go and turn
it on as soon as it's possible. So then imagine like, so I get Stuart Little on, right? Stuart
Little is on. I got somebody right next to me, right? And playing and whatever. And I'm five to
ten minutes into Stuart Little and I feel, hey, yeah. Oh, I paused the movie. John? John from,
from, from Davidson Academy? I know this trick motherfucker. And I'm just going to hit play.
Oh, play. No, sorry. Enjoy the movie. Nice standup routine. This is a comb stream.
All the new viewers don't understand what this is. It's for me to give you all my failed material.
Who is your favorite minion? Definitely the one that wears overalls. You know what they should do?
Then they used to do this, didn't they? They used to do this. Wasn't it? The movies just started.
And if you, they just played at the same time for everybody, right? It used to be like that.
They all did. Yeah. All of them started at the same time. They would even announce it. They'd go,
by the way, if you want to watch Stuart Little, it's currently on channel four, whatever. And it's
currently about to start. And it's like, okay, I'm going to, there's Stuart Little right there.
You're a minion centrist. Don't stop talking about Stuart Little.
Well, you don't like that movie. You didn't like Stuart Little. No, you didn't. Dr. House
is in that movie and he's great in it. By the way, Dr. House is a great show if you haven't seen it.
Um, what's wrong with you? Who would win in a fight? Ratatouille or Stuart Little? Stuart Little
would run him over with the car. Do Toontown now. Would you survive the zombie apocalypse?
Anybody that says with complete and total certainty that they would survive the zombie
apocalypse would not survive the zombie apocalypse. I'd be scrappy. I don't know
if I would do it though. I would try. Where would you go in a zombie apocalypse? I mean,
the easiest answer is the grocery store, right? But that's what everyone's going to do.
Oh, I know what I would do. I would go to the newest showing of the minions movie because no
one was going to be there. Ow. I'm just kidding guys. I don't know. I'm too old to care about the
minions. Once the minions replaced Shrek at Universal Studios, that's how I knew I was too
old. That's how I knew I was too old for anything. I don't even know if that's accurate. I just said
it. No, you know how I know I'm too old for anything? When I found out that because at
Universal Studios, it was at Nickelodeon Studios at Universal Studios Florida, right? When I found
out that there was no more Nickelodeon Studios anymore, that all there is at Universal Studios
that's Nickelodeon related is a store with SpongeBob on it. I'm just like, what happened?
What happened? There's a merchandise booth for Nickelodeon. There's no, where are the rides?
Where's Nickelodeon Studios? Nickelodeon fell off. Yeah, but still, I mean,
you know, SpongeBob is, everyone still loves SpongeBob. Don't kids still love SpongeBob?
They still do, right? Yeah. Why am I encouraging it? I don't know. Have you ever done psychedelics
before? No. No, I don't. I never want to. I'm not into that at all. I'm really not. Why not?
I mean, there's a few reasons why. I think like alcohol and marijuana, they affect you in a way
that you still kind of have like control and an agency, right? I'm not into the kind of loss
of agency, the loss of kind of control. I don't like that. So no, I would never do it. I know that
like I've heard that you can, there's lower doses, right? But I don't think so. I'm not into it at
all. Not at all. He's a control freak. Yeah, I don't, I, no, I can't. But yeah, I mean,
I also don't want to encourage people to do something like that because I honestly,
I have no experience with it. So I would never ever want to tell anybody on this stream. Oh man.
Yeah, dude, go for it. No, right? Like that's, that's not something I'm ever going to ever talk
about because I don't do it and I don't ever want to do it. So that's the way it is. What do I think
of Ludwig's recent show? I thought it was unbelievable. Is it true that you drink a shot of vodka before
big streams? Ludwig leaked it today on his stream because he did it before Mogul Money and called
it the German method. Yeah, usually. Yeah. What it does is it, everybody kind of gets together and we
do a big toast and it's a good way to kind of, you get everybody together. New lore. I mean,
people aren't fucking throwing back like booze the whole time. It's a toast. It's a toast. It's not a
everybody catch together, let's get fucked up. It's, it's a toast. And it's a way to get everybody
together and say, let's have a good show. And usually whether it's me or Jake or whatever,
we thank everybody for being there, especially the crew. And I don't know, I feel like it's a
nice fun way to make a, and it's never required or anything, right? It's one of those things where
you can do it if you want to, if you're obviously old enough, right? And if not, then that's all
good. But I like doing stuff like that because to the person like behind the camera, to the person
like at the audio deck, to the person like in front of the camera, doing a toast, that's like a
let's get it. Let's do it. Let's go for it is a really nice fun way to do it. Toast to health
and wealth. Yeah. Oh yeah. Usually Jake will say a few words. I'll say a few words and we just like,
let's go for it. Mogul Money Live was unbelievable. Ludwig should be incredibly fucking proud of
himself and everybody that was on that show is a great show. I said this before. I said this before
Ludwig has it. If you're looking for it, you look carbonated, turn the full cam off. I'm trying to
be real. No, it was, it was a really, it was a really awesome thing to watch. I laughed out loud
at least a dozen times. This is Jeremy today, not Jerma. Kind of the same, but not really,
maybe a little different. You look carbonated. Is that your bed on the floor behind you? That's
the bed that Otto doesn't sleep in. Are you green screened in? No, I'm not. But yeah. No, I,
let's talk about shows too. I love that shit more than anything. Doing the big stuff is just,
I love every second of it. I love being there. I love talking to everybody there. I love,
I love getting in it, into it big time, right? That's what the focus is. That's what the focus
is for the foreseeable future. If I can, you look like a cardboard cutout. What would, what would
my cardboard cutout even look like? They all look kind of odd and uncanny, right? And their hands
are always way too small. It's like this, right? It's always like their arms and there's a weird
perspective problem. So this is 2D plane and it's like this. Do a cigar tier list. I don't smoke
cigars. The dollhouse was incredible, but that's the thing. I've, I've, I told you guys about the
stress of doing stuff behind the scenes with this baseball show, and I won't go into that much
detail, but trying to do these things is very hard sometimes. And it's like just, it, it annoys me
that it is, right? And I'm at the point right now where I'm doing everything possible to make sure
that I can do some of these big things that I want to do. And how do you do that? Do you
get sponsors? Do you have like maybe one of the platforms will, will do it, right? Or,
reach out or whatever, but nothing's ever guaranteed. And I'm starting to realize that
fact right now that it's not just like, oh yeah, dollhouse was really cool. Let's do another one.
Oh yeah, let's do another one right now. Let's go right now. Let's go for it. Well, how much is
it going to cost? A lot, a lot. Okay. Does anybody want to pay for it? Maybe even if we reach out,
whatever. And we've, for baseball, there are sponsors we've been talking to, but it's actually
kind of a lot harder than I anticipated. It's been too long since the last co-op stream. Yeah,
it has. It has. Don't do it then. Just play shitty 2000s video games. I would quit if that's what I
was just doing every day. I have to be, I'm going to be honest with you. I have to. It's these big
shows that keep me around. I have to be real. And I always said this, I never want to force myself
to do something or I never want to do something just to do it. Which is another reason why you've
seen, I mean, stream two or three times a week, maybe less than that. Cause I can't do that. It's
unfair to me. It's unfair to you and anybody else that had anything to do with any of the projects
or anything. What's the worst comb you've ever had? A comb is just teeth spread out very finely.
It's not, this is, this is, this is, this is, this is all there is. Now that was a cardboard cutout
here. This lice in your hair. Now what? Now what? Uh, what were we saying? If you had a hundred
thousand dollars, what would you use it for? The baseball show. There it is. Or other stuff too.
There's so many things I want to do. I have, I just, this, I, what, what am I even going to
say about it? But just know that I've been desperately trying to do shit behind the scenes
and trying to make sure I can cover it, make sure I can do it, make sure I can pay for it.
He's desperately trying to shit. You should host a fundraising night. That's a pre mini event that
I don't want you guys to pay for that. That's the whole point. I don't want people to mention,
maybe you're dude getting the crowdfunding and stuff. No, I don't want to do that.
I don't want to do that because I don't want you guys to pay for it. This channel over the
last 10 plus years, I have not done very many sponsors and you guys have, I've had so much
money has come into this channel already that I really don't want to fucking do that. I don't
want to be one of those people that's like, Oh yeah, I mean fucking thousands of subs a month.
Hey, uh, yo, um, people that have already, you know, been paying me a shitload of money every
month. Hey dude, I want to do this project. I need like fucking 200 K let's make it happen.
Community let's go. No, fuck that. I don't want to do that. I don't want to do that.
I really don't want to do that. Um, because I already, there's already subs on the channel,
right? I don't, it's, that doesn't, I don't like it. I don't want to do it.
I would rather have a company come in, be able to cover the whole thing and that's it. And let's go
and a lot of the, look, the companies that come in and help, obviously my brain goes, all right,
what do I want to do? What do I want to show? What can I showcase? What, what, what, what
sponsors do I want? And a lot of times I have to kind of think about, okay, does the show being
paid for? And that looks good. We have the money. Okay. Who is the sponsor? Who is it? And trying
to find the right sponsor and the right time. And it, it's, it's, it's a lot harder than I thought,
but no, I don't want my viewers to pay for these two, $300,000 plus projects that the whole point
was I didn't want to have to write the checks myself. So I wouldn't go broke, right? Cause of
course I, I'm, I can't, what, am I going to sit here and pretend that I don't make a lot of money
doing this? I would be full of shit. I'd be full of shit. So, but on the other hand of that,
all the money that comes into the, to the, to these channels, right? I have the YouTube channel
that has ads on it. I have this Twitch channel, right? That has subscriptions, but if I were just
to pay for the show myself, all of these shows, they'd be gone. It just would. And I don't want
to do that either. I want to also obviously protect myself too. Cause yeah, could I write
a check to cover a $200,000 show? Yeah, but it would be fucking horrible. It would be painful.
I would be, I would lose a lot of my money. It'd be like, it would, it'd be, it'd be bad.
And I'm just trying to be realistic with you guys. You could with a bunch of question marks.
No, I mean, I could, if I physically had to, I could move a bunch of fucking money around
and do it. And I did that before. I did it before. I don't want to do it again. Show ass
resident sleeper. All right, that guy will do it. German rumble. Oh yeah. German rumble live.
For those of you that don't know, I've told the story a few times. We're going to TLDR.
I, that German rumble live action on the YouTube channel was about $10,000. It was a micro budget,
tons of stuff. We cut so many corners. And at the time I had like, I had like, I think I only had
like $1,500 to my name, like available. I liquidated my entire savings account. I had a 401k. I wiped
out the whole thing so I could make sure to cover the show and pay bills and stuff. It was worth it
at the end of the day. 10k is a micro budget. Yep, it is. That was kind of stupid. It was,
but the show happened and it was a great time. And I thought, I thought it was worth it. That's it.
It was worth it. Did you recoup the costs? I mean, you could probably make the argument that over
the long term, probably. Yeah. That video did really well. I didn't recoup the costs on the
video. Cause I mean, ad revenue is not at that point. That was like 2015, 2016. I maybe made
back maybe 20, 30, maybe 20% from the video. I learned a lot, right? Like somebody said,
and a lot of people found that video and like the whole wrestling thing. And it just, a lot of people
came to the channel and stuff. So, but that's, that's it, man. Every stream he loses 1.5,
$1.6 million. But I have to be realistic. I don't like, if I want to do two or three shows
this year, right. And each one of those shows is going to cost somewhere between like, you know,
if you think about like just cost of some of these pretty big projects, somewhere, somewhere
up into the hundreds of thousands of dollars, it'll be gone. All of my money will be gone.
And it's like, at that point, it's not worth it at that point, because seven years ago, when I was
still, you know, a YouTuber, I, you know, knew I had like 10 plus potential years in front of me.
I don't know if I have that right now. I don't know if I have 10 plus more years of this in
front of me. I don't know. I'm not certain of it, but I'm also not sure of it either. So right,
like almost seven or eight years ago, I knew I had the time. I don't know if I have 10 years.
No, we're not talking about retiring. Stop. I'm just saying 10 years is a long fucking time.
He's not going to be streaming in 2033, because I don't even know what's going to happen in the
next two years. I don't know what, three years, four years, five, I don't know. I have no idea.
Who's going to replace you? We already did that. But yeah, forget about, get that out of your head
right now. We're not talking about that. The goal was always, I try to get the shows paid for,
not have to, because I don't want somebody, and this is another one of the reasons why
I pivoted away from, you know, talking about subs and bits and stuff. I just want to make sure that
these things can happen and nobody has to front the bill for it, especially with the kind of money
that I fucking make, right? I just got to protect the future and make sure I don't go broke right
now. Why is your face so red? Because I just rubbed my eye sockets. You're making my girlfriend
cry. What? What did I do? I didn't do anything. Hey, think about baseball coming up here.
Baseball stream. The German Baseball Association. Hope you can find a way to make it work. Yeah,
I think we have some solutions. I think it's going to be fine. There's no cringe in baseball.
Is it crying? Okay. Can you please smoke cigarettes on stream? What's your worst case scenario?
There is none. There is none. I mean, worst case scenario is, I mean, some, I don't know. I don't
want to think of a worst case scenario. Stop reading smoking messages every stream. You know,
that's true. But this whole thing went off because, you know, why just, just don't even do them. Just
hang out and play games and stuff. And I don't want to tell you guys this is not true. It's not that
I'm over that kind of content. It's that I much prefer the other content. I'm much preferred.
If you guys go back to one of the Spider-Man update videos from like 2014 or 2015, I talked
about how much I wanted to do big projects. It was something I really cared about. And
if I ever had the opportunity, it was when I was going to really pay attention to and really care
about. Here we are now. Like, this is what I care about. Is this a meatball? No, that's a pancake.
Hash house a go-go at the link in Las Vegas, Nevada. One of the best restaurants I've ever been to.
Got the best cheeseburger, best cheeseburger in Vegas without a doubt, without a single doubt
in my mind. Nobody paid me to say this. It's just true. You look like a tourist. Why? Because I have
a t-shirt on from a restaurant? If you ever were to retire, would you announce it and quietly stop
or would you make one final bye-bye? What you can probably expect. Here's what you can expect.
Whenever this is. It's not tomorrow. It's not tomorrow. It's not tomorrow. It's not tomorrow.
This is not happening tomorrow. This is not tomorrow. This is not next week. This is not
even potentially next year. I don't know. But what you can expect. This is not tomorrow. I will
probably announce that I'm going to slow down. Because one thing I definitely want to do eventually
when I decide to stop whenever that is, is I want to give at least six to 12 months to everybody
of like still normal shit happening. But people know, right? This is not tomorrow. This is not
tomorrow. This is not tomorrow. This is not tomorrow. So I would probably give a long lead time.
Because people have subbed it for a long time and there's a lot of activity in the discord and shit.
I want like a year of people knowing that that's going to happen, right? This is not something
that I would announce and then be like, okay, see you later. I was fun. Goodbye. I'm done. No.
There'd be like a full year of lead up to it. So look, you got, hey, at the very least after
tomorrow, you've got at least a year. Get away from the camera when I drink. I'm kidding. Just
relax. Oh my God. It is tomorrow. No, I'm kidding. Show ass. All right. Time that person out. That's
like the only thing they've written in the last like hour. I do have a great idea for my retirement
stream though. Like the final retirement stream. And I'll tell you what it is because I think it's
funny and I don't care. Here's the idea. Don't leak this and don't steal it. I want to get in,
I want to get in full old person prosthetics and in like a retirement home, be like sitting in the
corner eating peaches while people just roast me, you know, get, like get a bunch of people that
have been like, you know, on the stream over the years sit and sit there and I can't even,
I don't even know what they're saying. I've been full like $5,000 fucking old man prosthetics,
like slurring peaches and look at the cane just like, and they'll like address me and stuff and
I won't even look at them. And then I'll get up there when that's my time, right? When it's my
turn. All right. That was like, no, there it is the retirement. I get up there and I take the
fuck the lashes off and I give one more, one more fucking, I tell you, you thought that was funny,
didn't you? And I, and I just go off and it's like, holy shit, he's still got it. There you go.
That's the whole stream. The final grandpa bit. If we leak it, he can't use it and he can never retire.
One final sus face. What are you going to do when you stop doing Twitch? I don't know.
See, the reason why you can expect me not to retire like soon is because I don't fucking know.
I want to maybe transition over to more traditional content, right? I love making streams.
I love coming up with ideas. I love producing stuff. I love that. So maybe I would do something
there. Try move into that part of the industry. I don't know. I don't know. I have no idea.
You should run for president. Somebody, somebody would just leak the naked picture of the smite
tournament and like, I would lose fucking half the country. I would lose like, I would lose like 30
states in one hour. You'd get more though. No, I don't think so. Produce the next minions movie.
You ever thought about doing a live show? I've thought about it before, but I think a lot of
the stuff that we do on this channel requires a lot of sort of camera tricks and magic behind
the scenes, right? I feel like a live version of a lot of the stuff wouldn't work that well,
just because it needs a lot of sort of other stuff in the background. You've been recognized
in real life. Yeah, actually happens a lot more than you think. A lot more than I thought either
too. Just go to Hollywood. No, I don't want to go to fucking Hollywood. If I go to Hollywood,
no, that's how you know it's over. That's how you know I'm retiring. No, not Hollywood. I wouldn't
cut it in Hollywood. Nope. I would go to an audition. I would get told that I was not for the
part and I would cry on the way out and I would move. I would have the paper and I would be like,
like, running out. Do infomercials? Well, you could be an actor. I don't know though. I don't
know if I want to do that. Hey, Jeremiah, you ever show a barber a picture of a video game
character when you get a haircut? What video game characters hair do you want? I don't understand
what. How come every time I comb my hair with a comb, it just looks like I have a toupee on?
It's too smooth, right? This looks like I'm wearing a hair piece, but now,
right? Now it doesn't. This is a little too long. It's okay. I'll grow it.
You show Steve from Minecraft. Will you ever get hair plugs? No. I'm just going bald whenever I
go bald. If I make it to 40, I'll be happy. Making it to 40 with a full head of hair is fine. I made
it to the level cap as far as hair goes. If you have a full head of hair at 40 years old, you made
it to the hair level cap. Good for you. You won. That's fine. Keep coping. It's 60. It's 40. I'll
give you 45. No, no grays either. No, not that I can tell. Not that I can really see. What's your
secret? Okay. You want the secret. I drink green tea and I moisturize every day. That's it. I'm a
big green tea guy and I moisturize my face with a good moisturizer. Done. You eat garlic? I love
garlic. Yeah, all the time. It's the Botox. Nope. I've never had work done. Dude, garlic is a secret.
Garlic is a secret, but don't overdo garlic because it can actually be kind of not great for you.
A nice like a nice green tea. What are your thoughts on the 2004 World Series squad for
the Red Sox? I have, okay, I'll give you an opinion on that.
That song played in every business, on every street, in every house. It was background
noise. It was white noise for all of 2005 and 2006 after the Red Sox won the World Series.
You'd be in the car with the radio on.
Okay, Boston, you're my home. Okay, let's go in this business.
Dude, fucking airlines were probably like flights coming into Boston after the 2004 World Series.
It was probably like, ladies and gentlemen, we are starting our descent into Boston,
home of the World Series champions. And they just played it. Five people know what you're
talking about? Okay, this is what I'm talking about. This first 10 seconds was everywhere.
Oh, yeah. Ladies and gentlemen, we are starting our descent into the beautiful city of Boston,
Massachusetts, home of the World Series champions 2004. Cloudy day in Boston, 65 degrees. We're
landing shortly. And everyone's just like, and everybody's in full Red Sox fan gear. Everyone.
Everybody. They have a hat. They have a shirt. They have like wristbands. And then when it
when it gets to this part here, the whole fucking plane yells it. Hold on here. That dirty water.
Everybody. Boston, you're my home.
Everyone's just fucking everyone's just so happy. After 2004, my parents painted my room and made it
Red Sox themed. Yes. And how many times did you open up the door to your house? And okay, hold on
for all of you Boston East coasters out there. How many times did your parents watch the DVD
presentation of the World Series championship cowboy up? How many times did your parents watch
the cowboy up DVD after they won the special edition of the documentary of them winning?
I was probably once a week I would be like in my house and I would just walk I would
be walking around and I would just hear like the intro to that to that DVD.
If you're cute, if you're like, what the fuck is he talking about? They play this song at the end
of every Red Sox win. If the Red Sox win the game at Fenway Park, they play this. No wonder you are
like this. This is so funny dude. Boston sounds like a cartoon town. It kind of is.
Wait, didn't hold on. I feel like they did a cover. Did they do a cover? Is this I feel
like I heard this one a shitload? Have I ever heard? Yeah, the Dropkick Murphys. Did they ever
do a cover of this? I got an ad. Hold on. That's right. This is live somewhere. Listen, everybody
screaming. This was probably impromptu. Dropkick Murphys probably like, hey, Red Sox just won the
fucking World Series. They're good too. They're residency for me. Fucking come on. What's up
Germaniacs? Stop calling people Germaniacs. That's not the correct term. Stop saying that.
I keep seeing that and it's kind of pissing me off. You're not the Germaniacs. No, you are the
Germimites. I don't know how many more times I have to say this. Not the Germimites. Germimites.
Excuse me, the Germimites. The Germimites. You're not the Germaniacs. Not the Germimites.
No, you're not the Germs. You are the Germimites. I keep seeing that. Drew Crew. I was there at the
start when we were the Germs. Yeah. Yeah, you were for a while. Not the Germanians. Plus like. Yeah,
I remember at the end of every video saying, hey, plus like if you'd like the video. I never wanted
to say it though. I always hated saying it because to me it was like, oh hey, make sure you like the
video. Well, I don't know. Did they like it? What if you hated it? Then I look like a dickhead.
Like you, I didn't want you to like the video if you didn't like the video. So I didn't want to
look like a shithead and be like, dude, like the video. Make sure to hit that like button.
Well, dude, what if this video sucks? Then that's not accurate. You pressed like already. That's
not accurate. I never liked to say that. Please rate the video. Yeah, there you go. That's better.
Are you a gamer? I beat Cuphead a couple days ago in about an hour and 40 minutes. I would say so.
You played the organ during Dawnhouse. What instruments do you play? I know how to play
the drums. I know how to play the drums. Very sparingly. Not really though. Like kind of.
Are you a guy that fell asleep to Five Nights at Freddy's? Um, very briefly. I gave the PAX East
video one star. What's your favorite thing of all the stuff behind you? I can't pick, these are all,
I can't pick a favorite child. Come on. I can't pick a favorite child. You have a vape pen? No.
Didn't they ban, isn't vaping banned now? I read that. What happened? They banned vaping. The vape
pens. Which ones? They banned Juul. Juul is banned in the United States now. What separated Juul
from all the other ones? Good night? Hey, have a good night. It's too much nicotine. Tons of
nicotine and marketed to kids. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. Juul appeals to young people. Big tobacco.
The company was bought up by Philip Morris. Oh. They're banning disposables in the UK at some
point. Saj, what will I do when I'm hammered on a night out? Um, you could not smoke inhaled nicotine.
I know that's really easy to say, but cigarettes are bad. Nicotine is bad. Cigarettes are bad.
Don't smoke. I'm not going to say that because like, look, I'm not going to tell you what to do
with your life. Smoking is bad. You shouldn't do it. Vaping is an alternative. That's still nicotine
and still a bunch of bullshit you're inhaling into your lungs. But look, but I'm me sitting here
going like you smoke cigarettes, you vape. And I thought we could be friends. I don't, I don't
care. You know what I mean? You really shouldn't be doing it though. Right in the middle. Get it
right in the middle. It's right in the middle. So, you know, these people can't be mad at me.
These, the smokers can't be pissed. The nonsmokers can't be pissed. We're right there. Perfect.
Perfectly placed. Cigarettes actually really piss me off though. They actually really do.
When they, okay, let me tell you something about cigarettes. Um, Las Vegas. No, you want me, you
want a non-centrist Andy? Take fine. I'll give it to you. Cigarettes are fucking annoying. Okay?
I live in Las Vegas, obviously, where smoking is, is allowed in the casinos. You can literally
just walk around inside and smoke pretty much 90% of the entire floor. You can just smoke
in the casino. MGM, near the company MGM, they decided, they said, hey, um, we're going to make
Park MGM smoke free now. 100% smoke free. I almost shit my pants because it's the only casino on the
strip. It's the only casino right now, I think, in Vegas that I can think of that is smoke free.
And oh my God, it's, oh, you mean I can, I can go like hang out and meet friends and there's not
somebody like this, like this. My face, by the way, is right here. Oh yeah. Hit me. Oh, I'm sorry. Is
that glove blowing directly into your nostrils? I don't fucking give a shit. Oh my God. Having the
smoke free casino, doing more of them, more, more, more, more smoke free casinos. I, every time
somebody ever comes into Vegas and they're like, oh, what do you want to do? Hey, um, you ever heard
of Park MGM? I mean, it's, it's a smaller casino. Um, it's, you ever heard of that? That's where you
should go. We should go to Park MGM. I think it's like cool and clean. Park MGM. Like how do we show
them that it's awesome? How do we show them this? Cause you know that they're definitely counting
fucking shit in the back room. I don't know. The whole smoking ban in Park MGM didn't really work
out. We lost 10% customer base. Turn the cigarettes back on. I love Park MGM. Keep it smoke free. God
damn it. I have nothing against people smoking a cigarette. What I, I don't, I just don't want to
be sitting next to somebody at a blackjack table. That's just, that's just, I'm breathing in their
cigarette for them. There have been cases when I've been down on the strip or downtown in Vegas,
wherever I am, whatever is casino. And I'm just trying to hang out and I am smoking someone's
fucking, I'm smoking someone else's cigarette. I'm that, that's, I'm that close. It's not like,
oh, I smell cigarettes. There's a cigarette in this room. No, like you are holding it here
and my fucking face is here. I am smoking your cigarette. God, it's a tactic to win more.
In blackjack, we all play against the dealer. There's no, you know, there's no psychological,
you know, it's a poker. You want me to lose at the table? What are you talking about?
Why would I, why would you want me to lose? We all play against the dealer in blackjack.
How often do you visit the strip? Once every, I want to say three or four months,
once a quarter, maybe once or twice a quarter. Yeah. I, cigarettes, I just don't like them.
Cigarettes have a very distinct smell too. That's just painful. I will smell weed, right? Like
somebody's smoking weed and it's like, Oh, somebody's, Ooh, Oh, somebody's smoking. What's
that? What's hmm. When I, a cigarette, it's like, I don't know where the fuck that's coming from,
but I want to get away from it now. Okay. Yep. I think it's come, let's go this way. Come with me.
Let's go over there. Let's, yeah, let's go this way. Like through there. If they're good cigarettes,
it smells good. Weed smells good. We can, yeah, but also we usually, weed's a lot more powerful.
What's on your shirt? Well, glad you asked. This is the Hash House A Go Go pancake. And by the way,
that's actual size. By the way, that's actual size. Yeah. And by the way, actual size.
Do you want pancakes? Three o'clock in the morning and you're near the link. Hash House A Go Go. Best
pancakes, best cheeseburger I've ever had. Best burger I've ever had. Weed smells like
a moldy carpet. It's better than an old ass tray. Why did you staple a pancake to your shirt?
That'd be weird. What's the burger? It is the blue cheeseburger at Hash House A Go Go.
I gave you a secret message at the end of that. I don't know if you can decode it.
That's my favorite music. I really don't really listen to that much music. Dude,
that pancake is bigger than your head. They're huge. Yeah, I know. You eat music. You're a blue
cheese fan. Yes. Yeah, I like it a lot. If you don't listen to music, what the fuck do you do?
I don't know. Watch TV and work on stuff. Go out. Go to dinner. Take a walk. Run errands. What do
people do? No, you're not going to pull this shit again. Somebody said, like a couple years ago,
what was it? They were like, oh, hey, man. Yes. Prove you're not a serial killer. What do you
do for the other eight hours during the day? And it's just, I don't know, man. What the fuck
do you do for the other eight hours or six hours during the day? What do you do for like eight
hours during the day? I watch TV. I do run errands, do some chores, make phone calls,
talk to some people, spend time with some people. What else do you do? Play games. You play video
games with, you know, get on Discord. What else do you do? And because I couldn't give five straight
hours of things that I would do after I turned the stream off or something, it's like you Googled
what normal people do. I just told you how Park MGM, I love that place. Like, oh, I go to Park MGM
and hang out. Who are you talking to? That joke is really funny, but I'm whatever. I laugh every time
I see that. Would you ever go to a non-YouTube or non-gaming convention, like an anime convention
or a pop culture convention? Probably not. I did the convention thing for a long time. And I don't
know. Probably not. Furry convention. I told you the only way I would go to a furry convention is
if I was in a full costume and no one ever knew it was me. I may have already done this. I may have
already done this. How would you ever know? Be in a full furry costume that has no ways to see who
is in there. And I have rooms at like seven hotels. So I could always like, wait, is that him? No,
I'm in a different, I'm in a different hotel tonight. No one fucking knows who I am. No one
knows where I am. I genuinely believe we would know. No, you would not. You would not. How would
you know? If I went to a furry convention and I was in a full fursuit and was just walking around
going like this, like, and I didn't do, I didn't move around too much and I didn't make it. I know.
Why would I be talking? I would not be, I would not say a single word. How would you ever know?
And then I would get to the hotel. I would go to the hotel room and make sure like I,
nobody knew who I was. And then I would just take it off and go to bed. And every time I came out
of the room, I'd be in the full suit. So no one would ever know. Why would you know I was in there?
You would be applying chapstick through the mask. Just like, you'd have wicked bad garlic breath.
No, and I would not be doing any like, like movements. I wouldn't want you guys to know the
movements. It would be super generic. Like that's it. I wouldn't do a single other move. There'd be
no like walking, like, look at me. No, it would just be chills. I hate that. You ever happen to
you where you're just like, you know what it reminds me of? Okay. It's, that's like a dog shaking.
You know what I mean? Like, you've thought this through. Yes, we've talked about this more than
once. We've, this is like the third or fourth time we've discussed this. You would not know.
And honestly, I would never tell you. I would never tell you. You would never know. Years later,
I wouldn't tell you. You would end up tripping up at one point. No, I wouldn't. You know why I
wouldn't? Because I'm going to order three of the same exact costume, custom made, and I'm going to
hire somebody to go into that costume and go down to the convention floor on one of the days. And
I'm going to have that person take off the helmet and pose for a bunch of pictures and like drink
out of a bottle of water, like very publicly. Like, and there you are. You would never know.
You keep telling us what you're going to do. Yeah, but you, how do you, you can't even look for that.
You, how would you even look for something like that? Oh, that person drank, drank water. Okay.
That's literally every single person at the whole convention. Don't tell your secrets.
I could tell you all these secrets. It doesn't matter. Please let me make you a fursuit.
No, how expensive would the fursuit be? I'm not telling you anything in case I ever decide to do
this. They have to sign. Yeah. They would have to sign an NDA. Whoever that actor was, they'd have
to, they would have to sign a document. Oh, but I would pay the fuck out of that person.
You know what I mean? It would be like, oh, hey, actor, what's your date? What's your day rate
to fill out? What's your, what's your like day rate as an actor? Okay. Triple it and sign that
paper. Triple it and sign this NDA. They ain't saying shit. It's 30K for three suits. Holy shit.
What? It's 3000. It's wait, it's 10K for a big fursuit. What? Holy shit. 10K sounds like a lot.
3K. Okay. I could see like 5K, 10K, 20K, three to 5K. Okay. I mean, the materials alone are,
are expensive and the obviously the grade of labor that goes into it makes sense, right?
But 10 plus 20 plus thousand, 10K is for the popular makers. That makes sense. 20K for a
high-end suit. Holy shit. New retirement plan. Some suit makers are really high in demand.
Well fucking good for them. Holy shit. Chain mail is expensive. Wait, what do you mean?
Chain mail. You're putting chain mail on too. You're putting on chain mail. Why are you putting on
chain mail for defense? Parry the furries. When are you going to do the slime stream? What?
Why are you making this so elaborate? Just wear a fursuit. It's 2022. But the fun is, is it,
is it me? I don't care about putting a fursuit on. I just want it to be impossible for you to know.
I don't care about wearing a fursuit at all. I just want it to be a mystery. You know what I mean?
Schrodinger's furry. Am I in there? Am I, am I not in there? That's so stupid. How you been? I've
been alright. I've been good. I've been pretty good. I'm in Vegas and I'm going to Hash House
to go-go. I'm going to try it before I go home. Hope it's good. I haven't been there in a while,
but it was good last time I went. I changed to 480p and the quality didn't change. Would you
actually genuinely do this? Probably. I met Jeremy at a furry convention. I was at FurCon. I went,
there it goes. It's gone. Mods are on point. Dude, Mods are on point. That was there for as long
as it took me to read the first four words. Gone. I have a debate with a friend. Is a hamburger
outfit a fursuit? No. I mean, is it, are you, no, that's not an anthropomorphic animal. Wouldn't
that what it is? Is Grimace a furry? No, Grimace, what is Grimace? Is Grimace a furry? What is,
what is Grimace? Grimace is an alien, right? What is Grimace? Grimace is a muppet. He's supposed to
be a nugget. No, really? Grimace is the cookie monster, but from McDonald's food. But what
animal is Grimace? A bison? He's an eggplant. He's supposed to be a human. Wait, Grimace is supposed
to be a guy? He's the purple cookie, but what is Cookie Monster? What is Grimace? McDonald's managers
clarify the character. Okay. The lovable spherical shaped purple character Grimace has always been
one of McDonald's most recognizable faces. Even if fans never knew what he actually is.
Okay. Ronald McDonald is a clown. Mayor McCheese is a cheeseburger. Birdie the early bird is a bird.
The Hamburglar is a thief. A Mac tonight is a moon. And the fry kids are fries. What the heck is
Grimace? Okay. Nobody knew what he was until now. Late last month, the manager of McDonald's in
Canada revealed the answer to the Golden Arches Biggest Mystery, telling CBC News that Grimace
is an enormous taste bud. Huh? That's fucking inflamed. That shit's inflamed. I thought maybe
it was a piece of candy. A gumdrop or something. Enormous taste bud? Can we just say he's a big
piece of taffy? That makes more sense. It's not inflamed. Wait, he also, wait, wait, wait, wait,
McDonald's reached out. Hold on. McDonald's stepped in here. McDonald's offered some clarification in
the statement. Whether he's a taste bud, a milkshake, or just your favorite purple blob,
the best part about Grimace is that he means different things to different people. Whatever
he is, we're just proud. Our bestie makes people happy. A milkshake? So he's a milkshake. He's a
bestie? Okay, into, hold on, it gets deeper. In 2012, McDonald's Corp tweeted from their official
account that Grimace was, in quotes, and I'm quoting, the embodiment of a milkshake, though
others still insist he's a taste bud. The account tweeted something similar in 2014 saying Grimace
lore says he is the embodiment of a milkshake or taste bud. So he's a milkshake? That's a pretty
gross ass milkshake. He's the embodiment of a milkshake. He's not a milkshake. He is the
embodiment of a milkshake. All right, so he's like a milkshake in theory. Thick? Creamy? What is it?
What else is a milkshake? Biblically accurate. Juicy? Every time I see Grimace, I just think of
the Barney the Dinosaur jump run. You guys know what I'm talking about? The I'm in a mascot suit.
I'm gonna do the excited jump run in the air for a quarter of a second where they go like,
and their legs go one, two, three, four, da, da, da. They like jump and their arms go like this and
their legs go like this and they kind of maybe go like that. It's the quintessential mascot is excited
jump. I just see Grimace doing that. Barney the Dinosaur used to do this all the time.
He would jump then his legs would go hoo hoo hoo. When was the last time you had a purple milkshake?
Never. We can hear your stomach? You probably can. Holy shit, you probably can. You can hear my...
Stop listening to me. Don't do that. I'm hungry. He's trying to convince us that he's human. I have
internal organs. I'm hungry. Go eat. This stream is not gonna be that much longer. I'm just gonna be
gone for a while. Well, not a while, like five days, four days away from the stream. He has a
loudspeaker in his stomach. Oh, but when we come back, you'll see me again. You'll see me again.
Maybe over there. You'll see me again. I'll be back. Not maybe. Of course I'll be back. When is
the Castle Griffin's deed? I don't know. I have a bunch of mods I want to do for GTA V, Elden Ring,
and Skyrim. We're going to leave that to next week. I've also got Call of Duty. Call of Duty
one campaign that I've been talking about for a long time that I want to play. There's also
the jumping jack stream where I do 10 jumping jacks and then turn it off.
And that's what I did for work today. There's that. There's that important stream. There's
the count stream where we count to a hundred. What about Grotto Beast? Grotto Beast is coming.
Grotto Beast is coming. I don't have a hard date for you, but it's this year, this year,
this year, actually this year, sooner than you think. Follow that Twitter. They post updates.
Go check it out. Grotto Beasts. You'd never be able to count to a hundred and thirty minutes.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine, twenty. Did I skip a whole thing? Wait, what? One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, twenty. It hasn't been thirty minutes. Dummy. Also the green screen stuff. If you want
a submission read the rules you have until the 17th at midnight technically which is the 18th
at midnight so midnight 12 o'clock july 18th whatever you want to call it that's when it's
over read the rules if you want to do a green screen video there's a lot of things you have
to pay attention to and a lot of rules you have to follow so please follow them i've heard this
some really good ones so far you got another week and a half or so to do it rules don't apply to us
well then they're not going to be shown on the stream so i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm very sobby okay i'm
sobby but if you do not follow the rules then i'm sobby it's not you're not going to be on stream
auctioneer andy what do you say have you seen any of them i have peeked i did peek i've peeked a
little some of them i've seen like two and they're fucking funny yeah go to discord you have a week
and a half i want to do that actually there's gonna be some pretty cool the end of july is
gonna be pretty stacked baseball's happening on the 24th and then the next stream that i do coming
back from baseball is going to be the green screen movie night i think that that would work out
pretty well so there'll be two really really fun things in a row because i want that stream to be
somewhere in the end of july two weeks to have you guys make videos and then maybe a week to
10 days to vet them get a good playlist do you think you bring back community content night after
i don't know maybe i would do an encore night again maybe maybe i don't want to say that oh
yeah let's bring community content night back because it's not inaccurate i'm just not prepared
for it july 24th is baseball i know i've moved it three times now but desperately trying behind
the scenes to make sure the show can go off in july and not have to wait any longer recommend
video editing software um premier is good premier pro is just solid everything you need for it i
used to use it all the time it was my editor of choice when are you and stir going to do the
remake and old channel vid yeah we talked about it we talked about it it's just stir got uh stir
had a lot of stuff going on with myriad and i mean the dude's making a full entire from scratch video
game rule set so he's he's pretty busy maybe i'll see if he's got time in the next you know month
or so because i think that's a really funny idea i think there's a lot of potential for that one
you're hyping up baseball are you sure it's confident as good as you want it to be i don't
know i've never thought like that though even before stuff like dollhouse or the replacement
show or the desert you know grotto beast thing carnival i i just think i'm just gonna if it's
fun it's fun let me try usually they are you might be under hyping baseball the reason why i have
not been going heavy into baseball is because we didn't know for sure the day and we had to
keep changing it so you see how a month ago it was the 14th of july then it became the 20th now
it's the 24th so now that we get a real day and a real date we're going to lay into a lot of uh
probably a lot of pr for it so don't worry you will know you will see but yeah i'm just going
to get up there and try to have fun and try to do the stuff that i wrote down on a piece of paper
that's it hey uh will you apologize hold on for laughing at me because i said i watched the care
bears at 24 my life's been an absolute shambles since i didn't i didn't my intention was not to
make fun of anybody i don't care what you're watching you put shambles in all caps though so
i'm kind of no no no i'm not laughing at the fact that you watch care bears i'm laughing at the
scenario of me apologizing to you for laughing at you for watching the care bears you understand
that's a there's a lot going on around this it's not just one little thing i don't care i don't
care i really don't if you enjoy television enjoy the shows that you would enjoy okay
i'm not i don't want to make fun of anybody come on and i won't except for this guy this guy right
here what he just said he said are you gonna play the demon souls remake not fucking happy with this
guy i would love to but it's still hard to get a ps5 it's still hard to get a ps5 i'll go to target
randomly sometimes and just be like oh maybe i can grab one and they're just like no we don't have
any oh all right and no guys i'm sorry i'm not going to go buy a ps5 from a third-party seller
for like eight hundred dollars no i am not gonna do that no not fucking doing it not doing it
i could i could order one but i just haven't cared enough to do that you got money do it i'm not
going to do that i'm not going to pay three times what a playstation 5 costs to someone no
honestly i would rather buy a playstation 5 off of one of you guys for five times what it costs
then do that online you can order from the playstation website oh all right maybe i'll
get one but you'll pay triple to sign a non-disclosure agreement or and an nda
that is a transaction between me and somebody that is not okay here's how it's different
here's how it's different if i got the actor into the room and i was like all right man so
here's what you're gonna do all right like i'm gonna get in directing mode okay so you're gonna
be walking around you're gonna be you're gonna be me in that suit first of all you're gonna be me
in that suit so you're gonna be making all kinds of movements and stuff pause i'm gonna take the
helmet off and like drink drink drink drink and he cuts me off and he goes you're paying me triple
or i tell everybody that's the difference that's the difference at that point i have to go what's
what's going on oh yeah yeah yeah like i'm gonna i'll do this and i'll do whatever you want but
my day rate was like 400 you're paying me three grand or i'm gonna tell everybody give me that
fucking pen that's an nda by the way you break this nda oh you'll be hearing from me find someone
else no you i couldn't do that i couldn't do that find someone else they've seen the costume
that person has seen the costume and they can just be like hey everybody look out for the fucking
this animal i'm not gonna say what it is right you can just leak it and it's over so yeah i
just i'm gonna have to he's actually gonna do it you have to yeah you have to make them sign
the nda before you tell them what they're doing but you can't do that who would sign that paper
hey uh yeah i'm looking for somebody to uh sign an nda uh they can't literally cannot say anything
about what happens and i'm not gonna tell you what it is i'm not going to that who is gonna show up
to that casting call hey uh you literally um you can't tell anybody anything and you show up and
then i'll tell you when you get here no you can't do that yeah i guys i don't think that's even
legal that's illegal i think you have to disclose at least what do you this no it has to be they need
to know and then you have to say all right if you're gonna do this and you have to sign an
nda you can't just not say bro what's an nda all right let me explain what an nda is well you
don't know what an nda is it's a non-disclosure agreement that means that if you sign that paper
and we do something that if you talk about that thing then you can face potential legal trouble
because i could like sue you for breaking contract right i don't even i don't even
fucking know how it works i don't even know how it works hey say can you say hello to me to foster
our parasocial relationship i mean i'll say hi to you because you're a founder of the channel
one of the first like 10 subscribers so there you go epic gaming you didn't say their name
well he's gonna have to sign an nda it's first 25 not 10 well you know still though he hates you
snoozing copter i said i said it now sign that paper do you watch vtubers i catch neanderth
from time to time i don't really watch that much twitch though unless i mean obviously we're
talking about the juicer the enemy come on i don't yeah the only like streamers i really watch
are i mean xqcl obviously um i watch who else do i watch like ludwig i'll watch usually i watch
creparian god it's great stream that's an awesome stream i don't really watch that much though i'll
pop in from time to time i usually watch streams that are late at night later at night because by
the time because i mean obviously i'm usually doing something around this time into five six
seven eight nine ten o'clock at night so it's usually the streamers that are on a little later
that i watch more frequently what about northern lion yeah i pop in i pop in yeah critical charlie
is always late too yeah i'll jump around joel yep if they're live yeah he hates streaming in general
jermis quit stop saying i'm quitting i'm not quitting you've not i'm you will know when i'm
quitting yeah i will tell you you'll have a full year in advance to know i'm not quitting how come
you look sick um because this camera sucks and i shaved that looks like fucking healthy now look
i got fucking health man i got health i could sprint from one end of the room to the other
hundred times you look sus yeah how does that look how does that look huh huh does that look
yeah how the fuck how do you tell me how the fuck does that arm look how the fuck does that
shoulder look with that fucking arm huh wendy's burger king mcdonald's five guys how the fuck does
that look huh spaghetti arms these are not spaghetti arms they're not i'm just saying i'm
just saying no they're not i'm just saying let your hair grow out i thought about it again
i want to see one for me who is the best looney tune daffy duck oh oh isn't that game coming out
this month it is right the multi versus isn't on the doing and it's coming back right the beta is
coming out oh you look like you made it a play dough i can mold myself into whatever i want
yeah i'll you guys made it a fucking stone come on gwen it's a forgettable game i that stay it
stuck with me i had a lot of fun and i did actually pretty well in that alpha jimmy neutron do a stream
recap i sat on a chair and smiled 30 to 40 times and talked about watching movies on airplanes
that's the whole stream they're gonna add gandalf to it by the way i can't wait oh yeah i told the
bat story too that's right somebody called me a seinfeld character when i told that story i forgot
to mention it all right dnd stream i don't know probably not can you do a comb eating stream i'll
see you guys soon it's ludwig's birthday that's a happy birthday to ludwig he's a really good dude
i'll see you soon i'll see you soon yeah happy birthday ludwig i'll see you soon i'll see you
soon i'm gonna see you soon okay i'll see you soon i'll see you soon i'll see you guys soon
i'll see you soon see you soon vaping is not okay i don't i don't think you should be putting
nicotine in your body at all but whatever i'm not gonna tell people what they should do
but stay away from it centrist andy see you soon i just got here what's happening i tried to comb my
hair and i put a new product in the hair it's like this really thick really um really gel
it's a really good hold pomade and i got the comb stuck and now i have to go to the fucking
goddamn i gotta go to the salon and have them take it out so i don't know what to do now because
like if i move this it's gonna it'll break so i don't know what to do so whatever you goofy
ass all right i'll see that's good that's enough i'll see you guys later keep an eye out right keep
an eye out see you soon all right goodbye see you soon keep an eye out see you soon all right keep
an eye out see you soon no you hang up no you hang up do i even need an outro yeah why not
no you hang up i have had a game running this whole time my time at porschea portia porschea
this game's been open the whole time oh shit this game looks kind of good maybe we'll play this
yeah it's been open the whole time i think i opened it thinking if the if i got bored in the first
like 20 minutes of the comb stream that i would um just move it up is my time at portia a good game
it's been recommended a lot of times yeah okay let's do it let's do it it's good all right
i'll put it on the list all right i'll see you guys later thanks for watching thanks for sticking
around i know this was a short just kind of chatting stream we just chilled for a little bit
but you know sometimes i just kind of want to hang out so i'm gonna go eat good night
take care of yourselves call your mother see you soon i mean i'm serious like i'll see you soon
goodbye take care good night