These? These are my sub-girls.
Hey! Whoa!
Dama!
Tipatalo!
Look at Andrew.
That's right. Look at Andrew. Never heard of him.
I'm going to see my armpits. So I'll lift my arms up.
Yep!
My sub-girls.
Can't breathe without these.
I feel like I'm making a TikTok video.
Who'd say like this is the lip I was doing?
Whoo!
Just a little too big.
Can't breathe without these.
I feel like I'm making a TikTok video.
Who'd say like this is the lip I was doing?
Whoo!
Just a little too big.
Can't breathe without these.
I broke the watch.
We should have started like five minutes ago.
We had to tape the watch on my hand.
I was putting it on and I was panicking.
And the thing just like shattered in my hands.
But anyways, how was it?
I broke the watch on my hands.
But anyways, hi. Welcome to day two of the dollhouse.
Do you need an introduction?
Should I give you an introduction?
Or do you already know how this works?
You should by now.
I'm going to go take a look inside.
Oh my god! I look fucking awful!
I'm going to be so self-conscious.
I don't wear this shit.
You understand?
In my own home I don't wear this.
Because I'm embarrassed about my neck
and shoulders and stomach come out.
And I think you can see my nipples through the shirt.
But I'm going to try to do my best to make sure you can't see that.
Let's go in the house.
The seats have been cleaned up.
You notice something in the trash out there?
Because I'm not sleeping on that fucking mattress.
That's not going to happen.
I'm not sleeping on that.
Because it's actually dirty.
Actually dirty.
I look like a fucking idiot.
You know the bathroom?
Probably pretty well at this point I would assume.
I love this bathroom.
Although I could use a little bit more stuff.
Please be aware.
You are in control of 98% of everything that happens on this stream.
Just be aware of that.
Should we check this door?
What do you think? Should I go in here?
Does this door work? We'll find out.
I can't open it. It's locked.
Oh!
That's where the bed is.
That's right. I built it.
It was broken.
That's why I decided to put it.
Because you got it for me at the end of the stream.
It took me like six hours to build it.
This is nice and comfy.
I actually kind of like how this looks.
Can we see?
Can you get it?
Can I like home shopping network this thing?
It's so stupid.
I feel like that mouse.
Who I'm not going to say on a stream like this.
I feel like that mouse wears this kind of stuff.
I feel like he has like 30 of these.
But we never see him wear it.
I guarantee he hasn't.
Welcome back though.
Actually, you know from the front.
From the front it looks okay.
But from the side it doesn't.
I need to like get a bigger chest.
But I got like these flickering arms.
Like I'm going to.
I can go like that.
I love the bedroom.
You got more choices now, don't you?
Toilet? I don't have to go.
Just so you can be aware that it is available.
Eventually I probably want to take these gloves off.
Enjoy the game.
Good luck.
I got full bars.
Which means I can do this.
That's embarrassing. I just did that.
How many people are here?
That was like actually pretty embarrassing to do with this many people.
73,000 people just watched me do that.
That's like embarrassing.
Back in like during like school plays.
There'd be like fucking 40 people in the audience.
They're...
No, I'm not peeing on them.
I'm not peeing on the flowers.
Why is that the piss sound?
That's not water flowers.
I'm going to stand like this.
So people don't think that's what's happening.
I enjoyed that very much though.
I did.
I'll tell you from the front this looks good.
Wait a minute.
We're going to do the same joke from the other day.
I still got it.
But what I was going to say is
back when I was a young, young boy
there'd be
school plays.
You're in like the fourth grade, the fifth grade.
Only people's parents
came to that shit.
Maybe the principal, maybe the old lady
that played the piano during the entire show.
She would just
every scene it would be like
that lady was like super into it.
I kind of wish we had one of those ladies.
We don't.
But the difference is
with 40 people's parents it's 70,000 people.
I don't know how many of you are.
Actually I think my mother is watching.
I'm going to go lie in the bed.
I'm going to go check the bed out.
Parasocial Andy.
What?
I'm going to check the bed out.
Okay.
There it is. There's the first one.
I actually
talked about the fart thing.
And I said five farts an hour.
There's more than five farts an hour.
So it's going to be in a lot of trouble.
It was five fart sounds an hour.
There was one.
I want you to keep track.
Okay, let's go.
I'll watch out for that manhole.
Do you see the mattress?
I'm in the right clothes for this.
Ugh.
Not sleeping on this.
We actually talked about this after day one.
I'm like
not a chance that I actually lie on this.
No way.
I got the popcorn maker.
Except it doesn't do anything.
Because I don't want to get electrocuted.
Check mail. Sure.
Why not? Mail.
Check the mail. What's in the mail today?
Let's find out.
This is somebody's shoe that's here.
Somebody actually on set here.
This is their shoe.
I don't know whose it is, but I don't know why it's in here.
What is it?
Has somebody worn this
in the last few days?
Money?
There's twenty bucks in the shoe.
Who would do this?
What kind of fucked up neighborhood is this?
Thanks for the twenty dollars.
What do we start with? Three hundred?
So that's what? Three twenty?
How much money? Forty? What?
I thought we started with three hundred dollars.
Oh, they bought the upgraded house.
Right. But why don't we have any money?
How are we supposed to get any money?
How are they going to buy anything?
I'm talking to you.
Remember, I have to go to work to make money.
If you don't send me to work, then it's not going to happen.
Oh! Got you.
I actually hit myself in the head.
I went for like a joke.
And I didn't fucking get it right.
My knee was in the wrong place
and that actually just hit me right in the forehead.
Ah!
I do actually feel pretty... I need to take a shower.
Let me get in here.
Don't close that.
I just figured it out.
You got to keep these bars green, otherwise how am I going to get promoted?
How are you going to make more money?
How are you going to be able to get more stuff in the house?
You can't, unless you actually
play and get me there.
I want green bars.
Coming up. Coming up.
I hit the watch.
I'm getting a little tired though.
Starting to wane a little.
I want cool items. I want fun stuff.
I want things to lie down on.
I want things to play with.
I don't just want...
What was that?
Go to work. I missed work by like four hours already.
Go to work?
Alright, I'm going to work.
Alright, fine.
I'm going to work.
I'm coming!
Night shift.
Thanks for the ride.
Goodbye!
That just made me wane.
That just made me tired.
That just brought my energy to zero.
It wasn't working for like six or seven hours.
It was doing the goodbye
like five times
is what made me tired.
I'm exhausted though.
Tired and a little hungry.
At least we made some money.
I'm hungry though.
How much money is in the account now?
$200? $140?
I'm going to my bedroom.
I haven't been able to sit in here for very long.
I'm going to my bedroom which is a little odd.
I'm going to lock myself out of one of these rooms eventually.
Oh man.
Tired.
Make a phone call. Who am I calling?
Call who?
Who am I calling?
I got a call?
No sleeping?
What are you talking about?
Oh!
Mom!
Yeah, it's me.
Yeah, it's been an interesting day or two.
It's actually really remarkable
that I can even talk to you mom
considering that I just pulled the line out of the wall.
So this is really good.
Some kind of alien technology which is interesting.
Oh yeah, no, hi. Hello, sorry.
I forgot to say like hi. How are you?
Yeah, it's good to hear your voice.
You're the only person I know.
That's kind of interesting.
Yeah, yeah.
And so I...
Oh, what?
Right, right, this shit.
That's right.
Okay, my couch is fucking ugly.
Mom?
Are you still on the phone?
Mom? I don't know.
Hopefully she thinks I'm alright.
Let me put this back.
What is this?
Can I get this back on?
Yeah, whatever, it'll stay.
Oh, yes! Oh, I love that!
Oh, sofa!
Ew. Yuck.
Yuck.
What is this? I don't want that.
I want one piece of singular bread.
I feel awful.
I hate sleeping on the ground.
Let me go to bed, alright?
Like, okay, there's a sofa here now.
There's a bed in the other room.
Don't make me use the phone.
If my energy's low and I'm just...
I'm hangry, alright? Just let me talk to you for a second.
If you put me in the bed and let me go to sleep,
then this won't happen.
You'll have plenty of opportunity and I'm gonna piss my shit
shit my pants.
I'm just eating a piece of bread. I'm eating one piece of bread.
It's good.
It's actually pretty good.
This is a good bread.
What kind of bread is this?
It's multigrain.
I eat multigrain bread.
I don't. I actually think that stuff's gross.
Okay, that was good.
Delicious.
Don't just leave it.
Disgusting.
I'm gonna do a thing that everybody does.
I'm gonna go to work.
Wait. Wait for me.
Wait for me.
One just full piece of white bread.
I've been at work all day trying to eat.
I've been chewing this single piece of white bread
for fucking six hours.
It's like eating saltines.
Everybody at work thought I was chewing gum.
I was like, no, I ate a whole
piece of white bread before I came in.
They were like, dude,
what did you have for breakfast today?
The first time I went like this
with a piece of white bread,
and they were like, do you want to go to McDonald's?
I'm like, I don't know. No.
I'm fucking horrible.
I feel awful.
I can see it.
Please help me.
Please. I can see it.
I can literally see the fucking toilet
in front of me.
What was that?
Wait, wait, wait.
Who's at the door?
This is my pants.
I'm coming.
Uncle Ted.
It's been so long.
What is he doing here?
I went to spring training. I told your mother I was going.
Look at the nice couch you got here.
You got good taste.
He's dead.
What are you doing here?
Give me a hug.
He's so fucking cold.
He's freezing.
What's the matter with you?
Let's go.
I went to my house.
I went to my house. You know what's there?
Nothing. I got no furniture.
That looks familiar.
I don't know what God I angered.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you like my couch?
It's beautiful.
I haven't had a beer in about 50...
Gemma!
Hey, hey, Uncle Ted!
You're going to pee so bad.
Uncle Ted!
There's a fucking ghost in my house.
This motherfucker is dead.
Gemma!
Is that the bathroom?
No, no, no.
I need to do something about this.
He has to pass on.
I've got all the time in the world.
The ghost of the goddamn walking dead.
Take your time.
Sometimes it takes a little while.
Lord, start at 100.
I'm going to pass him on to the other world.
I don't know what happened. I don't know what God I angered.
I don't know what I did. I don't know who I'm angering.
I'm going to run to Donald.
Gemma!
I'm going to get him to the other side. That would be fantastic.
I don't want to be haunted anymore. I want to pass on wealth.
Look at my spoons.
Those are my spoons. That looks like my couch.
I'm going to shit my pants.
I got that one.
I got that one in Dollywood.
Hey!
I love my grandson.
Hey, so how are you?
Are you ready for Uncle Ted?
You're not supposed to be here, Ted.
I'm not supposed to be here.
I had to get your address off somebody
because your mother, freaking mother, my sister,
my house is empty of furniture.
But this looks familiar. That looks familiar.
And those are my spoons.
I got that one in Dollywood.
I got that one in...
I've got a ghost that needs to go to the other goddamn side.
He's haunting me.
Come on.
Yeah, you're coming as soon as you can.
Ted, Ted, how are you?
Who's on the phone?
I was just calling my friend,
Granit Reapelson.
Granit Reapelson?
Yeah, they're an old family friend.
You played soccer with him, didn't you?
I went to one of your games and you played soccer with him.
I did, I did.
Did you go to the other world?
No, I'm good.
There's no money hidden under any mattresses?
No, actually, I had no money.
Somebody cleaned out my account when I was in spring training.
I went down to see this octet.
Let me get the door.
Just stay there for a minute.
Stay there for just a second.
I'm here for Ted.
Please come in.
Where does this go?
Yeah, he's over here. He's having some trouble
on the other side, if you could.
Hey, how are you?
This is my friend.
By the way, I don't think I've ever said about you.
It was just a joke.
If there's anything you need to say to me,
should I know anything about anything?
Dress up? Is this dress up?
Ted.
Yeah, yeah, it is.
It's time for you to come home, Ted.
It's time.
Well, there's no furniture in my home.
No, Ted, not that kind of home.
It's time for the long farewell, Ted.
I'm feeling kind of cold.
Shh.
No more tears.
Only dreams.
Come on. Come on now.
Here we go. There you are. That's right.
I'm not dead.
You're not dead, yes.
They all say that, Ted. They all say that.
Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, Jerma.
Jerma can't help you now, Ted.
Fucking family.
Come on. I've got a spot picked out for you right here.
Come on, Ted. Right this way.
There you go.
Shh. I'm going to take good care of you, Ted.
Off we go now.
This is the worst I've ever felt in my whole life.
What did he fucking do?
Why did he come here?
Fucking haunted by my Uncle Ted.
I tried to make amends and shit.
I don't even know.
I have to go to the bathroom.
It's here. Press it.
Jesus.
Holy. Goodness.
Okay.
The water's starting to come up over the lip.
I don't care.
You know when you have to pee a lot
and it just hurts still.
It hurts. Up here it hurts.
Right here it hurts.
All the way to here. This is killing me.
Oh, like I emptied everything
but it's just like this pain now.
Are you going to let that go again?
Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
And I'm going to say a prayer for Ted too
because being haunted by somebody
is just a very unnerving ass thing.
Oh, man.
I'm going to write about that in my blog tomorrow.
What should I title it?
My Uncle Going Through the Great Beyond.
Something like that.
I was fucked up.
What did I ever do to that motherfucker?
I didn't do anything.
I got money in the mail from him. That's it.
It was just the thing.
My mother called me and sold me.
What the fuck?
I don't know why I'm getting haunted by him.
Thank God he's on the way to the other side.
That's ten times better.
A hundred times better.
I'm not even fun anymore.
This is a nice watch though.
I don't want the clocks to come back.
Please do something.
I don't want the clowns to come back today.
Oh, yay!
Butterflies, but
they don't want to be caught.
They want to be free.
Butterflies don't want to be caught.
They want to be free outside.
No, I don't want to. Let me see.
There's one over here.
Oh, that's a monarch.
It's beautiful.
That's beautiful.
I think that might be a moth, but it's okay.
It sounds like I'm getting hit by a wave.
It's like, hold on.
That's kind of funny.
That's funny I can hear that.
I can't move around too much. It's just a microphone.
Life fucks up. I'm tired though.
Oh, what's that butterfly?
Oh, I think that's a
green-tailed sparrow back.
Wow!
Maybe I should keep him.
Actual psycho?
I'm fucking tired.
Doorbell!
I didn't press it.
That was fun.
I feel better. No, that's two.
We have 30 minutes or 45 minutes to go before we even do three more.
Life and death.
When somebody comes into the world,
they're essentially created.
And when they're taken away from the world,
they are destroyed.
So therefore, all of us,
at some point during our lives,
witness creation and destruction
in one life.
It's crazy to think about that.
And also, like, in the fact that...
Are we even real?
Is this a simulation?
Like, this is a simulation.
But is this a simulation inside of a simulation?
Could we in fact
wake up from this simulation
into another simulation?
Because we're doing it now!
Oh.
Have I eaten? When was the last time I ate?
I don't know. Fuck it.
I'm not ready.
I don't know.
I'm hungry as shit.
This is not a bad couch. Where did I get this from?
Oh, that's right.
Cool. Okay.
Oh. This isn't really good.
Unbranded beer.
I'm hungry.
I feel like I've got, like, a stomach ache, too. I don't know why.
When was the last time I ate?
What is it? Mystery?
Mystery box? Ow.
A mystery? Please handle with care.
Do not drop.
Something fragile in here?
Well, if it's fragile,
I don't want to mess with it.
This is pretty cool, though.
I would assume my fun meter is high!
These fucking stools.
Is there anything else in here?
There's a lot of paper in here.
But there...
Oh, this is a lot.
You know, can I say something real quick?
Real quick.
The amount of packing material
that people put into boxes
is getting a little ridiculous, okay?
I have ordered CDs before
that have come in a box
this big
that have this much packing material
and then what am I as the
consumer to do about it?
You can literally, like, throw a fucking CD
into the wall and it's gonna be fine.
You don't have to put, like, 600 fucking pounds
of paper in here.
Hold on.
Stool!
Cereal. I'll take some cereal.
That sounds good to me.
I'm not cutting a tomato.
That's me pouring a soda.
Oh, this is
liquid cereal.
Do I have any utensils?
Oh, I'm starving, though.
Thank goodness.
What was that?
I have a good thing I've eaten.
Real quick.
Hello. Uncle Ted is dead.
Is this from the insurance company?
What? Didn't Uncle Ted die, like,
three days ago? Two days ago?
What do you mean? My mother called me and said
I got $2,000
added to my account.
But I thought that, I thought, what, is this, like, just litigation
stuff? Like, I got it, like, a week,
two, three weeks later or something?
No, he's confirmed dead yesterday.
Oh. Okay.
Interesting. Thank you for the, uh,
thank you for the reply and thank you for the, thanks for the email.
What?
I was in smack-a-roos, though. I'll take that one.
Is he dead? What?
I thought he died.
Oh, thank you. Oh, thank you.
The cereal's actually pretty good.
Close to the door. No, I don't
eat on site. This is the only food that they give me.
Okay, can I sell this
watch?
I don't want to leave trash around. That's better.
I need to put a trash barrel. Put a trash can
in there. Why are the people
just at my house?
Stop coming to my house.
I haven't eaten breakfast.
Oh, my God. All right. Who is that?
Hi.
I'm Edna, by the way, your neighbor.
What are you doing here? You'll have to
forgive me. I was busy
with my cat sweater yesterday,
but this is for you.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Thank you. Welcome to the neighborhood.
Let's see the house.
Oh, my.
Oh, wow.
You've really done nothing with the place.
Okay.
Is this what you kids
call a house these days?
Thank you.
Is this a basket?
I'll take that back later, but you put
that wherever you'd like. That's for you.
There are apples. There's fresh fruit in here.
Yes, that's from the farmers
market. It's a stone's throw away.
If you ever get hungry,
you can go down there.
There's no worms.
It's a very big mix. My cat is the
one with worms, but there's no worms
in the apples. I can't have any of these.
No, those are for you.
But you're taking the basket.
Yes, it's my basket.
My first grandchild
was born, and we brought it home
in that basket.
That's really fantastic.
What's your name again?
Edna. What is this?
The placement's a little odd, but
you can sit down if you want to. In your kitchen.
I just moved in.
It was really nice to see you, though.
Have you seen these spoons?
Yes, I have seen those spoons.
My Uncle Ted left me those spoons.
Did they come with your uncle who?
You wet the bed? Okay.
That happens sometimes.
People wet the bed. It's perfectly normal.
Don't worry about that.
Yeah, sometimes they do.
They're under the age of six.
I'm a 35-year-old man.
How old are you?
I'm 35.
Okay, you look more like a 15
with those gloves, but that's
all right.
Do you mind if I sit down?
Please do, please.
No.
Oh, my.
I just have a bad migraine.
I'm okay.
You look lovely.
Thank you, sweetheart.
I do my own makeup and my own hair.
I've never seen in my life.
Well, sweetheart, I'm sorry, but
I'm taken.
I've been married for 45 years.
That's excellent.
Do you have
a stool by chance
for me to put my feet up?
No, not yet.
It's kind of an interesting scenario that I have here
in this particular house.
I mean, you can put your feet up there if you want.
It's too high. The blood flow.
It's too high.
How old are you?
You shouldn't ask
a lady that question.
That's probably a bad idea.
You ruined it.
Do you have food?
I do. I actually do have food.
Do you have bread?
I got lots of bread. Do you like bread?
Not really, no.
I don't like bread, but
a house isn't really a home without food.
I've got bread. I mean, I do live
like a 20-year-old that's in a dorm room,
but I have peanut butter, I have cereal,
I have mac and cheese, I've got bread.
Oh, sweetheart. Why don't we
whip something up really quick?
Maybe in a few days or something.
No, right now. Why don't you
be a doll?
I've got some stuff going on, but I'm not sure.
I'm sorry, that might be me.
That's you.
Don't worry about that. Hold on.
I have a lot of nice people who call me.
Okay, yeah.
I can get some food ready if you want.
I've got peanut butter, you know, I've got everything.
Hello, this is Edna.
Yes.
My social security number.
Okay.
I can give that to you if you want.
That's fine.
What are you doing? Yeah, so my social security number
No, don't do that. Don't do that.
Wait, wait, wait. Is that a family member?
Is that a family member?
My family wants to talk to you.
Is that a family member? Oh, no, no.
He's from the social security department.
He's from the social security department?
Yeah, yeah. Are you a family member?
Did he hang up on you?
They hung up. He'll call back.
He's a real sweet guy. Was that like a son
or a grandson?
No, there's a little bit of a mix-up.
I left my car on the south border
of Texas, but it's a whole
thing. Don't worry about it.
I wouldn't give your social security number
to people you don't know.
Will you be a sweetheart and get me some
flour and sugar and eggs and some
mayonnaise and maybe an avocado
and a couple of, I don't know, do you have
like a baking sheet or maybe a
pie tin?
I don't think I have any of those things.
You don't have any of those things? I mean, you can take a look.
Okay.
Just to make yourself comfortable and maybe we could plan this
maybe like in a few days, but not right now.
Oh, no, I'm busy in a few days.
Okay.
There's not much here,
but. What am I doing?
All right.
What, he only eats macaroni?
Is that you
or me? I don't know. It sounds like you.
I think it's me again. I need to make a phone call.
Are you getting another call?
How many calls do you get? It's me. It's me.
Well, I'm a very busy woman now, right?
I would change your phone number.
Hello? Yes.
I was telling you
the social security number, right?
Yeah. It's
I'm sorry. What was that?
Where is my grandson?
He's in prison.
I want to get more physically fit.
I'm quite busy right now.
Some leg routines, something like that.
He's in prison? Yeah.
Whatever you cost, it doesn't matter because it's not me paying for it
except that it is just bullshit.
How long has he been in prison for?
Okay.
What do you need from me?
It's 985. 985 Dollhouse Way.
Is everything okay?
Excellent. We'll see you soon.
Okay.
Well, how much money is it exactly?
How much money would you need from me?
Okay, so $10,000
and he gets out of prison. Scott?
Hang the phone up.
It's two seconds. Two seconds.
Okay, my wire details.
It's a Wells Fargo
or a Chase or whatever.
Hello!
It's time to get
fit.
Those look heavy. Come on in.
Get in there and get physical.
Oh, thank you.
Alright.
Upper body?
Well, I can tell you how we're going to get you in shape.
Excuse me.
I'm so sorry.
I'll have to call you back.
There's a strange man in the house.
Sometimes,
my phone calls are most effective.
Yes, they are. Hold on a second.
Don't take any more phone calls.
Well, I would get your phone number.
Go to your store and have your provider
and they talk to them about that.
I think you probably shouldn't be answering those calls.
What was your name? Gigi.
This is Gigi.
Nice to meet you.
So what are we going to do?
Some light aerobic exercise.
You can sit down.
I think I'll sit down for this one.
I want you to follow me.
Couple of moves. First one.
This sprinkler.
Okay.
Hey.
That's more movement. More energy.
Come on. But it hurts.
I can do this at home.
We're picking items at the supermarket.
We're picking
items. Come on. Get that arm up.
We're picking items at the supermarket.
We're swimming in the pool.
Are you feeling strong?
You look strong. Do you feel good?
Don't do those. I don't want to be
responsible if something happens to you.
I don't want to be responsible if something happens to you.
Just relax and don't take any more phone calls.
How do you feel?
I'm lightening up a little bit.
How much are these? How much weight are these?
Those are five pounds each.
Careful now. You don't want to hurt yourself.
We're yummy mummies
looking to be tight in the tummies.
You got it.
Those are like 60. You might need a sparr.
But you're looking good.
I wanted to drop those off. It's a welcoming
gift for you. Thank you.
You look great. Thank you. It actually feels
pretty good. You ever want to go out for like a 60
mile run? You just let me know, okay? Never.
You'll never get that phone call. Alright, I'll come back
tomorrow morning. Excellent. So are you going to leave these here?
Well, would you like them? I would
love these. That would be fantastic.
They're so sweet of you.
How much was that?
Do you need a credit card? No, that's okay.
Listen, we're coming back for a workout tomorrow.
Alright.
Get out of here.
Okay, bye.
That was a very strong workout.
That cost $200.
So what was your name?
What was your name again?
My name is Jirba.
And you have children? I don't have
kids. Why?
Why don't you have children? It just didn't work
out. I've just been trying to focus on my career.
Okay, and what's that? You have a job?
Yeah. Most of your kids don't have jobs
these days. You go to work regularly?
I don't get in a car
to go to work, but I go in front of a screen.
Alright, very interesting.
I'm sorry, what was that? I get
in front of a screen. It's almost like a car. Like I have like a mouse
and keyboard and I sit in front of a computer.
What does that mean? That sounds like you made up
a job. No,
I get in front of a computer and I talk
and I hang out with people and I chat with them and it's like we chat
and we're cool and everything's cool.
You don't have to make up a job to appease
me, sweetheart. I still
also care about you. And I'm a plumber.
Oh, see the trades
are a very beautiful job. Yeah, that's very
difficult. That's exactly what people need
in today's world. It's
plumbing, I go into the sinks.
Well, I tell you what, I'd like
you to, really quickly if you
don't mind, could you point me
to your bathroom? The bathroom's right in the
storage over here. Okay, I have a weak bladder
so just give me two. Well, so do I, but
apparently they don't want to take care of it. Oh, that's not bad
at your age.
Alright, she was talking about getting flour.
Yes, flour,
a whole package of eggs,
avocado, if you have
anything like noodles, salami,
anything like that.
Excuse me.
Oh my. Look, he's just like Jimmy Fallon.
He just like breaks it every time.
Oh, a stool.
Okay.
I need to get the flour ready.
And
I need to
get flour.
And
Okay.
Easy does it.
I'm a little
deeper.
Edna, are you in there?
What was that?
Would you like to dance,
Edna? It's a weird request,
but would you like to dance?
Okay, hold on.
Edna, come on, if you want to come on out here.
Would you like to dance?
Would you love to dance?
Okay, let's go ahead and do this.
Okay, I don't know what that means.
My throat was a little weird.
You remind me of my husband
when he was younger,
before he passed away.
Yeah, you spin me around.
Just like
Thank you.
We lock it in our locket fingers.
Why are we dancing for?
Because I'm very tired.
Please let go.
I'm trying to let go.
Okay.
Into the kitchen, if you would.
Into the kitchen.
Are you coming in here?
I'm coming in here.
Listen, I'm a firm believer
that a house isn't a home without cookies.
Yeah.
Can I give you
my mother's famous recipe for cookies?
Edna, did you wash your hands?
I never wash my hands.
You kids don't understand. I have a very good immune system.
Very good.
Okay.
No, that's okay.
If we're going to make food, then you should...
You'll do all the work, sweetie.
It's all in the feeling. You have to feel this.
Okay, flour, sugar, eggs.
What are we making?
Cookies.
What kind of cookies?
Water.
Eggs are in there, if you want to grab them.
What kind of eggs are these?
Those are free-range eggs.
What does free-range mean?
I don't know, I just pretend to know.
Okay.
I think that means the chickens are going to walk around.
Okay, we'll need all of these.
Is that all right?
All of them?
At least most of them, yeah.
We can use a few of them.
How much sugar?
Okay, sprinkle it all in there.
This is to make cookie dough?
Yes, go ahead. Just give it a couple of good shakes.
Put it all in there.
All the flour?
Well, I mean most of it.
That's good.
A little more.
A little bit more.
Okay, eyeball it. Does that seem good?
I've never made cookies in my entire life.
You've never made cookies?
That looks great.
You want to wiggle it around a little, see if there's any lumps in there.
You're fine.
I don't see any.
Okay, now dump all the sugar in it. People like sugar.
I like sugar, it's good.
And this is just how my mother used to make these.
They're very simple.
I have these Mickey Mouse gloves on, it's kind of hard to open.
I don't know why you kids do things like that.
It's just like...
Where did you get these spoons, by the way?
Those were left by my uncle Ted.
Okay.
Who recently passed away.
Can I have them?
That smells so bad.
Can I have those spoons?
Can you have them?
Yeah, I mean, you don't use them, right? Obviously.
Well, I mean, they were left from my uncle Ted,
who recently passed away, so I don't think that's appropriate.
You need help with that, or you got it?
I'm just going to open the top, because I have these Mickey Mouse gloves on,
because somebody decided I was going to put Mickey Mouse gloves on
and wear them the entire day.
Well, you're your own person, you get to make your own choices.
How much sugar goes in here, Edna?
The whole thing.
The whole thing goes right in there.
Perfect, that's perfect.
Okay, so that looks good?
Okay, yeah, now what I want you to do is I want you to crack
two or three eggs into that pitcher.
Okay. Two or three of them?
Two or three.
Whatever you're feeling today, do you want to be extra moist cookies?
Is there a recipe, or are you just doing this?
No, it's all in your heart, honey.
But is it...
I don't know what that means, Edna.
How many eggs do you think would be best?
If you're always on a quiz show, and you told me how many eggs,
I would say probably like four.
Then put four eggs in, and if it's terrible,
we'll make it again, that's fine.
Honey, oh, you've got to do better than that.
We've made a good decision here, that's for sure.
Oh, these gloves are coming off!
Hey, Edna, how about two?
Yeah, you know what, I think it'll be great with...
Even one egg is perfect.
You know, back in the war, when I was younger,
we used to have to ration,
and we could make one egg go a long way.
You know what, in the gift basket,
I brought over some applesauce.
Applesauce?
This is applesauce.
Edna, these are mint chocolates.
Well, if you boil them up,
it'll be a similar consistency.
I mean, we'll roll with it.
We'll roll with it.
Okay, so boil these...
No, forget it, okay, take this.
Here, you're fine, you're fine.
Okay, well, I need a stirrer.
Do you have water?
I do have water, it's right here.
Take a little bit of water.
It's fine.
So what is this going to make, Edna?
They used to say two spoons of sugar
would make the medicine go down.
In this case, you have a whole box.
So it'll taste very good.
That smell you're smelling, by the way,
is probably the eggs and the sugar combined.
It's probably filling the room.
I can't smell anything.
Thank God.
So how much water, just a little bit of water?
Okay.
Do I mix this?
What kind of cookies?
Really put your arms back into it.
No, like really work.
I want to see you actually working.
Okay.
It's good for you kids to work.
You've got elbow grease, we used to call it.
And this is sugar flour and egg,
and it's going to make...
Pecan sandies.
My mother's recipe.
Those are actually my least favorite cookie in the world.
Say that.
Because when you bite into them, it tastes like you're taking a bite of the beach on the ground
and it's like sandy, and it feels like gritty.
So you don't want extra pecans then?
Edna, when I take a bite out of a pecan sandy,
I feel like there's sand in my underwear from the beach.
You don't like that?
I mean, I don't hate them.
I thought that's why some people went to the beach.
I've got it all wrong, I guess.
Okay.
Are you really tired after that?
I mean, it's work, Edna.
Look at this, look at how much muscle I'm putting into this.
I just don't understand.
All right, that's good.
Is that good? Can we see? Is that good?
Do you mind for two seconds?
I have to make a quick phone call if you don't mind.
No, fine, that's fine.
You put it in the oven.
That's an oven-proof bowl, I'm pretty sure.
Okay.
Edna, this is plastic.
Can I actually use your phone?
Edna, before you go in there, I need to take a shower real quick.
Oh.
You can get on the phone.
Okay, I'll make a quick call.
I just need to take a quick shower.
All right, you're fine.
Let me get these in the oven.
Is it going to be pecan sandies?
Yeah, put it in there for like 20 minutes.
Okay, so 20 minutes.
Doesn't that seem kind of long?
Is it okay if the utensil's in there?
Okay, I'm going to take a shower.
I'm so sorry, if you smell something, it's not me.
I'm going to get fucking rid of this lady.
A neighbor?
What the fuck?
She just won't leave.
There's really nothing in this house.
So much better.
I think I'm just going to piss.
I'm just pissing right now.
Well, when the water was off, the water's off now.
I want to pee now.
Turn the water back on.
You don't just pee into an empty shower.
You pee when your shower's running.
Everyone does it.
And you can pretend like you don't.
I know you do.
I feel better.
Sweetie, are you there?
I would wash my hands, but...
What was your name again?
Justin?
Justin, are you there?
You don't by chance have nitroglycerin pills or anything, do you?
I don't.
What was it?
No medicine at all.
I've got acetaminophen, I've got ibuprofen.
It's fine. The cookies are probably done by now.
The cookies are done?
I already sprinkled the pecan in there.
You put the pecans in? Thank you.
Appreciate it.
They smell heavenly.
They do smell fantastic.
That's strange.
Just like my mother used to make them.
Well, open it up.
Let's see. How does it look?
The fruits of your labor.
It's the fruits of our labor.
I'm curious.
I think the plastic from the bowl
must have transitioned into this.
Is that the recipe?
That happens. It's called osmosis.
If you would have gone to school, you would have learned.
Edna, could you get one for me?
I have raw egg all over my hands
and I don't want to get salmonella.
You met my grandchildren.
Salmonella?
I've got a thing in my throat.
My twin granddaughters, salmonella, did they come by?
No.
Food?
They love these. I make them for them.
They're very good. Can I try?
Would you like one?
You can keep these, all right?
Just like sand at the beach.
I feel sand all up in my underwear.
It's fantastic. It feels great.
You look like you're loving it.
I was probably at the beach at some point.
These are fantastic.
I know.
You just have to feel it.
Anytime you want to make food, I swear,
just put the stuff in there.
It's been about seven or eight hours
since you've showed up.
Where do you live?
Do you need help getting home?
I usually get lost, but someone will call me
and I'll have to go down to the police department
or the bank or something like that.
It will be fine.
Do you live in the neighborhood?
Yes, you don't have a car.
I could point you to where your house is.
It's somewhere around that way.
It's getting late. I'm getting really tired.
I need the gift basket back.
Could I have an apple?
Sure.
It's a very beautiful apple
that you've given me.
If there's anything you ever need,
I know a lot of people.
Especially if you have computer problems,
you let me know, sweetheart.
I wouldn't answer the phone
for very many people anymore.
I have plenty of time.
It was nice to meet you.
It was a wonderful meeting.
Maybe I'll see you again. It was fantastic.
Thank you for the recipe and everything.
Absolutely.
I'm exhausted.
I hope she gets home okay.
Is she going to get home okay?
Should I make sure she's okay?
She said she doesn't even know if she really lives.
I have no idea. Should I make sure she's alright?
I don't know.
That was an interesting day.
She's here all day.
I'm just trying to be nice.
I'm not trying to get rid of an old lady or something.
You're here all day.
I got the fitness instructor here.
I feel a little tighter.
I also feel like...
And we're doing this now, apparently.
I'm going to do this into the bedroom
because I'm not fucking leaving the floor again.
I'm just going to sleep on the floor.
No. No thanks.
Ow.
What's today?
Saturday? Thursday?
Tuesday? I don't know.
Do I have something to do today? No, I don't know.
I think three or four people are going to call me.
They're going to have a meeting.
I don't know. Whatever happened yesterday,
I just forget it. As of today, it sucks.
It happens all the time.
Just bring me up to speed.
This is a cool bed.
Not that cool.
No, I don't want to...
Not today. Something else.
Something else. Not today.
Fuck. Whatever.
I'm not even being able to pee before you go to work.
I'm coming!
Just wait!
Look.
Pecan sandies.
Time to make the money.
Wait. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
Why do you always pull so far down?
You're pulling my driveway.
Why do I have to walk down the street to see you?
Hi, Adam. Hi, Sweden.
Are you with them?
You're falling very far behind.
I don't trust people that work out that much.
Seriously.
What do you have to prove?
You can take a day off.
You've got Monday, Wednesday, Tuesday, Thursday.
What do you have to prove?
I've been working out literally seven days a week. There's no reason to...
Shit.
Hey, how are you?
Hi. It's really great to see you again.
Yes, I'm one of those people
that talks a lot of things about somebody
and then when they see them, they pretend like
they didn't say those things at all.
How are you?
Yes, tomorrow morning.
16 miles.
Yes, of course.
Absolutely.
If you could do that
away from my house.
There's like six different intersections here
you could go down.
I don't want to hear that in the morning or in the night.
Fuck those people.
I feel like shit.
Long day.
I'm hungry and I want
to shower and I'm not having a great time.
Those people are having a great time
outside.
Why can't I have a good time too?
I've got like Ted shit here.
Thank you.
Some of you listen, some of you don't.
It's okay.
So much better.
But you know what I mean though?
It's like you work out so much that you don't have time for anything else.
I don't care
how much you've worked out.
Look, I'm just trying to live.
If I sit down and we're at lunch and you say
like, oh hey dude, by the way
I could do like
500 pounds five times for the rep.
I don't care.
That's good for you. You're saying that because I
can't do that. You're saying that to me because
I can't do it.
God, you know what I can do?
You know what I can do that they can't?
Not much.
Not very much at all actually.
Actually it hurts to walk around for me at the moment.
But you know what? One day I'll get there.
That feels better.
What is this?
But they that wait upon the Lord
shall renew their strength. They shall mount up
with wings as eagles.
They shall run and not be weary
and they shall walk and not faint.
You know, I've actually seen this in somebody's bathroom
before.
I've seen that before.
Whatever. I guess it should sit here. Here it is.
Showered.
I feel clean. I feel good.
Although I'm kind of not having a great time
but you know, whatever.
I got my expensive watch. That's all that matters, right?
Let's go to the bathroom.
Let's fucking stool out of the way.
I don't know. I have to look at this
every time I pee.
By the way, that's like
what are you blurring?
There's somebody like sitting on that toilet
that you're blurring.
Who is that? That's not
me. Oops!
Wait, I'm done. Okay, we're good.
Like there's somebody else sitting on
that toilet. No, no, no,
no, no. I'm going to the bedroom.
You gave me this like mystery box of
stools. I'm gonna place them.
What time is it? It's pretty
late. It's alright. We'll put two
here. We'll put one over here.
Not like it matters.
I don't know. I'm getting
kind of annoyed.
What do I even need these stools for?
I'm okay. Don't get too upset.
Hey, this is how tall I want to be.
All of you are the five, seven
men out there. You ever thought
about this? You ever think about how big you were?
If you were this big?
This is what? Six, six, two?
Man. God, what a figure
that would be. Wouldn't it?
How about, um,
I don't know. We can put them next to the bed.
How about like one here?
One here. And then
should all three go over there?
I don't hate that. I really don't.
Three stools in front
of the bed. I don't know if you get on the side.
If you're as tired as I am
right now, that seems like a pretty good idea.
That means I can get out of the bed. I can put my feet
down on three different places.
Ugh. I am
tired. How much
cash do we have? How much money?
What do we got for cash?
$19.60. Give me something
nice for God's sakes.
I got money. So, no, that makes sense
because then I don't have to clean all this shit up. That's a good idea.
Calling a maid is a good idea.
Thank you.
Because the last, I don't want to clean
anything up. I want to be able to have somebody else do it.
We got almost two grand. Let's use it.
Hi. Yes.
I would love to, I'd like to have a service
started please. Yeah, the address
is 9-8-5, 9-8-5, Dollhouse Way.
I mean, you know
you're in this fucked up cartoon universe
with the rest of us. Yeah.
Okay. Thank you.
Do you live in the neighborhood too?
Are you like down the street? Because it seems like everybody lives next to each other here.
Okay.
Thank you. Today?
I mean, I'm tired, but okay, fine. That's fine.
Alright, goodbye. Alright, let's get a maid
in here. I don't want to have to deal with this. They'll take care of it.
That was very, that was very quick.
They're here. They must, they must
live in the neighborhood.
I'm so tired though.
Alright, maid service.
Here we are.
Hi. Hi.
I'm assuming that
you must be the maid?
I heard you ordered a sexy maid service.
You can stop.
You have a big mess to clean, don't you?
Stop doing the lap track. I don't want that.
Yes, there's a mess in here. It's very messy.
Well, trust me. I can take care of your big mess.
Okay, come on in.
Show me where it is.
Pretty much what I want you to do.
Come on in and watch the door behind you.
You don't want to get hit by that.
Such a gentleman.
What a unique arrangement.
Yeah, so there's this trash here.
This is dusty?
Yes, it is. It's very dusty.
So if you want to dust, you can, there's
some fruit here that needs to be cleaned up.
Oh, saw stain.
So there's, in the bathroom,
the toilet needs to be cleaned.
The trash needs to be taken out, this flower,
the fridge needs to be cleaned.
This room, the bathroom, any other rooms?
Yes, come with me. I'll show you.
The bathroom definitely needs to be cleaned.
The sinks need to be cleaned.
If you have an opportunity to, it would be great.
How much do you charge?
Well, for you, I'll drop my prices to
$2,000.
That's $2,000 for this?
For the sexy maid service.
Why is this $2,000?
No, it's like $100. It's not $2,000.
Well, lead me to the bedroom and I can
show I'm worth $2,000.
No.
$2,000.
What are you trying to say?
Am I not sexy?
I didn't say any of that. I'm looking for
a maid service to help clean up, maybe make the bed.
Okay. How sexy
am I worth?
I don't have $2,000.
Okay, well you're the one who called a sexy
maid service.
Well, honestly,
I think you look great. I do.
I think you're probably the best looking maid service
maid I've ever seen in my life.
Do you mean that?
Yes, of course. Go on.
I think you're the most attractive,
sexiest maid ever.
I do. I really do.
Please keep going. You're so wonderful.
Let me show you the bathroom.
Okay, come on into the bathroom.
So, I have a plunger.
I have a plunger.
And if anything ever happens to the toilet,
I'm sure you'll be coming and going over the course of the
Do you just want me to clean your house?
Uh, yeah.
Why didn't you just call a regular
I'm a sexy maid.
That's...
What do you mean sexy maid?
Well, like a regular maid service is like a hundred,
maybe two. But when you add the sexy,
it's $2,000 for a maid.
Well, what would you do for $100?
Clean your house, I guess.
That's perfect. That works for me.
$200?
Are you coming here every other day?
Yeah, I'll come. You still think I look sexy, though, right?
I do, I do. $200,
is that all right with you? You want to go lower?
That's okay with $150.
But if you're ever interested in
expanding
my rules.
Yes, I will keep that very much in mind. If you come this way
and just take a look and start doing your thing,
I'll clean over here.
Pick that before I fucking shit my pants in front of the maid.
Sexy maid.
$2,000.
That's so much money.
I'm just trying to get my life
together in here before I go back in there.
And I'm fucking tired, too.
It's four.
Thank you so much.
Wait, where is it going?
Wait, what?
Am I sick?
Do I have
the norovirus? What's happening?
Sir?
Yeah? Are you all right?
I'm okay in here. You don't have to come in.
Do you have a big mess you need cleaning?
No, you can stay out there.
Okay.
All right, that's good. What did I eat?
Those pecan sandies, I swear to God.
Do you like
food? Yeah.
Do you like bread? Yeah.
I wonder if they'll help. Wait, my bread?
Yes, this bread. I got multi-grain bread over there.
Wow. Do you like multi-grain bread?
I like multi-grain bread. Yeah.
Could I ask you why?
Aesthetically,
I thought it made sense to put it in the corner here
to make sure there's enough room for people to come around.
There's not enough space. Maybe eventually
there'll be a TV up here, like a big screen TV
up here. Okay. Yeah, like they could watch
the TV, play video games.
It would have made sense so they could flush.
Well, you're a maid. You're not an interior designer.
You're right. I'm just a maid.
That was the bread.
That was the bread we have to eat.
I'll clean the bathroom next.
I can still eat it.
Uh, excuse me, uh,
sexy maid. What?
Would you like a piece of bread?
Sure.
Okay.
Let's get some bread on the fucking stovetop.
Would you like a piece of bread?
I've got bread, and they throw it on the ground, but it's okay.
Why don't you grab a piece of bread? I want you to eat.
Well, I've been cleaning. I wouldn't
dare touch it with my hands.
Right, but just eat.
Wash your hands and then eat.
I'm not putting it in your mouth. Right, no, of course.
Sorry, I'm just used to different
clients is all.
Out of here. I'm getting out of here.
I'm getting out of here.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom. I'm going to stay here.
And, excuse me,
this job
is not done.
The maid is scaring me.
Our job's not done.
I'm so tired.
God, I think I'm going to pass out.
I think I really am going to pass out.
I need to go to bed. I have to go to bed so bad.
I'm sorry if I smell
a little weird. It's just, it's been a long day.
Well, that's two hundred dollars.
Are you going to, what?
Two hundred? I thought it was one
fifty. I cleaned more than
I thought I had to. There was a big mess in the bathroom.
Okay, take two
hundred. Alright, sir, well,
I'll see you in a few days. Yeah,
and it's one hundred fifty each time, right?
From here on out, we'll talk about it.
And we're not doing anything else.
You still want me to wear this next time I come?
If you like, if you're
comfortable wearing that, you can.
You dog. It's been a weird
day. I'm tired.
Give me something to play with. Give me something to hang out
with. I mean, you guys, seriously, like, I,
I gotta go to bed. I can't
just sleep on a couch every fucking day.
Give me, like, give me, like, give me the bedroom.
Get me to get me to bed. What
is it? What does it say?
You didn't want it? What?
Why not? Scammed.
I, literally, I can,
all I can see is colors. It's
the only thing I can see. I just see pink and I see
like green. I see pink here.
It's just pink.
I need somebody who has to tell me to
go to bed. If I don't, then
you're just gonna get me fucked up again.
All I see is pink colors. Is it?
That was really cool made. I really
thought they were cool. I like to work out people too.
I'm gonna get into the bedroom as fast
as I can because I don't want to have a problem.
For the first time fucking ever.
For the first time ever you made me
go to sleep. Thank you. Seriously,
like, this is the first time you've ever done it.
Took you long enough.
Um, what is that?
What is that? Why is there a computer
in my, in front of my fucking door?
There's a computer here?
What is outside? I hear something.
Dog or something?
Oh no.
My god.
Oh my fucking
god.
I don't know what to do. What am I doing
in this scenario? Is it because of the food?
Oh it's trash!
Um, what time
is it? It's fucking like
one o'clock in the morning.
Oh shit.
Are you gonna see me? I hope
you can't see me. What the
what am I supposed to do about this? I gotta go in the other
I gotta go in the bedroom.
Oh my god.
But yay, computer.
Cool.
Huh? You want me to do
what? I don't know.
I'm not going out there. What the fuck am I
doing?
Uh, alright.
It's time for you to pay. I don't want to go
out here.
Why would you make me do this?
Hey bear, you're in deep shit.
Oh
oh
Oh my god, he's biting
me. Oh my body.
Jesus.
Play dead, play dead, play dead.
Play dead, play dead.
What are you doing?
Do you see what he did out here? Why
don't you make me go confront him?
Are you out of your mind? Are you out of
your mind? What am I
gonna do versus a bear
that's five times as big as me?
Oh
I didn't even sleep
all the way through the night. Oh
this is messy. Good thing
I have a maid. At least they'll be able to help me clean
this shit up.
Close the door for the love of god.
I don't want to fucking, why are there
bears here?
Oh god.
I'm here. Wait.
Go fuck yourself. Good thing I got my
watch. I feel so bad.
Oh there's a mess in my yard.
There's a mess in my yard.
There's a mess.
Wait.
I've covered his face. I've covered his bruises.
I need to go to the
sleep a lot for a while and then I need to go
and get something to eat and then I need to
have something to do.
Holy shit. I can't
stream right now. There's no way
I can stream. What do you want me to stream?
Oh no!
No! I refuse.
I can't.
Hey what's going on everybody? It's Jerma here.
We're going to be playing some Call of Duty.
So as you can see here
I'm going to be in the menu for a little while.
And welcome to the stream. It's good to have you here.
Of course I have a pretty good day today.
I had a crazy
scenario happen. A crazy scenario.
Yeah. Hold on let me get in here.
What's that?
Oh no way dude. Yeah that's so funny.
But dude I saw a bear outside today.
Yeah it was in the trash
and I walked out there and I was like what the heck
is that bear? And eventually
I went outside and I did like a little
horn and the bear like
got away from the horn.
Beep. Beep. Beep. Beep.
Beep. Beep. Beep.
Shit when I sleep. What does it say?
The fucking
water does that.
You have been banned
from Twitch for 24 hours as temporary
ban for sleeping on stream.
Oh what the fuck?
What?
When did I go to sleep? I didn't go to sleep on stream.
What are you talking about?
Give me a fucking break.
A ban? That's the first ban I've ever had.
Are you sure I didn't get banned because I'm streaming
from my toilet? Sleeping
on stream I think is way less offensive
than like shitting on the toilet
and streaming. Just
like that. That's six by the way.
I'd like to take a shower right now please.
Ugh. It's the first ban
I've ever had. I hope I didn't like see
anything weird in my sleep. Fucking
starving and stuff. Oh yi yi.
Ugh. Ban
from Twitch.
Can I call anybody?
I don't know. I say all kinds of weird
fucked up shit. Let me just brush my teeth real quick.
There we go.
Brush your teeth in the shower.
It saves about five minutes. That's a pro
tip for everybody. Coming up.
So what happened?
Why is there like
an office chair next
to the toilet?
Why would there be an
office chair here? In case somebody
wanted to watch?
Oh hey man you got an extra seat? Yeah.
You sit in the toilet I'll watch you.
Why is there an office chair?
I'm starving.
It's a piece of bread on the ground.
Good.
I'm not going to work today by the way
just in case you were curious.
Not going to work.
You can leave without me.
I got plenty of money. Go on.
Not going to work. Go on.
Without me. And tell the boss I said
I'm the biggest producer so I can
stay home.
What is this?
Does this work?
Is this an organ?
I don't think it works.
How about we play Radical Dreamers from
Chrono Cross?
Pretty good!
And how about Super Mario?
Sounds fucking
terrible.
Can I do like reverb?
What?
There we go.
Now we can now get it.
What do they want me to do?
Food.
How about a piece of
bread?
Because it's the easiest thing to make.
I like to toast it.
I like to toast it real quick.
Better. I do have to pee though.
Or, you know, the other one.
I'm sad that the
maid threw this on the ground though.
I'm going to play the organ again.
It works.
What do the pedals do?
Holy shit.
Hey, what? Ludwig?
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
You live here?
What are you talking about? You live here.
I'm sorry.
I've lived here for like seven years.
Hold on.
983, 983.
You're 983?
I'm 983.
I do not know.
I don't know. Just hold on.
Don't mind any of this shit.
It's fine.
Why do you have
trash everywhere?
No, don't worry about that.
There was a tornado that came in.
Did you see the tornado that came in?
No, but yeah, they come sometimes.
A tornado flew through here.
The tornado flew in
and it swarmed everybody.
You didn't get that?
I didn't.
The gloves are also a little confusing to me.
Is that normal?
Yeah, it's very normal.
Tornado came in, ruined everything.
It's nice to see you.
It's nice to see you too. Do you want to come in?
Sure.
I was just playing this
because it was a gift from a friend of mine.
I'll get it for you.
We should clean.
I want to clean first.
You want me to clean with you?
I'm sorry. Can you just help me for a second?
Sure. You know we've never met before.
When did you move in here?
I've lived here for...
Excuse me.
Sheriff Tony Andrews. How you guys doing?
Sheriff, how's it going?
Listen, we're looking for a bear.
Have you seen the bear around here?
We're going around the whole neighborhood.
I've got animal control with me.
How you doing?
He's an expert at this stuff.
There was a tornado and a bear came in.
There was a bear and a tornado?
I kicked the shit out of the bear.
There was a tornado.
I can smell them.
I was going to say I didn't see a tornado either.
I'm pretty sure there's no tornadoes around here.
You guys like organs?
No. Have you seen a bear or not?
I had a bear I encountered yesterday.
You're a full day late.
He's waiting to go.
I don't know. He's a bear.
He's a fucking bear.
You got a scent?
I can smell him.
I think he went this way.
Nothing tricks this.
Why is everybody coming to my house?
We'll find him.
Listen, Sheriff Tony Andrews,
if you need anything, give me a call.
Pick up the trash.
Let's keep the neighborhood nice.
He beat a bear in a fight, right?
Yes, I fought a bear in a fight.
There was a tornado and I got an organ.
I knew I liked you.
I really like you, but I didn't know you lived here.
I just live here. I was just walking by.
I don't mean to intrude or anything.
You were playing Battleship the other day.
You still owe me a lot from that.
I do. I have quite a few things.
I get to get in a shirt.
I get to do a thing in a shirt.
Milky Maids, 1500.
If you ever wanted to play again,
we could just sweep the debt.
Double or nothing.
Do you have another job here, by the way?
Do you work here in the town?
I'm a streamer.
Do you work here as anything else?
In this town?
Do you have houses or anything?
No.
Do you think my stream is not successful enough?
I stream like a month in a row.
It was a long time.
I know.
It was crazy.
You don't do anything else in this town.
Again, I just stream.
Whatever. I won't even push it anymore.
You're talking about we could play what?
We could play Battleship?
Why do you have bread on the floor?
I'm supposed to have it made.
You just ate it out of the ground.
Should I follow you?
Come on in the other room.
Wow. This is your stream setup.
This is my setup, man. Check it out.
It's convenient to have two chairs for co-op.
I could look up.
You could watch me stream if you wanted to.
This is a good setup.
By the way, it's cleaned very well
from whoever that person happens to be
who cleans the house every so often.
Maid?
Is it a guy or a girl?
It's you.
It would be you.
I think it's you.
Do you want to co-op stream?
Sure, of course.
Do you want me to do your intro?
Sometimes I get nervous before a stream.
Let's start the stream.
What's up, suckers?
It's not live yet.
I'm nervous to do co-ops in person.
It won't go through.
I'm banned from Twitch.
Why did you get banned?
Do you see where I stream from?
This reminds me of another doctor streamer.
You can make it work.
I'm going to fall out of the thing.
This has been eye-opening, man.
I didn't know that you lived here.
I didn't know that you lived like this.
You've got to have your setup in a good place.
That's what I agree with.
I think we disagree on how you accomplish that.
I've got to shower, too.
I feel like that shouldn't be a thing you bring up.
It's assumed.
In case you need it to, it's there.
Homemade cookies.
There are cookies.
What do you got here?
You want to play?
No.
I've been waiting for your arrival for months.
I didn't even know you lived here.
I have Mickey...
Let's just say mouse.
Weird mouse cartoon gloves on.
Can you go ahead and open that for me?
I'll open it for you.
Let's get this moved out of the way.
Sorry, I've got to piss really bad.
You take your time. I'll set it up.
I don't have to go quite yet.
Bring it up to me.
Just in case you don't know in the future that I'm going to have to go eventually.
Thank you for the information.
I also will have to pee in the future.
There's a bathroom there, too.
I don't know when.
Should I set up your board for you?
I think you should because I can't touch it.
I made cookies with this woman.
Do you know Edna?
She lives down the street.
Isn't she great?
She's a cool chef, but she's a little weird, though.
Weird in a good way.
I got it for you.
I can't even touch that.
I think this is how it goes.
This looks much more complicated than I thought it was going to be.
You know what? I was thinking,
since you owe me about $500,
we could just do a simple...
You want to do two ships?
Two ships. Maybe even just one.
One ship.
Just a two-piece ship.
I can't get this other glove off because it's taped to my wrist.
You know what?
It's a great watch, though.
It is a really nice watch.
Am I flexing enough?
Do you know that I make pretty good money?
Do you know that I make good money?
I saw your last stream.
You missed a day.
Consistency is key.
You make great money.
I don't want you to see my screen.
Charming place.
I'm not cheating.
Just place one ship.
You're not looking, right?
I got my ship placed.
Do you have your ship placed?
I do.
Are you starting this off?
I'm going to say C5.
Just be so incorrect.
So incorrect.
It's a miss.
This is $500 on the line.
What are we doing with some money?
You owe me money. This is a double or nothing.
Are you okay with that?
You can make a lot.
I didn't even know you lived here.
C5 is a miss.
I will go with C5 as well.
You're doing C5?
I don't like the aesthetic here.
Can you scoot to your left by 3 or 4 inches?
There we go.
I like the aesthetic there a little more.
Is that a bit better?
That's a bit better to me.
It bothered me very much.
That's fair.
So you said C5?
Yeah, C5.
You can literally see me.
I'm going to say F7.
Incredibly incorrect.
Fine.
Where are you going?
Maybe something in the first column.
Well, you have to say something.
D?
Maybe C1?
C1 is a hit.
And you literally looked.
I moved to your left.
You asked me to move to my left.
I just happened to move to my left.
I'm just going to take a random stab in the dark, D1.
No.
What?
There's something on D1.
First of all, I want to do this real quick.
Don't move.
I want everyone to see what I have.
Show them what I have.
If you ever have to go to the bathroom and take a shower, feel free to.
That's where I am and he looked and it's bullshit.
I've never looked at anything in my life.
Call me a cheater?
Yes.
So when did you move here?
I moved to 983 Dollhouse Lane.
983 Dollhouse Lane.
I've been living in Dollhouse Lane for a while, actually.
I was with my mother.
I was friends with a man named Ted who passed recently.
Sad passing, too.
I came out of nowhere.
Blindsided us all.
You weren't there.
By the way, I had a funeral.
It was weird.
No, I wasn't.
I didn't think I had to be there.
Wasn't he your uncle or something?
They're just friends.
My mom is not related.
You and I are not related at all?
No, my mom's just friends with him.
I'm going to go F3.
F3 is just going to be a miss on your end.
That's fine.
You don't have to pee yet or anything, right?
I have had to pee for the last hour, but I'm just going to hold it.
I like talking to you.
Okay.
Let me go with E1.
E1 is incorrect.
You already said that last time.
No, I said D1.
Oh, well, you were wrong twice.
Where do you want to go instead?
You know what? I'll go D2.
D2? That is a miss.
You already have a hit.
Hold on, I've got to get this.
Yeah, take it.
Who is calling right now?
Hello? It's just static.
I don't know who this is.
Hello?
What the fuck?
It was a prank call.
It could have been a prank call.
Since we haven't gotten a response, we're giving you...
Hold on, somebody's there.
A final courtesy call.
Before we close out your file,
I wanted to see if you were available to talk
for a few minutes.
If you'd like to speak to a specialist
concerning extending
or reinstating your vehicle's warranty,
press 1 right now
to speak to a warranty specialist.
I'd like for you to put me on the do not call list.
Put me on the do not call list ever again.
I don't know what that means.
You're going to put me in a database of people
that answered the phone,
so therefore I'm going to get ten times more phone calls.
The real play is for me to never actually answer the phone.
Because if I answer the phone, that means they have me
in the database of people that answered the phone,
so therefore I'll get more.
Have a good day. Fuck you.
What was your move?
It was C4,
like the explosive.
That's a hit.
C3.
C2.
That's a hit. You won again.
I have to pay you $500.
That's $500.
This is just for fun.
That's just for fun.
That's literally just for fun.
I guessed it correctly.
You guessed it correctly, but you didn't even...
Hold on.
Sorry, I've just really got to go to the bathroom.
Yeah, take your time.
Take your time.
Well, I can't go yet.
But I have to go.
I didn't think it'd be like this when we hung out.
I didn't even know you lived here. I thought you lived somewhere.
I don't know you lived here.
I've always lived in Dollhouse.
You walked over and I was doing my thing, playing the organ,
and I didn't know you were here.
Who are those fucking weirdos, by the way? Is it police?
It's the police. There's been a bear on the loose.
Have you had a bear in your house?
Well, before, yeah.
You've had a bear come to your front door?
What else would you do?
That's what I fucking...
What would you do?
I would call the police. But I fought him.
And I kicked his ass.
And then he kicked my ass.
You fought the bear?
Yeah, I kicked his ass.
Why would you fight a bear?
I can't believe this.
You're saying it with a tone that makes me think you might not...
I'll be right back.
Take your time.
Just hang out this food in the fridge.
He's so bad.
Ludwig is in my house right now.
He's awesome.
He's a huge streamer. He's fucking really funny and shit.
I wasn't prepared for this.
I got a piece so fucking bad,
you have no idea.
Please, help me.
I'll do anything. I really will.
Please let me go to the bathroom.
Hey!
How are you? I'm doing good.
Yay! Cool!
He's doing good. Awesome.
How are you doing?
I'm doing great. It's good to have you here, man.
It's really good to have you here.
You seem on edge.
You want something to drink?
No, I'm fine.
Ludwig!
I got a stereo in here.
I'm listening to weird music.
I get that.
I listen to drum solos.
It kind of feels like you're trying to drum over the sound of your shitting,
but that makes sense too.
Drum solos.
Why is the paper this far away?
Why would the paper be over here?
This guy's a bit of a psycho.
Thank God.
That paper is like three feet away.
Oh yeah.
Hands washed!
Ludwig, how are you?
How are you doing?
You've done this a couple times.
Hey, I don't want to stay too long.
It seems like you've got a lot of shit going on.
No, not really.
Just a few things.
But I'm really happy you came over. I hope you like the place.
It's cool.
It's all right.
It's a low mortgage.
I got it on a good deal.
You got a beer?
Yeah.
Is that okay?
I'm just going to help myself.
It's cool, man.
I don't want to...
It's all good, man.
Sometimes I just got to get some blood pumping.
Sorry.
Do I do it with you?
You can if you want to.
Sometimes I just feel like doing it
because I feel like I've got to get some blood going in my body.
Maybe you could move this
to not be in the middle.
That would be a workout.
I can't get swole that way.
That makes a lot of sense.
Hey, it's been a pleasure.
Thanks for the money.
How many times do I have to pay you every time I see you?
Don't want to be too forward.
Maybe it's worth getting a maid around these parts.
I know.
I thought about that.
Weirdly enough, though.
Maids are like two grand around here.
Well, the sexy ones, but you're not a perv.
You wouldn't get those ones.
Those are the maids that are like happy ending maids.
Two grand, though. It's a little high.
Well, it's a good ending.
End of Code Geass levels.
It's a little high.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm just getting my socks on.
I'll just see myself out.
I'll just get my socks on.
It was great seeing you.
I'll call you.
I'll just get my socks on.
This guy's a fucking psycho.
I can't sleep.
Why?
That was so fucking embarrassing.
He's really cool.
You literally just brought in...
That's one of the coolest dudes I know.
I'm trying to sleep.
I'm so tired, but I can't.
Why?
Why can't I sleep?
I don't get it.
I don't...
It's raining. It's really raining.
It's like loud rain.
It's like a thunderstorm.
Oh, whoa!
Whoa!
Whoa! TV!
TV!
Does it work?
TV?
How do I turn it on?
Holy shit!
A TV!
If I can turn it on.
Where is it?
Where is the TV?
How do I turn it on?
The rain is so loud.
TV!
Oh, whoa!
Wow!
TV!
How do I turn the TV off?
Oh, cool!
TV!
Wow!
Oh my god!
TV!
Oh, wow! TV!
That shit's fucked.
Oh!
Why don't we watch some TV?
Ah, the beautiful
rainstorm.
Take a look outside.
Wow!
It's coming down out there.
Holy smokes!
Time to stream.
Let's get some stream going here.
Alright, going live.
Come check me out.
And live.
Hey guys, just started the stream.
But before I get started, let's run some ads.
No, I don't see it.
It's not on the screen.
That's what you're saying. Thanks for the subs.
Appreciate it. It's not there though.
I'm not blind. I can't see it.
There's nothing there.
There's nothing on the screen.
I've turned around four times now, okay?
It's not there.
Stop fucking with me.
I'm just getting like gas lit. That's all you guys fucking do.
I don't know if that's somebody's
officer's, police officer's driving by or something.
Yeah.
That was a siren.
I don't know if that's a main road. It's a busy road.
Yeah, I got it.
Ring the doorbell or something.
Ring the doorbell.
It's hard to do. I'm freaking blind.
Can you knock it a couple times?
Do something, okay?
I'm freaking blind.
I'm pretty sure this is the right place.
Alright, let me show you how it's done, alright?
Hey, listen.
This is Sheriff Tony Andrews, I believe we met.
Yeah, we have.
We have a stolen TV in the area.
And the GPS tracking device is showing right here.
Yeah, the GPS tracking device.
What's that?
It's raining.
Interesting.
Listen, you're going to have to let us in here, okay?
We've got to inspect the area.
It's raining, can you see that?
Wait, is it raining right here?
I'm perfectly fine.
Yeah, that's a stolen what?
Yeah, you see that stolen TV?
My GPS says it's right at this location, right?
How do you have a GPS on a stolen TV?
Everything has tracking devices.
We've got to go in here, we've got to go in here.
Do I seriously go inside, dude?
Who is this guy?
He's a serial jaywalker.
I caught him loitering outside the library a couple minutes ago.
Listen, dude, you can just call me Snakebite.
Why are you bringing him in my house?
What's that?
It's a TV.
You see that red dot?
Yeah.
You see that TV?
I got it from second hand, it was second hand.
And where'd you get it?
I got it from, it was brought to me by some sleep paralysis demons in the night.
Sleep paralysis demons?
Yeah, okay.
Tell me more about your sleep paralysis demons.
You got any sleep paralysis demons?
Sleep paralysis, dude?
It's going down out there, you hear that?
Yeah, I don't know what you're...
He's crazy.
You're a psycho, you know that?
You think it's raining, you got sleep paralysis demons?
What do you want to do about the TV?
Let me ask you something.
You see that red dot?
You think that's that TV right there?
Officer, I don't want a criminal
just in my house.
He hasn't officially been arrested yet.
There's a whole other story.
This is boring.
Hold my phone.
Dude, this is crazy, man.
Let me just double check something, okay?
You can look if you want, I don't think there's anything wrong.
I mean, the TV doesn't work, it broke.
Yeah, that's the exact serial number with the GPS.
I didn't buy it, somebody bought it for me.
It came in here, sleep paralysis demons
bring shit to me and it takes my name away from my account.
Do me a favor.
I'm going to need you to help me pick this up, alright?
I'm sorry, sir, this is stolen property.
Unless you want me to...
You want me to arrest you?
This is your choice.
Okay, listen, you want him to take the TV?
I don't want anyone to take my TV.
This is my TV, it was brought to me by sleep paralysis demons
and it gave me the night time
and they drop shit and they touch my head sometimes.
They touch your head sometimes?
By the way, can I just tell you?
Yeah, what do you want?
You are probably, I would say,
probably the most handsome police officer I've ever seen.
You're aware this is like another dude here, right?
Like I'm a person, dude.
I'm sorry, I just...
The outfit, the uniform...
I really appreciate that, my mother always told me
I look good in blue.
You do look fantastic.
It's the blue, it's the double blue.
Listen, maybe we should grab a beer sometime.
I would absolutely love that.
I would absolutely love going out for a beer.
Hey, where'd you put my phone?
It's in my hands, bro, you made me hold it for you, dude.
Listen, here's the thing,
I can either find you for $300...
Don't find me.
...and I can say that maybe I didn't see the TV.
I don't know, but listen, man,
I'm gonna take the TV either way.
Well, guess what, officer?
The TV doesn't fucking work.
It doesn't work.
So you broke it?
You broke the TV.
You stole the TV and you broke it.
I just wanted to watch the sports program on it
and it didn't work.
It looks like it works a little bit, dude.
It's just kind of abstract, man.
You want me to hang this on the wall
and make it an abstract art painting?
I'm sorry, you're gonna have to keep your hands
off the contraband, alright?
Listen, I'm gonna have to confiscate it.
We're taking it.
You go ahead and lift that up for me.
You expect me to pick up the freaking TV?
It's part of your community service, son.
Really?
Go ahead.
Good luck.
Thank you, by the way. Thank you. Appreciate it.
By the way, like I've got to say before,
I've said it before again,
probably the most handsome cop I've ever seen in my life.
Can we not address the fact that I'm walking backwards?
Can you pick up the pace a little bit, please?
Dude, I'm literally going as fast as I can.
Watch out for the couch.
Dude, we've got cables all over here.
This is a major safety risk, dude.
This is a real jaywalk.
There's no crosswalk in front of the library, dude.
What am I supposed to do?
I've got to get around you for a second.
Okay, alright.
Official police business, huh?
Official police business.
Dude, this is ridiculous, bro.
This is silly.
Can you get a load of that?
Who is Sleed Peralis, the demon?
I've never heard of that before, dude.
Put the TV down for a second.
Go have a good day, go ahead and take it.
I'm not paying to find you.
I don't know if you've heard of Tic-Tac or whatever.
Don't Tick-Tock me!
If you're going to Tick-Tock me, fine.
Are you Tick-Tocking?
Are you Tick-Tocking now?
Yeah, I think so. I don't know how it works.
There, fucking leave, please.
Alright.
And I'm the one in handcuffs, bro?
I'm the one getting arrested?
You made me watch that.
Okay.
This is ridiculous, dude. How far are we carrying this, man?
Another couple miles, man.
Another couple miles, bro, dude.
Now I don't have TV.
And I smell so awful
to a point where it's disgusting people.
And now I don't have TV.
Why would you get a stolen TV?
Why? You had so many options.
Why pick a stolen piece of merchandise?
And I plugged it in and it didn't work.
Unbelievable.
Oh shit, I'm still streaming.
Hey.
If anybody's still here.
So I just had, hey everybody, what's going on?
Just had a little bit of thing going on.
Had my TV worked on. Had a handyman come.
You know, I was trying to get like
an ultra HD
screen put into the wall.
Because you know what I mean? Money.
I got a lot of it. So ultra HD
screen going into the wall back there.
Right in front of the kitchen, too.
I've got money, you know. I've got money.
I've got, mute the stream.
Mute it. I'll be right back.
Oy yi yi.
What a pain in the ass. I gotta
I gotta move.
This neighborhood is fucked.
This most ridiculous neighborhood. What an insane
neighborhood. It's eight.
I mean, I thought I was a weird guy.
Do I belong here or should I leave
here as fast as I can?
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
Hey everybody, I'm back.
I gotta go. I know you've only gotten
about four minutes of content.
And like a 62 minute BRB
screen.
But, you know, I just
I'm working on some stuff.
Make sure to check out tomorrow. There's gonna be
a dollhouse stream tomorrow.
I will check it out with you. We've got a lot of work done on it.
A lot of people were involved. It's gonna be a lot of fun.
So I'll give you guys a link
now. I'll give you the link.
Just send it in. Well, you're here
already, so that's fine. And I'll see
you guys tomorrow for the dollhouse stream.
And goodbye.
Play the outro. There it is.
Okay.
I hate doing this.
I hate streaming. I fucking can't wait till I'm done.
Is somebody calling?
Hello?
Oh, hang on.
Does that shit work on people? I don't understand.
Car warranty?
I don't have a car.
I literally don't have a car. I don't own a car.
How would a car get here?
I was just in there and I didn't go to the bathroom.
This place is a mess.
Disaster.
TV's gone.
My friends think I'm a weirdo.
I barely have anybody I can fucking hang out with.
What an absolute
disaster this has been.
What I'm going to need is I'm going to need the audience to give me some more volume.
That's what I'm going to need. I'm going to need more volume.
I need the audience to give me volume
to let me know what they want to do.
I thought this was going to be easy.
I thought this was going to be simple.
I thought I was going to be able to live here
uninterrupted, undisturbed.
That I'd be taken care of by
600 million people
watching, you know. There's 600 million people
here. You're making me look bad.
I do love this though.
It's a good touch.
I'm going to have somebody sit in here with you in the bathroom.
Alright, finally. I'm hungry.
This is out of the way.
I'm trying like an extension cord.
For the TV that I can't use.
That's great. What do we got?
We got beer that people keep
drinking. You know what?
I think I'm going to go for a slice of bread.
Or a cookie sandwich.
Don't put flash
on the stove, kids.
Is there blood on this? No.
You want to see how dirty these are
over the last like 3 or 4 hours?
Look at this. It's like I literally was walking
around in mud.
These were white.
I do have to go to the bathroom.
And I'm tired.
Very tired.
Can I sleep in the bed tonight or are we going to make me
pass out on the toilet while I take a shit and then
pass out and slash my head on the ground?
Can we make this a normal day?
Huh? Huh?
Normal day. Normal day.
Bars full.
I want to go to bed, I want to pee
and then I want to go to bed. Can we make that happen
please? Can we?
I'm trying so hard to not have my arms go up
because I don't want to see my armpit hairs.
Because somebody is going to screenshot it and like
keep it. I don't want you to have that.
I'm going to the bedroom.
All I have in my third room
is like
stools and a bed.
I mean the organs out there
and that's pretty cool. I'm going to go back and play that.
But like
give me a fun toy.
I'll take a second bathroom.
I don't think that's even possible.
Thank God.
This bed smells like Cheez-Its.
I didn't eat Cheez-Its in here.
Okay, alright.
Alright, I need two shadows in here.
Oh yeah, that's a bad dream for Joyma.
Hey boys, yeah
get him up, get him up.
He's having a bad dream, ain't that right
big boy?
You're all alone.
All alone in your house.
What, you miss that maid? You miss that cute maid
from the other day?
Yeah, get him up.
Get him up.
When's the last time you showered
big boy?
Okay, come on.
Yeah, that's it. Get him up.
Get him in the bathroom.
Oh, I can smell him from here.
Come on, both of you.
I'm not going to get my hands dirty.
Come on.
Yeah.
Big boy Joyma.
What's this, your game station?
Oh, take a look at that.
I can smell it from here.
What's that, dude?
You gotta go to the bathroom, big guy.
Looks to me like you gotta go
to the bathroom. Someone's not been
taking care of their needs, boss.
Get him on the toilet.
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah.
Then Jerma poops himself.
This is Kensington's class.
He poops himself in front of everybody.
No, no, I didn't poop my pants.
And then a cowboy comes out of the shower.
You can poop yourself in the shower.
That'd be embarrassing to poop yourself
in front of so many people.
This is Kensington's class.
And the cowboy's got a sword.
Yeah, you just pooped yourself.
You better keep pooping yourself there, boy.
And then he starts screaming.
You're pooping.
Hey, everybody, it's me, Jerma 95.
You live pooping yourself?
No. Yeah, you are.
Yeah, you are.
You're pooping yourself
on television. Oh, yeah.
I bet you like that, big boy.
I'm about to go live.
That's a TOS violation.
That's a TOS violation. What can go live?
And he gets up again.
I hear your stomach growling. Get up.
Kensington before 3 o'clock.
They get him up and then they go to the kitchen.
And he doesn't wash his hands, either.
Oh, disgusting. I wash my hands
every time. Yeah, sure you do, pal.
Oh.
No.
No, I didn't shit myself.
I'm a good boy.
Make the sandwich with you.
It's your dream, big guy.
Go make the sandwich.
Oh, no.
Make the sandwich with your fucking friend.
You don't have way back where I'm from.
And then Jerma woke up.
Oh, man.
What the fuck?
Huh? What am I doing in here?
Oh, my God.
You know, when you ever have a dream,
you ever have a dream where you,
and you have it, you have it, you have it,
you ever have it when you have it, you ever have it
when you have a dream, you have it when you have it and you had it?
I feel awful.
Why is this stuff all over here?
I had this dream, I like,
I had this fourth grade teacher
and I like pooped my pants
in the class, but whatever. You guys don't know that.
You don't need to know that. Nobody needs to know that here.
But pretty much the end of the story
is I had a bad dream about like how people like laughed
at me, thought I was stupid and like, you know, whatever.
Ugh.
What a fucking joke.
Why is all my stuff everywhere?
Why is my stuff everywhere?
And why am I holding two pieces of bread?
Ay, yi, yi.
Ugh. That was
very weird.
That was very
weird. That was,
that was...
I want to go play the organ.
At least I'll have some fun.
Ugh. Do I have any mail?
I mean, I gotta get rid of this.
I mean,
I didn't see that on camera.
What's in the mail?
It got
rain.
What's in the mail? There's nothing in the mailbox.
I don't see
anything in this mailbox. There's nothing
in the mailbox. There was no mail.
I'm doing this.
...
Public domain music?
Is that what they said?
Um, okay.
...
Maybe take a shower now.
That's fucking water.
Real shower.
Good thing I have my tennis shot.
Hey. There we go.
Nice and clean.
Ready to take on the day.
...
Um, you dropped this.
Oh, thank you so much.
Yes. You looking for an outlet?
Oh, yeah. I think there's...
I have no idea where one is.
I think there's one outlet in the whole house.
There's one right here, sir. Thank you.
You got it? Yeah, I got it.
That's a beautiful vacuum cleaner.
A lot of bathroom usage for you today, sir.
Almost as beautiful as you.
What?
That vacuum is almost as beautiful as you are.
I mean it. What is it? What's that?
That's the sweetest thing I've heard all week.
Thank you. Yeah.
Can I get a hug? Yes, sure.
Absolutely. Come here.
Thank you.
You need to go to the bathroom. It's right here.
Thank you for telling me that.
Yes, of course. Absolutely.
And you know that I mean it.
I keep getting this fucking huge migraine.
And I feel like someone is telling me
I'm being controlled by something.
What the fuck?
I mean, they look good.
They do. They look good.
Everything okay in here?
Yeah, no. Everything's great in here.
Sorry.
You might know I'm not that used to cleaning
up stuff.
Okay.
What's the problem?
What's the problem? Yeah.
It's a computer. You can just move it out of the way.
I'm unsure how to clean it, sir.
Well, just push it out of the way and you can just dust it or something.
Yeah, I'll be in here. You got it.
You're fine. Great.
I'll just move it out of the way.
Oh, I like what they did with this.
I gotta go to work.
Oh, that's not too loud.
No, it's fine. I gotta go to work. I'll see you later.
Have a good time. Thank you.
Again, I want and this might be a little neurotic,
but I like vertical lines,
not horizontal. Okay.
You like vertical lines, not horizontal.
You get a couch in the middle of your living room.
You use the computer in your bathroom.
I woke up and came here and there was a piece of
toilet paper on the floor. We prefer vertical lines.
You can do horizontal if you want.
I would hope.
Yeah. You can do horizontal.
Vertical lines.
You guys are psycho.
Not very much slack left, by the way.
Thank God for Uncle Ted, because otherwise
I would have no fucking money.
See you later. Goodbye.
That was a good day. I feel pretty good about that day.
Hungry. Thirsty.
Ready. But I made some money.
That's good, right? Still kind of a mess out there.
I really wish the...
I really wish...
Goodbye. Yep. See you later.
I didn't press it.
I gotta get that doorbell
looked at. I need like an electrician.
Okay. Why is this
open? Why is this open?
Ugh. It looks pretty
clean in here. Not bad.
I mean, it could be a little better, but
whatever.
Hi.
Um. How dare you
just walk in when I'm cleaning?
The shoes are in the bed? What?
You had your shoes on. I took them off. I'm not a psycho.
I don't sleep with my shoes on. But you took your shoes off
and the shoes were in the bed with you. Why were they not
on the side of the bed? Because I was cleaning the bed and I put
them on the side of the bed. You weren't here for that.
Anyway, it took me a little bit longer today, so it's going to
be $300.
Okay. Um. Is that because you slept
in the room, or is that because you do... You don't
talk to me like that.
Um, no, I was...
Amelia, it was...
It's fine. I was just saying, like
I come from work and you're in bed. I picked up a piece of toilet paper
with poop on it, but I'm the one to blame.
There's been more than one person here.
There's been at least four people here. I found a pair of
pants with poop on it. Did you poop
yourself? I'm wearing the same
pants I was five days
ago. That's even more concerning.
And by the way, I
may have pooped my pants, but
goodness gracious, I mean,
you look great.
And I think that you and I could probably
maybe go out sometime.
Well, I don't know. I'll see what I'm doing
tomorrow. Let's call it $300
and I'll be on my way. Sure, $300.
Great. Hey.
It's been great. It's been fantastic.
We should go out sometime.
You want to go out sometime?
Well, I just said I might be free tomorrow.
Yeah, but like, I got
a wild schedule. Can I confirm
it? Sure. Okay.
I don't think I want to shake
your hand after you said you pooped yourself.
How about this one? Great.
Yeah! Woohoo!
Got a date!
You know, there are, there are,
um, there are
three to four options
when you get a choice.
You know, there's a few
different things you can choose from each time.
Not sure you're aware of
that at this point. I feel pretty good.
I feel pretty good. I feel pretty good.
Although I'm very hungry.
Oh!
Can I eat something?
What are you going to do? I saw
mine, that's the first time I've looked at chat in like
four plus hours or so. I saw
minus twos. Thank you.
It looks the same
loaf of bread every time.
This bread has lasted a long
time. I hope
my hands are really clean. I've been cleaning them.
I'm actually glad I'm wearing these gloves
because, I mean,
they're just, they're absolutely gross, but I really
am happy I have them on.
I have an apple too. Why would I not eat the apple?
I want to hang out in here.
Ah! Ah! I'm going to sit down.
God! You work all
day. You come back.
You just want to sit on your bed.
Why were they sleeping in here?
I could have paid you hundreds of dollars
to sleep in the bed.
Like, I wonder how, I was gone
for six and a half hours.
I bet you they were sleeping in this bed before.
What?
I'm not going to, I'm not
smelling anything.
In fact, I want this bed
fucking removed from the house.
All right, let's do some Twitch TV
streaming.
Every time. Okay.
Let's go. Get these,
I got to get at least one off, right?
Okay, let's go live.
So, we're going to do some
Germacraft, some Minecraft.
I'm going to call this episode one.
Live Germacraft.
And let's go live.
Hey, what's going on, everybody?
Germa here with episode one
of Germacraft.
You know, of course, the series where I play Minecraft.
And it's going to be really fun.
It's going to be a lot of trials, a lot of triumphs,
a lot of fails. And
uh,
that was a funny
dream.
So, by the
way, before I turn the stream off, everybody, I just want to say,
um, if you
go to Germa985.com,
we've got
merchandise for you, we've got posters
for you, we've got all kinds of things you can get, and
some of them might even be signed, too.
Oh, sorry, I'm talking to you guys, too.
Have a good day.
I'm not even online. The stream's been off for like the last
three hours. I'm going to be banned for two days.
Am I going to get permanently banned
from Twitch if I do that again?
Just don't do that again. I actually might not be able
to stream again. If you want, like, income,
don't do that.
So that's what I heard. Ah, cool!
A bunk bed!
Oh! It's another
mystery box! Oh my
goodness, I wonder what's in this one!
God, you give people
a loot box option, and that's what they're going to pick
like three out of ten times, which would be 30%,
which is not that much. I mean like five out of ten,
which would be fifty. How about let's go eight out of ten?
You couldn't have put
anything else in there, in here.
You couldn't have put like rubber duckies or something.
It's three more stools?
This is the biggest bait ever.
People would probably be pissed.
Okay, I'm...
Alright, well...
Let's get this out of the way.
I heard an explosion in
this room. This bed is...
I'm moving this.
Get this out of the way. I'm putting
this over here.
Let me at least get this correct here.
Decorate? Yeah, I can do that.
Although I do have to pee, so
I would do that soon.
Um...
Can I get rid of the box part of the decoration?
Where would I want the bed?
I definitely don't want
the bed in front of the door. That would be a pain in the ass.
Let's go with over here.
Probably against the wall. I want it against the wall.
That makes more sense to me.
That looks good. Why would you have a bed
like over here?
I like that. It's a twin bed.
I don't have to worry about the other side. Who cares?
Alright, then what about the mystery box?
We can put that in the corner.
And then I'll put the...
I'll put these in the...
I don't know. What am I supposed to do with these?
What a shitty bedroom.
This looks like I'm still moving
into this house.
How about two over there,
and two over here.
Good.
I have to pee real bad, like right now.
How about on top of the
mystery box?
Beautiful day outside. Beautiful day.
I want one of these next to the
bed so I can put my legs over.
That makes sense to me.
There couldn't have been anything else in that box.
Anything else.
I don't know what to do with these.
I don't even have a shelf
to put anything on.
That's there. That can just stay there.
I don't care.
That's fine. That can stay.
How does it look? You like it?
What do you think?
Thank you.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is nice, 985. This is a wonderful,
wonderful place. Thank you for letting me be.
I appreciate it. Do you think we should try?
I don't see why we shouldn't.
I think it'll make sense.
It's even in tune.
This is perfect. Wonderful.
Why don't we start off with some 985?
We'll practice 985?
985. That sounds good.
Let's do that. 985.
I'm trying something new.
Alright.
Go ahead.
Or get outside.
God our
father.
He's our daddy.
He's our
friend.
He's our friend.
He's our hand.
Father, not daddy.
Sorry about that.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Edna, how are you?
I'm doing great. Who are you?
Jerma,
you were here a few days ago?
You came here last week?
Jerma, we heard you had this wonderful
organ.
I heard how impressive your organ was.
And I just wanted to come over and play
with your organ. With my
choir, of course, from church.
Bless you.
Bless you too.
If you want to join in.
Would you like to join in?
Why don't you just stick around
and see what happens.
Step on over with them. That'll be great.
Your organ is so big I'll have to use two
hands. Here we go.
I think you use two hands to play an organ.
I don't think you play an organ with one
hand. It's not like a flute.
Over here?
Let's take it from the top.
From the top of where?
You'll figure it out.
What page are we on?
God came
down from the land.
And he took
us all by the hand.
And then
we started
dancing.
And then we started
He's got the spirit.
Remix.
God came down to the land
in the land. God came down
to the land in the land.
I can't believe what's happening right now.
I can't believe what's
happening right now.
Oh, okay.
And he came down to the...
Why don't you lead us in it?
And he came down to the
land. And he came
down to the land.
And he...
He ate...
He brought wine
and sand. And he
brought wine and sand.
And then he
left my
front yard. And then he
left my front yard.
They went in the fridge
and he got himself a nice big tub of lard.
And went to the fridge
and got a big tub of lard.
And the...
Get you drunk.
On God's love.
What the fuck is happening?
On God's...
God bless you all.
Is he done?
Get you drunk?
That was beautiful.
But that's my organ and I'd like for you all to leave.
Well, we would like our book back.
Unless you, of course, would like to study on your own.
We'll save it for you at the church and you can come
sing with us any time.
Alright. Wonderful.
Bless you. And bless this house.
Thank you. Please actually do that a few times.
Because there's been a lot of fucking weirdos here.
Bye now. Bye now.
Have a great day!
Alright.
I hope one day they're ready.
But wait, wait a minute. Wait a second.
Hey, wait, wait a minute!
Wait, I really want that book.
I want that book.
I think the book... Can I have one of those books?
Yes, sir. Thank you so much.
I'd love one of these books. Can I keep it?
Yes, you may. You probably should.
What passage should I
read from to get rid of bears
and people that I don't want in the house?
Jeremiah 9
8 5 is actually my favorite chapter.
Okay.
Here.
I'll put it in the mailbox.
Yes, probably good.
He'll find it.
And he'll find his way home.
Yes, we have.
Good job, sister. Very good.
I hope they're still there.
I really hope they're still here.
What an embarrassment.
I don't want to play this too loud because they'll come back.
I'm fucking hungry. I'm tired.
And I have not showered.
You hear that? Thank you.
How does she not know who I am?
She was here like fucking a week ago.
That's over budget of farting.
That's definitely over fart budget.
Better.
Thank goodness.
Oh yeah.
I brush my teeth every time I get in the shower.
Every time.
It saves like two minutes each day.
That's too over budget.
That's too many.
I know it's fun to do that.
But
no, I know it's really,
don't just get them all out of your system right now.
I'll shit in the shower.
Get them out of your system.
You need a lot of characters in your time.
But character development
and internal characterization of yourself
is very important.
The more you think about who you are as a person
and what you do, the deeds you do,
that's how you can shape
yourself as a person.
Or if you want to know,
fill words to make yourself sound intelligent.
Oh, should I have a date?
I have a date with a maid.
Fuck.
Right now?
I don't want to bail on Amelia.
That would be a mistake.
I'm just so tired.
They'll understand.
It's fine.
This is too comfy.
Another time.
I'll text them.
Kind of comfy, but what did I miss?
Oh, I had a date.
It's okay.
Oh, my back hurts.
You can't sleep sitting down.
Not bad. I felt worse.
Okay.
Uh, had a bed
already. Hungry.
This is not very stable, by the way.
I'm not sure I can sleep on this.
I already had a bed.
Is that a bed sandwich?
That's alright.
I had a better bed
in my dorm room in college than this.
Ugh. I'm hungry.
Ugh. Can I make
some food, please?
Am I making something to eat?
I'm so hungry.
I am starving.
Does it matter? Can I eat? I don't want to eat bread
for a seventh time.
I really don't. Here.
You know what? We're doing hot dogs.
What do I got? Do I have hot dogs?
No. We're doing butter and eggs.
My favorite. That was very loud.
There.
Ow. Not bad.
Not bad.
A few minutes. Another 30 seconds or so.
Should be ready to eat.
There we are. Need another cup.
Oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops,
oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops,
oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops
it's all right it's all right it's all right it's all right i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it
this what the fuck oh shit oh oh no no no no no no no no holy shit spray it get out of here get out
of here you little bastard get out of here you little bastard shit no fuck no no no no no no no
no stay down there you motherfucker dammit things fucking jammed ah
fuck whatever okay it's all right it's fine it's fine it's fine it's all right everything's gonna
be fine everything's gonna be fine everything's gonna be just fine everything's gonna be fine
everything's come here come here shit i can't fucking hit them this thing what are you doing
What the fuck are you talking about?
Somebody's in the door!
I can't fight this motherfucker!
You're a big fire! I don't know if I can do this!
Alright, I'm coming at you!
No, no, no, no, no! I don't want to fight him! He's huge!
He's huge! He's a huge guy! He's a huge fire!
Stay, keep, wait, wait, ah, fuck!
Gah! Gah! Gah! Ah, shit! No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!