What is up, everybody? It is Jerma with another gameplay commentary.
This time I am on Koth Nucleus as a combat engineer.
This first kill right here is a demo man who was trying to attack my sentry gun with his axe.
And he's successful a couple times, so don't laugh.
Like I said, this is on Nucleus as Nucleus, not Nucleus. What am I, George Bush?
Combat engineer on Nucleus, trying to keep this little hallway up here secure as an engineer.
This part is great. This medic kind of actually kills himself with an uber.
So he lost his uber, which is not a good thing whenever you're a medic to lose your uber.
He was probably raging about that.
My sentry gets another kill up there. I think it was the scout that was up there,
but I'm not really sure. There could have been one or two more people.
But like I said, we're on Nucleus, trying to harass the point with my pistol.
That's by, I just say, that engineer's life. He was holding what looked like a,
I think it was a full sentry is what he was building outside the spawn.
So that would have been bad. I felt good about that.
I used my revenge crit on this engineer and tried to get this medic, but I end up failing
pretty hard right here.
What's that? Oh, I fall and get hit in the face.
I kind of got stuck on the side and another engineer killed me with a sentry.
But yeah, he started off kind of good there.
Ruined a medic's charge, killed a couple people.
It's kind of back and forth this entire time with the blue team and red team.
I like it when it's like that. I hate when rolls happen.
Here's that same demo man and he actually is successful this time and he runs away.
And I mean, that was great. Whoever that is should be proud of himself.
I think I'm going to come up here and get him and like trap him up here.
He's going to, oh, hey, what's going on? I'm right here.
I do it, but he ends up killing himself on me.
If he had just turned around another second earlier, I probably would be dead.
So I'm going to take that one with a grain of salt.
Just trying to harass the point up here.
Spy saps my sentry.
I go, oh no, it's a mini sentry. What do I do?
Oh, just build another one. It doesn't matter.
And see this medic through the window over there and I try to trap him too.
He's with somebody, but I end up just killing him with a shotgun.
Anyways, that's the same medic that I ruined the day of before.
So he's probably annoyed with me.
I like to use the Wrangler a lot of times with the mini sentry.
But kill that engineer, kill that demo man and get shot in the face.
I like to use the Wrangler a lot with the mini sentry because it shoots so fast
and it just really harasses people really badly.
Which is one of your number one objectives as a combat engineer is to harass people.
Like what I'm doing with the pistol right now.
Not really trying to kill anybody.
I tried going for the point.
I was thinking about going for the point and that demo man
was not going to let me do that.
And rightfully so because I'm an engineer and he's a demo man.
So who wins that fight?
Run on run, one on one.
I get some revenge crits here and I kill people from far away right here.
I get two kills right here from very far away.
And a lot of you might be asking, German, what the hell are you doing?
Why are you shooting people with a shotgun from like fucking a thousand feet away?
And it's purely for harassment.
I killed this scout with the shotgun because he was attacking my sentry.
You don't do that shit.
Just trying to cap the point.
I get blown up by random spam rockets or random spam grenades it looks like.
But what I was saying before is I like to harass.
And when you get shot with a crit and it makes that noise that like boo!
It makes that noise and you know you get hit with a crit.
It scares you.
It doesn't really startle you but you know you got hit with it.
And you back up and you start to think, okay, this guy's got crits.
He's hitting me with a mono.
What do I do?
Speaking of crits, I just get hit with one right there from this pyro.
But it harasses people and that's one of my big philosophies as a combat engineer
is to just harass the shit out of people.
And I find that to be quite effective.
This scout up here was trying to spawn camp sort of with the ball.
I come down here to try and take him out.
And I'm not successful at all.
This medic kills him.
I go, oh, somebody else.
I'll kill him.
This medic kills him too.
I get the assists.
That's a good medic.
I put the little mini sentry down there.
Hoping that I can get somebody coming out of the spawn on the right side there.
I get in a little fight with this engineer.
I run out of bullets on both my guns or on the shotgun.
And he only has like one shot left.
And you know, 2020 hindsight, you look back and you go,
if I had just shot him with one little fucking pellet or something, he would be dead.
But you know, it's for null, whatever.
I come back down here and I actually kill him this time.
Uh, with a shotgun shot, I believe.
This time, I thought I was going to fail.
No, it's a pistol shot.
See, this time I wasn't an idiot.
I wasn't an idiot that time.
That's a spy.
I know it.
And I'm out of bullets now.
And it happens again.
I fail again pretty hard from the end.
That engineer killed me again that time.
That's why I love playing spy.
Because you get to see people's health and you can say,
you know, if I just shoot him one time in the back, he'll die.
It's one of my favorite things about the spy.
But this is engineer.
This is a very, very close game right now.
Trying to get the mini-sentry up here to harass the point and I get a couple of kills.
And this engineer on the other side is doing the exact same thing I was doing.
So props to you, Mr. Engineer.
I get the crits.
I used it a few times.
Kill that engineer.
Get rid of his mini-sentry.
And it looks like we got the point.
Same deal.
Just trying to put the mini-sentry in a place somewhere where it will
get a few shots on somebody but I get killed.
And it is now a very, very, very neck and neck game.
29, 22.
I love games like this.
I hate when we just roll or when somebody rolls us.
It's not fun.
When you just roll somebody, it's not fun.
Like you'll see in a video that I'm going to upload next.
Rolling is just stupid.
I hate it.
This part is really great.
I end up dying but you'll see what happens here.
I kill pretty much the entire team with the mini-sentry.
Because nobody decides to turn around and look at it.
And if you can see, I kill about three or four people with the mini-sentry
and we win because of it.
And if you can see it right there, it has like no health.
But if they had just turned around and looked, they would have seen it.
But anyways, thanks a lot for watching, guys.
I look forward to more subscribers, more views, and I love you guys.