Alright, so I think it's going. Hopefully there's no problems with the actual stream,
because that would not be cool. Twitch.tv. I gotta change this. It says I'm gonna be
playing CSGO, but that's not the case. That's gotta be changed. Yeah, the chat is lagging.
I can't see any of these. The chat is all screwed up. That is not cool. I don't have
a solution to that, so I'm just gonna have to do it, play it by ear, and if something
happens, something happens, you know? Oh yeah, I'm trying to see how to spell principal right,
if you saw that in the Google chat. How do you spell principal? I don't know. Let's see
if I can pop this out. Alright, it's muted. Lower. Just want the chat. Mmm, that's not
working for me. That is not working for me. Come on Twitch, get your act together. I'm
refreshing the page. If you haven't chat problems, just try refreshing. Maybe that'll help. If
not, then I'm not exactly sure what to do. But it's okay. We shall persevere. Right there.
Okay, just gonna tell people what's happening on the various social media networks. It's
going on Twitter. And then, of course, the Steam group. Steam community groups. The inhumane
psychopaths. Party. Twitch. Jot TV. Oh, by the way, I'm also sorry for starting this
pretty late. I was trying to get that video up and it was not working. Don't know why,
but it just wasn't. Oh, not in all caps. That's me screaming. Woohoo! Fifteen minutes. That
was me. And one more. Gotta tell all the people on the YouTubes about it. Channel feed. Streaming
TF2 and Flash game. HTTP. Alright. Okay. Good afternoon, morning, evening, night time, whatever
it happens to be in your quarters of the world. Welcome to the stream. Oh, Flash Gordon game.
So sooner or later here when I get my server up and running, we're not gonna have to do
more. It'll just be, hey, I'm in my server. Everyone go there if you want to play. Because
now it's kind of like, where are we gonna find a good map to play on? How about the
Gold Rush? Alright, Gold Rush it is. Oh, no, wait, never mind. Refresh. It was like fifteen
people already in there. How about players are not full. That's fine. Alright, come on.
Stop with the refresh. Oh, come on. I just refreshed it again trying to hit stop refresh.
Why do you do that? Stop. Okay. How about, ooh, that one is Thunder Mountain. Cough Badlands.
King of the Hill Badlands. Here's the IP. Let's get started. And boom, heads in there.
All hands on deck. King of the Hill Nucleus should be a rockin' time. It's 4.05 in California,
yeah? Yeah, I'm sorry for starting late. I said this before, but I'll say it again. It's
probably like seven in the morning or like five in the morning for people that are used
to seeing this at like, at least at a reasonable time, and I apologize for that. I usually
want to start at around 5.36, but 7.30 is when we're actually starting, and I feel bad
for you European guys. That's my fault, and I do apologize. What do I want to do now?
Let's go. Oh, I'm sure the audio is good. How's the in-game audio? Should it be lower
or higher? How does it sound? Who am I bumping into? You know, I'll stick with the Direct
Hit. The chat's still broken. Yeah, I don't know. If you can not see the chat, I apologize.
There's nothing I can do. Oh, come on, you scout. Why am I using the...I have to touch
you, by the way. Come here! Oh, which way are you going to go? What? What was that?
Oh, it was a crit. Oh, okay. Yeah, the chat's not refreshing for me either. So I guess
just sit back and relax, and if you're playing, play, I guess. Five, four, three, long one.
I'm taking the Direct Hit off. Get rid of this thing. Why am I using the gunboats? What
on earth are these on here for right now? I'll keep the half-satoichi on. I'm not very
good with the Direct Hit. It's hard. It's very hard to use. Where do you go? Where do you
go? Where do you go? I'm going to jump around. What's going on here? Super lag. Super lag.
Oh, no. Sentra down. I need help. I'm loaded all my shots in this shotgun. I don't know
how that happened. Oh, my God. Come on, something has to change. That's why. Sensitivity was
all a little low. I'm going to have to deal with it, though. So when are we going to get
an update? When's the Teeny Fortress update coming out? How am I not hitting him? I feel
like I'm lagging like crazy. I'm starting to go in a roll here. Ding ding. Oh, here comes
Burger Boy. I wonder who that is. That can't be Burger Boy right there, can it? Burger
Boy. Hold that point. I wish I could see the chat. I'm refreshing. I can't see the chat.
Maybe if I do this, I might be able to see the chat if I go to the dashboard. Maybe just
the actual chat is screwed up. Maybe not. Maybe not. Twitch, what the heck? I'm streaming
on Twitch because YouTube is usually broken, and I guess not. I guess not, Twitch. Bing
bing bing. Oh, I'm going to get headshot. I know it. I know it. Run away. Oh, this guy
is screwed. Oh, I thought I killed him. You see that in the kill feed? It was like, oh,
nope, you killed the guy behind him. I think that was a dead ringer. I don't think he's
dead. Pretty sure he's still alive. Might as well go get some health. Right. Boom. Fire.
Oh, no. We've got to get on this. Oh, jump around. So get off your feet and jump around.
Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. I don't know what the point of that was. Oh, my god. Oh,
no. No. I'm just jumping around like an idiot. I'm not. I'm doing okay. Still no chat. This
is what it looks like, by the way, for me. Like, the wheel of death. So I can't answer
your questions. Oh, that's stupid. I'm going to try refreshing it again. That's what it
looks like. Unfortunately. Did I get the chat back? Did I? Of course not. Of course not.
That was a spy. My god. That was a dead ringer. Look out. Look out. Look out. Oh, that's going
to kill me. I need the equalizer. I need to put the equalizer on. We're going to lose.
If I can help it. Stay on it. Stay on it. Stay on it, my brethren. Get that spy and
the scout. Stay on it. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Yes. Nice job. Nice job. Good
job, guys. Look at this guy just like hiding behind like the stakeout area. Oh, now I
got the chat. Okay. I just said MGE live streaming. That's the last thing I saw. I was going for
an air shot. I'm not hitting people with rockets right now. I think every single one of my
kills has been with the shotgun. Except for that one. Except for Burger Boy. Need help.
Come on. Hit him. Oh. No. No. No. No. I can't believe I'm that stupid. Oh, my god. What
is wrong with me? Yeah, good game, guys. Good game. Oh, my god. I'm just standing there
like scratching my butt. What is going on? What the hell is this? What is it? A prop
hunt mod? Wow. That's pretty cool. All right. We're going to go in. Whatever this is, I'm
using it. All right. Good. Oh, come on. Get hit marked. Get hit mocking. How did I lose
all that? I thought I was hitting people. Oh, now I can read the chat. Oh, god. So, yes,
I will talk about my Steam Workshop item. Oh, no, Burger Boy. Just punch him. My Steam
Workshop item is going well. The modeler behind it, he... Thank you, Optimus Prime. But the
modeler behind it, he had to take a little break from modeling because I think he just
had some school stuff he was trying to get out of the way and had some family things
he wanted to get done. So, it is still going. I got a pretzel in my mouth. I'm sitting here
eating pretzels and I can't even like... Yeah, so probably in a couple weeks, I would assume
will be more updates on that. And I'm going to die. It's going to take one shot. I'm going
to go down. Might as well make it epic. That is a spy. How come I didn't get any medal
for this? Was that not really a spy? I swear I bumped into him. I swear to every single
deity that exists, I was bumping into that guy. Oh, man. Look at all these dudes in here.
Yeah, the pretzels are meeting. They're the small... Look at them. Look at me. I'm like,
hey, I got one hand playing it. Okay, okay. Let me wash this down first. Before, I was
an idiot. Oh, I got a kill. They're the small cylinder pretzels, like the ones that are
the best ones. I'm not a big fan of the really skinny ones. If you guys know what I'm talking
about, the tiny little skinny baby pretzels. Eh, not for me. Now, let's actually start
playing this game. You know what? I want this. There we go. Are you a spy? I bet you are.
Oh, no. Here comes Burger Boy. The insensitive one. Demo ends with spy. I can't. I got to
shoot somebody. Come on. One good meat shot on someone. Do you want some hats? Germa?
No, I'm good. I'm good to go. Thank you for offering, though. I appreciate that. I don't
need any items or anything. Oh, boy. Pyro coming in. Come on. Come on. Oh, no. I'm dead.
I didn't mean to taunt, by the way. I was just trying not to die. The chat is back.
Thank goodness. Can I play some payload? Of course. I'm going to try and find a good Gold
Rush or Bad Water map after this. What are we looking like? That's spy. I don't know
why. I'll put it right here. Give me those hit markers. Oh, gosh darn it. Am I a fan
of Frank Sinatra? Yeah. Who couldn't be with a voice like that? Luck be a lady tonight.
Luck be a lady tonight. Luck if you ever kill Germa in Team Fortress. Luck be a scout tonight.
I apologize for doing that. That was not cool. Oh, my God. I'm going to die again. No. Can
I make it? Take your bats. Do I make it? Do I make it? Go, go, go, go, go. Oh, come on.
I had my finger touching. I was reaching for it, too, and everything. Give me a break.
Oh, well. All right. This time. Every time I get out of spawn, something bad happens.
Getting kills with a mini sentry. That's one good thing that comes out of all this. I'm
going to move it. I want it up here. Oh, my God. You toast bastard. How much was TF2?
TF2 was $10. I think it was originally $20, wasn't it? $19.99 for a while. Then it went
to $9. Did it ever go to $9.99? I don't remember it being $9.99. Maybe it's because I just
never bought it. That's a crit. I'm dead. I was trying to strafe and drop down, not
in the pit, and I ended up landing on the crit. Well, you know what? We're going to
change this. Oh, by the way, I'm going to say this here just because, you know, it makes
sense to say it here. I still have to give away 33% of that backpack because it's been
about five days and the third person still has not responded. So I'm going to give them
maybe another 48 hours, and if I still don't see anything, we're going to talk about maybe
another small giveaway, potentially in the stream. So I might not do it. If I do it on
Twitter, I do it on Twitter, but I've not decided at this point what I'm going to do.
I'll probably just repick. Ow. Oh, put me out. Put me out. I was behind you. I have
not played Gotham City Impostors. I heard it's fun, though. Are we going to win? Oh,
they're going to get it. They are absolutely going to get this. I'm going up here. I'm
absolutely going up here. I'm protecting this room. This health is mine for the rest of
this god damn game. Oh my god. What's going on? What? What is it? What's happening? Oh
my god. During the live stream. Um, hold on. Hold on a sec. That just took me totally off
guard. Um, thank you so much for that. Hold on. Let me accept it. Hold on. Let me even
see what just even happened. Hold on. I got to duck away for one second. Oh, we won. Okay,
cool. What is that? What's happening right now? Where is it? You've received a gift.
Total War Shogun 2. Oh my god. Oh, this is from my wedding partner. Oh my god. I have
to show this. I forgot to show this off. So this guy right here, this Suicidal Engineer
is what his name is. He sent me the ring. Where is it? Where's my diamond ring? Look
at that. Special something for special someone. So thank you so much. I wanted to really mention
that. But yes, I will accept this. Yeah, this is like the Team Fortress 2 like Valentine's.
It's not wedding. It's like Valentine's Day. But yeah. Special shout out to that guy because
that's really, really thoughtful. So now I've got to accept your gift. I don't even know
how to do it. Where is it? All right. I accept. Thank you. Thank you so much. Add to my game
library. I will absolutely play this. Thank you so much. That's all I can say. You're
awesome. Thank you. Oh, our little Jervish growing up now. Yeah, that's awesome. That's
not a good way to go. Yeah, I did see the new Grordbord stuff. The new Grordbord. How
do you even say that? I always say that wrong. Grordbord. Grordbord. Gordbot. Oh my god.
Every time. Every time I exit spawn. All right. You know what? I'm going. I am going to just
plant. You know what? No. I'm killing this guy first. Before running away. That works
as well. Protect this room. Let's at least get some area denial going here. This guy's
down here. This guy knows I'm here. Where is he? Change it. Right here. Oh what? What?
That's a big sentry. That is a big sentry. My goodness. No. My god. All right. All right.
Time to go scout. Time to go scout. I'm going to use. Oh no. Oh that's right. You know what?
For the sake of my backpack being gone, we're going to go all default. At least item wise.
You are not real. And you're probably still alive. I can't believe I just did that. I
can't believe it. I can't believe that just happened. I can't believe I just did that.
I got behind two people. I want to just go punch myself in the face with like an iron.
Oh my god. That is really depressing. You know what I mean? It's just like I got behind
those two guys. That one soldier. And there was a crit. And I missed. There's a spy coming
up. I need help. He's going to headshot me. This always happens. Why did I just hit E?
God. This is a spy. Maybe not. Let's bump. No. It's Ari. Hey Ari. That's a bad place
to go. What? What? What just happened? That guy shot me through the staircase. I am mad.
All right. I'm putting the milk on. I need my milk. I need my calcium. Calcium for the
week. If I were to have any unusual effect on a hat or any unusual, I would want the
what is it? The searing towering pillar of hats. Because that is not worth like five
million dollars or something. That's like a lot of money. Two soldiers. I can't deal
with that. And a scout. And I have milk. And I threw it. Oh my goodness gracious. How much
what? Somebody tell me. What is the most expensive Team Fortress hat? Like in dollars. In U.S.
dollars. Is it searing towering pillar or a sunlight towering pillar? Is it like two
thousand dollars or something crazy? What is the approximation? The value of that item?
Oh boy. I'm in trouble. Someone just has to like burp on me and I'm going to die. Please
don't burp on me. I don't want to die. There we go. I have played L.A. Noir. Oh. What?
Oh. That just made me sad what just happened. I'm not even mad about that. I'm just like
upset. I just want to cry. Game to game. Sunbeam's TC is about 40 buds. So how much is one bud?
U.S. dollars. Get in there. Did I get him? Get rid of that mini sentry. I can't even
go over there. I can't even go anywhere. I can't take you anywhere scout. Hi spawn. Bye
spawn. I can't go over there. God. Oh that's not the right taunt. Wait we failed. Wait
I thought we were winning. I thought we had the point. Well that's uh. So one bud is 35
dollars. So that's a lot of money. That is a lot of money. Let's go to. Alright new server.
Thanks to you guys on this server right now. We're going to trade. Trade servers. Let's
try and get on a payload. Payload race. No no payload race. I don't like payload race.
I do but it can be too chaotic. Peel bad water. Too many bots. People won't be able to get
in so easily. Here we go. Hoodoo. There we go. Absolutely freaking lootly hoodoo. It's
going in the chat right now. This is the IP. There you are. Ladies and gents. The last
giveaway winner. I sent him a Twitter message and he still hasn't replied. I'm going to
shell check right now. That was a long time ago. That was a while ago. So be on the lookout
in the next week or the next 3 or 4 days. I may be picking another person on Twitter
for this 33% of this backpack. I want all your items. I'm probably going to play tower
defense again because that was always fun. Bloons tower defense. Here's the IP again
for those of you wondering. That is the IP right? Let me make sure. Yes it is. That is
the IP. Do. I don't think I've really ever done the scope sniper on a stream before so
you know what? We're going to do it. I need like a hat. I need like a hat. One of these
like party hats and like sunglasses. Oh yeah. High five. Ship boom. Pro ping right here.
How much ping? That's not that bad Norman. That's not too terrible. I'd say if you got
to like 160 or 150 you should start to count your blessings. Oh my god Boo. Yeah Boo sorry
there's like no Skype call. I was running very very very late. More than an hour late
to the stream so I had to just go. What is this guy doing? That guy was like standing
in the creator character position. You know what? This is a bad spot. I'm going to get
in trouble. Yeah I knew it. That's a bad spot. Late to his own stream as usual. Yeah I do
frequently. I'm always at least 5-10 minutes late. Hey better late than never though right?
Isn't that the old adage? Is that even an adage? Oh my cat's in here now going. Let's
get a couple of headshots huh? There goes the engineer that's in like the creator character
stance. What? Oh boy. I didn't cover him. My god what a total idiot I am. Stop the
bloody boom. Ow. Right in my face. Am I going to play Left 4 Dead 2? Probably not on this
stream tonight but I absolutely love that game so probably at some point yeah. Will you stop
meowing? You're ruining my stream cat meowing. Oh my god. Hey you look like you could use
some pee on your back. I'll like throw it right into one of my teammates backs. I just
puked cat. Oh I got to switch. I got to go heavy. They're going to win. Got to go heavy
with the brass beast and I'm just going to stand in a corner and just hold down this
damn button. Come on come on come on come on. Don't let them get it. Don't let them
get it. No. No I got to get right up on here. Bye. Oh my god I'm going to die. I'm just
going to eat the sandwich on the cart. Oh my god. Oh yeah. Heavy turtling. What do you
know about heavy turtles? The two heavy turtles. This is actually going to work. Who needs
sentry guns when you've got three super heavies? Are these two the same person? Oh hear me.
Help me. Teenage mutant ninja heavy alien turtles. So I know I asked this before but
I couldn't see the chat. Is the audio fine? Can you hear me and is the stream too loud
or are we just right as Goldilocks would say? That's good. That's good. Ha! You cannot
defeat the heavy. I just bumped into someone for sure. You can always tell when, you know,
you never know if it's lag or you're actually bumping into someone and that's, I don't want
to get hit by that again. Oh for the love of all that is sacred. Ditto zero zero zero.
How are you man? Look at, I love this heavy. Look at this guy. That is a true heavy right
there. Standing on the cart with sunglasses, a luchador mask and a Russian hat on. What
a goofy goofy person. I love him. Oh my goodness. Oh I have on the Brass Beast. Can't move.
Must punch someone in face. Nope not going to happen. I heard a backstab. I'm so scared
right now. That is the worst part about the Brass Beast. If you get ubered and there's
people like 50-100 feet away from you, it's all over. Because by the time you run up there,
it's just like, oh everyone just turn around the corner and run away. I'm sorry. You know,
we could use, I don't know what I want to do. Pyro. Saddled him. Going pyro. Best guerrilla
song is absolutely stylo. Either stylo, oh you know what, this is going to sound weird
but I actually like dare. For use of that song. I do know the lyrics of the song but
they're very odd. Oh pyro on pyro fight. That's, you are not real. That's not me. I didn't
just look in a mirror. That wasn't me. Bumping into somebody. Watch your backs. Oh he turned
and just smoked me. I started listening to the guerrillas because well they are a great
band. I'm glad you got to listen to them because they're awesome. My cat right now is just
sitting underneath, literally just sitting underneath my legs. Just rubbing up against
my legs over and over again and I just want to be like cat get out of here but I can't
because he's too cute. Die. Die. How much health do you have? Kill me. Oh we found
him. We got a winner. We got a winner. Come here. Come here. Watch out. No. No. Stay alive.
I need, I'm going to run out of ammo. Oh shoot me. Shoot me. Shoot me. Oh that would have
been a crit. Get him. Oh my god. What just happened? Somebody look at the, look what
just happened. What just even happened right there guys? I, what did I reflect? I tried
to put the heavy that was on fire. What even just happened? That was very very odd. Maybe
I reflected a, I'm so confused. Oh let me like put this heavy out and hear like the
crit noise and then kill somebody. Like what? So if that was you that I just killed I have
no idea how it happened. Whoa. Oh he's a sniper. Damn. Whoa hold on. Stop freaking out here.
Gotcha. Back the car. No. Back the car. Oh my god they're going to win. Oh sup burger.
Sup burger boy. You got to like, are you raging yet? Are you on, oh you're on this. No you're
on the other team. Burger boy why are you not like freaking out right now? No. No. No.
Trying to put people out. Oh man. Nice team Uber. Nice team Uber Ari. Oh here it comes.
Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. I'm upset. I'm going medic. I thought for sure I was going
to time that but he had the direct hit. He got killed by Herp and Dirk. At the same time
they both killed me. Where is grandpa? Did you see my latest vlog talking about that?
Oh my god. Spies everywhere. In my latest vlog I talk about grandpa. Oh my god they're
behind us. No don't die. Just, I'm going to sit down here. No I'm not. Oh god. Oh my
god. I was so concerned about getting shot from behind from people on the cart but I,
oh we won. There we go. I do want to play Grand Theft Auto on a stream. I really do.
It's just the only problem with Grand Theft Auto is it's very poorly optimized on the
PC so it can be very difficult to even record that game. So it's something I would have
to look into trying to make it run at a little bit lower settings maybe because that game
takes almost like 5,000% like CPU when you try and play it on like good settings. Now
this will be the last round in this server and we're going to go somewhere else. Oh look
at you. You match. Don't you just look so beautiful. Alright here we go. Ship bank.
Oh look my spray. My spray's cold. Who wants this? Who's getting this? I don't know yet.
You're all good players. I don't know who's going to get it. I guess the person that I
do it to is the person that's going to get it. So be on the lookout. No trades. Not right
now. Look at what you guys are doing. And why is everybody pink? Everybody's like, we're
about to go like driving Miss Daisy. And do it. Demo spam everywhere. What is happening?
Oh my god. Am I excited for Borderlands 2? Yeah I guess. Borderlands 1 I was, I had a
good time with it. But I don't know. You have to really play that game with other people.
You can't really play that game alone. It's too, it's just not my type of game to play
by myself. But I would probably play it with other people for sure and make videos. Absolutely.
Is there a spy for sure? Like look at this crowd of people. There's got to be a spy stuck
somewhere in here. Oh my god where are you? I need to heal you. I just saw him. Come here.
Come here. Come here. Oh. Hey at least I did that right? At least I said, at least I avenged
you. Oh Ari are you ready? Boom. Crits everywhere. Probably should have saved that but you know,
oh my god. No, no. Get out of here. Oh I backed up right into a knife. Right into a knife.
I'm going to spell out what I want to say but I'm not going to say it. S-H-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-T.
And then as many exclamation points you can put on the end of that sentence. That's how
I feel right now. I got you. I got you. Put that away. Let me heal you. Final push. Oh
wouldn't it be great to be on defense right now with a critscreek as a demo man and kill
every single person standing right here. My goodness. I think we're going to get it. Let's
try and get these people to stay and heal. That's one way. Alright nice job guys. Crit
needles. Oh my god. They just respawned. Oh my god. You want to talk about a way to burn
out a hard drive? A graphics card? Oh my god. Speaking of that, let me make sure I'm not
going to explode here. I say this every time. No I'm good. We're good to go. Alright changing
servers one more time. Disconnect. Browse servers. Refresh. Favorite classes engineer
then probably huntsman sniper. I don't know. I change it. My mind changes on a daily basis
so it's hard to say what my favorite class is. Let's go to a... We can always go to good
old gravel pit. Gravel pit for sure. Play a couple more rounds on here. There's the
IP. Oh there's decals. Maybe it's going to be cool looking. Maybe. Maybe. The reason
why I don't accept trade requests during streams is because I like to keep the action as high
as I can keep it. I'm sure people don't want to... Oh I'm going to trade. What am I going
to get? Let's do some trading. I guess maybe that could be entertaining to some people
but I like to keep the action flowing. I'll go blue this time. And I'm going to play with
my revolver. My spicycle. I just got this. I might as well use these things. Totally
strange brain. I don't have a strange sapper. Too bad. Too bad. Medic! Doctor! Medic! Doctor!
Doctor! Alright that's enough of that. Wait a second. I thought I was waiting for set
up time. Apparently there's no... Okay. It's just happening. Oh I'm looking at the chat
right now. I'm not even looking at my screen. I just tried to give it. That's weird. Okay
so the chat just screwed up. Can anyone see what I just wrote by the way? Can you guys
see the IP? Because apparently it's Twitch. What are you saying Burger Boy? Oh Burger
Boy. Blue's capture. I'm so confused right now. I think I'm playing. I don't know why
I think I'm red. I'm looking at the chat. Oh my goodness. Pull out the dead burger.
I don't have it. I do have it. Hey I'm a scout. Don't shoot me. Oh no. Oh god. Oh god. Oh
god. Run. Oh no. Please. Oh. So did you guys hear my idea for a spy video? I think I said
it last stream. Oh my god. Oh my god. That is... That is a... If you've never seen that
spray before that is Burger Boy spray. And he is a disgusting human being. God dang it.
I'm in trouble. Hey. I'll just go this way then. Instant respawn. My goodness. I think
we're about to win. Alright let's get like a new round started so I'm not so confused.
I don't want to be confused. I don't want to fall asleep cause I... That's two songs
combined in one. I'll miss you babe. And I don't want to miss a thing. Cause even when
I... Oh my god. Come on. My hands are in my face right now. I really thought I was going
to get that stair step. I really thought I was going to get it. And it didn't happen.
And I crouched in everything. I did. I crouched. I did crouch. Oh you're going to taunt? Are
you ready to get head shot? He's going to get away. Oh. Just running right into people
again. Oh my god. I'm not supposed to do this. I'm just going to be like the tank. Yeah heal
me. Spy's not working right now. I'm not playing spy anymore. When I... A lot of you guys know
this. I've said this before. Playing spy on a live stream is like pulling teeth out of
my brain. Like when I play spy I need 100% concentration. And if I don't have that it's
like I am essentially regressed to being like 9 years old. Oh dat live com. Oh my goodness.
Did they even have... Okay that didn't hit anybody. Oh my god. Bottle. Attack of the
bottle. Oh. Kroba. Kroba is my best friend on this team. Because his name is Kroba. And
I can say it. Walking lord. You want to go bottle? You want to go with the bottle? He's
gone. He's gone. Don't worry we got it. We got it. We're good. Where is it? Is there
something up there? There's nothing up here. Except this one dude. Oh. I'm like a hippie.
Rocket. Woohoo. Flying demo man. Here we go. Boink. Oh yeah. You know I'm going to take
this off. I'm going to put on the weed booties. And the frying pan. We're going to go sticky
tank. Sticky tank. Sticky tank. Worst item in the game? Oolipool caper. In my opinion.
I do not like that thing. I think it's just a dumb weapon. I don't know. I never use it.
And I think it's just a suicide weapon in my opinion. Which there's not something terribly
wrong with that. I build your uber for you. Look. Oh I missed the high five. I'm sorry.
Alright. Ready. Place your bets. How many people are going to watch the stream right
now and see what I'm doing and just not open this door? I bet every single person is not
here right now. Except for this one dude who might die. No. Oh I just waited one more second.
Sticky tank. They're all going. Hey. Get over here. Oh he's not dead. Oh for the love of
goodness gracious. Oh my god. Get rid of this guy. Blowing us all around like pot pockets.
That analogy did not make very much sense. Now did it? I wonder what that looked like
on his screen. That must have been so funny. He must have saw that. What? What? Oh he's
up there. Oh my god dude. Oh that was so funny. Defend the point. Oh another lucky crit. I'm
sorry about that. I backed into another knife. Gosh darn it. With a capital D. Is the chat
slow for anybody? I can't see anything. There we go. Absa-positive elutely my friend. Towering
pillar of hats. Two dudes with it. Except I'm not going to have it for very long. Oh
my god you are a spy. He's still alive. How many does it take? I do play in windowed mode.
I have to. Just stream it. How much health does he have? He must have a bunch of heads.
I don't trust you. I don't trust you you snake. Oh don't you back up into that. I can't believe
I didn't hit him. I am so shocked and appalled. Oh my god. There he is. Why? I thought we
got rid of him. I thought somebody killed him. How many spies are on that team? One
two three four three. Yeah I'm not doing too well either so don't worry. I'm on that guy's
head. I'm scared. If I was standing that would have been so cool. Of course I put the crit
down right in front of my face. Is that guy still up here? I think he is. Oh yeah he is.
I found him. Alright no more demo man. Not doing hot with him. Let's go back to Pyro.
Do reserve shooter. Come here let me put you out. Engineer. Dude I'm just the designated
putter router people of person. God let me reload. Good good good. Oh god crit screak.
I don't know if you want to give it to me. Might be a total failure. Oh my god how-
He's still up there. Oh get rid of him. Oh no. How are you still alive? I need more bullets
in this damn thing. What's my opinion on the royal wedding? That's cool I guess. People
getting married. It's whales right? Prince I think I could be totally wrong. Boo don't
be mad at me if I don't know that answer. Of course if you don't know Boo, BooMan61 is
a Eastman. No that's a little bit of a- I'm trying to think of the word. Trivia. I'm sure
everyone knows that anyways. Oh jeez. That guy did a double jump. Oh yeah. Let me get
stuck on the wall. Lagging very badly. I'm sorry. I apologize for the lag dude. I'm sorry.
Let's go this way. Yeah it's true. Oh come on. I have new items. What? I haven't died
yet. I got a feeling that there's a lot of people trying to- What even killed him on
the century? Mini century. It wasn't just a century it was a gosh dang mini century.
Oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy. Oh no no. Oh come on kill everybody. Oh at least I got two
or three people. Brass beast. Two and two on this guy. I haven't seen this guy in a
little while. This guy las. The chat is not loading for me so if you- What the hell? What
the- Well that's one way to die. Yeah the chat is not loading. What the hell is going
on here? Chat bastard. Cat. Stop yelp cat. Do I speak English? It depends on if I'm playing
a game and talking. At that point probably not. Probably speaking some other language
and nobody knows. I don't know how I didn't hit him in the first one. Will you be quiet
cat? You're messing with my feng shui. Or is that spy? Oh die. Oh god there's people
everywhere. Oh right into- Walked right into him. Favorite movie is probably- Now that
is a tough question because then you have to talk about The Dark Knight, Memento, Ghostbusters.
I cannot pick a favorite movie. No way. Even if I tried. Even if I really wanted to tell
you. Get him in the air. This guy's getting unusual. He means business. Oh let's go. Let's
rock out. I don't even care anymore. I'm just running into like an idiot. Fight Club is
also an amazing one. Ghostbusters. You never seen Ghostbusters before? If you've never
seen Ghostbusters, go. Go. Go do it right now. Go. Go to Netflix dot- I mean isn't even
on Netflix? I don't even know. Eight damage. Hitting me. There you go. Oh if I had a shot.
If I had a damn shot. There's how you shoot somebody in the face. How come I didn't hit
anybody? I didn't get a crit with that? Actually maybe I did. Probably just didn't show up.
Two minutes left. Hello spy. You happen to be in the base. Red spy in the base. Blue
spy in the base. Actually. Make sure no Rapscallions are coming up behind us. Damn it. What? How
did that not hit that dude? Just barely killed him. No. Stay away from my medic. I'm trying
to keep him away from you. No. I'm going to have to catch him off guard. For sure. Oh
he was just- Oh my goodness. How is he not going to die from that? I was going to say.
Oh get up in the air again. I'm sorry. I can't protect you. No. Leave my spedic alone. Watch
yourself. I don't have any air blast left. Retreat. Retreat. Crit to the face. I think
we're going to get it guys. See if any craziness happens at the very end. Oh don't jump. Probably
be a good idea to- Oh my god. That guy came out of nowhere. Might as well sit on the point
and just do this. And just air blast anyone that tries to jump up here. Nice game guys.
Oh. Alright. So I think I'm going to transition now to play some Bloons Tower defense. I'm
going to play until I die. Well hopefully I do. I'm going to go one more life. So if
I- Next time I die. My last life. I've been streaming TF2 for about an hour and ten minutes.
Just about an hour. A full sixty minutes. Yeah Bloons is fun man. Ten hour games by
play. Is Bloons 5 out? Can I play that? I've never had Bloons from my iPhone. I've got
to do that. My god. Alright so if you want to keep playing Team Fortress the only way
it's going to happen is if there's like nine medics on me. You know what? Let's do it.
Let's do it. Everyone on blue go medic. We'll see how long this lasts. If you are on blue
just go medic. And just octo heavy me. I wonder how long I will stay alive. This is the last
life. Here we go. Oh my god. Oh this is an immediately rigged fight. Is it even like
possible to die? I don't even think it's possible to die. Oh my god. Oh my god. Unless I get
backstabbed. There's no way I'm going to die. It just hurts to laugh. Oh what a bunch of
nonsense. Oh my- No don't kill my medics I need them. Oh no we lost quite a few. Oh no.
Oh I'm going to like pass out man. I just like laughed too hard. Oh my face hurts. We really-
No there's no way this is going to work. There's no way this is going to work. If this actually
works no way. No my battalion. I'm going to get backstabbed. It's going to end it. The
backstab's going to end it all. No don't kill me. Oh my god they're all going spy. They are
all going spy. Everybody went spy. No no no no no. Oh well you did it and I think we won.
Did we win? Did we just win the game right there? Oh come on we gotta win. We gotta win.
I'm going again. All right this is it. This is it. Is it possible? Is it possible? I thought
we were going to do it in one life. That would have been ridiculous. That would have just been
like a joke. Such a total nonsense. Careful for spies. There's a spy back here somewhere.
Look at all those stickies. That's all right. I am octo- Oh that's it. That's it. I'm dead.
I said it was going to be one life. Turn it into two and third time's a charm baby. Let's do it
one more time. After this I'm going to play one round of bloons. This is it. This is the real-
This is it. This is really it. If I die right here I am rage quitting. Careful. I'm not supposed to
keep my back turned. There's definitely somebody's hiding in this room. This is chaos. This is
absolute total chaos. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Jump down. All the medics
jump down. Watch out for the spy medic. This is spy medic. Oh my god he's killing everyone.
Oh my god. He's killing. Oh my god they were all spies. Oh my god how many people.
How many of those medics were actually spies is the real question. All right that's uh that's
going to be it. Oh I didn't get it in three. Oh meow yourself. All right guys. Oh my goodness. My
throat hurts from just like cackling for the last 10 minutes. This time because I'm going to give
this a little bit of time. I want to really get a tactic down because usually I end the stream
with this and I'm probably going to end the stream with this as well but I want to get a tactic down.
A real tactic. So let's see. So the the actual tactic is you're supposed to do it's- somebody
gave me a tactic before and they said you have to do- you have to raise your right leg and then
raise your left leg but you don't raise the calf. Like that. Like that. Like that. Oh my god come on.
This is the first time I've ever stepped more than two steps in this game. So the goal tonight guys
is- what was that? The goal tonight is 50 meters. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna get to 50. You don't
believe me? Just watch. 50 meters right now. Once I get to 50 I can end the stream. 50 meters. Come
on. Come on. Slug your way over there you bastard. 50 meters. We're doing it. I'm doing it. I don't
care if it takes me till eight in the morning. I'm doing 50 meters or at least 40. We'll say 40.
At least 40 meters or I have- oh my god. I'm okay. We're good. We're good. Gotta get to at least 40.
Here we go baby. Come on. We're doing the niche. We're doing the niche stride. We're doing the knee
slug. Imagine how bad that would hurt. Can you imagine how awful that would hurt? I seem to be
stuck here. I'm stuck. Oh my god. There we go. What you- there we go. There we go. Come on. Keep- stay
with it. Stay with it now. Gotta get to 30 or 40. Oh my god. This is the best I've ever done. All right.
All right. Slow down. Slow down a little. Slow down a little. We're gonna hit 30. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Slug. Slug. Slug. Slug. Slug. Slug. Slug. Oh dude.
Oh when I say 40, when I said 30 or 40. Let's try and get it again. Oh god damn it. I'm so mad right
now. I can't believe it. I can't believe it. I am so, so mad right now. Slug. Slug. Slug. Slug. Slug.
I'm gonna get to 40 with the slug. Just you see. So now that we got a little slug going here,
let's talk about a story. So one time there was a slug named Jerma and the slug was- I can't even
talk because I'm like balancing on one foot. All right. Transition here. No. All right. 30 plus 10
is 40. I did it. I just gotta get down. I gotta get down on like the ground. I gotta have this like-
I gotta get- I had it down the first time and you know what? I screwed it all up. 30 plus 10 is 40.
I did it. There we go. There we go. Nice workout I'm doing here, huh? Slug. Slug. Slug. Slug. Slug.
Slug. Slug. All right. We're at 10. I've made it to a combined- a combined 50 meters. Can I make it
to 40 doing this? I don't think it's gonna happen. I really don't think it's gonna happen. Oh don't
lose it. All right. 30 plus 10 plus 13 is more than 50. I did it. I made it.
Do-do-do-do-do. Do-do-do-do-do. Apparently I can walk up sideways. There we go. Just gotta keep this
rhythm. I'm gonna keep the rhythm. Boom. Do-do-do-do. Slug. Slug. We're gonna slug. Slug. Everybody's
gotta slug. We're gonna slug. Slug. Every day. You gotta slug till it's told till the end of May.
You gotta slug. Slug. The music helps. The music helps. The music helps.
Why did I stop singing? The music helped. Let's do it again. This is the last time. Here we go.
Do-do-do-do-do. Slug. We gotta slug here. I've never seen such a slug in my entire life.
When you slug, you gotta slug. When you go, you go. You gotta get on the track and be
super slow. You got it. The music. The music. Never, never don't slug. Never stop slugging
till you get to the end of town. Oh, I think that was a combined over 100 meters. Well, there we go.
Well, that's gonna be it. I've drained all my energy with this co-op. At least I got 30 meters.
I said 30 or 40 in one try. Actually, I said 40 or 50, but I'm gonna change my words.
I'm gonna be like a politician and say, well, I actually said 30 or 40. But yeah, that was fun.
That was fun. So everybody, thank you so much for coming. This is the end of the stream.
I need to go drink some tea. My throat is a little dry and itchy. But anyways, guys,
thank you so, so much for coming. All you guys that stuck around means a lot. You guys rock.
Stay tuned. I'm gonna hope this will all be uploaded to YouTube. At least this part.
I'll make sure to get the TF2 and at least the co-op part uploaded to YouTube.
Be on the lookout for that. Probably tomorrow. Tomorrow in the afternoon, I would assume.
But the chat, I cannot. The chat just died for me right at the end here. So I'm sorry if I can't
see anything that you guys are saying. But thank you so much, guys. And I'll catch you guys all
later. Take care, everybody.