Welcome to the fucking real meat and potatoes of this one. This is Hivemind. So how this works,
this was made by somebody in this community. Did they put their, uh, did they put their, oh I gotta,
I gotta refresh the page. They were gonna put their, the social media down there. Did they?
But anyways, uh, it's, there's so many, yeah, that's how many tabs I had open.
Hivemind is family feud in a browser. This is genius. It's hivemind.fyi. I am going to host a
game and here's how this is going to work. I'm going to send you a link to the chat and we're,
we, this is a test. We're going to see if we can have an absolute shitload of people use this.
The site might just explode. Uh, we don't know. But we've, it's been scaled up and I'm going to
give you a link. You click the link. You just, all you have to do is click the link. You don't have
to do anything else. And I am going, you're going to get a series of questions on, well,
I'll give you an example. So you're going to get two questions a round. There's five rounds.
It's going to say, hey, like, uh, name something that, uh, you put on your head.
And one word answers, guys, because it's going to take the top six answers that people said,
the top eight, and I'm going to have to guess what you guys did. Over the course of five rounds,
there's a lightning round at the end. The second question is for the lightning round. By the way,
um, because there's so many people doing this, don't worry. It's not like it's going to be like,
uh, name something that flies. Dick ass, penis, dick, dick. Like it's, and you're not going to
show up on stream. I just want to make that clear. Uh, it has to be like potentially thousands of
you have to say the exact same thing. So it doesn't matter leaking the lobby. It doesn't matter
because you're just going to click on the link anyways. Let's see if this works. Let's try this
out. Derma, what Derma, why did you say that? Why did you say that shit? Why did you say that shit?
What? That doesn't matter. Here we go. You ready? I'm going to give you a link. I'm going to host a
game. Here we'll read it. Hi, mine is a game where you try to guess how a group of people would
answer a question. When a game starts, there will be a link that you can share with your friends.
You'll then be shown a series of questions and you will have to guess your friend's top answers to
earn points. Pretty sick. So I don't know what you guys are writing, obviously. Let's see how this
works. Hosting a game now. Join the game here. And if you'll take a look, you'll see the, it'll,
it'll show how many people are actually here. Let's actually copy this so you guys can actually go
here. Let's see what happens. Down here it says how many people are actually connected. Let's do
this. I'm going to start the game in a minute. 1200 people. 1300. This is, this is an insane
experiment by the way. I can't wait to see how this plays out. That link is this lobby.
Let's see if it crashes. I am going to cap this at, I'm just going to go eventually here. I'm
just going to click the button. So if you want to play, get in there. Close out of all the tabs.
No, I like living dangerously. Okay. I'm going to do it. There's 4100 people that want to play.
I'm ready to start the game. Oh, hold on. All right. You get five seconds. Wait, why are people
leaving? Hey, don't leave. Hey, why are you leaving? Don't leave. Wait, everybody's clicked off.
Everybody left. Okay, here we go. You're about to play five standard rounds. In each round,
you have 30 seconds for the hive line to be surveyed. Afterwards, you get a chance to guess the
tops, the top eight answers. Game starts in five seconds. You get 30 seconds to answer. Make it
simple. No sentences, one word, lowercase. Name a bad job for someone who is accident prone.
You have 25 seconds to answer. Sight broke. Kill it. Oh no. Dead link. Wait, let's see. Hold on.
Did it work? People in game refresh. Wait, I refresh? No, it's loading. It's loading. It's
loading. Hold on. I'm not going to touch anything. Here we go. Name a bad job for someone who is
accident prone. It's trying. Lowercase only. Wait, did I get it? Okay, wait. Name a bad
job for someone who is accident prone. A waiter. You killed it. You're getting an error message.
Oh wait, let me open up Discord and see if the dev is saying anything. Did I get it? No. This
was the stress test, by the way. He was like, you know what? Let's just dump a shitload of people
on here and see if this works. All right, hold on. Where's my Discord? Where's my Discord? Where's
my Discord? Where's my Discord? Hurry! Hold on. Okay, tell people to refresh if you're in here.
Refresh if you're in here. Okay, let me try waiter again. I'm the dev. What's up? No, you're not. I'm
talking to the dev over here. Maybe we should try again? Should I refresh the page? You couldn't
even answer? Oh, okay. All right. All right, let me start a new game. I'm going to cap it at a thousand
people, by the way. Wait, it's loading. Do the bar. Oh shit, that doesn't look good. Application error.
Check your logs. Communicating with hivemind. Applicat- Okay, I think we broke it. Hey, what
about that glungus test? Go back, it worked. Did I- Wait, did I do it? Too many people went on.
Too many people. All right, hold on. Let me do some communication in here. All right, I'm going to
have an idea. Here's my idea. You ready for my idea? I got 83 points? No, I didn't. This is- I'm
going to- This is a new link. I'm going to do a new link. It's working? I don't think it is. I'm stuck
here. What the fuck? Stay on. Uh, I'm kind of stuck here. I got 83 points? Uh-oh. I think- I
think we might have to- We might have to pivot to Chubby Bunny. New game. Let's try it again.
You know what? Let's not even link this shit. Like, there's probably like- I think 11,000 people
that are here. Probably 8,000 of you. This is- That's too much work. You'd be like, oh,
no. Never mind. I don't want it. I don't care. So, we're going to- We're going to- We're going to
cap it to 1,000. Let's see if it works. I'm capping it at 1,000. Let's see- Let's try that.
Okay, cap it now. Here we go. You have 30 seconds. Let's see if it works. Let's try it again.
Name something you do in front of a mirror. And this- By the way, the second question that
you're answering is for the lightning round at the end. I can't see it. Oh, it crashed. More data.
Give us more- Give us more data on how much people can connect. I think it's- I think it's
working. I think it's just slow. Okay, let's see what happens. Does it load? Let's see. It worked?
Name something you do in front of a mirror. I saw what somebody wrote and I can't- I can't even
fucking say what it was. Why would you do that? Why would you do that in front of a mirror?
You guys are disgusting. Ah, shit! All right. All right, we'll try it one more time. We'll
try it one more time. We're going to try it one more time. This time, I'm going to cap it at
two- at 500 people. We'll try it again. Here we go. Ready? Refresh. Refresh. Oh, wait, wait,
wait, wait, hold on. I'm pushing- I'm pushing some changes. It's probably going to be working
in five minutes. Hold on. It doesn't cap, by the way. Oh, okay. All right. Dev's pushing changes
right now. Refresh it now. Refresh, refresh, refresh. All right, all right, I'm going.
Okay, name something you do in front of a mirror. Flex. Flex in front of a mirror. It's thinking.
It's thinking. Hold on. Did I get it? Maybe I should play Chubby Bunny in between rounds.
Oh, nope. Hold on. Just don't exit. I'm not going anywhere. Bingo! It works! 175 people said flex.
I got it. All right. Name something you do in front of a mirror. I don't want to write
Zerk off, okay? You know the real one. Name something you do in front of a mirror.
Sing? People like sing into the mirror, don't they? Maybe? Do you sing in front of a mirror?
Do you cry in the mirror? Did that go through? Okay, here we go. Now, there we go. The loading
bar. I already guessed that. Oh, no, that was strike. I got it wrong. Okay, same thing. Something
to do in front of the mirror. Top eight answers. Some of these are just going to be so fucking
specific. Something you do in front of a mirror. Oh, we got to get the music back on. All right,
let's go. All right, what do you do in front of a mirror? Brush. Brush teeth. Make sure your answers
are simple as fuck, by the way. Don't write like, well, I get up in the morning and I make a coffee.
No, just one or two words. Lowercase. You said one word. Yeah, well, that's what I mean. Like,
make it simple. Like, if it's brush your teeth, it's brush teeth, not brush your teeth. I'm winning.
What's underneath flex? Okay, name something you do in front of a mirror. Flex. Brush teeth.
I don't want to write it, but I feel like you all said it. Flex. Brush teeth. Pop zits? Pop zits.
People like lean in and they, yes, they do. What do you mean what's wrong with you? Who does,
you do that. I know you do. He did that an hour ago. You still have the mark there.
Nope. Strike two. You guys don't like, yes, you fucking do. Uh, hair. Comb. Comb hair. You do,
clearly. It works. It actually, I mean, it's a little, it chugs along a little bit. It works.
Okay, I got it wrong. Okay, top answers were flex, pose, cry, brush teeth, masturbate, smile,
shave, and dance. Who zirks off into the mirror? Just answer the fucking question already and let's
memeify this. How many times have I leaned over and did that voice? How many times have I leaned
forward and said something? All right, what is it? Name something you do multiple times a day.
I know, okay, I'm gonna write it. I'm gonna write it. By the way, fucking gross. Let me refresh.
Holy shit, there's 8,200 people connected to this goddamn thing. I'm surprised it's still standing.
The dev says I'm making rapid changes right now. Performance will improve soon. I mean, it's, it's,
I'm surprised this works. All right, come on, come on, come on. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Did you guys answer? So many people are joining. Are you, did you answer, everybody answering?
Close my, it has nothing to do with my tabs. Oh, he said refresh. Okay, hold on. Come on,
Gwen. It's working. Yeah, this dev is a fucking superhero. 10,000 people connecting to this
thing at the same time and this guy's, this guy's got, this guy's got it on. All right, here we go.
Something you do multiple times a day. I have to write it. I have to. I have to write it. I don't
do that, but I have to write that. I don't want this on my screen for this long. Get it off.
All right, here we go. 500 of you fucking degenerates. I have to, it's gonna be at number
two. I got it. Okay, that's two. Names like you do multiple times a day. Um, but I don't want to
write the real one. You know what I mean? Yeah, like pee. Pee? Are you pee like, what, 10 times a
day? 15 times a day? Eat. Yeah, you do eat. Come on, give me the loading bar. Come on,
give me the loading bar. Drink more water. What do you mean? That's fucked. Stop getting answers from
chat. I'm not. This is my own, my own doing. I think we're bottlenecked. Oh, here we go.
I got zero strikes. There it is. All right, what else? I won't look over here. I promise.
Something you do multiple times a day. Eat. Everybody eats. You eat like fucking four times
a day. Three times a day. Two times a day. How, people eat all, people eat all kinds of different
times. Give me number three. There it is. Bam. Oh, I'm gonna, you guys are, it's over. I'm gonna win.
Okay, pee. 100 of you said pee. I think you do multiple times a day. Masturbate, zerk off,
jerk off. I didn't write that one though, but I'm not going to. I don't care if I get it wrong.
Um, sleep? Some people nap, right? Some people sleep. Some people, they go to sleep.
They take naps. Come on. 20 of you said that. Always sleep. Something you do multiple times a day.
Sneeze. Eat. Drink. Yeah, you drink. That doesn't matter what it is. Drink. Fuck. Two strikes?
Masturbate, zerk off. Don't be mad that I did that, but it's probably number five. Is that okay? I
can't write that. Can I? No, I can. I can. I can. I think I can. Can I write that? Okay, so
something you do multiple times a day. You guys are masturbating, jerking off, zerking off, eating
and peeing. Some of you guys need to pick up a book instead of reading. Uh, reading! Read. No,
that's not it. Um, internet. Computer. Use computer. Use computer. Make it simple. Remember,
it's gotta be simple. Use the computer. You're on it right now. You're doing it right now. You're
on the computer right now. Of course you use it multiple times a day. Come on. This is relaxing
fucking music. Oh shit. Come on. Pull me back in. Pull me back. No, what was it? Did anybody get
a screenshot? Name an Olympic sport you'd watch more often if it were played in the nude.
What was it? Cry, poop, breathe and shit? Cry, poop and breathe. Zer- zerking off was one of them.
Okay, name an Olympic sport you'd watch more often if it were played in the nude.
Oh, I don't know. Archery? Baseball? Uh, Mario Kart. Not Mario Kart. Um, hurdles?
What? I got them all? It was hurdles? I think it just gave you the wrong screen the dev said. Oh,
name the worst place for a first date. That's so funny. Worst place for a first date. Um,
McDonald's or something. I don't know. You have five seconds. I'm gonna say McDonald's.
McDonald's is a shitty place for a date. It's a great place to get food, but it's a terrible
place. It's a terrible place. Oh shit. Did it work? Oh, we are killing this website. Oh, wait,
wait, wait. We're good. I think we're good. 87 fucking hundred people connected. What's the
song name? Song name is, uh, We Fit, uh, Yoga. We Fit Music Yoga. All right, hold on. I think
it's gone. It's not the worst. You just get food and talk. I don't know, but I feel like a first
date. I'm not going to, I'm not going to bring that up. I mean, if my date wants to bring that
up and says, Hey, let's go to McDonald's. I'm going to say, Oh, all right. Okay. Well, okay.
Fine. But I'm not going to say, Hey, yo, you want to go to McDonald's for a date? I would take you
to McDonald's. I would go to McDonald's. I'd have you pick me up and we can go to McDonald's,
but I'm not going to make that my idea. Give this a counter. Oh, here we go. All right. What
happened to the music? What's the music back on, dude? Star Fox 64. That's a fucking POG moment.
All right. Worst place for a first date. Do I need to write? Okay. I spelled it. Do I have
to spell it right? McDonald's. Number one. I knew it. Okay. McDonald's is number one. Worst
place for a first date. Uh, people go ice skating. You go to a restaurant. Um, go to a movie. What
are some bad ones? Okay. You go to a movie. You go ice skating. You go to a movie theater. You go
to the movies. You go ice skating. You go ice skating again. You go to ice skating a third time.
Uh, you go to a restaurant. You go to get the, you get sushi. Dude, that sushi was awesome.
Burger King. Show me Burger King. Wrong. Wendy's. Show me Wendy's. Funeral. Funeral? How about a
funeral? Fuck. Not Wendy's either. Okay. Only McDonald's. At a funeral. Show me a funeral.
Ooh, Mario 3D World. The worst game. No, wait. Sorry. That's wrong. Um, what's the other one?
The 2D one. Worst place for a first date. McDonald's was wrong. Hell. The sewer. Las Vegas.
That's fucking inaccurate. Jerma's house. Jerma's house. Bathroom and Switch. What's the 2D one that
I don't like? Hell. Twitch. Imagine going on a date to a Twitch channel. You don't bring dates here.
Don't say, hey, I'm going to open up on my phone. You open it on your phone and we'll watch them
together. And then you, then you laugh at a joke I make and what if they don't think it's funny?
No, you got to do something easy. If you're going to do a Twitch stream, it's got to be
like a no commentary Hearthstone stream or something. Or like a zero guy talking in the
corner. It's like, uh, checkers or something. All right, let's keep going. I think we're about to
load up. It looks like it's all right. We good? Go to Juggles the Great. I took a girl to McDonald's
on a first date. That's all right. That's fine. My boyfriend and I watched Twitch streams as a date.
Yeah, you do now, but you didn't meet your boyfriend and say, hey, it's the first time
we've ever talked. It's time for us to be in the same room on our iPads and watch German.
Does that happen? Oh, here we go. Name something that moves very slowly.
Something that moves very slowly. Wait, what? Wait, why am I? I'm like, I'm a, I'm a viewer now.
Who's, wait, what happened? I'm on the wrong screen. Who is in control? Who's getting the,
who's getting the actual game? Got them all. I'm the host now. This is so funny. Oh, hold on.
The servers are thrashing a bit. Cloud Platform isn't releasing the changes because so many
people are playing. It's breaking because it waits for you to see the page, but the timer
still counts down. It's a bug. It's working on it. I have 60 seconds. Name the first item you grab
when having to evacuate your house. Oh, money. Money. Okay. Lightning round. Move. Name a famous
wizard. Harry. I'm going against the clock here. Going against the clock. Harry. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Name something that flies. A plane. Name an animal with only three letters in its name. Dog.
Name a reason you might not get hired after a job interview.
Um, naked. Naked. You're naked. Name something that gets tangled. Hair. Did I get it?
Thanks for playing. Okay. Let's see. Name something you do in front of a mirror.
You guessed flex. You guessed sing. The top answer is to flex, masturbate, pose, smile, cry, shave,
brush teeth, and dance. Name an Olympic sport you'd watch more often if it played in the nude.
You guessed hurdles. Name something that can be spoiled. We got locked out on this one. Name
something you do multiple times a day. I got these pretty much right. Use computer. Breathe, poop,
shirk off, cry, pee, eating, zerk off, and masturbate. Name the worst place for a first date.
Got them all wrong. Name something that moves very slowly. I was the one doing the question.
Name something that gets tangled. You said hair. I'll pay answers for that. Where hair,
headphones. Why? Why? You. 34 of you. You psychos. Earbuds, wires, cables, rope. Okay. Name an
animal with only three letters in its name. Cat, dog, rat, bat, ant, cow, pig, ass. Name something
that flies. A fly, a bird, a plane, a seagull. Time. Flies. Germa. Bat. Fly. Okay. I like time.
I like that answer. Name a reason you might not get hired after a job interview.
You guessed naked. Messed. You're ugly. Name the first item you grab when having to evacuate your
house. 51 of you said your penis. He's going to bring the site down for a few minutes.
I'm going to do Chubby Bunny while he does a few bug fixes. We're going to do this again in
about 10 minutes. Give me a minute while I prepare for Chubby Bunny. Right back. God damn it. I hate
this. I hate every single second of this next 10 minutes of this stream. Right back. Okay. Here we
go. Those of you that have no idea what's going to happen right now. I did a stupid joke. I did
a dumb joke during a... Hold on. Turn that off. I made a joke during a stream like three or four
weeks ago. Didn't think I was going to have to do this. I got damaged in a mission in mafia.
And I said if that happened, then I would do Chubby Bunny. And I just didn't think I was ever
going to have to do it. But here we are. By the way, those of you that... I am not going to do
this until I die. No. I'm not... This is going to be very simple here. If you don't know how this
works... Oh, fuck. You take a marshmallow and you don't do this because it's fucking dumb.
It's stupid. Don't do it. It's a stupid thing to do. I'm only going to do enough for the photo.
It's dumb. Don't do this. Do not do this ever in your house. This is not funny. It's stupid.
You don't eat them. You just put marshmallows in your mouth and it's like you're the dentist.
I feel like I could be done right now. I'm not saying it. I'm not saying it. You can't... Oh,
this is what it looked like if I was a fat guy. I can't do more than three. I'll say it, I promise.
Mom, if you're watching, I'm sorry. Chubby Bunny. There you go. Mom, I'm really... My mother's
probably watching the stream going, what the fuck is this kid doing? I didn't raise him like this.
Chubby Bunny. They're coming out. Don't laugh. I feel like... I'll do one more. Chubby Bunny.
Is it? No more. Don't fuck... That's... I fucking hated every second of that. I hated every second
of that. Every second of that sucked. I'm not going to show it to you. That's just... Are you
kidding me? But hold on. I got a funny idea. Quiet. Wait. Oh, we're going to bring in fucking
mad viewers with this shit. What the fuck is it? No. Let's go. It hurts. I mean, it's a little sore,
but hey. Yeah, I'm all right. I just had some work done. I don't even know why I turned on the
stream. I don't know. I felt like I wanted to stream, but that's really bright. Hey,
can one of the mods find out how to turn off my stream? I don't know. I don't know how to do it.
I had all my wisdom teeth pulled out like a couple of minutes ago.
I'm going to play a new Crash Manicoo tomorrow. If anybody wants to see me play that,
I'm playing Crash Manicoo tomorrow. This is what a toddler does when they know they did something
wrong. Did you get in the cookies? That should be an emo. Stanley Kubrick's stare.
Oh, my chest. Oh, that's so stupid. New emote. Jerma Kubrick. Or Jerma in Trouble. Jerma
Toddler. Oh, I'm okay. The server's back up. Let's do this. Okay, let's take this off and
I got to fix my hair. I look like a fucking dickhead. Oh, man. Okay. Okay. Why am I talking like
that? All right. Let's move this back down. Let's try this again. There you go. That Chubby Bunny,
a thing that you should never fucking do because it's stupid. Don't do it. It's dumb. I actually,
like after I got five in there, it was like, okay, I have to stop doing it. Like, I don't want to do
this anymore. Don't do that. Don't try that at home. Seriously. Disclaimer. Don't do that. All right,
here we go. We're going to reload the page and see if it works. Oh, hold on. I'm not going to
address that because I don't want people to do that. I'm not going to address that one. I'm not
going to address this one because I don't want that's Wikipedia's shit. You have devil horns for
hair. All right, let's go. We're doing hive mind. Put the Kingdom Hearts music back on. Oh,
oh, this is DMCA. Yeah, it is. You're right. How about some Halo 2 music? Help YouTube advertisers
by answering questions. No. The ad asked me, I should have showed that. I wish I didn't skip
that immediately. It said, what is your favorite online mattress? It said Casper Purple. There was
a poll list. It's like they can do it. If you don't think they can, if they don't think they're
listening to you talking, you're wrong. Okay, here we go. Shadow of the Hedgehog sounds pretty good.
Okay. This is kind of gross. All right. I look kind of weird. All right, let's refresh the page.
Let's try this a few more times. Streams over in like 30 minutes. Just want to make that really
clear. We're going to do this again. Don't worry. All right, let's open it up. Hive mind. Start a
game and click. Why can I never get it right? It looks like I was just running really fast in like
a cartoon or something. And I stopped really abruptly. All right. Are we ready? Only a thousand
people. There's like 11 K people here. Click on it. If you actually don't, cause then the service
would be fine. I'm starting in three, two, one action. You're about to play five rounds. Go for
it. Game starts in 11 seconds. Name something you should never eat late at night. And you have a
bonus question to ask that. Don't tell me what that one is, because that's a lightning round
question. It was Overwatch. Okay. All right. Something you should never eat late at night.
Let's see if it works. It's pretty smooth. Okay. Something you shouldn't eat late at night. I don't
think you should eat. Um, I don't think you should eat ice cream at night because it's just a lot of
dairy and a lot of sugar. And it really gets in there. Actually, we need the loading bar to make
sure this is working. It is. Okay. Good. It's a lot of sugar. It's a lot of dairy. It like just sits
in you. And when you lie down, it just, I don't know. I don't think so. Good. Told you. There's
at least 72 people in there. All right. I like it. This is king. This is king.
No, it's not. All right. Something you should never eat late at night.
Coffee. What do you want to be up all night? Coffee's probably number one.
Coffee. There we go. Okay. Not number one. What should you not eat late at night?
Beef? A ground beef? Beef? What's coffee? Not number one. Um, what should you not eat late at
night? Eggs? I don't know. Eggs? Something? No. Okay. All right. How about, uh, well, we'll go
with the meme answer because I guarantee at least a hundred of you wrote that. If at least a hundred
people do not write this, I will delete my Twitch channel. All right. There we go. 500. Okay. Name
something you should never eat at night. Sorry. I'm a lip biter. I'm sorry. I looked over at the
marshmallow, like just gross marshmallow puke shit over here. Like it was in my mouth and now
it's making me sick looking at it. Uh, something you shouldn't eat at night. How about a, what if,
I feel like some people may have just written, written food. Don't you feel like that? People
just got lazy and they're like, ah, I guess, I guess food. What should you not eat late at night?
Ass? Ice cream? Coffee? I was supposed to write cigarettes. I swear to God, if you guys,
this is what people do at night. What are you talking about? People like having,
doing sexual stuff at night. What do you mean? What do you mean? No. Something you shouldn't eat
at night. Okay. That's not all right. Uh, cheese, pizza, marshmallows. Um,
name the worst place to fall asleep. Hivemind. That's the name of the game. That's right.
Worst place to fall asleep. Uh, during an earthquake. Well, that's the worst place. Not
the worst thing. Um, worst place to fall asleep. Uh, okay. This is, this is actually pretty smooth
right now. Name the worst place to fall asleep. Uh, I'm just going to write this because I know
that you all are really, really, really funny jokers. Guarantee it's up there. I would be,
I'm such a good host. Okay. I'll do you one more. Let's add the apostrophe and get the
rest of these guys. Right. Thank you. I'll take it. Uh, bad place to fall asleep. Um, I don't know,
in a, when you're in a car, uh, owning a lawn. Um, he's cheating. I'm not cheating. I'm trying
to make sure. Worst place to fall asleep. Bus streaming? No, that's not a place. That's a thing.
That's like an act. All right. Definitely like driving. You don't want to be, you don't want
to fall asleep, but you drive. It's D2. Come on. Come on. What? No way. Fall asleep in a bathtub.
It's not a place. Bathtub. What the fuck? Car, bus, outside, bed, floor, toilet. Worst place
to fall asleep in a bed. Toilet. Why is that so weird to fall asleep in a bed? It doesn't make
any sense. Okay. Name something that you crack or you crack your, I'm not gonna say anything.
Game and watch. Hell yeah. I know one. I know number one. It's going to be number one. Your
knuckles. Wait, I got kicked out. We're back in, put me back in, put me back in, put me back in,
put me back in. All right. Put me back in, back in. Next one. I lost the round. Crack. What? A
crack of fart? Name something that breaks down. This is such like a me song because of all the
noises. I love it. All right. Name something that breaks down. Car breaks down. A boat breaks down.
A bus breaks down. A atom. An atom breaks down. A, let's do truck. We're probably gonna write
truck. All right. That's pretty low. No. Okay. A YouTuber. Computer is another one. I was gonna
say. Computer. Car. Breaks down. I don't know. Marriage. Is that something? Marriage breaks
down. That was wrong. Computer. Why am I still live? Okay. So we had car and mind. The rest were
just different versions of me. Germa. Me. Penis. Eight people. Only eight of you. It'll always be
up there. Name someplace you might be where it would be inappropriate to laugh. Here. I don't
want to give you any ideas. All right. I feel like I'm going to get a bunch of these right.
Okay. Inappropriate to laugh. Germa's stream. Here. This stream. Germa. I'm gonna. I'm gonna
give you. We're gonna do all four or five of them. Easy to game you guys. It is. Oh. Undertale. Yeah.
Here. Here it is. Okay. This stream. I just thought of the. I thought of the Kubrick thing.
Come on. This stream. This stream. I know it is. Louder. All right. Fine. Let's go. No. Okay. And
then I'm gonna put like funeral too. Like some of you guys played this right. The dentist.
Okay. I have to use that one. Can I use that one? That was pretty good.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is that as a Geico commercial, isn't it? That's like a. Oh, you're Geico. Couldn't say like the
comedian dentist, right? That's a Geico commercial, isn't it? It could be. I think it is.
I imagining like the dentist telling a joke and being like, and the guy like,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha. This is bad idea. But if you can say 15%, that's a guy, that's a dumb Geico ad.
I'm using it. It's from your stream. That's my favorite part. No dentist. Okay. Funeral.
Why would you guess dentist? I don't know. Funeral. Oh yeah. That's, that's 794 points.
Like awake. Like just places that you shouldn't be laughing. Awake. Okay. In the bathroom. But
what about the guy in the stall that's watching something on his screen? He's laughing in the
stall. Did I not get it? That is dumb. What do you mean dumb? You guys don't know what awake is?
Oh, I lost. What? How the fuck do you guys don't know what that is?
Guess again. I get four strikes. Okay. Um, this is the free space of the bingo card of this stream.
Oh dude, this is Bayonetta. Never played it. Never going to. Funeral. Jerma's stream. Jerma's house.
Stream. Funeral. You guys spelled it wrong. Funeral. Funeral. What happened?
Does everybody spell it wrong? Funeral. Lightning run. I'm ready. Let's go. I have 60 seconds to
guess five questions correctly. Name an American city that has its own accent. Boston. Name a
Spanish word everybody knows. Uh, hola. Name something you should never be late to. Surgery.
Surgery. Fuck. Name something that comes in pairs. Shoes. Name something you might find at a backyard
birthday party. Come on. Name something that only happens once every few years.
Olympics. Oh, that's four years. Shit. Is that, that still counts. That still counts. Any more?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
I got, I answered the ball, right? Oh, the server's dead. That was working pretty
cleanly that whole time though. Is it Van Gellion? All right. Is it Gellion or Gellion? Somebody
correct me please. Gellion or Gellion? Gellion. It's not Gellion. Okay. And now is it Elon Musk
or is it, is it Elon Musk or Elon Musk? Elon Elon. Elon Musk. It's Elon. So I had it wrong
all the ways. Okay. Come on. I need to know if I, okay. Here we go. Something that you crack. Ass.
You crack ass. Okay. You crack egg. Good. Cocaine. Knuckles. Back. Okay. Can we just like
permanently ban like 200 of you? Name the worst place to fall asleep. Car. Bed. Floor. Bus. Toilet.
Outside. Name something you should never eat late at night. They guessed ice cream. Coffee. Eggs.
Ass. Penis. Dick. Okay. Sure. Name something that breaks down. Germa. Car. Me. Penis. Streamer. Ass.
Mind. Hive. Mind. Pretty good. Pretty good. That one was pretty good. Name some place you might be
where it would be inappropriate to laugh. This stream. My stream. Here. Stream. Germa's house.
And funeral and funeral twice. Something that comes in pairs. Balls. Shoes. Socks. Nuts. Testicles.
Twins. Pants. Boobs. What the f- Not like gloves. Shoes. Balls. I could see it. That's the third one
I was going to say. Name a Spanish word everybody knows. Nobody answered it. Name something that
only happens once every few years. Leap year. Cool. Sex. An eclipse. The election. Germa stream.
What? What are you talking about? I've streamed three days in a row. Your birthday. How's your
birthday come every few years? You remember Rumble? Olympics. Only 46 people said Olympics. Name an
American city that has its own accent. Boston. Thank you. New York. Las Vegas. No. Texas. Penis.
Name something you should never be late to. A stream. This stream. A wedding. A funeral. Germa
stream. An interview. Streaming. Or a date. What did I say? Welcome to Penis USA. What did I say?
Surgery. Mine was way better. You're gonna be late to your own surgery? All right let's do it. We're
gonna do it one more time. We'll do it one more time and I'm gonna go. Ready? One more. There it
is. I'm not gonna link it. I don't want to break the server. It's not there anymore. Can somebody
link me the picture of the cubic face? I kind of want to see it. I keep thinking of like a little
kid. I keep thinking about this face. It's freaking me out. It's driving me fucking crazy.
This is perfect. This is perfect. I have to show this. I have to do this. This is perfect.
Yes I'm sure. The cubic stare is one of Stanley Kubrick's most recognizable directional techniques.
I've added a shot composition where a character stares at the camera with a
and the characters at the peak of their derangement. Okay I'm ready to fly. Let's go.
Oh my god that's so fucking stupid. Name something besides jelly that goes well with peanut butter.
Don't take that one. There's another one? What the fuck is this?
You faceapped me and this is what happened? What? I don't understand. I got back from the
little sloppy. This is an actual photo. I look like what Bilbo Baggins looks like
in the Hobbit movies. No no in the floor of the rings. But wait it's like Bilbo Baggins gross
uncle. That's juggles. Wait oh the site crashed hold on. How do you feel like that fucking guy's
gonna come grab the ring? All right let's go. Name something besides jelly that goes well on it with
peanut butter. Peanut butter fluff. Flug. Fluff. Marshmallow fluff is incredible. It better be
number one. Excuse me? What the fuck are you talking about? Okay um I'm kind of I'm shocked
at the moment. I don't know what to do. Uh uh nope not fluff's not number one. Settle down. Settle
down. They just they don't understand. Um jelly. Jam. A peanut butter and jam sandwich. Peanut
butter chocolate chocolate banana. How do you spell chocolate? Chocolate. Chocolate? Peanut
butter and chocolate. Peanut butter and peanut butter. Peanut butter. Right peanut butter and
Reese's. Reese's peanut butter puffs. All right chocolate peanut butter uh banana. Banana okay
banana. Banana's number one or no? Why is fluff not up there? I'm fucking pissed. Banana. Banana.
Ah banana. There it is. All right peanut butter and banana. Peanut butter and chocolate. Peanut
butter and caramel is a caramel or caramel caramel or caramel fine i'll write it i'll write it and
get number one just so we can get on with it peanut butter and it's better if this better
not be number one it's gonna be number one just write a swear word and you'll get at least one
of them see i just write any like well that's not a well that's a everybody has an ass but you know
what i mean just write like ass dick balls okay let's try that out let's see if this theory works
balls ass dick uh penis right like we did the ones that people actually would do
oh my fucking god oh my god oh my god i hate you guys there's that many people that said that and
there's not not even 200 of you said chocolate not even 200 of you said the word chocolate but you
said that one that word name the best this is specific name the best german 985 joke
oh this is interesting what's the best joke i've ever done oh i get to go too actually oh what
that's the best my favorite video this very thing that's my that's my favorite thing i've ever done
pretty much if you've never seen the video it's called the photos are in just type it into google
youtube doesn't matter just watch that video you'll understand uh that's too bad it broke go to go go
to youtube right now and type in the photos are in you'll get it it's my face watch it that's my
favorite video i've ever made oh we get to go with you we're doing again refreshed it's very
there's a list of about 50 that are really really like neck and neck and neck and neck
it's got to be doverine it better not be doverine name something that people are afraid of what
oh i think that name something people are afraid of i will say those this is a great beta test
with some bug yeah i see i see with some like the kinks worked out of this this is fucking awesome
it already is he's even got a versus mode that he's working on too and remember keep in mind
this is really important to know all of you here this was just this is a project that somebody in
the community made they were like hey uh you talked about like a family feud thing with the
community i'm just gonna make that this is not this is not some website that i like just oh i
just found it oh wow i found hive mind somebody made this here somebody that was here in this
community that's fucking pretty pog clap you know what i mean all right something people are afraid
of bugs everybody's afraid of bugs spider how do we support this i'll show you what's up clowns
bugleberry penis ghosts rats spiders germa 985 name a reason you might not get hired after a job
interview oh we got this one before i already know what this wasn't gonna be i'm just gonna
apparently there are over a hundred questions and he can just put in new ones as he sees fit
he said there's like 400 questions that are not really implemented yet but he can it's yeah it's
crazy it's pretty crazy also keep in mind that this is the uptime on this website with 10 000
people all opening at the same time that's ridiculous i i thought we were just never
going to be able to play it all right here we go name a reason you might not get hired after a job
okay i let's just do the same ones i did before close the stream i need to go home well i'm done
in like probably 10 minutes we get to the end of this end of the stream voice yeah yeah i will call
it after this it's been a fun night uh yeah there it is okay i hate writing this word i find it to
be like just disgusting i hate writing that i hate being saying it or thinking it it's it's just it
disgusts me holy shit okay you chubby bunny before you close no i keep thinking of that
fucking image okay uh you fight like you fought the guy you fought the guy interviewing you
you fight farting oh okay fart if you fart during an interview
i'm trying to think if i was the person interviewing i would just pretend it didn't
happen i don't think it would affect the actual job outcome i think i would just be like fuck that
was probably really awkward for them i'm not going to even say anything it actually might actually
help how i feel about you you know oh fuck he farted in here and he was wicked embarrassed
oh maybe i should give him this job hmm the other people didn't fart and then nobody farted in here
besides them all right they're hired they're i'm gonna hire them okay uh what was the other one
you were naked interviewers don't look at you as humans uh if you're naked okay if you um
i have one strike left oh i forgot about ugly i got it you were too ugly airline check looks
all right ugly all right i only need two more if you're naked if you're ugly if you farted if
you're zirking off if you zirked off if you masturbated something's higher than fart and
zirking off what is it add an ing to it let's see just wrote my name name a reason why you
might not get hired after a job interview germa and oh and penis okay name a wrestler you you'd
like to partner with for a tag team match i'll get these ones a good one funny stuff i know who
i would want to team up with up to you though who do you want to team up with oh shit those are all
right all right come on come on let's go let's go let's go let's go only got one more all right
rest all you want to keep up with uh let's go for it i'm gonna do it a few different ways i'm gonna
do glue man two words glue man one word i'm gonna do uh the egg benjamin franklin come on that's
number one at boy burger boy green screen i cheated captain crunch you're right i'm cheating
that's okay you cheat sometimes you can cheat sometimes not all the time but sometimes uh no
glue man that's still low oh that doesn't look good bad internet i don't have bad internet quick
oh i'm in i'm good it was 321 points oh your ip germa germa germa germa why do you use a vpn
germa why do you have a vpn on on stream germa why do you have a vpn turned on why would you turn a
vpn on you're fucking kidding me you just saw why oh it was worth having it on for a fucking year
it was worth having it on for a full year i feel so validated right now you have no idea
turn that off you're fucking stupid you don't need a vpn why is vpn turned on
let's go name a wrestler you'd like to partner within a tag team match captain crunch uh crunch
aroni massive brain what no captain crunch oh you are you serious dr otker no i don't
people don't know who that is i spelled it wrong no i didn't did i captain cry i spelled it right
what are you talking about captain crunch uh how about i don't know how to spell benjamin
franklin captain crunch captain crunch like that right two-person horse i'm gonna call my mother
tonight like ma ma what the disco diaper 30s milkman penis john cena john cena is not has
nothing to do with this universe oh me hulk hogan hulk hogan over like the 30s milkman over
like whatever i guess that is the sort of wrestler that you would like want to like team up with i
guess all these viewers are post rumble they know that's it that's actually true that's true a lot
of people here probably are post youtube that makes sense that makes sense name something that
has wax oh shit this is this lightning round uh candle name a famous wizard potter famous judge
dread name an animal you would have you would hate to find in your bedroom uh snake a snake
definitely i have a bad job for someone who's accident prone that's construction construction
here we go name something people are afraid of i got it wax name a wrestler you'd like to
part with for a tag team okay glue man germa glue man i guess it's just glue man i mean hulk hogan
cool i would do jackson penis i'll never get away from the penis people name something besides jelly
that goes well with peanut butter skip name a reason you might get hired might not get hired
okay naked ugly penis fart zirkin off zirk off masturbate cool name a famous wizard gandalf harry
merlin dumbledore cbt wizard and penis this you how boring does that have to be every answer is
penis you just type the where you just type penis and doesn't matter what it is something that breaks
down germa me hive mind car penis a famous judge judy good rbg right dread me judge judy judge penis
name a bad job someone who's an accident prone streamer that's not true that's like you get more
viewers if you like break something on stream what are you talking about like if i if i were
to go like like throw this marshmallow thing into the wall back there 5 000 people would show up
that's not an accident this is anger if i like okay if i if i tripped right now and hit my head
on this microphone i'm getting more viewers tomorrow i'm just saying that'll be somebody
posted somewhere okay so uh streaming surgeon yeah that's true construction thank you uh doctor
germa and doctor and pilot yeah name something that has wax candle ear ears bees germa
balls balls wax of course i'm out that's the end of the stream uh i this is a lot of fun
i had a ton of fun this is a lot longer than i thought it was going to be i'll be completely
honest with you uh thanks for watching everybody i mean want some marshmallows don't show that
that's disgusting uh i will see you what's day today is the 20th i'll see you know i'll see you
guys on saturday we'll do saturday sunday or maybe friday saturday check the sus like tomorrow we'll
see either either sat it's gonna be either friday or saturday and i'll see you later thanks for
watching see you soon if you have a good night hope you have a good night too yeah have a good
night thanks take quizzes with me thanks for hanging out with me and let's get the fuck out
of here we're leaving here come the subs thanks for subbing all the subs that came in today let
me see if there were any major big ones i think there were a few i hate missing shit like this
uh actually i'll go through them right now because there were a lot spliceable spleen thanks for five
community subs yes is online five fbi official five destroy dude five super daza five flug boy
ten freddy dread 50 earlier remember that one that was fucking crazy unionize your workplace
five drop shock five i think i caught the other ones we also had two very major donations come in
we had two fifty dollar donations come in back to back well they were like three hours apart but you
know uh five thousand bits from corey can thank you core can for the ridiculous amount of money
it's a huge amount of money no one's ever expected to give me that kind of money i'll take it it's
my birthday today i'm 32 catching up to you yeah it feels kind of weird when you get to be over 30
especially over 35 i'm definitely getting older i can feel myself getting a little older i'm getting
a little bit of crow's feet i'm getting the hairs thinning a little so i'm 35 now when i'm 40 45
that's only five years away from five years away from 40 that seems so odd to say out loud 40 years
old in five years i feel like i'm not ready to be 40 i'm not ready for that but happy birthday
thanks for the 50 you don't don't give you don't have to give me 50 on your birthday
oh shit i want to do this too hold on wait wait wait one sec one sec one sec uh here is if you
want to support i've mined and it's development uh he actually has one of these links he has a cofi
link if you care enough he put this together just he was like hey i made that thing that you talked
about so that's awesome very very cool i look forward to the development of this continuing
there's going to be a versus mode the servers will be and the servers actually stabilized pretty well
we had a few crashes but that's okay that's to be understood got a lot of good potential it sure does
but uh thanks for making it and uh let's see i'm gonna go out here why did i feel like i was
gonna turn the stream on at 144p i don't know why oh yeah and i gotta turn the stream on at 144p
because i said i was gonna do that and let's uh let's let's hey let's go to ludwig in a while
since you're ready to ludwig talked about him on stream today so let's go go say hi to ludwig tell
him and i sent you of course he's gonna know what is he doing what are you doing what are you up to
sorry ludwig is aoc vod review he's reviewing a vod all right let's see what he has to say
take care guys we'll see you uh in a few days thanks a lot everybody hello i'm german on 85
senya ludwig is a good dude go show some love i think i did it right like i was not showing up
why did that not work there we are here we go i see you guys later goodbye see you in a few days