What is going on, everybody? Jerma here again with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
This time we are the Demoman, the default stock Demoman. There's no unlockables here, folks.
Only the default vanilla 2007 Team Fortress 2 setup, sticky bomb launcher, grenade launcher, and the bottle.
I kind of just felt like doing a gameplay where I just did the default stock, because a lot of you guys don't really have any of the new items.
And I figured why not just do a complete stock gameplay, playing on Dust Bowl.
And I gotta tell you guys, this is a very, very, very good gameplay.
I think I only died two times and I killed like 700 people. That's a lie, but you get the idea. I do very well.
So here are some Demoman tips, especially on this part of Dust Bowl, the first part of Dust Bowl.
You want to stick around up top on this little building up here.
Heavy Medic comes around the corner, but I get lucky crit right there and I just barely get the kill.
This little house is fantastic, because look at underneath inside. There is two full health packs and ammo.
You do not even need a Medic to hang out with you up here. You don't need a Dispenser, nothing.
If you get hit, just drop down the little middle there and get yourself some more health and ammo. It's a fantastic place to stay.
I would say same thing for Soldier too. If you're Soldier or Demoman, I would suggest sitting in this spot right here.
Prime example right here. Take a look, I get lit on fire, but it's as if it didn't even happen at all.
Full health, full ammo. Let's keep going. Sir, spam a lot now. Accidentally kill a disguised Cloak Spy.
I hate when that happens, but you know how this game is. You give and you take, right?
Anyways, here's a good tip for you guys with the Sticky Launcher. Watch what happens.
My Medic gets lit on fire and you have to place your Sticky Bombs five to ten feet in front of somebody when they're running after you.
Otherwise, they're just not going to get hit by any of the blast radius.
This is especially important for Pyros because as a Demoman, you don't really have any close-range combat abilities.
Except for, of course, your melee weapon, but who wants to bring out a melee weapon for a Pyro? That's pretty much a death sentence.
Get Ubered by the Quick Fix and as you saw, took out pretty much the entire left-hand side right there.
Big deal because if they had gotten up there, they probably would have gotten on the point and capped it.
I'm glad I could get over there. Good Quick Fix Uber by that Medic.
And now I'm back up on my Dragon Perch, just shooting and spamming into their spawn area.
A nice little pop-up right here on this Demoman. I get the kill.
Back on my house, hanging out in my little shack over here.
Got to move away from it now though because it looks like they're coming out the right-hand side.
And I get sniped by Sitting Duck, who gets me with a nice body shot coming around the side there.
That's pretty much what you want to do, especially on this map on Dust Bowl.
Demoman at this point is an incredibly powerful class.
Spy I saw out of the corner of my eye and there he is. Boom, he gets blown up.
Now kind of on the right side over here, trying to do some work, just putting pills out everywhere.
Century Gun now is going up on the point and look at where I end up.
Take a look at where I am right now. Back on the Perch with this Soldier.
This is incredibly dominating now because if you have more than one Power Class up here
shooting into the spawn area, it's very difficult for anyone to get out.
And even an Ubert Heavy is going to have trouble killing anyone
because we can just jump backwards behind the house and kind of ring around the Rosie with him.
So I kind of get embarrassed right here, guys.
I jump down here, see this sniper, try and kill him, and then a Demo Knight comes over here.
And rather than just pulling out my bottle and going toe-to-toe,
I didn't really have enough brain power to do that, so I just get murdered by him.
That's the only other time I die. I think I actually...
I'll take that back because you'll see, this is a pretty crazy gameplay, how this ends.
It's one of the most ridiculous things ever, so I'm not going to spoil it for you what happens,
but you'll see, it's pretty insane what happens at the end of this gameplay.
And let me take this time just briefly to talk about my livestream
and how thankful I am for all the people that showed up to it.
It was a success, an absolute success. I think I peaked out around 150 viewers at one time
for maybe 45 minutes there was 150 people watching or something like that.
Really, really cool, really awesome. I'm really sorry that I couldn't get Deus Ex to work,
but apparently you have to go through like a dog and pony show to get the thing to load into windowed mode,
and obviously I can't do it in full screen mode because you can't really stream anything in full screen,
but my plan, guys, is for every Monday and Friday, or maybe every Tuesday and Friday,
is to do a livestream twice a week.
Hopefully I see a lot of you guys there, a lot of new people.
I'll put it in the description, the link to my Twitch account, so hopefully you guys show up.
It should be a great time. Probably going to do one tonight too.
Tuesday and Friday probably is when I'm going to do it.
So let's get back into the gameplay now. No more talking about my dumb livestream.
So as you can probably tell, it's becoming painfully obvious that this team can't even get out of the spawn doors.
They're getting up here instantly dying. They can't even get close.
They can't even get remotely close to the point.
So I'm just kind of hanging back here thinking to myself, should I do something about this?
Should I switch teams or something and make something happen?
And you'll see my conscience really takes hold of me after about another minute or so.
You'll see what happens. And ultimately you'll see how this ends.
So anyways, shooting more spam, getting more random kills, going to fill my ammo up.
I get Ubered right here in about two or three seconds. I think it's right here.
Yep, I get Ubered. We come down to the spawn, start spawn camping, just being real jerks.
I hate when people do this and every time I find myself doing this I always go,
Okay, let's turn around. I don't want to do this anymore. This is not fun.
Because it's dumb. It really is dumb doing this.
So you'll see after about another five or ten seconds we get back down into their spawn area and I just kill myself.
I just go right in front of their spawn door. I drop three stickies.
I kill myself and then I switch teams.
And after the team switch you'll see what happens. It's insane.
I can't even begin to describe how insane this is after I kill myself.
So let's just turn around here, spam a few more times, maybe get one more kill.
I think I get one more kill here. Yep, it's one. Here it is.
One last kill. Here we go. Going back down to their spawn there's a heavy and a sniper.
I get the kill on the heavy and then here we go.
Boom, see you later heavy.
Okay, time to kill the spawn, right?
Let's load this door up with stickies and then walk into it and kill myself.
So now I'm on blue team. I just switched to blue team.
Take a look at the time. Three minutes and 47 seconds.
Come out here just spamming like crazy. Get a couple kills.
I want to make something happen. It was a goal of mine, guys, to be able to win this game now.
Medic Pyro coming up towards the spawn.
Get the kill on me, but my teammates are so fed up at this point, I believe,
that they just started to push really, really hard.
This Medic-Soldier pair really do a lot of work and they really help the team out a lot.
Too much suppression, too much domination.
Kill the Sentry and the Engineer making it and now we're...
Look at the movement. Look at how fast everyone is just jumping up here to get on the point.
Now this wasn't all me, guys.
It's kind of coincidental that I switched and now all of a sudden we're winning,
but really I think this team was just getting sick of being in the spawn
and they really started to make a push.
Now look at the time. I want you to take a look at the time.
Seven minutes and 28 seconds.
Let's count down to see when the game ends, okay?
Watch this. Get out here. There's nobody really here, by the way.
There's one Soldier who kind of gets dominated by that group that was right there.
Engineer is trying to build a Sentry on the point and I think I distracted him enough
that he decided I was going to be his top priority and not build up a Sentry
and it ends up being the downfall of the team.
Take a look now. Everybody is starting to get on the point.
We're going to cap it now. We win the game in less than two minutes
after switching to the blue team. We won.
Unbelievable. I can't believe it. I was speechless when it happened.
I said, holy crap. Talk about a gameplay that's a keeper right there.
Anyways, thank you all so much for watching. I really appreciate it.
Show up at my livestream Fridays and Tuesdays probably around 7 to 8 o'clock Eastern Standard Time
is when I'm going to do them.
Take care, everybody. I'll see you all soon.