I'm just trying to be very quiet so I don't scare anybody. Hi.
Oh, hold on. Very cool. That nice relaxing music is about to be replaced with some scary shit.
So this is a game that I'm actually scared to play because I feel like it's going to be
insanely loud. So let me ask you this. I have to ask you. Should I turn this down to 1%?
No. So is this one, is this going to like blow up my ears? No. I'm so scared. You have no idea.
This game is way too dank. Whatever. Okay, let's do this. I'll do it right here for now.
It's a puppet combo. Turn it all the way down. Turn the filter off. 20, door turns brightness.
What the fuck? Which one should I put on? 16 millimeter is cool. That is kind of cool.
16 millimeter, PSX, CRT. None, none, none. Scan lines one. Just normal, please. This hurts my eyes.
Let me do PSX and turn this off. Let me see how that looks. New game. Let's try that. Prologue
Murder House. I mean, I feel like we're going to have to play the prologue. That looks fine.
That's not my mic. Don't people are going to be complaining about that. That's not me.
Get my green tea. Okay, kid. You're next. How do I move? Come on, kid. Get your ass up there.
That's not my mic. Oh, kid. Say cheese. Cheese. Easter. Turn the volume down. Yeah, the volume's
way down. I must have fallen asleep. Just turn it down. How do I move? Oh, I thought it was first
person. Okay, that's weird. All right, hold on. Why is there no sound? I'm so paranoid about the
audio. I don't think this is supposed to be audio right now. Mom, is the mall closed? No, I can hear
it. Just low. It's going to be loud. Yeah, I know. Just be, just be ready for it. It's going to be
horrible. It's going to be terrible. Just be ready for it. Oh, you can do Dolly in FPS. Which one should
you prefer? FPS or the kind of old Resident Evil style? FPS. FPS. FPS. Oh, man. That sensitivity's
got to go up, though. Way higher. Rumble off. Invert Y off. What are you talking about? Auto-aim off.
Okay, let's see. That feels better. Dolly, please. Change the game and the title. Oh, shit. Good idea.
Oh, it is Murder House. It's correct. Zoomers are picking FPS. I'll switch between them. How
does that sound? It's meant to be played in Dolly. Okay, well, I'll go back. I'll play some with Dolly
and one without. What am I supposed to do? It's closed. Do a poll? You know, that's not a bad idea.
All right. Mods run a poll. Do you want FPS or Dolly? Which one? It's closed. What do you think? Okay.
So I'm supposed to just leave the mall? How do I get out of here? It's a landslide for,
for what? I can't get out this way. Okay. You know what's crazy? 77% say Dolly. What the fuck?
Zoomers BTFO. Is it really that much? Dolly's what? I mean, that's, that's unanimous. I can't,
I have to go back. 77%. All right, let's go back. I think I want to use the controller because this
is weird to do with keyboard and mouse. The tank controls don't work. I can crawl under it. How do
you crawl? C, control. I need the control plugged in for this shit. This is, I can't do it. Oh,
that's much better. Okay. That's a little too sensitive though. That's far too sensitive.
Looks good. Don't quit. There we go. All right. Now I'm happy. Enable rumble on the controller.
I don't do that. I think rumble is the dumbest thing that's ever been invented. I truly believe
it. I think rumble is just dumb. I just really do. I'm sorry. I just, I, it just like shakes
your hands. See back like 20 years ago, they created rumble because they wanted it to be
more immersive. Like, and as you can see, when you jump over the ledge and there's like somebody
shooting, it's, oh, I can feel it. That it's like 20 years ago, right? It was, that was cool. But
like, I don't, I don't need that anymore. I'm sorry. I just don't need it to me. Now it's just like,
I don't. Okay. Stop, stop, stop. Every time you get hit,
no, I don't, I just want to play the game. I'm sorry. This might be weird. I'm a complainer.
That's fine. The Easter bunny's chair. I guess he went home for the night. I don't know if you guys
can hear this, but it's making scary sounds. I fucking hate tank controls more than anything.
Tank controls are just the cinematic mode in every car game. I feel like I'm playing GTA.
It's just on foot cinematic mode. I can't leave now. Where am I supposed to go? It's closed.
Omega Lo, no audio. It's there. It's there. Fix your stream. What are you talking about?
Audio is actually kind of low. Turn it up. It's puppet combo, man. I feel like you're going to
regret this very shortly. Warning, actual warning, loud audio warning for real. Where the fuck am I
supposed to be going? What is happening? I can't get out this way. Where do I go? This is the
beginning of the game. Fuck. I went all the way to the back. This kid's going to be out of breath,
but I get lost in malls. It doesn't matter how many times I've been to a mall. I could go to the same
mall a thousand times. And if you say, Hey dude, can you tell me where the, you know, can you tell
me where the Macy's is? I'd go. I don't fucking have any idea. I could go to the same mall a
thousand times. And I still could not tell you because it's just like, it's just lines with
stores. And then I have to sit there and go, what? I don't know. I don't remember. It's always so
embarrassing because especially if you, let's say for instance, if, Oh, you've got a local mall. Oh,
let's go explore the local mall. That sounds like fun. Oh, you know, I'd really love to go.
I'd really love to go to Auntie Anne's Pretzels. Yeah, I would too. That sounds like fun. Oh,
okay. Let's go. Auntie Anne's Pretzels walking distance. Where is it? It's in here somewhere.
Okay. I think it's this store over here. I hate it. Who is he talking to? Where the fuck am I
supposed to go? I can't get through here. Another security gate. This one's locked. shiny. Take the
key. Yes. You took the key. I can use the inventory by pressing Z key. What is that on the controller?
Okay. That looks like Tim Heidecker. Okay. A key. I can't use that key here. Do I have to go all the
way back? Get this camera in the right place. Am I going the right way? Am I going the right way?
Oh, I got it. This is going to be some Slenderman bullshit. Resident Sleeper. There's got to be a
way out. The exit's right there. All right. It's going to be like... Should I lower the volume?
I'm going to lightly put this in. I warn you. These are lightly in my ears right now. What does
that say? Locked. Locked. All these are locked. This one's opened. Why is it doing like a... Should
I hide? Yes. This is a good hiding place. I could peek out with the action button and get a closer
look with the look button. Okay. So I can hide here. All right. Let me out. There's no shitting
mechanic. Why would there be a shitting mechanic? Okay. All right. I got to go into the bathroom.
Where's that bathroom? Where's the bathroom? Farting and screaming. Quick, quick. Hide, hide, hide.
He locked the door? What do you mean he locked the door? Dude, what are you talking about? No way.
He's going to kill me right here. I got to go now. Got to go, go, go, go, go, go, go, got to go,
got to go, got to go, got to go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, got it.
Where is he? Didn't he go in that stall? He's in that stall right now. This shit's locked. What do
I do? There's a keypad. I don't know the code. Will you take the flashlight? Yes. I got the
flashlight. How do I use it? Okay. It's equipped. How do I turn the fucking flashlight on? What is
that? Okay. Screwdriver. Is there a TV here? Can't be the fuck out of here. I don't like this. I don't
like this at all. I really don't. I unlocked it. What's in here? I don't like this. It's too
nerve wracking. I don't like it. Okay. I have a screwdriver. What do I do with the screwdriver?
I thought I could get it. So what do I take the screwdriver? Broken vending machine. Fix it.
I don't know what the fuck to do. This is back in the bathroom. Shit. It moved. Do I need the
screwdriver for something else? Literally omega low. This dude's gone. What do you mean I'm gone?
I'm fine. The bathroom is huge. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Lockers. Come on. Really? Just some
lockers. That's it? I can't pry one of these open. Oh, you're full of shit. Come on. I was already in
here. I remember one of the lockers you can open. It was kind of weird. You mean like right here?
This one has blood on it. You missed the shower. The answer is within this room. Hey, thanks. Where
am I going though? Shower? There's a shower in the locker. You know, I played Resident Evil 1 when
I first came out and I got to like the first part where you had to like walk around and find the one
place to go. I just stopped playing it. There's something below the drain. Oh, there's a key.
What door do I need to open this with? There's a tiny key. It says 1024. 1024? Is that the...
Okay. I don't remember where to go. 1024? In their door? That's... Where's that door? Right here.
Oh, fuck off. What door is locked? 1024. No, no, no, no, no, no. It's not this place. 1024.
In here? Or a locker? No, they don't number the stalls. What am I talking about? It's definitely
a locker. Where are the lockers? I'm lost in them all. It's a stall like 1024, 1025, 1026.
I need a map. I don't remember where the lockers are. I have no object permanence.
If you told me to draw a map of Dust Bowl and TF2, I have a thousand hours on that map. I still...
I wouldn't be able to draw it for you. I really wouldn't be able to. I got it. All right. 1024.
How am I supposed to know which one of these is 1024? None of these are numbered. Oh, wait.
This one is 1024. Hey. SS34. 5534. That's a number. All right. Get out. 5534. This motherfucker's
going to be right here. Huh? Where am I going? Where's that door? 5534. A toaster. Frigerator.
It would be rude to take someone's lunch. They're not in there, right? Is that the Jacksepticeye?
That's so funny. It's too quiet. Janitor Jack. The voices are too quiet. What if Janitor Jack is...
Hold on. I can't turn the dialogue up. Look out the window. Janitor Jack, I think, is in trouble
here. Well, Janitor Jack is probably the Easter Bunny. The Easter Bunny's going to walk in here
and be walking slowly towards me. It's going to be Janitor Jack. Of course it's Janitor Jack.
I was making a muted joke and it caught me. I was making a, I have no audio joke. Murderhouse.
It was definitely Janitor Jack. Oh, pancakes. No, that's not it. That was the prologue. Tutorial
complete and Jacksepticeye as Janitor Jack. Turn the volume up. Ever since the Nun game,
I'm terrified to turn any of these puppet combo games over 10% audio level. Ever. Did you miss
the jump scare? You did. The Nun game is literally the loudest shit ever created. Nothing can even
compare. All right, so now where are we? The lights are already off. I can't turn them off
anymore. Present day, 1988. This is the murder house and it's for sale. People died in this house.
Fuck. I have to move? Like we're here. This place? You left you have this after the incident with
the poodle. That could have happened to anyone. These are all just Sims 1 characters. All right,
let's get started. We don't have all day. Who? Megalo? He's dead. Make yourself useful and find
a survey in. That reminds me, somebody made a video of me testing cigars that I saw. It was
really funny. Anybody got that video? I want to show that video on stream. It's fucking hilarious.
Somebody took the eating the tearless stuff and they they made it as if I was testing cigars.
It's so stupid. Does anybody have a link to the video? The actual like video video because like
pulling it up reddit up is a pain in the ass. He saw it. Oh yeah. Oh, let me get it. Yeah,
long lost Gerald985 cigar tear list from the 20s. Let me get it. I love this video. It's just so
dumb. We're going to watch this first. Let's see if I can get it full screened here. Okay,
is it audio on here? Yeah, this is so fucking stupid. I love it. All right, you ready?
It's so stupid. Look at all these cigars. Oh Jesus. Okay, let's go. It tastes like marshmallows.
Wait, my stamina will drain. I have to pick a break. Hold on. Here's this loud game. Too many
cigars. All right, so do I get to choose who I play with or no? Oh, that's a cool little feature.
Tracking. All right, so we're here doing a story. This is this person's car, right?
You look terrifying right now. Why? All right, here's the news van. So I just gotta get in the
house. This is really creepy. Locked. Windows really dirty. I can't see inside. Can I break in
here? Oh, the side. The flashlight under your face. We've already done this before. It's an old
routine. I look green. Why am I green? I'm green and now I can't see. I actually can't see. Turn
the ring light on. It's all right. It's on right now. That's why you can see my face. I just can't.
I literally can't see. Can I grab it through here? Looks like a gun. I can't reach from here. Okay,
are we going to hear a distant scream? We're going to hear like, oh my God, I'm going to go
investigate. Somebody saw a rodent. I'm a writer too. There's a fellow writer. I, I can't, where am
I? Why is the camera doing this? Name one book you've read. Sure. Dance of Dragons from a song
of ice and fire. Book five, 10 years ago. Well, I don't know how to get in there, so I don't think
I can. Have you ever read the Bible? Um, I think parts of it. Name one book you've read. I don't
know. I don't, why do I need to prove that I've read a book? It's creepy in here. So I was going
to open the front door. I don't even have a flashlight. This is stupid. This is dumb what
I'm doing. I need a flashlight. Can I have gotten a flashlight somewhere that I didn't see? What?
Empty cabinet. This will make a great hiding spot. Okay. Where do I get a flashlight? It's a big
basin sink. I don't know where to go. A dryer. It's, I thought it said seasoned. Washing machine.
Okay. Oh, fuse box. An average fuse box. Wait, I think a fuse is missing. Okay, I need to get a fuse.
Can I open the door? You've unlocked the door. All right, so everyone can come on in, right?
Oh, there we go. Okay, so come on in. I found a way in. Do they, do I have to go tell them? Or should
I just keep exploring? Empty cabinet. Make a great hiding spot. Yep. A greasy fridge. There's no way
I'm going to open that. Kitchen cabinet. Search it. Yes. Kojima fell off. I don't think Kojima made
this. What's that? Hole in the floor. I see something shiny at the bottom. I can't reach it.
I don't have any items. How about, how about I don't have no items? No items? None. I can't open it.
The doorknob is missing. No items. This is no items. Finally. No. There's enough items. Pencil.
What the fuck am I going to do with a pencil? Can I pick the lock with the pencil? What's this?
Stack of boxes. No, no, no. This. Left a note. Hey, it's Jerry, the real estate agent. Looks like
someone broke the lock on the basement window and got in the house since the last time I was over
here. They stole the goddamn fuse so the power is out. Don't worry. I know there's another fuse
around here somewhere. I'd let the front door open in case I don't hear you guys drive up.
Just shout at me when you get inside. Okay, well where's the fuse? An old dusty mug. I don't want
to go back down in the basement. Spider on your face. All right, I'm just going to go talk to them
because the door's open now. I'm going to say, hey, I got a back door. All right, come on in.
Stupid. Idiots. Idiots. Idiots. Oh, come on. Did I not open? Whatever. Just idiots. I have to unlock
the front door. Yeah, but I don't know. This is not my house. I don't know where anything is.
So straight ahead should be the front door. Straight ahead. There we go. Go through here.
I can't go through there. I don't have a doorknob. Do you know where anything in your house is?
Oh, there's an upstairs. There's an upstairs. This is the front door right here, but how the
fu- I couldn't even see it. There's an upstairs, Lois. Fucking goddamn family guy.
Yeah, you should have. You still can. That's a huge ass microphone, by the way.
Grab all the equipment in the van. Let's set it up. All right, what do we got here?
Microphones, lav mics, shotgun mics, C stands, cameras, HD camera, maybe a GoPro to put
somewhere. He won't finish this in three hours. Shut up. All right, I gotta go to the other one.
Do I have to unpack it? He won't finish this. What if I don't finish it? Who gives a shit?
What do you care if I finish this game or not? What do you care? What do you care? Clean the
camera. No, it's dirty. Why is he so toxic now? I just am, okay? When are you gonna do a comb stream?
I don't think there's ever gonna be a comb stream ever again. All right, the lights are up, but
there's no power in this house. I need a fuse, right? Fuse. All right, can you stop smoking?
Turn it back on. I don't know how. Figure something out. He's a real piece of shit, isn't he?
23k Andy doesn't care about his chat anymore. That's not true. Do I have a- oh, that's- I
thought that was a cigar. 23k Andy. Holy shit, there are 23- 24,000 people here. Hope you're
having a good night, good day. Apparently getting scared. Scary games tonight. I guess that's locked.
What's with all this bullshit? I'm telling you right now, I could probably elbow drop through
this and break it and get what's in there. This doesn't look that sturdy. I could just run across
the room and just slide and tackle and kick this and break it. If I needed to get in there, I could
literally jump from the bed and just stomp down and land on it and break it. Locked. Okay, there's
two locked things up here. Covered table. A lot of these hiding spots. I'm imagining this is important
later. Not right now. This is the locked room. Okay, okay, I have to remember where this is.
That's the dark room at the end of the hall. So keep that in mind. Write that down. Dark room end
of the hall has two, three locked things over here. What about this? Hey, that guy that took a four
month break after dancing. Oh, I can't move this. I need someone up here to move it. Oh, a fuse. Nice.
Okay, check everything. This is a weird bed. Covered table. Another pencil. What are the pencils for?
Let me guess. It's a save point. I need to use a pencil to save the game. Stupid fucking god. What
was that? Stupid fucking god damn fucking idiot. Stupid fucking game. Fucking stupid fucking piece
of shit game. What is that? Solid iron. No way I can open this. Maybe there's somebody there.
All right, well I have the fuse. Let's go back down. All right, can somebody help me move the
thing up there? Later, somebody will help me. Let's go down to the basement again. Locked.
Flimsy lock. You're a sellout. What did I do? I didn't even do anything. What are you talking
about? All right, where's the fuse box? This guy buys porn. All right, screw it in. Power's back
and the washing machine is on. The door is jammed shut. Should I have a pencil on there? Okay, well,
whatever. I got the power back on. So now what? All right, we're gonna have to do interviews and
stuff. All right, good. Everything's set, Tom. Lighting's ready. The cameras roll. Hey Gary,
I was thinking we could- I don't pay you to think, Dana. I pay you to read the goddamn script.
I hate this job. Well, pull it together. Ready, everyone? What are we doing here? All right,
action. Anthony Smith, more commonly known as the Easter Ripper. What's her boom mic
and a handheld mic? The mere mention of his name sends shivers up the spines of parents across
the country. His horrible murder spree leaving lives shattered and families ripped apart. Tonight
we'll go inside his vacant home where 11 innocent children spent their final moments in agonizing
pain and terror. What the fuck? Untouched since those horrible crimes eight years ago,
some say his spirit still haunts the home till this day. I'm Dana Turner and this is a News
Nine special report. Silenced tears inside the home of serial killer Anthony Smith.
Cut. Let's take a break. Gary, I think I want to redo the line where-
This isn't 60 minutes, Dana. It's channel fucking nine. We're out here to win a Pulitzer.
So why are we even here? We could have done this whole thing from outside the house. If we're not
trying to be thorough and have a really deep investigation on this, just do it in front of
the house and then leave. I'm going to find a place in this gross house to fix my makeup.
Right? I think I heard that. Wait, did she say I'm going to go fix up my gross makeup?
What did I just hear? I wasn't paying attention. I don't know. What did she say? Gross house.
I need to go fix my gross makeup. Okay. So I think why would we stay here? Is it Pulitzer
or Pulitzer? I don't know, dude. You and I ain't ever going to get one, so it doesn't matter.
What if they will get it? Speak for yourself. Speak for yourself. Too bad the house doesn't
have cable. Should I go to bed? I'm sorry, but if you expect to win a Pulitzer prize, I mean,
you got to just do what you're doing. You don't just say, I'm going to win a Pulitzer prize
soon. You got to work and get it and work for it. You don't just say I'm going to be a Pulitzer
prize winner. I mean, I said that like five years ago when I thought that my stream was going to
really take off and become like this really important thing. What is the Pulitzer prize even
for? I don't even know. Is the Pulitzer prize science? What is the Pulitzer prize? What is it
for? It's journalism. Oh, why did I think it was science? What's the science one? The Nobel prize
is science. Okay. So what do I do? Nobel prize is for whatever. Nobel could be pretty much for
anything, right? There are lots of different categories. Can I go to bed? I want to find a
way back into that, whatever it is, a greenhouse or something back there, whatever it is. Go get the
gun. I need a key or something to get in there. What about down here? The cool one is science
though. These are all locked. I need a key somewhere. This game is a real talkie by the way.
Where do I go? A mannequin. Should I try to get into the greenhouse? Help. Whoa. Can you fetch me
a glass of water? You want a glass of water from here? I think I'm going to say it. I'd probably
drink my piss before I drank out of this sink. I would drink a glass of my own piss before I
drank out of the sink here. All right. I need to get a glass of water. That's Vera Lunatic. What?
Okay. Where do I get a glass to cover it or anything? I need a glass. Why is he always
talking about drinking piss? Literally said it once in like a year. Fine. I will concede that you
find me one point in the last year that I said I was going to drink my own piss and I will concede.
I've said I've did it maybe once in a year. It was literally two weeks ago. No, it wasn't.
Here's your water. I have no idea where I'm going. I need to deliver the water. The voice
actors is in chat right now. Oh shit. Really? Dana's VA and you're playing you playing this
made my night. Good luck. Look, holy shit. That's cool. Wait, did you bash this? Oh, we got to keep
Dana in the chat. That's cool. And maybe we can get hired on our real network. All right. So I
got a key. There's a lot of member of the doors. I got a key now. People to sleep here with this
boring story. Time to sex this up. Hey, you. Me? Yeah, you put this sheet on. Gary, what the fuck
are you doing? No one's going to want to watch this boring thing. And your dry reporting isn't
helping. I'm reading the teleprompter. People want to see ghosts. So we're going to fake a ghost
sighting. Okay, intern, when Dana says he still haunts the home he grew up in, I want you to run
through the background. Got it? All right. Let's do this. Okay. After Dana says he still haunts the
home he grew up in, I need to run through the door. Action. The rampage started in late March
1979, when Smith walked into a local mall and took a seasonal position as an Easter bunny.
A job meant to spread joy and cheer put him in the perfect position to abduct young children
until his capture and execution in 1985. Many of the bodies have not been recovered. As told
by the sole survivor, Randy Martinez, Smith would release the children in his greenhouse
and force them to go on a deadly Easter egg hunt while he stalked and murdered them. What the
fuck? Two years later, many say he still haunts the home he grew up in. God damn it. I said one
time not to stand in the shot. I couldn't. Oh, because A is. A job meant to spread joy and
cheer put him in the perfect. Relax. A job meant to spread joy and cheer put him in the perfect
position to abduct young children until his capture and execution in 1985. Many of the bodies
have not been recovered. As told by the sole survivor, Randy Martinez, I don't know how to
release the children in his greenhouse. I thought I had to skip the dialogue on a deadly Easter egg
hunt while he stalked and murdered them. I'm not in the shot right now. Many say he still haunts
the home he grew up in. God damn it. What? I fucking just ran by. I just ran by. Run through
the door. A job meant to spread joy and cheer put him in the perfect position to abduct young
children until his capture and execution in 1985. That's not even in the shot. Many of the bodies
have not been recovered. That's not in the shot. As told by the sole survivor, Randy Martinez,
Smith would release the children in his greenhouse and force them to go on a deadly Easter egg hunt
while he stalked and murdered them. Two years later, many say he still haunts the home he grew
up in. What was that? Tom, did you get that? I apologized to the viewers at home, but I just
felt an energy pass by behind me. Let's continue deeper into the house and see what secrets we
uncover. Cut! This is ratings gold. Let's take a break and pick up in the bedroom. Great timing.
I'm going to go use the restroom. Hey you, I'm getting hungry. Take the van and go pick us up
some pizzas. Use the station credit, Todd. Okay. Reddit gold. All right, let's go get some pizzas.
I'll go get some pizzas. Let's just go with the front door. Fuck it. What's your favorite pizza
place? What's your favorite pizza place to get a pizza? What is it? A chain. What's your favorite
chain pizza place? Little Caesars? Domino's? No. I'm sorry, that's wrong. Did you find anything
juicy yet? Not yet, but I think I'm onto something. I think there's something hidden here that nobody
knows about. Good work. Domino's? Come on. Don't mention this to anybody, especially Gary. He'll
steal any story for us. What the fuck? Domino's is good. I don't know. Is it though? I feel like
it's not. I know what a Domino's pizza tastes like, and it's not, I don't think, I don't,
I don't remember it being good. Should I do this first? Just to have items?
No. The sauce is really busting. You drink piss. Why would anyone care about your opinions in this?
Um, you name one time when I drank piss. I can't open this? What the hell is this key even for?
Really? Really? What's taking so long? I can't function on an empty stomach. Sorry, I'm going
to go soon. Soon? Make it pronto. You know, I have not had Little Caesars in a very long time. I feel
like I'd probably like it. I bet you I would really like Little Caesars. Aren't Little Caesars
pizzas like three dollars? Aren't they really, really cheap? Five. It's five dollars for a pizza
at Little Caesars. Five dollars. I'm sorry, but you cannot do better than that. Five bucks for a
pizza? We're talking five dollars for a full pizza? I feel safe in this room, like nothing bad can
happen here. Save the game. Okay, so game saved. Are you sure you want this? You'll need to use
another pencil to save again. Yeah, okay. Flashlight. Hell yeah. Cigar? Oh, it's a pencil.
Hold on. This is a lot. Let me read this. Little Caesars parent company owns the distribution
center that sends ingredients to all the pizza chains so they don't have to pay for their
ingredients like Domino's, Papa John's, or Pizza Hut. For real? Really? I mean Pizza Hut. Oh man,
oh man. Oh man, oh man. I get fucking worked up when I start thinking about Pizza Hut.
Large stuffed crust pepperoni pizza with a side of eight buffalo tenders in the mild sauce with
some blue cheese. Oh man, oh man. That's nothing better. It's so fucking good. Everybody can say,
oh my god, that's gross dude. Oh no, it's not. You're just not, you just don't get it. You know
what I mean? You just don't get it. If you don't like the stuffed crust pizza from Pizza Hut
pepperoni and it's just right out of the oven, you just don't get it to me. To me, you and I,
we're just never going to get along with the buffalo tenders and they're nice and hot and
ready and they get the blue cheese on them. What was I doing? I'm playing a game. You just don't
get it. You just don't get it. That cheese that they put, wait, I actually need to go down here.
The cheese that they put in the crust at Pizza Hut is a magical cheese that does, I don't know
where they get it. I don't know what it is. It's magic. It tastes just so delicious. I don't even
know what it is. Looking at the mod chat, my Pizza Hut went out of business and I tried it once. It
was terrible. No, you just don't get it. You don't get it. No, you don't get it. You don't get it.
Okay, I can actually see. What about your thoughts on Costco pizza? I actually don't think I've really
ever had Costco pizza before. Not that I can really reliably remember. I hear it's pretty good though.
Okay, I can actually see what's over here. Bridge, place to hide. This is going to make me throw up.
Empty cabinet and puke. Whoa! Shut up. I wasn't even that big of a deal. This is gonna hurt my
back. My shoulder hurts now because of that. I just, I actually hurt my shoulder. I just pulled a
muscle in my shoulder. Oh, let's open this. What is that? A doorknob. Ooh. Okay, let's open up that
door that needs a doorknob upstairs. You're old, dude. It's getting dark. Yeah, I know I'm old.
I'm older. Okay, so what's in here? Is that a fire poker? Pretty good weapon. Oh, hell yeah.
There's weapons? How do I swing? It's unlocked. Oh wait, there's something over here. Old fireplace
sealed up. Two-handing a fire poker. Yeah, it's dangerous. Yeah, I love Pizza Hut's awesome. It's
really good. Oh, this is unlocked now. All right. Well, I gotta go get pizza. Are they even open?
The van. Who would do this? There's a note pinned on the windshield. No where to go now. Looks like
we'll be playing a game. You'll be hunting eggs. I'll be hunting you. Find them all and you can
leave. Don't find them and you can't. Find all the eggs. Should I go try to get the gun? Looks
like a gun. I can't reach it. Yes, I can. Really? Why do I look so scared? Because it's a scary game.
I don't see any eggs. Stop being YouTube Andy. What are you on about? Can't reach it? I have a
fire poker. How can I not reach that? Where should I go? I'm gonna go upstairs, I think. I'm going
upstairs. Where's the safe room? Where are the pizzas? There's something going on here. The van
has been wrecked and the gate is locked. Where's Tom? I don't know. He's dead. I can't find him
either. Must be the goddamn real estate agent. I told you to get another 50 bucks when we were
done. Come out you chicken shit. Damn it, Gary. It's dark and this place is scary and gross.
Can we finish this? Still holding the mic. Fine. I don't know where the hell Tom is so you're gonna
have to hold the camera. I don't know how to work this. It's easy. Just hold it steady. That's about
it. Okay, action. This is Dana Turner on location. How do I zoom in? I've just been informed that we're
stuck here. Someone has wrecked our van and we can't get our fucking pizza lunch promised by my
producer. Is Anthony Smith executed in the electric chair in 1985 back from the dead
and back for revenge on anyone who enters his house? Find out soon if we don't get the fuck
out of here. That would actually be kind of crazy. I can't work under these conditions. Isn't it like
10 o'clock at night? Hey intern girl, see if you can find where the hell Tom is. Okay, gotta find Tom.
I'd be pissed too if I didn't get my pizza. Especially if it was a fucking Pizza Hut stuffed
crust pizza with a side above a loving her wings. I would be also very annoyed by that. You need to
shut the fuck up. You need to not care if I like Pizza Hut or not. There's nothing in here, right?
Shut the fuck up, Jeremy. There's nothing else here. Fuck Pizza Hut. I'm serious. I feel like a
lot of you guys probably haven't had it in a long time. When was the last time you had Pizza Hut?
Solid iron key you're gonna need. All right. Well, I don't know where this guy is.
2011, 1997. That's what I mean. I feel like you're not being fair to the Pizza Hut. Let's stop that.
Where is this guy? That doesn't count. Like you cannot say I had it in 1992 or something.
No, even like the air was tasted differently in like the early 90s. Like everything smelled
different. You know what I mean? Like everything was different. I already picked that up, but
where is this guy? Probably down. I remember the 90s had a smell. It was, I can't even describe it.
My everybody's car had a 90s smell. The air just kind of had this, it just smelled like,
it smelled like the 90s. It's everything had a different smell. What was that? Cabinets locked.
Tom? Tom, I didn't think I would find you. This is getting weird. Do you think the Easter Ripper
is back? It looks like we're stuck here. All the doors are locked. Let's get a key blade. We're
fine. I found a key, but I can't figure out what it opens. Let me see. You take it. Maybe you can
find the door. I'm going to go look for another way out. I'll catch you later. Okay. So there's
a lot. This looks like an iron key. That's definitely through the upstairs door.
Can I get the fuck out of here? Oh my God. I'm walking in circles, dude. Why did I stop? I don't
know. Dude, I'm wicked fucking high. Okay. You all right? Do weapons have durability? This is
definitely the key to upstairs. There's no way it's not. Why is she holding this like a lightsaber?
Only a master of evil, Doth. That's how, that's how Obi-Wan holds his lightsaber. Watch out.
Only a master of evil, Doth. He's right here. I thought I was downstairs. Get back here. We good?
No, I want to pick up the microphone. You need to save the game. Where do I do that? How do I
save the game? Where do I save it? Oh, there's an Easter egg shoved in her mouth. Take the egg.
I took the death egg. It's under the stairs. Oh my God. So now I'm going to go upstairs and I'm
going to open the big door. There it is. Circuit breaker or something. I don't think I need to use
this. Bed frame. Dresser. Ooh, what's that? Letter opener. What can I do with that? A letter opener.
What did I need? Did I need to use that somewhere? Broken refrigerator. It's a table. I don't think
there's anything else in here. Got the letter opener. A normal light. That's weird. Why would
you say a normal light? Letter opener though. It's pretty sharp. I need to find something to
use this on. Shit. Shit. Letter opener. What do I use the letter opener on? Use it on a letter.
Can I get it? Can I pick it up? Do this or something? What is down here? So I'm going to
lift the letter. Open it with a letter opener. Where do I go? Back to the basement? Maybe Tom
would be down there. I think Tom's probably going to be down here. Is Tom still here? Tom? I can
hide in there. Where is he? Shit. I heard a bunch of bullshit over here. Letter opener. That works.
I can actually pry it open. Magnet. I can get the gun. What the? There are hairs in my mouth. I can
get the gun with the magnet. God, he's going to be right here. What's that mean? It means he's
coming. It means he's coming. Upstairs? There's a locked door up there. No. Major stream of reactions
coming up here. Really? Just go in here for a second so I can breathe. Where is there more
locked doors? There's one down the hall here. I think that's it. There's a locked door down the
hall. There it is. A note. The big bunny watches us. Its big black eye follows me when I move.
It always watches. At night we hear noises coming from the walls. The first time I heard them,
I got happy because I thought it was you and mommy shouting for me, coming to save me, but it wasn't.
When the shouting starts, the others cover their ears, but I try and listen. I put my head against
the wall and hold my breath, but no matter how hard I try, I can't understand what they're saying.
They shout and cry a lot. It isn't mommy and it isn't you, but it sounds like adults and they
sound sad. Really sad. Did the Easter Bunny take them? Dana is dead. I thought that was a bunny.
Help me find an exit. Uh oh. Oh no.
Black light? Just a stupid black light. What am I going to do with this?
Oh, that's... I'm far back, aren't I? This video game is a genuine first generation copy
produced on behalf of and with the approval of... What is that?
Oh, that's just the intro. Fuck. All right. Oh shit. Where was I on this? I got the...
Oh fuck. All right, where was I? I don't remember. I gotta get the magnet from downstairs,
magnet from down in the basement, come up, get that, go upstairs, right? What do I mean? No,
fuck. I need the letter opener. Where's the letter opener? Letter opener is up. Oh,
letter opener. I need more pencils. All right. At least I know where he comes in.
That's not the wrong save, but I went down. We're going to watch Gary. Yeah. Okay,
letter opener, down to get the magnet, up. All right. I need to save the game again.
Okay, let's go. This is the right save. Okay, down, basement, letter opener, thing,
get the magnet, magnetize, save the game, and then whatever. Where's the fucking basement?
What game is this? This is Murder House. It's a house where people get murdered and you have to
solve the mystery. Where is it? It's in here, right? I only have three saves total. Should I
not use it? Should I try to get around the bunny and then save it after that? You just have to run.
You suck at this. It's a horror game. Come on. All right, so let me get out of here. Go upstairs.
Maybe I should just save it. Who cares? All right. I really don't want to do this again.
Your health is too low to fight. Maybe I'll just save it then and go upstairs.
Your health is too low. Do you have any potions or food? I don't think I do. Where do you get
heals? I have the thing that looks like I can heal. Okay, here we go. I'm just going to save
it. Whatever. If it's a bad idea, it's a bad idea. What are you guys doing? All right, let's go.
This time, I'm going to try just to run by. Let me scope out some areas here. All right, so what's
where's a good hiding spot? I could just probably kill him. Where's there a hiding spot in here?
Is there one? Is that? No. He's gone. What? Oh no, I need to take this. Why is he not here?
I'm confused. Why is he not here? Oh, that's back upstairs. Okay, what does that do? Does
that reveal anything? Can I hide in something here? No, where can I hide in here? It's very
important. Itchy face. It's a dumbwaiter. A rack of torture devices. Oh, I unlocked it. Okay,
I need to save the game. This is the door right here. I need to save the game. I told you. I knew
I was doing the right thing. Where is he? Why won't he walk over here? Why? Why won't you come over
here? I'm trying to lose him. Oh, fuck it. Let's go. Torture devices. Why does it keep doing that?
It's not even him. He visited again. No one saw him, but we woke up and there was a big basket of
eggs. I was so hungry. I need to take the wrapping off. We all took big bites, but the blonde girl,
when she took her bite, her mouth was covered in blood. She dropped the egg and inside the
chocolate, the Easter bunny had played a trick and put sharp razor blades. There was a lot of blood
and she wouldn't stop screaming and the wall started to laugh. Man, faster if you could. My
God. You got to be fucking kidding me, dude. This is fucked up. Long girl's gone. Gracie won't
stop staring at the big bunny on the wall. Randy says the chocolate eggs make us sleepy. Not going
to eat tonight. Randy told me to memorize this song. I don't know what he means. 8883-553-1212-10108.
Somebody write that down. Thank God. I just have to get out of here safely and I can save it again.
I'm going to be sick. Oh, okay. I got to get out of here. How do I get out of here? I actually need
to get out of here and go save. What's going on? What's going on? What's going on? What's going on?
Do I need to take this? Okay. I got to get out of here. Okay. Let's get out. Get out. Give me out.
Give me the fuck out of here. Okay. Get me the fuck out. Get me the fuck out of here.
Get me the fuck out. Get me the fuck out now. Get me the fuck out. Give me the fuck out. I'm
going for the head, by the way. I'm going for the fucking head. I'm going for the fucking head.
I got to get out. I got to save the game. Fight or flight. I'm going for the head. I'm literally
going for the head. I'm going to swing as hard as I can into the person's head. You know what I
mean? Just like I'm going to crow hop twice and go right to the head as hard as I can.
What the fuck? No, don't go into this weird chamber. Oh my God. Oh no. He's going to come
down. He's going to... Did he open the door? Oh my God. Go in the dumb waiter. Go in the dumb
waiter. Go, go, go, go, go, go. Huh? I couldn't go up the dumb waiter. I took it down. I took
the thing down. Oh, fuck that. Come on. Oh, shut up. Okay. Well, I know we come through there now.
Please do infomercials instead. Fuck. Now I got to go up and then down and then up and then down
and then left and then up and then down and down and then right and then... Oh, come on. Do I really
have to do all this again? No. Wait, where is this saved? Is this not the wrong save? No, it's not
the wrong save. All right. He dies up here and then I got to go down and then... Oh, fuck. I'm just
going to run. I'm going to run. I'm just going to run. I got freaked out that time because I thought
he grabbed me and I thought I was going to get in a death animation. Oh, this is fucked up. I got
to go upstairs. How come he's not here? All right. We go upstairs, do the black light, move the thing,
go down, get the... What was it? The rope or something? We go up here, do the black light,
move the thing, go down the dumb waiter, get the pencil, get the rope. You need to open the draws.
You already did this part. Yeah, I know. I know. This and then I just got to run. I'm just running.
This dude's accent is really exotic. Exotic. I barely have a Boston accent anymore. Sometimes.
What? Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Just get in,
just go in and just pick up the shit off the ground and then leave. Fuck out of the way.
What was in? There was something in here. There's a pencil, I think. Right? Yep. Okay. Get the pencil,
get the rope and then get out. Please say harbor. Yeah, I know you wanted me to say like harbor,
but I did that. Whatever. Leave. Then I'm just running through and I'm going... What do I need
to go from here? The save room. Okay. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Get me out. Out, out, out,
out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out. Nothing else. And I was running. Oh, wait,
was something in here? I forget. Was anything in here? No, it's just a note. Maybe I have to
have it read. Okay. All right. I fucking hate this. Here we go. You need to drink Coke starlight.
All right. So should I just run? I think I'm just going to run. Here we go. Run. Just run straight.
Run. Where the fuck am I going? What did I just do? Where's the up? Where's up? Where's up?
Where's up? Where's up? I need to go up. Where's up? Right here. Get me to the save point right now.
I need to save point. Oh my God. Tom's camera. I'm so stressed. Me too. What does it say? It
feels like somebody's holding the door shut. What are you talking about? What are you talking about?
I can't go in here. You got to be shitting me. I can't save the fucking game right now. You can't
be serious, right? You can't be serious. What am I supposed to do about this shit? Where am I?
Where's my character? Where's my character? Where's my character? This is the wrong room.
Oh my goodness. Are you okay? Gary's dead. What's this? An egg. I got to go to the TV room,
which was the room right next to this. Okay. Okay. All right. Give me out. Please don't be here. Oh,
fuck you. Okay. Was it, was there a number over there? Where's the room that has the TV in it?
It's this one here. I don't remember which one has the TV in it. I can't save the game. The door
is closed. Save? What do you mean save? The door is shut. Somebody's holding it shut. Oh, thank God.
This is just pure anxiety. Okay. At least I can save it. Now I'm not scared if I die. All right.
I got to go watch the TV. It's in the room that I was looking at before. Is it this one here?
What, what room is it? It's not this one. Is it down the hall? I don't remember where it is.
What's your favorite pizza? Stuffed crust from Pizza Hut. It's the best. Is it this one? Okay.
Here we go. I need to make sure I can hide somewhere. Can I hide under here? Can I hide in
here? No. I got to find a place where I can hide because I'm going to watch this tape and then this
asshole is going to come in this room. I can't, I need two people to move this. Okay. We're gonna,
I'm hiding right now because I just heard somebody crying. This motherfucker is probably coming up
here now. You didn't just open the door, right? Okay. Here we go. Let's run with the piano in the,
are you going to hide in the piano? Okay. Oh no, not Tom. Did he, did the killer hide something
in the piano? That piano room is the one with the fireplace. Where is that? I think it's upstairs.
This is the last egg. It's down on the stairs, the red door at the bottom of the stairs.
Okay. All right. All right. Okay. Okay. I don't have any saves. I wish I could just
save state right now. I must be in use the piano.
Super Mario eight, eight, eight, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
12, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12. That's an old McDonald. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh
God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. Oh God.
Hide. Hide. Hide. He's an Easter basket. Does it need more eggs than this? Oh fuck. Where do I go
from here? What should I do? What should I go? What should I do? What should I do? I'm hiding in
here. Is he here? What's that? Did I get there in enough time? I think I'm good. No, I didn't want
to come. I wanted to look at my menu. What do I have for items? I have rope. What if I take this
rope? Can I go outside and get the shotgun? Use the rope to get the shotgun, right? Like, yeah,
I think it's go get the rope with the scope, get the gun with the shirt with the go get the rope
with the shotgun. Help me. Right. Bod watchers sniff. I got to go up to the wardrobe. Can I
actually use the rope and pull the thing? Where is that? Oh my God. He's here. That's upstairs
in the room with the TV, right? I don't want to fuck around because I don't want to go all the
way back. That's upstairs room with television. I don't remember where that is though. My brain
just can't do it. Where is that fucking wardrobe? It's upstairs somewhere. Something else here?
Gun. Do I have any bullets in this gun? Excuse me. How do I use this? Okay. I have a gun now. Yes.
I can save it. Where am I going? I'm trying to go to move the wardrobe. I don't know where
that is, but we're going to go. It's the game is stressing me to fuck out. Save it. Save it
right now. I just don't know where the bunny is going to show up. It took him five minutes to
get here. I know, but I hate not. I hate not being able to save. I'm just doing it. I hate not being
able to save. Cry more. Is it? I think tie the rope around this and pull it down. Um, what the
hell is this bathroom? I'm not opening that yet. Search it. It's cabinet. How can it? Oh, band-aids.
Should I take those now? I'm at warning health sucker. I can recover some health. Am I don't,
I'm not going to take it till I'm red, right? I can take one more hit. I think. Okay. That's unlocked
toilet. Ooh, pencil. Good. Weird. Okay. All right. I'm going to open the curtain. Here we go. I'm
ready to shoot. Whatever's over here. Wait, unlock this too. Probably right. Yep. The real estate
agent. That's the last egg. The egg room was the piano room, right? I'm not saving it yet.
This didn't take that far to get here. Unlock the exit. You bastard. Now what do I do? Is there
anything I haven't checked? How do you reload the gun? How do I reload the gun? Is that eight or
three? How do I reload the gun? I'm saving it. It's a zero out of three. How do I reload? All right.
Third slot zero out of three. How do I use? How do I reload? So where's the exit then? I'm trying
to think of a door that didn't open. Is there an exit? Holy shit. I don't know where I'm going.
I just, I think I just walked in this way to go. No, put the fucking gun on, dude. Put the fucking
gun on. Get out of here. How do I get out of here? How do I get out of here? How do I get out of
here? Is he still chasing? Which way do I go? Don't run through the main entrance. That didn't work.
It's locked. We're stuck in here. Down into the basement. Okay. How do I get to the basement
from here? Okay. Got done. How do I get out of here? I get the fuck out of here. How do we get
out of here through here? It's open. This has bullets, right? This has bullets. It says zero
out of three, but how can I reload it? How do I reload the fucking gun? Zero out of three.
I need to reload the gun. Reload the gun. How do you reload the gun? Three is the max. Oh,
fuck. This is bad. Where's the shotgun? Where's the shotgun? It's here somewhere. Where is it?
Where's the shotgun? I'm going to blow this guy to hell. Where is it? Where's the shotgun?
There it is. Right? It has to be. Give me. Give me. Quick. This guy's dead. All right. Now get
me out of here and get me to the car. Where's the exit to the greenhouse? Am I supposed to know who
this is? Tom? That's right. It was quiet. Innocent, Tom. Harmless. Walk all over him, Tom. Mama's boy,
Tom. When I did, I killed them all. Why? To avenge my brother. Anthony wasn't the Easter Ripper.
I was. He turned himself in to save me. I thought I could control the urge to kill,
but it's back. And now I'm going to kill you. Tom. Tom. I have a shotgun in my hands and you're
holding a sickle. You want to do the math there real quick? Oh my God. Don't die. Oh no. Why won't
he die? I shot him four or five times with a shotgun. What? He's bulletproof. What the hell
was that? Give me a break. What was that bullshit? All right. So what do I do? Wait, wait, wait.
Where am I right now? I just have to go down to the dumbwaiter. Just go down to the basement.
Right? I still have heal. I'm not going to use it. Down to the basement and then out.
Just like I was before. Yeah. Let's get out of here. Just get out. There's all the eggs. Okay.
Out. Have you tried talking it through with them? You can find more ammo. I think I'll be all right.
Fucking don't know. I still don't know where the hell I'm going down here. I need to hit him with
the... Okay. Get me out. I need... I have a heal. I'm not going to waste it. If I need to fire poker,
I'll just swing and run. I have a heal. I'm not going to use it yet. I can take one hit from the
sickle. Stop touching your nose. I'm a weirdo, man. I'm going to be touching my face. Give me
the shotgun. I can't... No, dude. I wasn't ready to leave. What are you doing? I'm not ready. I was
trying to walk over. Why? God damn it, Tom. Oh my goodness. I'm just getting stuck on everything.
Tank controls are the shittiest things ever. Just get the fuck out of my way, Tom. What happened?
Oh my God. Tank controls are the stupidest fucking things on earth.
Just kill me. Fucking please. Just kill me. Oh my God. Tank and... Fucking God. I'm going FPS.
I don't give a fuck for this. I'm just going FPS. I'm going to FPS this guy. Hold on. Let me play a
video game. Damn motherfucker. Why is auto aim turned off? I don't know. I'm going fucking FPS.
I don't care. You can call skill issue all you want. I ain't... No. I'm sorry. That was weird.
I'm going FPS. And I'm going to auto aim. And I'm going to get rumbled in here. Okay. I don't give
a shit. Let's go. I'm ready. Melania didn't make you this mad. Yeah. Well, Melania also... Melania
also, I don't have to run through half a fucking level to get to... Where's my... There it is. Down
to the basement. You need to start with a summon. I'm fine. Okay. Let's go. Let's go. I'm not using
mouse and... Wait. Should I use mouse and keyboard for this? All right. Mouse and keyboard. What the
fuck? No. It's weird. I don't like it. It's weird. I don't like it. It's weird. Okay. Don't go that
way. Go over here. Give me the shotgun. I'm going to shoot this guy four times and I'm going to beat
the fuck out of him with this wrench or whatever the hell this is. Okay. Come on. Where is he?
That's right. To avenge my brother. Get out of the venue. Swing. I had another round. I did, man.
I had another shotgun shell. It wouldn't shoot. I had another shot. I did. Do the math. God damn
it. Where can I get some more bullets? He's not going to show up, right? If he does, then whatever.
I'm going to get bullets. Somebody sit in the attic. I need bullets. There are draws here for the
letter opener. You shitting me. Where? Where? I don't see any. Where? No. I don't see any. Where?
In the corner and a pencil. That's like a washing machine. Where? Where? You full of shit.
You said in the basement. There's more ammo. The attic in the basement. I thought you said attic,
not basement. You said attic. Anywhere else I could look. That was hot. That was a hot slice
of pizza. There's nothing in here. Only ammo is in the basement at the end of the hallway.
Are you kidding me? Did I already get it though? I feel like I already did it. In the basement.
I already get it. In the basement at the end of the hall. You're full of shit. I found it.
What is that? Oh, this is a big first aid kit. Oh, that's not what I want. Basement at the end
of the hall. Use the bandages. Bandages. Okay. You're telling me there's ammo down here. Is
that what you're saying? You're telling me there's ammo down here. That's what you said to me. What
do you want about? I need help. You need to tell me. I walked by it. No help. No help. No help. No
help. We said the attic. It's down in the actual dungeon. Well, I need to go down there anyways.
This one here. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. I just got to go. I got to go. I'm
just leaving. I'm just going to go. I don't need to save it. Fuck it. He's right here. All right.
I've got pistol. I've got full health pack and I've got everything I need. All right. Pistol,
full health pack and a shotgun coming up. You do the math. We're going to start with the pistol.
It's eight shots and then we're going to move to shotgun to finish it. I have a full health pack.
I should not fuck this up. Okay. Here we go. Bang, bang. I can take that if I need to. I'm ready.
Here we go. Eight shots. I'm going to run first of all. I'm going to get across the whole map.
What the fuck are you doing?
How many was that? Eight? How many was that? I got one more shot.
What the heck? Did I win? That was too... I don't like games like that. It's just too
trust. It's too stressful. It's too stressful. That was pretty, that was pretty crazy.
That was too stressful. Well, there you go. The info of that was murder house and then
blood wash. You aged 20 years playing that. Is there a new game plus? I'm going to wait
to see if there's anything after credits. You know what else I was looking over at the mod chat too?
There's those, the dread collection. I haven't done any of those. It's kind of like a jackbox
horror game party pack. I could probably do those at some point. Play Nunn Massacre. I already did
and I kind of said I'm never coming back to it. Yeah, there's five of them or something, right?
Dodge caravan sliding door dot wave by CGFX. Unlock and lock a door with key.
Page turn. Draw slam two. When did I play Nunn Massacre? I think that was when I did all the
Itch.io games, right? Yeah, I think we could probably call... Maybe I'll play... Vampire
Survivors got an update, right? Somebody's saying that. Maybe I'll play a round of that.
Wind down with some Vampire Survivors and then call it. That sounds good. What do they add?
It's a hell of an update. Really? There's a... We're still in the credits. You should play Stay
Out of the House. If you have... I said a few weeks ago that if you have a one to three hour long
horror experience that you want me to play, throw it in the recommended in the discord
because I feel like I missed all these. It's a long credit sequence. It really is. System Shock?
Ah, maybe not. Yeah, play Stay Out of the House. Okay. Do you even read that channel? I'd say once
every week or two, probably once every two or three weeks, I will just open discord solely to
look at the recommended channel. Tons of stuff I pulled over the last year from there. I go,
oh, okay, that seems pretty cool. So I check it all the time. I really do. I might not be that
active on discord, but I check that channel a lot whenever, you know, every few weeks.
I kind of just scroll back. What about the comments on the second Jerma videos? I will tell you I
don't think I've read a YouTube comment, goodness, in probably five years. It's been a long time.
I don't think I've read a YouTube comment in five years. Go read them now. Holy shit, did 500 people
work on this? This is crazy. There's a lot of people. I think it was good. I love this old PS1
aesthetic. I'm glad it came back. Did you play Soma? Yeah, one day. This is, oh, it's Patreon.
Okay. For a second, I thought we were still in, okay, all right, it's Patreon. Okay. I was like,
holy shit, a lot of people worked on this. Didn't you say that you hated it like three weeks ago?
Soma? What do you mean? I said I hated Soma? Go reply to a YouTube comment from 2020.
I don't think so. I want to see if there's anything at the end here. I'm very curious.
New squirrel stapler. What about Bloodborne PSX? I don't think I'll ever play it. That's really cool.
But I played so much Bloodborne that I feel like I wouldn't like it. I feel like I would play that
and be, I just want to play the regular Bloodborne. It's really short. How is it short? Is it the whole
game? It's not the whole game. Oh, I thought it was just a, it's not the whole game. Oh, it's its own
thing. What? Okay. I didn't know that. I'm going to look into that now. I thought it was the whole
game. Okay. All right. All right. Anything after the credits? Cut. Brilliant. Congratulations, guys.
That's a wrap. A wrap? That ending doesn't make any sense. Well, it's a wrap anyway. Oh, it was
just a horror movie. It was just a horror movie? Can I put the mic down now? Clapping the clapper
is my job. All day. Clap, clap, clap. It's enough to drive you crazy. Okay. I would hate to have to
edit this piece of shit. What do you think? I think it's stupid. Hey, how would I know Nick
would skip town two days before we wrapped up the shoot? But Tom, he's not even tall enough to be
to kill it. Don't worry about it. No one's going to notice. What? What's in the house? What's in
the attic? Pizza. Any more pizza? No, your buddy Dan finished it up. I'm starving. There's plenty
of gelatin salad. Yeah, I'll think about that. It's not that bad. Gelatin salad? Is that? Wait,
why is there blood here then? Is it fake blood? Maybe what happened to Nick, huh? Who? The guy
who played the Easter Ripper. Oh, that guy? He was a weirdo. He didn't say anything to me the whole
shoot. Easter Ripper costumes. Okay. So what's in the basement then? Anything in the basement?
Save the game? I don't think I need to. It's post credits. Okay. So what's down here? Skeletons?
Yeah. Thank you. It took me so long to pose them. So what the heck? What am I supposed to do? What
am I going to do? Tuber commentary? This would be a pretty shitty tuber commentary. I'm just going
like this. Where do I go? Do I go down? Where do I go? This would be pretty awful with tuber commentary.
Oh, can I get a poll in chat? I need to get a poll in chat from a mod. When you brush your teeth,
dude, sometimes you go, it's very important. Do you gag? I guess. I don't know. Not every time,
but sometimes you just kind of go like, and I'm not talking like crazy. That was a little too
too much. I don't mean like, I mean very lightly, just like a, no, guys, you don't brush your teeth
and go, oh my God. I'm not talking about like this. Why can I not open this thing? I'm not talking
about going like, no, I'm talking about like when you brush your tongue. I'm not sitting there
brushing my teeth and I was puking. That'd be weird. What do you mean you don't brush your tongue?
Oh, we've got some people in this chat with some fucking stank ass breath. You don't brush your
tongue? Okay. I don't know what I'm supposed to be looking at here. What? There's nothing here.
Brush your tongue. I just, I not, you don't have to do it. Fine. That's fine. But I brush my tongue
because yeah, you can have like smelly breath. Go to the front door. What was in the attic?
20% of chatters. Hold on. Do you brush your tongue? You don't, don't, I'm not talking to go crazy.
It's just very light, but maybe that would explain why maybe 20% of you don't go,
but even the people that do brush their tongue, I feel like that's maybe you say, I do, I do
brush my tongue, but dude, why, what are you doing? But sometimes you're in a fucking hurry.
Sometimes it's like, oh, I got to brush my teeth, but I got something to do. So I got somewhere to
be real quick. Come on, come on, come on, come on. Okay. All right. Go, go, go. Rinse, rinse, rinse,
rinse, rinse. Sometimes it happens. I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing here. Something's
supposed to happen. Somebody's missing. You need to go to bed. I'm going to play one round of vampire
survivors. I don't know where to go. Do you guys have a, I'm not reading that one. Okay. Well,
that was cool. I can't, I, it's cut off, but I think it's when wiping your ass. Can you imagine
somebody is, Hey man, I'll be right back. I'm going to take a shit. Yeah. I'm just going to
use your bathroom for a little bit. And they leave. You just hear it's like, holy shit. Like,
what do you mean? Are you like, you're wiping your ass and are you like puking or like gagging
because it smells? I'm 36 and we're going to move on. Okay. It smells so bad in the bathroom that
you're gagging to your own business, dude. Okay. I'm 36 this time. We have to move on. I can,
this is ridiculous. This is a ridiculous conversation to have. Do I just walk home?
Where do I go? Just in the bathroom taking a shit. What are you doing? Rehearsing for my next role.
What's that? Bikini babes on werewolf planet. I play queen Zion. Except you want to help with the
part. Sure. Queen Zion. People are realizing you're 36.
Isn't it in my info? I should put it in my info.
You think I'm a fool? Take their bikinis. You'll have to settle for just
a bit. What do you think? You're great. You look 26. It's wild. It's called I
moisturize. I moisturize my skin. Everybody says question mark. What are you talking about? When
I come out of the shower, brush my teeth, I dry my hair, I shampoo and condition at least once,
twice a week. You don't be careful not to shampoo too much, but I usually do. So when I come out of
the shower, dry off and I use, you want to know what I use? Would you like to know? You want to
know what I use? You want to know what brand I use? Is that what this is? Yeah. Okay. Okay. Fine.
Sure. I use the, it's, it's called the belief cream and it's called the Aqua bomb. You can get
it at Sephora. I've been using it for fucking a decade almost every day. I'm not shit. I'm not
kidding. It's the belief cream. It's called the Aqua bomb. It's this light. This is, that was
blinking for a second and you just do a little bit. It's really light. It's kind of like a gel
and this is how, when you're 40, you'll look fucking 25. Damn it. I look good. How do I leave
the trailer? You're 40? Not yet. Okay. So how do I get it through this? It's nighttime,
$40 moisturizer. Everybody shut up. That moisturizer will last you a very long time,
an incredibly long time. This is not, you don't open the container and smear it like, like pick
it up like this and then drag it all over your face. You didn't use the whole bowl.
You do a dab. You open up the container. You take your ring finger or your middle finger,
just a little bit, and then get it on the cheekbones right here under the eyes. Don't
put it in your eyes. Are you crazy? Come up here onto the forehead, on the nose, the chin,
and then cleanly smear it around in a semi-circle. You're not going like this and drenching your
face. No, that will last you two, three months. And guess what? Taking care of your skin,
the biggest organ. I bet you didn't know this. You're a scientist. It's the biggest organ in
your whole body. You got to take care of it. It's the biggest organ in your whole body.
You should be taking care of it. Bet you didn't know that. I'm going to quit the game because I
don't know what to do. If you don't want me to quit the game and see the last bit of the ending,
just tell me where to go. The other trailer. What's wrong with you? Too many pizzas.
How many did you eat? Three. Slices? No, pizzas. I was bored. Not much left to do since I died.
Oh, thank God. Maybe someone could give me a ride into town off this hell set.
Yeah, skincare. Take care of your skin. You know people really got killed in this house.
That's just a rumor. Watch how much sun you're getting. It's nice to get sun, but just be
careful how much sun you're getting. You know, you don't want to be out there just cooking. Use
a good moisturizer. No one cares. I do. I need a hot shower after this sleazy picture. I do.
I do. All right, so that was fun. That was fun. I'm going to just leave now. Go to the car.
What temperature are your showers? I wouldn't say too hot. Not too hot. Not too cold. Hot, hot,
hot showers. They kind of make me feel weird. I don't like it. I don't have my keys. I must
have dropped them somewhere. Oh, where are my keys? The keys are in the basement. Somebody said I'm
literally buying that. I don't like moisturizers that are really heavy, greasy. Cream. It's not a
cream. It's a light gel cream. It's not what you think. It's not one of those. Nope. It's light.
You're giving ads for free. I don't care. I've talked about things that I use in company. I can't
just say that I like something. Somebody has to pay me to tell you that I like a product. That's
not going to happen. I mean, if they do. All right. Where are these keys? That's not a requirement
in the basement. I'm in the basement. Where are these keys? Come on. Come on, Gwen. Really?
For here? In the dungeon? When are you going to do a skincare stream? Do you know where my keys are?
So much to do down here. There are my keys. Hey, hey, hey. What are those? What are those
brown slacks called? Oh, they're called cockies. How do you drive your car off with fucking cockies?
Could have been playing vampire survivors. Smash the desk. Okay. Bye guys. It was fun making the
movie. I really hope it's not a real killer that comes out and grabs me. Let's party. Did you guys
have to ruin all of these costumes? You shouldn't have eaten any gelatin salad. You're weird for
eating it in the first place. I shot about 30 slashing movies this year. All that hard work
finally paid off. I feel like I would be dancing like this too. That was a fun party. All right.
Goodbye. That was a fun party. What? Oh, I'm not cleaning up. I'm sorry. If you are at the party,
then you clean up. If I walk through the party to say goodbye, I am not obligated to clean up the
party. That's not how that works. If I'm not participating in the party, then I'm not going
to clean up the party. Oh my God. Look at the backseat. What is that? Oh my goodness. I'm so
nervous. I did. Okay. We did. I did. I could have just ended like 30 minutes ago. All right. Let's
do vampire survivors. That was a good game. That's fun. I actually enjoyed that. Give me one second
while I open up vampire survivors.