What? What? The lone cow and the endless plains. What are you doing out here, man? Don't look at me like that.
I'm gonna mess you up, cow. Eat the raw meat. Eat the raw meat. Alright, let's go. I got leather.
And jump with joy because we're going to a crazy awesome theme park. We're going to the carnival.
Going to the carnival. We're going to the carnival. I can't contain my excitement for the carnival.
Okay, that's enough. Oh my god, I'm so excited. We're gonna go play carnival games.
Welcome to Woosh Games theme park. At the entrance of every game, you'll find descriptions.
What am I doing? Why am I like, I'm like looking, I can't, how do I get back to first person?
It's F, it's like F5 twice. Oh, okay, because I was like looking at myself like a bird.
Alright, so what's the rules? Alright, each, ow. Why you do that, man? I don't know. Read the rules, man.
Alright, you read the rules. I'll look. Did you, are you making the piano chirp? No. Do you hear that?
There's a bird in here. Is this like the clerk? Oh, he's the one doing it.
Like, can I order a double cheeseburger? Alright, cooked chicken, steak, or cake?
Uh, no double cheeseburgers. Goodbye. Goodbye, McCrafty's.
I'm taking a cake. So do you just want to start, start and go down the row?
Let's just go down the row, man. Let's do it.
Alright, ride your pig, make it step on the plates so your opponent will be shot. If you kill his pig, you win.
Red and blue lines are for the players to spectate, follow the orange line.
Alright, you're blue. You take the blue line, you just follow that line. Egg.
Okay, so we can hit the pigs, just don't kill your pig, man.
So the goal is we're trying to kill each other's pigs, right? Right, the first person whose pig dies loses.
Well, I hope you're ready to get destroyed. Oh, he's right here. Ride the pig and press I am ready to start.
There's like, how come there's more, there's like three pigs down here? Man, you are cheating hardcore.
How many pigs? I don't have any pigs down there.
Kill that pig that's in that pen.
Oh, now I've got another pig. Okay, now it's even.
So how do you put the saddle on the pig? You just right click the pig with the saddle.
I can't do it. He's like, he won't let me. I'm on my pig.
He's like, this is not, oh, there we go. Okay, I'm on it.
And push the button. Ready? I am ready. Go.
Uh oh, my pig, my stealthy pig jumped up on top of the mop, so did yours.
Wait, let's go pig. Oh, there we go. I'm down. I'm down. I punched him.
Oh, I punched my two. Okay, we got to make him step on the pressure plates.
Come on pig, me and you. Me and you pig.
Kill him. Kill his pig. Yeah, come on pig.
Get out of the corner. My pig is hiding in the corner.
Did you kill your pig?
Hey, looks like you won. Oh, it looks like I did win.
Well, I still have this pig. Not for long.
The next one. Next game on the menu is piston boxy. Boxy.
Why not? I got to throw some trash away.
I got some like raw meat to throw away.
Yeah, I got like a ton of arrows to throw away.
It's just like fire. Lava trash cans.
What a practical. Oh, here's your trash cans. It's just actually a lava pit.
We need some more recycling cans around here.
Make sure like your kid doesn't crawl in there.
All right. Okay, two players need it.
Avoid punches. Knock your opponent down.
Red boxer, brown boxer.
It doesn't really matter to me. I'll go brown.
Take your pick. So we're supposed to box each other?
We're going to be pushing some kind of buttons to box.
So it's like rock-em-sock-em robots, except not.
All right, so I think I understand. Rock-em-sock-em robots.
Okay, fight. Fall into the white blocks is what it says. Okay.
I'm in some sort of arena now. So I see you over there.
All right. So I think we have to punch each other.
Whoever wins, wins, right?
Apparently by pushing these buttons on the left and right.
You ready? Ready? Go.
Oh, I'm going to dodge him.
Oh, no, that was coming. No, no. Oh, damn it.
I don't know. I think you went off first.
Oh, I did go off first. God darn it.
All right. Game number three is a PvP game.
Players needed at least two dodge arrows.
Shoot your opponent. You want to read the rules?
Welcome to dodge ball.
It's like playing dodge ball, but instead of a ball,
you shoot flaming arrows that will push the opponent against lava.
How terrible.
The player who dies loses the game by pressing the pressure plate.
You get bonus items. Okay.
So the yellow line is for people to watch.
All right. Don't leave your side.
I don't want to see cheating from you.
Oh, hey now.
I resent that slap on my face.
All right. Have fun.
Are you ready? Do it.
Okay. Here we go. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Are we still taking the armor?
I'm still taking the armor.
All right. All right. All right. I feel you.
Okay. I got this.
I got to like hide from you because I don't know what you're doing.
Yeah, I see you. I see you.
Oh, damn. I don't think so.
No. Peek around that corner.
Don't hide. Hide, hide, hide, hide, hide, hide, hide.
See? Oh, give me this.
Oh, golden apples.
What? What is going on?
No. Eat the apple. Eat the apple.
No. Eat the apple.
Don't. Quit right clicking, you idiot.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
See, I was trying to save.
I can see your feet.
That's the French part.
Hold on. I was trying to save.
Oh, God. Eat the apple. Eat the apple.
Oh, shit.
You see, I was trying to save time by just shooting at you.
I didn't put any armor on.
So I was trying to sneak attack and shoot you before you put on all your armor.
That was so funny.
Didn't work out so well, though.
As you can see.