Do I seriously have to immediately stop playing this game? Because of me having to vomit?
Alright, well let's just get...
Oh no. No. You can't even see everything. It's like 2D on 3D.
Like, I have no depth perception. I can't even tell what... am I close to this thing or am I far away from it? Let's find out.
I guess I was pretty close. Okay, let's just go this... can I jump?
Oh, okay I can jump.
Sick jump. What the hell is that?
What the fuck are those things?
What are these, like, little muppet things? These little, like, weevils?
Can these hurt me?
It's...
Okay, can I jump on them?
I don't think so.
Come on, last try.
Okay, it's very evident that I can't do anything with these things.
These, like, daffy duck green, like, mob and mosh and things, alright?
Let's just keep going. Apparently I touched him again.
I love how... did you guys hear that?
Aren't these game designers wonderful?
Is what that thing just said. Aren't these game designers wonderful?
I think that was a joke. That was a pretty good joke.
Considering this game probably gave horrible nightmares to a bunch of kids that played it.
I never played this back in the day.
I don't even know... did this ever even release? I don't even remember this being on store shelves.
Good grab. Oh, good animations.
Can I jump over this wall?
What are the point of these enemies if they can't move?
What the fuck was that?
He's, like, spitting at me like a Jurassic Park spitter.
Get me out of here.
Get that spitter away from me.
Oh, I'm invincible.
Oh my god.
How am I supposed to move this? Can I grab this rocket?
Can I even change the camera?
Dude, is this thing moving very slowly?
I feel like it is, but I have no perception at all.
So I don't even know what's happening. I don't even know if anything's even going on.
If I'm gonna run into this rocket and see what happens.
What? I have one really important question for you guys.
You don't have to answer it if you don't want to, but I just really need to...
Need a clip. Good clip. Need a clip.
You like that clip? Need a clip.
Hi, Gemma. I didn't get the joke.
Star! Hey, everybody, Star is in the video!
Whoa! Whoa!
My, like, parents are, like, yelling down here.
They think I'm, like, in trouble.
Hold on a second. This might be funny.
This could be, like, pretty funny.
Come on, come down here. Aren't you concerned that your, like, son just got in trouble?
Whoa!
No!
Game over! Fuck you, game over!
Need a clip? Good clip.
Do you want to continue?
Uh, I kind of have to continue because I need a clip.
Want to continue? Good to continue.
Good to continue. Need to continue? Good to continue.
Oh, I know all the strats. You see, now I can speedrun this.
World record's going to be two minutes and 35 seconds.
There it is. Look at that.
That's what we call a speedrun. See?
I wanted to do that because I could jump down.
Speedrun. This way.
Touch that arrow because, you know, it gives you an extra one up.
Go this way. That's my split.
All right, I'm 20 minutes ahead of the world record. Let's go.
Okay, it goes right... Oh, my God. I'm going to beat the world record.
Jeremy, are you okay?
What's happening down there?
Are you in trouble? Are you sick?
Is the dog okay?
No, Mom. It's okay. I'm just playing Bubsy 3D.
The shittiest game I've ever played.
Oh, okay. Well, I'm glad.
And is that the Chester Cheeto on the screen?
No, Mom.
Chester Cheeto. It's Bubsy.
The lovable Bubsy. Oh, I've never seen that cartoon.
It's not a cartoon, Mom.
Geez.
See what you just made me do, Mom?
He just appeared.
That guy just, like, appeared.
Or I'm an idiot. I'm not sure.
Well, you should have been... Mom, you don't have to be a backseat gamer, okay?
I know what I'm doing.
See, I have to go this way. I'm still...
I'm going to, like, puke.
So, those of you that are asking why this video ends up being, like, four or five minutes,
it's because I'm out for your sake.
I don't want you to puke.
Because, like, I'm going to puke.
In fact, I think I already did puke.
I just, like, cut the video. You saw that cut.
I puked. All right? You want to know the truth?
I fucking puked.
Whoa!
Right when I talk about puking.
Oh, stop doing that and just wait and be patient.
That thing is making so much noise.
Can I please just be level one?
If I complete level one, I'll be happy.
Just wait it out. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, go.
I think I just beat level one.
Nice, like, cutscene.
Whoa, this is getting wacky.
Whoa!
He got squashed.
Did you see that, guys? Bubsy just got squashed.
Let's move on to level two.
And by move on to level two, I mean, like, end the video.