Good afternoon. How are you doing? This moment's going down in history.
It's the second time I've ever sworn off a Mario Maker game in one day.
I got a lot of heat for this one. People say in German, you said
Mario Maker, you said you've never played ever again and you you hated it.
I didn't hate the game, but I mean I did say that, but this is Mario, this
is a different game. This is Mario Maker 2.
Not the same game. Yeah okay so I swore this is a bit different video game.
It's the same game. No it's not. They added Super Mario 3D world levels.
Sorry so much research you've done. Wow.
What really? I was under the assumption that everybody like loved
Super Mario. What happened? What happened?
Nobody likes Super Mario anymore? All right give me one second.
All right so we're gonna do this for a little while.
And I don't know if it's fun. We'll keep doing it. If not then
I got no plan man you know. He came back. Yeah of course I came back.
So let's go. I mean why not right? Here it is.
I've only got 335 seconds remaining. Oh wait I have to do an audio test
with you guys. Hold on let me just test the audio.
Make sure this is synced up. All right ready?
I'm gonna jump and I'm gonna grab the coin. Ready?
Now got. How we doing? Jump jump jump jump jump.
Are we synced? I think that should be good. Should be is the right
question. My voice is low. Hold on. I did do some messing around with my
audio. So let me see if I fuck something up.
Better? I think I think that's better. I don't think I was messing around
with audio bits. I should be louder now. All right
So anyways I don't I don't know anything about this.
I didn't watch the direct. They did a whole direct about here comes
Super Mario Maker 2. Get excited for it.
I didn't watch it. All I know is that they just made another one.
Is there anything I need to know? This is yeah this is all fresh to me.
Completely fresh. He doesn't know. Well I opened this and I made an
account. I ain't gonna make a level by the
way guys. You think you're gonna get that on this stream? You are out of
mind. So there's a campaign. Should I play the campaign?
There is a campaign. Well it wasn't easy but we finally finished the castle.
Yeah out of this this is messing with my immersion. Mario's a plumber. He's
not a construction worker. Couldn't have done it without you
Chief Princess Peach. He'll be thrilled. Mario's not a construction worker. He's a carpenter. He's a plumber.
They changed that. Yes he was a carpenter back in the in the in the
original but this is 2019 Mario. The resort reset rocket lying around.
It wasn't me Chief. Pretty sure it was
the dog. Is it a dog? New character. Oh it's the dog. I can't make a name
up right now. It's Marshmallow. No that's like a
it's a dude that like makes like EDM music.
Get off the button. What the hell is going on? Okay see this is why I'm a cat
person. All right so all that hard work just
gone. See this is why I'm a cat person.
I can't believe it. Princess Peach's castle.
We have to rebuild it but we've used up our entire budget. This is
really bad. Oh too bad you can't say like
your problem. Leave it to me I'll handle it.
I guess I'll handle it. Of course why did I think of that? You can collect
enough coins for us to rebuild. With help we can make an even bigger
and better castle than before. Go see if the task master can scrape
together a few jobs for you. I need funding. Mario secures funding.
Okay I wasn't eavesdropping or anything but I kind of sort of
overheard your entire conversation with Chief.
Lucky for us I got a line on some jobs from around the world.
If you complete enough jobs we should be able to make enough coins to rebuild
the whole castle. I gotta say no one you're gonna
single-handedly fund this entire construction effort really takes the
pressure off me you know. Okay no time to waste check out this
job from someone named uh Goomba Lover. Most of these clients
don't use their real names. I don't ask too many questions
as long as they cough up the coins. Got like what would this
okay never mind. Downhill battle 100 coins.
I made a course full of Goombas. First one to get the gold pole
gets paid. Here's a tip tilt down on the downward slopes to wipe out the
Goombas. My Goomba Lover. This guy get off
to this? Is that what's going on here? I don't
understand. All right let's do it. I'm already big can I get a big guy?
Yeah I can. Oh it's been so long since I've played Super Mario.
What's what I believe in you. What do you mean? This is probably the
best song that they've ever made either.
Either I mean ever. So do I have to collect the coins or
do you just get the coins? That's a secret hold on.
No wait okay this is the panic button. Every time you get a star you have to
go panic mode. If I die on the first level I'm going
to stop playing again. Just make sure I want you guys to be very aware of
that. If I die on the first fucking Goomba
Lover level I'm going to... okay we're good.
You can't die. Yes you can if I walk into the Goombas twice.
Collected payment. Did they take this shit from
Mario Odyssey? We have to get like a currency and pay?
All right so let's play the foundation. Do I have enough money?
Did you get some coins? Yes I do. Oh you do. It does add to your balance.
Mario Odyssey invented currency. No but I like how you had to pay the
currency to make the ship better and fly. I have to pay the currency to
build the castle back. Yeah okay. Choose foundation to put in
the work order. Do I get to make my own castle?
You sure about that? No I'm not sure. Just keep it leveled.
Let's work out of a tent from now on. Do I have to tap the screen really fast?
Construction has started on the foundation. We'll keep working while
you're off making moola. So get out there and do some more
jobs. I got three new jobs for you. All right a word of advice from old
Taskmaster Toad. You can run the same job as many
times as you want. You won't get paid for it again.
But you get coins that you pick up.
Now back to work. Some new jobs just came in.
On-off switch research expedition. These are these are
I wouldn't eat here. All right on-off switch.
Might as well just do them in order. Hmm the on-off switch. No one really
knows how it actually works. Wireless protocols. Ancient magic. Get
to the end of this course and reward you handsomely.
Dr. Gizmo. Good luck out there big red.
This is a new style. Hold on on. Oh that's how the on-off switch works
guys. In just a case you didn't know. One two three. All right I'm done
playing. I'm gonna like stream myself eat a burrito.
Like I don't think I want to do this anymore. Um that was quick.
Trap him. Oh fuck I can't die here otherwise I have to fucking delete my
account.
Do you guys think that that's a joke?
Okay when I when I'm done. When I'm when I'm fucking done and I mean done
with Twitch YouTube don't matter right.
I'm gonna do that one day. I'm just gonna be like you know what yeah if I
die here I'm deleting my account and I'm gonna die and I'm gonna delete
my account and you'll never see me again.
Got him. Well I need those coins. Too icy.
What's happening right now? Why is everything this is happening today?
You guys are acting like I'm doing this in an hour. Hold on wait.
There's a secret down here I think. This is a secret.
Fuck I can't get it. Super coin. How do I get down there?
I'm gonna keep it off. I found it. Check this out.
Now it's not blocked. Now it. Wait. Oops. It's all right. I. Now.
Let's go. Can't go up. This is gonna be weird. Check this out.
No no no no. Stay in there. Can it just kill me? Will I get teleporter exited
if I stand there? Let's test it. Nope. Got it. I'm gonna do that every
single time. So you may as well leave now if you
don't want to hear that again. You're not gonna win enough for that
to happen. So I asked this in the pre-stream chat.
Did they get rid of the 100 Mario thing? Is there still expert difficulty?
Is it still regular? Just normal? How did they do that?
I need two more. I kind of like this. What's going on? Once we finish the
foundation the real work begins. This is kind of fun.
All right so we got hello 3D world. I've played at all these cute trees in my
garden. Would someone try reaching the goal by climbing the trees with up?
I haven't weeded the garden in a while but if the piranha plants give
you trouble just stomp them into the dirt.
Okay. You don't have to read this. It's Mario.
Why wouldn't I read it? I'm just gonna skip it?
Why wouldn't I read that? Did I just say
I am so in love with this teaser of Diablo 3
image screenshot here? Some of you guys are gonna know what I'm talking
about. Stomp them, right? How do you stomp?
Like that. Oops. What the fuck am I on?
It sounds like you got it. I don't need to explain everything.
People get mad at me when I explain the reference. They go we know we know
and I go what the fuck? Climb the tree.
That's cool. Can I do the double triple jump?
So I'm a casual fucking fan. Not even. I'm not even a fan.
Some people would probably mad at me knowing that this is the
the last Mario game that I actually opened and played
was Mario Maker 1. On top of that before that
you have to go back to Mario Galaxy 1.
Am I a cat? Oh the internet's gonna love this one.
Can I do anything else with the cat? You just scratch.
Wait a minute. How do I get that? Whatever.
Hey big bro if you're having trouble with the course use some assist parts.
Oh shit there he is. It's Luigi. He's showing up already. I can't wait
till the next time I die and it goes don't cry. Give the controller to your
older brother. I can't do Mario. Don't worry don't cry.
Okay I gotta attack that with the cat.
I didn't know I could do that. I didn't know. When was this? Have they ever
used this suit before? Wait you can climb walls as the cat?
What? I need you. No I want to jump. I want to jump his head. Hold on.
You can sprint faster as the cat too. That's I don't need anymore. I don't need
anymore. He's not reading chat. Why I can't how
am I gonna read chat and play this incredibly incredibly intense game?
I can actually climb this too. Oh it has the cat curtains. I get it.
That's cute. How do I get these?
No no don't do it again. I'm all right. Funner.
Funnest. What is this? I don't care. What is that even for?
Oh shit. Hold on. Get rid of those. All right so can I can I climb that wall?
Does it have to be a specific cat wall?
Oh he falls off. So what uh Mario was this one from?
Climb it. No not climb. Climb that. This is fun. Cat's really hot right now.
That's because I played Super Mario Galaxy 1
10 years ago and I just admitted that on the internet.
So I may as well have like strangled three people.
All right got the foundation. Two foundations. I haven't owned one since
the Game Boy days. Relax. There's like some.
Oh nice gazebo. Castle's gonna be rock solid.
Okay let's get this castle rebuilt. Where do you want to start?
Oh I don't know. West hall. Main hall. East hall.
What do you guys think? West. I mean what I what I what I was about to
say. Who cares? I would be so desperately
reaching for a reason at this point. Well I used to live on the East
Coast but now I live on the West Coast. Who cares?
What does that have to do with anything? But wait a minute. What about the one in
the middle? I need more coins. Why do you hate these games? What? I
don't hate these games. What? Where are you getting this? I'm gonna do
another job. I'm not. I can't make a decision.
Talk to the chief whenever you complete part of the castle.
Should we have something new for you to build? No the question. Why do you
guys hate this game? When I told you I was playing Mario Maker 2 it was
like oh oh oh really?
Let's do this one. There's one guy. No it was at least three.
How many are there? Like 3,000 people there? At least three of you. Sorry that's
like that's 10 percent. Well that's like 0.1 that's 0.01
percent. So that's like pretty I mean that I mean that's as much
that was you. No. Hold on. Today in the desert expect clear skies all day
with a chance of solar flares. There's an excessive heat warning in
effect from sunrise to sunset. So don't forget to slather on a thick
layer of sunscreen before stepping outdoors.
Either that or find a propeller and press R to avoid the burn.
Cool. The angry sun level is tricky. Time to be a god gamer.
All right which one is R? I haven't played this switch in like a year.
That's not it. That's not it. It actually flies down at you too. I'll
get it. I remember this from Mario 3. What's this thing? I've got like a
bozo hat on? Oh right and now I've seen this
before. I know what this one's like. How's this tricky? Oh wait it is
gonna get tricky here. Come on come on. This is part of the
secret up here or something. There's like a super coin up there.
It's not even tricky. Shit. No no I need that.
There's 10 in there. It's a distraction. Oh god.
Thank god I got the fucking oh shit. No and I okay I bumped my desk and it
did that. Oh my god it bumped the desk. My fat
like stomach leaned forward and hit L. That was not hard. Why are
you freaking me out? All right now I got enough. I'm
gonna do the middle. Let's do the expensive one first.
Miss 10 coins. It's okay. I'm all right with missing a few coins.
Let's do the middle. You sure about this? I'm sure.
Don't even build the left and right side. Just have a big cylinder in the
middle. Main hall first floor. Red Toad is heading up the project.
We've got the construction covered. Just get out there and complete more jobs.
I kind of love this. Is that weird? You can flip pages in the jobs list
with L and R and you can look for a list of incomplete jobs by pressing
Y. Back to work. New jobs are in. All right hold on.
The mystery of the haunted manor. Swinging claw ropes course.
The key master. This game is perfect for my
ADHD brain because I don't have to play any of the other Mario games.
They're all here. This is a shitload of levels that are every single Mario
game. Why would I need to play any of the other ones?
Let's try this one. So I made a ghost house recently but I think I got a
bit over my head because I'm kind of sort of trapped in here.
Should be able to get up with something strange about this place.
Can someone come and help me? All right here we go. This one's a
two-star. It's too hard.
It might be. See this is great. Now hold on a minute here. It's a
ghost level so I'm going to be deceived.
Isn't there a kid you do like the spin jump thing with big Mario?
They're like what? Yeah there it is. No I shouldn't be doing this
because those are going to turn to coins. Can you pick up the turnips?
Yeah you can. All right hold up. What does this mean?
You can't. What? Oh it's the first time I'm with Yoshi.
Oh stop it. Go up. You can just jump off Yoshi right?
Just eat them all. I can't eat that. He's dead.
Oops. Quick get over there quick. I can't jump on his head?
Why not? It's a ghost. Wait just take the other one.
That's different for some reason. Oh so I'm not crazy.
Good to know. All right let's eat. I already know how this works.
Don't worry everybody. I know how to do this.
See give me a break. I can do the two-star level.
But this is different. Okay oh I don't want to do this one.
Um hold on let's go in the door. What the fuck was that?
That actually scared the shit out of me. All right why is this
P.T. Mario? Oh god. Oh god. Oh fuck. Now what? Oh I have to reset it.
Lisa get me up here. Wait hold on. Um I want to get
there's another P. But should I? Is this going to take me out to the?
Hold on. Let's go. All right I've unlocked everything. What was this?
What's the P? Oh wait. Oh oh.
Okay. No stay on Yoshi. Oh oh oh oh oh.
What does this one do? I want to go in the P door.
I want those 30 coins. Check this out. You're going too slow.
Do I get out of here? Can I not be on Yoshi? Oh I think that's it right?
Yeah. I'm not soft locked. I'm fine. Now that I did that.
Now we. But wait. What's. Am I gonna get a P?
Now I could have brought a P with me probably. But what about this door?
Why have. I don't understand why I have that door. That hurt my ears. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Yeah that was really fucking loud.
I just. I'm sorry about that. But I mean that was a times 10.
Sometimes you have to scream. How we doing? Need more? More coins?
I did peek the mic. There's people that have been asking about that for
like six months. You got it. All right. This one's easy.
We rebuild the castle. What if. What if this is the whole stream?
Right? This is hard. I buried some coins in an underground room.
What do I care? Coins mean nothing to me anymore. What do we think about it?
All right. Reach the goal after grabbing all 30 coins.
I have to get all 30 coins. Reach the goal after grabbing all. I don't
have a hat anymore? Reach the goal after grabbing all 30.
Well I can tell you right now. Look at my brain just working.
Look at how good this brain is. There's gonna be one up here that they don't
tell you about. All right. These are all things I
didn't even know you could do in Mario.
What's this weird top thing? His brain.
Oh! This is just like the old game. Remember that old game?
I can't believe I just got fucking reverse Pac-Man. God damn it.
All right. Now I know what's going on. Now I know that the hat. Wait. There's
only one. I'm not taking it. I'm gonna need it
eventually. For the lobsters? Used to do this to the lobsters. Yep.
And they never brought that enemy back. They never brought back the weird
crab lobster things. Oh god damn it. I didn't want to do
that. Don't do it again! I've stopped
screaming. Fuck. I gotta put like a limiter on my
voice. No. Let's not kill every enemy.
Just collect all coins. Oh that's why I need the uh
that's why I need the star. Uh oh. Tricky.
Where they going? Tricky. Why would I go in this one?
Just an illusion. Well who cares? I got you coins.
Kick him over here. No. He's gonna. Oh.
Where's it going? Oh! I can't do it. I'm so. Holy shit. I almost died.
Just give me the coin and get me out. 30. I win, right?
Secrets. Got it. No. I'm not doing left and right. We're going straight up.
I'm doing main hall four and then main hall
two f. So you can do any amount of them, right? You can do a million of
them if you want. All right. Swimming claw ropes.
Oops. I should have read that. No. But everyone. That's all right.
That was unsatisfying what I just did. It was very satisfying.
And this is original Cake Mario. There it is.
There's Cake Mario. I knew I was gonna see it eventually.
Didn't get it. Whoa! Sorry. How did I get past?
No. No. No. I want those coins. I need the coins to build the castle.
I get itched my face. Wait. I think I needed those uh turtles.
Can I respawn them? Yeah. I need the turtles for that one.
Like you can't wall jump in this one. Do with no balls.
Why would I just die? Send me back. Send me put. Send me back. Send me back.
Send me back. I can get it.
Yes. I can feel every single one of those.
I'm not gonna spend any of it. I'm gonna wait till I get to 10 grand.
I'm gonna put it on one hand of blackjack. Wait. What did she say?
We got work to do. Yeah. I know. You want jobs? I got jobs.
Shoestopper. These shoe goompas are too much but the kicks they are rocking are
useful because you can walk over spike traps.
The shoes probably don't smell great but you can always press R to take them
off and if you find a big shoe you can always slam down by tilting
down in the air. Oh that's a cool snow level.
Oh it's a song from Undertale. Bean Bag Mario.
I tried. I thought I could get it. I got greedy.
What I just did right there is the equivalent of staying in and swinging one
more time in Dark Souls and knowing it's a bad idea but you
still gonna try it no matter what. See? Like I did it again.
I need another shoe. Thank you. Bean Bag
Mario and Bean Bag Sonic should be friends. That's what somebody said I
think or something like that. I'm paraphrasing.
Whoa. Why does it crashed into that guy?
There's a big shoe. Give me the big shoe. I can't get in the big one?
Yes I can. I can't get in the giant shoe tank. Of
course I can. What happened there? Well that was one
pixel that I didn't get on that. Wait hold on.
Can I? I'm too big. I need a little shoe. Any more little shoes?
Is this a giant high heel? All right hold on. Wait.
I need to get the giant heel. How do I get that?
Oh shit. Oh shit. I need to get in there.
How does one get in there?
I don't know why I'm so paranoid to jump on these guys. I can I can jump on
those guys right? It was the flame that hit me.
Yeah all right. All right I gotta do this.
Ready?
I feel like I'm playing Joust right now and I don't like it. It's making
me feel panicky. Shit I needed that. No not
anymore. I should have jumped out. What am I doing?
Go back. You can't get them all. All right first hall.
First main hall first floor is done. How much is the second one?
Cool. Wait you got a new building right?
Looking good. Go chief. Oh right you can press R to see the whole castle.
We have new building options now. Yep.
1200. I'm almost out of jobs. What happens when all the jobs
go away? So I made a ghost house. I'll pay anyone who can make it to the end.
Here's a little hint. You'll need four keys. More if you want to get the true
ending. Wink.
So I need more keys to get the true ending. I gotta try to get the true
ending. A little horn. All right well this
one key. I can't get it right now. So we've
got options here. We've got our spring which. Do I have to bring
it somewhere? I mean I don't know. There's nothing in
here. It's probably hit. I just fucked myself
completely. Can I like even get out of here without him killing me?
No. Look that pixel was bullshit. Did you see that?
What happened there? Oh really? I have to.
I need to get bigger. Hold on. Can I make it all the way back and grab the
thing? Yes there it is. Found it.
Ding dong. Three keys. Now what's in the other one? I need a
POW. I'm gonna take a guess and say the POW is gonna go in this one.
This one. This one right here. I don't know.
Well I kicked it. How do I get a secret key in here?
Spring? Well give me the POW. That's gonna get me killed. Just get in
there. Get in there. Oh they have melted
ghost snow. All right I didn't even need this.
I don't know why but I thought there was fall damage for a second. So there's
the one on the other side. A couple more. This one I don't
know. I think that's it. I think it did it.
Oh no it didn't. But that's the right place.
Get a mushroom? No I live dangerously. I'm gonna do it without a mushroom.
That's too much time. Oh fuck I should have listened.
All right I'm gonna get a mushroom. This is gonna freaking me out.
You're right. I need to get a mushroom. You're correct. I know. I'm gonna I'm
gonna listen. Just give one to me. So there's the
fourth key right there which is the P but I'm not doing that because I
wanted to get the true ending. So we need to bring the spring
somewhere. Where I did it? Over here? What is it like in here?
Yeah there we go. I need to get you. This is like a
you fly up. So how do I move you over there?
How do I get you to move? Is it an enemy? No it's not an enemy. Okay.
Wait will he actually? No give this to me.
No I want it to be no. Give it put it down here.
There we go. All right I got the five keys. No I don't. Not yet.
What? Get up there. Why is it? What? Am I insane? All right I got them all.
The fifth key is there and I get the secret ending.
Five. Out the door. Two. Three. Four. Five.
Two. Three. Four. Five. What do I do with the fifth one?
What? I need more keys? They said five.
No nobody said five. They said find more.
Four or more not five. There's so many that's a lot of
coins though. All right so what have I not used?
Do I need three more keys? I guess I didn't go
I didn't go on this. Let me look in here. Well this is obviously I need another I
need the spring here. And then we jump. I get it. Check this
out. Spring over on the left. Yeah I'm gonna jump from spring to
spring and I should get it. No I need this one over here. Everybody
thought I was stupid. Really? The intent was there. All
right now this is what about this one? I don't know it's the other one.
So how do I do this? The spring? The pow? No.
It's probably the spring. I have to like get on top of that.
Obviously I have to get on top of this. Oh shit.
Okay now I'm gonna hit a there's a secret block somewhere here and it's
probably gonna be like right here. Oh fuck. How about over here? Here?
Here? I'm gonna jump from the spring up. Oh god this is gonna kill me.
Hold on. I need a mushroom. I need to get a mushroom first. I'll
screw this up. What's that sound? What? Oh I have a
hundred seconds. I need one more. Where's the last one? Hold on give me
a mushroom. This one more. Where is it? It's the P. P right?
Hurry hurry go go go go. Did I get this one?
I already got this one. Wait what about what about if I'm
getting it's like uh Far Cry 4. You just have to go in the
beginning. Up there? No it's too late. It's too late. I don't have time.
Oh I have to come back and do this again? I got 40. No no I gotta go. Get
out of the way. That's a lot of coins but I don't I can't
I'm not I can't do it. Anything else in here? Just check in here.
Nothing else? Two, three, fuck. No just restarted? No I'm not going to
restart. I'm just gonna do it. I'm just gonna finish it. Use the
uh I feel so unfulfilled though. See I would have gone at zero but
I don't know in Mario specifically this one. Does it
kill you at zero or zero one die? I wasn't gonna take that risk.
Redo it. All right let's I'm gonna redo it.
So where's the where's the first one? I know how to get them all.
So I'll just get them all quick. This won't take very long.
I'm gonna start with POW. We're gonna go to the right up this one.
I have plenty of time. 500 seconds is like 12 minutes.
I got plenty of time.
Seven minutes. Yeah but whatever. It's enough time.
Give me the spring. I got springs over here.
Straight up this one. And I'm not gonna turn it in till I have I mean I
when I used to play Diablo 3 and I mean that game's not like that
great but when I used to do the bounties I
would collect the bounties and have like 10 of them and open them all
at the same time. I want to have all eight keys.
Oh my god he almost got me. Sometimes it would be 20.
I don't have time for this shit. Come on. Even Mario was looking at that going
like all right. All right that's all of them over here.
Get the P coins. You can be Luigi.
Wait is that a joke? I thought you were joking. I'm sorry.
I need this. Watch this. Ready? Wasn't that cool?
Could have been. Can I hit it like this? No.
There we go. But I still have to grab it. No I don't. It's free.
One two. I'm trying to count the keys. One two three. I only have five.
How did I get the other ones? Well there's one there. Right okay.
So that would be six. Oh yeah the conveyor room. Right.
Does this kill him? It does. Should have used it before.
All right look at all those bounty caches I got. Look at all those bounty
boxes. One two three four five six seven. One more. So let's see. I'm gonna say
no. There's one more. There's one there. I need I need to go find one more. Let's see
it up here. And there it is. What the hell do I do with this?
What's wrong with them? Is it a battery? Did I just give him like a
battery? Let's go. Oh my god. I'm gonna go up.
Got them all. All right. I just ripped his brain out. Have a nice life.
I did it. Now I get all those coins. And I got time to spare.
The good ending. The expensive ending. And yeah here's the anxiety music.
And why is it still on? Will the jack in the box come out already? I'm
waiting for him to pop out. And that was a nice little song. I have
to get these all.
Would that be there? Well uh why would that be there?
Oh god. Oh well. Oh all right. It's all right.
I can get them back. Those last three coins are just
trapped. You can't get them. Where did it go? What did I just throw it to?
What? I threw it. That's so dumb. At least you got the coins. Yeah and
then they all. This game's Sonic the Hedgehog's you.
You lose them all. Yeah it was for three coins.
Come here. I want it in here. Stop picking it up.
The POW. I really didn't think I was gonna be on this for this long.
Slow it down. I don't want to mess it up again. So and I didn't even mess it
up. I got trolled last time. So that doesn't count. Third first try.
Let's make this happen. Let's get the coins first.
Got it. All right then we just have to do the
throw. I'm just gonna take the POW. Let's do this one.
It's right here.
Get it. Now all we need is the pancake. All right that's it. Riders need the
this one here. He sounds annoyed. I'm not annoyed. Am I tall enough to
get this? It's one coin.
One two three four five six seven eight. The last one is up there.
This time I'm gonna bring the spring. I'm gonna go get a spring. Can I go get a
spring and put it here? Here we go. Come on down. You can keep
your brain this time. All right now I'm gonna bring the
spring up here. So let's hold on. Can I...
No I have to do this first. I gotta get the key. Come back.
Get the coins. All right. I can just step on it now.
All right. I'm ready. That's eight right? One two three four five six seven eight.
Hooray. All right up. Same deal. This time don't fall through the hole.
And I get to build this next part of the castle. It's worth doing.
Hey you get to hear the song again. Oh shit. Is there anything up there?
Oh I did it. It's still times 10. Times 10 is not even a big deal. Why did I
scream? Castle level two. Let's do it.
Bingo. You sure about this? I am sure. Nice. More jobs. More jobs. Six new jobs.
That's one hot car. Yo this fire junior clown car course that I made is off
the hook. Hold Y to charge up your cannon and
then let it go to fire a charge shot that can cook fools and bust hard
blocks. Press R to get out of the car. You
need to go down that. You need to go down a pipe at some
point. What? Is there an actual clown car level in
this game? Hold Y to charge. Oh it's not really a
real clown car. That felt good. Good coins.
Hey hey hey. Let's grab them. I can't get hurt down here.
I almost got hit by that bullet. I don't know why. I thought it was an
indicator. It's R to get out right? Touch it so
don't spritz it. All right I gotta get a pipe at some point right? But
wait not yet. There's probably something over here.
Too bad. I can. Oh that's cool. People are going to make some cool
shit with this. Definitely. Upgraded triple shot.
I cannot get rid of the cannons but yes I can.
Drop them in. I think it has made this harder for myself.
Kind of. Get it there. Go go go go. Get up.
You can make a bullet hell. Yeah. Shit. I tried to duck.
That's not going to work. Just get up. Oh my gosh. Standing in front of it.
All right into the cup. Touch the axe. Touch the axe. I did it.
Continue the build. You just just killed an entire castle so you could
build your own. My castle's not evil.
Swinging claws. Oh cool. Imperialism. No I'm this I'm taking out the evil
people. Oh I love when they do this style.
Makes me feel like I'm just working on a game boy.
Get over here goomba. I need to jump on you to get up there.
Oh god damn it. Come on. No pick him up. Pick up the goomba.
All right then I have to get close when he gets close enough. Don't do
that yet. No no. I want to drop him on that.
Because bullet that head would do something. Nice. There it is.
More claw games. All right then drop them here.
Oh shit. Hold on. All right then drop them here on this prize machine.
This is cool. This is innovative. Oh they you have
I get it. Pick him up and then you have to put him down here.
So oh god. All right hold on. Pick him up
and then place him over there. No get him.
Get somebody get him. He's he'll get him on the way back right there.
Right now. Got it. All right and then let it go.
You gonna pick me up? Oh wait wait wait wait. What's going on here?
And then you gotta drop him on there. Pick him up and then bring him this
way. Oh shit he died.
All right put him in that. Ding dong. Now you
I didn't think they were gonna come down here. Oh shit. I need to get in
that. All right now don't die here. Are
those. Does this flappy bird shit kill you? No.
That was cute. That was a cute one. Two more levels and I can get. It's
probably gonna be way too much money. Tree top fireballs. I managed to plant
some trees and they actually look pretty good.
Can you try climbing all 12 of my trees? Yes I can.
Do the harder ones? Well I want to just get them all done. I'm just doing it as
they come. Climb on the trees. One. The snow comes off too. They've
thought of everything. I don't know. I don't know what
that does but whatever. Is that gonna hurt me? No it's
just there. One more trees.
Only one to kill that guy. It's usually like six.
Oh all right. They give me a nice little break.
Burning the locals to death. I mean are these.
They're they're killing us. They're trying to kill me.
No they're not. They're kind of not at all.
How's this not 12? Did I miss one? Oh it's right here okay. What just. I
was. You can climb the hole and all right. I got a pretty good score
regardless. 174 dollars. All right one more and then I'm
gonna find out if I don't have enough money.
We'll find out real quick. Plenty of cheap cheeps in the sea. This swimming
level is gonna be horrible. There's way too many cheap cheeps.
Is it even possible to beat this? Someone help me.
Well sorry. Well Toad you have to be able to beat your own level before
you put it up here. So you had to have already beaten
this. Nice lie. Oh it's a water level. Might as well skip it.
I hate these water levels. I don't have the kind of control that I'm looking
for. The exact precision that I want. It always causes me a huge problem.
Although this is not that hard. Nobody likes water levels. No.
Oh no. No. No. It's like timed. I thought that was a mushrooms output to
grab one. Okay good. Wasn't that bad. Wasn't
as bad as I made it out to seem like.
Timed underwater escort mission. Yep. Oh there's the tweedle dees. Whatever
they're called. What are those actual caterpillar things
called? Oh got it. Mario time. The wiggles.
There it is. Now let's do middle hall three.
It's so beautiful. Keep up the good work. We're gonna try.
Oh I have to do something else now. I got the money to do it. Let's do
west hall. Can't just go straight up. Sorry. I
also have enough money to do these tall as well.
Doing both. We get more jobs. Six new jobs. Six new jobs. Six new jobs.
Something about this is just actually very very satisfying to play.
All right so let's do let's do a hard one.
This is a hard one. No jumping allowed.
Here's a challenge. Try to get through the whole level without jumping
off the ground and landing. Any takers anyone. There's a prize for
anyone who succeeds. Here's a hint. Use y to dash.
The game master. I can't jump. Reach the goal without landing after
leaving the ground. So wait. What do you mean without
landing after leaving the ground? Does that count if I land up there?
If I land up top there does it count? I didn't even make it fucking ten
steps. I was trying to. Whoa no! I gotta
I gotta get my fucking brain. No I don't need to be Luigi. Don't
worry. What the fuck? I thought he was gonna go
down. Oh my god. I'm gonna lose all my characters.
I thought he was gonna go down into the ground after passing once.
Oh no. Here he comes. Wait. Does that count?
That doesn't count right? Because I'm not touching the ground. That's
that's a that's a donut. That's not a ground.
Okay. Oh shit. All right. Give me a flag.
Do they have a platform? I can't go. I don't want to go down.
Fuck. Do I have to stand on that? Oh my god.
What happens if I run out of lives? What happens if I run out? Does anyone know?
You save gets deleted. False.
You get reincarnated as an ant. Oh interesting.
Come on down. What are they shooting? All right that just freaked me out. Now
this is important. So let me watch him. I need to see
where he goes. He runs over here and that I didn't even
move. I didn't even I didn't even fucking move.
Okay that it freaked me out. What happens if I
I didn't even move. I have to complete this. No I can't.
Tape the button down. Too bad. Do I lose the game? Do I did I just lose?
He can do it for you. Do we get to watch him play it?
I hope it's actually a cell phone call. Hope you actually call him.
Hello. Hey can you help me beat this level?
I'm in traffic right now. Stop fucking calling me. Oh shit.
I didn't jump. Everybody gets a one. You call it 15 times.
The game just launched. Maybe you should try
What is that game? Candy Crush. Okay I'm I don't understand this. Here we go.
I don't understand it. I don't understand it. I don't understand it.
Yeah I have to use the draw. I'm gonna let him do it.
I'm gonna call Luigi. I'm gonna say like hurry home from work.
I need you to beat a level for me. I just stand still as I did the last
time and I fell off his head and it discounted me.
All right I'm gonna do it this time. I'm not fucking this up. I'm just gonna stand
still on his head. Come on booze let's go. What now what?
Hurry they're coming. What do I do about this? What happened?
You went into the air. I didn't go in the air. I didn't go in the
Did I already lose? I gotta call Luigi.
What was that? What happened? What happened?
Let me try again. Hi this is Luigi. Mama mia call me back at a later date.
Take a message. What happened? I could just call him. What's going on?
I can't. He has to do it. I can't. I have to press I have I can't do it.
This task is too much for me to do. It really is. I just can't do it. I'm
like I'm like looking over at chat and I'm
like fucking falling off the ground. I can't do it. I can't. I can do it.
I'll do it. Guys I can't. Luigi I can't call Luigi anymore.
He called up Verizon and had my number fucking blocked
permanently. Okay so what happened here?
Just stand on it and just let it... I walked off.
Give me a break. There's even more of this shit.
Now what? Get up. What's over here? Should I let this pick me up? I
wasn't fast enough. I need to watch this for a minute.
Two. Two. How do I get that? Will the bomb blow it up?
They can disappear. What's the purpose of that? That has to be a purpose of
what you're doing there. The donuts just walk across the
donuts? Do I bounce on the donuts? I've never seen the donuts before.
What the fuck was that? It's lots of slipperiness there.
Does this count if I go through this? Am I gonna land on something?
Oh shit um do I have to direct him here? I don't dude I don't care about the
coins anymore. I almost just pressed jump.
That was kind of hard. I have to do both at the same time. Mental breakdown? No.
Not yet. What else we got for jobs? We got fire koopa clown carnage.
Uh yep. Ask again in a few hours? Yeah. Ask again in a few hours. We'll
see if I can be the first person on twitch to complete this.
Um the game's been out for like 12 hours. I don't think that's gonna be
the thing. I can jump again. What am I doing?
That's so burnt in my brain that I can't jump. He's been conditioned.
At this point yes. Spread out. Oops. Did I not kill these? What if I
should jump on them? They don't have a chance? Yeah they
shouldn't. Oh what does this do? Can I? Oh it's like an extra health bar
right? Yeah it's one extra hit. That thing comes off. Like that.
Like that. Good thing I had a hard head.
Boom. Get one up too. I'll take it.
This is dumb luck that I haven't been hit yet.
How fast does he go? Where the shit in the battle toads?
All right hold on. Slow down. Slow down. Slow slow slow. Oh fuck.
Watch out for that really slow moving arrow. Just get out and get it.
Oh shit. Hold on. Is it still there? Go back. Go back. Go back.
Need that spike helmet. Yeah that's true. That's sweet.
Double. One more job and then we'll be at probably what?
Somebody up there? Oh I can go in the castle. Oh this is cool.
What's going on up here? This is this is a regular toad.
I need your help. It'll be bad if the chief overhears.
Mutiny? Heavy stone heave ho. We went off a budget and ran out of stone
for making stairs. And of course the chief says we only
use stone from the desert. I'll do it myself but it's so heavy.
Could you bring me some? Reach the goal while holding a stone.
Let's go. Oh Mario cake. It's my favorite kind. It's my favorite Mario.
I gotta hold the stone the whole time. Whatever happens if I let it go.
I have to hold down this button the whole time which I get really sweaty
greasy hands. So this is gonna be hard to do.
Go here. Oh fuck. I could have got it.
I want that. How do I get that though? Okay well that was easier than I
thought it was gonna be. You can put the stone down. How do
you know that? I thought I'd wait I just had to
it's a left for dead gnome run. Only 17 coins.
You didn't try? I didn't want to lose any an extra life. I need those.
Okay so what was the oh that's it. Let's go.
25 percent? 30 percent? 26 more workers.
Mario we need some blocks to get to the east hall from here but
Mario can you keep a secret? Thanks and good luck.
What was the secret? That's the secret. Purple toad who makes the blocks hasn't
arrived yet. Got the schedule wrong management am I
right? Anyway please bring the purple toad
back here. Reach the goal with one toad in tow.
What do you mean in what do you mean toad in tow?
Where do I get this toad? I just realized something.
All these mushrooms you know because before it was just there was just the
one toad. Now there's a shitload of toads. This
toad's everywhere. Take a look at what the mushrooms in this
game look like. They look exactly like toad's head.
Think about that and we've we've come to learn that there are
hundreds if not like millions of toads.
Where the mushrooms come from? Look at them.
Look at this little his face and look at that toad face. Look at the
look at the mushroom. Somebody get the with those
theorists on the line.
Jump on top of them. Risky move risky play. Oh shit.
Risky move here. Shoot one more. Not gonna shoot another one.
Right at the bottom. One coin. Why is Yoshi born with shoes on?
Man that's kind of weird. I'm gonna have dreams about this shit.
How many more do I have to do that like three or four more times?
Well anything else you need me to do over here on the
rampart? Okay you didn't hear me say that. Oh I'm ready to start working
the rest of the east hall. Oh you have to. I see. Hello you.
We're gonna find a new toad. The chief took my cloud because she said
she needed it for something or other. I don't want the chief to hear this so
let me just whisper it in your ear. The chief asked me to get a Lakitu's
cloud for the west hall. Can you believe that?
Who asked someone to do something that they don't want to do themselves?
Oh hey can you go and get me a Lakitu's cloud Mario?
Comedy. I can't wait for like the glass door reviews
of rebuilding the magic kingdom. Whatever this is.
Oh I got my time. How much time do I have? Not very much time at all.
12 seconds. Four. There's a four up there.
I had four seconds left. What? Get out of here.
Blocked. What? I had four seconds left.
Oh my god. The cloud has its own timer so what's the extra three seconds for
on the clock? Why not just make it 12 seconds or 16 seconds?
Okay I made it over. It was so sloppy. Oh god damn it.
I kind of want to call Luigi. I want to know what it does.
I'm not calling him yet. It's really slippery in the cloud.
Oh my god I can't fucking do this. I was being so careful.
Oh oh all right just it's not even that big of a deal. I'm just freaking
out for no reason. Nobody can do anything with this music
on. They should make relaxing music here.
Like calm down music. Imagine if your boss was fucking
yelling at you to finish doing something.
You screwed that whole thing up Jacob.
You missed like two lines there. You gotta go back and fix it.
You gotta go back and fix it right now. Jacob fix it now.
Okay which line? Two lines down. It should say they
and plus six. Hurry the fuck up Jacob.
You had bad grammar. There was an extra T.
Oh hey I know that you're clocking out of work here in
like the next 30 seconds or so. Oh but can you make
we need six more hamburgers made right now. Go!
I'm gonna get it right now. Oh my god it's so floaty.
Whee! It's fucking easy. Thank you. I don't want to watch this every
time. Just let me jump on it. God Nintendo come on. The chief took
my cloud. Can't believe it. Don't tell the chief I said that.
Hello. I'm ready. 26 percent building the whole damn castle
today. Do you hear? What? What? I'm sorry. I
did my static. There's a little bit of frame drop there. What'd you say Jeremy?
Building the whole castle tonight. Snake blocks in the sky.
This is a 40 hour long campaign. Is it?
No it's not. Is it? It's not actually a 40 hour
campaign. I'm already like 30 percent of the way done. It's been two hours.
Two, four, six, eight. I'll do this like six and a half, eight hours.
I need to practice to be able to do the multiplayer levels. You think this
is the last Mario Maker 2 stream? Yes you think so.
Uh I don't know. It might be. I messed up.
How do I get that? I think I missed my opportunity to get it.
No I didn't. Hold on. It's all right. I do have a terrible record with
Mario games. Yeah. But correct me if I'm wrong. As of two
hours into the stream last Mario Maker stream,
I was already talking about... I was talking about problems with the
controller. So I got input lag right? And then it
was already like a huge problem. Remember? I remember that. That shit
was on the Wii U. The Wii U's controller. I was on like
the big brick controller. I don't think I even had the
the... Yeah. No. That's one of the reasons why.
And it was all stained and shit. I think I blew that opportunity. Do I have to ride
this? Wow. You can ride it? Don't crush my head!
Cool. This is fucking radical. Oh I thought I was gonna... I thought
I was gonna just shrink. I don't like this shit either. Like you
meant to get called into your boss's office in this place.
That just... That just murdered me. That double tapped me I think.
Get out of here. I don't need you. You can do that?
Why can I do that? I don't understand what the
purpose of that is quite at the moment. What's it for?
Watch out for the... Okay there it is. I can't see. Don't go forward.
What? That was gritty. I missed the flag.
Should I just... Wait. There's a pipe here.
Wait. That was... I don't know. I'm a weird cough.
I wanted to say something but I had nothing to say so that was my body's
instinctual response. It was just a cough. Did I die or he died?
I think he did. Yeah. How much money do I got? A thousand?
I think I can do some other builds here. What do you got for me?
Making great progress. This design is too perfect. Almost too perfect.
We have a new building option. Let's go with
West Hall, second floor. I am certain. Construction is underway. How big is this
castle? Square footage wise. Have they ever
released that information? Can you look up the Mario castle on
Zillow? That would be a cute idea. Don't you
think so? Imagine like Zillow or one of these other
places did a like oh this is not a good idea at all.
No one would use this and it'd be stupid. Never mind.
Twister. If you press B as you enter the twister you'll be thrown skywards.
Yeah I know. Twisting through the desert sands.
It could be a cute April Fools gag. Yeah I mean maybe.
You can scroll through photos of inside the castle and tell you how
many square footage it is and then you get to the price and you
go Mario how the fuck can you afford that?
And then you check the estimate. Find out what like your
mortgage estimate would be for Peach's castle.
$61,000 a month's estimate. I can't. I don't think I can live there.
That's it? Got it. Geez. Whoa whoa whoa easy. B. B.
Oh my god. Say the line. What line? Cake Mario?
Do I weigh enough to get this? I have to wait till it goes all the way to the other side.
Damn it. Not bad. 107 coins so far. I'm gonna run out of time though.
That felt pretty damn good. All right what's the cost for the other ones?
What's that thing over there? There's a number muncher over there. Why?
Looks like you've been hard at work. I suppose it's time I get back to work
myself. Adios. Mr. Eraser.
Sorry I'm gonna go chew on some prime numbers. I'll be back in a few
hours. Come on. That was cute. That was
cute. That was cute. From a split on that one. The way of the shell. Oh it
was the begone rotten mushroom. I bought some
mushrooms for a new recipe but I left them in the car and now they've rotten.
Rotten and vengeful. You're going to have to outrun them if you want the
reward. Begone rotten mushroom. Outrun the mushrooms.
This is a pretty awesome Halloween level. I did the joke before too.
Hold on. Let me do the same joke that I've done already like a
thousand times. Get out of my way for a second.
Mocking him. Whoa he can do that. He can't climb right? No. Can I block
him down here? No. Wait. Holy shit. Don't do that far.
You blew everything. You're making this. What?
How much money? 674. Need more coins. Where we at? Did I do all the
following? I got a lot to do down here.
Bonsai bill ambush. Guahaha. I've got an army of bonsai bills guarding
this place. Hoping to surprise Mario by sneaking up
behind him. Any of you chumps out there desperate
enough to test it before Mario shows up?
Get to the end and get paid. Good luck out there.
Go talk to the dog? I will after I get another thousand dollars.
Talk to the dog or I'm unsubbing. Just hold on.
Cat. I like the bullets in this. They're pretty cool. It's a nice touch.
Who made this? I made this. Oh they're cool.
I didn't know there was a get here.
What was going through your thought process? What the fuck just happened?
Oh. I had the checkpoint. I didn't press up.
Wait a minute. I can turn it around? Just let them destroy everything.
What? Oh wow. Missed coins. He missed coins. I don't- it's all right.
I had to jump on one of their heads to get this.
That guy down. I gotta get on the cloud. Did the cloud fall?
No. I can't just do this. Of course. This seems kind of out of place.
Fur suit. Guys, Mario has been wearing fur suits
for 25 years. This ain't new. Seasaw catapults. Jump and tilt
down to do a ground pound onto a seesaw to send anything on the other
end flying.
I love little cute Mario. What a perfect thing to have on a key chain.
Don't you think so? Or cake Mario. I think cake Mario I think is my
what I would put on a key chain. They definitely have it.
I don't pound this, but why would I ground pound any of this crap?
What? What's up with that? I just like was-
I just like broke his neck. I can't like sever his head. Like I can't
break his neck right there. Yeah right. I always thought you
couldn't kill that thing, but it just got angry.
Break that. I get it a lot. You know, the thing is
let's see if I can get that. Okay, hold on. Not quite.
Shit. All right, I gotta shut the fuck up. Wait, can I skip that?
He's gonna be squiggling around in there. There's probably a
coin over there. I'm gonna just give it a look. See, he
does get mad.
Whatever. It is bright here. It's fine. Whatever. It's 10 coins.
That's nothing. I thought I said I could launch him.
I can do it from the bottom.
Yeah, see? I'm not sure what that even did for me, but
I gotta get it. You're right. I'm looking in the chat right now. People
are just like, you fucking idiot. Stupid. Like, how dare you miss that?
And I'm like, geez. I mean, it's just Mario. It's
just Mario, guys. I'm done. Somebody said I hate you in all
capitals like 10 times in a row. Just like,
relax. It's all right. It's gonna be okay.
Just Mario. Just Mario. Ooh. Now, that was fun. Shit.
What am I? How do I do that? I'm gonna go from here to there to there.
What?! It's the buttons. The button. I fat-fingered it because I'm
using the Nintendo Switch. My thumb.
Using my thumb. Luigi, get out of my face.
The Switch. I'm using the Switch controller and sometimes when you
press one button on the Switch, you press
all of them because they're like sprinkles on your controller. It's like
having chocolate chips on your controller.
Sorry, I pressed all the chocolate chips at the same time.
I don't even have big hands. Yeah, I kind of do, but not that big.
If I fuck this up again. What's underneath this?
Sorry, I pressed every single little like dinner mint
at the same time. Look at those candy dots that were on the sheet of paper.
Those are bigger than the Switch buttons. Dog, dog. All right, all right, all right.
I'll talk to the dog. Bark, bark. I have jobs. Woof.
Woof, woof. Come on, please. Ooh, there's a dog level. Swinging claw escape.
Arf, Arf, I have a job for you to do. I keep getting caught by the
swinging claws hanging around my walking route. Could you show me a path
I can take to avoid getting grabbed? Reach the goal without using any
swinging claws. Who's a good boy?
Oh, okay. That just like freaked me the fuck out when I looked over there.
All right, don't get grabbed by any of these. I can jump though, right?
Just let that happen. Get grabbed.
Don't get grabbed. Slide. Wait. Okay, now slide.
Sure. Okay, that's fine.
It is a dog level, so it makes sense. I did the same thing again.
I just let it happen again. Like, sometimes I think
if you like split my head open, there'd be watermelon juice in there.
Like, sometimes I think it's just a coconut. Oh!
That was probably, that was so loud. I can tell. I looked over at the
monitor and it was really loud. Okay, I'm safe here, I think.
Where is the other ones? There's going to be another one.
See, the thing is, there was no point in me doing what I was just trying to do.
I, there was no point in that. I just had to go up. I don't know.
Don't do it again. If this happens again, I truly have
like orange juice in my brain. Remember those old
gushers commercials? They would eat the gushers and their heads would
turn into like pears and shit. Don't get grabbed.
Just kill me.
Does it start over button? I have to go down with the ship though.
Literally five coins. Do I really hear that much about it?
Don't even, don't even start talking shit about the jello. I, somebody said
jello and I got immediately angry. Hold on, I will
talk. No, I'm not talking about jello anymore.
Jello is jello. Jello is jelly. I can't even fucking believe it. I've
I'm already getting heated. I'm already getting like, I can feel my
like blood. Don't do that. Just get the thing.
Jelly is jello. Give me a break. Jelly is not always made with gelatin.
I can't even, I'm already getting mad. I can stop. Stop, stop. Just play.
Stop. You think I'm gonna go for two coins?
They respawn. Okay, wait. Go now. Drop it. Oh shit.
Home stretch. Don't blow it. I don't care if I didn't touch it.
Jelly is bones. No, jello is always made with gelatin. Jelly is not
always made with gelatin. Sometimes it's fruit preserves.
So therefore, chat was I-N-C-O-R-R-E-C-T.
Another job for the dog? Sure. When was the last time you guys tried to
spread jello on a piece of toast? Really?
What the, you can't, that's not gonna happen.
Arf, Arf, I have a job for you. The nights have been so cold lately.
Could you bring me something that will shelter me from the storm?
Reach the goal while wearing a dry bones shell.
If you spread jello on your toast. What? Hold on. What the fuck?
I didn't even get a chance. I can't see where we're going.
Oh, thank god his arrows. Oh boy. Okay. I think we're safe. Can I jump on these?
Yes, I can. Yes, I can. No, you can't. Yes, I can.
You can't. Yes, I can. Did you just watch? God.
What the fuck?
I'm gonna get it. He doesn't even want to take it. Get in the shell!
Get in the shell! What the hell? How is that even possible? This purple jello.
Ah, every time. I don't stop. Don't say that anymore.
Does he have a glass break? I'm cutting this way too close.
Like, honestly, I don't, I don't, I just, I don't care. I don't need to think
about this. I don't care about the world's most
disgusting snack. Like, who cares? The jello, jelly, who
cares? Doesn't matter. I, who, that doesn't matter. Who cares?
Got it. Oh, fuck. Um, should I go? Oh shit! I got it. Imagine being Mario
right now. What a nightmare. 87 coins. Cool.
I got enough money now. Is that it for the dog?
Ooh, I got him a dog house. He's got more. Should I just do all the dog missions?
No, I, we gotta start a build here. Looking glorious.
We have new building options now. Cool.
West hall cannon. Main hall three. Main hall three. Let's just get it done.
Do auto mission. I will. I'll do it right now.
Got another job. This is a full-on four star difficult. First time we've seen
it. Tonight, chain chomp chiller and I get something.
What do I get? A mystery t-shirt. The path I usually
take is littered with chain chomps. Could you show me if it's possible to
walk through there without jumping? Can't wait.
Get Luigi on speed dial for this one. I did it.
This is gonna suck. What? Wait. Does this one
fly? Some of them don't. Some of them go fly forward.
Oh no. No. How am I gonna? Okay. Just get me to a flag.
I don't know when to go. Right now. Okay, hold on.
Is he gonna go up? Did I put this down? Should I put this down? I'm gonna put
it down. Should I bring it with me? I'm gonna bring it with me. Might need
it. I'm gonna make him jump up there. I'm
gonna bring it with me. How was that four stars and the other
one was three? The other one was harder than that and it was like two.
I got the reset dress. I want it. You can
equip the outfit in the course world. Is that it for the dog?
I got the dog's shirt. Need some more coins to get some jobs over here.
Let me get through these. Tunnel to the dark side of the
moon. I think I tunnel all the way to
the other side of the moon because everything is upside down there. It's
pretty neat but kind of disorienting.
If you want to slide down a slope you gotta hit
up. I really didn't think that I was gonna
have this much fun in the random build the castle single player
but I kind of am. Wait. On you? Yes. Can I bounce you up the wall?
Oh my god. I didn't mean to do that. I turned the wrong way.
Okay, I'm gonna bounce him up the wall. Just getting him.
Oh. Well now that makes more sense. Upside down.
No, wait. Check the other thing. That's a death, isn't it?
Uh. At least I know I don't have to do that.
Just go in, grab, turn, run, jump. Nice. All right. Is there a point to
that? Anything over here? I don't think there's anything over
there. Slide? You can't slide as uh Cake Mario.
At least not upside down. Oh shit. I thought I was gonna go through.
Oh boy. Watch out. I can't get up there. I can get up there now, right? Yeah.
Just flip the switch upside down. I mean you
could do that. Maybe. German nuke the chat.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
All right. That was as if like a toddler was like walking towards
the stove. And like reaching up to the stove.
All right. Be careful, careful, careful. I can't kill the uh spike
head. I feel like if I jump too hard, high, it's gonna kill me off screen.
Is that gonna happen? No, but I can die. I can fall off here though, right?
Will that happen if I fall off here? I think so.
Just careful. Oh my god, that's gonna happen if I do that.
Can I get in this door? I just pressed down.
Don't go that far. I can get it twice, can I?
No, I can't. No, that's not gonna happen.
Super Mario, Super Mario, Super Mario. We've got a game of the year contender
here. I just pressed a button on my like OBS.
Am I still streaming? I think, yeah, I am. I like pressed my key. I like
mashed like a couple buttons on the keyboard.
Stop streaming is highlighted though. So I'm kind of,
I'm just gonna move my mouse to the other monitor. I said that's all these,
right? All the way up through 21. This one's
an easy one. I like easy ones. Am I gonna do a
Jerma Game Awards at the end of the year?
I'm probably not. I don't really do that anymore. Not since um
the YouTube days and even when I did it on YouTube.
It's kind of a joke anyways. I usually just tell you
I had to obey. I'm sorry. I was sinking, guys.
Gonna jump eventually. Oh, no. This is why I need Yoshi. Can I go
get him again? I want that coin. That motherfucker is
drowning down there. Come here, Yoshi. Where are you?
Yoshi. Come on. Hurry up. That's my opinion on Anthony Banthly for 2020.
We don't talk politics on this stream.
That candidate sucks. I just killed the thing that I wanted to come all the
way back into Respawn. I don't even care. Just go in there.
Oh yeah, I forgot. If you have a shell, you swim better. There he is.
Oh, I can't. I can't lift that bump. Should I do it again?
Should I? Should I do it again? Wait, things are doing?
I'm not a monster. I thought there was something up there. Where was the 30?
Some people said there's a 40 hour single player campaign. I don't think
that you were correct. I think you may have been just a
slight bit incorrect. Above the clouds, beyond the vines.
Vines growing all over it. Be my guest.
40 hour campaign. The game's been up for like 18 hours. Yeah, how would you even
know that? Unless like the press told you that.
Wait, I gotta go from keychain Mario to like grown-up Mario. There we go.
Which side? 40 hours of journalist difficulty?
Yeah? What were you gonna say? Tell me again?
What was it? Of journalist difficulty is what you said?
I almost just did it. I don't know why I just freaked out there. It was just half.
I love that like, it's kind of like the way.
What is it? What am I doing? What the fuck happened?
Can they go sideways? That's what it is. I didn't think they could go
sideways. They've evolved. They never used to be able to do
this shit. No! It's all right, let me get that.
Luigi, you would have died to that too. That would laugh my ass off
if there was like a problem with the game or something. It was a bug.
And Luigi got fucking smoked in the first 10 seconds.
Luigi's gotta call somebody else. Wario gets on the phone.
This game is a bullshit. This goddamn candy controller, I swear to God.
I could probably eat one of the switch controls and be fine. I really think
that. I could eat it and it would just,
it would come out be fine. Where am I? Good cloud.
This is gonna be risky. Risky play! What? Why did he
magnetize the other direction? I think I'm safe.
You're never safe though. Hold on. What is that? I don't, can you skip like the whole level?
Did I just put that out of reach? What the hell is the point of this?
It's the dev exit. Listen, I, the, I've got, I,
Mario, in all the Mario games, if you go over the flag, it just
stops you and you're at the top of the flag. Not in this one.
What do you mean not true? That's true. If you go over the flag
in the original Mario game, you, no that's right, that happens like the
first two or three of them that do that. That happens. What do I think about
chocolate pudding? It has bones in it. Chocolate pudding is fine, but chocolate
pudding is not jello. I mean, it could be. It could be chocolate
jello. Chocolate pudding is not jelly. I'm done.
No. Why did you do this to me? I'm not, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm
playing Mario. Goomba clubhouse. This sounds fun.
I love goombas. I love them so much that I made them a clubhouse. Aren't
they so cute when they scoot through those clear pipes?
Someone please go hang out with them and stomp on their heads.
I'll pay you. Wait, I think I have to have the rocket boost.
Yep, hold on. Three rocket boosts. Holy shit, I didn't die.
The audio is desynced. I thought it was going to crash.
You can't crash in the tube? Okay, what the fuck am I doing? It's
desynced. So listen, um, let me, I can do a test here.
Ready?
Are we synced? The audio is ahead. The game audio. Or me. Hold on.
So wait, hold on. You like, you know, me by 60 milliseconds?
So I'm a little late. So like, okay, let me see if it happens. Tell me if it
happens when I do this. Ready? Clear it, clear it, clear it.
Ready. One, two, three.
Game audio is ahead. Hold on. All right, ready. Clear it, clear the
clear.
Good. All right, here we go. I need all these keys. Oh, that's how
get this 10. all right so where do we go now? I'm thinking like a dank right here. if I just fell
down the hardest thing to die in, it might be time to throw myself. so we're in the middle. no stop!
coins on this side, coins above, coins down, coins back up.
oh, let's go all the way around. that's all right, this is the exit. all right, go this way.
I can't, like, go, I can't, you can't tele-frag them. I need one more key over there. what?
all right, let's, I'm, it's fine, I got it.
unless, wait, no, no, no, no, no, it's over here. there's probably not, there's no screen,
right? it's just this. I didn't get it. so bald. I can't, what's my voice doing?
main hall three. is there a fourth floor to the castle? I don't remember. oh man, oh fuck, oh
shit. oh man, this is bad. we've got a problem. I shouldn't say this out loud, so here. oh,
red toad got kidnapped while we were taking an unauthorized break. please bring red toad back
before the chief notices. we're all busted. no, it's not worth screaming. it's only, it's been
three hours. if I screamed, I was going to, I, I, my voice would be gone in, like, the next 45
minutes. reach the goal with one toad. fine, I'll do it myself. wee. why did I just get the,
this is low gravity. oh, this is the best song, I think, in the last 10 years or so.
you know. we're dead. he weighed me down. toad, you weighed me down. that's what happened.
hey, there's like that advanced technique where you can do that. you're kidding me. why were
you just standing still? don't, how did I not, I almost died in the same spot.
is it yellow fish? that's a 30 over there. can you jump? jump. oh, oh my god, what's
happening? oh my god, I, I, that hurt my body. I fell off that cliff. peek, today's peek the
mic day apparently. yeah, apparently. I'm not going to peek the mic again, it's not going
to happen. I have to get toad. if I accidentally press the ground pound again,
there was a time when you had to press down and like right or left trigger at the same time.
not just down. no, no, don't start over.
I wanted to get out of the pause menu. accidental button press god. it's all right.
that's not worth it. it's 10. who cares. it's not worth it. it's not worth it. I'm freaking
out again. jump up the, oh, toad, come here. oh, it's got my sights on me. toad, get back
over. I'm not trying to peek the mic. this is a bunch of free one-ups.
almost enough, right? red toad is back.
I think one-ups I would have if I didn't do the ground pound. bark, bark. let's go talk to
red toad and see if red toad has anything for us to do. something cool. red toad,
thank you so much for saving me. that was legitimately terrifying, but they just let me
go out of the blue. not that I'm complaining. maybe I was taken by mistake. why can I just
jump off the edge? sleeping on the job. there you are. hey, kid, want to help me out with a
job? you help me out, I'll erase the blocks on top of the pipe over there. molten rain.
your target this time is seven lava bubbles. once that, you don't know how to take out
lava bubbles. you want to pack your lunch too? don't worry so much, amigo. you'll figure it
out. defeat seven bubbles. I'll try. mario's like 40. mario's way older than 40.
oh. 58. get them all. for the true ending. never mind. who cares? give me one.
all right. take them down. this is the guy that beat dark souls. yeah, this is the guy that beat
the last boss in securo. the true last boss. stop. settle down. did he just, like, die?
he just used his whole head to do that. is he all right? anymore? he's got more.
erase the blocks gumming up the path over there. spiny busters. kill 15 spines.
use whatever tools you have at your disposal. adios. I'm counting on you.
so how do you give her to be, uh, spines? I get it. okay, I got them, but it doesn't work.
come on. I can get it. ready? oh, no, no. I got it. I'm fine. touch it? I clearly touched
that. that was pretty clear. get rid of the path here. sweet. nice work, kid. out. off those
blocks now. all right, uh, you lousy bunch of blocks. this is going to hurt me a lot more
than it hurt you. adios. that's it. there's 10 coins. I make 10 coins in my sleep. you help
me out. I'll give you some fancy clothes. I got $1,229. I make that in my sleep.
a single pom-pom. this time your target is a single pom-pom. they probably know
you're coming, so expect a trap. adios. and I get a t-shirt. defeat one pom-pom.
everyone's streaming Mario Maker 2 today? well, it is brand new. brand new game on
a beloved franchise. reach the goal to defeating all the pom-poms. let me hit you! oh!
oh, that's the one. you gotta let her do it. what the? one more time. thanks for the key.
you moving too much? I gotta move enough. so what's the, uh, what I get for, uh,
clothing? I love it. it's like a cookie monster shirt. can I put these on? or is
that my me? I think that's my me. what does this put? okay, hold on. where does this go?
new area. why did you do that? hello. have time for a job? there's something good in you for you.
house of blocks. we're in the market for a new house, and we need someone to inspect this place
we found. hit the blocks and climb to the top to check it out. you can also tilt
and mid or ground pound. hello. I hate doing that.
so the goal is that it's the climbers. I like the background. start building?
yeah, so I'm getting too caught up in the cartoon characters. how that works?
all the way back down. really? oh, please. was this super easy, boy?
good music. I'll take the music track. okay, get out of the way. I almost did it again.
can't. get me up there. no! there's a coin! I can get by. I'll just go back.
whatever. I got plenty of money. it was ten. it wasn't that big of a deal.
I'm gonna go build the rest of the hall. thank you. all right, I'm gonna make something good.
buildy buildy, roo roo, miracle roo. oh, cool. I put a special block somewhere.
well, you just told me where it was. stop being mad. mad? what do you mean mad?
all right, we got... no, I need to go talk to the chief. we need to start instruction. anyway,
main hall, third floor is complete. the castle is bursting at the seams with elegance. it's
looking... it's like looking into a mirror. we have new building options now. west hall cannon.
that sounds fun. and I can afford the west hall top. 582. west hall doors. do it. I am gonna
go hit that block though. so what's in the special blocks? why would I ask... chat that question
when in the time that there's like a five second... three to five second delay, I would have
already hit it in none. what's wrong with you? I want to punch toad in the mouth so fucking bad.
why? what's... why would you say something like that? yellow toad's been sleeping.
paw wake up call. reach the goal after defeating all nine spinies. hit some paw blocks.
you might be able to wake up this nameless toad. so we're gonna defeat all the spinies. punch him
in the mouth. where's the other one? just... just... it's done, right? that's it. nine out of
nine. get out. that was quick. that was cool. 40%. 41... 42%. something like that.
I had to go through all that to wake him up. why wouldn't I just kick him? I mean like gently.
or just scream. does it lean down and just be like... hey! hey! wake up! yawn. that was a
quality nap. couldn't get my hands on the stone that the chief wanted so I took a nap instead.
would you go and bring me back some stone? let's see. yeah I think this would do.
it's gonna be easy. reach the goal while holding a stone. bring me a stone. reach
the goal while holding a stone. where's the stone? one of these? can I break one of these off?
you didn't mention what stone. you just said a stone.
can I actually play as Luigi? I don't want to call him though.
I don't want to talk to him. somebody else call him. that very clearly was eaten and
puked up. where's the stone? how am I supposed to get up there? I mean that's how I'm gonna do it.
where's the stone? I didn't even see a stone to pick up. oh! kill them! eight seconds! you can't
throw... it's too heavy. I tried to throw it up like three times. the thing is really heavy.
twitch acting! get out of here! this is bullshit! this is bullshit! oh my god! I get called one more
time by Luigi. I'm gonna fucking be mad. gimme this motherfucker! get over here! kill all of
them! kill them all! literally kill them all! I don't want to see any of their faces ever
again. that's what's making this so stupid is just dodging the fucking six bones that are on
the screen at the same time. get out of here! all right now I can play the game. they're gonna
come back aren't they? I'm so like tilted right now. I guess someone called me an actor
because I couldn't throw a brick on top of the stove or whatever the dumb thing is. oh yeah?
yeah? is that what it is guys? come on man! go! I gotta get three! oh do I need more?
I need more than one! I'm gonna lose time again. actor! thank you for the applause! that was a pretty
good acting job. that was a one star quest. oh go get more stones this time. make sure you eat
it through the wall. I'm gonna do this one first try here. this doesn't require me to eat
it through the wall with Yoshi. I'm gonna get this. wall jump off this?
oh my god it's already fucking time to go to bed. oh shit hold on.
dive kick. I want those. whatever I don't have time for this. I thought that was gonna kill me
for a second. where's the uh bomb? there's gonna be a bomb here. oh no what can I kick?
what did I just do? what did I just do? what did I just do? okay hold on. I want that.
I want that shit. I don't think I can get it. the bomb bomb thing was gone.
I thought another uh bomb build thing was gonna fall. such emotional range.
good acting. all right one more. and the stones. I hate the stone ones.
the worst addition to the game so far. let me go. let me actually go up.
oh you got you got a combination of a stone level and a water level.
I may as well just punch the toe in the face like that guy wanted to like an hour ago.
no don't let it fall.
the active thing is making me laugh like over and over again.
I need the water to come down.
no up. thank you. only five? I'm so tilted about the actor joke.
no I'm not tilted about the actor joke. I'm tilted about the stone.
I couldn't do the stone and because I couldn't do the stone level
the fact that somebody said that I was pretending to not know how to do the stone level
because I didn't know how to do that. it was infuriating me because I actually didn't know.
calm down and have some jello. all right I got I can I can do it with the build.
this new area looks pretty good. that was close. oh that car almost hit me.
I flinched and moved. I felt that one coming in here. okay I need a thousand.
so that is that all the jobs that um stone toad wanted me to do?
so let's get some more money. is it gonna take forever? I'm already 52% of the way there.
it's only three and a half hours guys. what are we talking about? booze towering house of terror.
am I gonna play animal crossing when it comes out? maybe. that depends on if anybody wants to see it.
it's worth the shot. I felt the world start moving to the right so I figured maybe
this is a possibility. jeez. come on. come over. careful. careful. scooby doo house.
um sure. gonna go all the way to here. this is making my blood moldy.
blood mold. and why do you have blood sitting out? that's I think a better question. those ones
are faster. oh man. oh man. what do I do about this? I think I have to go over like this.
oh man. oh why did I turn? oh my god. I want a mushroom. I don't feel safe right now.
I need a mushroom. once the blood gets out it starts to sour. I don't. I don't. oh yeah right.
talking about like the blood that you were eating or something right? big showdown on
little star. has toad given me any four star levels? it is one. it's already done though.
yeah that's what I already did. big showdown on little star. if anyone receives this transmission
please help. bowser jr has invaded this small planet and we require assistance. the gravity is
odd here but you can still hold b while bouncing off of enemies to do a super jump. stomp bowser
into submission. oh cute song. it told me if I held b it would jump off of this and you told
me if I held b. I'm holding b right now. I'm holding b at the moment. right now. it's not
that bad. not as bad as I originally thought it was gonna be. here's the moon. can do anything?
the moon attacks you too? he has a smiling face. the sun is angry. moon shouldn't be like
this. worth a shot to see if anything in here. you guys weren't kidding when you said it gets
you lives. try to avoid it the whole time. okay. is that bowser jr? this is like infant bowser.
thanks for the key. love thud. see I want to play more levels like this. the fun cute ones.
boring boomer levels. well you gotta do them. you gotta make the money.
uh what do we need? a thousand? what about the little block down there? no I need money.
I'll go do the block stuff when I get enough money to build again. red yoshi's cheap cheap
cleanup. reach the goal after defeating at least 25 cheap cheeps. he's only in it for
the money. yes in mario maker 2. am I gonna do any created levels tonight? um yeah we'll
probably see. I'm assuming I'll get this single player stuff done in um probably in the next
couple hours. we'll see. we'll see how it goes. am I gonna hurt him? I missed a couple.
free. shit. shit. shit. oh no. oh that's fine. wait it's not fine. can I do it again?
I don't need yoshi anymore right? all right let's go. but yeah after the end of this
this will probably take us to the six to seven hour mark. I feel like I would just do mario
maker 2 again. I'll just do uh created levels because I feel like I don't know part of me says
that the multiplayer there's probably some cool stuff but it hasn't even been a day. I think
I'd want to give at least a few days or something for people to make cool levels.
all right this one's two star. hit the on off switch to get the pink coins.
there's been some neat stuff already. yeah we'll see how this is. I'm having a great time here.
this is just what I'm looking for right now. do a germa level thing. that's another thing too.
I mean if people wanted to make stuff I will. I'm definitely gonna play this again.
that's certain. so maybe people want to make some stuff they fairly felt like it.
all right so hold on. I'm gonna do this like puzzle. all right so there's that.
there's that one. and okay we could do this. two. oops. I gotta get that.
there's one. there's two. there's three. switch it off first.
it's a daisy. oops. just keep it on. what are you doing? now turn it off after it bounces.
I want to give you my pokemon cards. you keep your keep your pokemon cards.
this is gonna be worth like thousands of dollars one day. oh shit. okay hold on. I gotta time this.
no no no no. keep I'm gonna keep it locked in on the other one. and then now we do it.
not now. no. so I can get it. nice. should I break them all? or at least these ones?
there might be some treasure in here or something. it's possible.
all the ones I have to step on. like that. if it ain't broke don't fix it. I thought there
might be a coin thing in there. secret block. right. that's what I'm saying. if it ain't fixed
don't break it. blink blank blunk. I made a house for ant troopers out of blinking blocks.
can someone check to make sure the path is clear? I will do it. and then after this I
have enough money to do the other wing. I need 1100. and then we'll go back down to the block
guy and see what he wants to do. bye. that was instant. I'm gonna fall over here so I can just
kill him. like that. yeah these look. yeah the ants look super weird. they really do.
I gotta get as many coins as I can possibly grab with two hands. can I say ants again? ants.
why?
thought that was the end. two three.
you fucking idiot. oh my god. I tried to do it so fast. it's all right. I'm right here. two three.
what the fuck just happened to be. no.
okay I'm fine. that's 50. slow down. I'm just gonna fall. all right I'm good. just jump on them.
unnecessary. unnecessary. in between. I love in between all this.
somebody just writes. why this like. I don't even understand. all right.
uh west hall roof. might as well just finish the west hall. now I'm gonna go down to the block guy.
construction has started on the west hall roof. we got the construction cover. just get out of
here. seven new jobs. but I want to go over here because now doing these jobs will complete
the building. right? okay darkness ahead. darkness below. could you take a look at
the basement and tell us how spacious it is? maybe a dark level. do I have any thoughts
on gaming? no. not really. it's pretty fun. this one's gonna be hell. I remember
doing this one in donkey kong country and it made me break a like a nintendo 64 controller.
oh no. whatever it was. super nintendo. scary. actually scary. there's a lot of coins though.
I can't wait for people to make horror games. they're going to. oh why did I wait that
extra second for. I waited a half second for no reason. I don't know why I did that.
it hurts. glare. ding dong. did I find a secret? get me out of that one. amazon package. yeah
that's true. all right. after this next one I'm going to take the first break in the night.
I'm going to grab something to drink. go to the bathroom and I might even eat
a piece of turkey as quickly as I can. where are you putting this one? I put a oh a hidden block.
red flower. red flower. interesting. you got any more? yep. one last job and we get an
outfit. finally found a place that we love but it's been infested by the whomps. could you
please survey the damage they've done? yeah. hi top. the whomp tower. can I stand on his head?
I can. sometimes I don't know. cranberry sauce is fruit jello. whatever your opinion is on that
I respect it and that's fine. that's it. I probably could have seen that one coming but
I didn't. he's getting impatient. this is where it starts to derail if he does anything
else stupid. calm down. Jesus. oh oh same audio clip. oh oh oh oh for real. I have to get that.
I just had to trigger it so much earlier. I just got that was hit. oh dude hitbox point.
hitbox. oh I missed a secret. I don't care. the stream title is actually better than others.
oh it's yeah it's just you should have seen it before. I went through two or three iterations.
I love this shirt. what was it before I turned the stream on? it was it to me and then space
in brackets. hey greg smith. I just want to let you know if you're watching if you come across
this you have a package that I have for you. just come in and confirm that it's your package.
end bracket. it was something like that. it was like a whole three sentences. all right well
I gotta find that hidden block. yeah it also was haha what? wait red flower? I'm gonna make a
wicket. so what's up here? 50. oh there's a frog up here. secret frog. a castle so grand you
build yet still the atmosphere lacks. if you'll do me a favor I'll cover the ground with
flowers so sweet. cheap cheap maze. this one's pretty hard. this is sound frog. it's super
frog. no I hope it has candy. take the break? I forgot. sorry it's underwater. delete. I'm just
gonna close my eyes. I'm closing my eyes right now. I don't who cares to go. how am I doing?
have I hit anything yet? I think I'm in a wall I think. I'm definitely like trapped in a wall.
should I open my eyes? I'm gonna open them. okay well I'm just like floating here. that's
cool. was I just floating the whole time? turn it into the orchestra one.
okay I'm fine. can I make it? is it enough? is that's enough? no it's not. is that space
there? fucking just don't do that. play. thought about it. I lost all the coins that I got though.
pissing me off. pissing me off. okay good. oh my god. I'm just I don't like this one.
what the fuck. oh my god. I gotta take that break. no I don't. do it. get it done.
yeah I do. you know I don't. should I go over them? I guess. oh god.
I have to do the whole thing again. guys I don't have a switch anymore.
I just frisbeated out the window as hard as I could. oh the music box. never mind.
you guys are trapped here forever. oh come on. just whatever. oh what the hell.
oh my god. it's the floatiness of the water combined with the smallness of the character
combined with the music in the background combined with the darkness that is making
me have a problem. got them all didn't I? no I didn't. no I got it. okay. I'm good.
are you mad? are you mad at us? how could I be mad at you guys? for what? my thanks are yours.
the flowers bloom and down we get... ribbit. do the floss please. brightness. come on. two more,
right? yes there's more. that means they're gonna be harder. I'll move some mountains.
hold your breath. another underwater one. uh I'm determined to show my dearest my finest
qualities. I know she'd be impressed to see me swim across the river without once coming
up for air. reach the goal without getting out of the water. I'm not looking forward to this.
is this the way to kill mario?
please grab this. whatever it is. you missed. just...
I didn't get out. I'm still in. I was holding my head under the water.
get away from me. can I step on your head? yes I can. don't. fire under water? don't
really make much sense. I know but it is video game. I was looking over a chat.
someone told me to shut up so I just looked at it. I was like hey why'd that person say shut up?
why is everything 10 fps? shouldn't be. this one's a lot easier than the last one. I'm not
gonna choke. I'm good. I'm gonna choke. that took longer than winning going forward.
I thought it was gonna be a mushroom. I wasn't on top of his head? I wasn't on top of his
head. I was on his head. I don't understand that. I'm going fast. go up water. go up go up.
already got it. don't even need it. all right come on. do this underwater level while holding
your breath in real life. that's a pretty dumb idea. so I'm gonna have to say I'm gonna
decline that gamer funny challenge there. just shoot him. I'm still in.
oh oh oh I'm sorry about the mic being peaked. I really am. I'm not like this. this is the first
stream you've ever watched on my channel. I'm not like this. I don't like... did he just
get rid of the pole? how do I complete the level? I don't usually... no I don't usually
snore. you're right. this gg idiot. what is this? I can't even hear it anyways. never mind.
I think I might have the headphones plugged in. the mountains move. a groove so funky. here we go.
there they come. kind of ugly. got anything else? you got one more. it's gonna be a four star.
special close. it is a four star difficulty sea of sorrow. my dearest has dumped me and
so I float aimlessly adrift on a sea of sorrow wallow with me mario. that got sort of sad.
is this supposed to be him crying? get in the shoe. what? punch all of the ghosts in the face?
look at chap. he doesn't know and that's why I look over there.
let's continue. watch out. you're gonna crush the blocks, right? and then come down.
come down? do you come down?
guess you kind of do.
all the way? what's over here?
this is one of those freaky levels. yeah this is a freaky one.
what's the goal here? what's the end goal? well leave me be please. I can't believe he
just fucking sniped me. you gotta be kidding me. it's all right. this is it, right? okay.
that wasn't even really that bad but it kind of was. oh frog cap. what does this mold your
blood thing? I don't understand. don't mold your blood. mold mold. is this like a new
thing that I don't know what it is? yawn. okay seven jobs. how much is it to build?
okay keep up the good work. I'm gonna do main hall roof. I need 1500. I need money.
is there a uh there's no cost. I can't like change my costume right now.
all right we got three more and then we got a pretty hard one. so
deep in the windy valley. can you withstand the cold and make it to the bottom of the
valley? let's see. am I not gonna make any courses? not on stream. no. I am absolutely 100%
not capable of making a interesting level on this stream. no way. I'm gonna wait till the
wind blows this way. he doesn't believe in himself. I mean I just I just don't believe I
could make anything that was worth watching because I have no idea what the hell I'm doing.
I didn't do the I didn't really make any the first one. I'd have to relearn all the tools
that would be like a six hour tutorial stream. I'd rather just make the cool shit that people have
and enjoy the awesome creativity that the community puts forth after I beat the single
player because this is fucking fun and I almost got really mad. there's the key.
played league of legends. now that's something I can guarantee I have never heard before on
this channel. that's a lot of coins. I'll take it. gonna play league. sorry. unfortunately.
not gonna be playing league of legends on this channel. he offered you to play league. I
doubled. I will double it if you don't. whatever he will offer you to play league,
I'll double it if you don't. can I just say no? why does that have to be money involved?
they're getting a little harder. seesaw's ancient seesaw fortress.
you don't have to play lol but you have to make an obnoxious youtube ad for it.
does league have what the hell did I just say? oh I'm respawning. I already blew the
opportunity. can I just die? kill me. there are there are league of legends youtuber ads.
you don't actually have been seeing a lot of lately on ipad especially ipad games.
is pretend youtubers and fake pretend streamers. they're playing the game that they're advertising
on their whatever their 15 20 30 second ad is and they pretend that this is a youtuber.
like oh my god I can't believe it. guys so this new game that came out it's just like
this that's not a real person. it's a fake name too. like this person is not a streamer.
they have a username and all and the person doesn't exist.
uh should I be doing something here? I guess not. uh come on do I not weigh enough?
come on get it up there. come on give you the shoe. I just got like pinballed
but it's okay I'm really not that far away. actually wait a minute come down here.
I want I could hit that coin I think. yeah get over here. get over here. just step off.
oh you are really really being dumb. didn't get it. lost a pinball. I know. I know and it's
really funny that I lost a pinball. cannons. hey how do I get down there? don't go faster
than the ball. oh um this is gonna unearth the bombs. how long does it take for them to explode?
oh man don't. hey how do. it's gotta walk up this. like that. this shit's dangerous.
that was real. I sneezed. that was sneeze. now my back hurts. do I have to launch you up here?
I have to walk you all the way up here. does it know what I have to do?
why is he so much heavier? he's so much heavier than me.
oh come on. is he doing the chad pose? what is the chad pose?
first of all I gotta knock. I gotta get his. I gotta think about this because what happens
if I fuck this up? oh I don't have it anymore. sometimes you gotta just hit take the damage
frames. damage frames are not cheating. they're a part of the game. all right let's build.
uh how much do I need? 12? 15. yeah I want that top roof done first. or you know what? nah.
no I want. yeah let's complete the top roof. this is the. this one's worth 300. dash on,
dash off four stars. dash through and flip the switch. rush ahead with all your might.
faster than the speed of light. change charge ahead into your sparkling future. 300 bucks
four stars. I have to go that fast apparently. oh well uh yes I do it's timed. okay never mind.
noises. zero zero zero. okay miss calling. that's that's not a whole lot of time.
look what we can do. oh now that was a funny noise. construction has started in the main
hall. where are we getting close? I think I can do this in like another hour or so.
I don't know. I'm gonna get at least to the end of this. I'm into this. I'm having a blast. funny
noise. I'm clapping. I'm clapping at my computer screen. uh boo ring course. boring course.
I think you can get through it and return. already lost. play community levels? I will.
I'm going to. I'm trying to enjoy the entire experience. this ring is just gonna
follow the whole time huh? I need to see what's out there. can I see more of that level?
what the hell? this is dangerous. this I can't see. oh boy. more coins? more? one more. come on.
one more coin. one more. let me get you. okay. what's next? they explode into many boos.
all right. I gotta go. I have to go right now. I gotta go right now. I have to go.
let that sit there. it's all right. not a big deal. where's the explosion?
explosion. damage frame Susan. yes. easy easy easy easy. that wasn't easy. it was quickly.
it was quickly. haven't really played like 50 something levels. underground piranha creeper.
the underground menace. I'll pay you to take care of it. 40 equals 50. I have played 50
something level because I did 40 in a row here on this list and then I also did the dog.
I also did the eraser head man. I also did the yawning guy. it's like 55 or something.
you don't think I know what I'm doing?
oh shit. I gotta outrun the snake. I like these things. this is cool.
fire flower? give it here. shit. I swear to god. I swear to god. I just...
the stick against the wall thing is just... I'm not... I just...
I had it but then I did go on the other side. that's a big oof.
this is the ASMR level. I'm gonna get that 10 points. watch.
damage breaks. oh my god. don't do it again, Jeremy. please.
the button. the stupid little tiny fucking chocolate chip buttons. I pressed them all.
I got a niece, right? this niece is... is that... she's six. I really do believe
that she would have trouble holding this and pressing buttons because her hands are too big.
if this guy kills me, I quit.
I have to... liar. I will... hold on. I'm gonna quit. that doesn't mean I'm gonna...
I'm gonna watch luigi beat it for this. liar.
all right. I quit. cigarettes. I'm not gonna smoke them anymore.
that's... that's what I meant. today's the day. save me, snake walk. sure.
need to find novel ways to use the snake block. this is gonna be fun.
do you actually smoke? no. like, you just... no. no. because, you know, obviously no. I don't.
I do not. you know, if it were me playing the game right now,
I would have jumped and freaked out like five times. sometimes. you just have a confidence
boost here that you can do anything. for instance, I can do anything. I can do anything.
I don't even need to look. I wasn't aware you could get crushed on the top of the screen.
I didn't know the screen had a sky block. and why did it kill me? the screen goes up.
what? one of these mario video game historians tell me why that happened.
that's going too fast. gotta keep up. come on. I'm moving fast as the screen is going.
oh, shit. do more. 63%. almost do the other side. with a land of the dark level. pitch black
underground. this one's gonna be a blast. change the outfit. the outfit is only for my me,
isn't it? because I don't want to lose my weight. what? I? okay. I thought I could jump on it.
does it keep going? you just beat the light. you go forward. how do I not get any of this?
I don't know. well, was something else supposed to get? oh, my god.
thanks for the help, Luigi. do I run out of these or something? how do I delete them?
can I delete them? I hate this. I'm just gonna take it slow.
the p is just the light. it's no other purpose. what the fuck?
I just gotta let it go forward. I'm leaning back in my chair. that's bad. I gotta get up.
okay. follow the p and prepare for that shit. how do I get those?
I'm missing so many cool secrets. was it 50? is it 50? can you tell? is it 50?
30. can I stand on those? holy fuck. I was looking. you've gotta be fucking kidding me.
I thought I... I am so dumb. I was looking at chat. I thought it was gonna just take me
like the whole way around. can I get that 50? I can ride that POW. where's the rest of that?
I need the POW to be over here. I think I have to jump. holy shit. be careful. it's up.
okay. what did that do? anything for me? not really. what if I hit the POW? will that get
the coin? I made it. I didn't get the 30 coins, though. one more. it fell down. oh, shit.
bouncing through the clouds. reach the goal after grabbing at least 40 coins.
and there's a bunch of bullet bills. gotta get 40. there's no time.
with the quickness. with the swiftness there. maybe you guys said bullet hell.
and there it is. and there it is. and see what. I just gotta pay attention to where the
bullets are. and not that else. I have plenty of time. holy shit. I'm just gonna kill them.
now. that's it. with 65 seconds to spare. very cool. how long do switch controllers last?
outside the dock at full charge. more than like seven or eight hours? or is it less than that?
there's the top of the castle. it's done. now we gotta finish the right side.
avant-garde style of the interior parapets. it looks amazing. keep up the good work.
east hall. second floor. build it. congrats on the main hall. roof germa. thank you.
thanks. that means a lot. thank you. how many. all right. did I do all the jobs back here?
the first five. all right. the first five pages are completely done. all right. we got
bumper jump around. bumper jump around. I added some bumpers to my athletic course.
change outfit. I will. after this level, I'm gonna change my outfit. we'll see what it looks
like. all this shit saves, right? well, now I gotta use gamer skill or else I'm not gonna make it.
that's what I need. pick me up. pick me up. I avoided everything else. this time I actually
have the hat on. get all the coins. good job. don't blow it again.
what am I doing? hurry up and get it. such a stressful game. it just is. flag was right here.
this should be relaxing. you know, it's weird because it's 50% relaxing. 50% build the castle.
I just want to build it. I kind of don't care about anything else.
platforms really are stressful. change my mind. I don't think I have to change your mind.
I think I probably agree with you. we've got a couple of relaxing ones ahead of us though.
master the trees. we just have to climb some trees. reach the goal if you're doing a hand
stand on all the trees. this is a one star. what time is the movie night tomorrow? same time
as the regular spring. by the way, if you have not gotten a submission in and you want to,
make sure you get it in by tonight because if you get it in by tomorrow morning, afternoon,
pacific, it's gonna be hard to add you to the list. oh, I forgot to change the outfit. I'll do
it after this. never mind. I guess we'll do it now. and remember that this tomorrow is not a
contest. we're just picking some of the, I guess we're gonna, there's like a, essentially
a net to try to catch some of the higher quality submissions. ready to submit? there's
a google form. only submit one video. we can get the google form link if somebody has it.
and it has to include video footage from the green screen. you can't just, you can't just
submit. I'm not gonna say it because somebody will. so just make sure it's green screen.
okay, hold on. were you running through this?
what am i talking about? so six months ago or so, we did a green screen movie night where i
went in front of the green screen and recorded like six or seven hours with the stuff.
and then the community came together and made a bunch of random stuff that was the green screen
movie night. there were hundreds and hundreds of videos that we watched.
and people thought it was a lot of fun, so for the longest time, i wanted to do another one, which is
not as long as the first one. that's what tomorrow night is. that dive kick is freaking me out.
climb up. done. am i gonna get bounced around here until i die? oh my god. jeremy, turn up my
jeremy. turn up my mic. what's wrong with my mic? it looks fine over here. on my end, it looks like
everything's fine. i don't know. that's weird. maybe when i got really loud it just fucked up.
all right, outfit. yeah, no, no, no. outfit, outfit, outfit, outfit. it's hard to hear me.
i swear to god, there's some weird thing how this pulls in through obs and pushes out.
because over on my obs, it looks like i'm about to peek every single sentence i say. it's strange.
i'm at like just about like minus eight db, or minus like five, like into the red. so i don't
know. that's weird. i get that a lot though. it's definitely not just one person. so don't
ask me why it's like that. i'll dial myself up a little bit here. all right, so what do
i go to do this stuff? back to the title, notification settings, play guide, back to title.
like where would i do this? watch me lose all that progress. okay, play, right? course world.
my stream's always relatively quiet. i wonder why. there i am doing the charlie brown dance.
change outfit. i got some new hats. where are they? where are they? i got another one,
didn't i? oh, it's weirdly spaced. oh, i have an animated hoodie. is that for pre-ordering the
game or something? i like this one. and then what's the full suit? oh, it's the dress.
okay, i like the cookie monster though. there we go. hyped. that's how i'm always just so
hyped, right? that's usually what? change face? no. all right, i'm not ready for this yet.
i want to... i'm still building the house. upside down stretches. i think my life would be better
if i didn't watch germa. well, i... that's a... i mean, that's like a... that's a... that's a you
thing. i... i don't know how to tell you about... and i just jumped off the edge because
i'm just trying to... i'm reading. i'd probably get more shit done, to be honest.
don't go anywhere. don't go anywhere just yet. hold on a second here. what about those
funny tuber moments? what if you... what if you missed the... all right, i'm done. not with the
game, but just like with what i was just doing. no, i'm not. i'm gonna keep going. what about those
funny tuber moments? but you might miss those if you didn't hang out. why hasn't luigi decided
to help me in a long time? he blocked him. no, he blocked me. why did i just... how do i rate
this level? i want to give it a one star. he's doing his own shit and living his own life.
all right, any buttons to press? no. don't kill me. they worked hard on this. how could you say that?
yeah, i worked hard on my birdhouse there and people told me that i was stupid and it sucked.
are we gonna... will we have a couple of different standards here? is that
understood? careful. careful here. careful. careful. i can't go up there. how am i gonna
get away from that? all right, i'm good. watch out. there's the one dude there is just kind
of hanging out. this is messing up my head here. this is screwing up my brain. i have to get rid
of that thing. there we go. all right, i got through that. get rid of this snot ghost. almost
there. cock strikes again. yeah, unfortunately they tend to do that. i have to get a running
start. be careful. okay, hold on. how can i get that? this is bad. this is gonna be bad,
right? can i fall and then go to the right? i mean, yeah, i need the left. no flag either.
that was... that was close. you're right. that was a close one. get all the coins.
oh, shit. no, that's... that's not okay. that's not good. i can do the whole thing again.
no, i had... i did have a flag. i did. why does it feel so far away?
no, that's not okay. did i die in mario maker or did i like rear end somebody
in traffic? oh, no, that's not okay. that's not okay. oh, no. all right, i gotta get this again.
all right, luigi is adamant on giving me parts here for some reason. he's like,
are you sure you don't want these? are you sure? you're probably gonna need them.
just jump over everybody. all right, so can i just flip it upside down again?
or right side up, should i say? oh, oh well. is the audio delayed again? i don't know what
is with this thing. why is everybody doing minus two? i didn't... i just... i didn't do anything.
all right, ready? two. one. i don't know. i didn't see... people are abusing that now.
i'm seeing some abuse on that system. you said right side up. yeah, but i just had a slip.
i just... i wasn't... i just... whatever. i don't even... it's not explaining. i'm dead. i'm
dead. i'm dead. i'm gonna die. i'm gonna die. i'm dead. all right, float me over there. you gotta
watch out for when the little things pop. pop. it's over the coins. what does this do for me?
nothing. um, do i need to go in that? oh, look at... did you see that hitbox? i did and it was
bad. i couldn't even believe it. why is this... oh, he's like, we're gonna back problem now.
there are too many people standing on this and i... i'm too panicky to get rid of them all.
now they... it's like just rolling the dice. nobody can do that. nobody can effectively do that.
if you do something like that, you jump on a shell that's in that small quarters,
just throw dice in the air. oh. oh. oh. what? oh, it's blocked. this one's kind of hard.
i would just stand in the middle, but you can't really do that either.
greed. tilt it up? oh, shit. no, it's gonna be down. not that far down.
i've been streaming this for like five and a half hours. i haven't even asked the question yet.
so are these levels levels that were made by nintendo teams? or were they brought over
from the first game? or are these just, hey, check a look at what you can do and what you're
capable of? and they got on. made by nintendo. showing some of the new features and stuff.
that's cool. half of these mechanics were not even in mario maker 1. that makes sense.
cool. what's left to build? you know what i mean? how much left of the castle is there to do?
new building options. what is now? okay, east hall cannon, east hall doors,
and what? the red carpet? watch it turn around and you only do the front side of the castle.
it's just cut in half and i have to do the back. let's do another job.
ant trooper march. then i've done these somehow already, a bunch of them.
let's clean up ant trooper march. hope you like to use why.
good luck. why? let's run. or dash. good music, boys and girls. no, never mind.
holy fuck, this is fast. that's really fast. they ramped that up real quick. it starts off
like this and then they just drag the screen over. get out of here, luigi. i'm gonna let
luigi do the last level. just get in. i don't, i have to get over this. kind of not fair.
he's holding down. oh shit. it's too fast. oh. mario, i wish you wouldn't just grab onto ledges
like that. stop grabbing onto ledges and hit the... he just bounced twice on his butt.
he didn't even slide. he bounced. i died in the glass. you should be safe in the glass.
he should be able to die in the glass. i even followed their instructions, too. what's after
that? perfect. sweet. that was really short. a lot of money for not a lot of time. 75. almost
there. the castle is almost done. we're so close. fly-by-night clown car. it's not
one of those fly-around-and-shoot-things levels. all right, gotta kill bowser. should be easy
enough. i blew it. oh, i want to restart. just do that again. uh, best song. again.
one bowser's. triple shot. all right, let me get a good pace here. talk... i should have gotten hit
there. it's a miraculous way i did not receive damage. already time to go. you have to play
the panic music on me. what is that? he's dead? one bowser's. i'm just playing cuphead. speaking
of cuphead, when does the new cuphead stuff come out? this dlc that's primed. soon here,
right? is there gonna be one real answer in this? i guess not. the doors and the cannon.
and that's all there is left. you know, there's probably like a cherry you put on top or like
a whip cream or something. no date set? just sometime in 2019. cool. i will be into that.
lava rising three stars. 200 bucks. don't even need to read the description because i know
what it is. there's just some finesse work to do after this. yeah, i want to try the
multiplayer too. once it's not day one, i would put some time into this. the reason why i wanted
to do the single player first is because last time i jumped right into expert levels
and i wanted to quit the game forever. and i did. that's close. i'd like to get back into
the groove of playing a mario game before i do the hardest levels i can possibly imagine.
well that's ways more. what should i do? oh my god, the lava comes up. right. shoot shoot
what's that? someone link the i quit clip from a... i did not think that was gonna go that fast.
was there an actual i quit moment? no, that's real. hold on. no no no no. i'm
talking about from like two years ago. dude, this is the wall. here comes the wall.
this is the wall. i'm at like 77 percent where i made it to the uh to the gear check.
holy fuck. does it go down? don't leave me behind here. oh my god. oh no i was on it.
no i have to do the whole fucking thing again. it's just a line on the screen. it's a loading
screen. you're not even gonna have luigi actually do something? they just let you win.
there's nothing else. and it's an actual just full-on win. uh okay. well oh but they get
they look what they do to you though. they put a luigi flag on it just to remind you forever.
i'll go back and do it as mario. the wops and chain chomps and passable castle
pick up buzzy shells with y and wear them. but that ain't gonna happen. i've got like
a lot of gas in my like upper gi track. it won't come out. i want to burp but i
feel like if i burp too hard, if i try i'll throw up. you know what i'm saying? you guys
have been there before? too much information? i did i gave i gave you barely any information
there actually. that could have been way more explicit. how do i get you up there?
you don't come up here? oh god just do it! just do it! just go! just do it! i know. i
don't know if i should have done that. i definitely should not have done that. but
get the flag. forget about the coins. they're not important.
hmm i could bump it up but i can't. i don't have the helmet anymore.
y. that's fantastic. ends all the way over there. great. give it to me. come on back.
big enough to get it. so i think i have to kill bowser with the guy's face. this is
gonna be annoying. you can't go through here, can you? i can still hear him. got him.
easier than i thought. i thought i had to get him hit by the the whomps. but apparently
not. just had to hit the axe. six fifty six sixty fifth. six six feet. i can't even talk.
83. any more jobs? so what happens when we finish this? i still have like 20 levels left to do.
lava bubble limbo. create an ocean of lava bubbles but now i can't get through it.
get through i'll pay you. i don't remember peaches castle having artillery. there's a
new thing? there's a new development? so what's the deal here? i just have to
swim with this? just get through it. but get through what?
fire flower. nice. i just have to swim with them. okay well. easy enough. that fish was freaking me
out. all right so i made it. now that they get bigger i get it. they just make it more annoying
to have to weed through. i really should be more in front. i was dilly dallying too much.
not gonna be good. double bounce. that was good. wasn't that bad. it was pretty easy. help. i can't
hold my breath anymore. we'll stop doing that. you don't have to do that to impress me. you
don't have to do that. let it go. i was still building the castle. we are. i think we're done.
i think there's just finishing touches because we're. what else is there to build?
you got something else for me? all right we're making great progress. i need a new word to
describe how great this new section is. how about splendorificana zarivalis.
we have a new building option. oh the roof. the roof of the east hall. okay. all right.
okay that's fine. dry bones lava lurker. reach the goal after defeating all the dry bones.
i'll hold my breath for. let's see. is it water in this one? well there's lava.
they're collecting taxes from the residents of mushroom kingdom.
that doesn't sound nice. why would i collect taxes from them? it's not like king mario
and like queen. all right. you know what? who's the queen? there is no king and queen. why is
there a princess? and is there a prince? does it drop? don't get it yet. i don't know.
the mushroom kingdom is a principality. bowser is the king. bowser is not the king.
who are all the toads? are they like are they supposed to be you know servants of the castle?
butlers? and but where is the king and queen? there isn't one. whose goddamn castle is this?
princess toadstool. but who was before princess toadstool? blinking block blitz. two stars.
there's a plumber in a non-toileted society and you're upset about the missing
monarchy. there's definitely toilets. there's definitely toilets. we're about to install them.
i hate cat mario. i don't like it at all. where's dog mario? i'm already losing time.
get in there. i'm gonna get inside. ready? one two three click. stop doing like the m bison move.
i hate the cat. i don't like the cat. i don't like the cat. i hate the cat.
i'm not gonna pick the power up app. i'm just gonna do the level without the cat.
all right i'm good. i want that 10 bucks. just give me the give to me.
where's the flag?
cat levels stone level are better than cat levels. let's pick that up. no. and you
attach to every single fucking wall. i don't want to grab every wall mario. i tried to
grab the tree. i hate this character. i hate it. i'm gonna lose again. no i'm not. i'm throwing
off. i'm getting the costume off. i just want to oh my god i it's the costume. it's the god.
vader it's the goblin. it's the goblin. i swear to god i i never want to see this
stupid fucking garfield looking shithead ever again. now you can do yoga. great. get in
there. you're as mad at mario as i got with uncharted on crushing. what's that mean? dive
bomb. rotten pro. are there a use for the dive bomb? what's it there for? let's go eat some
rotten mushrooms. getting mad at uncharted. i've never played uncharted. is that possible?
no mistakes. no mistakes. here we go. i'm gonna do it first try. i'm gonna get everything
perfect. every coin go. since when do mushrooms go to the left side? it's never happened.
there's too many. why are they going to the left?
i was on it. i missed the coins. who cares. do joe rogan rant about oh oh okay mushrooms.
88 88 percent. we are so damn close. i can feel it. koopa clown car coin collecting.
reach the goal after grabbing all 50 coins. this will get us to 90 percent. all right
i'm gonna calm down now and i'm gonna just relax and we're just gonna play. all right.
it's not working. where did this come from? where did that come from? why is a mushroom in one?
no no. get back in. okay seriously. i have 25 seconds. oh get those. no don't. it doesn't
matter. can i break this? i have 17 seconds. i gotta get all the other ones. little stragglers.
37 30 39 40. okay seven seconds. you gotta blow this up right now man. come on. you're gonna take
this up right now. blow it up. blow it up. please. please. what do you mean jump? jump? now i know
what to do. oh because i put i that i can break them. i didn't. right. whatever. oh upset.
irritated. not happy. mad. no calm down. oh this is like a twitch chat. twitch integration.
you guys just gave me a mushroom. i see how it works. 44. what if that's something. 29.
wizard last one. that's it. good. you can now leave. oh my god. no. oh no. no. i can't. grab it.
i was trying to jump on his head so i could go in there. yeah. damn he really is bad at this.
no i just i jumped over it and i was trying to. 90 percent. the darkness lifts. use a dim
light to make. get over it. wall jumps are great. get over it. if you mess up you'll fall into a
lake of boiling poison. this haha i suck at a kids game joke isn't funny. mario's no joke.
mario does not mess around. these games are made with skill in mind. um okay. i have just
barely saved my life. i'm gonna wait until the last second. into the claw. oh my god. okay.
not in the poison. easy. where the hell is this? they did say wall jumping. so that's what you
have to do. i am not going to go on the other side of that. 30 coins. someone else will get
them. when you load up your copy you can just you can go on the other side and get that.
what is going on? does it go back up? shit. all right. that was tricky but not that bad.
not that bad. i'm still gonna have money. what's the point of money after you build
everything? because i think that's it. unless there's some other random stuff that is
possible. i don't know what to do with the money. 91. oh everyone's stressed. that means
that something's wrong. oh man. oh this is bad. big red. we got a problem. i shouldn't say this
out loud. so here. oh total eclipse. i can't believe it. every last member of the crew
was kidnapped during lunch. please you've got to go and rescue them all before the chief notices
and docks our pay. get all five toads. i need every toad. i'm gonna go down left. no i'm not.
down right. who's over here? one. is there a secret toad? you know what i mean? i gotta
get these toads. but is there a toad that is a secret toad? well now what do you do?
trapped there. he was supposed to be a hero. he died fucking instantly. he didn't even know
he died. it was horrible. it just seared his head off. up here. all right. this time don't
run. don't rush. holy crap. holy crap. where did that come from? oh my god. what the
hell is happening in my brain? it's like the my brain is moving faster than things on the
screen. it'd be nice if i got one of these. am i tall? i'm gonna like crush my head.
okay now just walk across them slowly. thank you. toad number two. that leaves us with bottom
left and top left. and then i got them all. what is this gonna do? rush twice.
thank you for that. appreciate it. who died? be faster next time. this doesn't hit us, right?
one more. i need a i need i need mushroom. one two three four five one two three four. sometimes
i try to do a gotcha moment there where i jump up and it instantly turns back on.
got them all. let's get the hell out of here. wait what? i get the hell out of here. who did i
miss? who's still who? who did i not get? didn't i already go down here? i remember like jumping
over this. did i not go this way? oh all the way to the right here. oh here you go.
i just don't want anybody to get hurt. someone's gonna get just clubbed by one of those 30.
that's a lot of coins. all right. slow. this is like a seven minute level. i don't want to
blow it. there's a boss at the end of this. that was way easier than i thought. i just
dropped them all in there. put on a face cam? all right fine. there. all right. don't worry.
good to see you. let me move this down. good. old joke. oh it's because of this. hold on.
i don't care. i don't want to do it. they're all back. you rescued the toads. you did it.
congratulations. now paint it. my crew finally came back. was there a lazy toad convention in
the bathroom or something? confirmed bathrooms. the person that said that earlier. mario's a
plumber. everything's done. we have new building options now. stained glass 2000. all right. so
it is the stained glass. that's the finishing touch. a bathroom without a toilet? would it
be a bathroom? i mean i guess if it had bathtubs in it. this is expensive bullshit that requires
completing everything. well i'm pretty close. really. just the darkness is killing me. i just
landed them. holy shit. something just dropped. oh man. all right. all right. slow down.
i thought we were going to keep going right. this is why i skipped this one.
he sees 10 coins and immediately beefs it. what was it immediately? i mean to be fair
it is a pretty prize because you need the currency. coming back. i didn't try to get it.
is that gonna come down? holy shit it is. i could have jumped and got it. how the hell. i hear
something. what do i hear? i hear something. oh my god. it's saws. 50. oh i want it so bad.
nope. luigi can have that 50. yeah. i missed a 50. it hurts to miss a 50. it does.
unfortunately. angry angry sun. cloudy with a chance of gamma ray burst. i recommend using
the cloud cover to avoid getting a nasty sun burn. can you do face cam? sure i'll do it for
a second. i'm not fixing the audio because like it's gonna take too long. wait for the wait
wait wait. all right. hold on. that's better. hi. if i had just paid attention to the game.
oh a hamster. i don't do cam man. i don't do cam. i don't do cam dude. sorry. all right. i'm
it's fucking my brain. this is this level's. just watch the sun. give it to me please. all
right. relax. bring it back. i want. why am i reading chat and walking off of a fucking cliff
at the same time? what would the purpose of that be? get out of here you fucking banjo
kazooie looking dick. that was uncalled for. yeah but where has he been? all right. where has
he been for 20 years? he walked out and didn't come back. holy shit. i can still do it. greed
is killing me here. greed is killing me. it killed me. all right face cam on for this one.
watch out for the sun. watch out for the sun. i'm thinking about getting the coins.
oh shit. where's this going? the sun's just being annoying now. get up there. fuck did i go?
oh. i'm trying to jump to get the coins. words first. marticle. marticle. vertical mario mvp.
all right. get out of here. how much is left? there are a shitload of levels left. what happens
when we build the castle? reach the goal in the koopa troopa car. do a multiplayer before
it's too late. well it's not going to be too late because we're going to do it again.
it's actually a car. how do i drive it? holy. this is awesome. imagine the levels
that we'll get out of this. somebody will recreate the whole track. i love this level.
this is one of those levels in the original that just played itself and it was like
impossible to lose. you just had to drive and left the show. remember the songs? these are the
best. hey. you can go up or down. right on top. yeah that's a full letter grade up. you're
right. if this was like a b minus so far. like a b. it's now an a. although i don't know if i
would classify this as a b minus. it's just fun. buzzy the movie the book of the ride.
reach the goal to grabbing 80 coins. click coins while trying not to fall to your doom.
once you grab buzzy beetle's shell you can throw it up. all right. street fighter the movie
the game. all right. reach the goal to grab and at least 80 coins. let's go. uh what? right.
that's what it wants me to do. red the needle. nice. come on. do it again. idiot. can i?
i was so... i was staring at that 50. all i saw were dollar signs and nothing else.
i really am like a money bug. it's like a light source. i just saw money and i was like
money. give it to me. money. i don't understand what the hell they want me to do.
thread it. oh shit. all right. i'm all right. no. give me. i want to catch it. here we go.
perfect. get away from me. did i do it? 105. yep. how did he get that 30 down there?
what is up with that? what is going on here? what did it do? what did it do? what did that
do? there's a door. should i go in the door? oh no. that's the normal door. it stopped the
conveyor belt. i have enough money. we got work to do. now here's the thing. the re... how this
is possible to continue to... it's probably gonna be 10 plus hammers there. only five.
never mind. construction has started on the stained glass. okay. there's even more jobs to
do here. let me see. let's go all the way to the end for a second. 19. no. we already did these
here. invincible wind sprinter is currently the last one we have here. 100 coins under the sea.
grab all 100 coins. do it? no. i'll do the last couple. if they're still available, and
this kind of ends, you only have to do 60 or 70 levels. and i'll try some of the crazy
ones. and then i'll do a multiplayer night where i'll play a bunch of levels and then
do some multiplayer. i'll probably do that. let's see what's today. tomorrow's movie night.
so after tomorrow, i got... i want to do dark souls randomizer and then...
we'll do... all right. i got a plan. we're gonna do that. that got a lot lined up.
do i have to do this? i mean, i don't... you talk about the single player thing? no, not necessarily,
but i think it's kind of fun. plus, like i said before, i don't just want to jump into mario maker.
i want to, like, just get some good hours in just doing the single player and then
go hard on the multiplayer stuff. i'm going to do more cook serve delicious.
whenever, really. don't have a plan. and this is a relaxing level after the weird ones.
which, i'm probably going to do the enemies and items randomizer. it was heavily requested
long ago. seems like fun. so i'll probably do that. i don't think... i don't know if i'm
gonna do it with any other person, though. i feel like doing that with two people is hard
because if somebody dies, don't you have to, like, restart everything and, like, re-sum them
and stuff? i was gonna just kind of do a night where i do a bunch of weird things,
i was gonna just kind of do a night where i do a bunch of random weird ones.
but yeah, that's next week. well, i'll probably do tuesday, wednesday...
i gotta do... i gotta work on that carnival shit, though. i'm probably gonna have, like,
a meeting. i'll figure it out. the world's greatest cannon ride. that one is doing it
for me. i want to try it. termicorp board meeting. no. you see, i wouldn't be able
to do any of the things i'm doing right now if i had... remember mario maker 1? i couldn't
even make small jumps. i'll be ready for the the new levels in the multiplayer the next time i do
this. come on, get out of the way. gee, psycho! uh-oh, didn't have a good view. don't blow it
right before the... get up top. no, don't get up top. what do i do? oh, here. how do i get
that? like this? i got greedy and it was a mistake so far. don't die here. why do the bombs look so
weird? do they? to anyone who bought germa stock during the dread hall stream three months
ago, sell for profit. are you gonna sell my stock before the carnival? i think that would be
a mistake. what's the carnival? uh, oh yeah, that's right. i probably should talk about it
more often. at some point in the end of august or into somewhere into september,
i'm currently working with a robotics team and i'm making an entire twitch controls
carnival games stream. dunk tanks, claw games, and it's happening at some point in around
september. how long is that stream gonna be? it's gonna be at least four to six hours long.
has to be. and i'll be on the dunk tank yet. this is a project that is a very very long
time in the making. i really wanted this to happen like back in like april or march, but
kind of just didn't. but now it is. it's finally gonna happen. how many votes will it take to dunk
you? well, that's the thing. i don't really want to talk about it too much because i'd rather some
of it, at least most of it, be a surprise and more uh more than just like, hey here's everything
that's gonna happen. because there's a lot of shit that's gonna happen on that stream
that at least is planned to happen. so i'd rather not just be like, and here's this is
gonna happen and this is gonna happen and then this is gonna happen and then this is gonna
happen at the end. but you will have- i will tell you very specific dates, very specific times,
weeks in advance, if not potentially a month in advance of when the stream is gonna happen.
how did i do that without- i was barely paying attention to that one. million dollar joke.
not that much, but um for those of you- i won't give- no no no that's not- no i don't
want to do that. no, it's too early. too early to talk about that. you'll see. you'll see.
uh oh. 10? oh i could have got it right there. is there gonna be a clown? just know this.
i'm going as hard as i possibly can on this stream. i don't need- i don't want to say
anything else. that's all i really need to say. i can't have that just empty here,
you know what i mean? i have to do it. climbing twister cave. do you ever feel
nervous about doing big streams like that before them? no, not really. because it's
just like that shit that i've- oh come on i missed those. because by the time that you see
something on stream, i've probably gone over it a dozen times. i probably like talked about it
or planned it for weeks in advance. so i want to do it and i want to get going and i want
to do it now. you know what i mean? usually like at least a week or two in advance a
lot of those like random streams like that that would happen. oh come on i can get that.
do the people helping you actually know what you're doing? oh yeah and they're very much
included and on board. they're very excited about it too because it's just hopefully it's
just going to be a really fun project to do. really? are you going to come out like that?
well do it again. that's not a good idea. do it from here. it's 30 coins i have to try.
jesus i don't think i can make this jump from here. god damn it i knew that was going to
happen. thank the people helping with this for us. yeah you- they're- you will know-
you'll know exactly who they are because this is gonna- they'll be very- it'll be very evident
on who is- i did it again because the people that are working on this it's- they have like
a legit mobile unit. you know it's not- it's not like the last big big big project i did
which was essentially- it was germa rumble live was the last huge project that i really
really did. that was me and like my friends and a couple of people. this is a bunch of people that
do this kind of shit for a living so- and it has to be that way because there's a lot going on
in this stream that there has to be a lot of people essentially working on it. i gotta be
careful i have no health. yes i called it health but that's kind of what it is.
am i gonna put an act on or is it gonna be- it's i mean it's kind of just gonna be me.
holy fuck i thought that was an enemy one two three go i'll do that get it
really i've been moving real quick haven't i i haven't been moving fast how much more is there
oh yeah yay no he's killing everybody holy shit at least i have the time back
don't b come on press b try to bring a bomb up there i feel like that'll help
no give me a new one
no that's not gonna work i needed that extra hit for this he's kind of just has to kill
everything otherwise i'll fly into him i'll just leave one i could probably go now okay one two
three whatever the courtroom stream that i mentioned on the podcast we just couldn't get
it done it just wasn't gonna happen we had we were in contact with a couple of different
courts and a couple of different groups that wanted to kind of do it but they flaked out both
of them essentially at the very last second they were like eh stop returning emails and it was
good we were gonna have uh santa's uh oh i'm taking taking down the fourth wall here
um media meteor showdown meowser showdown what the hell is this the chief has been abducted
by bowser here's the last one we need to go it's the only difficulty level three uh we're
gonna have santa's prosecutor was going to just sing all of his lines and we had a guy that was
perfect for it there's gonna be christmas be music in the background while he sang all of
his lines there's gonna be character witnesses it's gonna be ridiculous why well because he's
like santa's magic fucking attorney so he's of course he's gonna be a christmas spirit kind
of thing we had a lot of plans for that too it was so disappointing that's a really cool looking
enemy click click click click click click click click out i've never played mario 3d world
before how do you beat bowser did jump on his head i've never beat bowser as just me
you don't cart oh shit oh no i crashed it's all right oh the lava is rising
i don't know how i didn't make that jump twice finally imagine not having the arrows
thank god luigi's holding my hand how the hell would i ever get this done
what just happened i had to go faster than that that guy's just sleeping
come on what's wrong with this car speed it up mario all right what in the name
of god is happening wrong here i'm just holding down dash and jumping am i missing the bounce pad
well i didn't know that get the coin i can do it go fucked up it's fucked up it's
fucked up i got like stuck and it fucked up and like i didn't move anywhere i have to do the
whole thing again all right get me through this get me through this first part of the level
gimmick why i tried to hit the one time that i pressed the down button and it doesn't work
i'm so ready i'm so ready i think i've been pressing on these buttons too hard for so long
that i drained the battery faster like i think i've been pressing too many buttons that have
drained the battery faster it feels a little less fluid i have to shake up my controllers to
recharge them just wait till they start doing that shit i can't wait you know those like
flashlights that you shake and they get charged that's gonna happen pretty soon with wireless
controllers you're probably gonna get out of the way try just to step on his hands
i'm just fucking panicking right now i'll just go all right here we go i'm not gonna get the
coin this time i'm just gonna beat the level i'm not gonna be an idiot up okey dokey turn
let's go there's a lot of unnecessary animals that i just ran over just get out of the car
please don't tell me the lava is gonna be right here i'm gonna go right into it
oh shit give it to me how do i climb this
i what am i doing give me the pow no give me the pow stop all right throw it at him
why is he a cat too why are we both cats coins beautiful there's more i think i beat the
story i think i did it i completed the first time ever in over 10 years i just beat a mario
game in quotes i did it i rescued the chief fresh air finally i owe you one mario
stained glass is finished we're almost done there's one more thing to do
100 that's it now that was just a model now zoom out we got to do the whole castle see
you in 500 hours my name could go down in history for this but now is not the time for that let's
go to get princess peach cutscene mario you haven't changed clothes in like seven or eight
days you aimed those at bowser when he came to try to kill you all we even he even says
thank you for playing thank you for playing because they're fireworks you don't think if
you get a firework one of the big ones shot directly in your face it's something bad wouldn't
happen is he gonna press the button again and redo them are we in an infinite loop hey look
at that that was fun i think we're chasing him that was really fun seven hours of six to seven
hours and there's still like 20 or 30 levels that are there i'm gonna check and see after
credits what it looks like now i'm ready for super expert mode yeah that'll have to be for
another night though i'm gonna go check out the other levels that were the
final ones though isn't super expert gone actually i think it's just an endless mode right
it's no longer is it normal hard super hard i like this rendition they removed 100 lives
with the difficulties the same that makes sense i kind of liked the 100 lives thing though
it gave you that pressure that you only had 100 tries to get somewhere it's kind of
interesting although if you did run into one of those levels during the 100 mario challenge
if you run into one of the troll levels that guaranteed you were going to lose like 40 times
i mean that did happen didn't it you could skip yeah you could skip that's right that's
true the co-op sounds fun when it actually starts to work right isn't there isn't it not
that great right now didn't they not even add a bunch of the co-op multiplayer features
into the game yet no online with friends until later how much later you gotta buy it i thought
you just had to have the nintendo online pass thing well that was cute i want to go back and
see oh i got the hard hat it can actually be in builder mario super hammer wait you've earned a
new part you can use it in the super mario 3d world game style in course maker so you have
to play through the whole thing to get the super hammer congratulations on completing peach's
castle you can make all kinds of courses like the ones you played in story mode head over the
course maker and bring your ideas to life where's peach is she here is peach like on the level
what's your problem thanks mario oh new job from princess peach i think that's what he just
said let's go builder mario clear the way with the super hammer you need to only create a
builder box with up and why could you give that a try and see if you can reach the
goal this is from peach and i got a gear so this is the super secret princess peach end
of the video game after the credits post credit scene oh shit what the hell all right hold on
what this is crazy so you can build blocks and i only have three i guess i can have more than
three there's a lot of cool use cases for this oh you can only have okay you can only
have a certain amount dig mario dig reflexes like a goddamn animal can i yeah wait there's
something over here now i miss the mario has the hammer he didn't really have a hammer anymore
does he they put mario in all kinds of like fursuits but they don't really you don't utilize
his hammer anymore what is this the wall well he has it now that oh this hurts you right
right oh look out can't whoa all right well they can't be killed can they be boxed
no i just slingshot it down that hole i went so fast down that hole get over here
box it up again please thank you okay oh because i hit the wall that's why
all right don't screw this up again please so what am i doing wrong here you have to block
them off yeah that worked cool mechanic just jump over them do try this level i'm not going
to do any online levels tonight doll the princess pete's dress cool i'm gonna be wrapping
it up here seven hours probably take about 40 30 40 minutes to the bits i'm getting a little
tired but i am going to do a multiplayer and we're gonna do it again we're gonna do it
that was fun just to do all that i've had that was i loved that and now i got the necessary skill
set to be able to play online and do the levels and do the and that also gives time for people
to make some stuff there is stuff that already exists i'm sure that's great good luck because
multiplayer is wonky and not that great but that's what i mean maybe over the next
three or four days right maybe they'll fix out kink out some of the bugs but i'm ready for
the online stuff the other story levels yeah i mean maybe i'll work here's okay here uh listen
let me just slow down and then use my words clearly because i'm talking over myself speaking
somehow uh i will warm up with some of the harder ones here and then that i'm going to
do that for less than like probably 20 30 minutes and then we'll spend a good like
regular stream time between like six to eight hours doing all the online stuff i'm ready
but it can't happen tomorrow because tomorrow is the green screen movie encore night again if
you do not have that this is the last chance you're going to get probably the last time
i'm going to talk about it until obviously the stream is tomorrow did i explore everything i
think i saw all this secret stuff no i didn't thank you for saving the chief we couldn't have
done it without you that said mario you could probably get into that pipe you forgot
rid of that piranha creeper and look to a tomorrow i might just do this tomorrow because
it depends how long the movie night is you know you know what you know because the movie
the encore movie night is only going to be a couple hours that's not going to be that long
so why not either do that first and then just do mario maker again that makes sense i think
because it's not like i don't want to turn the stream on and turn it off in like an
hour and 25 minutes all right that's the plan if for some crazy reason the movie the green
screen night takes like four or five hours which i don't think there's no way it will
we'll just uh do the multiplayer stuff tomorrow we'll do the online courses tomorrow and stuff
the last movie night stream was seven hours or so this one shouldn't be that yeah especially
there's going to be like 60 less videos than the first one but that's where i'm going to
wrap it up but time tomorrow we're going to start at three to four something between three
and four p.m get three coins to be funny i'll do it some other day yeah the last movie night
had hundreds of videos this is going to be probably less than a hundred so maybe uh i'll
probably i don't know we'll we'll gauge the room but that's happening tomorrow i want to
link the form one more time if somebody didn't get it because obviously this is the last
chance you're going to get me shouting this out grab the link i might as well turn this on too
uh if you leave i'll see you tomorrow same time starting somewhere around three to four p.m
pacific potentially earlier it depends on when i uh get up and get going but plan for the
normal time anywho if you've taken off hopefully we see you tomorrow if not maybe
we'll see you again soon let me just go let me grab the grab this here is the submission form
only submit once not more than once have it be less than three minutes and again this is not
a contest so not all submissions don't if your submission doesn't get picked it's not like it
wasn't any good we're just trying to condense them down into ones that are not so similar
and some of that are maybe a little bit higher quality and don't see the same kind of thing over
and over again right it's not a contest and after this is all done and i'm going to probably see
if we can do just another big playlist and not stream it but have a second encore playlist
with most of the submissions or at least some of the ones that were um that we could show
afterwards you know but uh i'm gonna just go p i'll be right back we'll do the bits
and i will be right back see you sure
just walking back up i feel like a bad migraine right now where the hell will this come from
strange being old probably well we don't have very there's not a whole lot of bits tonight
so we should be able to get through this pretty quickly mario migraine now i probably
just need to eat something anyways uh thank you to lazy luke for the 250
germa i made this plus two minus two counter you can put on your stream as a browser source
in case you want to ruin your stream thank you lazy luke uh i'm going to copy that
and i'm going to i'm gonna hold on to this if anyone wants to see
germa.org but thank you lazy luke uh we also had d stroke thanks for the 10 bucks how is
burger boy doing is he still living in the brash boston life yeah burger boy has a family now
he's got children he's married and he's he's doing just fine but thank you for the 10 bucks
appreciate it also thank you to uh swiggity swanky for the five dollars remember this show
this to chat you look so young and still so cute hold on let me see where let's see browser
source let's watch this i gotta unplug this this is the other mario maker stream
is this where i said i was gonna quit the game forever i can't hear it why i cannot hear this
can you guys hear this i can hear that why can i not hear this is it because it's muted
it's muted why would you do that look at that big ass suit on my face stream germa
stream sucks the germa height experience right
well you have a few days no you don't you have until tomorrow apparently and maybe we'll do it
again but wouldn't mean i looked so young that was two years ago that was not that long ago
that was like that was 24 months ago i had better lighting on my face i'm not aging
fast i was 32 there i've already aged as much as i'm gonna age until i hit like 50
why is my brain doing this right now where were we down here right here uh thank you to
omega rose for the ten dollars cheers from disco deer where's it was disco deer
disco deer well thank you for the 10 bucks we also had uh hamster the pie for 250 hey
germa could i ask you about the old boston spending the summer there and given that
you're a native pro gamer of the area do you have any recommendations on cool or obscure
sites to see what things to do while i'm here best wishes i mean the easy answer is
go to a red sox game the red sox it's gonna be probably hard to get tickets at same day
where whenever you're going for the red sox play it then weighs awesome uh i would also
say if you're in that kind of area uh jillian's is awesome it's they got a giant arcade they've
got pool they got bowling it's pretty much everything you want it's like dave and busters
if dave and busters wasn't kind of like the chuck e cheese of chuck e cheese for adults
you know what i'm saying so i would say go to jillian dave and busters is the is the adult
chuck e cheese jillian's is what dave and busters should be it's like a dave and busters 3.0
that's not saying that dave and busters is bad chuck e cheese is cool museum of science
is yeah i said that uh this past week too museum of science is awesome
jillian's is awesome and maybe go see a red sox game fenway is like a fucking thousand
years old at this point it's kind of worth seeing place again how do i lose my place
every time uh here we go spoons for self-defense thanks for the 15 dollars
germa just want to say that you're my favorite streamer thank you so much for what you do
this next part is in parentheses is personal so please don't read it out loud
okay uh i'm gonna read it out loud so i'm sorry but i'm gonna go get some wishes here
ha ha ha germa you're a loser game sucks streamer sucks you're gonna start crying and
chad is gonna think i said something nice to you don't read this out loud well thank you
but hamster the pie thanks with 250 and i hope you enjoy boston it's a great city and
and also spoons for self-defense thanks with 15 dollars uh griff thanks for five bucks yo germa
can't tell you how excited i was to finally catch you live i never can due to my schedule
thank you for all the effort you put into your content the only person that has made
me cry laugh just from watching something cheers men have a good night griff have a great night
as well thank you so much for the five dollars thanks with those insanely kind words
uh and then let me get the credits on here bring credits all the subs all the resubs
on this particular night tonight where are they oh here they go thank you hey the
gun game you played a while ago on the vr just got an officially sanctioned team fortress 2
with fully realized weapons rocket jumping etc we mean are you talking like a tf2 update
we're talking about that Pavlov oh the meat fortress right right yeah yeah yeah we saw that
uh that video yeah i know i saw it for uh holy hand grenade and horseshoes and hot dogs
whatever it is yeah i'll come i'll go back to vr eventually just got kind of too much going
on because already the next couple weeks of streams are really sort of planned out at the
moment so it's released now well that's awesome hopefully it's fun jeremy i just got back from
going out is the vod worth checking out uh do you like super mario because it was just
super it was super mario i beat the whole but not the whole thing i completed the storyline
of the mario maker 2 campaign i had to get myself back into the groove of playing mario
it's been a while and i enjoyed it and i think you should watch it
but um thank you too uh that was hold on all right i'm fine that was the right side of my
head just like for some reason it's just like this happens it's from sleep i can always tell
when i'm gonna have a migraine during a day because i will it sleep triggers it for me and
has to be because i'll wake up and then fall back asleep for four hours or so and that's
what gives me the headache later on it's weird but thank you friday and weapon for the 250 happy
friday germa hart i was pretty on the fence about mario maker but i think i'm gonna go for
it maybe just maybe i might make some bomb ass levels there is a lot to do in mario maker so
there are lots of people that make some crazy shit so i wish you luck thank you so much for
the 250 uh exil exili exilicon thanks for the five dollars some bits to help support the million
dollar joke did i say does it key will that keep was the key we're here tonight
how did i miss key will be in here what kind of a friend am i you were raging oh was i just
losing my mind but thank you for the five dollars uh support the million dollar joke
i appreciate it i'll be working on that after tomorrow business man now you know i'm wheeling
and dealing now but i'll see you guys tomorrow this is essentially the last call for you to
do a green screen submission over the next couple hours i cannot guarantee that even if
you have an immaculate unbelievable submission i cannot guarantee that if you don't get it in
over the next few days enough what it's tomorrow over the next few hours i cannot guarantee that
it'll be included so i will feed everybody on stream legends when i end the stream
i am gonna go take a tylenol and go put my head down because i don't know what's going on
it's kind of just eating me alive at the moment so good night take care much love to
you i'll see you guys soon have a great night