You guys even counted down. You counted down and I got it right at the exact second I went to 12.
It was like three, two, one, bang, live. I'm not even here yet. Give me my two minutes that I have
in solidarity while I just sit here and breathe deeply and get ready and talk into my mirror
that's right here on the left side of my screen. You're gonna do this. It's gonna be a good stream
today. You're gonna knock it out of the park, Jeremy. Give me a minute. All right, I'm back.
Good morning or good afternoon, wherever you are. Today we're gonna play Evolva which I it's who
knows. This could be a home run or this could be a foul ball. What do you mean foul ball? Because
if I don't like it we're gonna pivot to something else. It's not an immediate strikeout. Strikeout
would mean that the stream turns off. No. I have another one lined up and I don't want to say what
it is because that's the problem I have with these streams. Whenever I have a backup game
and I tell everybody what the backup game is, all of a sudden it's like do that instead. No,
no, no. Just don't even play this. Let's do that. Please do that. So I'm not going to tell you what
the backup game is. You'll know what the backup game is if we need a backup game, okay? No,
it's not a sir's wrath. I'm sorry to all the people that hate me now because I'm not going
to play that. I do have something to tell you though. Something important. It is the official
date and the official time of FTK, Favor the King, Minecraft. I've got a real date for you
and a time. It is going to be September 13th at 3 p.m. Pacific. It gives everybody that's involved
across all the many time zones to get it put together. I'll give you some very brief details.
Detail number one. You don't have to be a multi-sub to be there anymore. You just have to be an
active sub. That's it. Nothing else. It is not what you think it is. It's not the same game
that has been completely reimagined and completely redesigned. You just have to be a current
subscriber to the channel. The server is going to be shit like last time. No. The problem with last
time was there was only one or two servers that were handling all the traffic. This time,
there's a lot. I think there's like 10 servers that are handling all this.
Make it 20. Listen to 100 gecks. I already did. What do you want me to do? Do I have to watch 100
gecks at the beginning of every stream? Is that like a routine? Is that like my new starting soon
screen? It's going to be, oh, we're going to watch 100 gecks starting soon. Thanks at my starfish
for the five community subs. I'm a little winded. I ran up and down the stairs like four times
as I wanted to be exactly on time at exactly 12 o'clock. So I went like up, up, up, down, down,
down, down, up, up, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
where's my keys? Where's my phone? Where's my phone? Phone, phone, phone, get my phone.
Shit. No, I've got to get a water. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
water. Okay. Poor quick. Get up there. It's 1158 up, up, up, up, up, up. Wait. Hold on.
Where's the dog? Oh, top. Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, get like up the stairs. Oh, top.
Looking for a watch up. No, no, I see you. You're right there. So I, I, I like exercised
like five to 10 straight minutes before I turned this on. So I'm, I'm a little winded.
It's okay. He lives in a mansion.
No, it's just one small staircase. But when you go up and down at like 30 times in five minutes,
you get, you get a little disheveled in an eight story house. No, I would never want to
live in an eight story house. You know how much that would suck? I don't want to live in a big
ass house. No, fuck that. That would be horrible. It would scare the shit out of me. And every noise
I heard would be a person in the house. Somebody could live in your house. If you had like 12
bedrooms and your house was like 15,000 square feet, somebody could literally come live in your
house and you wouldn't fucking know they were there. They could just sleep in one of the bedrooms.
And when they heard you come and just hide in like the closet, Oh, okay. He's gone. Like you
have so much food in your fridge that you can't even tell if one guy's eating like fucking Cheerios
out of your pantry or not. Nobody would even know. No, forget. No, no, I'm not doing that.
I'm never having 12 fucking rooms. They could like jump from room to room and it would be like
playing hit man without killing anybody. You're just trying to sleep in their beds. No, not
happening. Get out. That's just a sitcom. All right. Anyways, anyways, anyways, anyway, we're
going to play Evolva. This is going to be either a POG champ or a frog damp. Who knows? Oh, come
on. That was not that bad. Like damp versus like POG. I'm taking that one. I deserve it.
I deserve that one. I ate my fucking vegetables last night. I deserve at least a plus two for
that one. Let's go. You just made a new saying. Yeah. Thank you. Yeah. Everyone's getting a bit
mad because this game's not in like 16 by nine. There's no widescreen for this game.
So it just doesn't exist. Unfortunately. So it's stuck in a four by three window. There's no
widescreen patch. I already looked. Ready? All right. Here we go. We're going to do a new game.
Hopefully it's not too loud. For this game, you get a team of Power Rangers or whatever they are.
You get to make your team and they all evolve with the course of the game. It's too ugly. Oh,
please. You've watched me play a PlayStation one game on this channel with like a cell phone
quality image. I think you can handle this. We have an agile, a speed, a heavy and an intelligent
purple alien. Yeah, come on, man. This is purple alien from the fast germa and purple alien saga.
Can I do purple alien? Okay. It's going to be purple A for purple alien speed type. Oh,
I can change the color. Wait, doesn't have to. It doesn't have to be purple. It can be anything
I want. All right. Well, should it just still be purple alien? P alien. Yes. Okay. Fine. Purple A
or P alien. Okay. Yeah, that's fine. All right. This is the agile. This is the speed one. This
can't be fast germa. They can't do that. Make this Sonic. This team sucks already. Purple alien
Sonic. This is not beanbag Sonic. This is like smushed with an anvil Sonic. Like smashed head
in car door Sonic. Car door Sonic. This is going to be CD Sonic. CD Sedonic. No, CD Sonic. Come on.
Do I really? This is the heavy. This was, I think this was doing all the damage. I want to be able
to, I think you have to really be able to differentiate between them. So we're not going
to have all the same color. Make him the Hulk. If I make him the Hulk, you mean like a makeshift
shitty fourth grade Hulk costume. Like the big kid in class. All right. Big kid Hulk. I'll have
abbreviations before. All right. This is big kid Hulk. And then this is the intelligent one.
Which is absolutely it's going to have to be me. Jeremy E. There we go. It's like I'm filling out
an application. Fast germa. Evil Jeremy. No, what color? What color should I be? Red. Well, green,
blue and purple already taken. I have to be teal. Aqua or chrome. Red. I have to be red. Yellow.
Is yellow. Can I even do yellow? Yellow doesn't exist. I should be chrome. Okay. Like a chrome.
I'll be like metallic or something. No, I'm just going to be red because I will lose track of who
the fuck is who. That looks good. All right. Name of the team is Gino team. That's not going to work.
What should it be called? We've got P, Alien, CD, Sonic, BK, Hulk and E. Jeremy. Just the family.
My family. Imagine that's your superhero team name. My family. It's going to have to be my family.
My family. My family rocks. The Incredibles. No, my family. Here we go. And I was this. The probe has
detected planetary debris indicating biomatter entering. Okay, I'm not going to try that hard.
You know, what do I have to do that for? The probe has detected planetary debris containing
biomatter entering the X-92 system. Untact with the debris was lost when it entered the atmosphere
of planet X-92-3. Twelve hours later, the probe recorded a significant increase in seismic activity
analysis. Did I tell you guys this story, how I used to do that to my mother? She'd be reading
me a story and she'd be reading like that and every time she would nod off, I would kind of
nudge her a little and she'd go back to where she was. Happened all the time. She'd be reading
me a story in bed and I would have to, she'd start to nod off and I would go like just nudge
a little and she'd go as if I was powering her back on. I was like turning my mother back on with
zero battery with an iPhone. She would turn on, I would see the Apple screen and then immediately
would shut off and I would fucking be like annoyed. All right, what are we doing? Briefing. Deploy
your team of geno hunters. Absorb sufficient indigenous wildlife to adapt to the environment.
Locate and assimilate any non-indigenous biomatter to for aid further analysis.
Use the O arrow on your compass or objective to find your way to the objective. Attack dead
creatures to absorb their meat. Mutate your geno hunters using the genes and the meat
to give them a new ability. Use the new ability to gain access to the previously inaccessible area.
This is a metroidvania? And a genetic sample from any non-indigenous life form by mutating
your geno hunters. Get all remaining geno hunters to pick up point. I promise. What did I promise?
I can't alt tab. Somebody explains to me. Tiny cut scene. That's the littlest cut scene. I can't
alt tab. What does it tell me what it says? I'll crash the game. Tell us the skeleton radiation
story. Oh, right, right, right. Hold on. I will after this small screen. So this is us. This is
my family. Are we going to earth? Is that earth? It looks like earth. But we send down an avocado pit
that turns into my family. Pretty accurate, I guess. The whole stream like this. The reason why this
cut scene looks like this is because this is back in like 2002. It's dodge. Holy shit. Can I get one
of those on my team? Those things are awesome. It's the most insane reaction ever. It's because all
games in 2002 had like a 240p rendered full motion cut scenes. Use the O on your compass to find the
objective. Do I have to control everybody? This different, this two or three different cameras
down there. All right. I feel like this is a multi-block stream. This really is what it's like to
play WoW with multi-blocking. Can I select other people? Oh, there's a punch. I just punched somebody.
Hold on. First of all, this is so loud. It's just, I found my calling in life. It's this.
It's just to listen to this over and over again. All right. I was supposed to turn it down, not up.
Okay. Mouth sensitivity. That's fine. Okay. I'll tell you the, the, the, okay. So I had a nuclear
bone scan, which if you don't know what a nuclear bone scan is, they put a small amount of radiation
into your body and you go into this camera that looks like a jokey x-ray vision video game machine
where if you put your hand under it, after getting this tracer put into you, you can see your hand
like a cartoon underneath it. And I looked at the images afterwards and it was the most ridiculous
thing I've ever seen in my life. My entire skeleton as naked as I could possibly be was just every
angle of my body, every angle of my skeleton. And I want to show it on stream. I don't have these
images yet, but is that like term, is that TOS? Cause that would be me, the ultimate in me showing
you my naked body on stream. Is that TOS? That's what's under my clothes and what's under my skin.
So it's only when the skin is on top that it's TOS, right? Is that how that works? And muscles.
Yeah. Whatever. What about your penis bone? It's done. You got it out of me and it hadn't even been
20 minutes. Okay. Let's go show it. I'll show it when I get it, but it was ridiculous.
It was one of the most weird kind of, is there a gun? Who has a gun? Somebody's shooting a rifle.
All right. We're going to go. How do I select other aliens? Or do they just walk behind me?
Okay. I have a punch. We eat these eggs. All right. Eat these, eat these, eat these eggs.
Why do I feel like this is three of you guys just waiting for me to do? Hey,
do not punch him. What do I do with those? Wait, that doesn't listen. It was the objective this
way. I feel like I should be able to eat these things. Can I? Oh, the objective is like right
here. Oh shit. It's down here. Okay. Okay. I can't control these guys. I cannot control the other
three chat members. They have their own camera. Okay. Just don't stand over there. You see,
if this was really chat, one of you would have died by that. One of you would have died. I'm
surprised it wasn't me. All right. We have to find the first mutator. There's no way we're going to
be able to get through that. We're not going to be able to do this. Can I switch? Does somebody
else have like a power? Don't get that close. Use the fast one. Oh shit. Faster. No, no, no.
Don't follow me up here. Oh, dead creature. Who should get the first power up? Big kid Hulk for
sure. All right. Good. What did that do? We level up. Mutate. What happened? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa. What happened? He gets a jump. What? He just changed. He can change to be green.
Greener. Did we make him greener? Okay. He's. Wait, he has a jump. Oh, he has a jump now. He
didn't have one before. Oh shit. What are we doing? Oh my God. I don't know what I'm doing to him.
Okay. Stay there. Don't move. You can stay there like that. Use new ability to gain access to the
inaccessible area. Oh, his jump is huge. I get it. Okay. What about everybody else? Can I mutate you?
Okay. That's what you're. I think it's a bigger jump for everybody. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
What do you mean? What am I wasting points? Am I giving everybody? I'm just making everybody.
I'm just changing everybody's color. Okay, so we're good. Now we should be able to go.
Should I jump something? Oh, I can jump this now. Don't come down here. Don't come down here. Don't
come down here. Don't come down here. Don't come down here. Don't come down here. Nobody come down
here. Just leave me. Leave both of us. What the fuck? Wait, they're doing this on their own.
Gain a genetic sample from any non-indigenous life form by mutating your geno hunters.
If you find. What did that say? Oh, we can just go this way. We're fine. Where's the other guy?
Oh, there he is. Okay, we're good. I hope we can start growing like weird toes and stuff.
The other guy actually made the jump. Wait, what the hell? We didn't already do this.
We all have to get together for this. Oh, oh, hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up.
Out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out. Wait, I can't make this fucking.
Nobody can make this jump. No, we can't make the jump. I need to mutate more to get more jump.
Okay, good. Is that working? This is the only spot where I can make this jump, isn't it?
Jesus, come on. What the fuck? I don't get it. I don't get it either. I think that's doing it,
right? Why are you playing it? Because it seems like it's fun. Hold on. I get it.
No, stay over there. This is a chat member. This is one of you guys just being like, dude,
it's wicked easy. Just do it. Get over here. Do you think it's so easy? I'm taking control
of your body. Stay up there. Stay. Oh, my fucking God. Damn it, dude. Stay. Where's the fast one?
Give me fast germa. Where is he? Two. Oh, are we actually all the way down here? No, I don't
do this shit again. Wait, can I? Is there a way I can go up to not have to go through the explosions
anymore? Your family sucks. Stop. I just got to get the hang of it. Look, you can grow like big
horns and have like big asses and stuff. You guys are going to be all over this. Wait, what was that?
Shit, I have to go through this whole thing again. I have to. I'm going to get the hang of this.
Somebody's going to die and it's going to be wicked embarrassing. OK, I have the jump, but
I can't make it. Why can the computer make it? This point right here. That point right there.
Move out of the way. Get out of the way. Move. Get back here. Got it. OK. Do it. What's wrong
with you two? Come on, number four. Let's go. All right. Fucking leave him. Who cares?
Has he not been mutated to make the jump? Oh, shit. He wasn't mutated to make the jump. OK,
I get it. All right. Come on. This is your family. I don't all come down here. Was I supposed to be
down here? This too. Come on. What happened? I fell in a fucking hole. Whatever. I can do it.
I'm just going to go and fuck it. Who cares? I'm going to get there. I didn't. I didn't know. I
didn't know. I turned. There was a hole right there. I didn't see the fucking stupid hole.
All right. Where is this indicator pointing? Just start killing. Come here. What are these things?
Get up. Get up. Number three. What are you doing? What happened to number three? Wait, why is number
three just standing still and being exploded? What is he doing? He's on his own. He's so slow.
All right. Any more mutations? Oh, this is a new one. What is this? Nothing. What is this?
Nothing. I guess we're going to do this one. What does that do?
It's making the jump better. Usually it has an animation. Oh, wait. It is making the jump
better. You're right. Holy shit. Hold on. Wait. That's the problem I'm having. All right.
You have to accept it. It is making the jump better, isn't it? Cool. All right. I'm going
to forget to evolve one of these people and they're going to be worthless. How about you? All right.
We all have the better jump now. I like fast Jerma. Plug in their audio jacks. I don't really
know what that's supposed to mean. It really wants me to be over here. Why? Oh, give me the big kid.
We all do this at the same time? Help me do this. I need more power. Are you kidding me?
We need to like kill more stuff. All right. There was those other two monsters. All right.
Give me fast Jerma. What does it blink on one? You should role play an E3 trailer with three
other aliens. This is not going to happen. I'm sorry. Come on. We need to eat another monster.
I need to kill something. I hear something. Hold on. What about down here? What does the shift do?
Okay. What does that do? Figured it out. I know what to do. I know what to do. Follow me. Follow
me. That's a super punch. Are you kidding me? Shit. Wait. What about the big guy? God damn it.
All right. We have to eat more stuff. What about jumping? Can we jump on something? Next game. No,
not yet. Not yet. This is very important. We have to get to the first boss. Yeah. There are bosses
on every level. We just have to find something else to eat. Found it. Get it. There's so much
food down here. Holy shit. There's food everywhere. Come on. Get over here. Please. We just need to eat.
Eat. Give me the fast one. What's the point of using anybody else?
Everybody can level up. This is different. This is what? Run speed? I lose jump, but I gain run
speed. This is more jump. Run speed. For sure. Absolutely. Let's go. All right. What about you?
Run speed or higher jump? Run speed. Give everybody run speed. Don't do anything else.
Eat more. Yeah. I got to level everybody up though. Ready? Let's move. So much better.
All right. Kill everything and we're going to eat all these. Holy shit. Okay. Kill. Fight.
Why do I have to do everything? Just fight. What did I just do? I said G. What did G do?
Okay. We need to be able to punch through the wall. More speed? More speed. More speed. This is a
shitty survival game. We have to give all these games at least 40 minutes. Don't you understand?
How long it's been? 36. We've got 10 minutes. Give me the fast one. Go.
Actually, we have way more than 10 minutes. I'm sorry to say everybody. What's that? Are we
throwing rocks? We can't get in this shit. How are we not strong enough? All right. Whatever.
I need more speed. No, I need more power. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help.
Help. Help. Where is everybody? Where is everybody? Where is everybody?
Is three okay? Oh, there he is. Okay. He's just slow. This is an MMO grinding.
No. Is it? Yes. This is multi-boxing. Wow. It's fine. We can run with that. It's okay.
That's a lot of juice. What do I do with the juice? Mutate. Oh, this gave tux. This gave tux.
Fucking claws. Even I can't pretend that it was cool. I'm sorry. I tried.
I want to get... What do I do? This is going to be... Yeah. Claws. Give him the claws. What else?
More claw? More claw. What else? More claw. More claw. Bigger claws. What else?
Even more claws. What else? Bigger claws. As big as your arms. What else? Do it again.
What else? Do it again. Are we doing this? Get all remaining geno hunters to pick
up point. All right. What do you have now? I don't want you to close. I want you to speed.
Now he's too powerful. That's fine. I can definitely break those rocks now. What's this?
Yeah. I'm the one dickhead in your friend group that has thunder fury
and the rest of you just get to walk around with them. It becomes exhausting to play with this
person because they kill everything in one hit and you just, you use it as a time for you to
hang out with them. You're not playing well. You're just watching somebody else play while you walk
around. Here we go. And there's random encounters. Sign me up. Do I give everybody
claws? It's a really good character. All right. I need to actually build a good team here. We need
tank, DPS, healer, and friend of healer. Okay. Good. You stay that way. I don't want you to change.
This is the fast guy, right? We don't want claws on fast guy. We want fast guy to be fast guy.
That's pretty fast. We don't need claws on you because look, you can be the one that runs around
fast. What about you? Wait, I'm doing this all wrong. The heavy, the heavy should have heavy weapons.
All right. We'll give you heavy weapons too. We'll have two DPS. This guy is the guy that's
supposed to be doing all the damage. All right. That's good. That's good. Good. Leave him alone.
It's two different claws. Faster or more damage. Yeah. Good. And now what about you? This is
intelligence guy, right? He's growing leaves out of his body. All right. We're going to make
intelligence guy. We'll give him some damage and give him some speed. Let's go. He's literally
making shit up. I don't see at least a hundred pogchamps from that. That was fucking awesome.
Hey, friend of healer. Can you make me 20 waters? Oh, sure. Thanks. Now what? Oh, we're up top now.
Cool. All right. What is it? Oh, get all the, get them all to the pickup point down there.
I don't want to go down here if I'm not supposed to be. Yep. This is it. God, I love the two FPS
boxes. I guess that they serve a purpose, but that purpose is a little weird because
how, shouldn't I be able to toggle that? What does one do? Don't you think this is something
that's an interesting thing to toggle and not something that's on the screen all day?
Playing wow again on stream. We can all make that jump. Where's red? Red. All right. Just like me.
One, two, three. Good. Keep on. Where's number one? Here he is. He's fine. We got to make this
jump. Don't fall in. All right, let's go. Right behind you. Right behind him. Shit, I fell down.
I'll be up in a minute. Okay. We'll be up here. Just wait for me. Don't come down here. Don't come
down here. Don't come down here. Don't come down here. Don't come down here. Thank God they jumped.
Just switch, switch, switch, switch, switch, switch to somebody that's not stupid. Okay. All right. We
lost our leader. It's okay though. I'll do my best to. Need heels here. Need heels. I'm out of
mana. Need heels. Where are you supposed? Hey, where am I? Do you guys know where I am?
I don't know where I am. I'm in the water. I don't know. I don't know, dude. Just get up here. We're
almost there. We're almost there. Can you guys make this jump? I don't have wings of justice.
All right. You make the jump, dude. Just go for it. Yes. Nice. I don't know where I am. I'm still,
I'm still in the water. I've still, I got out of the water about two years ago.
I'm in the water. It's okay, dude. Don't worry. We got you. Need help to me, to me, to me, to me.
I got two. I got two. Fucking idiots. I have two. Come on. We're on our way. And I'm going to die.
I'm going to die here and that's fine. I'll fucking take it up with the guild leader later.
This is like, this is the type of shit. This is why we can't get the fucking top 100.
It's like Larry over there gets fucking stuck in the water and that's okay. Whatever.
That's fine. I did it myself. I did it myself. Anybody else getting hungry? Dude, I shit my
What do you mean? It's Alvin. It's Alvin. How is it? Why are they all down here? Where's four?
Wait, why do we it's out? Wait, it wasn't supposed to be. Wait, what does it sound like?
It's supposed to just be like lower pitch. Alvin and the E3 monks. Okay. I forget who is who.
Dude, can you fucking get a better mic? It sucks so bad. I know none of us here like
to bring it up. But like, I'm gonna bring it up because it's fucking annoying. Yeah,
it is kind of annoying. No, dude, it sounds even fucking worse. It's like, it's like you
ripped it out and put it back in. You know, just don't even talk to yourself. Just mute.
Yeah, just mute until you can get it figured out.
Okay, let's move out soldiers. This is fucking toxic. Also guys, remember, if you roll need on
anything, you're going to get kicked out. It's on Master Looter. If anyone wants to roll on
something if you roll need for something, you're going to be using your DKP. And I run this guild
and I am at every single event. So I have like 50,000 DKP. What a great system this was. I can
get anything I want whenever I want. No matter what it is. I have five DKP. Do I get anything?
Do I get anything? Do I get anything? Can I get some armor? Yeah, dude, we'll have somebody in
the guild craft you something, man. They'll craft it for you. It's like tier one dog shit,
but you know, whatever. Who cares? I keep falling off and they keep following me to my death.
Kill this thing. Come on, kill it. Toxic, toxic, toxic, toxic, toxic, toxic, toxic.
Hey, can you guys wait up? I got lost back here. Every fucking time. Seriously, dude, every fucking
time. Pop this shit out or fucking leave. Just leave the guild if you can't fucking handle it.
Well, I didn't. I'm just like, I'm busy. Yeah, you're busy, but you can't do anything. You
fucking know. You're absolutely worthless. I'm sick of this shit. Can we stop fighting, please?
It's not even. He's such a fucking idiot and I'm sick of him being in this guild. He always brings
us down. He always is too slow and he always is causing problems. I'm not going to be in a
guild with him anymore. What the fuck, dude? Chill the fuck out. I'm not going to chill the fuck out
because I'm sick of you having to need shit and have to come up through the rankings here to get
gear that I could use. And I have my DPS meters like fucking 10 times higher than you.
Let me talk. This is getting too real. It's too real. I have to beat the mission first. That's
important. That's a 50 DKP mine. That's an old one. That's old. This is a toxic fucking guilt.
Yeah, we'll deal with it. You signed up. You went through the vigorous application process,
didn't you? And what did you say? What did you say? No, tell me. Tell me what you said.
Look, we all went through the process. Don't be a dick to him just because we all knew that
it was going to be 10 hours a day. We have shit to do, man. It can't just be all about World of
Warcraft. I mean, not that. What are we playing right now? What's this fucking MMO? Evolva,
dude. It's not just all about Evolva. You make everything all about Evolva and it's actually
kind of irritating. It's not all about Evolva? What are you talking about? What are all of you
talking about? You know what? All three of you. All three of you. One, two, three. Out of the
fucking guild. Goodbye. I will find other people that will replace you that can actually pull more
than 4K DPS. That's right. Jake, you can't fucking pull more than three and a half.
I'll show you how it is. Fucking dick. If you beat me, you get killed later. How's that sound?
I'm going to do my best. Stop trying. Come on, Jake. I think I'm going to get beaten by some
worm recruit. Not going to happen. Stupid idiot. I got you into this guild. Don't forget where you
came from. Don't forget I got you into the guild. I don't care where you are. My voice may have
changed, but it doesn't even matter. I don't think we can kill each other. I think, oh yeah,
right. We're in Shattrath City. We can't hurt each other. That's what I thought.
No, I just want to beat. Oh, I just want to beat the mission for the love of God.
We've lost him for good this time. Wait, everybody already made the jump and I just,
if you see me on the kill later, I can see you follow me. I don't follow anybody else.
I'm fucking losing my mind. I have to, I have to beat this. That's a whaling caverns jump.
I just have to get the jump. I just have to get the jump. All right. I'm going to make this jump.
If I don't make this, if I do not make this jump this time, I'm going to gift a hundred subs.
I swear to God, I'm going to gift 100 subs if I don't get it this time.
Dude, that's kind of a lot of subs. Are you sure you want to do that?
Shit. Dude, that's kind of, dude, that's kind of a lot of subs. Are you sure that you want to do that?
I am sure. Thank you, Jake. I am absolutely sure.
No more. Give me the fast. Give me the fast guy. Give me the guild leader. He'll do it.
Okay. We're good. I made it. Okay. I don't have to give a thousand subs, whatever the hell it was.
Oh, look who didn't make the jump. Look who didn't make the jump after all that.
Shut up, Jake. I mean, Bob.
Look who didn't make the fucking jump. And there he is keeping us up again.
Take your time, by all means, Jake. I just got the game two days ago.
See, I can't do it.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good. Give it to him, everybody.
Anybody else not care that he died? Not really. He was kind of a good person.
Yeah, he sucked. He sucked big time.
Jake, why don't you lead us from now on? Yeah, that sounds like a good idea.
All right. Me? Me? Okay, I'll try. Ready? Jump. You guys can do it. Come on. You can do it.
Uh, you know, maybe I should lead for now and then maybe eventually you can take over
and you get, you know, your bearings and everything and everything. Good to go.
Yeah, that's probably a good idea. Okay, let's go. The streamer doesn't have to
gift a hundred subs because he made it to the point that he got to. I'm watching the same stream
as you guys. That doesn't count. I don't have to give a hundred subs because I fell off. No,
falling off is not, I didn't try to go for a jump. I said if I didn't make the jump,
then I would gift a hundred subs. Not if I fell down backwards off the cliff. That's not, that's,
we don't, I don't have to do that. That's a scam. No, I said if I fall off. No, shit. I said if I
jump, he gave me the clip. Jake is still stuck down there. That's fine print. That's not scam.
No, I made the jump and then that was over. He's scamming. Technically, technically,
I haven't even saved the game. Not like copyright. Okay, there you go. Stop watching this scammer.
Hold on, hold on to your seats, everybody. Hold on. I'll meet you halfway at 50 because I
fell. I didn't jump. How's that song? I'll meet you halfway. I'll meet you halfway. I fell. I
didn't jump. I fell back. I'll meet you halfway. Deal? Deal. Deal. Is that a deal? 75 is not halfway.
Okay, let me do this. I have to like, am I logged in? There is a, there is, what was that? That's
YouTuber kind of days. There is, okay, there is a mature audience warning at the beginning of this.
You guys have been lying to me for like a year. Non-descript civilian making up my subs that I'm
not giving. All right, gift a sub. Let's go. I'll meet you at 50. I didn't, I technically,
I fell backwards. I didn't jump. Come on, Gwen. There it is. Did you get it? Did you get one?
Did you get one? 50 community subs from Chirba985. Thanks, dude. I really appreciate that.
Five from Pugatron, five from AjaxTheMidiocre, 10 from AjaxTheMidiocre, and then $105 from StormyChu.
Holy shit. You made up the other 50. You don't have to do that. That's insane. 200, like,
that's a lot of money. You don't have to do that. That's 50 community subs from Inferno23.
You don't gotta make up for me. That's a shitload of subs. That's a lot of money.
You just gave the money back. StormyChu, thanks for the $105, which is also insane. Now,
I haven't laughed this much in a very long time. I'm glad I tuned into the stream. Thank you.
Glad you're having a good time. Let's keep going. What do you say? Thanks for the extreme amount
of money. Me and friends. He called his friends. He called them friends. He called them friends.
He called his friends. It slipped. And thanks for the five, Jamie. Thanks for this five subs.
All right, let's go. All right. Who's still alive? That's seriously, that's a ton of money.
What is number four still doing? Can four not make the jump? What's the problem? Why are you
still down here? All right. I'm just going to keep going. We're going to go with the new leader here.
What's this? This is the pickup point? Oh shit. This is the pickup point. Get on up there.
You set them to hold position. I did. What button was that? Enter mutator, group genos,
ungroup them, select them, command mode, command all, best geno. All right. Command mode. Pause.
Pause. Oh, regroup them. Don't regroup to you. All right. Group. Regroup to me. Command. Group.
T. All to me. There they go. All right. Nice. What is best geno? Command. Hurry up. Get over here.
Come on, Jake. Let's go. I'll take control. Come on. Just go. Go. I almost didn't make it.
Get to the checkpoint. Hurry. All right. We made it. F10. We only lost one. Mission status completed.
Objectives. Do them all. Killed 65%. Killed 76%. We got jump, claw, and speed. New genes.
Land number two. No boss. There is a boss. We have to beat the first boss. I'm not moving
until we beat the first boss. Employ your team of geno hunters. Locate and destroy any non-indigenous
structures in the vicinity. It would appear that these creatures have been created by some organism
for its own protection. Scans have revealed that the seismic activity relates to the rapid
appearance of a number of structures interconnected by tentacle-like roots that may serve as conduits.
Resident sleeper. Whatever. Okay. All right. Obtain type one explosive plant spore. Who's back?
The dick. Oh, that means there's probably going to be like a T-Rex behind them chasing them. Yep.
I knew it. All right. Get in. Get in. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. All right. Get in.
Nice DPS. All right. We're going to use the strong one. Big kid hulk. That name doesn't
make any sense anymore. It doesn't. What the hell is that? Is that machine guns? Okay. This machine,
this guns. All right. Let's take a look at the mutating. I can do more power and more speed
or more jump and more power. More power and more speed. Always. All right. Keep that the way it is.
What about you? More power, more jump or more jump, more speed. More power, more jump. Your speed
only. We got power or just even more speed. Even more speed. I do even more speed. Even more speed.
What about you? I feel like you've been pretty neglected. What can you do?
Is this damage? Damage and speed? Sure. Good. Yeah. That's fine. All right. Let's go.
Use speed so you can get this done.
Come on. Oh, safe spot right here. Get up here. More evolve. Don't fall off. All right. We're good.
Keep going. Everyone with me? You're doing Dexville. Is it boss time? I don't know. Maybe.
Watch it. Watch it. Don't go any close. Stay over here. Come over here and stay.
Stay. I thought T was stay. Somebody dead? Come on. You two idiots. What are you doing?
Go. Make your way through it, please. All right. Here comes one. He's still having trouble. Whatever.
All right. How do I make them? T. T. T and S for stay. One is having trouble. All right. What's up?
Fighting down there. Okay. I'm going to go to one. No, no, no. Do not follow one.
Don't follow one. Are you following one? You're not supposed to be. Oh, fuck him. Who cares?
Wait. Okay. Good. Wait. None of them have jump. I hope they can make this. Finally. You made it.
Fuck you long enough. There's a hole. All right. Who's got the biggest claws?
Three. All right. How do I get people to stay? I want you to stay over here and stay here.
What's the stay command? Group and group nearby genos. Group all genos. Ungroup them is H.
Command mode is tab. Command all genos. B? Team chat. That's chat. What are you talking about?
It's H. Okay. Ready? Let's go. All right. Now. One at a time. Don't. Oh, fuck. Take him into the
electrocution room. Don't get yourself killed. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Just go. Go.
Go. Eat. Eat. Eat. Eat. Eat. Eat. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Eat. Eat. Eat. Eat. Eat. And go.
The neg? Can I pick this egg up? What's it doing? Is it healing me? I think it's a heal.
Oh, this is the explosive. How do I get it? How do I pick it up? Okay. It's R. Obtain type two
explosive. Oh, shit. Can I pick up these little guys? All right. Let's go back through here.
Is this a Dreamcast game? Yeah. Go this way. All right. What happens if we. Is it fall damage?
Yep. It's quite a lot actually. Well, we're going to lose the leader again.
Dreamcast fucking sucks. Laughing my ass off. Favorite comment ever. I think I can level up
again. Chuck E. Cheese is streaming fall guides. Yeah, I know. I know. It's a guy in a Chuck E.
Look, you had my attention at first when you said it was Chuck E. Cheese, but it's not the 3D
animated Chuck E. Cheese. It's a guy in a Chuck E. Cheese costume opening his mouth every so often.
Like if it was the 3D animated Chuck E. Cheese and he had like a guy talking for him and stuff.
VTuber Chuck. VTuber Chuck E. Cheese. Kill this thing. We need more damage.
Ridiculous. Ridiculous. Eating the explosions. Just back away when they get like that.
Okay. I gotta level up. Let's go with one. What do you got? This is new. I don't know if that is.
Okay. This game just got cool. This is becoming a cool game now. I can breathe fire out of my mouth.
Yeah. Oh, I'll take it. Okay. What about new? New two. Shit. Is that? Okay. No. Okay. Oh,
you can do them all. I don't have to get out of the menu. What's this one? Is this fire?
What is that? That's not fire. It is fire. Damage. Damage. Well, I don't want two people doing fire.
All right. You don't do that. Don't do that. Something else. Give more jump. Oh, this guy's
fucked. Whatever. Who breathes fire? Where's the fire breather? Back up. How do I breathe fire?
Oh, it's okay. There you go. You have to select two. All right. Does it use mana?
All right. That's awesome. That's awesome. Holy shit. Is this too loud?
Why didn't everybody tell me this? It's still too loud. I can finally hear myself think.
Okay. Go in. I can't wait to get the first boss. Burn. Fire versus fire. I can burn the leaves.
That's cool. I'm going to raid Chuck E. Cheese right now? You want to raid Chuck E. Cheese
right now and have my stream end? No, I'm still streaming. All right. Give me claws.
Mirror. Please. They said they... No. I'm not having you guys gaslight me and telling me that
Chuck E. Cheese said he was a big fan or something. No, that's not going to work.
It's not going to work right now. Help. He did. Whatever. I used to love that place. I used to
love bringing in my report card and clearly there's like a bunch of C's and D's on it,
but they didn't want anyone to feel bad, so they gave you the same amount of tokens.
That's the person that came in with straight A's. If you showed a report card with like B's or higher,
this is a real story. I'm about to give you guys some real story. I may have told this before,
but I can tell it again. I don't care. When I was a little kid, we would go to Chuck E. Cheese
and my mother, God bless her, she would use my brother's and sister's report cards and try to
get a package deal because my report card sucked. It'd be like, well, take a look at this.
This kid's got straight A's. This kid's got straight A's and B's. I think that's okay.
We deserve the tokens. I was sitting there just like with my finger in my nose. I don't do good
in math. It was like a 17-year-old behind the counter. He's not going to be like, well,
he didn't have exactly a 3.0. We think they care? No. What? Of course not. All right, let's get
fast, Jerma. Let's burn, Jerma. Burn, Jerma. I don't like the fire. These ones hate it.
Anybody level up yet? Jerma, look. That kind hates ice and fire. Three is about to die.
Three's dead. Two hits. Does anybody have a heal? Where's the healer? Somebody help me. Save me.
Save me. Where's two? Uh-oh, two's almost dead too. Jerma, don't look. The link sucks. Does it?
What? Anybody level up again? Yep. All right. This is fire. Yeah, more fire. More firepower.
More firepower. I don't know what the hell this person's doing, but should we give them the claws
back? No, let's make this fast jumping guy. He doesn't do any damage. That makes sense.
You need to have your one scout on the team, right? And this is...
You're going to have to be DPS now because we lost the other guy. All right. Yeah, four is DPS.
Look, chat. There's no way I'm not going to cut my hand off. What the hell is this? What the hell is
that? What's the point of writing that? Wait, didn't three have a... Combine type one and type two to
create an explosive. Uh, where's the other egg? Wasn't three carrying the egg? Okay, thank God.
Wait, combine the two of them. How do I combine the eggs? I think it'll just do it automatically?
Germa, it's real. All right. If this link is not at least a seven or eight out of ten,
I'll be very upset with you guys. If this link is not at least a seven out of ten,
I have an issue. Fuck you, cheese. Yeah, I'm a fan of Germa and love him. Is that doctor? Is that
real? Is this a doctored image? Wait, is this actually the... Hold on. I got to be careful
here because... Let me show you. Let me show you. This is important. We have to discuss this.
Did somebody just make this account and start broadcasting and then screencap it or fake it?
Or is this the real account? That's real? So this must mean I must get infinite tokens at every
Chuck E. Cheese I ever go to. That has to be what it means. Can I just show this at any Chuck E.
Cheese and be like, hey, yeah, I mean, you know, so act like it's a report card. Let's go.
Of Germa and Chuck E. Cheese crossover. I don't want... Okay. Chuck E. Cheese was awesome.
It was such a fun place to be when you were a kid. Did I just say the tagline? No, it's where a kid
can be a kid. Is that Toys R' Us? What is it? What's the tagline? But 35 year old man doing a
collab with Chuck E. Cheese. Well, I don't know what we would do there. What does that mean?
And that wouldn't be kind of a little weird. It would. But how would you do that? I don't
know if I... Look, okay, unless I have like a niece or a nephew with me at 35. I'm not going
into Chuck E. Cheese, guys. I'm not going there for the pizza. What would I do? What would it be?
Why would I be in there? You're a loser. Why? Why not? Because it's where a kid can be a kid.
Not where a 35 year old man can be a 35 year old man. We have enough bowling alleys, guys,
but you're a kid inside. He drowned. So he just pushed my head under water. Don't tell him, guys.
I'm right behind him. He streams in a bathtub. He streams in a four foot deep pool. The computer
is up on one of those weird rafts. I just dunked his ass. Can I get some plus twos? And I come back
up and like, oh, what the fuck, man? I wasn't ready for that. What is it where a kid can be a kid?
What is that from? And why do these guys only have eyeballs now? DPS? Nobody's just lost.
Will you fight it? Chuck E. Cheese has blackjack now. Can you imagine a bunch of like little kids
sitting around playing blackjack? And the dealer would have to be a kid too. That's the only way
that would work. That's the only way this works for me. Sorry, sir. You busted. Oh, no. Oh, man.
21. I got blackjack. That's right, kids. Come on in to Chuck E. Cheese. We've got all your
favorite slots. Blackjack. Poker. And they give Chuck E. Cheese like a big gold tooth.
And he smiles. Come on in, kids. He leans in and is in his teeth. He pulls back his mouth and smiles.
Deep. Ding. Right into the camera. This guy's not strong enough to break this. No, we need fire guy.
In fact, fire guy's the only guy that's good. Kids out of blackjack table. Things that you should
never see. Wait, Chuck E. Cheese. What? Hold on. What does this say? I need to read this. Apparently,
this is... God damn it. It was all a fucking lie. It was all a lie. It was all a lie. It was all a
lie. This is all a doctored lie. The whole thing. I got, I got gaslit again. Again,
it happens every stream. It happens every single stream. It's a fake account. It's a fake fucking
account. You put the stupid fucking thing on here. Of course you did. Yeah. Chuck E. Cheese would
never say something like that. Got my hopes up so bad. Chuck E. Cheese would never say that.
I can't believe it. I knew it too, because I'm like, yeah, you could have just like made this in
10 seconds. Chuck E. Cheese holds himself to a much higher standard than that. It's real. It's not real.
Chuck E. Cheese does not ask me if I eat ass. Chuck E. Cheese did not say that. I, I am absolutely
positive about this. If I've, if I've been positive of anything in my whole life, ever, it's that
Chuck E. Cheese did not ask if you eat ass. There's not a chance. Like, you could tell me,
look behind you, dude, there's an alien spaceship that's about to just drop fucking beams of light
of death onto us. And I would be like, yeah, that's probably more, that would probably happen.
That's accurate. I'm okay with that. That's fine. Sure. Whatever. That's more able to happen than a
do you eat ass Chuck E. Cheese comment. I like, I didn't even believe it either. I believed it for
like 10 seconds. Check the VOD. What lucky T on the VOD. At some point you see him reach over to
his keyboard and just start like enter. Wait, don't go that way. We still have fast guy. Yep.
Oh, we have to blow something up in chat. He's not in chat. He's busy playing fall guys and
entertaining millions of children around the world. You didn't have time for me. I need claws.
Back it up. What do you mean? I'm looking at the viewer list right now. And if this is another
just total gaslight campaign, I'm going to be so bad users in chat. Okay. So Chuckle Morris and
Chuck E. Cheese real are the only two people in this chat that have Chuck in their name.
So, wow. I can't believe it. Chuck E. Cheese real is in here. That's unbelievable. Like,
that's so weird. Remember if you put real at the end of your name, that has to be real.
All right. Follow me. Oh, can I revive three or is he dead the whole game?
Guys, there's a stop running into that. There's a real German nine eight five in this chat.
So yeah, that's easy to determine. Will you guys leave them alone? Can I destroy these?
Oh, all right. Fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast. EPS. I need to control the DPS.
That's our only hope of victory at all. This game's actually kind of fun. I could see
four. Did you hear how crazy that that Sybilis was? I mean, I just whistled to you when I was
like 14. I would have loved this. I got to be a level up tune. What tune are you going to be on?
I died. I never I did the tune. I don't ever like to tune. I like character. Get out of here.
Out, out, out, out. Don't stand in that. Don't be stupid. Attention. Attention. What do you want?
You got it. You've got my attention. You have my attention. What is it? Actually here. Wait,
is that real? Is that a real name, though? Chuck E. Cheese is here. What are you? What's
what is Chuck E. Cheese doing here? What have you got? What did you guys do? Why did you do this?
Why? I all right. Make sure I look. This is like a job. This is like a bigger than a job
interview. Chuck E. Cheese is here. Fucking mustache hair. I got to fix that. Hey, Mr. Cheese,
I'm Jerma. You may have had some people come into your chat and just be all rambunctious and crazy.
Sorry about that. I respect you and respect your of your establishment. I love what you do. I love
your pizza, by the way. It's good. He left. I failed the interview. I should have turned the
webcam on with funny whiskers on and put like eyeshadow on and be like screeching into the
camera. That would have been perfect. Idiot. Why you guys? Why? He's this is high Jerma in the thing,
but I it's because you gave him 10. You gave him $10 to do that. You isolate going all over the
place right now. You gave Chuck E. Cheese $10 for him to say that he's typing in the chat.
Should I be am I going to VIP Chuck E. Cheese? This feels like the strangest day of my life.
Doesn't this feel like the day that just shouldn't happen? This just shouldn't happen.
Chuck E. Cheese. This is what happens in a dream. When you have a this is a dream scenario.
I think I've had a dream like this where like I VIP like Hulk Hogan in the chat and it was like,
oh my God, Hulk Hogan's here guys. I'm not modding Chuck E. Cheese. I don't know what he would do
with that kind of power. Feels bad, man. Like I just fucking rip up from my bed. That's what
happened right now. It didn't happen though. Sweat is pouring down my body and I have somehow I was
in full clothing when I went to bed and I'm naked in the bed like just covered in water and sweating.
Okay, so thanks Chuck E. Cheese for what am I thanking him for? For like for showing his
his presence. Thank you Chuck E. Cheese for even I'm saying the name saying the name over and over
again. I'm saying Chuck E. Cheese I've said it like a thousand times in the last 40 minutes.
Whatever you're doing it's it's working. Whatever you're doing it's working. His name is Charles.
Chuck is short for Charles. You're a corporate. If you okay I'm sorry but if you think Chuck E.
Cheese is like corporate it's an arcade where they serve fucking pizzas. It's like that fucking
corporation. Yeah those corporations like Chuck E. Cheese. What are you what? Yeah we're talking
about corporate fucking Amazon corporation that just it's huge. Google, Apple, Chuck E. Cheese.
You're gonna get banned for life from Chuck E. Cheese. I'm not gonna get banned for life
from Chuck E. Cheese. You're swearing in front of Chuck E. Cheese. Chuck E. Cheese had to click
on the yes I am gonna watch the mature audience stream. So this is not me. That means that Chuck
E. Cheese is like 40 or at least 18. So we got a game here it's called Evolva. I'm not sure you ever
heard of it before. I can't believe Chuck E. Cheese is playing Fall Guys. What a brilliant idea.
That's like the smartest thing I've ever seen like a company do. What do you mean company? I know okay
look yes all right I'll play along. I'll play along. I'll play along. Wow Mr. Cheese I can't
believe you. You're so good at Fall Guys. You're simping for these people. Simping for Chuck E.
Cheese. You want to cue into him on Fall Guys. You want me to hold on a minute. I wake up wake
up wake up wake up wake up. You want me to stream snipe Chuck E. Cheese in Fall Guys on stream.
They're like having fun with it. Okay I gotta reduce the THC by at least two milligrams.
I feel like this isn't even happening. This is I'm like still playing the game right now.
I'm just walking around in the game and like hitting shit and killing stuff and getting
experience points. This is just going on somewhere in my head and eventually I'm going to blink
and I'm going to be playing the game and I'm going to be and the whole chat is going to be going
you all right is he okay what's going on is he okay what's wrong with him is he okay
like I'm going to this is what's happening right now I'm sitting here like this.
This is what you guys see. This is what you see but that's not what's going on.
Get me up. Somebody's got to pull me up. This is a shitload of enemies. Stay alive stay alive.
He's out. Oh shit he's dead. Level up. Level up. Level up. Level up. Okay give him
extra power. Look at those claws. These claws are huge now. No stop stop like
stop. Okay yeah oh look look Skittles is here now. Look you don't have to look I get it. You're
trying to make me feel like cool and feel good that every candy bar and like junk food cartoon
kids company is following me. I know and look it's okay we don't have to pretend. I know you're
really trying to make me feel good about knowing that cartoons think I'm cool I guess. I fucking
lost. I'm so annoyed at this that I lost this but I don't even wait I failed it so now what?
Oh my god that's bad. What was the last time I saved the game? He just keeps coming in here
writing feels bad man. Feels bad man. How do we make him happy? All right all right Chuck E. Cheese.
I will make I will be I will I will take everything back and I'll say hey you're the man you're
awesome and I love Chuck E. Cheese but you've got to you've got to put your hand behind one of the
arcade cabinets and drag like this and if your hand isn't black with dirt then I will take back
everything like if you you gotta go back behind one of the cabinets like this and go like this
if it's not like dead bugs and red black and brown and stuff if it doesn't look like that
it's just dirt and dust of the like what okay well dirt and I need to wake up you're insulting
him to his face no I'm not okay you ready I don't think I want I don't think we should do this
he's behind my monitor clean what he's gone I love Chuck E. Cheese it was a different hand
what did he say what did he say he said something wait he did it he did he did he put his hand
behind the thing what does it what does it look like what how is he here and playing fall guys
it's clean okay that it does not he did not put that sign up what else what
what he said something else too this is fucked up what else do you need cap oh wait are we making
like a weird avengers it's germa 985 Chuck E. Cheese Count Chocula a guy from the subway
can we make our own can you can we be part of the avengers that's just germa rumble well now you're
gonna be in germa rumble you have to be now you have to be you're gonna be in germa rumble and
I mean your stats are gonna be absolutely zero but you're gonna be in what's up okay those of
you I get this is I don't care if this whole thing got derailed those of you that are annoyed at
brand brand oh he's putting a brand in germa half of every character in germa rumple is a
branded serial character they're all brands don't be surprised if you see the oscar mayer wiener
in 2020 they're all brands that's a sellout whoa got something going on back here something
going on back there I need a haircut uh no uh you gotta be in the rumble though but you're not
gonna be chuck e cheese you'll be like rat kid I don't know he wants to be in the rumble wait
try this chuck e cheese what you want to be part of the rumble chuck e cheese can you imagine
germa rumble 2020 brought to you by chuck e cheese I can I could sell it I could sell it
I don't think they have any more money and they don't I right I'm just trying to be real what
about the fruits actual sellout I I'm sorry guys if like chuck e cheese wanted to sponsor a stream
that's like the most outrageous fucking thing I could ever imagine like that would be hysterical
to me but let hold on let me just make sure I can make this really clear none of this is about
any where there's no current partnership I have no connection with chuck e cheese at all zero
I have nothing to do with them I'm stating my opinions on how much dirt is behind the machine
okay that's it that's all this was this is just opinions my thoughts and opinions based on no
connection to any company guilty innocent innocent innocent innocent wake up Jeremy
wake up it's time to get up it's time to wake up wake up Jeremy wake up shit it's real
holy shit this guy's losing it hey ban that person please don't be that far away I need to be through
a boss I have to get through a boss ban that person okay we're okay we have both the eggs we're
fine all right quick fast all jokes aside I've really I really do I like chuck e cheese it's
like it was a really fun place where a kid can be a kid I spent countless hours in chuck e cheese
I want to know the report card lore if I wasn't a chuck e cheese fan huh
huh it's not an ad I've not I don't guys haven't been to chuck e cheese in like at least 25 years
you're reading a script wait what is this is this the first level this is the first level isn't it
oh god I have to get to a boss I'm not stopping this stream until I get to a boss
level up omega low level one Larry no it was not 25 when I would I don't even know what the
inside of a chuck e cheese looks like this is not level two I mean level one this is level two
you gotta get the two eggs and then why is this one would run in a circle oh right right right
right I remember this part first boss is level five all right well strap in this person even
get up here chuck e cheese Andy it wouldn't just be chuck e cheese why would it why would it
why do you have to have Andy I have to this person has to be able to defend himself it's
ridiculous it feels like it was ages ago that we lost the big guy and he's the guy that does
the actual damage all right let's go Andy cheese because you think the Andy joke is funny well I
mean it it's cheese Andy all right it's time for fire breath everybody get over here and stay back
I'm trying not to hurt everybody Charles Albertson cheese all right get in there fight
save it let's quick save so I can spam it f5 f5 got it chuck e cheese has a better stream
okay should I be sad about that I'm gonna cry on camera I'm gonna pull the camera up and
just start crying all right this is where I was last time I'm gonna evolve again after this
put eye drops in and just start crying all right why don't you just put eye drops in and just have
them running down my face in full face cam and just be quote in the middle of like a sentence
so when people I'll always be talking like this we'll wait till at least a few people come in
like and I I I I I that's what I went there I saw it right like you go in the middle of a sentence
so when anybody comes in it's not like you're waiting for them to come in for you to do the bit
you're in the middle of it you're just talking so if I sit here like this and I go
wait wait wait for somebody to come in wait for somebody new okay so uh I'm crying no no I'm
crying and mid like uh and then somebody will get somebody yeah because the people will know it's an
act fucking face none of you guys know anything about acting okay back it up back it up don't
fall don't do it true don't stand next to it don't stand up to it twiddle d and twiddle dickhead
this is impossible nobody can even beat this level what the fuck give me that egg just I'm
gonna we're gonna bomb it just bomb bomb bomb bomb it bomb it bomb it bomb it bomb this thing
how do we pull a bomb down plant the bomb all right it's in there plant the bomb plant the bomb
it's working just get into the thing who has it just run run run run run just don't even fight
these things it's a thousand of them all the minus twos yeah arming minus twos that's what I do best
okay then bring how do we explode this how do we pull this up put them both in here and then what
is supposed to explode combine type one and type two how the fuck do you combine them
did I do it okay I did it worse noise yeah does that count though because that was on purpose
that was as awful as I could make something be and sound on purpose does that count if it's on
purpose all right now just one needs to get in there get out get out get out it's okay somebody's
life run run I won I won all right cool okay land number three almost the boss okay herd
indigenous creatures to containment area defend these indigenous creatures from attack ensure
that the population survives clear this region of enough parasite life forms to ensure reinfection
does not occur this is going to be an escort mission herd indigenous creatures to containment
area all right let's go fast guy do next game I'm not done with this one where's this indigenous
creature next game we're gonna play is that uh the game where you make money and you clean up
like a space shuttle and you have to take junk and stuff whatever it's called it's got a long
name that's hard to remember what's it called no not viscer cleaning it's it's called something
else hard space ship breaker yes that's the one it's the one with like the warcraft npc name
how do you only play games no one heard of uh I played fall guys like I played four guys like
three days ago I like I like nostalgia I just got a headshot you got fucking snipe holy shit that
was bad okay well I don't really want to save it what is four doing what's the last new game I
played but hey okay that I we hear this argument and I love to rebuttal this argument it's like
why do you play old games that nobody likes what's a new game that people like you know I
think I could swing it that way so okay name me like a game that's come out in the last year
that was like wow it's worth it I can't think of one how the wilds didn't come out this year
in it everybody got destroyed no my warcraft guild is dead wait I can still make it to the
indigenous creature give me some speed give me some speed give me some speed what's that it's
like ice I don't know what that is but what is it looks cool that's awesome speed speed okay we're
good the gun this game's cool you guys just don't want to give it a chance all right where's this
creature shit all right we're gonna play uh spaceship breaker whatever it's called now I
actually enjoyed this though what that was fun it's a cool concept too it was fun I liked it
let's play hypno space ship outlaw whatever it is just in case for some reason I come back here
wait wouldn't quick save to be a dead screen why would I save it there does that make hold on that
is okay let me I'm just gonna go pee I'll be right back we'll play uh the ship game