What you guys don't know is when I press the go live button, so I'm you know, I started somewhere around noon today, right?
One two four, whatever it is. I press the button and
I fucking sprint out of here
And I run out of the room and I finished the last second things that I need to do and I know I got like
I know I got a minute or two before I have to talk
So if I have to go to the bathroom or if like wait, I forgot I forgot to put ice in my coffee
Sprint
And then i'm back here. You have you have no idea you don't know do the chaos that happens
Two minutes before I start talking every day
He forgot to no I didn't
You would just do it before you start you have no idea
You have no idea. I I do everything I sit down. There's no ice in the coffee
or
It's the coffee's at half. I gotta refill it. I can't i'm not gonna start streaming without a full coffee
I gotta run down the stairs
But not spill it, you know
He's bullshitting us
You got to sing the late song
What is this?
What is this? I have to sign this
I don't want to sign this
Wait, this says
Let me read this to make sure I know what i'm doing
says
contract
I Jeremy Albertson will not make any reference to
the binding of Isaac
world of warcraft
Hearthstone or dark souls during this stream
If I do I will gift five community subs per reference
That's kind of unfair. What do I get if I don't do it?
Well, what if I get if I don't do it? I'm not signing this. Where's my end of the deal?
I get some debt removed
Well, how much debt this is important?
100 million. No, it's gotta be more than that
200 million final offer. I'm not doing it
No deal. What do you mean deal? I've seen a lot more deals, but you have to sign it
Hold on. I can't. Oh, yeah. All right. I'll sign it. I'm not signing it until
But hold on a minute. I need to I need to be sure that this is gonna wipe away 200 million
It's not even worth it's not worth even 50 million. You know it. Are you kidding me?
This is like the four games I talk about every single day
You are taking
Okay, let's say during at any given stream. I say
I don't know
10 000 sentences
You are deleting 4000 sentences from my vocabulary
I'm gonna I'm gonna have to talk about something else
140 million take it or leave it. All right, i'll take it. I'll take it 140 million the deal
All right. How do I gotta sign this now?
All right, if I don't make any of these references during the stream, I get 140 million right away from that goddamn debt
All right, I gotta sign it
Let me sign this
Okay, hold on sign it in just a second
Gotta get my pen out. I gotta get my pen out write that out real quick. They're the same font that you used
Wait, wait, wait, I didn't even spell my name right. Hold on
Hold on. Let me let me rewrite that
There we are
Wait, I gotta get it in red ink
There you go
Signed it. Yeah, but don't forget about the amendment
That's at the end here
That I get 140 million dollars wiped off the debt if I don't do this
Addendum, whatever. All right. I'm no I okay. Hey, I signed it. I'm not gonna say any of this shit
um
Okay, I so I remember I can't say any of these words
But hold on a minute. Let's talk about semantics here
It has to be like in quotes those things
I I can say the word
I can say the word
I can say that I can't say these words at all
The no no, this is a reference to these games not I can't say the word the
I have to be able to say the world the word world
This is unfair
These are references. Yes. All right. I get it. All right, it's been it's been signed
I gotta keep this on my other monitor
So I remember what games it is because i'm gonna be like, oh man. Oh, here's the enemy from
Never mind
I can't wait to not do this and just get 140 million shaved off
All right. I got the games right here
Oh
Oh shit, I burnt it into my monitor
Oh well
That's that's just my watermark
Yeah, we're gonna play hades
I welcome everybody. Hope you had a good a few days
Oc don't steal it. Don't steal it. It's mine
What's your name on top?
No, i'm not i'm not gonna just put my name. Uh, here's my name up top
That would be so weird
Like i'm so desperate i'm so like scared that somebody's gonna steal this stream or something
Why didn't you watermark a stream? But why would you watermark a stream with your your full name?
Wouldn't it be a username or a production industry or company or something?
Uh, we got we got community subs
10, uh to be exact
By an anonymous gifter don't know who it is, but that's actually your name on twitch
So we know who you are, but we don't know who's behind the mask
Thanks for the 10 subs
And we also had five subs from ruined ruined bloodline. Thank you for the five community subs
Both you guys back to back there. Thank you
As he played this before I have never played hades before
The title of the stream should tell you all you need to know
I saw that it was nominated for game of the year. It's been recommended a bunch of times and I didn't play it
so this is a uh
This is a this is a game of the year nominated bandwagon stream
Well, I guess I got nominated for game of the year
So, uh, i'm gonna play it. I guess I did the same thing with celeste
So, you know
That's what we do here
Is it it's it's apparently it's very very good
Very good from what I understand. Oh my god, please don't turn the camera on. Okay. Good. Hey easy cash
Thanks for the 10 community subs
Easy cash another 10 and i'm ready. I think the settings are good. I turned off screen shake
Screen shake in my opinion should be something you have to turn on not turn off. I don't know who likes it
I don't think i've met a single person that actually likes to use screen shake screen shake. It's weird, right?
Does and does anyone like it? It just like hurts your head. What about the wisdom music? Am I echoing?
Okay. No, that's just the okay. Never mind. It's on it's very low
It's all right. I turned it on
I don't like music in my ears loud. I'm telling you you guys already know that it distracts me
I I I drive a car silent. I play games in silence
But on god mode why?
Music's so good. All right, and you'll be able to hear it slightly on god mode. You're gonna need it
Well, that's a great opinion of yours that you can have
Until I don't get hit one time in the first hour of the stream and i'm willing to bet
Okay, I was gonna say a bunch of like way. I can't say these words
Not bet no more bets. Let's go. What's hell mode?
Don't even want to I don't even want to see what it is. I'm just gonna go
Inspires. Oh if I get hit in the first hour of the game, i'm gonna go that's it which we all share to tell you such a tale
Listen carefully
Okay
That us
Oh, wow. This is weird
This is weird to help with this place this top like this angle and the the color is
Can't hear anything. Yeah, you can you can hear it. I know you can hear it
There is that better?
Wait, okay. Let's go
All right, the combat's pretty fluid so this is like a
No, it's not on this list
Is diablo 2 is not on this list. You really fucked it up. Didn't you?
You didn't fuck it up. Did you? Oh you did actually you fucked it up bad leaving mine. Stop me
All right. All right. I get it. You cannot add anything by the way. This is a dash
There's a there's a roll
like in um
Like that game, uh
Splinter cell
Is there a dodge roll in splinter cell
Is it now it's too loud. You see i'm telling you you guys it's you guys have goldilocks in this
It's i'm gonna turn the all right. Here we go. I'm gonna turn the music up and the sound down
Check this out ready sound down
Music up
How's that?
All right, dude, has it been an hour yet?
It's been like an hour
I haven't even got touched once it's been an hour. It plays very good though. I like it
Like to break everything
It's like an arena. Oh
Is it an arena game? Oh, okay except it's got to be her here goes nothing in the name of hades
Olympus I accept this message
The hell is zogger us
Hail noble cousin
Now let's get you from that miserable place. I'll see that all of us upon olympus do our part. There's athena with me
Athena and zogger us
They make up this guy's zoggers. I thought this was supposed to be hades, isn't it?
Okay, do choose one bonus of athena
Divine your attack is stronger and can deflect 40% more attack damage you serious
Okay, your cast damage is posed in a small area and can deflect
85 your dash deals damage and can deflect
I think we're gonna have to go with divine strike press or hold x to use your main weapon
And we can deflect
The dash the dash dash awful awful awful. Well, I don't know your dash deals damage. All right, let's try it
I know you can't hear me all the way where you are goddess. Oh that it doesn't end a different animation, too
The reflect is good. All right
Stand aside. Oh, it does 10 damage. That's pretty good
I do 20 damage a swing. That's 50 damage just from dashing
Oh, that's a trap
I know there were traps in this game. How was I supposed to know?
I'm getting booed. I'm getting booed
Stop booing me for what?
What did I do? All right, should I try deflecting?
You should have listened gain one key. Oh, I kind of like this game
Each exit has its own reward. I like this game. This game's pretty good. It's pretty fun so far
I hope it does. I hope they don't drop the ball in the end zone
Okay, each what what are the symbols mean? What's okay? What's the steer? What's the like steering wheel versus the pitch for?
All right. I'm gonna go steering wheel. I'm gonna go the ship steering wheel. All right concentrate
Okay, I see that the things pop up over their heads. Is that is it like batman? Are they about to shoot me?
Like batman when it's like the indicator pops over their head and I press y to block it
Like I can deflect it. So here he goes. He's about to shoot you
Bad ending bugsnacks in hades banger stream and banger stream. Thanks
So this is an upgrade, okay, so this is a boon of athena so that's what that steering
Oh, this is an epic one. What's that?
There's different rarities your cast damages foes in a small area and can deflect so that's a different move
Your abilities that can deflect also make foes exposed. Oh shit so I can wait. Hold on a minute
Don't don't look at the flashy purple letters. I can dash through people and hit them in the back
This is 90 damage reduce from traps. I don't want that. That's I mean, i'm sure it'll be useful for me
Because i'm 90 damage is good. Yeah, but if I step on stuff all the time. Oh, yeah, that's probably good for me
But I want this one
I can go wham wham wham wham wham
I'm already making a build. I don't I don't need your advice
I had over like 300 days played on team fortress 2. I know how to make loadouts
I know how to make a character look good. I know how to make a character strong. I gotta be careful
I'll slip up there. I will that's a tf2 reference. Yeah, it sure is not on that list though, is it?
Get out of the way. I'm trying to do the thing. What the fuck does that do? Oh nice
Nice. All right. Cool. This game's pretty good
Oh this i'm i'm i
I like it
It's juggles
Wait, what is that?
All right, there's one more fat guy over here
Backstab backstab backstab juggles is the great. Oh, I got hit
You can cleave too
Oh gain 10 what was that 10 what that's plus 10
The clash of clans currency. Thank god. I didn't say in one of those four games
This is gonna be way harder than I thought
I need health
I have to be so careful. All right, let's let's pull don't just be an idiot pull one at a time
This game's a hard game. It's not an easy game. No, I don't want three of you. There's my one
How did you hit me? What really?
Do not spawn
Oh shit, i'm in trouble. All right
Oh good, we're good. We're good. Oh my god. We're not good. We're not good. Wait, can I go into the traps?
Use your special
I didn't know I even had one
What?
And why?
I don't even know what that I didn't know I even had this move
Is this a reddit game? Probably
Just because you said it was if you but hey, don't you know if you think it's a reddit game?
It's a reddit game
You wouldn't even have that you wouldn't even think that it's a reddit game if you if you could if there was any doubt
There's only one hatcher I know of it's a twitter game hold on a minute anyway in the name of hades olympus I accept this message
All right, I had to clear my throat
All right, so there's a new message
Artemis i'm not like all the others on olympus the power of the hunt helps keep me company. So
Maybe it'll help you to use the fucking buttons. I I look i've just I don't know they didn't tell me I had like a heavy attack
It started five minutes ago. I just started five minutes ago
You don't tell the the the kid and his first day of culinary school
He has to bake make a wedding cake and if it's not the best wedding cake that the teacher's ever eaten
Then he's gonna just get kicked out of school. That's not how this works
Oh, what a minute any damage you do has a chance to be crit. All right, so this is just like fuck this thing
This thing's way better
15 crit or he's get three percent crit
That's terrible. All right, we're doing deadly strike. It sounds like good company to keep
the
double cube for boon info
Can't heal myself, but I can fight this shit. This just shows you everything you have
That's helpful. It's a fucking cursed link. Hold on. Let's take a look at whatever this cursed link is
I'll be the judge of that. Yep, which path all right, wait, this means it's a boss there and then this means health
I'm getting the health
Kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill. It's pretty clean
That's not that much health at all. That's no health. That's none. That's zero health
It's 25 health. I thought it was gonna be like a full heal. Oh, these are elites which is they absorb my blow
How could they?
Well, I just saw somebody say the word and I I must was like, you know what? Yep, what's gonna happen?
Ooh
Starting to have to pay more attention to things
What's wrong with me? What's my character being weird? Is the game good? Yeah
So far, I mean i'm in the first zone. I'm assuming it's gonna get way harder
You have controller drift, is that true?
Well, I gotta use y more often. It's good
All right, let's go bring it on
Shoot me. Oh
Come over
Game is low. It's not I can see how loud it is right now
It's very loud
Ooh, what's this?
Pomegranate versus bag of treasure. Hmm. I'm gonna say bag of treasure hurts my ears
Do it louder we can take it. I don't think you can take it
Oh
Hold on. I get
I get the mcdonald. I get the travis scott meal
Or a pomegranate. What do I want?
Nobody liked that one. Some of you did some of you did so they get the pomegranate. I don't even want to do it
What does it do?
I'm useful
arm of power
Uh, okay. I just get to pick an upgrade
Oh wait, you can up these upgrade
That's pretty cool
Okay, so dash deals damaging into flight. So this just increases the damage
Bonus backstab 70%
I think I have to do this one. That's so much more of these upon olympus. Who's this guy?
This is charon
I get to see you care on night just minding my own business taking in the sights and
Sure is awfully convenient to be running into you like this charon
Guys, I haven't I don't know. I look I know like I know
The only reason why I know these characters is because of smite
you know
mercury
He's probably in the game
hades
um
artemis
uh
athena
This is not a okay. No
Place might is the games is that is the game still fun or did they ruin it? They could have the infernal heirs of the zoos
Yeah, all those greek gods zeus athena tiny tim's great thirst for riches
All right. Well, I got my I got what I wanted
tiny tímacus
They added the ninja turtles. Yeah, I know
Like we we already talked about it. I've already very upset about it
I got a backstab to do more damage
Why even deflect they have a little shield who cares just smash them
You're gonna do a bake state
There it is 93 damage pretty good
I like this game. I think i'm pretty good too. I think i'm pretty good
I think i'm pretty good
You can always tell right?
In a game where I don't know what the fuck's going on i'm really bad
I usually would be just walking around getting hit by random projectiles going. Hey, wait, what did this one do?
Gain a hundred points
you can
dash over
I missed it. Somebody says something important
All right, so I don't I don't have a key
What was my key list? I can either get purple currency or go key
Dash over what you can dash over gaps. Oh, can I fall in gaps?
You cannot fall in gaps. Thank god
Um, let's stay consistent. I want the purple stuff numbskulls
That's what they're called
numbskulls
Just smash everything
I'm gonna have to drink a little bit more coffee for this game. I thought this was a family friendly stream. It is
Your family is just psycho
You know, I will say here's an automatic plus one letter grade. Um, hold on. Don't stop stop stop talking
Hold on. Stop talking. I could pick this back up. I didn't know I could do that
Oh my god, why did I look at chat? That was stupid. Okay. Uh, this gets automatically plus one letter grade
because
Uh, it telegraphs
Where the enemy is going to come up next in the spawn and it's there for a full second or so
Absolute plus one letter grade
I'm gonna die
that's
Uh, well, how can I get health shot probably right?
Yeah, you can talk
good
Ooh
How much do I have?
All right, what heals more the food?
All right. Hold on. I'm having a little bit of trouble understanding
Oh, this is max health. I was wondering why 25. I was like, why is this so much more expensive? Okay
That's max health
I get it. And then this is a super upgrade
I don't have enough money for the super upgrade
Please drink a sprite on stream
The prince's reckoning no, I don't want to do I only drink sprites on airplanes and I can reckon quite a bit
All right. I'm good
Ginger ale or pineapple juice. Well, this is awkward. Oh
boss fight
Omega lull it's oh mega mega
All zagris not one step further. This is this character is not in smite. I don't know who this is
that's the problem zagris and
Omega mega are not in smite. So I don't know they don't be may as well not exist
Besides don't you have someplace else to be your father sent me i'll be on your bad side than his
You can turn back and a education or I can send you home the painful way
No, the true twitch education here would be
Hey, give me a tier list. I'm gonna do a tier list of the greek and roman gods
Oh, this is a fight. All right. I'm ready
three two one
go
Oh that hurt you get to summon guys. That's not fair
Where is she? Where is she? What's she doing?
I'm gonna die. I'm dead
You fucking asshole
i'm dead
Okay, so i'm gonna be i'm gonna be very very clear
I lost that because I was so trying so hard to not say I have to treat this like
I was concentrating on not saying a sentence versus playing the game
Yeah, it's scripted anyways, it's supposed to it's scripted look you're supposed to die
Some of us more than others
Probably me
Some of us more than other streamers
Like the 180 attempts I had at cuphead
See if I come close this time
What's this stupid boy? Oh there is I told you nobody gets out of here
Transacking of my domain. I know viewers are leaving is bugleberry
Greetings father father was a delight. Thank you for asking
So i'll just be on my way again
What do I care
You shall never reach the surface
go
Seek yourself
at the dog
There's a good boy. Of course, you can pet the dog in hades
Yeah, that's servers
Oh, we're gonna have to fight this dog later. That's the ultimate
trail
Okay, so who are these people?
Oh, I know her I know nix and maybe she has the candle and smite
Believe it nix grateful that you put us into contact. I know you took a considerable risk in reaching out
The risk is not to me
I expected the olympians would involve themselves in this any junk.com game reveal to them no more than they already know
The hell are you talking about we understood
Yes, we are then go you need to address horny chat, you know
Can I gotta make a statement here? Can I just say I don't know what happened
I think it was since the great ass revealing
You guys are
I'd say like plus 40 percent hornier than like a year ago. Is that what happened?
What what's going on here?
Watch dog servers regards the underworld with mixed emotions. Stop saying that it's november purest joy
Oh, well deepest melancholy
I'm not i'm not gonna even respond to that you watch over things for me. Won't you boy? I'd take you if I could no
non-stop
Something something in this month
That's fucking ridiculous returned
Who are all these people?
Achilles
You're training out there. That's this is the reason why your your heel is named after this guy
Because he had a he had a bad foot and during one of the wars
He like twisted his ankle and it got like it's like stopped on or something. That's wrong. I just I have no idea
And fear is for the weak. Take care achilles. He was random ghosts. You should play smite
You know if I I would play smite on stream if it wasn't guaranteed
I'd get like 10 viewership and 100 embarrassment
House of hades appointed layer of the underworld's king
Is home not just to him
But to his willful protony
Oh, so these are all my trinkets
You know, I can hear you old man. Oh relax. Well, you can just relax as comfy as it looks
Oh, why not? That's
pissing me off
Okay, cool
So what does this person do is this do I is this a is there like permanent upgrades?
It is a roguelike
There are no permanent upgrades there are
Oh, I didn't say I didn't make any reference. Hey room. Hey room use the mirror to grow stronger
Oh, man
That's what the clash of clans
Ten dollars for a hundred gems is for
Deal bonus attack and special damage when striking foes from behind per rank unlock talents
Oh, this is never-ending i'm gonna be so happy about this
Restore a small amount of health when you exit a chamber one health. That's not good
Restore 50 percent
Instead of dying when your life is depleted. Why would you not do this immediately?
Oh because the next rank is 500. Okay
I'm probably gonna say this one. No
there's
Yeah
10 more damage and special damage from behind
He fucked it up. Why don't I fuck it up already? So that's why yeah
You're not supposed to just beat it quickly in one go. You just you gotta get better and get stronger
Despite his lord house repeatedly insisting that he pick everything up speed run speed run
Why does every character in this game talk like the new castlevania netflix series
Where if you don't have subtitles, you can't understand a fucking word anybody's saying
Oh what what happened rewind that and put subtitles on
That's pretty morbid dude, you're painfully american
No, i'm it's like the audio too like the volume of the speaking is too low
It'll be like they'll be like riding on a carriage and talking and the carriage is like
I can escape through that pink window there. Well, what's all this need more keys? Oh, this is new weapons
This is a new starting weapon
What the fuck is all this stuff?
Okay, this is a law here
Used to unlock a weapon. What is this weapon? I'm doing it. There we go. It's a
Heartseeker let's deal something
Cool all too wait
Oh shit, sorry nice place. You got your boy. Oh named skelly has it going but enough with the smart talk already
I'm here to do a job. So let me have it. Give me everything you got
Okay
payroll mate
Who's your supervisor sans no, not every single skeleton is one of those two
Just try and beat it out of me. Okay, so let's see
so
press fire volley
It's a spread
That's awesome. Okay
Can I just shoot normally? No, you have to you have to hold it so release while flashing for a power shot
So it has to be like that. Okay
You gotta time it
Now what's this other one dashing?
Need that again
I can dash to one
What'd it say dash plus attack?
like together
Oh, you can like slide into it
Dash attack is faster charge. Is it?
Oh it kind of is you're just gonna soft walk the game by killing the skeleton
Like
All right. That's pretty good. I like this. I'm gonna try it. Uh
Nico cat gave 50 dollars right now. Thanks for the 50
Fucking dollars. I say stop saying swears. There's your children watching
Uh, they say germa since you've watched the castlevania show. Do you think you would ever play castlevania on stream?
Maybe symphony of the night
Oh
I don't know
Maybe one day. Wait, did I miss anything over here? Is there anything cool I can do here? Just look
I can do this. Oh figure something out. No, I don't don't don't no
No, I'm no turning back. I don't know. I never was a big fan of castlevania
under is this really him?
Okay, oh zeus in the name of hades olympus. I accept this message
So what can I do? I get an upgrade, right?
Your father's always been rather difficult and he's not so much as cold than quite some time santa
Thunder
Ooh, we got a blessing thunder your special causes a lightning bolt to strike nearby foes. Uh, yeah
chain lightning that bounces between people
Or your dash causes a lightning bolt to strike nearby foes. I think I want this one
Is it that replaces the thing I had before?
That's why right
I love the ball already like i'm gonna i'm only gonna use the ball. I'm not gonna use another weapon for the rest again
So wait, isn't that supposed to do your special cause is a bolt to strike nearby foes the blade it's it
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Did I fucking ruin that?
I messed that up
This lore over there. I have what did okay. Look hades
Is in the underworld aries like
fights back against his parents
Hades i'm fighting against my parents all the zeus's kids. Oh
Oh, what's his name? Not not not omega. Um
Odin all the kids fight against odin. Oh, it's sons versus their parents daughters versus their parents and all these greek and
Roman games and like norse it doesn't matter. It's just the sons versus the parents
Look, i'll i'll spell it out even better for a lot of you zoomers in the chat here
Okay, so imagine a youtube thumbnail with a red green and blue sectioned off area
And uh zeus
No, sorry odin loki and thor are doing a colored food challenge video
Where they have to eat only one color of food?
Those videos are insane. That's like the youtube children's content
And it's it's weird as hell a lot of these videos they narrate over them themselves talking
The characters the people in the videos don't talk
They're narrated over pretending to talk and they all just eat like green foods in like every fucking video
It's just oh, we're only gonna eat blue foods today
It's every video people think i'm crazy right now and everyone's like what are you talking about?
Oh, yeah, some of you know what i'm talking about
Jesse, what are you talking about? Some of you guys know some of you guys know like the red green blue thumbnail and you're just like
Oh, it's one of these
Yeah, well, how would I know that because you know, I gotta I gotta assess the competition
You know, what's what are people doing on youtube now? I gotta like see what what I'm gonna see what i'm up against
That room was pretty good use your special and look at the damage
The same audience. No, it's not the same audience. You guys aren't six
50 damage that wasn't that much
40 that's pretty good
Holy shit, that's really good
That's so good. I'll tell you I probably would rather have the controller or uh the
um
Oh, but it's okay
Your special is the volley. Oh, so what is this one then?
What what is that?
All right. I have not been in the trident room before it's a cast
Is aim assist on pc2?
Oh, well, I probably turn it off
This move is so good. Why even use any other move?
It's a trident. It's uncle number two. It's got to be then in the name of hades don't use other moves. I accept this message
Don't use any moves
ever
It's me
Every single god has ever been recorded
Nobody knows what the fuck we actually sounded like we actually may have sounded like this
Boy, they're hades you recognize your uncle. Do you not?
We've a lot of catching up to do but first things first you get yourself out of that door underworld as for me
I'll see if I can stir things up a bit to cover your advance
Don't forget the echo
But I like it's just so it's so simple of a big strong
Character that has the control the waves and shit. Of course, they're gonna sound like that
But we don't know
gain a random assortment of
of jewels
Hmm. I think I want this way whether your attack deals more damage and knocks foes away. That's good for the bow
Your attack is special is stronger the first 10 seconds in an encounter
You do 50 more damage for 10 seconds when you go in a room
I mean, that's good, but I kind of want to random like pull the slot machine
Holy shit
See you should be of help. I got five jewels
I got one
Should I get this too tonic? I got a snack. I got another five jewels
Okay, there's more currency. All right, I got it. All right, i'm gonna go in the key room because
I want a key
What are you aiming at dude?
What the hell is he doing?
Whoa, okay. We're good. Now you're gonna lose
I don't think i'm gonna lose
What's the range on this?
Key this can unlock something back up. This is a boss
That's what it means right this boss there. Wait
It might be treasures. How can I break that drink out of the cauldron drink out of the cauldron?
Drink out of the cauldron. Where's the drink out of this?
Let's see what's in. Whoa gain 29
points for health
No
That's nothing
You deal 50 damage striking undamaged foes
for six rooms
Gain one
Okay, so I get an extra special
Probably this one
Yeah, i'm taking that one for six rooms. That's kind of cool
All right, let's go
Doomstone
Doomstone watch it
Whoa
Give me way
You gotta break these fucking things. That's how they bounce
Oh bunch him up bunch him up
Get out of here didn't even take one fucking hit
Less giant evil crystal then I did actually right here. I did took two damage. That's pretty good
Wait gift minus one
Why am I gonna lose my uh potion? I don't get it
Don't give it
Look, what does that do?
You give it to zeus. Okay, but what does it do though? Should I do it and see what happens? Don't do it
You don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. It's the dating sim
Well, do I want to date zeus or do I want to date Poseidon?
There are more than two characters
Okay
Like why am I going do I would I rather date zeus or Poseidon zeus and Poseidon are both sitting in their living room watching this
From the clouds and they're both going uh, dude
Like what is he talking about like he thinks he's gonna just like date one of us
Is that what he thinks he's doing down here? Um, so I wish one of us should go down there and tell him
I'm gonna save it
Holy shit, that's pretty good. All right
Do I date zeus or do I date Poseidon which one? Uh
There's lots of single people in the world of valhalla
None of us have been married for 4000 years, dude. I don't like that. I like this one. I like this one
Wrong valhalla, whatever, you know, but it's heaven and what they're all it's just heaven
heaven
Lost souls with nowhere left wrong religion. It's not a religion
Into odious forms which defy description
It is no, it's not what do you think it is?
It was a thing that they were these real people
I'm kidding. I'm fucking kidding. Relax
I'm kidding. All right. Let me play my game please before everybody yells at me
I'm liking the lightning. I should have dated zeus
Stop saying that
The bow is so much fun
I've ruined the game for myself
Because i'm not why would I put somebody said i'll get the spear. No, why why would I ever?
Oh shit
Too much fun game ruined. All right. I got four more encounters with 50 more damage to foes
Break everything
All right, somebody in chat, please correct me. Is this a break everything game?
Could there be something in there or is this a waste of time?
No, no, not even okay. It may maybe eventually. Okay
Some jars have money. All right, who's that?
I don't have to deflect on my dash anymore
Anymore, here we go
Oh, what am I thinking turn off auto aim it sucks
All right, I will
I feel like it's helping me a little bit though. I really do
Shit, hold on because see how it's like automatically going right at some people sometimes
But other times it doesn't
Sucks turn it off. I can't turn it off right now. Oh, yeah again
Aim assist turn it back on turn it back on not good. It's not good. Not good
Omega l you suck. No, it's a controller aim. Don't you get it? Don't you understand?
Oh what there's a reward in here? Oh
plus 12
Using mouse. No, but I like moving around. That's this is the worst thing
You know what I need. This is what I need. I seriously need this
I'm dead serious about this. I'm willing to put forth the effort to make this happen. I
Like to move around in games with the thumb and the controller and I love the face buttons to do everything
I don't like WASD and moving around that way, but the mouse is so much better to aim
I love the mouse more than I like aiming with an analog or most people do
So here's the solution that I have if I get an eye tracker
Can I use my eyes as the mouse and use my controller as the keyboard?
You know what I'm saying?
So then I can I could get best of both worlds
So my eyes with an eye tracker actually are the mouse and I can still move around with the thumb pad and use the face buttons
That wouldn't work, but it would be so much better
What about tunnel vision?
What's this?
Trespasser revive for 45 seconds
Okay. Oh, that's not good
Didn't want to take damage there stupid. Oh don't get stuck in the corner
Oh
Now to collect what's that?
This is uh, oh, this is aphrodite. I'm a mess. Let's see here in the name of hades. I love this. I accept this message
Little god thing
I have to say you're quite the specimen and so i've decided I shall aid you for the moment
You interested chat close your eyes?
Brush shot your cast is a wide short range blast that inflicts weak
ooh
After you take damage damage foes around you and inflict weak
The week just makes them deal less damage. Okay, that's cool
Or any upgrade to your health rewards are worth more
Oh
That's pretty good
That's really good. I want that one
and the power to break hearts
Sure, I don't see why not
So unfortunately, oh I have 320 gold
Wait, this is actually like somebody has a real
A paragraph of information here as someone who owns a thrust master
And has it set up in left-handed mode using a joystick and a mouse at the same time really depends on the game
Sometimes games just won't use a joystick and keyboard. Wait, is that a real thing?
I feel like this is like a meme and you just talked about like I just that's like a zirconov thing
I mean, it's called it's called the thrust master
It's a stick
No, it's not the throw. Okay
I own a thrust master t one six thousand m
And it's in left-handed mode
Okay
That's what it's called. I thought I really didn't want to read the rest of the message
It's a flight stick
Oh
It's real. Okay. All right
It depends on the game though. Okay
Well, I got enough money to do
All right, maybe I should just buy wait you have something to say yeah, I can give him something
Does this reduce the prices or something?
If I gift him this
Will it drop the prices by like 10% or something?
Hey good to see you out here mate. Looks as though you've got some fine ways for sale. Don't you?
boatman
Mate
All right, so we're definitely gonna get
50 60 70 that's only 20. All right, let's do a power up or zeus's grace
I think I can do all of them. I'll take it
Okay, your dash causes a lightning bolt to strike nearby foes boring your lightning effects also make foes jolted
Victims next attack self inflicts lightning damage. That's 60 damage
Your lightning bolt effects deal damage in a larger area 60 more area
Yeah, definitely jolted
Shocking and i'm gonna i'll get a ball. I'm gonna get the pomegranate
Cool. All right your attack if it's a chained lightning level two
Your special causes a lightning bolt to strike nearby foes. Ooh
That's level two of this one
Oh shit, they're already jolted
three
What that's gonna do 100 damage when they attack?
And i'm gonna eat this too. I want full health
Okay, i'm ready
Give it to him. I don't want to give him the gift. I don't want to do it. Give it to him. I don't want to
Give it. I don't want to
Oh, I know who that is
That's hercules
Hey prince said must look like i'm slacking off with the old bull. I was gonna say hercules or quasi moto
Is quasi moto greek god don't often leave me be where'd they go? What are you doing here?
He was a greek. Well, okay. Was he at least a greek citizen?
No
Was he roman? Was he a roman citizen? He was french. He was french. Oh, never mind
It wasn't like a whatever
Okay, so he's got this uh
Big boulder. Oh, you know just add on a little stroll as all do me a favor though
You see the fury sisters. Let them know I was headed down the way I came from will you
Oh, i'll let them know. All right. I hear you loud and clear that michael cain. I'll just go about my business now and you take care
Your will highness just take care. I'll make sure go about my business now and you master rank you take care
Oh
Your life total is lose it all for an express trip to the house of hades
What?
This is I just die and I go back to the house of hades
Used to permanently grow stronger
purchasing items during
price of benefits
Okay
Stop stop reading so hard
I thought if I pressed this it was like oh your life total is 75 out of 75
Lose it all for an express trip back to the house of hades. I'm giving it to you
He's going to get his rear back and blast me in the face
Okay, so this is just what he's going to so I want healing then
Purchasing items during an attempt all the lost on death. All right, so don't I want that out, but I have upgrades
All right, take this one
You want this should I give this thing to him?
There's a shop right here
Why is he why they're doing like chat faces?
Did I just say something that like really made a bunch of people uncomfortable
You bought something that made us uncomfortable. All right. Here we go
Take a look at this bingo
This is a boss fight. All right, i'm ready for this one this time and see if I can do it
What the fuck up oculus commercial i'm trying to watch germa
Yeah, a lot of those oculus commercials they move around you see how they move around those commercials like super fluid and like tons of movement
They should really make a realistic commercial
How much more would you think it was interesting for like an oculus
If that person was like doing the moves and like dancing around and stuff and they smashed into their walls and into like a shelf
And stuff like a bunch of times in the commercial that'd be fucking hilarious
All right, everybody
All right. I'm gonna beat this lady
Okay, let's go meg
Maybe my whip might make you reconsider whatever it is
I had to look over to make sure family guy wasn't on this list. You really blew it
Yeah, shut up meg
I can do it. It's not on that list
All right, i'm ready i'm gonna i'm gonna be quiet and i'm gonna beat this person three two one go
I don't think so. Oh
Oh, come on where'd you come from
What does that mean
Where is she? Oh
What's that? Oh my shit
I gotta kill these guys
What no
Fury vanquished
Five subs god damn it. Hey up, just keep track keep track of it. I'll do it later. What is this?
Come on, why?
why
height and blood why
No
You need to have mods for a chat this big. There are mods here
What is this i'm so pissed off that I did that i'm just a parrot I hear it
I just and it just pops into my head and I have to say it aloud. I i'm gonna lose every time
This is exactly what i'm talking about
You nailed it. You absolutely nailed it, but you put no question marks. You fucked it up. You fucked it up
You gotta write
On there you have to write on there and it's 10.01. Perfect. Take the question marks off and say
epic like epic dad versus mom
Food eating challenge and I gotta tell you this too
When they eat the broccoli and the vegetables they puke and stuff
What are they teaching our children? The blue candy and the red candy is delicious. Yeah, eat it
Eat it every day they eat the whole bottle but once it once it gets to the broccoli it's like
Like what the hell is going on
I don't understand like the primary colors shit
Why is every one of these videos blue green red and yellow?
And they all play the same sound effects, too. They play like
Every five seconds
There's like mutating our children's brains. I love the fact that you've watched them. Of course I have
It's always primary colors. It's always like half the room is like green half the room is like orange
Just sit your kids in front of sesame street, please
Do not sit them in front of like the bath salt fucking youtube kids channels
Oh, how did you sit them in front of this stream? Do not do that either
I am worse than the primary color kids channels in a circle of chambers connects to barge in anyway
Make a lot of moolah
Please
Um, I have to say this because it's a failed german 985 experiment that I was gonna do years ago and I told
One person about it years ago
While I was just streaming I wasn't gonna say anything about it
I was going to make a kids youtube channel and make just awesome incredibly good
Like wholesome children's content on youtube on a new channel
And I was gonna do it for like a year and I wasn't gonna I was gonna wait till somebody found it
I was gonna try you know, like the slime joke
I'm gonna see if I can get slime to be more popular than me
My goal was to have like a billion view a day kids youtube channel. That was good shit
We're talking like puppets and and counting and and geography and bringing that back bring it
I'm bringing the puppet. I want to bring the puppets back. It would be there would be
Only a few cookies eaten every video, right?
It wouldn't be like squeeze the sugar into your mouth like half of these fucking shows
We would sing songs about like broccoli, but they would be good. They would be good fucking songs
It wouldn't be shitty
I was gonna try to be like a billion view a day youtube kids channel and see if anybody found it
You thought quasimodo was a was greek. That's why you hire people to be able to I what I you you hire like
People to come in like educators you bring in educators and they hey
What's a good lesson plan that we could do if we could have some fun characters do fun cool shit, right?
I want cool shit bring in a bunch of like teachers
Guidance counselors like all of them. Sesame street does that too. That's right, but I want to do it as well
Oh, wait, what's this? Is it free? Is this just for free?
Is this is this like the bread at outback steakhouse? Am I gonna get charged for this?
Okay, good. I don't want to
I'm also by the way implying that you don't get charged for the bread at outback steakhouse not that you do
sell sell
Oh
Oh, I can sell all the things I have on me. I don't want to sell
How do I go back shop?
Oh, I don't have any money
Bye. Bye. Bye
At this time of come oh
Going up the tower that wing is a weak choice. So this is area too. How many areas are in the don't tell me
I can't believe I did the fucking gnome reference
What the hell wasn't this whole expanse once lush and green I was so confident too
I was like this is so easy to not do the once verdant plains of asphodel are now engulfed in scintillating flame
Having been flooded by the river flaggathon
Whose hideously superheated contents could bring death swiftly even to those resistant to most eat
I'm gonna die to lava a hundred percent only flame resistant pump flame proof. I mean new contract. I want a new one
I die to lava then I have to go
one community sub
But if I don't die to lava for the next hour, I shave a hundred million off the debt
No deal. Okay fine
a hundred subs no way
All right. What what is this?
This is locked. Oh, this is a new hub world. Here's one of these
But the lava though this guy shoots love at you. Oh, you can't hit him
slam dancers
Slam dancers
Not as strong as I was before that's for sure
They slam and they dance. Well, that was bad. Don't get near me. Oh shit. That's
Oh, I see why you can die to lava. Okay, you can you can actually fall in that lava. Oh shit
I'm not doing any damage. I need a new weapon or something. I need like a new weapon
I need like a you need a new weapon not like a new weapon
God, you're supposed to be teaching children soon get your vocabulary higher
Oh, that was 41 bucks
Soon
Oh nice another hundred
So these are open now. All right. Do I want the key or do I wait? I don't want the key
I want the extra to go
Oi
Why can you fall off like that?
um, okay
Burn fingers
slam dancers
What else we got?
Finger lickers
I gotta go across
KFC. Oh shit. This is a new enemy. What is it? Nice
On my authority belly itchers
Do I want the shop? I don't think I have enough money for anything. Do I I guess I kind of do
These are hobbit last names
Sort of all right. Do I want Poseidon or do I want power up?
I know searing flame and ashes of the river flaggathon mean nothing to the ferryman keron
Who travels all the waters of the underworld want the fruit the dead you want Poseidon and all their fineries
You want uncle?
I do enjoy dead people's final race. Sure. I'll get i'll take the uncle power up
Don't spend it all in one place
Tell me little nephew strewn among the inventories of their most disturbing river boatman. That means you win my blessing
Oh
Wait, why would I no give me this?
Yes, make some waves
I got another gift too. Perfect. I have two gifts and I have a ton of that currency and i'm gonna get even more of that
Currency, let's go. I'll pay for that hundred currency now
And I can buy the power up too
Kind of have to do that
121 damage every time they attack I have to I can give the gift now
I'm gonna I'm gonna see what it does
Here take it
What does it do?
Here on you've been such a reassuring sight. I thought I'd offer you a token of my gratitude. I have another one
Wait, you don't have to give me something in return. It was a gift. Oh wait a gift. You're insisting aren't you?
That's one hell. I don't know what to say mate
this
worthless one health
It's a keepsake. Oh
Keepsakes not gonna keep me alive. It was a bone hourglass
What the fuck i'm so stupid. I was looking at chat and I see it. Oh, it's okay. Let's go
You're ungrateful ungrateful little shit
All right, come on jolt him that I didn't know exploded
Jolt him nice
Oh
Don't god damn it. I don't like the lava place. It's too hard to die. It's too easy to die
Get away from me
Asphodel is easy to die in. Yeah
Oh, we're up to eat
Oh jolt
Jolt jolt jolt jolt
Jolt build
We're doing a joke build jolt build joke build
Okay, instant restore 36 health. I think i'm gonna get that you deal 50 damage to armor
Pretty good
Your special deals 40 more damage
I don't even use the special feel like it sucks
i'm taking the help
I'll take this one special is good
Any build you make is a joke build
Oh, i'm in
i'm in asphodel so
Got me this far
Special is y. Oh, what is b?
What is that gem the weird like gem that I throw out?
What is the uh, the your sim has zero in every category icon?
What does it do?
It just gets cast. Okay
Well, that's actually really great then
Use it
Yeah, see but it okay
It just shoots out this little blob that does 50 damage and it takes a lot. Do you have to aim it?
I gotta pee
You need an augment you have to upgrade it. Okay
That's a problem. I can't oh shit. Okay, I can't destroy those
Get away from me
Thank god. I didn't just say the thing I was gonna say
Oh
Watch it watch out
I need to slow. I just shut up. It's not that big of a deal. You touched the lava once
Cool until next time gigantic gorgon head olympus. I accept this message. Come on zeus
This one's rare
Finally, I have a new cast your cast is a chain
lightning
After you take damage your foe is struck by lightning. Uh
Your dash causes a lightning bolt. This is good, too
But again, I actually get a cast
Yeah, give me a cast. Let me see what the hell it even does
Yeah. All right. Cool. I actually have a move now
Shit, you gotta get it to hit to prog
proc
I mean, it's not that great. I do that much damage by just shooting somebody once
Anybody else feel like he's saying things that I say but way more collected way more cool
Really? You want to go?
He's just way more interesting. He's way more soft spoken than I am
I actually get hit by that
He's hotter than you
Okay
Oh no
What do I do?
This guy's hotter than me
I have so much of this currency. I'm gonna be a level up 10 times
Wait, what else is there?
Ooh. All right. Do I want no, I don't have enough money. Let's get the uh pomegranate
Okay, I have a feeling i'm probably not gonna beat the boss because i'm feeling i'm not doing as much damage as I should be
Why does this look so easy to take this?
Being traversed the flaming river flaggathon to gain this vantage point relentless sagrious must now confront a foe of unimaginable savagery
Who lies ahead?
Awaiting patiently. It's time to strike
All right. I'm clicking it
This is hades
not hades
Wrong link how?
As i'm being spammed
It took me a second to
uh
Let me get this one out ancient tablet
I love how uh cnn politics is still a thing
A thousand years from now apparently wait to spoil the surprise old man. God's grant me strength
I have to do it. I don't even care what the other ones are. I want this. I want to get this to 200 damage
He doesn't get it
No, wait, so that's not supposed to be like I that's lore about me like a thousand years in the future
Like that's been buried. That's like an old tablet of like the great assening great like ass revealing
Great ascending the great ascending
Uh, this is a new room. It's a boss too. All right, I gotta I gotta wipe my hands
Chat doesn't get it. Well, I mean, yeah, I get it
I get it. I get it
You're thinking too hard
All right
All right, here we go. Hello. It's a snake
Great. Let's take a look. Hold on. Don't just let's just see what he does first
All right, he's he shoots things you can use this to block and I dash through them. I can
It's not that big of a deal. Just relax
Plus we have like thorns on him
Make sure I gotta keep this on him because they'll hurt himself every time and this is this guy's a joke
Oh phase two. Oh, well, never mind. I spoke too soon
Just dodge and jolt
Just dodge and jolt. That's the that's the build I have so make it work
Really?
Make it work
All right
Get him
Whoa, that's different
Oh you fucking controller aim dog. Shit
I gotta use that to my advantage
Shit
Here we go
Same deal. Just dodge dodge dodge make it happen
Holy shit
boy
All right. We're good. We're good. We're good
Get the fuck out of here. That's two
Oh huge ray just came in. Hold on rt game crowd with the with the monster raid. What's going on guys? Welcome
Hope you had a good stream
What was it doing today? The game's too easy. I took a lot of guts
planet coaster
Oh cool, is that game good still did they update it at all? Is it like fun?
Give me something. I remember I tried to get a gorilla to like
Punch people in the face to like climb out of the enclosure and kill people
Has it gone any different from there?
I've let it one time for like four hours, uh, but welcome guys. They're playing hades first time playing ever
First trying the second boss, which everyone told me guaranteed. He dies on the second boss
Sometimes you have to show them what you're capable of
Sing the raid song
They're leaving because you're not singing the raid song. No that they're they're sticking around until at least an hour from now
I can heal
I kind of is all right. Is it weird that I want to die?
So I can spend some of this currency
Sing or we're gonna leave
Thank you
for
Raid there. I thought it hurts. I'm sorry. I I was doing that way too close to the microphone
This is what happens when you make me sing and make me do this don't tell me to do that anymore
Don't tell me to do that anymore. That was pretty fun to say
He's clapping his ass. I'm just shaking really hard
All right 20. Yeah, give me that
Oops. Oh, yeah, get that
I have 140, uh
purple gems
Thanks to the raid rt deserves it the epic stream today
Yeah, of course he does. Everybody loves rt. Come on
Beatbox the pepsi man song. I don't even know what that is the fields of elysium
I got an achievement that just says I thought it said escape asshole
It's you escaped asafoel
I kind of want to die the rare heavenly splendors of elysium reserved for only the most great of mortal souls
Spread forth luxuriantly all about the fire-stepping prince
You escaped as a whole
Hey, how would you spell that asshole?
Uh, which one of these do I want?
Probably pomegranate. That's jolt though, right?
Jolt is pomegranate plus
Oh, I can't wait. You didn't hurt him that just bounced around like wow that hurt
Is that egg shooting me?
it is
Kill this thing
Can't why would I get close to a guy with a sword? That's what I want to know
Do you have to kill them before they go back to this sword?
Oh
I just walked right into that. I'm okay
Oh my fucking god. I these things stupid. I hate them. I want to die. Anyways, I seriously do
I have like a fucking hundred. I have like 200 gems to spend
He's throwing now. No, i'm not i'm not i have jolt six
I can't throw
Definitely the health is diminishing returns
That's doing anything
All right. All right. That was free. I guess
Am I stunning him somehow?
I'm stun locking. Oh, that's cool
Don't what are these bugs?
I think can these hurt me. I feel like these things can hurt you
Yeah, they can of course they can
Ow, all right. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Give me that extra health
Thanatos waiting room thanatos is in this game
Thanks for ruining the rest of the game for me
Poseidon or shop probably Poseidon great shields
Great shields you gotta hit him from behind
Don't worry. I got jolt on him
Yeah, if who cares just jolt him you actually just hit me with that. I'm fucking furious
dodged in a line
Kind of done. It's done. It's done. It's done. It's done
All right, get him
Don't let you do what you want to do
Oh that hurt. What are those? Oh, the spears hurt you on that side
You get it. Oh fuck you you did
Really?
No
All right. Come here. How am I not behind you?
Space plus m1 space plus m1 space plus m1 space plus m1 do I give the gift of Poseidon?
Oh, yes. Yes. Yes. No bugsnacks tier list waiting room. Does it exist? Maybe I'll do that some maybe I'll do that like tomorrow
Don't want it. Don't care. I accept this message
Okay, your attack and specialist stronger for 10 seconds. Yeah, I don't like the timer any
gem
darkness or
Obol award
Is worth way more. I mean, I don't have anything on my dash. I might as well get it
Yeah, it's good for the bow. We're good. All right, so this is um zeus
or
Something new a mirror a mirror
I don't I want to see who it is
Mini boss let's do it from the bowels of hell. This is not your place
Agreed on both counts just passing through so if you'll excuse me
I will not be such a contest neither will I I don't know why I think that's funny
Wait about the champion of elysium. You're the bull of minos. I can't imagine who's even stronger than you
Is it heracles? Tell me it's heracles
You just act did you say hercules wrong?
You talk to my destroyed come get destroyed. All right, let's go
Let me see what he does first
charges
What the fuck where do I go? All right, that's what I do
Hmm, holy shit, he's got a three combo
Where is he?
I'm good
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. What do you want me to say?
It's stressful
How would you go the wrong fucking way?
I'm sorry. I have to mute. I have to be and i'm not gonna stop doing that
What the fuck what the fuck it's me grandpa
I come out under extreme stressful scenario
Kind of like your what some of your favorite tv shows and movies
You know when the main character has like something else going on where like he turns into another person when he's under a lot of stress
like lucario
That's me
But I what he did he taunted. I don't know what the fuck that was. He taunted me
And he had like a shield on him. I thought he was gonna summon enemies
I thought he was gonna be like fight by minions and never I don't know
Whatever. I wanted to die anyways. I got 140 gold. It's rather hard
Dead
He just jumps and swings
I had it down for a little while
But when he started when he did the shielded taunt, I thought something else was gonna happen
Do not question my power hades
Your son was bound to be discovered the closer he came to the surface
The olympians are give to the dog. They have a distant relative thinking about it and bid him welcome to their mountain
That is all
Thinking about it very limited
I feel like that's too easy though. Do not speak to me about this. I've seen their evens firsthand done this mistake
Give it a skelly
You don't think about this to me of foolish mistakes
You cannot change the course that has been set
Try all you like
It's
The hell is this
I gotta let me pee i'll be right back
Uh, sorry, I did the thing you fill your cup with ice and the ice comes out way too fast
And four or five ice cubes just blow out all over you and go underneath the fridge
And you're just like I I don't want like five ice cubes under the fridge
So I went under there with like a straw and I was trying to get them all out. I got him
He's rich. He's got a rich fridge
What are you talking about isn't every refrigerator made after like 1995 have an ice maker in it
What wait what?
It's just it's just a regular fridge that has ice in it. I don't have a smart fridge
I don't want that thing listening to me
You know how many weird noises I make in the morning when I open the fridge
I open the door and my stomach and my body just makes sounds just like
I don't want that anyway. I don't want like fucking amazon to hear that
All right, let's pet I can I don't want no I feel like everybody does this
I want to give it to somebody else
But you just told them through twitch. Yes, that's true. That is true
Can I give it to hades?
No, what is this renovate?
Some sort of special offer for me my good shade what but I can upgrade the the hall
Brand opening deal the house contractor is offering this particular renovation for free
An otherwise inaccessible location to be found in the ever-shifting underworld
You're total you're okay. So wait restore some health amid the gloom
added chamber
You just get it for free authorized a fountain chamber in the depths of tartar. It sounds like an excellent idea
Oh, okay something from the fates
uh
Under so I can just essentially this is making
Chambers may contain an infernal trove
Okay an enhancement to some part or artifact of the ever-shifting underworld
list list list do list list what
Treasure chests worth more than more the faster you slay the foes guarding them
So wait, this is i'm putting things in
To i'm giving myself cooler things in the runs like treasures and
Upgrades and okay
Make the fates prophecies come to pass and be rewarded an object that unlocks something you could not do without it. It's pretty weird
text, okay
the quest list
Yes, you cannot do without it weird but cool no get the list
Isn't this the fated list of minor prophecies list of mercies that sounds somewhat exciting. I suppose. Okay, so I have ten more
What about this one?
So this is what you were talking about you said not now but later there'll be treasure chests
Switch keepsakes between underworld regions not worth it yet
Okay, so i'll do this one the ever-shifting chambers of the underworld ought to be a little lie of this
Cool, all right. So then what about these?
It's just this is just paintings and new drapes and new curtains and stuff
Head chambers. Yeah, this is just cool stuff
That's pretty cool. All right. So what's the quest?
Over half of the game's upgrade require pool scrying
Best go all the way now. Leave me be and don't think you're gonna be so lucky next we meet out there
Sis whatever whoever you are
All right, so how where how do I get the quests? What once was a small lounging area house of hades?
I skipped us destroyed the lounge again. Achilles is off duty
Or did this give the skeleton? Hold on
I'm just looking around see let us this
Oh, that's another way out
Sorry chat. I can't believe it. He's such an idiot. He missed he doesn't know where to go
Hey, that must be the fated list. Oh, there it is fated list of minor prophecies
thousand
gems
The son of the god of the dead shall someday break free from the realm in which he was born as a thousand gems
How how do I track that the son of the god of the dead shall someday? Okay, so wait, I need to meet
uh
The other gods I need I have ten kids
All right, this is just meeting other characters. This is unlocking moves and using them
Is unlocking all the weapons?
Okay, I just just play the game. All right, just play the game and eventually you'll get stuff get it got it
Here we go
All right
I got a lot of money perform one additional dash in quick succession. That's incredible
That's just bang bang
And this is just more damage when striking from behind
That's huge
Okay, uh, i'm gonna do this
Should I do this though? I can do that. How many times can I do this?
Okay, get if it was like five that'd be really good. All right, i'm doing it
I'm doing three I get three health every room and I have enough to do this once
So there you go
I have 20 more damage from behind and I heal three health every time I go in a new room and I can dash twice
It's just that changes everything that this actually changes everything
Skelly, all right skelly
Let's talk skelly. You look like you know your way around tartarus
Plant some of this ancient titan blood out there and I was looking to score some more
All right, you come to the right place regarding that there pal
Yeah, I kind of want to gift this guy there that can find his stuff
Once you get all the way through tartarus with one that's all the blood you're gonna get for the time being anyhow
I like his artwork
Am I supposed to keep track of which weapons i've earned these with then it's just how I feel like when I take the vr helmet off
There's always the invention of writing stuff down. You'll figure something out. All right, i'm gonna give you a gift skelly. Take it
For you mate thought you might get a kick out of this for me pal
Awful nice. You're just awful nice. But guess what? I got this for you
Tick fatalia in this stand it deals the deal
What is it?
plus one
lucky tooth
Check the display case
Got something new. Oh
Items from the well of charon have durations increased by plus four encounters. What's a well of charon?
Oh, that's the shop instead of six
It's 10 automatically restore up to 50 health when your life total is depleted. What?
Wait, don't I I want that I can only have one right?
Should help don't I already have one so that means I can die twice
I have two extra lives about that son, but why would I ever take this off for any reason?
All right, you know what? Let's go back to sword. Let's try it. You know, let's do it
You can charge it too, right?
The spear sucks. I don't even have enough keys. All right. This is gonna be a key run. Thanks for the extra life
I'm only gonna I want I want keys because I want whatever these are
Key run that was not of reference just because it's in another just because there are keys in other video games
I doubtless it's the died alice encounter hammer. Okay, your special hits a wider area and deals more damage
That's I like that
Your attack fire is a wave that pierces foes. It does okay. So it's like link at full health
I like that
Holy shit
um
Why would I that's 200 more damage and more
All right, so this is this is a key and lunge at people run
I was only doing 30 damage
Wait, I guess 200 of 15 is not that big of a deal
Wrong move isn't that's not thrust
Now that's thrust
Trust is the third hit. Okay commosed of such innumerable ever shifting interlocking chambers
The underworld is all but guarantees the dead shall there remain good thing i'm not dead this game's really good
I'm all right. I understand why i'm like a bandwagon streamer
I got nominated for game of the year and all of a sudden. Yeah, me too. I'm gonna play it
It's very good. It's very very good
So far hold on. I remember where we have a scale here
We have a like stock market line
right now
I will say this is
This is like an this is like an 89 right now. It's right there
Which it's still going up. We'll see
That does so much more damage if you hit people from behind too. Oh, yeah
Now there's no reason to sell yet. Why what do you mean sell? There's no why there's no reason to do that
I'm treating this like a bow and I can't here we go
Quick buy buy
All right
uh
Extra health or the mirror
I like health though. Oh, i'm drinking coffee new enemy
brimstones
What do they do?
All right. Hey, that's very slow. I got it
Very slow. It's dodgeable very dodgeable
It was two was that 270 damage?
That was a shitload
Well, sure then oh, it's
Going look you have got to get here with the rest of us already
We've been saving you a spot. Let me see what I can do make life a little sweeter for you in the meantime
All right, this is the person that I want to give all the gifts to your attack inflicts hangover hangover damage for every half second
nice
Your special inflicts hangover
Your cast lobs a large explosive that bursts into festive fog. So this is a stun. I kind of just want the hangover damage
For this one, that's five. How long does it last for four seconds? So that's five ten fifteen
That's 20 extra damage in two seconds things up around here. I like to get the big big big groups
You got the worst one omega lol worst one for you. Not for me
Worst one best one for me. You suck
They give you three options. I don't know how to correct. It's how you want to build your character
Uh, look at I wouldn't have killed that guy if I didn't have this one selected would I i'm so glad there's no
Mana or anything in this game?
Oh, that's good
The sword's good, too
What reference man? Oh, he says mana. Oh, okay
mana
Oh, oh, I thought that was beetle. I love the sound
Can I call pests?
Don't let him do that
Wow
Wow, I just almost got shocked by that. I was gonna kill by that. Wow. That was close
Wow, I almost got murdered there
All right boss and more gems. It's not a reference we're talking about. I didn't know it's not
How is me saying? Wow, I almost got killed. How's that a reference? I'm gonna get a gift. Oh shit
Here we go
Good, it works out pretty well
I love I love dots
Damage over time. That's not a reference to any particular video game
It's not a
That's a dungeons and dragons reference
All right, you're making me get hit stop
ooh
Passive traps deal 500 damage
That's ridiculous. I'll take the help
All right aphrodite or the shop aphrodite
Watch out
Take it slow. You don't have to go fast. What's the point of why do you have to go fast? You don't have to
nice
Oh, it's aphrodite
Poison stacks, oh well way better now than I know that
You're the only exception
Your cast is a wide short range blast and that's probably what i'm gonna take
ooh
10 damage across the board reduced
Is that better than having a cast that does 100 damage? Hey, but if I hit them with the cast
They do 30 less damage. Anyways, so this is 10 without doing anything. This is 30 and 100 damage
strength and beauty
ooh
Really short range
Yeah, it is isn't it?
It's okay
Look, here's what I can do. I can
I can go bang bang get in there blast get up and just watch the dots
It stacks it stacks it stacks
Ooh
That hurt
Oh shit, they're getting okay
I gotta I gotta get I gotta I gotta get in there and get rid of these too many too many way too many over here
I'll get cocky
That's a lot of greed, but it's worth it
All right, we're fine. Zeus
Lightning all right, and your attack emits chain lightning when you damage, right?
I really like that
But I feel like that's not as good when you don't have a bow still one. It's still better. It looks cool
Chain lightning is a is a shaman spell
Yes
Sure, but that's not I didn't reference that
Holy shit. This is really good
Jesus there's so many of these. All right. Well, i'm taking too much damage here. These dicks are just everywhere. Don't get stabbed. All right
We're gonna do nothing
dicks
Dicks every key run
dicks everywhere
I meant like these guys are dicks
just spawn camp
Spawn camp don't let you all these guys are gonna blow up
Wow
Shit too far away. Just tick them down. Just tick them down
Tick them down
You just got to get in there man. You just don't be so shy and just go don't be such a coward
You just got to get in just go just be good and just spawn camp right where they spawn just get in there
Stun them watch it. I want that
You dead
One word take one word every minute
I'll tell him capable of doing
Drop here. All right. What is this?
29 health we got a new we got a new link
Are you gonna apologize for that? Ayaya thing?
I
I don't get this
But maybe some of you do I don't get it. I don't get it. Thanks though
Is this this is the one you wanted
Okay
also, no
What is is it this one?
What's this? Okay
I'll expect one at four eleven two sixteen pounds. That's way smaller and way fatter than I am
Walled with a beard finished bug snacks on stream. I love that's a bullet point
We just want to make sure everyone knows he finished bug snacks on stream
That's some major
monumentally important piece of data
nemesis crest
Oh, I want to I want to save it read the ticker
Trimmer germa 95 has accumulated 2.49 billion dollars plus right? All right, we can go key run
That armor what the hell are you hitting me with what? Oh, I was so clean, too
All right. I gotta move around too many. Oh my god. I'm getting destroyed in here
Holy shit. This room sucks. This room was horrible
There's traps everywhere and this projectiles in every corner
This can unlock shit, that's too much damage. All right, not gonna get hit for a while
uh shop
Four keys and
extra super health
Strength of the centaurs. What do you want? Hey carol
If there happens to be something really horrible awaiting me beyond that door, then
Give me a sign. Won't you please stop hitting me over the head with a broom?
Oh wait, oh this boss time
I gotta get this ready. This is this guy this first boss. It's not a problem. Let's go
Cyberpunk is out. I didn't even know it came out again. Is it out? Oh my god
No, 3080 no ps5. No cyberpunk. I'm sure he'd welcome all this feedback. Let's let's kick this lady's ass
Holy shit, I just ate that
I haven't played with a sword the whole time
Been a while since I played with anything besides the sword
Die
All right, here we go. This is the weird part
All right, get her get her get her get her
Oh shit, what am I doing?
I'm not a sword user. It's very evident. Okay. Fuck you. You just spawned on me
Oh my god, i'm i'm not a sword user. I'm not a sword user. That's very clear
I'm terrible with melee
This lady was a was a cakewalk with the bow. I'll still do it. But holy shit. That was painful. Remember just do coke
Oh, uh, no
Oh you don't
Okay, that's that was way harder with melee. I'm a bow guy
Got you told some sort of power but for what I always use the bows in games
Melee is for suckers. Imagine be able to hurt things from 500 feet away
Other than walk one feet away and try to hurt somebody. I mean, come on. How would you know?
Why would you ever use anything else of honor?
You know, what's really really honorable?
And really hard to do is to shoot somebody with a bow from a half mile away
That's not honorable at all. That's is it what is honor keepsake collection just with the house contractor
That's incredibly dishonorable
Shooting somebody from a half a mile away versus facing them one on one
I think that's the definition of dishonor
Can I read this thing? I don't need these they dishonored on stream
No, I already did
Didn't I play dishonored either in a youtube video or already did it?
Even as its dangers lie in wait by the shield. Yeah, this is a key run. I want to unlock the other weapons
Wait, hold on. Somebody has something important jerma, please read you chose dog shit boons
Zeus boons are great for synergies with cast and dash
Aphrodite and aries are great attack boons and dianesis
Has an insane cast boon you'll learn more synergies, but please stop talking taking shit boons dash modifiers are actually really good
Especially zeus. I've been playing the game for like an hour like two hours. I don't even know who aries is
I don't have 4 000 hours in the game yet
I haven't even unlocked all the gods yet
Closer to the surface
I didn't even know aries was in this game until you just told me the asphodel meadows
Within the suffocating heat of asphodel reside the vast majority. It's literally greek myth on the earth and died
I know there they persist until the end nobody's gonna get banned for trying to give me advice. Okay, please relax
Or I will strike you down chat. I will do sub only
20 minute time to talk
Crush the bones to dust
All right, I want maybe no
You're a key here. See you later alligator skull cry. All right, I gotta play
land
That was pretty good chain
That was pretty good chain. I'll go in the lava and chase them. What are you doing?
This game is outdated play something dude. Did this come out like four months ago?
It came out this year
Saints row two waiting room. It's outdated
uh
Popping granite play something fun for once this game is fun
Some of you guys mad that's got nominated for game of the year or something. I can't reach
Come over. I don't want to go in the lava to fight you
Wow, they have explosives
Did I get hurt that hurt me?
Oh, no, I got art. I got art
No, not I didn't say anything after hurt
You want me to say a particular rock after that, don't you?
That's heat. Okay
Double that's chain lighting too
Or more hangover. I think I want more hangover. Okay, we got shop or
gems with a fight
Each character gives you a trinket on their first gift. So give a gift to everybody. I will definitely what the fuck Jesus
Okay, these guys are a lot different. That guy has my thing. Hold on
I all right. We're good
Oh shit, oh shit
Drive my thing. I don't who has it
Gemstones ten of them. That's a lot of the house
Remember, this is your sister ever since that lego star wars stream. My kid's been asking me what the what the word fuck means
Uh, and I can't explain it to them. They love their uncle. Whatever
I don't want to eat one of them. Okay, so
This is new that's Artemis and wait, is that a new god?
We're should do the quest you should go to fart of us singing I agree what?
Uh, oh, it's a new god
Okay, the god of chefs could dash clear through that wall. I think
Hey, you must be the hades kid. You're a dice. How's it going then your royal majesty
Nice to meet you. I'm Eurydice
What brings a big important guy like you?
Instantly corrected
Hi, Eurydice
Uh every to see hi gonna nice to meet you. Good to see you again. No need for formalities
I'm zagreus just heading out on some official business past the menacing bone hydra. Don't mean to be rude
And i'm just curious. Does uh, does that does that come with jalapenos?
Yes, it does it comes with jalapenos
But there's one rule in my place gift which is
Nobody leaves here empty-handed you got that
So take your pick
my treat
Is that cassadelicum with jalapenos?
All right. Let's see
Up to two random boons of yours are upgraded to the next rarity. That's pretty awesome
Or random boons of your of yours gain level one plus one level
Isn't the part which is better?
A rare and fragrant beverage the next three boons you find have upgraded rarity. Uh, yes that one
Sure here. Thanks so much. Can I eat some of this?
Like can I give a gift?
This is not like, uh, some of those games
Where you can some of those games that exist where there's fighting of non-playable characters
and
Didn't say it. I didn't say it
See you see you
Like say like oh, yeah, like you can fight characters that are non-playable. All right, this is boss fight
Stack the fuck out of this. What am I doing? Oh wait, you could hit that you can hurt yourself that for real
yourself
die
Hey, I have a feeling i'm gonna lose really badly to the dragon thing. Here we go. Wait your hangover effects also make those slower
Your dash causes a hangover several times near where you started
That's that third one's not very good
22 slower move speed. That's really good. But this is good, too
They're all pretty good. But this one is you get max health
when you pick up
any gift
Every time this one hold on your dash causes a hangover several times
Near where so it's gonna stack. I want this one. That's one two three
Or eight twelve. That's twelve. That's like 50 damage
So you go in so you oh, yeah, this is gonna be good. So here you go. You go you get in stop drop, right?
Holy shit. Yeah, do you do double tap, right?
So you get in there you do why double tap and they'll go
Get in smash double tap. I feel like that's gonna be good
Somebody will always be hung over here dracons. Holy shit. That's really good. Yeah
That's gonna be good
I'm just gonna be a this is a coward run
Yeah, this is a coward run
Yeah, this is absolute coward run
Just stack it
still alive
Get out of here
Two two two two two
Did I already give uh zeus a gift? I don't think I did did I?
Not yet, right lord zeus. Um uncle, please accept this offering and all my gratitude
That's the flash
Offering indeed. Oh i'm thankful for your piety to me and as a show of generosity to you in turn I present this
He took an honorable weapon and made it a coward's weapon
My thanks lord thunder signet
We'll see what that does later
Okay, you dash just before getting hit bolt strikes a nearby foe
Your chain landing effects bounce more times than before. All right, that's four times. That's huge
All right, let's keep going
max health or pomegranate
Uh, i'm gonna die
or shop shop
Holy shit zeus raid. No way
zeus
What were you doing today, man? I've already done this. We did this joke already
Like a long time ago
Am I getting just another key?
I don't have another gift
I think I can get them all
No, I can't
Definitely taking the key. All right key max health or
uh
Didalis
Whatever. Let's go. Whoa
Holy shit, that's um
That's a hangover every attack does hangover so I can dash in there to hangover slash
It's but is is that is that better than?
The zeus I mean i'm gonna do it
I mean you have I have to do it uncle zeus won't mind
So this is just like get in slash slash like get the fuck out like it's just total poison
Is that seven fourteen twenty one right if I go set in one dash in
That's seven
Dash out. That's fourteen twenty one and if I get this in there, too
That's just like 30 damage a tick
Just go in there go wham dash out go
And just run around just run away
It's fourteen per second. Holy shit. Okay
zeus left
Don't worry. We're gonna get raided by uh
INS's soon anyways zeus you viewers leaving whatever
All right, i'm probably getting my ass kicked but whatever let's go
Here we go. I will keep coming like your stupid heads
It's pretty good
Okay, just eat this
What am I doing? I'm freaking out. All right, here we go first wave
Itchy nose
We got shit, you know pretty good
It's pretty good, man
Don't get greedy. All right. Well, he's gonna do he's gonna do the machine gun
Wow, he's gonna swing
Holy shit. I messed it up so bad
All right, i'm good
And spot
Jesus, this is such a terrible spot
Oh my god
One more just be careful
All right, get ready
easy
fuck
No
I didn't know he's gonna do that again
Oh, I didn't know he's gonna do that again
I thought he was gonna shoot. Oh, I just fucking got so greedy. Damn it
That's so much harder with melee
Oh who said that i'm gonna slice you
I was so close. Yeah, I saw the big number. I saw the 300 crit and I was like get in there
Dude when they spawned those five dragon skeleton shit that shit's fucked
Okay, so I can do this
This is now I can now get uh
Treasure trope house contractor my good shade. I've yet another job for your distinguished team
Please stop. Okay father
What happened ouch?
The only place for anyone to have a little fun around here and you seal it shut
Oh, I had little choice about that boy. You see after you fled the first time Cerberus
Well, I have a bunch of keys very much upset utterly tore the place to shreds
It's now under repair all thanks to you
I think I can get all the weapons me for not minding the dog while I was out and while you all were here
I laid the blame entirely upon you. Yes, who else it's fortunate that Cerberus has calmed himself since then
Come to his senses. I should say
May you yet come to yours?
What's all the paperwork he's doing?
Did they tell us about that yet?
If I don't patch your other heads don't bite my arm off deal
Cool, let's go get the other weapons or are not we each have our commitments to this house megara
There is no shame in yours
And whilst your sisters are away you bear their burden of responsibility as well
So that like whoa
Get loud thing did my limiter come in and just try to kill that did it even help? No
It didn't help I have a limiter on it should have uh, it should have at least squelched a little bit of that
I understand
It's just am I supposed to keep pretending nothing's changed
This house is cracking at the seams and no one's going to admit it. It's too late. We heard everything
House shall stand eternally
Although in what condition it is ours to decide our obligation is to keep the house in order
All right. I'm gonna go check on the uh
You're right. Of course. You're right. This game's really good. I'll do my best. I'm having a lot of fun
I'll do my best for both our sakes next
What was that about? I don't know. You're the nosy one
Let me take a look at my quests. Something's added to the fated list
Okay
Freddy dredge just gave 50 bucks. What's up, freddy can't sleep. Thanks for the 5 000 bits freddy already says I freaking love this game
It's very good. Well, oh, hold on. Okay. Wait, should I use the keys on the mirror or
Use the keys on the let's up. Let's get the weapons first, right? Give me the weapons, but thanks freddy
Thanks for the huge insane amount of money. Thanks for the 50 bucks
Yeah, let me i'm gonna lock the weapons and then we'll go from there and i'm gonna see which one I actually like the most
They'll get the coward's shield
I'll try it. Oh, i'm paid to take it not to dish it out now. Give it to me
Okay, so uh, I can't get both
I can get shield or I can get spear
See what this is shield of chaos the shield
Okay, x is bash
There's no combo. It's just one
old to defend
Okay, and when you release you dash forward
That's a huge dash
Throw oh you throw the shield. Okay
and then this is
You can do this while dashing
Cool you hold it. It blocks all damage
Really?
Okay, i'll try it
I'll give it a try
So it's a block all damage that's inside of those lines
Or is it like 180 degrees in front of the character?
Just that front just those lines. Okay
Oh, what's this new thing? I got that one do the next boon you find will be from zeus
His blessings have plus 10 chance to be rare. I think this one's just better for me. Anyways
I get to come back to life twice. I feel like it's necessary
All right, let's go. Wait, there is a combo is there that was weird. How come I just went?
Oh, I guess you can do a little combo if you do the dash too
Yeah, you can do a combo if you do the dash
Achilles achilles achilles achilles achilles achilles achilles achilles
Where is he? Is he here? There's no teacher like the real thing have something for you
Gift you're giving me your codex. I can't accept codex
Please I insist
I want your love of history to grow not just your love of warfare
Besides maybe you can finish out the rest of it. I have a question for all of you guys that have played all of the
super
Massive giant games. Uh, I really like this
Almost everything about it. I passed on transistor and I passed on
Bastion should I play them bastion is like this bastion, especially okay higher. Wait, is bastion by the same company?
Yeah, it is very okay
Denied what?
All right, so this is just lore codex undiscovered. Okay, cool. Got my lore codex. Thanks guys
Yeah, because I don't know
Transistor and pyre they didn't I they didn't do it for me. I wasn't into them. I was like, uh
Are they like this? I feel like this is different. All right, let's just try it higher is the most different
Okay, how many times have I referenced one of the four games so far? I believe twice
once accidentally
So, I don't know if it counts
One absolutely absolutely at least once
This one was bound to show up I guess in the name of hades olympus. I accept this message finally aries, right?
Has to be the fighting spirit in you there. I have to say
Most intriguing and yet no surprise for someone born in hell itself
You come on out of there and tell me all about it
I'm a fellow student of death you see
Okay doom you and your attacks inflict doom
After a brief moment the victim takes a burst of damage
Okay, does it happen?
after every swing
Your special inflicts doom. I feel like that's better because it's ranged
Dash creates a blade riff where you started
It does doom does not stack. Yeah, this one's probably way better because it's ranged
Yeah, I mean I can that's an extra 60 damage on range
Holy shit. Yeah, that's amazing. That's incredible
It doesn't stack
Yeah, but still I mean I can do
This is a coward run prince delves back into the underworld
It's ever shifting chambers realign to frustrate his attempts to perhaps map it out built to ensure no one gets out
We'll see about that
Wait, I should be looking for chests shouldn't I?
Didn't I unlock that?
This bounces too
I want to test the damage reduction. What can I do that to?
Holy shit, that's awesome
Are there any is there any caveats at all with that?
Or is it truly just you can just eat damage forever
If I just sit like this I can absorb a hundred every second all damage. No matter what
forever
That's very useful. Can I cancel it?
Can I can I can I cancel it? But do I have to dash?
Okay. Well, here's something I will say
All the weapons so far have been very very interesting and very different. Do I want money or do I what's this one?
Is this a god right? Yeah, that's a god
Very good. That doom is so good on the shield. It's so good
You just have to touch him too. It just bounces around all over the place. I don't have any gifts, right?
Harry's reached you didn't always found his conduct. That's a bandwagon opinion. Whatever. It seems he's helping you for now
Okay, your attack is stronger and can deflect
well, uh
that seems to be very very good because now I can block all damage and just
Hit back all projectiles does the block count as an attack?
Because if it is I can launch I can just sit there right it does
No, i'm seeing this is no it doesn't it does it does not know. Oh
I don't want this one. I mean you it's gonna be this one your wisdom guide me first is better. Yeah, so what can I
Wow, even not even projectiles. It's everything
This is incredible
Oh my god, it's so good. It's so good
And with the doom on it, too
It's so good. It's so good
That's broken
Well, I mean not maybe a little
It's not broken at all
I mean, I don't I don't think it is
You have to look you have to really really stand still and things can just spawn behind you in this game. That's not good
But it is very very good though. Like very good
This is the kind of play style. I like safe
It hits everything in a line too. All right, that's a little broken
That's a little overpowered that I can hit everything in this line, not just the first enemy
We got to build on this though
Oh
I don't know
More damage with the attack but more doom damage
Yeah, of course. Absolutely
Do I do more keys or should I go for upgrade run? Hey, this is a boss
Yeah, where is it? Oh shit. You're so there's blocks. That's right
All right. Where are you? Where are you? Oh, how are you an elite?
That's an elite
I guess you're doing a shitload of bombs
Oh my god, it is a lot
Oh my god, all right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait kill this guy
Oh, this is the real coward. This is the real coward move
Give me that key
This is total cheese
That's another aries door
Yeah, that's another i'm gonna be able to upgrade doom again
All right, let's do this. Just wait
Don't be an idiot here. Hold on just because you can block everything doesn't mean you need to block everything
This is doom run. Yeah, it's just doom doom doom doom doom doom. Don't don't don't don't don't
All right. Don't freak out. Just dodge
Just bounce it around
I swear
Lucky tooth rank up
What happened? I ranked up lucky tooth
I gotta give this guy a gift. Seriously
Except you see dear cousin that some members of our family are predisposed toward the unspeakable
I caution you around my half brother is all
Now keep sakes level up the more that you use them. Oh, okay
Oh, that's right. It was like 25 000 points or something
You only do as you see fit lord aries mind that you continue pulling in the same direction as us all
Yes
What's this?
What hold on? Wait a minute. I need to look at this
Your dash creates a blade rift who cares
Your doom effects deal more damage when applied multiple times
but duo
Your abilities that can deflect immediately activate doom
So I put the doom effect
And then I just hit x and it'll detonate really so I can go just
Throw shield x throw shield x throw shield x throw shield and it'll just be 100 100 100 with extra combo damage
Oh shit, all right. Don't i'm not gonna get complacent here because this feels like this could be really good
I gotta watch my health. Take care. Be easy
As I will blow this i'll ruin this whole thing
Oh shit
Oh nice
So I just got a free fountain. I don't have enough money. What is that?
Is that two gods in one perhaps unimaginable occasionally is to be for not a moment. That's a duo in there. Oh shit. Let's do it
All right, i'm gonna play good
This is an elite room. Let's see how this works
Wait, what whichever god I don't pleased whichever god I don't pick will be very mad at me
So who do I pick?
Ares again and just go full doom
Okay
Rift cast your cast sends a blade rift hurling ahead. I don't care
After you take damage and flick doom on foes around you
After using death defines deal more damage that encounter. That's okay
I mean, this is the one that's a synergy here. I mean if I take damage I can it'll just doom
They all kind of suck. Actually, i'm gonna stick with this
Just doom build now. She's mad punishable choice. But if you wish to face the consequences
So be it
You angered the gods
I hate to do this athena. Hey, hey, hey, why are you? It's so good
What are you linked to?
I took too much damage here. Oh now athena gives me some cool shit incident and keep our focus on the task
Half-life two crowbar
Uh, I don't have a cast
But this is just
Your abilities that can deflect also make foes exposed
I need a cast though, don't I?
This is really good. It's just straight up five percent damage. Five percent's not that much though
Yeah, just take the bonus damage. It's just bonus damage. Just take it. All right keys or gems. Uh,
Let's get keys so I can get the spear
Easy
Oh my god. Okay. I'm fine
Just throw the shield. I don't have to do anything just throw throw the shield and block attacks. I'm good
Who's next? Whoa, what happened? He exploded
Key to a weapon. I'm sorry. I'm loud. I know i'm sorry i'm gonna i'm gonna go away from the mic
Locked bounce bounce bounce bounce bounce bounce bounce. Oh my god. I'm getting overwhelmed
Stay in the corner for a second
Bounce it bounce it bounce it bounce it
Wowee
What the fuck is happening damnable fools finally
Taking too much damage from these rums
Throwing no i'm not throwing good. I'm gonna get i'm gonna get my ass kicked by that fucking goddamn snake boss again
Have to take damage your phone. I kind of don't want any of these but here's a cast
Mmm
This is good, too, though
Yeah, i'll take three
Is my hair sticking up
Let's see
12 health for 23. What a terrible terrible waste of money, but I need it
Ain't a random item
Do I get this?
Ain't a random item offered from the well of sharon. Maybe I maybe
random item
Should be handy. What is it in 20 movement speed?
Kind of sucks. Oh, all right. I need the I want the health
This is probably just I know but like the hammer is good, but like I well I only have 50 hp
Always hammer. No, I need the health so bad. I'm gonna die. It's the snake skeleton thing
Who's next? Okay. We're good
hammer
Your dash strike deals 50 damage in a larger area
Your special can strike up to four additional foes before returning your ball rush charges faster. That's really good. That's very good
I can hit four people
Okay now i'm getting the health. Thank you
75 and here's the boss. All right, let me pee first for this fight. This fight's a piss fight. I gotta pee
I'll be right. This is the stupid bone animal in a minute
Okay, I am ready to tackle this. The best part about this is I can just hold x
And block the machine gun. So I just have to get through the insane five person snake encounter and i'll be good
theoretically, right
I'm gonna sit here and go like this and block the whole thing and then go bang bang bang bang bang run away
Oh, it's meg, right? Oh, well fine. Whatever. What are you doing zagreus? What the hell is this weapon?
It's just a ribbon
It's like, oh, that's a prank lightsaber
This can't stay sealed shut forever make might get some practice in you know
Well, you're the first boss of like eight rooms floors or whatever you are
Wow, that hurt a lot. What the fuck was I doing?
Just don't be an idiot. I'm good
I think I peed out all my gamer sense. I really think I did
Can you do that? Is that possible?
I think I like pissed out all my vitamins
Fucking trap. I swear to god it hit me again
It's the second time I got hit by the dumb trap
Oh my god, I I pissed out all my gamer sense. I really think I did
I I feel visibly slower right now
Okay
I like peed out all my skill when I was peeing. I felt it too. It was like yeah, i'm ready to do this boss
I'm slowing down
I'm like slower and relaxed. What am I doing playing a game right now? I'm okay though. Enjoy the searing heat of asphodel
Wasn't even that hot. It was okay
It's my keepsakes
150. All right eel always heal
always
Don't sell anything
searing heat
of
Asshole, here we go. All right, come on
Let me get back to the tower number three
ice level
I need some gamer fuel or something not the drink not like the powdered fucking like sugar stuff
I'm not no, I need like some gamer energy for how do I get it?
You can no longer say the word game fuel without it being game fuel tm. I need I need something
What do I need? I need something
Oh my god, i'm on fire because I held the button in there. Who's next?
Oh, no, that's don't dash here. Don't even block here. You're gonna go in the lava
I forgot I even had the lightning bolt thing
Give me that all gamers raise your hands terminate five needs your energy
No, I don't I don't need that. I need
I need like peanut butter
You have that do you ever get any peanut butter?
hype hypers
Somebody came behind me like put like a sack over me
Uh, what should I do?
Let's get out of here. I'm free to do as I may
Oh cool, cool, cool cool cool money
We've been residents in asphodel
Reverberates the golden sounding voice of law neur cole
Who once attempted to escape the underworld? Oh, it's cool. It's your redo
Gift gift gift gift gift gift gift gift gift gift
Ur solarium thank you for making me feel welcome and you're ready to see
can't say the same for most places i've been lately
I have a small gift I wanted you to have. Oh, that's awful sweet of you, Your
Royal Majesty. Bringing me fresh ingredients like this. You're ready to see. You're ready to see.
You know what? Here's something for you two. Help keep you safe out there. Thanks so much.
We got the evergreen acorn. What is it? Evergreen acorn. Okay. Where the... where is it?
Evergreen acorn. What's it under? You don't have it. Idiot! You look like you're in a rush, though
There's always time for a quick snack, right? You have any peanut butter in here?
All right. Next three boons you find have upgraded rarity. Up to four random boons
gain plus one level. Or two random boons of yours are upgraded to the next rarity.
Hmm. Probably this one. Let's do one. Hope you like it.
First of Vengeance and Blinding Flash got upgraded. Oh, that was bad. Oh, that was
very bad. Come on. What's the percentage there? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight?
Really? Two out of eight? Well, whatever. Sucks. Somebody said chat actually sucks at
this game. Well, do they? I don't know. I mean, let him attack. Just kill him. Wow! He
almost just... I gotta stack that shit up, you know what I mean? Yeah. I gotta be doing that
like X, Y, X, Y, X, Y, X, Y. It just does 140 damage. You've been choosing good stuff
on accident and chat has been suggesting terrible stuff on purpose. Prove? Trial? Earned up
to $100. The challenge. Okay. All right. That's a... What? Yeah, I thought... For a second
I thought he said I didn't get it. I was gonna say that's bullshit. Oh, this is a new god.
Shouldn't this get out? Come on, dude. Really? Oh, fuck me. Hermes, you better be worth
it. Did I miss that? All right, Hermes, you better have something cool. Restore all health
every second. Mercury! Each time you enter a chamber, a game
a bit of wealth. So I get 10 gold every time I go into a new spot. Old castifier in rapid
succession. Dash? You can dash more times in a row. Wait, that's three dashes in a row.
Appreciate the lift, Lord Hermes, sir. Now let's go. This is such a good build. Please
don't waste it on me being terrible at everything. Restore 10% of your health when you go in a
new chamber. Yeah. That's three chambers. 10% of 75 is 7.5. Gain this instantly. Payment
in full. And I'll take them all. Give me all of them. All right, here we go. Finds the barge
of death. These explode. Just activate them now. They're gonna kill me. These will kill
me. I know they will. Just activate them now. Kill him. Holy shit. Why am I dodging to the
dodge and the glom? All right, I'm good. Ooh. Ooh. Wait, how many? Your dash deals damage
and can deflect. What? Oh. What is this? I get extra health points. This triggers doom.
Deflecting does doom. Look at this. Look at this crazy build I've got going. Shit, this
is pretty... Okay, pay attention. You're gonna die, cloud. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah. 128 for doom. Definitely one. That's a 30% increase in damage. Where should I go?
Okay, max health, the shop, or Hermes again. Oh, this is tricky. I don't know. Max health,
or the shop. I don't know. Oh, this is so hard. They're all good. I have like 300 plus dollars.
I gotta spend it. Yes. What a good choice that was.
Let's do this first. Bye. We do.
Your attack, special, and cast deal more damage. That's just more damage. Yeah. 13% more damage.
All right, now let's buy the pomegranate. Your dash deals damage and can deflect.
After you take damage, your foe is struck by lightning or backstab bonus. Probably this one.
Probably not going to happen that often. I don't care about damage on this one because
it's doing boon already. I don't get extra like boon damage, right? Oh, yeah, this one.
And then I'll take the meal. I'm ready. I'm ready for the boss. This is it. I have to beat this guy.
Okay. All right. I'm going to be quiet and I'm going to do this right and I'm going to try
and I'm going to just do it very, very closely. I'm going to just defend and then all hell is
going to break, break loose when five spawn, but let's go. No more talking. Here comes quiet
gamer time. Don't you have something to say to me? What did I do that for? Oh my God. What happened?
We go. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I'm good. If you choke, I'll delete my account. Well,
uh, it almost happened. What are the diamonds do for you? Anyways, I'm glad you didn't have
to delete your account, dude. All right, let's move on. It's for upgrades. Ooh, special upgrades.
Get a good refresh here. Uh, gain 20% movement speed for, yeah, why not? Whatever. All right.
This is how far I got last. I got to the Minotaur last time. Acorn. The final encounter in each
underworld region. Take zero damage for the first three times you get hit. That's pretty big too,
though. This thing about getting hit once is bad. Getting hit like more than twice is bad. I took
one hit from the boss and took 20 damage. If I have revived with 50 damage, 50 health, wouldn't
it just be better to block 60 damage? Just don't just, if I get hit from a boss, that's cool though.
Tooth is at 75. Oh, right. Because I, I've been playing and I upgraded it. Okay. All right,
I think I'm ready. Let's go. I think the boss is Medusa. It looks like it could be Medusa.
Could be. Let's beat that Minotaur. Let's beat the Minotaur. Key. I want to be able to unlock
the spear. Don't come back here. Oh my God. What did he hit me with? Holy shit, dude. I'm getting
way too confident. Stay back and play the way with the shield you're supposed to play. That's
what's hitting me. Okay. The shield was gone for so long. Oh my fucking God. Why? Why? Jesus,
that took, that was so stupid. I took like 30 damage for no reason. Whoa. All right, relax.
Give me money. Watch out for that shit. Give me the shield back so I can kill him. It's a new enemy.
I don't know what that does. Oh, it's the butterfly thing. Okay. Fuck, just hit me.
Dang. I need to heal. He's forgetting. He's forgetting to breathe. I'm sorry. All right.
Good. Heal. Heal. Heal. Heal. Heal. He forgot to breathe. Yes. Thank God. Here's the fee.
This one's cheap. Zeus or the cheap pomegranate. It's a random. Oh, that's why somebody's talking
about giving me Bitcoin. I feel like this is necessary now because now that's jolt.
My special does, yeah, let's do this. The special now, I can actually do it. It's better. Okay. I'm
going health. You don't have jolt. I don't? Oh, wait. I don't? Wait, wait, wait. Are you sure?
Come on. What? Don't I? Your lightning effects also make foes jolted. Yeah, I do. My special is
a lightning. Is it my special lightning? Somebody has a fucking crosshair on me.
I'm trying to hit the stupid thing. I want to hit the bomb. I'll do it myself.
Come up. Holy fuck. Not yet. Oh my God. Get him. Yes. Extra HP. What's this? What are the choices
here? Hammer or Zeus? No. Poseidon extra. Always hammer, right? Every time. Chariots.
Chariots. Chariots are alive. Well, they're going to have to catch me, aren't they?
You can deflect that shit back. Don't forget that, Jeremy. Hammer. Your bull rush gains a
power rush that deals 500% damage. Your special deals 50 damage to foes around you when you catch
it. Or your dash strikes deals 50% damage in a large area. I mean, what does it do right now?
How much does... Has anyone seen the numbers? I haven't really been paying that much attention.
What does it actually do? You need to time it for the power rush. Oh. One requires actual skill.
Okay. So besides the passive aggressive, you're terrible at everything. What's the best one to
do? What do you think? Probably this one. Yeah, that works. Key. How do I get that off? How do
I get the cursor off me? What does it do? What does it mean? Oh, I'm very powerful right now.
Get that cursor off me. Oh, the stupid lightning rod things. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Pomegranate. That's... Pomegranate. It's double, I know, but I have to fight a bunch of horrible,
scary things. Don't need it. I don't need it. Double, do double, duo, double. No, but I don't
need it. I don't need it. I don't need it. Should I just pick Ares? Just always pick Ares. Your doom
effect deals more damage when applied multiple times. Or your doom effects deal more damage
but take half a second to activate. Number three. Because I can activate it whenever I want.
Definitely three. I'm taking three, man. 60% more doom damage?
Okay, here we go. Holy shit.
Holy fuck. Oh my god.
I still have no health. You're attacking its chain lightning when you damage a foe
after you dash just before getting hit. Or your cast is a burst of chain lightning that bounces
between foes. I mean, yeah, I'll take the cast. Yeah, all right, we're good. I need money or health.
No, I'll do Hermes. Do I have enough? I have enough. Yeah, I have enough money to buy
whatever I need. I'm doing Hermes. What did I really miss? That dash to activate the doom is
incredible. All right, Hermes, give me some. Is that rare Hermes? I think that's a rare Hermes.
Oh, okay. After you dash, you become sturdy and can move 100% faster. Each time you enter a
chamber, you get money. Or you can... Yeah, these are all terrible. Probably this one. This is going
to mess me up. This is not good for me. I'm going to dash and I'm going to go too fast and walk into
something. I know me. I know myself. Trust me. It's not good for us. All right, chop. Here we go.
Yes. Okay. Give me the meal. I can use this. Nice. All right, here comes the boss.
I've never fought this boss before. Do I just do all these? I could just do them all. Okay.
Gain when you pick up that. Gain max life when you pick up any of those. That's probably what
I'm going to do. Bonus damage per fountain. Using a fountain restores all health and gives
you damage. It's this one. That gives me full health. Well, pretend full health and then
whatever this is. Verse of pain level one. Okay. I don't know what that does. What is it? Verse
of pain level four. Oh, shit. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Here's the boss. You ready?
See if I can beat this boss. I'm going to be very careful here.
Looms tall, rousing prince. As if to goad him into such a competent. Cheers for the vote of
confidence, old man. Here we go. Wait, it's the Minotaur. Beware you face a foe more terrible
even than the only foe whom I've ever faced who bested me. Is that Hercules? Fiend, you'll walk
not one more step toward the light of day. So long as I am here. Theseus, no way. You two are
legends. I'd be honored if we had a sporting contest here. Ah, a naked attempt to sway me
from my convictions. Defend yourself. Defend yourself, you blaggard. And may the gods show
you some mercy, for I shall not. It's kind of unfair. Holy fuck. Oh, shit. Okay, I get it. All
right. This is don't say it. I was going to get this 05 subs. Shit. Run into something, you fucker.
Run into this pole. Oh, my God. Please let me do a pole. What's going on here? What's going on?
What the fuck? Holy fuck. I'm in trouble. Oh, bring me back. Bring me back. Bring me back. Bring me
back. Oh, yeah. Oh, that was tough. I got a super juice. A super juice. What? Oh, I think this is
regular one. Wait, this is different. Cool. All right. Who's that? Is that the king? Oh, up to the
left. What? Look, you have a fan. I do? Red guy? That's my only fan. I just beat the two strongest
guys in the Coliseum. That's bullshit. That was crazy. Is there anything new? No. I only have 20.
Wait, is that enough to heal? No. That's expensive, but that's really good.
Sell something for it? Hold on. What should I sell? I don't think I can sell enough to do that.
Don't, don't, don't, don't. I want, I want. All right, so I have one more of these left.
Is it worth switching it up now or just stay with what I know? All right, well, let's go.
We're getting closer. What have we got? The Temple of Sticks.
Somebody said, I swear to God, if he beats this game in fucking four attempts.
I don't, I highly doubt that will happen. Wait, I have to fight Cerberus? I told you I was gonna
have to fight Cerberus. Am I at the end of the game? This feels like a last area. Kill, I have to
fight the dog. All right, let's fight the dog. Let's go.
No, but seriously, boy. Oh, I know why you're here. There has to be a way to make you look the
other way. What if I helped you with the satyr problem? Would you let me go? He doesn't even care.
Yeah, I do. I have to find Persephone. Oh my God, a human, thanks to the five community subs.
You know what this means to me? Men's hesitation and ration. A racious hound of
ox wants prince who sets off in search of something that can say to the monster's appetites.
Humans out, humans out, humans out. Okay, now I just need to head out the beaten path here and
see what I can find. I have to find like a treat for him? Well, there's a lot of choices here, hold on.
Oh, uh, are you sure this is not the, this is like a last, is it, what? Are you sure this is not like
the final area? I don't have any money to buy anything. Okay, um, I guess we're going this way.
Uh, I think I want the health. Yeah, I need the health, but that's a soup. This is the hard,
this is a super hard one. Probably money. Should I get money? I'm going for it. Fuck it. I'm going
for it. I'm poisoned. How do I take the poison off? How do I get the fucking poison off? How do
I get the poison off? Cure. God, I didn't know. I didn't know. I don't get the health. I have to
keep going. God damn it. You don't, fuck it. I'm just going to do this shit. You want to play games?
I'm not playing games. What hit me? What hit me? This area is way too small.
Cure that. Cure it. Cure it. Oh my God. This is so, dude, this area is tiny.
Grats. I don't know what I'm doing, but it's working. Okay. God damn it. Holy shit, man.
They all bounce the fuck around. Holy God. All right, we got to go in now. Health. I needed one
of those. Fuck. Okay. Shit. I need to do this, right? I have to. Oh, but I wish I had money.
I wish I had money. No, I don't have any money. I can come back to life one more time. Okay.
Come on. What the hell is this? That's just a tiny ghost. I need vermin. Where is he? He
teleports around. All right, be easy. Where is he? He's inside. Holy shit. He just killed me. All
right. I'm coming back. I'm back. I'm back. He moves so weirdly. He's teleporting around.
What the fuck? Here come rats. All right. Just dodge around. Just move. Don't be an idiot. He's
going to run at me freaking crazily. Heal that shit. Where's the pot? Where's the pot? Where's
the heal pot? Where's the heal pot? Where's the heal pot? I'm dead. Fuck. I am unstoppable.
So vicious yet so tiny. Okay. Now what? What happened to this guy? That was a really cool fight.
Okay. So now I go back. I have health. I have money now. So I can buy. Okay. What's this? What's
the anvil do? I can buy this health. What? Should I save it? Can I replenish? Athena. Athena. Athena.
Athena. I don't know. This is high. This is very high risk. I'm not sure what to do. Wait for the
refill. Athena has a replenish. Does she? All right. Should I go for the roll? Should I roll
for Athena replenish? Okay. Here we go. One, two, three. Gamble. Come on. We got to gamble.
Yes. We got it. Reflenish. One use. I got it. Hell yeah. And when I come back to life,
I've been vulnerable for two seconds. Let's go fill it back up. I'm ready. Come on. Oh,
I have to do. I'm going to do the money door? All these tunnels. Yeah. I'm doing money door.
Obviously. Go. Money door. Don't get poisoned. I'm very bad at getting away from the poison.
I don't even know what these things do, but just kill them. Money. Site of storage. What's that?
That's a big sack of money versus a little coin of money. I don't know which one.
This is a restore 34. Okay. Hold on. I can take them both. Go with your gut. I don't wait. Can I
do them all? I can take this. All right. I can take them all. Again. Oh my God. I have $272.
Okay. Hold on. I want to spend this. Anvil or health. I don't know. I think it's going to be
health. I think it has to be health. Let's go. Okay. I wait. Okay. Here we go. Talk to the dog
now. Go back in for more money. That's a dangerous game that you want me to play.
That's a dangerous game you want me to play. I have a, I have a revive and I have 140 health.
I got your favorite treat, but you have to promise to let me pass if I ended over. Okay.
All right. I'm going to fucking zone in here.
All right. Let's relax a little. Go in. Here we go.
Let's go. I'm ready. I'm going to fight him here. This is tiny.
I suppose you must prefer it to the air below. You know, you're right. The air up here seems
pretty good so far, but I will reserve judgment until I've had my fill. I have to say though,
father, the helm of darkness suits you and touched. You dust it off on my account. It
should not have had to come to this for all your antics with me at around the house. I always kept
my temper. Have I not felt like you? It's your nose. It's your face. And then I'm going to be
dead silent. She flies all over my face. Get him off. He's nervous. I mean, kind of,
I'm at the last boss. I'm all right. I'm all right. Here we go. I skipped the lore. Who cares?
Me. You'll understand then why I wear the helm of this.
Where'd he go? Don't make me laugh. It's the last encounter.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I know that I'm not going to celebrate prematurely.
I don't know about this. I don't know about this. There's always a second phase. Of course,
there is. I thought I had it. I was like, yeah, let's go. Damn it. Oh, man. Shit. Of course,
he's got a second phase. God damn. Damn it. I'll take it. I'll take it.
I've never seen anything like this. Don't want to talk about it. Wait, I give her the gift,
right? Why not? Surprise. Hypnos. I got you this. Oh, you can't bring that in here.
Just kidding. Thanks. But wait, I'll trade you. Look. Don't say SCP 2521. This did. She is hypnos.
Coin purse. Well, dad's not even here. Yeah, of course. I'll take it though. That was fun.
I really thought I had it, too. Yeah, you never actually have it, right? Achilles, is it really
true that Cerberus ripped the lounge up right after I left? He must have gotten in a lot of
trouble. I only wish you could have seen it, lad. The place looked like a vineyard after a typhoon.
Your lord father was in it. Oh, I haven't even unlocked the fourth weapon. I should probably
do that. Poor Doosa, though. She's picking the place up. What became of Doosa? She's always
worried father's going to fire her even without something like this. Come here. You don't like it
when I pet your other heads, huh? No. Unlock some more things. Yeah. Oh, that's right. I have eight
keys. It's five keys, right? What do I next went? Hmm. Not a bad idea. What's bound to happen?
Really? Oh, man. I got. OK, cool. Three potions. My extended family seems an interesting lot.
That's good. Oh, fuck. I have a lot of these Achilles already gems. I'm getting somewhere with
it. Oh, not quite. Not quite. All right. I got a lot, though. Let's unlock the next tier.
Show me something new. Oiling blood. Oh, raise your supply of that. That's that's that's that's so
that's so necessary. Rip spear. Oh, shit. Oh, well, I'm a shieldy guy. Don't worry.
Gift the dog. Yeah, well, I'm going to I'm going to go give gifts to everybody. I didn't give gifts
to gift the dog for you, boy. As one of Cerberus's heads receives the prince's gift,
another muzzles something back into his hand. Spear sucks compared to the shield. Really?
Old spike collar. OK. Also, I can do this. Add a fountain chamber. Ambers may contain urns with
five coins or fountain chamber. I'll put a fountain chamber in Elcium. I probably should
put a fountain chamber in. I should do that first, right? Fountains first. Let's make it happen. I
have to keep an eye out for this next time out. Those rooms are so important. Underworld Innovation
Fountains provides 10 percent more health than usual. Elysium. Oh, whatever. You're asking price
good contractor. Well worth the fruits of your hard work, I'm sure. OK, now let's go give some
more gifts. Who have I not given a thing to? Hades? Anybody up here haven't given this to?
I didn't give one to Hades. He's not here anymore, though. Did I give one to...
Does it say if I... Oh, it does. OK. Poseidon. Holy shit, a lot of people need it. Did I give one to...
Where is he? Achilles. I did not give one to Achilles. Give me your treasure.
Hey, Achilles. Look, this really isn't much, but here. This really is for me. You beat me to it,
then. As I had meant to give you this when next we spoke. Please, take it. What is it? Thanks so
much, sir. A bracelet of some sort. All right, I still have another one to give. I gave one to...
Should I give a second one to Skeleton? You can give up to three, it looks like, right? Is there a
reason to... Is there not reason you shouldn't do it? What have we got? Let's see what that one does.
Receive 100 coins to spend as you please once per escape attempt. What? So if I put this on,
I get 100 coins in the first floor. Is that every new floor, or is that just the start of each game?
Just once. So you just put this on and then take it off. OK. Take minus 20% damage from the front,
but take plus 10% damage from the back. Ugh. And this is just plus 25 added health. Well,
we'll just put this on and then take it off when we... Because I shouldn't be dying, right?
What do you want to talk to me? Next.
That pal is nobody's business but my own. Besides, it's impolite discussing money out of time.
Now, back to beating me to powder. Pyrus? Oh, if it was Papyrus, it'd be,
that pal is nobody's business but my own. Besides, it's impolite discussing money all the time.
Now, back to beating me to powder. Don't do that again. Oh yeah, I forgot. Everybody has their,
like, their way that he talks. And how dare you talk a different way than what's in my head? How
dare you? Uh, are there two other weapons? Or is that DLC coming up or something? Um,
I kind of want to... I know that I just almost beat the game with the shield, but, you know,
I thought, I want to play some, I want to change it up. Let's go back to the bow.
Bow users in chat. Yeah, I'm one of them. Count how many times I've gone up to the top left
thinking I could leave. Let's try, whatever. If I die in the first room, who cares? Whatever.
Fuck the bow and fuck bow users. Okay. Oh wait, I give Poseidon a gift, right? I didn't give him
one, did I? Maybe I did. I did already. I didn't, did I? I don't remember. Nope, I haven't. Hey,
here. Take this. I gave one to Dionysius, right? I'm gonna press escape and hit give up to get a
secret. Why? All right, what's the gift? I'm not gonna do it. Is it like a racist save file or
something stupid? It's no use. Oh, I didn't even take the gift. I didn't even grab the thing.
To see if you were worthy. And you are. My aid is yours. So call me if you need anything,
especially to smash your enemies to bits.
Well, your call makes you surge into foes while impervious for 1.2 seconds.
What the hell is this thing? 350 damage max gauge bonus. Press RT. I don't know. Let me
pee first. So whatever happens here, this is probably gonna be the last run because I have
an appointment. I need to get to an appointment later this evening. Part of the reason why I
started at like noon. So let's go. So this thing is this is okay. This is a new move entirely.
Press RT for an Olympian's aid if you have such a boon. Uses one stock of your god gauge
for all four stocks for a much stronger effect. So I have a new meter. So RT uses it. Holy shit.
I didn't even have all the moves in the game. Are you kidding me? Oh dear god. If you max it,
it lasts longer. That's a 350 damage. Wait for it to be max and do it in bosses. Oh my goodness.
I'm looking forward to this. It resets every room. Oh, okay. So it's only for the current
room you're in. How do you build it? Is there a better way to build it than how I'm doing it?
Do I have to like string together like perfect or something? That's damage. That's it. Okay.
Deal or take damage. We're gonna hammer right off the bat. Bring this. I'm getting a... Oh,
I can't. Don't say it. You know, I don't care. I'll give five more community subs. I don't give a
shit. Okay. In Binding of Isaac, you know when you have an insane run that lasts a long time
and you have a ridiculous build that does very specific shit and then you end up winning or if
you lose, you go back to just shooting regular tears. I was able to dash three times before
and I was just completely different. It's fucking me up. Whatever. I'll give the five subs. I don't
care. That's pretty good. Your power shot is easier to execute. Wow. 150% more damage or two
shots. They're all good. I'm doing this one. Uh, gems. Oh, what the fuck? Wait, what? This is doing
a lot. That's a lot. That's a lot. That's the most of... Okay. Well, sure. I think this is going to
be pretty good. That's a new God. I can one shot almost everything. This is insane. I'll kill this
dude. He's a problem. 100. Okay. If I can do that again and this is going to be an ice shot,
it better be. I'm going to be very, very upset.
One way to find out. Then in the name of Hades. Olympus, I accept this message.
I understand, young Sagrius, that you would seek to leave that bitter darkness for this bitter cold.
Quite honestly, I fail to see why. You unlocked Demeter before you unlocked Spear.
You've arrived for plenty of assistance and you soon shall grow fond of it, I think.
Gilf? That stands for grandmother? Your attack is stronger and inflicts chill.
Wowee. That's a big wow right there. And it chills. Your cast drops a crystal that fires a beam at
foes for five seconds. Yeah, but this is going to do like 225 damage a shot. I'm going for just
straight up single shot death. I want more of this. Why is that? Excuse me. Hold on a minute
here. Is there armored? That's 203 damage a shot, dude. That's insane. That's the most damage I've
done this whole entire game and it's the first zone. I'm just going to make that do like 400
damage a shot. Yes. That's good shit right there, man. Insane. And got health too. Which way? Oh,
upgraded again. Do it again. Truly an item build for his massive ego. Fucking 145 damage a shot
and I didn't even get started yet. Hey dad, you're fucked. I typically would be afraid of these guys.
Let's do it again. Wait. Your special is stronger and inflicts chill. That gives
chill to my Y and makes it do like 40 damage. While all foes are chill affected, they are 15%
slowed and decayed. Wait. While all foes are chill afflicted and they take 30 damage every
second? For how long? For eight seconds? Wait. That sounds insane. Is that as crazy as I think
it's going to be? So this can stack 10 times and it's going to do 300 damage a
second if I get it. That's insane. Holy shit. You're going to be a kiting god.
These guys didn't even get an intro. They're dead. Oh, that guy got an intro. It's so good.
Guys, I said it was an 89 like an hour ago. It's gone up. It has gone up. Oh, man. Freezing and
water. All right. I'm going to take, let's take the chill first. Pick Poseidon, please. Trust me.
Don't. No, I'm taking the cold. I'm going chill. Your dash shoots out a gust that affects chill.
Okay. So this is just even more chill. Your boons become common, then gain rarity every three
encounters. Wait, what? Well, I go back to one and then every three encounters they upgrade.
That's ridiculous. Holy shit, dude. I'm at one. If this is the one to go out on, this is the one to
do. Oh, my God. I was so busy looking at the amazing damage that I just stood still. Oh,
what? It's homing. Okay. That was confusing. Use the call. Oh, fuck. I forgot I even had it. I
didn't even remember I had that. I think I want the random assortment of treasure chests.
Dash damages foes in an area. Your boons with knockback affects your rupture. Rupture foes?
But look, I can get a bunch of treasure. Oh, it's an okay. It's a knock. So it doesn't happen here.
It happens here. All right. A potion or a big chunk of upgradable fluid. If the big chunk is.
All right. I gotta stop fucking around. Damn, this is so good. Okay. And I have a random
quest encounter. What are you selling? Sell, sell, sell. What? What do you mean sell? What
are you selling? What do I do? You said big chungus. Oh, right. Well, I mean, I was just
replying to what somebody said. Within the depths of Tartarus reside the most wretched of all the
shades who linger for eternity within whose lord and masters especially unkind. No, it's. What?
I just. Somebody said it in chat. I'm just responding. Lots of wretchedness to go around,
I guess. Hello, sir. Do I have any gifts to give? No. You know, prince said I'd not expected to
run into you again. Not after all this time. Something I missed out on the house or what
not had much company of late as all. Worst stream and worst game. All right. Actually time that
person off for five seconds. They have. They are. They are very lost right now. Well, something's
just about always in this back home, sir. Figured it couldn't hurt to check up on things in Tartarus
a bit more frequently. Well, I am grateful for it. I am the old boulder there in turn.
I'm used to going like these stretches on my own, but having visitors from time to time
would do me well. Have you ever filtered your piss? Uh, no. OK, should I heal? Should I give that?
Uh, probably the money or should maybe total health. Yeah, that's good health. Certainly,
highness. Thank you, mate. Five second rule. That was five seconds, right?
Oh, piss in the Berkey, right? The Berkey. I forgot about the Berkey filter arc.
Oops. I got so caught up in getting that. Um, all right. So which one should he in the Berkey?
Pee in the Berkey. Now let's have a look at your supplier, shall we? I really would too. I would
do it. I would do it. Uh, let's take you. So Hank, actually, that'll be good. That'll be good too.
That would also be good. I'm going with this one. Health is so good. Health is so important.
Let's go kill Meg. You never get casts. Who needs it? I got my strong arms.
Let's freeze the fuck out of this lady.
You're running from yourself. I can slow you down a bit, I think. No, you can't. I don't know. Okay,
I thought in the title, I thought that just said mod that guy instead of Megara the Fury.
What happened? What's going on? Oh, you touched me. You touched me. Too far away. Step on a trap.
Oh, you analog gamer. Meg, you're not even hard anymore. You were, remember I was like,
oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, I'm gonna get killed by Meg. Meg, you're so easy.
I'm so good. Oh, I just upgraded something. Toxic? She's like goddess of hell. Tell me,
I can be toxic to satanic individuals? She like drinks people's blood. But I can't say,
get out of here, you idiot. I'm good. You're a satanist. No, I'm not. I've done so much
dark energy elimination from me. You are. I'm not. I've removed so many dark energies from me.
Okay, your special deals 40. I don't want to spend any money. Tooth on. I think I'm good.
He's gonna have an enema. Yeah, but here's the thing. That's like, that's like a procedure.
That's like a medical term. Or you could say that's gross. That's a medical term.
Why are you defending enemas? Spread this. I'm not. I'm just saying that that's a medical
terminology. Stop, stop, stop, stop. I saw somebody write something funny. I'm freaking out
because I stepped in the- what? I'm made of ice. Why would I care about that? Ice melts. Ice cools
down fire. Uh, pomegranate or money? Money. Ice cools down hot liquids. Okay, riddle me this, chat.
If I had a, let's say like the square footage of this square up here, and I dunked in an ice cube
that was as big as your house, what would happen? Would that temperature of this lava, would that
temperature of this hot liquid cool down? Yes, it would melt, but it would cool down. Whatever it was,
it would make it colder. It would explode. It would not explode. It would explode. It would because of
the heat. No, it would not. It would not explode. We get a link? Let me see. Who made you the
psychics professor? Wait, what? You missed something? What did I miss? Remember, you missed an NPC that
gives free dash upgrade. Location of Bob Hades. What the hell is Bob Hades? Bob Hades? That's not
even a real person. Bob Hades? Bop-a-deez.
That doesn't even make sense. What do you mean? Bop-a-deez nuts? What do you mean bop? Like,
I'm punching you in the balls? What are you talking about? Hey, yo streamer, bop these nuts.
I don't think I want to do that. I don't think I want to punch you in the balls.
Hey, bop-a-deez nuts. It's F. Bof? Bof? What word are you trying to say?
Bofa? Bofa? What is Bofa? Oh, both. Okay, I was like, what is Bofa? Like, what the hell is Bofa?
Bof supposed to be. Bofa. What is this? I've never seen this before. It was like Bop-a-deez.
I don't even know. Whatever. I'm gonna buy this.
Ooh, your special causes a lightning bolt to strike nearby people. Might as well.
I'm gonna, I think I'm gonna save my bunny. Well, you know what? Let's roll the dice.
What do we got? Idle dash. Nice. Ooh, nice. Buy the Bunger. Oh shit, what time is it? I got time.
Have to say the barge of death is never late. Oh, this place sucks. Just dash when I knew
to and just cause absolute destructive damage. Oh shit. Whoa, that's a lot of people right there.
Fuck is rough. These guys have the goddamn damage mitigator. I didn't get hit, did I? Oh yeah,
let's go. Did I give over? I got a rarity upgrade. This is a god build now. Did I give her a gift?
I have not. Let's give Athena a gift.
What's this thing?
Bop-a-deez.
Owl pendant.
What do we got? That, what is it? Your special is stronger and can deflect.
It's gonna replace that. But, okay. Come on. This is just 7% straight up damage. That's pretty good.
That's good too. You know what? Yeah, I'll take just a straight up just 7% reduction in all damage.
That's pretty good, I think. Most of the time it's 5. And plus that can upgrade itself, right?
Every three rooms that might just get grabbed and be 10%. Get out of here. You're nothing.
Drop, drop, drop. It's a 92 right now, by the way. And potentially still climbing.
I think I'm going for the health. Go back, go back. What?
Restore 10% when you enter a chamber. That's pretty good. Go back. Chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos,
chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos. There's chaos down here.
It's 25 health. What the fuck is this?
Okay, let's try it. Chaos.
The god of chaos.
Of chaos. The most ancient sculptor.
Who is the god of chaos? And best take all the evidence I find.
Is there a god of chaos? This is not someone I recognize.
So in the name of Hades. Hello, may I ask who's calling?
Gonna be Kronos.
What are you holding? Earth? Are you trading me one earth or something? What do I have to give you for earth?
Hopper shot.
The next three encounters you cannot earn money.
Afterward your cast deals plus 30% more damage.
The next four encounters you take 377% damage from traps.
After you deal 34% more damage. Holy shit.
Your dash has 50% range. You deal 65% damage. Okay, it's two. It's absolutely two.
Holy shit.
A few chambers from now.
Very, very cool. All right, let's go.
How much damage does a trap do? It's like 400% of what?
Try it. It's 40. So it would be, it would kill me instantly.
Lava counts as a trap. Okay, I gotta be careful.
What is this one?
Juremios. In Greek mythology Juremios.
Pramius, however you pronounce that, possibly meaning short, is a titan of god of rats.
Juremios is a bad streamer and balding who is most known for being two and a half trillion
silver in debt to the Olympian gods. His dump truck ass and his delusional
conversations with hallucinations in his head, collectively known as chat.
The best part about this is these are hyperlinked.
His dump truck ass is a link to another article.
Not dump truck, not ass, his dump truck ass.
So that means my ass has its own Wikipedia page.
Interesting.
This one's, all right, I'm gonna keep going. I gotta like hurry up.
Mega fucking LOL. All right, I gotta keep going.
I might have to leave in the middle of this run. I'm not even kidding.
How much is this meal? 48. That's a lot.
I don't need it.
Business.
Finally, a cast.
Wait, maybe three. Yeah, three.
Yeah, I gotta leave very soon.
I gotta leave soon.
Um, I love this game, though.
I'll beat this boss and then I'm gonna call it.
We'll pick it up again.
Holy shit, look at this damage. You kidding me?
He's already hit 50% health almost.
All right, let's go.
I gotta be careful here, though. I don't have very many movement abilities.
Don't kill me. Check the lava.
No. No, thank you.
I won't.
Machine gun.
All right, last one.
Shit, I'm taking damage here.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, oh my God.
This is unbelievably powerful.
Oh, fuck. It's okay.
I've died.
Remember, every time I get hurt and die, I have to go.
All right. What the fuck?
Oh, there's one idiot left.
200. 200. 200. 200.
Hooray.
That was plus 100. Holy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a minute. Is that increasing?
Isn't that like 20 last time?
Thank you, John, for the five community subs.
And this is MC for the five community subs, too.
How much time is it?
I got a little bit of time.
I have a little bit.
I have just enough time to do the three encounters.
So when I play this like tomorrow, I don't forget about it.
Step in a trap and die instantly.
Oh, Slipper's DLC came out today.
I know a lot of things are around, aren't they?
I want to see what these are.
The next boon you find will be from Athena.
And her blessings have a 10% chance to be rare.
Next boon you find will be from Poseidon.
But you can just game this, huh?
Yeah, I'll keep the tooth.
I don't have any money to do anything anyways.
All right. All right.
Let me just do this.
Let me just get this done.
I have, what, two more rooms to do?
One more room.
Or I instantly die when I step in lava.
Or step in a trap.
That must have been pretty good up here.
Where are you?
Always hammer.
Three more rooms.
Okay. I hate the little assholes that come out of there.
Oh, don't let him touch anything.
Who's left?
Oh, you.
Oh, a chariot.
Don't you dare.
You know what?
What do we get?
Your attack hits up to three foes.
Dealing plus 15% more damage for each.
Your special fires four times.
Or your special pierces foes and deals 400% damage to armor.
That's pretty good.
That's the armor breaker.
But this, I mean, I don't know.
It's probably one.
Your attack hits up to three foes.
Yeah, and more damage, of course.
The deadliest foe of all.
All right.
Only two, two more encounters.
Okay. Money or Hermes?
Hermes.
We've got a good link here.
All right. Hold on.
Hold that thought.
Did I get hit by it?
Oh, it's because they're on fire.
Shit, okay.
Watch it.
Why doesn't it hit cats?
What the fuck is hitting me?
Cats, the music.
I'm a cavity, I'm a cavity.
There's no one like me, cavity.
You're the biggest.
Anyone seen that movie?
It sucks.
But who cares?
It was like $500 million to make it.
Can you imagine?
Whatever my...
Hello?
My controller's fucked up?
Uh, what?
That was weird.
Hermes.
Good.
Bonus charge one, yeah.
I mean, you have to.
I don't even care where the other ones are.
The other ones could be god powers and I don't care.
Hermes thighs.
Whatever.
Is it...
Oh my god.
Okay, here's the...
We've clicked on the hyperlink, apparently.
Brother used to see extreme death.
Jerma's dump truck ass.
Also known as caboose, a wagon, or a star.
Is a feature of the Earth's surface visible from Earth's orbit.
Satellites have captured an image of it below.
And scientists are still looking into whether or not it can be harnessed
to create geothermal energy.
Jerma is still under contractual obligation to make said image an emote.
You can see it from the orbit.
What the fuck?
All right, let's go.
What time is it?
But that's a trap, that could have killed me.
Uh...
The mirror.
I won't touch the traps, no matter what.
Just let them explode.
On their own.
Jerma dump one, Jerma dump two, Jerma dump three, Jerma dump four,
Jerma dump five, Jerma dump six, Jerma dump seven, Jerma dump eight.
I won't touch that spear.
Still alive?
Oh my god, the traps do 5000% more damage.
What am I doing?
Be careful.
My nose is itchy.
Hold on.
Watch out!
Okay, did I do it?
The curse of chaos has been lifted.
Okay, now I do 34% more damage.
Let's go through the others, but it's so damn dark down there.
You're gonna be late?
I'm not.
I got a minute to just get my bearings.
All right, so here's an interesting thing to do.
I already have 7% damage reduction.
When I'm below 40%, that's 17%.
Using a fountain will restore all your health and give you damage.
Probably for the best.
But wait a minute.
Don't I...
Is there a fountain even down here?
Did I even upgrade that yet?
Restore up to 100 health.
All right, let's go.
Watch it.
All right, how much did I get?
52, that's enough.
So slow, doesn't it?
I just...
I got a full health.
All right, what time is it?
All right, I gotta go.
I have to leave.
But hold on, let me go to the shop first.
And, um...
He's defeated.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I can level this up.
450 damage?
That's pretty damn good.
Okay, how do I save the game?
Wait, but hold on.
I gotta get this part.
All right, all right, fine, fine, fine.
All right, all right, I'm done.
I'm done.
How do I, um...
Am I good?
You can't.
Clear this chamber to quit.
Go to the next room and it will save.
Okay.
All right, I'm good.
Let's do...
I want ice.
But I want to save...
Hold on.
I want to get the ice first.
This game is...
I love this game.
It's very good.
We're playing this tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow for this game.
I know what they're doing.
I feel like I know...
I know they're regenerating.
Who's left?
450.
That's so much damage.
It's insane.
All right, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
All right, let's do...
All right, I gotta fix this by tomorrow
because this is happening.
I'm losing connection to my controller
for some reason.
If that happens in the middle of a game,
that would be horrible.
Okay.
Any health effects are more potent.
We're so 62 health now.
Or your cast drops a crystal that fires...
Oh, that's pretty good.
And I can do two of these?
Oh, now that's going to be...
That's going to be awesome.
And two of those can go down at the same time.
That's insane.
Okay, so progress saved a minute ago.
So go through here and save progress.
I have to go now.
Did it just...
Did it save already?
This game is awesome.
I'll play tomorrow.
See if we can beat it tomorrow.
I feel like I'm getting close.
I will see you later.
I have an appointment.
I have to go.
Or actually, this game is awesome.
Or actually, this is medical stuff.
So I might come up with some interesting scenarios after today.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Tomorrow, we're going to start more normally.
I'll be somewhere around like one or two.
Two, probably.
Maybe one.
Somewhere in that range.
Two.
And I do have to leave very, very soon.
That's why I...
Let's do the credits.
Oh my God, I thought the webcam was on.
Thanks for all the subs, everybody.
Thanks for your continued support of the channel.
A lot of you.
Thank you.
Look at all these names.
Butt puncher.
Butt killer.
Carbon dioxide.
Why are you always naked?
I just don't...
I don't know.
I like to not...
I wear minimal clothing.
That means pants only.
Or shorts only.
If I'm leaving the house,
if I'm leaving where I'm going somewhere,
I will put on adequate clothing.
So for instance, right now,
I'm about to go put on adequate clothing
to go to a medical appointment.
Me too.
Medical appointment, in quotes.
Medical appointment at 6 PM.
Yes, it is.
Why...
Wait, medical appointment at 6.
Why does it have to be in quotes?
You're going to buy drugs.
What, you guys...
You've never heard of a doctor's office
that's open till like 7 or 8?
In quotes, medical McDonald's.
That's weird.
It's not...
No, no.
It's a medical appointment.
Okay, I'm out of here.
I'm leaving.
It's a doctor, in quotes.
No, I'm getting out of here.
I have a medical appointment.
It's a medical appointment.
No, it's not a casino.
Medical disappointment.
Oh man, all right.
All right, let's get out of here.
Just go, just go.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm leaving.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Raid?
All right, who do we raid?
I see we got a few people streaming right now.
Oh, let's go to Star.
Star is running his game tonight, right?
The Myriad episode 4.
I think this is Star made this, right?
Star like made this game.
This is his like D&D campaign.
Yeah, go to Star.
Let's go, let's go.
Don't be a fucking asshole though, okay?
I know a lot of you guys are going to go there
and be like, D&D!
He's like running a game right now.
And it's like, it's a really, really interesting game.
All right, go be professional.
You know, whatever, I don't care.
Uh, go watch.
It's apparently very interesting.
I've seen a little bit of it.
I used the word apparently.
I have seen at least like an hour of this.
All right, see you later.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Yeah, he actually like made this whole thing, right?
He still got my game to make too.
So this would be a good opportunity
to see if it's any good.
See you tomorrow guys.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Take care of yourselves.