Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2.
Gonna be playing on Harvest, just casually playing some Sniper.
Try to shave some people's heads down a size.
I love Harvest, you all know that.
Where the hell is everybody? Am I gonna have to go like Super Secret Sniper?
Let's go. Watch your head. Watch your head. That's a two piece double cheeseburger.
I'm actually very, very tired right now. So anytime I play Sniper, if I'm really, really tired, I can do very, very well.
I don't know why. I think it's because... Ah, there's a spy.
I think it's because I just relax a whole lot more than if I was, you know, stressed out and trying to get headshots and stuff.
But I just, you know, just... Who cares? Let's just play. Who cares?
Ready? Ready? Come on out. Come on out and meet your maker. Anybody. Any second now. Any... I missed.
Right here. Pyro.
Are we gonna win? Oh, we did it. Good thing I was here for the whole round. Let's do another one.
Try to win Shiv, huh? Let's go in the spawn and just like smash, smash, smash.
Uh oh. I ran out of coffee. Trying to keep myself awake and I just completely ran out of coffee.
That can't happen for a Jerma video.
There has to be a full coffee here at all times, ready to go down my throat, into my stomach, into my brain.
And let's do it, baby.
A zoo.
Oh, heavy. If you didn't have crits, I would have killed you. I still might.
Oh, sneaky little snake.
And that's how you snipe somebody's skullcap off. You're real. Let's get it again.
That is... That's a spy. You are def... You are not a real Pyro. I do... Yeah, I knew it. I could tell. I could tell.
Neither are you. You're not real either and I just keep missing these spies.
I love that hat, by the way. That Antla hat that that engineer has on right now. I love that thing.
That's like one of my favorite hats.
What is it? Merasmus's hat, I think is what it is.
This is a very bad spot for me to be right now. Very... Oh, damn it.
Come on. What's going on, y'all?
I'll take it. I'll take it. Oh, no. I'll get this guy. I'll get this guy. I'll get this guy.
I backed up right into that. How many people are in this server? There's plenty of people in here.
There's at least like two dozen people in here. Oh, no, there's not. Two dozen is 24. Right. Yes, Roger.
All right. Let's get some more kills. I got to make sure... No. Spy behind you. I got to kill him before he kills him.
Oh, he... Oh, he got the... He must have got... No, he didn't.
You? Spies everywhere. And who's behind me? You little prick. Come here.
Oh, thank God, Heavy, you just saved my life. All right. I need to get my head on straight here.
I'm gonna die. Get my head on straight. Don't get backstabbed. Right as I said it. Right as I said it, I got backstabbed.
All right. You know what? Am I going to do this right now? I think I'm putting on the Razorback.
It's time for the Razorback to go on, bros. Backing up into spies, backing up into knives. This started off pretty well.
No. No. He's not dead. Make sure he stays dead. Is it... Is their team just spies and pyros? What's going on here?
All right. We got the point. That's a good thing. Oh, you...
Stay in sniper. I'm going to stay sniper on principle. This is a long respawn. Holy shoot. That's like an 18, 17 second respawn.
I've only killed four people. All right. Let's pull this out here. I got to get some more headshots. Let's go.
We're going to win this. How are we winning right now? There we go. You stay still. But there's a spy somewhere.
Somewhere over the rainbow way.
I'm like singing karaoke. How did I not hit him? I was going to say it. I hit that guy right in his mouth.
That too. I should have hit that guy right in his face. God damn it. Oh, hey. Yeah. Yeah. You didn't get me that time, spy.
I hit Razorback ranked up. What's a level one? Yeah. Oh, I got him in midair. Did I? I don't even know. Where's he going? Where's he going?
Hey, that guy was... That engineer. Wow. EngineerGG. We got time for one more? I think we got time for one more. Why not?
All right. Well, we have changed maps to Nucleus. How are we going to end this? I'm going to give myself three lives right here.
Three lives to do as much damage and as much offensive power as I possibly can. I might not even do anything. We might just win the match.
Let's see. Oh, looking for someone like this scout. Where is he going? Oh, no, no, no, no, no. This spy is so dead. Maybe not.
He's going to kill me. No, he's definitely not dead. There's no way. I hit him like in the shoulder blade. Whoa. Who's on that point?
Oh, I got him in the head. Didn't matter. I can't. I can't shoot with this thing. Oh, that was so lucky. You cannot shoot from the hip with that damn thing.
Why did I pick it? Well, because it's awesome. That's why. That's why. Bro, you are. Are you kidding me?
He was like sitting up on the ledge. He was like chameleon blending in with the background, too. That was ridiculous.
Whatever. That's one. Two more deaths. Maybe we'll win. I'm assuming it'll be like one death per minute. Maybe not.
Yeah. You want to dance around? You want to dance? Yeah. I swear I thought that was a spy. Speaking of spies. Oh, man. I can't even shoot anybody.
Team is just too good. All right. So anyways, apparently we have the point locked down. Yeah, there's people on the other team.
I think there's just oh, almost fell off the cliff. What? How did that hurt him in the face? I can't believe that.
I run that back. He's got one health. That that line went right into in between his eyes.
That was a bunch of baloney and cheese sandwiches stuffed underneath like my grandmother's ass. Oh, my God. That was gross.
Baloney and cheese. You know, I love baloney and cheese sandwiches, but you have to be in the mood for baloney and cheese sandwiches.
Otherwise, it's just gross. Well, this was a completely successful round. I killed like one person.
You know what? Just get over here. Get the hell over here. You can shoot me all you want. I'm going to get this. I'm going to get this kill.
And this one, too. You know what? Oh, no, he's got a big sword. Your sword's way bigger than mine. All right. Well, that's three.
You know what? We'll wait till the end because we're about to win right now for as well as my team is doing.
I haven't really done anything. I just be kind of just sitting around like a real freak. Here we go.
Twelve seconds. I got to get an epic headshot right here. Epic headshot. No, this has just been like me versus but you know what?
I got an epic headshot right here. Didn't get it. Just might as well jump off the cliff over time over time.
Hey, I know you got like your camping gear. Look at this guy's just like opening and closing the gate over and over again.
I think you have enough ammo and health. I think you don't know. Stop. Stop opening that. You don't need any more.
Look, you got to save the rest for the rest of the damn team. There's rations in there. You're eating them all.
Anyways, guys, thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
Facecam Fortress 2, Sniper, Tire, Jerma for the loss or for the win. I'm not really sure, but I'll see you guys all soon.
And of course, take care, everybody.