Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And what is going on on the screen right now?
This is Randomizer. If you don't know what Randomizer is, this is a crazy mod for Team Fortress 2.
And what it does is it makes you spawn with a random class and a random loadout.
And I don't mean a random loadout like as in you spawn as the heavy and you get a random heavy loadout.
No, no, no, no, no, no. You spawn as the heavy with a flamethrower and like the Jarate.
It's crazy. I suggest you try and find a server. Sometimes it's hard to find a Randomizer server.
But if you can get in one, my god, this is like the funniest goddamn thing I've ever done in this game.
And the reason why it's so funny is because everything just gets so broken.
You'll see coming up later, I play as the soldier with a Tomislav.
And whenever you shoot the thing, your Tomislav goes up and down a hundred miles per hour.
It is insane. It almost made me want to, I had, I got a headache.
I had to stop doing it. I was like, okay, I want to die with this class.
Screw this. And really this last, I'd say last three or four days,
I've just been going into Team Fortress and playing these crazy mods.
One of the mods, one of the favorite ones, my goodness, Balloon Race.
I've only found one or two servers that actually play Balloon Race.
And I want to play them all day now. I got to get some more guys into there.
Got to get more awareness to Balloon Race because it is so much fun.
And also all crit servers, I've been doing that too.
So I've been being a real weirdo on Team Fortress lately.
Expect some videos on some of these crazy mods.
I'll probably do a Saxton Hale mod, probably do Prop Hunt.
So expect those at some point in the future.
It's just something I've been having a lot of fun doing.
So now I want to go on a different track.
And I want to talk about a certain bet that I made with you guys.
Probably a week or two ago when I did the face cam video.
All I've been seeing is comments telling me I got to eat the egg.
Where's the egg? I got to eat that damn egg.
So if you missed the video or to refresh your memory, this is what I said.
So judging by what happened in the video, I have to eat an egg.
And I did say in that video, I did say to eat a raw egg.
I was going to eat a raw egg.
But guys, you can't eat raw eggs.
If you eat a raw egg, I mean, it's not terrible.
But there's a chance you can contract Salmonella.
And I don't want to have that looming over my head when I eat it.
So this is what I'm proposing to you guys.
This is what I'm going to do this weekend, this Saturday during my live stream.
It's going to be the egg stream.
And what do I mean by egg stream?
I'm going to cook up 12 or 24 hard-boiled eggs.
And every time I'm going to play Team Fortress 2, every single time I die,
I'm going to eat one of the hard-boiled eggs until they're all gone.
So if I'm having a really bad night on TF2,
I'm going to eat a dozen eggs or even more than that.
Maybe two dozen eggs if I'm doing really bad.
So I suggest you try and show up to that.
It's going to be pretty entertaining for you.
Awful for me potentially.
I like eggs. I mean, don't get me wrong. I like eggs.
I just don't like eating 50 eggs.
You know, it's going to be interesting.
So now that that is out of the way, I'll talk about Randomizer for a little bit
and what's going on right now.
I happened to bonk that heavy, but he ended up getting the kill on me.
Actually, somebody shot me with... I don't even know what the hell...
What gun is that? I've never seen that before.
Well, anyways, this is the part what I was talking about before with the...
I feel like I'm in a blender when I watch this. Oh my God.
This is exactly what I was talking about when I said things just become broken.
As you can see, that's not normal. That is not normal.
You are absolutely not supposed to get electrocuted when you shoot the Tommy Slop.
That's not supposed to happen.
And I found from playing this for a little bit,
the best thing you could possibly get is probably the scout with the minigun.
Or second best would probably be heavy with the medigun.
So you can be a healer with 300 health. It's just mind-boggling.
And the worst loadout you can get is anything to do with a soldier banner.
Because I don't think they even work.
I tried to blow the horn. I had the buff banner at one point when I was playing earlier.
And I got like 9 million damage and it didn't even matter.
I tried to blow the horn. Nothing happened. It just kind of was broken in my hand.
And I'm pretty sure there's a lot of other stuff that's broken as well.
I can't really think on the top of my head right now, but I'm pretty sure engineer buildings.
I don't think you can do them as other classes.
Or the spy disguises or the spy watches.
I'm pretty sure they don't work.
And how funny would that be though?
How hysterical would that be if you could see a heavy kind of crouching in the corner with the disguise mask on his face?
Just sitting there with like the cloak and dagger or something.
Now that would be so awesome.
But this is going to be the end of the gameplay guys.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And come to that livestream this weekend.
6 p.m. Eastern time if you don't know, if you've never been there before.
If you are a long time stream goer, should be a great time, should be crazy.
I wonder how many eggs I'm going to be able to eat.
That's the real question.
Question of the video. Here it goes. Ready?
Here's the question.
How many eggs do you think I'm going to eat in that livestream?
So I look forward to your responses and I'll see you guys all soon.
Take care everybody.