Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2. Playing as the soldier with stock everything.
And this is on King of the Hills sawmill. I'm very, very tired right now. Not sure if you guys can tell, but what? What? What on earth?
That was weird. I haven't slept in a long time. And those of you that know what I'm talking about when I say this, when you don't sleep for a while, you get a little weird and get away.
You get really weird. So I'm in that mode right now where I'm in super tired mode and the world just doesn't exist. Well, actually the world exists. That's a pretty big understatement.
This sniper is so dead. You know what? I just want to shoot him with my shotgun. No, I can't run away. I can't run away. I can't run away. I'm dead.
There was no escaping with that non escape plan. Only 30 seconds. Holy crap. Holy crap crap. Let's go. Get out the door. You bastard jump.
This is I jumped into a pretty close game. Six seconds, seven seconds. Oh, the Oh, no.
Am I like really tired right? Am I just am I hallucinating right there? Was that just a century point in this way and a century point in this way like connected?
All right. Maybe I'm losing it here. No, it really was.
What the hell was that? Oh, yeah. Get that demo man. That's up stairs. But nice sticky just like rolled off.
I think it's made out of jello. Get him. I wish that killed him. That will. Yeah, it will.
Oh, I got mangled. That guy got mangled. What is going on out there? Hold on. I need a bit of vantage point here. That what the what is going on outside again?
I was so distracted by that scout mangling his body in front of me that I lost all concentration. That happens when you get tired.
You look at something like, oh, look, hey, oh, cool. Let me sit here for like five minutes. You lose all track of everything that's going on on your screen.
I'm going to get those sentry guns, though. There's one thing at least I'll try to do is that see if I can't.
OK, you got to be careful. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Look at all that cottage. I just got up. Oh, my goodness gracious. Oh, I'm so I'm done for.
Oh, I'm so done for. I got to know that engineers like mad. Oh, I'm so much trouble. There's nothing I could do.
I didn't think there'd be that many people just like standing there waiting to die. That's interesting. I had this entry still there.
I'll get it again. I'll get it this time. I'll get it this time. It's way too many dudes standing around for me to be able to just go bang, bang, bang.
Soldier, where do you think you're going? And Pyro coming down to spawn. Excuse me, Princess.
Oh, you want to play that game? Oh, you want to play the reflect game? And he's probably I'm probably going to die. Where are you at? Where are you at?
Where the hell did he go? I went out the door. All right. It's time to get rid of this stuff because I can just sit back here and get rid of it.
Get out of here, man. Get out of here, Pyro. Get out of here. This guy's like freaking me out. And I'm going to die from the flames.
No, that was so close. All right. I'm if these stupid things weren't in the way, these saws, I would take all this out right now.
In fact, I am. I'm going to sit back here and take those out. Freaking saws. There we go. It's going bad stuff.
I need that health again. I need this health like so much. Give me, give me, give me.
This guy is moving this all over the place. No. Oh, no. I'm going to burn. Yeah. Get out of the way, saw.
Oh, we got to get this capped. We're going to get flawless. We're going to get destroyed.
Come on. Capt this with me. Capt this point with me, soldier. No, that's not a real heavy. Yes, it is. Get out of the point.
Get out of the point, heavy. We're going to cap this point. Help me. Any medics? I don't think we have any medics.
This is not good. Oh, I know. One of these times I'm going to get hit by that saw. Whoa, I killed myself apparently.
Womp womp. All right. Let's let's win this. Keep him off the point. Oh, this guy. Look at this guy in this crazy position.
Just launching over nades. I think we got this. I'm pretty sure we got this. I think we're in a good position right here.
No, I spoke too soon. Spoke too soon with that one. It's only one guy apparently. Now we're at two guys.
Now we're at like three guys. And now I have like no health. Get that out of here. Get rid of these sentry guns. Geez.
Well, that's good. Oh, I can't even like step out here. I need health. I have to get this health. It's down here.
No, I only have the shovel. I don't know. I can't like run. I keep forgetting. Watch out. Watch out.
Wood. Get out of my way. Wood. Oh, I missed him three times. Damn it. Oh, man. This guy needs one.
Where did he come from? Where did that guy even just come from? Son of a bitch. Oh, don't let him get it.
Don't let him get it. We got to get. We have to stop this. Come on. 55 degrees Celsius. Watch that bang. Headshot. Headshot, baby.
I don't like that. That's not what I like to see, man. We'll get it back. We'll get it back right here. We'll get it back right here.
No, there's the sentries are back. Can I get rid of this son of a bitch? Oh, my goodness. They're like, get out of here, Pyro.
Geez. I'm like burping. I can't even go out here. Oh, I'll get out here. All right. Bounce it off the dispenser.
Man, I can't take this crap out. Don't run up there, man. No, we got. I got a wall bang this. Oh, come on.
Oh, there's nothing I could do here. I'm trying to like wall bang and I can't grab it. Oh, yeah. Cap it. Cap it.
No, no, no, no, no, no. If I stepped out there, I would have got my face shot off.
Well, that is going to wrap it up here, guys. Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time. Hope you enjoyed this tired edition of Facecam Fortress 2.
And I'm going to go get some sleep. So I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.