Hello. Hi. Yes, sorry. I apologize to everybody. It is 420, 20 minutes later than the two hour
later delay that I gave you earlier today. And I apologize for that. I'm very sorry. I'm battling
a headache. I know that's like the easiest excuse to get out of anything, but it's true. I have,
I've had a headache. Weed is legal? Weed's been legal in Las Vegas for like three years.
Hello, how are you? Haven't seen you guys in a while. This is longer than I ever anticipate.
You'll have to wait for a stream. Even being once a week Andy does not mean once every 10 days Andy.
I'd rather it be six or seven days tops. But there's been a lot going on and very soon,
very soon, we'll be able to talk about it. So lots of exciting stuff. Let's just say that
August and September. Holy shit. That's all I'm gonna say.
Let's go. Yeah, let's go. Holy shit. What do you say? Why, why are you streaming? It's Thursday.
You seem like the kind of guy that can sneeze on command. It took a long time to learn how to do
that. Countless hours studying people. Let's go. Yeah, let's go. So today, this is not going to be
a short stream, by the way. I'm gonna play King of Retail. This is a game that looks really good.
I'm very excited for it. You make your own store. You sell products. It's like a chores game. And
you know, that's what I do here. That's like what I play. But yeah, this ain't gonna be like,
we've done like three to four hour streams the last three or four streams. That's not gonna happen
today. Even if King of Retail gets boring, if I don't like it. I'm like, okay, I had my fill.
We still have, I mean, we've got the 2020 Olympics game, video game. That's incredibly important that
we play that. I don't know if it's today, but we'll see. Have I played Papers, Please? I have.
I've got to the point of Papers, Please, where I can't play it anymore. Because once you incorporate
more than four documents, I physically cannot play the game. I can't do it. I actually can't do
it. I always play Papers, Please until you get to four documents and I talk about how much fun it is
and then I don't do it. And I skip it. But yeah, I'm ready to go. I should eat a whopper. Hey,
I'll eat whatever I want. All right. King of Retail. Make sure the face cam's not on.
All right, we're good. There it is. This is King of Retail. We're gonna do new manager,
create a manager and get ready to conquer the world of retailing. All right, let's go.
First name. Should it be me or should it be somebody else? Who should it be? This is a Unity
game? Yeah, every game nowadays is a Unity game. It's free to license. It's cheap and it's easy to
use. I used to say the same thing and then I realized, holy shit, like this is like actually
like really good for independent developers. Don't you have to pay like 40% of your entire
life savings to be able to use Unreal or something? What's the licensing fee for Unreal?
There's something crazy, right? Unity's not free. Well, I'm making that up then. 40% of your soul.
Now, Unreal is free too. After a million dollars, they take a 10% cut. As a developer who uses
Unreal, I have to correct you. All right, then yeah, correct me. All right, yeah, I'm completely
corrected. And it's even got green text. It's got green text. I don't know. I feel like this
would happen if you like character melded me and Elon Musk together. Oh, never mind. Now it's me
and Elon. Now it is. I like this one so far. I like that one. Yeah. Oh, whatever. I say the name wrong.
Elon. Elon. Is Elon? Elon. Elon. Elon. Elon. Elon. Whatever. I kind of like that. I can't even
really make Mr. Green. All right, we're gonna change the character's name because it can't even
be Mr. Green. It's gonna be like, it's got to be a more tame version of Mr. Green. That's even worse.
It's a character from a children's book. John Sale. Cousin Green? Cousin Green. I think that
might be worse than the last one. No, who can't? This guy is just a, this is a side character.
Doesn't matter. All right, that's fine. Are you happy with this manager? Yes, I am. Let's go.
All right, single store mode, campaign mode, or business school. As the owner of a new store,
do you have what it takes to expand your customer base and make a profit? Work for other companies
and earn enough money to found your own and go from managing a small store to large retail chains.
Can you dominate the city? Learn about the game. So this tutorial. Just go flunk out of business
school. This is tutorial. All right, you know you're, you know you're like not doing so well
as a professor when you pump fake crowd sound into your, into your class. He doesn't have to do this.
I'm the only person that signed up for business 101. Welcome to all of you. Please talk to the
instructor to participate in one of our classes. Please be quiet during the lectures. If you have
a question, please raise your hand and yes, stupid questions do exist. I have a stupid question.
Where are all the people? Know your area. Dark horse. Shut up. Oh, there we go. Thank you.
Know your area. Oh God, what the fuck is this? To run a successful store, you want to know more
about the city and the customers that reside in it. Each city consists of a unique mix of customers.
They're categorized into the following segments. Fashion high, low, and wealth low, high. So fashion
low, wealth low is farmer. Fashion low, wealth high is techie. Fashion high, wealth low is student.
Is this how we're measured? The kind of clothing we wear? What? Wealth high, fashion high is
celebrity. Where do you sit on the political compass test? Uh, hipster, techie, accountant,
celebrity. Oh dude, I got celebrity on the political compass test. Okay. So yeah, I get it.
As you can see, the chart shows what each segment looks for when they go shopping. Are they quality
or money oriented? And how important is it that the article is in fashion?
Click to share your results. Click share. I got hipster in the political compass test. What will
you get? Zero likes, zero retweets, zero replies. As if I did that, it would be zero likes, zero
retweets, zero replies. Understand? That's essentially an ad that people have to scroll by.
No one looks at those. Not one person. It's an annoying Twitter ad. A pie chart of the population
could look like this. Farmer, pensioner, student, ecologist, laborer, hipster, techie, accountant,
and celebrity. There's a lot of celebrities that live in this town. Damn. In the chart, you can
see that this city mainly has a low income population, so your assortment of articles
should primarily consist of articles of the lower price range. Okay. Customer flows. The various
segments also have different shopping patterns. So the peak hours for farmers and students may be
different during a given day, but the peak hours for farmers in a workday compared to the weekday
will also vary. Weekends are in general busier than workdays. Well, wouldn't I have to have the
store open at like four o'clock in the morning? Because farmers get up really early. On your
computer, you can see... whatever. Don't forget about article saturation. When you sell articles,
the market will get saturated with those articles. The more you sell an article, the fewer customers
will require it. I just realized I'm just standing up here in the front of the classroom reading
this. No one's teaching me anything. These are sa- these saturations are averaged out over several
days. To tackle this, you can occasionally switch your focus to different articles. All right,
all right. This is important shit, though. We gotta know this. You're standing up on the desk.
All right, this is important shit. Just hold on. When customers go shopping, they have various
needs for the different categories. The customer's need is the most important factor when they go
shopping. If the customer has a big need, they are willing to compromise a lot for the right article.
Whatever. Reputations. All right, just, like, don't have, like, rat shit everywhere and people
will be happy. The store is a reputation with individual customer segments. Those are a reputation
for selling the various article groups. When customers go, look, I'm just gonna- I'm just
gonna sell, like, white t-shirts and, like, sandals. That's- everyone can buy that. That's in fashion
for everybody. Each time you sell something, your reputation goes up. And if a customer leaves angry
and disappointed, your reputation goes down. Before you start buying articles for your store,
you might want to investigate the type of city that you are in. This information is available.
All right. Yo, teach! When is it lunch? Should I do the other stuff? Oh, there's a lot. Know your
article. Managing your articles. Influencing your customers. The art of selling. I already know how
to do this. Managing staff. This is a lot. This is a lot. I think I have to- I gotta read at least
the first three of these, okay? Everybody relax. Know your article. I'm just gonna- I'm gonna skip
through it. I'm gonna do exactly like I did when I was in high school and college. I'm gonna have
to read like two sentences and then get like a D on the test, but still be fine and pass.
All of your articles have various base parameters that make them unique. Price, score, fashion.
Got it. All right. Quality, design, and luxury. Got it. All categories of a city average price.
To see if an article is either expensive or cheap, customers will compare it to the average price.
By decreasing or increasing the price, you can adjust how attractive articles are to certain
groups. Okay. Quality, score. Quality of an article. If it's a very high quality, then all right.
Article fashion. This explains how stylish an article is. This is- this is the blue line
is stylish. A farmer, on the other hand, doesn't mind the fashionability, but doesn't want to pay
extra, okay? Luxury. This is for like the celebrities, right? High luxury. Effort to sell.
That was easy- what? That was the class? This professor sucks. I could have googled this.
That's the most- all right. Managing your articles. Just wait. I'm- not only- I'm gonna do it. I need
to know what to do. Stop it. Guys, fine. You go sleep. Go sleep in the back. I'm up at the
front learning, okay? If you want to sleep, then sleep on your desk. Whatever. Between the moment
you order articles and the moment the customer takes them home, the article usually goes through
the following phases. It has to be delivered? They don't take it from the store. They just point at
it and then I deliver it to them? Okay. When your unit arrives, they're prepared to the warehouse.
Okay. After when the articles are the delivery units, you need to unpack them. Got it? Minimum
storage system. To make things easier, you have access to multiple systems on your computer. One
of them is storage. Okay. Let's just go fail five businesses and like figure it out. You know what
I mean? All right. I'll be all right. Stop shouting. I'm trying to sleep for fifth period.
F. You're gonna get an F. All right. So you have to store stuff. You have to order stuff. Things
have to be delivered with the flow. There's a flow. I got it. All right. All right. I think I'll be
all right. I think I get the general concept of the game. Let me see if there's anything else
important here. Let's go. Let's go. I'm ready. Let's go. If I need to figure it out, I'll figure
it out. How do I leave college? All right. New manager. Wait, no, no, no. Load manager. Wait,
did I just go to school and that's it? Puzzle and green. Okay. Load. Why is he in a different
clothes? All right. Let's do campaign mode. Let's go for it. Campaign. New game. Message from City
Hall. Dear retailer, from what we have heard, you are interested in running your own company in our
city. Before you can do that, you must come to us to prepare the essentials. We'd also like to offer
some advice on how to get it off to a solid start and what the city has to offer. You know,
you can navigate around the city using the WASD keys. The arrow keys are replacing the mouse at
the edge of the screen. You're sincerely the mayor. What a weird last sentence to get. I would think
he was on drugs. This guy is shit faced. Imagine getting this letter. Oh shit. Okay. All right.
Company not founded. Welcome to the city. Before you start on your own, you need to require capital.
Work for hire. Okay. Bills outfits. $16 a day. Very low population. So this is where I have to work?
Holy shit. Look at all this. City, take courses here. Learn more about the game. Oh, that's...
Okay. $16 a day? This is the City Hall. This is permits and then a big baseball field.
I have to work here. This is my first job. $16 a day? That seems like fucking nothing.
Completion bonus $80. All right. Will go work? I have to work? Go to the store. What time is it?
Complete the current contract. You must serve five customers. Congratulations on your new store.
This is your pre-opening day, meaning you have all the time in the world to get your store ready for
the grand opening. We've prepared a list of things to do to get you up and running. That's something
that is that in the store? Bills outfits. Oh, Bill, we got to talk about your sign. Bill, your sign is
like what my school principal had at the end of his desk. It's a name tag. Okay. Buy a delivery unit.
Design, leave store. Normal. We can do fast speed. Oh, shit. Okay. We're not doing that.
I have $2,400. Why do I have to design his store? Buy inventory. Buy a storage unit. Okay. How about
buy inventory? All right. Buy a delivery. So buy inventory. Registers. And you don't need
a register? Okay. Delivery units. $80. All right. What's going to get this one? It has
30 units. Oh, shit. I got to go in here. All right. This makes sense. Right here. This is where I store
stuff for deliveries. All right. Storage unit. 160. Well, I'm just going cheap right now. I'm
just learning how to play. How do I flip? Okay. Order articles. Clothes. Shirts. Okay. Hold on.
Buy inventory. Manage articles. Order articles. Clothes. Shirts. Oh, God. Oh, what do I get?
How about fun and games? I took an arrow to the knee. Should I set up a meme store? Nobody wants
this shirt. That's so stupid. Okay. I'm going to get fun and games. How many do I get? Oh, drag them
here. Okay. One. I buy like 10? I'm going to buy 10 arrow to the knee shirts. Okay. Now I need to
request a delivery. Staff room is tiny. All right. Request delivery. Before you open, all deliveries
are free today. All right. Give me it. I'm on my way with the articles you ordered. See you in a
moment. Where does he go? I'm just going to stand here and look at the door. Imagine having only one
shirt. Oh, GTA. Drop it. All right. Cool. Unpack. Buy displays for your articles. Oh, I have to
actually build the displays. Oh, no. Okay. All right. All right. Wait, what's all this? Oh,
shit. That's where I'm storing the other shirts. Okay. Buy displays. This game actually might be
pretty fun. All right. Design. Manage signs. Design. Buy inventory. Displays. There it is.
Displays. Clothes. Shirts. Do I have the racks in the middle? How many do I have? $320. These
look like things that kids play on at the playground. Okay. What about... All right. We're
going to go with this one. Does it matter? All right. Add articles to it. Edit articles. Design.
All right. Edit articles. Clothes. Shirts. What am I going to have on here? Okay. I could have four
slots. Okay. Pack article. Remove autofill. Manage all spots. Oh, shit. Okay. I think that's all
right. Fill article. Where is it? Okay. If you can't... If you came into this store, you are on a
candid camera TV show. There's no way this is not a hidden camera show or like you're on video and
something crazy is going to happen around you. This is a set. Okay. So add articles. I need more
t-shirts. Okay. I use them all? How many did I buy? All right. Update the store window. Whatever.
Fuck it. Select article to showcase. But what... I don't even have these. Should I just do false
advertising? What am I doing? Final touches. I feel like a roller coaster tycoon shop. Over there
is still... I need to buy a register. Open the register. Buy a computer. Okay. Open a register.
Buy a register. Let's get the... How much money do I have? 1,700? All right. Let's need a little one.
I'll rotate. There it is. It'd be right here. This store is so small. Where do I put this? Okay. Do
I have to sit behind there or do I have to hire somebody? Open the register. Open for customers.
Close register. Design. Wait. I can design the register? Oh no. Okay. This is kind of cool.
Haste? All right. Open the register. Close the queue. Buy... Wait. I need to buy a computer first
before I open. Okay. Buy a computer. Do I have enough money to buy a computer? Registers? Office?
Is this a computer or is this a monitor? Okay. Monitor. Advertise to increase reputation.
Oh shit. All right. This is going in here. Now over here. Do I have to do anything with this? Use.
You can't do that today. Why can't I use the computer? All right. Let's open for business.
How much do these even sell for? I have no idea what these even sell for. Here we go. Open. Welcome
cousin? Oh, my name is cousin. Right. Whatever. Might as well pull the fire alarm. Where are the
customers? The perfect insurance fraud scam. It's pre-opening. Starts end the day? End the day. How
do I end the day? Just leave? Computer? Manage staff. Manage articles. Manage signs. How do I
just end the day? Leave store? Go to the office. Wait. No. Didn't I go to business school? Close
the register. I think I did already, didn't I? That it? Go to office? My office is in here.
This is going to just teleport me in there? Daily payment? No, I didn't even make any money. Why
do I have to pay rent? Can I just work here? When your store closes, this is where you go to finish
up the day and go to prepare for the next in here. You have all the time in the world to do what needs
to be done before opening tomorrow. To interact with any of these objects, go to press E. Walk away,
press escape. All right. Let's take a look at what you can do. This is the catalog designer. This is
where you can design various advertisements to be put in magazines that are read all over the city.
Okay, that sounds fun. These can give a boost to your reputation, increase the needs of the
customers, as well as temporarily increase the number of people passing by your store.
I think it's exactly, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Whoa. Expanding and rebuilding the store.
You can manage the layout of your store and if you own it, also expand the store itself. Green tiles
are your sales space. Yellow are your storage. Blue are your staff rooms. Oh, shit. You can add
free standing walls and edit the size and shape of your rooms. When changing the rooms, remember
to make sure that there's a door leading to the main area. This is way more detailed than I thought
it was going to be. Holy shit. Game auto saves each time you enter or leave the office, so don't worry.
But if you have changes you want to keep, you can also save and quit the game from here. Oh my god.
Today's results. You can see this game actually could be really, really, really good. Really good.
We're going to find out. You can also see statistics on your sales performance. Green represents
income and red is expenditures. All right. So yeah, but I had to put some inventory in the store.
Here's the schedule for your employees. You can assign working hours, lunch breaks, tasks, and days
off on a weekly basis. Is everybody only working on Thursday? We all come in on Thursday and then
no one is in the store for five or six straight days. To change a schedule, move the mouse to an
hour. Click and hold the left mouse button and then move the mouse to a different hour and release
the button. Add a lunch break design. Click the right mouse button on the desired hour. Oh my god.
This is going to be so much fun. Courses and talents. At this board, you can view and manage
your staff individually. That guy's name is Jerma. Other than viewing their personal information,
you can see their talents and send them on courses as well as promoting and doing wage
renegotiations. This is your personal computer. Here you can do various things. Okay. As well
as ordering articles, you can see various stats regarding sales and customers. Use this to analyze
your store and prepare for the next day. If you're in a pinch, you can also apply for a loan to get
extra money immediately. They have to be paid back with interest, right? This is your application
inbox. It contains letters from the various persons who want to work at the store. Each
application contains hints about the skill and experience of the person behind. If a person
sounds interesting, you can start the interview process from here. Will you learn more about the
person and negotiate a wage? What? What is all this? This is too- this is insane. This is the
negotiation table. This is the table where you conduct your interviews. When an interview has
ended in an agreement, the contract itself lies on the table for you to sign. You can then hire
the person, discard the contract, or simply let it be until you are ready to decide. Here's- here you
can set the operating hours of the store. Simply click the arrows to increase the desired times.
Wait, can I have a 24-hour store? Oh. City regulations allow stores to have- to be open from
2 to- oh shit, it's uh- it's military. This always fucks me up. I have to count backwards. I don't
know what that- I don't know what time that is. Is that 11 o'clock? PM? No, that's 10 o'clock.
That's 10- is it 10? That's 10 PM, right? I don't use military time. I don't- whatever. I have- can
I change that? Subtract 12. I don't- I don't- I don't- it's- it's hard to look at. I know it's like
so- it should be so simple. We shouldn't- we should always- it's- why do we start over at 12, right? I
know. It should just be 24 hours in a day, so it's 24. I get it. I know. Trust me. It gets hard.
All right, so that we can uh- when the store is open, that's cool. As a manager, you always meet
in one hour before the store opens and leave one hour after it closes. Oh, what? I'm like 20 minutes
late to my own streams. I'm gonna come in an hour early? I'm gonna- I don't think I'm gonna be able
to do that. An hour early. If you can- if you change the hours to also check your staff schedule,
this will automatically update. Okay, cool. On Friday, there's sightseeing for pins? What does
that say? A picnic? A pins? What does that say? Pensic? What's pensic? Okay, so this is if people
are gonna be in the area, they're gonna be sightseeing, they're gonna want binoculars,
they're gonna want uh- uh- cockies, right? They're gonna want cargo shorts. I get it.
Okay, here we go. I'm kind of overwhelmed, but I'm really into this. I only have $1,100. This- I- I-
oh, I'm- wait, I'm- I have a bird's eye view of the store? Shit, okay. I only have $1,139
to run- I have to run a whole store like this? All right. Advertising. Let's- no, no, no, no, no.
Fuck that. I have like a bunch of shitty shirts. I have to go in there and fix that.
What's the schedule look like? Where's the schedule? No, there's nothing on there. Where's
that schedule? You have no staff? What? I thought I just had like 10 employees. Where's- where's
where's Jermarcus? I don't have any staff? Oh, that was just a lie. All right, do I sleep on the couch?
All right, I'm ready. What's today? Okay, so on Friday, there's a sightseeing for a pensic.
A tourist group of 20 people are visiting your area from the pensioner segment. All right, we
get- by Friday, we get to load a bunch of pensioner stuff in here. Let's go. I made $1? Guys,
I found that on the ground on the walk to the store. All right, this is not- okay, let's go,
let's go, let's go. All right, no more of this meme shit. I want to actually have a business,
you know what I mean? Do I have $1,100? The pensioners like this? Let me see. Edit articles.
What- clothing. All right, what do I got? Shirts. How can I tell? How can I tell? Design the
inventory? Design the interior? Holy shit, hold on. Oh, should I just have like- should it be a reptile
store? Oh, the store's not open. I gotta open the store right now. Hurry, hurry, hurry. Come
on, come on, come on. Open store. Open store. Open the store. Open. Come on in. Buy a t-shirt.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. A grand opening of Bill's Outfits. I would literally anyone go to this
store. I need to make money somehow. What about the computer? Who am I talking to somebody?
Student? Pensioner. What's this? Am I like making a Reddit thread? What am I doing?
Oh, fuck. Somebody's in here. I gotta get off Reddit. Come on in. Anything you like? Hi. Spare
two seconds. What? This is a celebrity. I'm thinking of buying this, but I'm not quite sure.
Begin sale. All right, fuck. Why do I have to do this? Improve customer happiness.
Is this guy peeing? Oh, I thought he was peeing. This is perfect for you. And it's, um, a success
rate. Um, and let's- and tell me more? What- just fucking buy the shirt. What are you talking about?
Buy it. Keep- keep this between us. Finish the sale. Buy it. What the fuck was that? What do you
want? Nice. All right. Good, good, good. What was that all about? Oh shit. I'm actually making money.
What? Are they confused? Why are you confused? Are these people not aware they're going?
Come on in. There's six t-shirts left. How many of you are out there? What? Come on. What do you
mean they can't path? Why? I need more inventory. I- all right. I get more inventory. Just wait.
What time is it? All right. It's 11 for- it's- it's almost noon. Come on in. I haven't seen this
store before. What do you sell? Shirts. We have a wide selection of shirts. I have no interest in
that at the moment. Can I interest you in a shirt? Sounds interesting. All right. Go buy one. Thanks.
You're welcome. You want me to buy something? Yep. Just wipe out all my stupid shitty meme
inventory so I can actually play the game. They're stealing? No they're not. There's five shirts left.
Hey, can I help you? We sell shirts here. I don't know if I like shirts.
Do you like shirts? I don't like shirts. Let me- let me tell you something. We got- you remember
the arrow to the knee joke? We got that here. There's only a few of them left. And let me also
tell you that we've also got a improved conversation rate. I- what does this even mean?
It's very interesting. Yes it is. Didn't want it. Can I buy mo- I gotta buy- okay. Inventory. Um,
how about- can I sell cash registers? Would I do that? That'd be kind of cool.
Manage signs. No, I can only buy shirts. Shirts, okay. Inventory. Oh, I need to buy- wait, wait,
it's- it's- it's manager articles. Okay, there it is. Order articles. I can only- can buy shirts.
Okay, I have too many of these. Oh, fuck. Hold on. Hey, can you help me? Just a minute. Hold on.
Congratulations. You met the terms of our agreement and we're very pleased with your
reference. We thank you for the cooperation and a job well done. See you in the future.
On the board of directors. What? I only had to work for one day? You sold three shirts. That was
just a drug front. They just hired me to pretend to sell stuff while they did drug deals in the
back for like a week. And then I'm the guy that- I'm the fall guy. I'm the one that- I'm the one
that's gonna go to jail. On a budget. Okay, what are we looking for here? Selling shirts and shoes.
Achieve a turnover of at least $1,600. Okay. What about the other one? Is there more than one?
No, it's just this one. All right. I have to build a solid financial foundation.
Okay, let's go. We need to sell shirts and shoes. Total sales is currently at zero. I need to sell
$1,600 worth of merchandise. Okay. Oh shit, this is already here. That's literally the red shelf
right there. That's the exact thing that I have. All right, so thankfully all this stuff's already
here. We got a computer. We got delivery units. The shirt's already in here. There are shirts
already in here. So let me put these. Cool. All right, let's make a display. Edit articles here.
Clothes. Shoes. Let's put flip-flops over here. Flip-flops. One, two. Yeah, put them everywhere.
Okay, add them. Okay, there's flip-flops. Um, how can I- why can I manage spots? Where's-
this is spot one? How come I can't put any on the other side? Remove that. Okay. Shoes. Oh, well,
the sneaker's on this side. All right, that looks good. Fill it up. Wouldn't that be- this is, uh,
one, right? What the hell? Fill. Add the articles. Why is it not doing it? You only sell one shoe at
a time. Because aren't these on two already? This business is doomed. I- remove articles. Okay,
take them off. What am I doing wrong? Okay, that's what I want in the spots. Made it- yeah,
that's what I want. So fill it up. Okay, what the fuck is that? All right, good. What do I have for
shirts? Or two- we're gonna go over here? Yeah, this is fine. Load it all up. You need more meme
shirts? When I make my own business, then we'll do whatever we want. I need to get to that point
first. All right, what else do I have? Clothes. Shirts. Oh, I have no more shirts. Should I get
some more shirts? I gotta put some more shirts over here. All right, well, I'll get some meme
stuff. Fine. Buy delivery unit. All right, let's do it. Okay, inventory. Delivery unit. 80. That'd
be a Rick and Morty shirt store. I don't need to do that. Hot Topic already does that. Okay,
that looks good. Hot Topic is just such a Rick and Morty store. I'm surprised that the employees
don't do the voices. They should be dressed up in Rick and Morty costumes, doing Rick and Morty
accents and impressions and stuff. All right, all right, Morty. Look, I got one Rick and Morty
keychain, one Pickle Rick, and a Morty- and a poster from season two. Oh, have a nice day.
Shut up, Morty. No, I'm turning into, like, Alex Jones. Shut up, Morty. Let me start with
Morty. Morty, not a Morty. All right, I gotta buy something. I want to do this shit. All right,
hold on. Goku? Don't I already have a storage unit? I have, like, three. Why do I have to buy
more of these? I already have a bunch of these. Why would I need to- this- I can't even put this
anywhere. All right, I want to get this right. Clothes. Shirts. What's this? These anime t-shirts?
All right, yeah, we're gonna just do a bunch of anime t-shirts. I can't even see what that is.
How many- let's do five? Four of each? Five of each? How much goes on- what goes on one rack?
Four or five? Is it five? Air it! Okay, now give me that delivery. I'll put the anime shirts in the
window. You look like Captain Kirk. Perfect. You know, okay, you know those Halloween stores where
all the employees are dressed up in Halloween costumes and stuff? I wish that was in more stores.
It'd be so cool if, like, Captain Kirk was just walking around talking to you about merchandise
and stuff. I'd be like, holy shit, this is cool. I mean, Hot Topic. No, Hot Topic, they don't, like,
dress up as, like, they're getting characters or anything. That would be hell for the workers.
What would be whoever wanted to do that? Oh, by the way, they get paid extra. You're getting paid
extra to do that, too. Dude, I would want whole acting sequences to play out in my store. Imagine
you're at a Best Buy. You're just sitting there looking at headphones, and all of a sudden, like,
a- like, a pirate's- like, a pirate ship rolls in, and they're like, oh, land ho! And they're
looking around like, can any landlubbers point me in the direction of the televisions?
It'd be hilarious. It'd be like, holy shit, there's pirates here. It'd be like going to Disney.
And by the way, I heard that this land in particular had 40% off their Vizio TV section.
And, like, they grab a guy, like, throw him overboard. They make him, like, walk a plank
into, like, a pool. You would shop there all the time. I know you would. I would, too.
Where is this guy? Did he already come in? Wait, did I just completely miss the guy coming in
and delivering? Oh, shit, he- I did. I was not even paying any attention. That's just a renaissance
fair. It kind of is. Who would want to walk the plank? I don't know, I- if you have, like,
a circus background or something, I don't know. Okay, there's one more rack. I need one more.
Nah, whatever, who fucking cares. It would cause customers to cringe away in fear of being seen
in that store. I don't think so. No, it wouldn't. I would- you would think it was, like, I would
think it- wouldn't you think it was funny? Buy displays for your articles. Okay. I need to-
Buy displays. This? Buy displays for your articles. Floor sign? Ceiling sign. God. Um,
is it lit? No. That's way too much money. Where is it? You can't even see that. Sorry,
to the naked eye if you walk to the store, that's like, like, a bug trap. That's not a display.
Buy displays for your articles? Wait, I already have them. Oh, what the hell? You already- they're
already in here. What? I just got virus detected? What the fuck are you talking about? All right.
Um, what's the cheapest one I can do just to get this off? Okay, there we go. Well, I gotta
buy more shit now, right? I gotta buy more clothes. All right, let's buy- I need five.
How many can fit on here? I can do 10. So I need 15 shirts. What should it be? Let's see. Manage
articles. 15 shirts. Uh, I'm gonna complete the anime rack. Wait, sweaters? What about just like
a button-up shirt? Lock guy? Um, sure. Why not? Okay, what else? And I'll just have like a whole
rack of just- these- these just button-ups. Oh, these are kind of cool. No, no, all right,
here we go. Sportswear. It's gonna be a sportswear. Here we go. This is a lot of money, but I'm doing
it. All right, update your store windows with, uh, what do I want to showcase here? I think you
subpar umpire for the 10 community subs. Appreciate it. Why can I put stuff in the windows that I don't
actually have? Well, I have a lot of these. You can lie, but yeah, why would I want to lie to my
customers? All right, I'm also gonna have a bunch of the sports shit. So I'm gonna have- I'm gonna
put sportswear in the window. Where is it? It's right here, right? Where is it? Sportswear.
Yeah, all right. Yeah, I got these. This is giving me actual retail PTSD. I hated doing this at my
store when I worked there. Oh, sure. Oh, I'm sorry. Okay, clickbait window Andy. No, I'm not-
How is this clickbait? I actually own this stuff. Where are my shirts? Oh, I have to unpack.
That should be a sprint. Remember, the back room looks like it's an Invader Zoom.
I like tacos and pancakes.
Wow, do you hate that show too? What, do you hate that show too, guys? You all hate that show?
Everybody hate that show too? That was a terrible impression. I don't have the robot filter on.
That's what he said, and Gurr talked about how he liked like tacos. That all I can fit. Oh shit.
Well, I'll fill it back up later. Everybody hates Invader Zoom. No, they don't. I thought
the show was pretty good. All right, I'm ready to open store. Let's go. Can I do anything with
that sign? I already did all this shit. I don't know. I'm not gonna buy the stuff that's already
here. No, no, I'm not gonna do that. Let's go. Where are all the customers? This is day zero.
Oh, okay. Well, I'm running out of money. All right, let me just- Let's go. Let me make some
money. I need to make 1600 bucks. The dollar that I found on the ground. Perfect. Store is open.
Here they come. Do I have a staff? I don't have that much money. Actually open the store.
It's not open. Yes, it is. It's open for customers. The shop is not open. What?
Door is opened. Wait, I had to physically go and open the door? God damn it. I missed out on so
many people. I heard Jermarcus. That's gonna be my first hire. Somebody come in here. You guys
take way too long walking on the road. Everybody in. I got shirts. I got shoes. Get in here. What
the fuck? It's open. Look. What? I haven't seen this store before. What do you sell? We sell shoes.
We have a wide selection of shoes. If the perfect one shows up, I might buy it. All right. You want
some shoes? Did I set one aside for you? Handsome success. All right. Improve the customer success
rate. What the fuck does any of this even mean? Tell me more. Come buy it. Thanks. You're welcome.
All right. Come on in. Did you catch the game last night? What grade are you in school? Do you
have the lasagna? It's my favorite. I love that guy. I love that. I love that infomercial so much.
Like one of my favorite things ever. 70 bucks. That's a lot. 49. All right. Come on. Need help
over there? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't, don't, don't leave. Don't leave. Don't leave.
Okay. 104 bucks. Holy shit. Nice. Come on in. Looking for shoes. I got sandals and I got
sneakers. Which one? Need help? Nope. You're good. Oh, God damn it. All right. Hold on. Does
this guy want to buy something? They're shirts and shoes. I'm thinking of buying this, but I'm not
sure. Okay. It's very popular. It's very popular. You should get it. Holy fuck. You were just not
pleasable. Not sure what to look for. What do you recommend? Click on an article. Um, what do I have
the most? Oh, the most expensive one. That's perfect. Good. Fuck. Hold on. Hold that thought.
Okay. I need Steph. He's so scary. Do you want to come in? Looking for shoes. Yep. I got them here.
Oh, and for the Pickle Rick shirt, I would highly recommend it. And you're going to go for a pair
of shoes too. Yep. Red sneakers. You got it. Get them both. Get them both. That was a lot. That's
like a hundred bucks. Stand and face the ball until a customer comes in. Okay. Is it weird that like,
if I ever ran a business like this, I would like, you would get a bonus if you did this.
And if it, like, I would give you 50, I would add 50 to a hundred dollars onto your wage,
like for this day. If you, if you did that for like half an hour or something, like it'd be funny.
And then when somebody's like, excuse me, you go, you turn like screaming, like you're like,
like they startled you. Can I help you? I'm making actually a pretty good amount of money.
And I would like come down as like the boss and be like, what's going on in here? We'd be like,
we do it like a big play. Like eventually like a slime would drop on me and everyone would like
cheer. Like the, like the, the, the, the annoying boss got like fucking slimed. Oh shit. I need more
shoes. They're really popular. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. You better pay them well
to put up with all that. Oh, absolutely. Absolutely. Give you back to streaming in a week.
Oh, I need to buy stuff. I need to buy more shoes. I need to buy expensive shoes.
Eilish. Here we go. What do we go? What's expensive? 41, 48. That's it. I'm like really
expensive shoes. Really expensive. We're going to get like just a bunch of loafers. Hello. Delivery
$45. What the fuck? What time is it? And get two shirts. 27 bucks. What? It's kind of expensive.
I'm loading up the shoes. Hold on. The store is closed. Somebody's still in here. Door's closed.
Unpack this inventory. Let's go. On the office, office computer, you can adjust the markup.
Really? Okay. I can put more sportswear out there. Nobody's buying the sportswear. I need to,
okay. I need like a sign or something. Yeah. I need, I got to, I got to advertise or something.
Manage signs. Sign on the wall. Huge. Behind this. Say like, here's the sportswear. What the
fuck just happened? Did I pass out? I blacked out. Okay. That actually scared the shit. I thought
something was wrong with my computer. I thought I was about to get a weird message or something.
I actually had a small internal panic for a second. I was like, what the fuck is going on?
I got to tell you guys about a dream I had. I don't, I need some dream detectives to tell
me what the hell's wrong with me. You want me to do it now? I do it now? Because I actually need
to know why this happened. All right. Lay it on me. Here we go. Okay. So I had a dream that I was
driving around with some friends in a car and we'd been coming back from a store and I was
driving, I think one of my friends home. By the way, it was not in my car. I was in an old,
like kind of beat up old fashioned car. It wasn't even mine. So get near this person's neighborhood.
Okay. Yeah. I know where you live. Get out here. And when I turned the corner to go into the street,
I noticed something very bizarre. It's a small street. It was like a little cul-de-sac. There
were maybe 15 houses, maybe 15 houses total on this road. And all in every yard, just walking
around aimlessly lying down, like just bathing in the sun and shit, are tigers and lions.
They're everywhere. Some of them have like blood all over their mouths. Some of them are like kind
of running around. It had to have been like 20 to 30 tigers and lions, at least. It was like,
what the fuck is going on in your neighborhood, dude? Why are there tigers everywhere? They're
everywhere. And it's like, keep the doors closed because they were like walking around. Like I'm
almost like if you're on a safari and it's like, holy shit, like the elephants are coming over here.
It was, it was weird. So I kind of freaked out and I was like, what do I do about this? I was
going really slow. I was going maybe like five miles per hour, maybe two miles per hour because
I didn't want to hit any of the cats or anything. I was just like going slow, trying to navigate
around. And I was like, I need to tell people about this. Like this is fucking horrible. This
is a neighborhood. So I'm just like, I got to do this. So I held the horn down. I was going like
while I slowly drove around this neighborhood, trying to, I don't know, warn everybody in the
neighborhood, be like a big alarm. I was like, people need to know this is horrible. And I
did that for maybe like a full loop around the cul-de-sac. And over on the left side,
one of the houses, the door opens, the front door of this person's house, just
and it was a lady and I couldn't really see her because she was kind of behind the door. The door
just kind of opened and she just screams, I'm not going to do the roar. It was like, what the fuck?
And like 10 lions sprint into her open door and you just hear like,
like crashes, plates breaking and like fucking smashes and stuff. This lady was getting
mauled by like 10 tigers and I'm sitting there going, oh my fucking God. Oh my God. What the
fuck did I do that? Did me beeping the horn cause her to like open the door? And did she even,
did these people know that there are tigers out here? Am I, did I kill that lady? And like I saw
a couple other houses like start to stir a little bit. Like you heard noises and I'm like, oh my
God, I'm going to kill this whole neighborhood. What did I do? I was trying to warn everybody.
And the whole time I'm panicking. So we got, I'm like, all right, one of the, by the way,
one of the tigers was like up looking at the car, like kind of running at the car, like
doing like that thing that cats do where they go like, and they like their faces like go like,
did that make any sense? Do you guys know what I'm saying? I can't do that sound. That probably
sounded insane. No. Okay. Let me try to do that better. It's like, I can't do it. It's a fucking
cat noise. I'm a human being. So, but anyways, it was like going after the door. So I just hear
this. I keep hearing screaming coming from this lady's house and other people. I'm thinking,
I just think I might have just, I think, did I kill everybody in this neighborhood
by warning them? Why would I hold the horn down? Like people, maybe people don't even know that
there's tigers here. What's wrong with me? So finally we get out of the neighborhood. Like I,
we can't, I got to get out of here. We got, I don't know what to do. So I go home. I go home
and my mother, I open the door and first of all, the weird part about this is after getting out
of the car, my friend had a shopping cart. Like, oh yeah, like he just had a shopping cart. Like
he was in the car. It was like two or three frozen food items. I don't know. So he's just pushing it
as a guy. That's what we just did. So we go into the house. My mother's on the phone. She's looking
at me. Yup. Oh, um, yup. He's here. Oh, that's not good. Oh no. Yup. He's here. And I'm sitting
there going, that's the cops. That's the cops. And like, I killed, I like, I killed that lady.
Like I was just trying to warn everybody and like now I'm not going to go to jail or something.
I'm going to have to go to the, I'm going to talk to like a detective. I don't know. I'm,
I'm fucked. And she's just staring at me. So finally she's like, okay. Yup. He's here. He's
here. And she hangs up the phone. I'm like, uh, like who's, uh, who's that ma? She goes,
oh, that was your sister. She's at the bank. And then I woke up. I have no idea what that meant.
I have absolutely no idea. But let me tell you something. When I like seeing the tigers with the
blood all over their mouths, like they would, they had been feeding. I don't even, I don't even know
on what, maybe on other animals on each other. That was probably 20 to 30 tigers in this little
neighborhood. I'm not going to do the roar. Like what is that supposed to mean? It's fucking crazy.
Do the roar. Yeah. I have one thing that I always wanted to do and maybe I'll like,
I have to have more crazy dreams though, but at some point I think it'd be really funny
to do a stream where I hire a handful, like a handful of animators and they just animate
not just my dreams, but other people's dreams in the community. Do you know how many insane
things we've heard people say, oh yeah, I had this dream dude that like, you know, you were a
fucking magician and you teleported to three different planets and then you like, uh,
captured me. Like we've heard some really wacky shit before and like I have wacky dreams too.
It'd be kind of fun to have like a fully animated, like here's like the 10 insane dreams that I had
and then some from the community. I don't know. Do the roar. You should have seen it though.
You should have seen it. The second the door opened and she screamed, it just every, all the
cats went just heads tilted, like at least seven or eight of them that were in her lawn.
And it was just immediate just sprint, sprint, sprint, sprint, sprint into her door. And just,
it was just carnage. You heard some of the most awful sounds I've ever heard in my entire life,
ever. But anyways, didn't I have a dream before about a tiger mauling a guy and he's like,
oh, hold on, I got to get my cigarettes. Right? I told you about that one. What's with the tigers?
Why do I keep seeing tigers and lions? That's at least the second or third time in the last year
that a tiger has mauled somebody in one of my dreams. What does that mean? It means you're a
furry. Well, if I was a furry, wouldn't I be one of the tigers? Like, wouldn't I have the POV of
watching the people in the car drive around the neighborhood while I'm just baking in the sun?
Whoa. All right. Well, how do I, I need a staff. Where do I get a staff? Wait, somebody has it?
Somebody have the actual, wait, wait, wait. See one of the big cats in your dream represents
the feminine aspect of which you have neglected or overlooked. You may also be looking for
excitement in your social sphere or in your life. The dream of a large pride of mixed cats
symbolizes that you have not allowed your true self to shine through. I feel like that's not real.
No, but hold on a minute. This is where it's different. It's not just me seeing a bunch of
tigers. It's the fact that they were like terrorizing a neighborhood. Does that change
things? I didn't just drive by and see a tiger. These tigers were literally mauling people.
There's a ton of them. All right. I just freaked out for a second. I looked over at the preview
on OBS. I thought this was my desktop. I was like, what the fuck happened? What's this one say?
The dream meaning of a ferocious tiger means you don't act according to your expectations.
Some people who live around you might be afraid of the way you work with them
and you hurt their feelings. Be more careful with your actions. The way you talk to others,
be careful not to act on impulse. That's what the fuck are you talking about? That's not even,
give me another one. Your ego is telling you that you're hurting the people around you, but your
ID is telling you to stop seeing patterns where there are none. That sentence doesn't make any
sense. The tiger in dream is an embodiment of freedom, power, intuitive understanding, strength,
courage, optimism, free spirit, and protection. This mighty animal also reflects your subtle
emotions and feeling of being restrained. Okay, but this person says, I actually study psychology.
Tigers attacking others in dreams normally means that you have many obstacles going on right now
and aren't fully paying attention to them. Also, the blue is wheezer blue. What blue? Seeing
feline animals, particularly violent ones, is an embodiment of imminent danger, more so danger of
you pooping your pants. He he ha ha ha. Good. Somebody said, it means you've got to collab with
neanners. All right, I'm reading one more of these and that's it. They indicate raw power and
emotions. They're also a symbol of sexuality. Tigers are also a sign of vitality and good health.
They also indicate unpredictable and aggressive behavior and uncontrollable urges. This dream
might reveal having some vices and bad habits you can't control or get rid of. A tiger is a
symbol of persistence as well. It warns you now it's not the time for change and about the need
to have patience in order to achieve your goals. Hmm. Tigers apparently mean everything, yeah.
No joke, I had a dream where I invited Jerma to DJ my cousin's kindergarten graduation and he
kept making unfunny jokes and people were staring at me angry because I brought him. That's pretty
good. All right, one more. The tiger represents something you can't control in your life and it's
giving you anxiety. At least that's what I think based on how you've reacted in your dream.
Okay, I understand that one. If you dream of being attacked by tigers, which I wasn't, I like,
I was the catalyst to somebody else getting attacked, right? Like I held the horn down
trying to warn people of the imminent danger and I actually killed them because of it, right?
There's got to be something there. Okay, here we go. Last one. This is really interesting though.
Dreaming of ferocious animals and animal attacks means that there is an aspect of yourself you're
not letting show. It can also be a sign that you are repressing your inner catboy maid.
Oh, okay, thank you. It means that there are many things in your life that you think are hurting or
affecting you in a bad way and the tiger represents the feeling of fighting back these things.
It also could mean five billion dollars has been added to the debt, you fucking sleazy gambling
piece of shit. Roar for chat. Oh my god. Sleazy. All right, let's go. But that was a crazy dream,
wasn't it? I'm not gonna do the roar. Lady, oh god. So I need, let's log out. I need to hire
somebody. I have to have a staff. Oh, here we go. No, no, I want to see this. Article stats,
quality, fashion, luxuries. People want quality right now. That's what that means, right? So
people are looking for quality and luxury right now. Video Vivi just gave 20 immunity subs. How
do I hire staff? Minimum storage, summary. Where do I get staff? Oh, here we go. Applications.
There's nobody, nobody's applied to the job. Okay, daily news, price hunters. All right,
we're gonna do price hunters. It's gonna be a huge ad for our shirts. Place category,
at place customer. All right, Matt, it's gonna be for two days for our shirts. Create the
advertisement. What am I doing? How do I, I don't get it. It's too big. Oh shit, okay. 50, I'm not
doing 50% off. What an awful ad. How do I shrink this? This is just like, you get this in the mail
when your mother invites like the, like six of you to a birthday party. I can't fit them? Yes, I can.
Techies. Oh boy, they just have blue shirts on? Oh shit, wait, wait, wait. Okay, this is the one.
This is the shirt I'm trying to sell. They're like a hundred bucks each. All right, get rid of this
one. Get rid of these two. Place it. No soup for you. Thank you for the 10 community steps. Place it.
Put it down. Why can I not put it down? What the fuck? What's going on? Magazine, price hunters. Oh
shit, fashion land. The golden coin. All right, how about fashion land? I can't even move any
of this stuff now. All right, well this is the ad now. I, whatever. I don't care. Two days, buy it.
Okay, so that's going. Anything going on? No. All right, let me get back in the store. Let's go.
I didn't find any money on the ground. Does this game have gamba? Gambling? All right. How's the
inventory look? I need to fill this up with shoes. With new shoes. What do I got? Didn't I get some
new stuff? I did. All right, these are expensive. Okay, do I have enough? I need a sign for these.
Give me a sign. Design, a sign. On the wall. Right here. Thank you, Germafans69 for the 10
community subs. We've got a lot of subs. You guys are subbing it up. Change. Oh, okay, here we go.
Current type. You're assigned to select. Oh, shit. All right, all right, all right. Now I make it.
I don't have money. What? Holy shit, I only have $215. What? When did that happen? Okay, now I need
to editor. Oh, shit. Type. It's a fashion. What is it? Oh, fuck. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. Um, do I draw on this? Load poster? Quality? How do I do this? Click background?
There are people. Why are there people in the store? The store's not even open. What?
Why is the store open? I'm not sure what to get. That. Looks promising. Go get it. Yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Great. Cool. Cool. Cool. I need. Okay, leave. Oh,
my fucking God. Customer needs. Improve impact of conversation. Article hype. Hype up the article.
Improve the impact. Refill the patience. Go for it. Thank you. Okay, that was such a pain. That's
too much work. Hire help. I need. I don't. I need to hire somebody. I thought that lady wanted a
pizza. All right, come on. Go buy the expensive stuff. Import an image of your face. Uh, somebody
give me one. Make sure it's something easy like a PNG. Wait, I mean, somebody give me one. The
links are dead. Do I have one? How do I pause the game? Hold on. Do I have a picture of my face,
like on my desktop somewhere? Do the sus guy? No. Sus face. Fine. Fine. Just I'll take sus face.
Give me the sus face. I'll take it. It's got to be one of the mods that does it because the links
have been nuked. Uh, that, but that's not the sus face though. That's the regular face. I hate
this image. I almost just set this as my desktop background. That would have scared the shit out
of me later. All right. Let me drag it in here. All right. Let's see if this is easy. Let's see
how easy this is. It's just as simple as they're just dragging it into this folder. Let me see.
What's it called? All right. Uh, it's, it's in there. I wonder if it worked. Let's find out.
Pause the game. Oh shit. What happened? There we go. I'm like in windowed mode now. What the
hell happened? What happened to my screen? All right. Well, I wish I could just fucking tell
everybody to leave. Tell about your shirts. Just fucking buy something or don't. Buy something or
don't. Leave. Oh my God. I need somebody to talk to her. Okay. Whatever. I need to hire somebody.
Load important new image. What the fuck? Uh, this is not, hold on. That is not what I thought that
was going to look like. Okay. What if I do that? I, I, this is, I have no idea what this means.
I don't have that many guys. I don't have that many drives. I have one drive. I don't have 20,
I don't have 26 hard drives. It would be fucking insane. It's in the game files.
I dragged it into the folder. See? I don't think that's going to work. Hold on. By the way,
you know what? Just a fucking, I don't, I don't, I got to fix the screen too. Why do I cut? The
screen got cut off. Hold on a second. I got to stay. Oh fuck. I'm losing customers. Just stand
at this thing. Whatever. I just sold that to nobody. I think I just took that guy's money.
All right. This is okay. Here's my biggest problem with games that have like an import image feature.
It's always seems to be so like difficult to use. Like this should be simple. Okay. Editor,
load an image. Oh my Lord. Yeah. This is like every one of my drives, but I don't even have
any of these program files. Yeah. I'm not, I don't want you guys to see what kind of programs I have.
What, where is, where is steam? Steam, steam apps. Common. Yeah. I don't want that. This is like,
this is spoilers for the games I'm going to play like next week. King of retail,
king of retail logos. Germa sus fatal error. The game has crashed. What the fuck?
Okay. I hope it's saved. What the fuck? Yeah. That showed every steam game I have installed.
I don't want you guys to see the games. I'm coming up like in, I'd like it to be a surprise.
It was a virus. I don't think so. Oh, where was I? I kind of chose to make my own store. Yeah. I
want to, okay. This is cool and everything, but I don't really want to, I want to make my own store.
Yeah. This is all right. This is much, this is what I'm talking about. All right. Population size.
There's 667,000 people here. Should be huge. How about a small, a city or a million people?
This one. Okay. Yeah. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It don't matter. Whatever.
City's wealth. They have a lot of money or are they, is it lower? How much is the middle of the
road here? Ashen cents. Um, I don't know. Maybe like here. That looks good. Okay. New store.
Select, select categories. Food, food and computers, food and beverages and computers.
No, just food. I was gonna, it's just gonna make a restaurant. Food and drinks. No, just food.
Select a logo. I can't, I can't. That's it. Oh, okay. Joe custom. I can't, where am I? I tried
to upload it. Where is it? Oh no. Is there a burger one? I didn't see the burger. Where is it?
Mayo burgers. I'm probably the one with the apple. Get stuffed. It'd be different blue like this.
No, that looks too like tech. This looks too tech. Orange. There we go. It looks good. Stuffed with
mayo. Okay. That's fine. Whatever. Can I make the logo a different color? Whatever. Main colors.
Orange and um, I don't know, like something like, like a, like orange and green, like a harvest.
That looks good. What's wrong with that? Nickelodeon. Yeah. They close Nickelodeon
studios, by the way. What? What's all that about? I can't, you know what? They close Nickelodeon
studios in Universal in Orlando, right? To make room for what? The fucking minions ride? That's,
all right. I have four. I thought it was four million. I can't look at this. This has to change
immediately. All right. So what do I want for the floor? Why is everything orange? Like I have to
fit the theme of the store. All right. Should I have as you will close? Ooh, I kind of like that.
Actually don't like it anymore. I kind of feel like I'm in a pizza oven. Tiger. Um, this is ugly,
but I already bought it. All right. Walls. Fortnite. This is Fortnite. It is. No, ugly.
All right. Should I make every bonus level in Mario Sunshine? Okay. I hate this, but whatever.
And the ceiling. It's a Mario pipe store. Yeah. Oh dude, I should sell fucking pipes,
bongs and shit. That was ugly. All right. So what do I want to sell here? What do I have to,
options to buy? Groceries? Refrigerated. Does it have a bunch of these?
I'm just going to be selling deli meat. What? Or like almond milk. How much money do I have?
All right. What can I put in here? Groceries. Food. Refrigerated. Is bacon. Onion rings.
Fried chicken. French fries. Hummus. Diamond standard. Is this pepperoni? Onion rings. Okay.
Well, let's put, let's get onion rings. How many can fit in each one? Onion rings and French fries.
And then definitely pizzas. Pepperoni pizzas. Um, is this a fish filet? Shrimps? Oh, fish sticks.
Organic veggie bacon. Plant-based, just a shitload of plant-based meat. Sausages. Chicken breast.
All right. I need a bunch of chicken breast. Steak. How much money do I have? Okay. Um,
what about fruits? How about a fucking pumpkins? Corn and onions. I don't, I don't know. What do
I do? What else should I sell here? Can I make something else besides food? How do I edit my store?
I chose only food. Well, can I just go back? Oh shit. I need to, I need to storage. I know,
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know. I'm going. There you go. Finally. Storage. A big one. All
right. Come on in. Deliver it. All delivered. Come on. Let's go. You need to start a new store
to change and add categories. Are you serious? What? God damn it. All right. Well, I'll come
back to this one. All right. It might be all right. Unpack everything. Why didn't you sell,
why did you, what store doesn't sell beverages and only food? I don't know. In my brain,
I thought this was a restaurant or something and I was gonna be cooking dinner. I don't know why
I thought that. Restaurants have drinks too. I don't know. Why would they even let me do that?
It has to be idiot proof. There's no more room for this stuff. Well, now I get it. I get it. I get
it now. I'm out of room already. Kind of money. What? It's more than 700 bucks for this? 800?
How much shit did I buy? Groceries. Food. Refrigerated. Add a shelf. Let's do meat over
here. Add, drop a single spot. Drop to add shelf. Fill shelf. This is a very confusing UI,
I just say. Drop, add single spot, fill shelf. That's what I want. Fill the shelf. Okay. There
we go. Why is there still a menu for it? I only have two things. Okay. That's meat. We're going
to do meat first. Steak. We'll go in here. Why is it only single? Why is it only singles?
Okay. Meat, steak. This place sucks. I'm sorry. Pizzas. Why would anyone shop here? I don't know
if we get to get a quick steak, to get a quick pizza, frozen pizza on the way home. All right.
French fries. Fill it up. And then we'll do two French fries. This place is fucking terrible.
Oh shit. I didn't have enough. It's all right. It looks like people shop here.
Onion rings. Okay. And then the fruits. Groceries, food, fruit, corn. Okay. Then it was
pumpkins. All right. This is the, my kid dressed themselves for the day of creating a grocery
store. Like my three-year-old dressed themself today. I might make some, look, I'll just make
everything really expensive. Fruits. Okay. What are they? What are these? These apples?
I have no idea what these even are. I don't, I actually don't know what these are. They're
onions? Apples? Potatoes? I don't know. Is it garlic? No, it's not. And this is going to
be the miscellaneous shelf. Okay. All right. That's fine. Now I need a, what do I need?
Oh shit. I need a register. Do I have enough? Yeah. I have enough for the, I have enough for
the good register. The big one. All right. Let's go. You only sell yellow food. This is bizarre.
What do you mean? Whoa. Why did I do that? That's weird. That's really fucking weird.
Why did my brain do that? I mean, this is not yellow, but everything else is.
High displays. Update your store. Oh, the store windows. Right, right, right. Okay.
You eat too much McDonald's. This is not the only game we're playing, by the way. We're playing
something else in a little bit. A chicken and steak is in the window. All right. Well, this
place sucks. I know. It's awful. I'm not good at this, but it's all right. You're putting steak
directly into the sun. It's in a refrigerated unit with a tinted window on it. We're fine.
Next day. Wait, what if I run out of money? Oh, like there's no such thing as like being tired
in this game. I'm just going to do everything. So I might as well just stay open until everyone
just stay open. Unread emails. Trying today. Organics is offering discounts on selected
articles for our suppliers. Well, like I have refund. All right, let's go. Let's do it. All
right. So I'm going to give you guys a choice of the next game. Here are your options. 2020
Olympic Games or wait, maybe a mystery. I have to make sure it runs. It's an FMV game. An old FMV
game. I don't even know if it runs. I feel like we have to play the 2020 Olympic one. The Olympics.
And this Olympic Games, this new game is just crazy. I'm trying to figure out what the goal
here with this game is. You'll see what I mean when we play it. I'm open. Hi. I'm open. The store
is open. I should have been open already. Is it Sonic and Mario? It is not Sonic and Mario,
but weirdly enough, Sonic is in the game. You can just be Sonic the Hedgehog in the Olympics,
like the real Olympics. It's not like a cartoon world. I don't know. It makes no sense.
It's supposed to be a 2020 Olympic Games simulation, but one of the people you can play as
is it's not even Sonic the Hedgehog, the cartoon Sonic the Hedgehog. It's a guy in a Sonic the
Hedgehog costume. Nobody's buying anything. This one guy is going to buy an order of onion rings.
Eleven dollars. Minus 22. Shit. God damn it. It's a store with seven refrigerators. Yeah,
I'm just getting started. I'm an aspiring food business. Fast forward time. I can do that.
You're right. I still have negative one dollar. What do you guys want? Come in here. Hello? This
game sucks and it's even worse if you're bad at it, man. Jesus. I'm sorry. You know, the best part
about that comment is the man at the end. You know what I mean? It wasn't just like, oh, this
game sucks, especially if you're like not any good at it. No, it was like, yeah, this game sucks,
especially if you're not good at it, man. That stings. That's like the stinger. All right. What
do people want? 2020 Olympic Games. All right. I think I need a controller. Nobody's stealing.
What are you talking about? Remember, this game is good. I played it on Roblox. This game is pretty
good. I can't decide between the corn and the corn. I'm not quite sure if I want a pumpkin or
not. Can you sound me on this? Sure. Uh, what month is it? Uh, it's January. Don't buy a pumpkin.
Oh, okay. Why? No, I think I'll take it anyways. Somebody stole pizza. Nobody stole pizza. You
can't steal in this game. Hungry? What the hell? I just ran so fast. I stole the pumpkin. Nobody
stole anything. What if I just leave the store? Excuse me. Did you pay for that? Oh, steal from
your competitor's stores. Yeah. That'd be funny if you could do that. Somebody said, imagine if you
walked into a small store and there was just nobody in there. That's kind of like the equivalent of
when you go to class and the teacher's not there and you know that the substitute's coming soon.
It's like, oh shit, what do we do? There's always that one kid that gets up and starts drawing on
the board. Teacher comes in, substitute comes in. Eventually everyone's sitting down after like
everyone's written a bunch of bullshit up on the board. They just ignore it. They just erase it
and start talking. All right. I'm going to play 2020 Olympics. Let's go. This game was fun. I like
it, but I just, I'm not, I'm not very good at this and it's all right. It was fun. I had a good time.
I told you about my dream. Uh, I told you about a bunch of things that happened. We're going to
play Sonic and Hedgehog at the Olympics. The 15 minute rule never existed here. Well, I told you
this was not going to be a short stream. We have a few things to play. This was the number one. Who
knows Sonic? Uh, it's not Sonic at the Olympic games. It's just the Olympic games. All right.
Let's take a quick break. I'll come right back in about two, three minutes and we'll play, uh,
no, I keep saying Sonic. We're going to play the Olympic 2020 Olympic games video game. All right.
See you in a minute.