Hello, ladies and gentlemen of the Jerma nation. I'm here to address you guys and talk about a few things.
If you missed the pre-stream chat, we had just a little tiny little couple of bumps
about what we may or may not be doing today. Sorry, yeah, banana bros. You guys hear me out here?
A dog just barked at me. People are barking at me. Let's talk about this for a second. If you
didn't- if you weren't in the pre-stream chat, we had a- well, to understand what's going on now,
you got to understand the history. Last night, I made a bet, which was a totally just fun- just
for fun bet, uh, in the realm of around two and a half billion dollars with chat. And I was told
that if we got to pick the game today, that that debt, at least- at least 250 million dollars was
gonna come off that debt. And do not be mistaken, I will shave money off that debt. 100 million here,
500 million there. This is worth at least four to five hundred million dollars. In like joke,
like hilarious funny drama currency, not real United States dollars. There's already a debt
counter. That's hilarious. Uh, last night, in bed, I continued to laugh. I couldn't stop. Uh, I woke
up with like a hangover this morning. I was actually like humor hungover, somebody said.
But anyways, I was like, I'm gonna shave off some of the debt here. Just a lot of debt. Uh, so I was
like, let's do a viewer's choice. You- whatever game anybody wants. And they chose Star Wars Legos.
Lego Star Wars. Didn't get here easily. It was very, very dramatic. There were like 30 polls that
had to be done. We eliminated Neopets. We even eliminated Doki Doki Literature Club. Can you
believe it? I can't. And we're stuck here. Well, I say stuck here. This game's fun, isn't it?
Isn't this game good? I feel people love this Lego Star Wars franchise. I've never played any of
these. I always skipped them. Because to me, these were the licensed, licensed video games. I never
gave them a chance. Because when you have a licensed video game already, it's like, okay,
this might be dog shit. But then when you have a licensed, licensed video game,
that's where you lose me a little bit. I'm not sure. It's good. Okay. They're so good.
Recount. We already did a recount. Because I put a few games up there that I was like, oh,
how about we play these ones, guys? And then everyone freaked out. It was- if you just came
to the stream right now, I've been sitting in this chair for like an hour and 10 minutes.
Just debating with chat back and forth. And like trying to quell the uprising. It's been like a
full hour. Why didn't you tell anyone? Because this is important. Pre-stream chat has a lot of
power. And it's a lot of people. It's like a thousand people. Pre-stream chat decides a lot
of things. They do. Now do another recount. It's like 500 people. No, it's like 10,000 people.
But anyways, yes, today we're going to play Lego Star Wars. I hope these are fun. Because if not,
then we have to pivot to signal simulator. And if we have to pivot again, we're pivoting to my
choice, which is the Black Masses. It's like a medieval 5,000 people on the screen first person
game. So there's a tiered amount of options here over the next few days, over the next week.
I'm a new viewer. Can I get a song? Hey, sup. Hey, sup. I don't know what your name was.
I was so desperately reaching to say your name after hey. It was like, hey, fuck, what was his
name? I don't know. I was trying so hard. Okay, here we go. I don't- we're going to start- this
is the complete saga. There's like 12 games in this. I'm only going to play- I don't think
I'm going to play this again. I want to make that really clear to a shitload of people here.
I don't think this is going to be a thing that you can expect to see on this channel all the time.
By the way, see you in hell when I get this whole stream removed. Can I turn off the-
should I like mess with the music? What if I just fuck with it? Does that count?
All right, go, go, go, go, go before I get in trouble. New game.
F2. I try to play with two people at the same time on keyboard. All right, hold on. Wait,
the audio is so low. Are we in a bar? Let's turn it up. Okay, so who am I? I'm a big Star Wars fan,
so I don't want to mess this up. This is Qui-Gon Jinn, and that's Obi-Wan Kenobi,
and that's Megamind. I just- wait, you can- I just killed a guy. I just killed a guy.
Who are these people? Are we in a bar? Holy shit, what am I doing? Zero percent?
What? What? What's happening? Why am I killing all these people? How do I- how do I do the
tutorial? Holy shit, Qui-Gon's dead. What was I supposed to do? One minute. Okay, you can't kill
the band. How do I do anything? Qui-Gon Jinn. Holy shit, that was cool. It's the hub world. Oh,
all right, all right, hub world. What do I- oh, I can force grab. This is actually kind of cool.
Just go to the door? Oh, okay. Episode one, the Phantom Menace. Oh, cool. Wait, what is all this?
I'm so glad I don't have to do this puzzle on my own. Oh, sick. Okay, I got a heart piece and a
coin. I have 1,100 coins. Oh, did I just go into the Phantom Menace? Why are we in, like, another
cafeteria? They're called studs. I don't know the Lego-Lingo. The last time I used Legos was
probably, I don't know, 100 years ago? Phantom- okay, chapter one, negotiations. Here we go.
Story. Yeah. No, stop! Turn that off. Turn it down. I can't turn it off. Yeah, I can. Okay, Phantom
Menace, chapter one, negotiations. Turmoil has engulfed the Galactic Republic with a
blockade of deadly battleships. The Trade Federation has stopped all shipping to the
small planet of Naboo. The Supreme- this isn't the same without this, is it? The Supreme Chancellor
has secretly dispatched Jedi Knights Qui-Gon Jinn and Obi-Wan Kenobi to settle the conflict.
All right, we're good. Dude, you- I can't hide a DMCA from that. That initial- my channel's gone.
Like, all it needs is that first- they have that exact algorithm in place. Is this voice acted?
Are they silent protagonists? Wait, why was C-3PO just not textured? He was not even-
he wasn't colored in. Isn't he gold? Oh, that took me all morning to make!
At least those guys are dead. What? Walk- what? Walk up to friendly characters and press Y to
take control of them. Oh, shit, you can, like, mind jump? Jedi mind jumping. Okay, I'm gonna be
honest. I'm more of a- I'm more of an Obi-Wan guy than I am a Qui-Gon Jinn guy. That's a fake fan.
How am I a fake fan? Is that, like, Obi-Wan more than Qui-Gon? What's the point of collecting- is
there- all right, is there a reason to collect these? That's a Reddit take. How is that a Reddit
take? Because I like- Obi-Wan's a classic character. What are you talking about? Wait.
All right, let me out. Qui-Gon, how do we open the door? This is a double jump. Jedi mind grab.
Okay, I got it. Here we go! Okay, if I was 11, this would be the most fun game I've ever played.
Can I throw- wait, I'm putting it back together again. That's pretty cool. You missed a stud. Do
I really care? Get the blue or- all right, all right, I'll get the blue. How do I block? Okay,
I'm gonna be very, very honest with you. This feels very strange without any other sound effects
besides music and lightsaber sounds. This makes these guys psycho. This is terrifying.
Well, pepe D. Wait, so this is just one of those games where you walk around and just touch things
and let them play their funny little- oh, look, a point and click adventure. I clicked on the shoe
and it went- no. Not even, like, any attack sounds? Silent protagonist Jedi. I don't like it.
Rip Vod. I don't- okay, look. Where- I gotta ask that question. This is an important question
for twitch.tv's lawyers. What- where's the line? Can I play Jedi Star Wars on stream if, like,
there's a Jedi sound effect? Can I play this? Am I not allowed to play this? No, I definitely am.
This is in the context of playing the video game. I'm not- I'm not showing you guys, like,
my favorite Star Wars soundtrack. Okay, I can understand how people think this is fun.
Everyone of these little buttons has toys in it and you just collect them.
Press every button. Wait, what's this? I can be C-3PO? C-3PO, answer the call. He's trying to call
us. All right, I gotta stop treating this like you guys are 10 years old. C-3PO is trying to call us.
Hello? C-3PO. He's not there. Guys, I hope he's not in prison or anything. Who's behind this door?
Oh, I don't know. Bad guys. Bad guys, alert. Watch out. C-3PO. Okay. Just kill this- oh, mini-boss.
Don't you guys think it's fun whenever, like, there's like a kid in the room and you're playing
a video game and you're, like, clearly killing people? You have to say, oh, yeah, I gotta get
the bad guys. That means I'm killing people. Oh, bad guys, get the bad guys. Oops. R2. Bad guy down.
There is this C-3PO. So, if I fill that meter in the top, what does it do? You're a fake fan.
Can't wait to use get the bad guy. I don't know, when I play, like, an FPS game and I, like,
shotgun somebody right, like, in the face. Oh, I got the bad guy. Oh, C-3PO. Oh, wait, C-3PO
can open the C-3PO doors. Droids can operate Lego panels. Press B to activate them. R2. Press B.
B. Oh, he has to go to a 3PO-only pod. It's over here. 3PO-onlies. Okay, 3PO's are allowed in here.
Is this regain control of your other characters by moving up to them and pressing- I don't know,
I want to be 3PO. I'll be Qui-gon. What am I supposed to do with this? All right, put this
in the- wait, what is it? It's doing it on its own. Oh, it's just doing it on its own. I did it.
Now move it, right? I can't- I made it too high? I don't know what the hell's going on.
You can bounce. It's an optional puzzle. I don't know. I don't even know what I was doing.
Okay, you can't say like, oh, I'll bet I'll go to a little kid's game. I thought I had to, like,
move them into the lasers or something. I didn't know this was a puzzle. I didn't know what was
going on. I'm fine, look. Softlocked in a kid's game. Hey, no, stop doing the fucking Mario
backflip. All right, I actually don't get it. Toddler. Is he stoned? Stand on it. I'm back in
free play. Wait, I can't- there's a wall. I know there's a wall over there, but I can't- but do I-
No, I'm not- I can't do anything here. Come back later. Wait, why would they make a backtracking
in a toddler game? Go in the vent. You can't go in a vent. Wrong character. Don't you have to be,
like, R2D2? Okay. Need a small character, sure. I'll go get R2. All right, where's that- where's
that guy? Where's the PO? You need to come back in free play. Oh, well, how am I supposed to know
that? All right, come on. Get in there. In the- in the back of the box said there was 120 playable
characters. Is that real? There's 120 playable characters? I feel like I'm playing The Lost
Vikings for that Blizzard game. Oh, what's this? Oh, sick. Hold on, Otto wants to leave. I tell
you what, go. He's a good dog. Run on player two. No, I'm not gonna do that right now. I actually
kind of like this. It's fun. All right, so how long is this one? How long is the Phantom Menace?
Within an hour? Two hours? 40 minutes? It's about an hour. Whoa. Watch out! 10 hours. At this pace,
10 hours. I don't- I- Press X to dodge or deflect blaster bolts. I tried to double tap. All right,
deflect. Power up ball. What did I just do? Kill this little guy. Spare no one. All right,
I gotta block it back, right? That's pretty sick if you ask me. Oops. Holy shit, I just destroyed
that guy. Watch out, Qui-Gon. Okay, we did it. Get him, get him. Come on, little brother. Do
something. This is definitely a play with your little brother game and they'll do exactly what
Qui-Gon is doing right now. They just want to see the colors. Come on, get the bad guys.
Wait, what? Okay, get the bad guys. We need an R2 unit. Fuck. The blue. Swore in front of the
little brother. Oh, shit. Okay, I thought that was a clone. R2 unit. Where? Get the bad guy.
Watch out! They have shields. All right. Harry, you deal with those guys. I'll turn off- I'll do
the puzzle. Fuck. I have to deal with my little brother. If I had like actual gaming, I could
actually do it. There he is. Poxic to little brother. I need to get that blue. Got it. Oh,
yeah. Two out of 10. Fucking Mega Man energy containers. Can't wait until Kit Fisto shows up.
Yeah, I'm gonna fucking slam. That's R2 in here, right? Save R2. Shields are down. Get in. Come on,
Qui-Gon. Nice. You got him. All right. Watch out. I'm gonna get- Oh, I'm over here. It's all right.
Get him. I'm gonna swing at him. Get him. Oh, nice job. You got him. Oh, Half-Life Alex puzzle.
You're losing studs. I'm losing studs. I'm fine. What does this thing mean?
I'm like sucking in C3 for you. Fuck him. Whatever. Oh, put it together. What does this do?
Oh, I don't know. This is just a cool collect-a-thon, huh?
True Jedi. I'm in True Jedi. What's that mean? All right. I dropped a red one here.
Oops. I was trying to kill that guy. Okay, so we have to turn this on. I do like that it molds it.
That's pretty cool. That's really interesting. Game mechanic. Kids. Jump the fence. Wait,
see, 3PO can't make it. He's molding. What are you talking about? All right, we need a 3PO.
I don't think you can even lose. How many lives do I have? I think I just have infinite lives.
You can't lose in this game. All right, we need to turn that thing off. Where's 3PO? 3PO. 3PO,
let's go. It's the only sound effect that they keep using. They just use it every time.
Nice Lego hair. All right, I'm going. We did it. I see 3PO. What? It could be people around us.
You could have hired somebody like me to do this for like $100. Oh my God. What the fuck is all
this? Is it all the characters? So what does True Jedi mean? I've never played them before.
Mini kit. Can I build my own stuff? There's 160 levels. Oh, I don't know what the... I feel like
I'm getting iPadded here where they're like giving me like unlocks and level ups to things
that mean nothing. You're a level 2 golden cube. It means fucking nothing. What is it? I don't get
it. Save game. You spend them on stuff. Really? This looks kind of fun. Wait, episode... Wait,
didn't we just see this? I can't turn the... Okay. Chapter 2, Invasion of Naboo. Wait, every single
one of these is a new movie? It's 150 movies. The Trade Federation has launched a full-scale attack
on the peaceful world of Naboo. Hiding aboard the landing craft, Qui-Gon Jinn and Obi-Wan Kenobi
have secretly hitched a ride with the invasion force. Now they must make contact with local
forces before it's too late. Did you get all that, Harry? Hey, Harry. How's your grilled cheese with
the custard crud off? It's good. Yeah. You're my little guy. Oh, no. I was going to just... No,
I want to be... No. All right. Wait. Yes. Oh, this is... Unlockable. Is this dinosaurs in this game?
Fake fan. I have not watched the prequel series since I was like 17, okay?
Look, this franchise has spanned like 50 fucking years, okay? Sorry, I don't watch these movies
start to finish every three days to keep up on who's who. I watched them when they came out like
three times and then I forgot everything. I mean, I'm going for True Jedi. Was it a camel?
That's cool. That's cute. I like that. Kids could just pick up stuff and look at things and
this is a good viewer's choice. Wipe the 2.5 billion dollar debt clean screen.
You know, I agree. Oh, Jar Jar. Jar Jar fight? Oh, none of that. Okay, never mind.
Fake fan. I just saw him run across. I don't know. No, Jar Jar does fight though, doesn't he?
Like actually like combat, right? What's wrong with the two? Oh, that was a big explosion. Get
those balls. Somebody just asked why is he doing this? Well, first of all, excuse me. This game's
like a classic and two, I was forced to to pay off a two and a half billion dollar debt to the chat.
He's gonna get run over. A wheel just like runs over Qui-Gon's head. I'm sorry. This is like a
kids game. Kids might find this stream. You think about that? This is a mature content warning
before you click on this. Why? Let go Star Wars. Just want to let you know that this is,
I could be fucked up. Um, how again? Oh, not family friendly. He can jump really high.
Do I have a lightsaber or a blaster or something? Oh, missed what? I missed something. Is he
force powers? Oh, no, it's not force sensitive. Don't worry. I am. Wait, didn't get the jewels.
It's a weird camera change. Okay, let's go. Yeah, he can jump higher, can't he?
Holy shit. All right, let's go. Miss something stream. Do you really care? It doesn't matter.
Oh, come here. Get up here. I want to use your jump ability to get these. Yeah, a lot.
Play the game or don't play it. There's a difference between play the game and collect
every object in the game. Come on. Come on. Only bounty hunters can access these areas.
Wait, force grab. We got a force. I got a force grab this. Something in there.
Yep. Only bounty hunters can access this. That's fine. One stud is one dollar from the debt.
All right. All right. Fine. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Good. Good.
Good idea. Yeah, sure. That's a good idea. Yeah. I'm going to collect all of these fucking things.
I'm going to get like a billion. Oh, shoot. I'm good. I'm going to parry.
Why does he put the lightsaber away? No, I need that. I need that money. I need that money.
What the fuck is it doing? Stop spawning me. No, I need this money. Stop. Stop. I'm serious.
Okay. Switch bodies. What the hell was that? All right. I get every stud is one dollar paid
off of the debt. Come on. Hurry up. I need a lightsaber user. Come on. I need a saber user.
All right. Nice. 12. What is it? It was 12,000. Every 10K is one. Every 10K is one sub.
Excuse me? No, it's every stud is one dollar off of the fucking German national debt counter.
Lock it. Why am I not playing in co-op? I don't know. I didn't even know that existed. All right.
Let's go. Collect everything. Press F2. No. Sick. All right. The blue ones are the ones I really want
to get. I think this is like the local only. He hates Legos. I don't hate Legos. I just hate
everything they stand for. Watch this. Sick. All right. Counter's going up. That's all I care about
this stream. First it was, oh wow, I'm going to play Lego Star Wars. Now it's like, let's pay
that debt down. Oh yeah. Let's go. He hates capitalism. I told you that. I want to switch
to this guy. All right. Now move the rocks. Somebody squeeze in here. Oh shit. Hold on.
There's got to be a way I can jump up there, right? So you love capitalism.
Oh, what are you? There we are. Gold one. Sick. Somebody's gave me $50.
5,000 bits from the Zack Zuck IRL. Thank you for the 5,000 bits.
And they say that's $50. German national debt alert. Your debt may only be abolished if you
give us the one thing we want. The one thing we need, we need the German's dump truck ass emote.
You promised us five new emotes within a week. One must be the rockin' badonkadonk. Pay that
debt. Pay the debt. Okay. If I have a German like thick ass emote, that is a, that is a full
one and a half billion dollars taken off the debt. That is no, that is, that is two billion
dollars taken off the debt. And then I only owe 500 million. Well, and we'll hold on. Whatever,
whatever we have here. Is that a deal? All right. Well, first of all, I need like,
I gotta make sure I can even do that. Imagine compromising with like a chatroom about not
wanting to pay two and a half billion dollars. So you'll have a doctored footage image of your
fucking thick, huge ass that they can share and spam as a compromise. What the hell is happening?
What is going, what is this? How did I get here? I was playing, I was playing Noita last night.
What happened? All right. I gotta put this, I gotta put the thing together. There's that piece.
There's the belly. There's the head. Head on. All right. Ah, that's not it. Hold on. Take,
get, move that. Get that off. These are the legs. Move that. Where's my little brother to kill these
guys? Get these guys. Did I fuck it up? No. Take it off. Take that off. Fight. Fight. No, I don't
want to lose money. Why is that a flower from? No. Yes. So what are these cams is actually worth?
Oh, oh. What about your filters on that? And I'm available. All right. I'm taking over.
25,000 bucks dropped. The worst noise. Um, I can't click links right now with guys. This is like a
crash the game if I alt tab game. I can't, I can't do it. Not yet. Oh, this is the guy that goes.
All right. I will do this. Cutscenes in the frame in the name of anime surprised noises.
Next. Jar Jar Pinks. True Jedi. Didn't get true Jedi. Look at that stud total. That's
$60,000 off the German national debt. And I made an airplane. Not even close to two and a half billion.
Um, when I, I've done it, done with the game. Fake Jedi. Fine.
You're not going to get 500 million either. You don't know that. Hold on.
Only level three gold block. Omega level chapter three, the Phantom Menace escape from Naboo
dump truck emote. Oh, look, I have to like contact my like Twitch person and say, Hey, can I,
is it okay if I put like a doctored picture of my big fat, thick fucking ass for an emote?
I can't wait to get in an immediate within 24 hour. No reply. Um, we're escaping from Naboo
and there's people that are attacking us. Oh, this is the battle. Uh, this is going to be like
battlefront, right? It's going to end up as a global emote. That would be strange. Did they
both have brown capes? All right. Sometimes it looks off here with these suits. Did we both
order our Halloween costumes from like the party store? Like we both got the Star Wars Jedi costume.
Ooh, this level. Wait, like, can I be, who could I be? Oh, I love when there's like a
rocket launcher involved. How do you aim? All right. I like this. I like this character.
It's my favorite character so far. All right. I thought those were enemies. Come on, shoot him.
Come on. Stop hitting the lip. What the fuck? This is Padme. It's Queen Amidala. Oh, she has
a shooter too. I can't hit him. Blaster characters can grapple to other areas. Stand on the red
circles press B. Wait, I need as much money as I can get. Can't hit enemies directly. They'll
make a lot. Just wait a minute. I'm, I'm a little busy trying to collect as much national debt as I
can here. Press B right now. No, you have to be in the circle. Look. Wait, I can't, wait, can I force
push these? I can force shoot them. I need to get true Jedi on all these levels so I can
put the national debt down a little. This is going to be a real boring snooze fest of a stream.
Guy tries to collect like a hundred million dollars in Lego coins. The blue ones are the most
important. Blue ones are worth like a thousand. All right. Only collect blue ones from now on
and gold ones and get the, get white ones if they're in the area. Wait, what's this? I can
like mess with this. Purple is the most important one. I haven't seen any purples. You can buy
multipliers and get billions easy. Oh, really? Well, it's like this national debt's only going
to be available for a few hours. Ban that guy. No. VIP that guy. Do it. Right now. What else is in
here? What about that painting? Yeah, I need to be able to force grab it. I don't have any force
users in my party right now. You can push objects that have both black and yellow stripes. Does it
kill? Wait, you can slap people. Okay. That's more fun. Oh, puzzle. Also. Oh, I did it wrong.
You've never played a Lego game before. No, I haven't. All right. What does that do?
I don't know what that did. I can't push it. I can't push anything else. Can I break shit? Oh,
shit. Whoa. Wait, no, no, no, no. Get coins, coins, coins, coins, coins, coins. And I know
people saying they're not coins. Yes, they are. That's Poland. Did I just ricochet a bullet off
of the metal and hit shoot myself on the head? What a way to go. I put this back together. Can
I not? Okay. Cool. So how do I what do I do? Any more pieces? I have to come back and free play.
You know, I'm getting real sick of that word being said, I have to come back and free play
whether the developers didn't design it in a way that it could be completed without doing a secondary
playthrough to pad the length of the video game. And you guys said this is one of your favorite
games. I'm not going to stand for that. I'm not going to stand for that one. All right. If I don't
know, don't play with fire anymore. You'll burn the house down. Don't do it. Oh, nice music.
Double or nothing. Make it 50 billion. Oh, shit. I didn't even punch that person. He said a deal.
Well, you don't even know what the deal is. How could you say deal if you don't know what the deal
is? Got to come back and free play and put the windows back together. All right. Shave
10 million dollars off it if I do a really good fake sneeze. How's that? Does that sound good?
No. Oh, come on. No deal. Oh, yes. I met up with the party. I get a million. Sure. One million. All
right. This is if I do a good like fake sneeze. No, I need to like a real consensus on that. I
can't just do it. No one said that. A few of you did. A handful of you did. I've got to shoot this.
There's one, two. There's probably another one over here. Oh, wait.
What does that do? Stand on that. Oh, shit. All right. Wait, wait, wait. Guys, come back here.
Why gone? Show auto? Oh, I know I could show auto for a clean like 50 million. Wait, where are they?
You can't come up here? Why can't they not come up here? I think we've come to a good compromise
of what that actually costs. We don't negotiate with criminals. Who do you negotiate with? 25
million for auto? Really? What? Really? That's it? That's an easy 100 million. Yes. What? 20?
That's it? It's got to be more than that. No, no, I don't. No, no, no. That's got to be. Okay. 50
million. How's that sound? Hit me in the middle. 20 million? What do you mean you're going down?
30 million. All right. 30 million. I want 30 million dollars shaved off the national germadette.
Deal? Got a deal. All right. All right. We got a deal. Yes, there is a current debt tracker,
by the way. I can't believe that was made that quickly. You guys are fucking fast. We have a
deal. We have a deal. Showing auto is to erase 30 million dollars off of the national debt.
Just print more bald coin. That would be great if bald coin wasn't worthless.
By the way, it always was worthless. I created bald coin during the peak of the pumping shit
coin bubble of 2017. So you think that has any value right now? As I back in the shit
coin bubble pop of 2016, 2017, I could have had Cookie Monster as an advisor on my coin
and people would have still bought it. Show feet for 10 million. Nope. I would rather owe forever.
10 million, dude. Really? Oh, wow. 10 million. No. That erases the whole thing and I'm never
going to do that. They're getting no compromises from me for that one. No. Get that fucking shit
at it. Nope. All right. Some of you guys in the chat right now just some playing along and you
don't really care. When I said the word like, oh, show feet. Yeah. And all of a sudden you care.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah, dude. You're like, that would be good. Just to clear the whole debt, man.
Just like, yeah, it's just like, show them though. That would like clear the whole thing. Yeah,
do it. Let you like, get everybody like involved and like get about like a whole campaign about
like how we get just cleared. It's funny. Some of you guys heard the word feet and then just got
super interested in this like little game we're playing. Dude, just as a joke.
You're just doing just as a joke. Not a game. Why am I laughing? Because it's funny.
Like you don't think that that's a little humorous. How did that do? Shortcut. Nope. I
just blew it up. What does this do? Let's investigate. It was kind of worthless.
Really wasn't worth doing. This is a serious situation, Jeremy. Yeah. Well, hey, I got,
look, I got plenty of time to erase this debt. Mr. Blue. Mr. Blue stud. Where? It's despawned.
All right. What do you guys think a direct like fart into the microphone would be? All right. I
just like, like somebody with like their algorithm that like listens for the word,
like feet farts and like ass and shit. Just like, wait, I heard it. I got to join the stream.
That's extra debt. As debt. I got my fucking audio algorithm set up.
Jeremy, you're irresponsible with money. This is, wait, I get, I need to have a blue
lightsaber hit that. What? In fucking half. That's not what this is.
No, that's not what I meant. That's not what I meant. It's not what I meant. That's not what
I meant. Oh, you guys shut up. Don't say that. What's this one? I have to be a shift Lord
add debt. No, you know, I'm sorry. This is nothing we have to talk about with this.
You can't just add debt. That's not how the, I can, we can take it away, but you don't, we don't add
it unless it's very clearly specified that it's been added. No, you cannot. I have to agree to
that. Is there a fucking sprint button is interest. What's the interest rate and what's the, is it
annual? Well, how, how are you calculating interest? What's the way I, what's the APR?
2.5% per day. No, 2.5% per day of 2.5 billion is an unsurmountable amount of money that I will
never be able to erase. Oh, interest-free. That's an interest-free debt. Plus two and minus two
should decrease or increase the debt. No. Dude, do you understand how manipulated that would be?
I would never say anything funny ever again for the rest of my life.
It would use, you guys would just add it no matter what. No. I got a hundred and five thousand,
a hundred and thousand five hundred dollars. It would be 62 million dollars per day.
Oh, to the Cantina? All right, we'll after this. Moss Espapodris, Queen Amidala and her Jedi
protectors have fled Naboo heading for Ruscant. They plan to inform the Galactic Senate of the
Trade Federation invasion. However, the Royal Starship's hyperdrive is damaged in the escape
and they have been forced to land the remote planet of Tatooine for repairs where they will
meet their new Wizard of Oz party member, Luke Skywalker, his father, Anakin Skywalker. Hey,
Apollo 900 just gave fifty dollars. Thanks to the five thousand bits, add a deal and no deal emote
for a hundred million. No, that's not going to consume the stream. Oh, it's this guy. What's
his name? Oh, Waldo. Yeah. Right. What's his name? Watto. Oh, that, what's that guy's name?
Bulba. It's Bulbus, right? It's a Bulba. Jesus Christ. How do I drive? Does it just drive
automatically? How do I jump? Can I jump? Oh my God, this is too fast. Go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go. Now this is uh, debasing. What place am I in? I don't know what that means. I have like two,
I have like two stars. Two out of three stars. Are the cops coming? Bad joke. Hey,
add it to the deck, motherfucker. How do I get over there? Oh, right. I have to go in front of
Subalba. Well, there's more than can't die. Oh, right on your ass, Subalba. Where's my like laser
shooters? Come here. No. What was the point of that? It's just Subalba and Anakin Skywalker.
When will he take the lead? Okay. You know when you're going really fast in a game or something
and you realize just how fast the sides of the screen are going and it makes you almost want
to throw up like instantly. That's happening right now. Oh, Subalba. How are you? Past. First
try. First try and a good load of money. Come on. Dead. I don't know why I thought that was,
he just looked like Dexter from Dexter's lab for a second. That's $500 taken down from the debt.
Why does R2 look like somebody put painter's tape all over him, spray painted him, took the
tape off and didn't add the detail work? No true Jedi? Oh, I'll take another $130,000 though.
Odd champ. What is the building? Oh, that's Subalba's car. All right. Somebody said go back to the
cantina. I can buy stuff at the cantina with, I'm not buying anything. I don't want anything.
I need to, this is money I have to save to deposit into the, yeah, I'm not buying anything.
If I buy something, then I lose it from the national debt. Oh, ice cream. Buy the multiplier.
Not a bad idea. Smart guy. It sounded like condescending, but it really wasn't supposed to
be. What do I buy stuff? Ooh, put this puzzle together and I get extra money. Thank you. Stop
helping him. Stop helping him. Go buy new characters. You can buy new characters? Wait,
if Yoda's available, then I don't care. I'll blow up this whole national debt for this.
What do I buy stuff? Oh, okay. Right here. 3.8%. What's this timer going? Hints. Characters.
Extras. Enter code. Gold brick story clips. Oh, no. I don't want this.
Extras. Extra toggle. Fertilizer. Disguise. Chewbacca carrying C-3PO. I don't know what
the, what is this? Characters. Bonk droid. PK droid. Battle droid. Battle droid, I want a battle droid.
Droideka. Captain Tar Pals. Boss Nass. Royal Guard. Padme. Watto. Does it sound like?
Watto. The rest of these are locked. Get gonk? All right, I got gonk. Stop spending money. All right,
hold on. Hints. Double jump and press X when in the air to do a special attack. All right,
what do I do? How do I buy the extra, how do I buy the multiplier? Where is it? Is it code?
Okay, hold on. How many letters here? One, two, three, four, six letters. Uh, Han Solo, like
Chewbacca. Um, like Luke. Saber, like lightsaber. It's gonna be some stupid Star Wars word. Um,
like a country or a planet. Um, Lando. Lando. Lando's gonna be one, right? Like Lando. L-A-N-D-O-E?
Or is it D-O? Lando. Whatever. Gold bricks. Wait, I can buy gold bricks? What's, why, what's the
point of this? What could I do with gold bricks? Buy them. But what do they do? It's fertilizer.
Invest, invest, invest. All right. Gold brick two. Okay, I got two gold bricks. And I'm gonna get
the disguise. All right, I got disguise. What do I put it on? Disguise on. Adaptive difficulty is on.
I don't even know what that means. Please read chat. VXZ123 is the code. That's cheating though.
That's cheating. Yeah, that's cheating. I can't do that. Look, if I can unlock it with money,
okay, but that's purely, that's pure cheating. I just like fucking executed that guy. Um,
all right, let's go to episode one. The Phantom Menace. Oh shit. Wait, no, this is my friend.
Pick him up. That's my, like, cube friend. Oh, he's gone. How many levels? Dude, I'm almost at the
end of the Phantom Menace. Let's go. You just airlocked that guy. He's fine.
Retake Theed Palace. Sure, I already know how the movie goes.
That's Earth. That's Texas. Oh, how come only one of the, one of those guys had it on?
All right, this is where they have the big Harry Potter shield and they throw those like
ball liquid slingshots at people. Oh, big battle. Why do they have disguises on their bow?
Looks like somebody was on the comedy tab in Pornhub. Okay, we have the comedy section here
where they put like disguises on their like penis. What possible context would that joke be in?
Those guys had the fucking, the nose and the mustache like on their crotch.
What are you talking about? The droids. The droids. I'm talking about the droids.
Oh, that's right. This is a kid's game. What I meant to say was uh,
I don't want to get any like parents to write me any letters.
So hard to add it. He's lost his mind. No, you lost your mind. Oh, R2.
You are high. I know it. You don't know anything. You don't know. You don't know anything about me.
Okay, you know, Dr. Don and Dr. Dan from Point Blank. This is Dr. Don. Small characters can
crawl through access hatches. Go in it. Press B. He is small. He can't, why can't, go on and get in there.
Small characters can crawl through the access. All right, well, let's go.
How are you smaller than him? How are you smaller than him? He's the smallest thing here.
Do something. Look at the guy with the gun. Somebody shoot somebody.
All right, we all have to stand on one. Nope. We need to, wait, what?
Was the, who, I can't, I'm not gonna say that. Was that joke worth it?
Um, hold on. I need to be somebody that shoots. All right, now somebody stand on that.
Oh, shit, it's gonna be a million. There it is. Do an, okay, acting challenge. R2D2 dying. Easy.
I think that deserves at least 10 million shaved off the national debt. Don't you think? No deal.
By the way, I had to turn and yell that into the wall because if I had done that sitting straight
in front of the microphone, a lot of you would have been injured. Honey, why did you cast your
ballot? What? I don't only have 3000 gold coins. This is stupid. Get that picture of Superman out
of here. If you peek the mic, how much? Wait, peek the mic does what? Please take a look at some of
the links. All right, I will take a moment to look at some of the links. Hopefully the game doesn't
fucking crash. 100 million to peek the mic. No, that's not worth it. I'll break, I'll break
something. Yeah, the debt counter. Right. I've seen it. What is this? New footage from Star Wars
DMCA movie? This person just made this account. This person has one follower. They just like made
this account. What do you want? What are you doing? It's wrong. It's not okay. Let's, this is
scariest fucking thing I've seen all day. I don't know. Is this a real picture? Not a real picture,
but what is this? Not a real picture, but is this a picture of somebody or is this a picture of me
that somebody fucked with? I can't even tell. All right, give me the next one. I mean, this one,
I mean, that's just, that's Watto, but it's just my, it's the thing face.
It sort of just looks like there's a brain-eating slug just pressed up into my nose, sucking my
brain out of my nose. What else you got? What about the GIF? No, fuck that GIF. I'm gonna put it on.
That's what you want. That's not what you're getting. Joe, you're a coward.
I can't. I get, no, I don't want. I can't. I can't. Dude, what the fuck?
Emote, emote, emote, a hundred million to show it. What? For real? Leave it on stream. No,
absolutely not. It was worth it. Deal is off. I showed it. This is good too. Hold on.
This is good too. 30 million for only the dogs. Sorry, but without the emote on the table,
I can't accept. I'm out. But wait, you forgot to say that you would do like in perpetuity a loan
to me, which then I have to pay back over the course of like four or five years. And then you
get a 1% royalty on every single time I ever show a picture of the dog. His deals, nobody ever takes
his deals, by the way. He's just there to kind of be in the middle and just say strange things.
No one ever takes Kevin's deals. Why can't he just say, I'll give you $200,000? Why is it always like,
I'll give you 75,000. But then I want in perpetuity royalties on top of 5% of every sale you make.
It's just, dude, just give him $75,000 and just fucking be done with it. I just don't think he
ever wants to give any money. I think he just likes to be in on the show as business. All right,
last one. Then we're going to go Barbara. I love how you like know who these are. Like these
characters. This is unrelated to the things we're talking about right now, but it's, I mean, kind of
funny. Tank. Deal 4 damage. Corrupt. Then deal 2 damage to all enemy minions. What is corrupt?
Wait, this is a real card? Uh, excuse me. Excuse me. I'll take, I'll take $100 million off.
That's a real card. All right, let's continue playing. Star Wars. Revenge of the Phantom Sith.
All right, we need R2. R2. Wait, he can shoot? R2, auto D2. Wait, are we keeping track of how
much the debt is actually being paid down? I just did, no, okay. I screamed really loud and it was
what? 10, 20 million? What was it worth? I'm gonna keep track of that. What was it? It was 20. It was
20. Do a monkey noise for another 10. That needs to be confirmed first. That's, I'm getting a lot
of no deals, so I'm not going to do that unless it's a deal. No, I'm not seeing very many deals
here. Shit, I just got shot in the air. Hit me! Don't let them all go to waste. You know, if any
other character would do anything, it would be great. Irma is dummy thick. Thanks for the
five community subs. You know, it's funny too. I've gained like 20 pounds. It's definitely gotten
way bigger. Oh my god, can I play the fucking game for a second? Just reflect. Reflect.
Fuck the fuck, dude. I'm out of money. All right, just who cares about the fountains? It's like $20.
Actually mad. Just stand in the middle of everybody and like it'll hit the other people.
Hit it!
My favorite part of that song, by the way. And it goes...
I always like fucking nod the fuck out when I see that. What if the active debt counter has a
thermometer on the screen? All right, we need someone to crawl through this. You. Come here.
Crawl through that. I go open the door. Oh shit, the only thing I had to do the whole game.
Did I do it, Obi-Wan? Did I make you proud? Surprise, Ruby. Thanks for the five community subs.
Thanks, dude. Oh, this is Anakin Skywalker. He's huge. Don't you think he would be like
three feet tall? Why is he like six feet tall? He's seven. Yeah, and Obi-Wan's like 45.
Why is he as tall as Obi-Wan? The debt, the debt, the debt. What about it?
What do you want about it? Crunchies. Stop growing at 15. What are you talking about?
The debt, the debt. I was trying to double jump across the chasm. I guess I can't do that.
Open. Open. Oh, I need a little guy. Little guy. Are you little enough for this?
Of course not. I need a little guy. Little guy. Link. Hold on. Not yet.
Try to just reflect. Thank you. This is a bad deal. What's a bad deal? I didn't make any deals.
Pay debt. I didn't make. What deal did I make? What are you talking about? What's going on?
Wait. Okay. Hold on. It's bad. This link sucks. Is it? Okay. Hello, Dermot. We are treasurers
of the great Dermot95 sub debt. Our terms are as follows. Show Otto for minimum one clip
worth of content is 20 million. Okay. Play TF2 on stream. 350 million. I'm not doing that one.
Play Doki Doki Literature Club on stream. That's 1.75 billion. You had your chance this afternoon.
Funny faces and sounds only stream for a minimum of 30 minutes. The debt is erased.
Wait. What? Funny faces and sounds for 30 minutes means it's all erased. Make Dermot Dump Truck a
four-part emote like Joop is 1 billion. And then the rest cut off. Okay. Well, let's keep track of
what we have known right now. I'm at 20 million resolved. Yes. That was for the R2-D2 scream.
That was part of the deal. There was no deal. Yes, there was. Yes, there was. There was a deal there.
I want you to go back and watch that. There was a deal. All right. I need to get everybody across
the bridge. Where's the little guy? Where the fuck is Anakin? He bailed. What? I mean, he bailed.
Oh, they're all down here. All right. Let's go. Anakin. You. Who the fuck is this? Oh.
Can't double jump. Is there a staircase that I'm missing? Stairs. Stairs. Stairs. Just hold on.
Let me just take a sip of my coffee. Where are these magic stairs you're talking about? Oh.
Hey, Pronovar rocks. Thanks for the 10 community subs. A lot of subs today. Thanks, guys. Thanks for
the subs. I'm going to be enjoying a nice sub sandwich later. I don't know. What's your guys
favorite sandwich? This is multi-level marketing. What did I do? I didn't do any multi-level
marketing anymore. Taco Bell is not a sub. Surprise Ruby. Another five subs. Thanks.
Surprise Ruby. What is Jersey Mike's? I don't know. Jersey Mike's turkey sub with mayo. Damn.
You got my attention. You actually do have my attention. You really do.
You have it. How do I swap? I guess you could just, dude, kill Anakin and you get to swap.
No, you don't. Let's go. Can I swap? Oh, that was of noise. That's worth a few bucks.
All right. Attack. Stones. Stones. Yes, sir. How? Get the stones. Stones. Yes, sir. How?
Get those stones. What is that from? What is that? Stones. What is that? From this stream?
That's from the fifth element. Oh, right. Yeah, it is. And it's Gary Oldman. Right. Yeah. Yeah.
I got it. It's my favorite childhood game. Collect. Collect. Anybody else jump high?
Wait a minute. Crafting. Anakin. It's not a vent? Sure. Okay. Hold on. I need to have somebody stand
on that and then this is a co-op thing. I'm not making an Among Us joke. No, you're not going to
get that out of me today. I don't even care. Stand on it. Oh, I'm over it. I'm over that.
Aren't you? Why is he doing that? Of course. He made it and I didn't. Fuck. When they jumped
together, I thought they were the same. Like, they blended together. They have the same fucking
Halloween costume on. Vent. Free money. All of you. Remember, they don't celebrate Halloween in
space. Now you're going to next see something they don't celebrate Christmas or Thanksgiving
or like New Year's. There's a version of it. We have to get everybody up here.
And everybody pulls like the Warcraft. There's like a feast of winter time. The winter's feast.
It's Christmas. You know what I mean? A feast of winter veil. Yeah. If there's no like
Christmas or like Hanukkah or whatever in space, then they'll make their own one up.
What is this? Mayonnaise. Why is there a mayonnaise emote? Who has a mayo emote?
And why are there not enough people up here? Get up here. Who didn't come up with us? Whatever.
I have to make the path for them. Ah, fuck. Somebody else will do it.
I did it. What's an actual good deal? Make the path for everybody.
Right? I gotta... Neopets for a hundred million. All right. Somebody... I was going to do Neopets
before we did the insanity. Somebody said that like my credit card information is going to get
stolen. What does that mean? Somebody said like, don't like... Neopets is like a not even secure
like HTTPS website. Like what does that mean? Help me. Is that fake? Is this false? A lot of
money. What happened to me? Oh, it exploded. He's just a Neopet hater. I never played it.
All right. So can I get everybody up here now? Play Toontown. Oh my God. How do I open that?
How do we get everybody up here? Is this like a magic thing I have to do?
Please play Toontown. Please play Toontown. Break the flowers.
Well, that's a weed, but almost an MMO shit show part two and never did it.
Yeah, you're right. I did. Yeah, you're right. I did. Oh my God. That's what I had to do.
All right, Qui-Gon. Let's get up there. Get on it. We've proposed a new offer.
No, hold on. Let me like, let me just get to the end of this level. I'm almost done with the
Phantom Menace. Link, hold on. I'm almost done with the Phantom Menace. Wait, you're distracting me.
Switch sides. Eat a spoon of mayo. Or wait, does that work? Is that for real?
Is that an actual part of the deal? I tried to double jump and it didn't work.
I literally, I literally pressed double jump and it didn't do anything.
Stop.
Depth perception. I'm jumping in the perfect angle.
Perfect angle. All right, let's go. Well, everyone was waiting for me.
Yeah, I took the long way back. Sorry, guys. I know you wanted to pull the next mob,
but I got lost in the instance. That's another wild joke. I'll take a fucking plus two, please.
For a good wild joke, that's, I mean, that's at least $50,000 off, right?
Something like that. Begging. Mutants! Mutants! How do I sprint? Somebody said this is a way to
sprint, right? Oh, by the way, that Star Wars VR game that's coming out, is that an actual
lightsaber fight? Somebody finally made that fucking game. I cannot believe out of everything
we've ever seen in VR. No, they didn't make a VR game. A lightsaber. What would, what would,
what could you possibly be thinking? It's all space combat. I don't understand. You have the
perfect opportunity to have a lightsaber one-to-one thing that everybody has wanted for a decade.
A decade. And you're gonna make a space combat simulator? No. Blade and Sorcery. But Blade and
Sorcery is just a fun little way, and I'm talking about like a Jedi lightsaber Lucas Film co-sponsored
video game where you play as a Jedi with the one-to-one lightsaber. We have that already.
We do not have that already. I mean, we have that already. No, we don't. Star Wars Connect.
That's not even close to what I'm talking about. Vader Immortal. I don't, I feel like you made
that up. What is Vader Immortal? Vader Immortal. How do I get up here? It's an Oculus game. Can I
do anything up here to open this? It's real. Break the chairs. That's good money. Did you even read
the tutorial? There was no tutorial. Or Scrapple. Is there any more stuff? Table. I just joked.
I just joked R2-D2 for no reason. Wait, that's a red brick. What's a red brick do? That's gotta be
worth some money. So what the hell? I need a third table. The gray tracing floors. They actually look
really good. Oh, wait. I just rearranged the furniture. It didn't do anything. That doesn't
help me. That link. Hold on. That link, that link, that link, that link. That's a scary link.
And you have new terms. Let me see them. Hellman's extra heavy mayonnaise.
Wait, there's an extra heavy mayonnaise? What is extra heavy? Is this, that's not a real product?
Extra heavy mayonnaise? Hellman's extra heavy. Eat the whole thing on stream for one billion off.
I'm not, I'm not going to do that. What is extra heavy? That sounds gross. Here's better terms.
Okay, real deal. Let's see what this one says. Real deal. Dump truck ass emote. TF2 stream.
Four additional emotes. Get erased when all is fulfilled. Hmm. I don't know. I don't know. Some
of those, at least one or two of those things, I'm not so sure about. You never stated it had
to be a four-part ass emote. You guys are gonna get me fucking banned. I'm gonna get dropped from
Twitch TV. It'll be worth it. Take the risk. Why would I take that risk? Four-part like mega ass
emote. Might, you know why that, here's why I, it's nothing about me getting banned. Here's why I
don't think that's a good idea. Because you will, you guys will go to whatever other streamers that
you watch. Whether it's, you know, this person, that person. You are going to four-part thick
germa ass emote and fuck up their stream and they're going to be really annoyed that there's
just an ass, a huge thick ass that keeps showing up and that they can't stop it and they can't turn
it off. You're gonna start, you're gonna start getting banned. You're gonna start getting like
timed out in other streamers chats and then they're gonna come back to me and they're gonna be like,
dude, did you make like a four-part huge like thick booty ass, huge ass emote? And I'm gonna
have to say yes. I'm gonna have to explain myself to all the people that I annoy. Watch out rollers.
This really is just multi-boxing. I'm just trying to, I signed up for like refer a friend like 12
times. So we have like a six million percent increase in experience. You're just gonna start
seeing randomly gold particle effects. Just fly around each individual one of these people
at random times. Dear Mr. Dump Truck. That's, hey, that's Dr. Dump Truck to you.
Hellman's real extra thick male is, I can't read it. You guys are going too fast. I can't,
I don't know what you're doing. I can't read it. Oh, R2 can't make it. Dr. Dump, Dr. Dump Truck
could be in the rumble. Yeah, maybe if it was WWE 2k13 or 14 because then I could just have like
the ass speed, the slider that's all the way to the end and everything else is tiny. I have this
too. All right, you know what's confusing me as well? They all have the mustache on. So I,
it's hard to, they're all the same person. I thought, I don't even know who that,
these are all the same. Who are these people? It's all like different Marios. Ooh, shake it.
By the way, this, we're almost like done with the Phantom Menace of the complete saga.
Who the hell is Darth Maul? He didn't show up once. He's up your ass. All right. That's such
an old drunk fucking fat guy thing to say. Anybody seen, anybody seen my glasses? Yeah.
Yeah, they're up your ass. They're up your ass. Have you checked up your ass?
No, I haven't. Up your ass, Andy. Quiet. Mario. Mario. Shake it up and you get the goods inside.
Okay. Stop crack Mario. How's that crack Mario? Can't hit these bricks. All right.
We're all about the links the last few days, aren't we? Tons of crack links coming in more
than usual. There's tons of just crack links. Who can get up there? You guys get up here.
Who can jump this? Nobody can. There's one guy making all these bad links. One man link spammer.
Is that what you're saying? Didn't I save these guys? I saved these two. All right. I got to
save the rest of them. One man spam. Got it. Okay. So now, now what we're going to do chat.
Okay. So, hey chat, here's what we're going to do. All right. Get on this. I'll get on this one. Okay.
So chat. Here's what we're going to do. Chat. I've seen this before. You guys don't like being
just called like a chat, right? What do you like to be called? Germamites? By the way, people get
annoyed when they find out that that's what I call this community. Well, what's the community? The
germs? The germas? Like the clowns? No, the germamites. And they go, fuck that. Fuck that.
Don't tell me how to run my community. First of all, second of all, that's what that's what it is.
How dare you tell me to run my community? Paul. Everyone right now is fucking searching for like
the streamer or the YouTuber whose name is Paul. Who's he talking about? Who's he talking about?
Who is that? Who's Paul? I wonder who that is. Who's he? Who's he? Who's he? Who's he? Who's he?
Hey, Paul. You're an idiot. This has got to go first. Place it. Place it. Pull it. Pop it.
Twist it. R2D2 sound. Gotta collect every coin. Every single coin. I will not part with one
single coin. Not one. Trinket. Oh, little thief. Oh, you're so magnificent. The stories they tell
us surely are immountable and insurmountable to you, most smog the powerful.
Is that what they say? Thief. I almost want you to take it. If I can see it, eat him aside.
To watch his very bright brain. I haven't seen the movie in a very long time. I tried.
The take they leave in. Come on, break it. What is this? How can I not open this?
I just walked off the edge. Alright, let's go. Come on. Go. Where's Darth Maul? Why didn't I
play Lego Lord of the Rings? Wait. Wait, where's this last person? Where's this last hostage?
What's cool in Lord of the Rings? This is plus a full letter grade. Yeah, this is plus a full
letter grade. What are you doing then? Be free. Is somebody just holding a gun? I thought I was
going to die. Is somebody just holding a gun to one of the hostages somewhere? This is watching
this. It's like, where is he? Where is he? Oh, down? No, he's up above the entrance. Wait,
I get this person to jump over here? Wait, wait, wait, wait. He's all the way back. I need to sprint.
How much for ASCAM? Zero. But no, seriously, what's better Lord of the Rings or Star Wars?
That's a tough one. Lord of the Rings or Star Wars? What's better? Well, Lord of the Rings is
probably... This is actually kind of hard. Oh, there he is. All right, somebody shoot that. Shoot
him. Shoot him. Shoot him. Shoot him. Shoot him. Shoot. A saw. Yeah, a saw is better. I need to get
up there. Come here. Get up there and shoot. Okay, so if I really had to do it, if I really had to
make the decision, I would probably say... Okay, I like the Lord of the Rings world more, but I like
the Star Wars objects more. That makes sense for some of you, right? I like the weapons in Star Wars
and the stuff and the ships and the lightsabers and the... I like that more than the swords and
the shields. Oh, wait. Wait. Okay, Game of Thrones... All right, hold on. Game of Thrones before
season seven versus Star Wars. I don't know. I like that the swords have names and stuff.
Finish the level. All right, hold on. What is the Lord of the Rings? Yeah, they do. What? Yeah,
that's true, but... A goblin cleaver? Yeah, I don't know. Shit, this is... I don't know. I might be
up in front of my own bullshit here because the lightsabers don't have names.
It's just green lightsaber. It's not like the sword of the morning. It's just yellow lightsaber.
Some do. Yeah, like two. Yeah, like the darksaber, right? Okay, there's one. What, there's two others?
Sorry. Out of like the 4,000 lightsabers that have been crafted from the fucking
Adamantite crystals, there's two that have names. Leia's Gonkdroid. I don't know how to do that.
The crystals have names. Oh, they don't. Yeah, it's called like the... What are they called?
Cyber crystals? The hyper crystals? Kyber crystals? Yeah. I don't want to do that. All right,
here we go. Here comes the boss fight. The final boss of episode one. I had to do that. I'm sorry.
Fake fan. Chaos emeralds. Yeah, it doesn't matter. They're all the same thing.
Don't be surprised, by the way, if in like three to five years, the chaos emeralds are turned into
beam swords. Why the fuck not? It is a Sonic game. That would be actually pretty cool. Why have they
not done that? Imagine a Sonic the Hedgehog game with lightsabers? It's Darth Vader. No,
oh, he has the mustache on. It's Darth Maul. Here it comes. Look at the skull. I want to be able to
see their faces. Obi-Wan, no. That wasn't supposed to happen to you. That's supposed to happen to me.
Oh shit. Oh, no. No, Obi-Wan. Well, I want to do that. Can I catch them in the air?
Aha. I can do that too. Traitor. Fuck. Darth Maul's a traitor, right? Traitor. I like this guy.
Spin, spin, he's spinning. He's doing this wrong. What do I do about this? He just blocks it. Oh,
he's three. He's no hearts left. That's Count Dooku. Count Dooku, join me. Join me, Link,
and together we can destroy the Sith. I'll never join you. That's unfortunate. Now you will have
to die. Fan fiction. I said Link. Yeah, I did say Link. And dude, in my fan fiction, Link talks?
Are you fucking kidding me? Do you guys think they'll ever give Link dialogue ever again?
I don't think so. Give me that canister. Maybe, why not? Maybe. It's probably gonna,
but it's gonna have to be a celebrity. Let's be real. It's gonna end up being Tom Holland,
and you all know it. Right, get in the car. All right, other side. Elijah Wood. Yeah, I could see
that. I would, you know what? I wouldn't even be bad. I wouldn't even, I would be okay with that.
That's doesn't even, that would be all right, I think. I think that'd be fine. He's 40.
But are we trying to say that, are we questioning the talent of Elijah Wood?
You're actually doing that right now. Are you sure you're doing that? We are right now questioning
the talent of any age Elijah Wood. I need a stormtrooper to get up here. All right, well,
let's just walk over here. Yes, that's unbelievable to me. All right, get him.
I was trying to like murder him. You're an Elijah Wood simp. Oh, please. He's like a wicked nice guy,
and he's really talented. Oh no, I can't believe you're sipping for that guy. He's like a good
person. Oh shit, this is bad. Face us. Wait, no, no, no. I want to change character. I don't
want to be the one that gets, uh, the one that goes shopping later. Why does the double jump
doesn't work? Okay, I, double jump doesn't work sometimes. Why would I work right there and not
work here? Click, click. All right, let's go everyone. I mean, Qui-Gon. No, stop running away.
That was, wow. Does you guys like this game that much? That was very clearly a let's have a final
boss fight here, and they took him away and ran him away. That one song I'm going to hear in my
sleep. That din-din-did-a-din. Fuck. Qui-Gon, help me. Qui-Gon. Holy shit, we just got like
the AI director. It was like pissed we were taking too long. Hold them off. Spike. Wait, Qui-Gon fell
off. Click the link. Just wait. Hold on. All right. Your toast, Darth Vader. Maul. Oh wait,
this is the part where it goes. What are they actually saying? I've heard that song a thousand
times. What are the lyrics to that song? It's gibberish. Wait, is it, it's actually just
gibberish? They just go, la la la. They're not saying anything? No, that's not real.
No, it's Latin. Wait, blue. What are they, what are they saying? Where's the other one?
That's it? Wait, is this thing where it's like Lord of the Rings where they made up a whole
language? Wait, can we fight him? No, wait. Isn't, wait, doesn't, there's not how this
work happens in the movie. Yes, it is. Wait, no, how come we're both here? Let's change the,
let's change history then. All right, but if you're playing with your little brother and he's playing
Qui-Gon because you don't want to play Qui-Gon for, you know, obvious reasons incoming, then what
happens when the little brother be really sad? By the way, I feel bad for people that have never
seen Star Wars and they're like just waiting for some reason and you're going to see like the Lego
version of like a major plot point of a movie. Okay, if you've held up with us long enough watching
Star Wars, you never were going to watch it, so who cares? Here we go. This is it. This is it.
Good block. How do you swing? How do you swing? Click, mouse, enter, space bar, A, Z, control,
shift. How do I swing with, how do I swing with Qui-Gon? H, J, K, L, semi, M, period, colon, slash,
numpad, numpad. Okay, this is hard to do this. Fuck each other.
Just like in the movie. We're getting into an argument. Now Obi-Wan, you, leave me alone.
Oh shit. Spoilers. Yeah, you didn't remember this part.
Eventually we'll get it. Yeah, you guys don't remember the part where like Qui-Gon turns on
Obi-Wan right here and he joins the Sith and then they have to battle it out and then dude Darth
Maul breaks his double-sided lightsaber in half and hands the other side to Qui-Gon and they fucking
both fight with a single saber at it. Ow. I don't know how to do um force pull with uh the other.
Oh there we go. Thanks for saving me. He's putting his lightsaber away. Hold on a minute. I just,
I lost something over here. Get him in the back. Oh no. Nooooo. Am I right? Wait, that doesn't
happen. Ow. Ow. Ow. That fucking hurts. That's so, ah I didn't expect it to be like that.
His eyes go X and he just smashes his head on the star. I'm not a monster. It was unexpected and
quick. It's so abrupt. That doesn't even happen in the movie. Why are you laughing? I'm not
laughing at that. I'm laughing at, I'm laughing at the fact that it happened not the fact that it was,
I look at laughing at that way that it happened not the fact that it was sad that it happened.
This is where we all get the medals right? Oh here it goes. Did that was, it was very enjoyable.
That was, hold on a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Um that was
like two hours long. Did this game come out on its own? No. One, two, three did. Okay. Because
I was gonna say if this like was a standalone just video game like the Phantom Menace that you bought
at Walmart. I'm not sure you got your $60 worth but it's three games. Okay. You guys know how
the credits look. Who cares? 6.3%. Okay so that was the Phantom Menace. Oh shit. How do I delete
the second player? Drop out. There we go. It was like 30 bucks. Well that's good. We need a link.
All right hold on. I'm gonna do a link and I'm gonna go take this. All right what is, what do you
got? That's, I'm not gonna click that. I will, I clicked it but I'm not gonna show that and that's
um something I am not, I will, there will be no comment. I'm gonna have an emotionless comment
on um on that image that I was just linked. Okay so anything else you'd like me to see before I
like get out of here? Go to the bathroom. Okay good. I'm the like the fat face penis shirt thing.
I've already linked it last night. Uh this is a, this is a, I, I, why do you have this picture?
That's the pants. That's the way the pants are. That's like the pants.
Like okay do you think I have like a hamburger dick? Please. That's the pants the way the zipper
is pushed again. Larry David did an entire episode of his critically acclaimed hilarious
television show Curb Your Enthusiasm about this exact thing. I don't even need to describe this.
This is a Larry David routine so just go watch Curb Your Enthusiasm. I'll be right back. Does
Jerma hate Adam Sandler? No. I actually think Uncut Gems is a really really good movie and I
thought he was very good in it. I think uh Adam Sandler uh gets a lot of hate. Doesn't get a lot
of credit for some of the things that he's done. From the Saturday Night Live years through like
the mid to late 90s he made some really really actually really funny talented interesting things
and he got a little complacent made three or four real stinkers in a row and then he uh got into
some serious acting and I think he's I think he's pretty good. I think he gets too much hate for no
reason. Well hold on a minute. Yeah he deserves quite a bit of criticism for like the five movies
in a row that were like like 10 on Rotten Tomatoes right. It was a string of about six straight years
seven straight years where almost everything he did was awful just awful awful awful. We talk
about like the before times and then the after times of like the mid-2000s Adam Sandler disaster
career. Donkachino. Donka donka donka donka donkachino. Don't give me that. Don't give me
I saw it. People initially were very we were very mad that I just did that. Let's do this. Let's
get back to this. We're gonna do episode two which is um back in the clones. Oh wait I have money to
spend. Wait this bot right he's so slow I can't he is gonk an oven. What kind of droid is he?
He's a trash can. Oh okay I knew he was something. When am I gonna get like some of the heavy hitters
like Palpatine and oh wait this is the prequel saga right. Okay uh I mean I want to buy some stuff.
All right Phantom Menace. Wait I can do whatever one I want. I don't have to go in order. Oh I got
to do I'm gonna do my favorite Star Wars movie then. I don't have to I didn't I thought I had
to go in order like one two three four five. Did I watch the movies? All right fuck the whole prequel
drill. This stuff sucks. I want to wait but I want to do which one episode. Okay Empire Strikes Back.
Empire Strikes Back. By the way I'm also not going to be one of those like haters that says that.
I actually enjoyed the prequel series for what it was. Sure there was a lot of problems with it
but I mean it was I thought it was okay. I thought it was look it they added some things.
Roy Decker. Why did I just buy that for? Extra toggle. What's that? Why am I buying these? What's
an extra toggle? Where's where's Roy Decker? I just bought it. Not Roy Decker. Where's Roy Decker?
Start a bar fight. I did that in the very beginning and I caused a lot of problems.
All right let me do Empire Strikes Back. It's my favorite movie. This and Return of the Jedi are my
favorites. Empire Strikes Back. I don't want to be Qui-Gon anymore. Make a custom character. How? Use
the character creator. Wait how? Where? How do I do that? Go back go back go back. Where? In here?
Bonus. What's bonus? Is this like deleted scenes? Back to the main place. It's in the cantina.
Boob guys please. Tube tube tube. Indiana Jones. What's going on? Trailers? Is this a trailer for
Indiana Jones or Indiana Jones the game? Lego. I don't care about Indiana Jones at all. I really.
Indiana Jones is now available to buy in the shop. You really gonna do that? I really I have to be
honest. I really don't care. Indiana Jones is like at the bottom of my interesting
American cinematic trilogies. It I just don't I don't hate it but I'm just not into it.
Bathroom? All right give me out of here. Temple of Doom was awesome. Temple of Doom was crazy.
But I'm not I'm not a big fan of the other ones really. It's the worst one.
Is it? I think it's the only one I've watched. I just remember being like a little kid.
How do I get out of here? All right I was like I was like 12 and I remember there was like a guy
that like pulled people's hearts out and they like ate like animals brains and stuff and I
remember being it was like I was scared. Over here two player arcade mode. Right right right right
right right. Question mark. Oh look at this. I I need okay who do I want to be? Oh definitely
a slug guy. C3PO. This now you talk about fan fiction. That's okay yeah yeah yeah definitely.
I definitely want an R2D2 Jedi. If I had my lightsaber by the way it would be um white.
It would be just white or um yeah be white. Just R2D2 with a gun. Silver yeah whatever it is.
Well it has to match him. Blue. This is just like this sucks.
He's standing on two feet. Where's his droid body? Did I pass it? Okay as a stranger one. No hat.
How do I take the hair off? What's going on? Gonk gonk gonk gonk gonk gonk. What what is it?
Okay so how do I use them? Ow. Auto D2. All right this is a good link. You're right.
You have to do it in free play. Oh auto D2. That's the that's who is inside of the case.
That's very cute. All right so I can't use them in the story. Fine. All right let's I want to do
episode five. Let's go. Empire Strikes Back. I don't know if everyone's gonna call me like a
Reddit normie for saying that this is like one of my favorite movies in the franchise. Sure go for
it. Turn of the Jedi is probably my actual favorite one. This is dark. You guys know the story. For a
second I forgot what game I was playing. I just knew it was Star Wars and I saw how weird polygon
looking that ship was and I thought something was wrong with the computer. Here's the force Luke.
I'm also one of those weirdos that didn't hate The Force Awakens. I wouldn't say it was my
favorite but I didn't hate it. Why don't I get to do that part? I don't get to do that part.
That part's awesome. They're all good. Uh these Darth Vader simlish. It's uh I love it.
Uh no I think I mean here's the thing about Star Wars. It's such a beloved franchise and
everybody loves it. Everybody is like oh it's the best thing ever but let's be really honest.
Like probably half of these movies are not very good. The other half though
they're fantastic. Like fan-fucking-tastic. Oh shit that's B to use your toe cable.
This one is this one's awesome so far. Okay well you can do it on the um the 8080s right?
Ow out of bounds. Luke, Luke stop doing tricks and focus on the enemies. This is where Luke
gets way too overconfident and he just lets his force powers do he because he can just do
anything he wants. He's like cheating in the lobby at this point. VAC. All right how do I get rid of
this? I need I need a tie fighter to open this. Oh Luke why are you doing Peter Griffin? Peter
Griffin? What are you talking about? I did? When did I do my Peter Griffin? I have to do that to
10 of these. Oh so long King Bowser. Wait we're fighting over the bomb. Who's gonna get it? What
do I do with that? I gotta throw it in there. All right throw the bomb. What? Wrong way. Wrong place.
There it is. Throw it in. This is literally a kid's game. Yeah I know you I've never played it
though. You played this game like a thousand times when you were a little kid. I didn't play it.
Dropped him. I was 20 when this came out. When did this come out? This is pretty old doesn't it?
Are you how are you as old as me? How old are you? When did this come out? When did this actually come
out? When did I do it? 2007. Now that's not that long ago. 2009. That's not that long ago at all.
Oh never mind. I don't know why I thought this game came out in like like 2000. Grab the bomb.
Uh what? I don't understand. This is just like Tony Hawk. Ow. All right wrap him up. Let's go.
Prove to everybody why you're my favorite movie. Boom. Bomb. It's lice. Blow it up. Blow him up.
No get out of the fucking way. There it is. All right that's another one dead. How many more of
these do I have to kill? Somebody said this sucks. It doesn't suck. All right roll it in.
This is vomiting. Hold on. This whips. Don't make me laugh. Actually now that you said that why did
you say that? Now am I gonna get sick? Don't say that out loud. I actually now I'm gonna puke
because you said that. I was fine until you said that. Okay yeah. Get up there. Shit why did you say
that? I think we're good. What? Go up the ramp whopper cock. Okay destroy all the little droids.
One more. Kill it. Kill it. All right now what? Now I gotta blow something up. Please stop moving
for a second. I'm gonna vomit. What should I have for food today? I know that's a weird transition
but what should I eat today? A whopper? No Burger King sucks. Burger King just it's not it used to
be good. It really did. You know maybe like 10 years ago I would have agreed with you and said
yeah I'm gonna go get a whopper. Or like a like a stacker. Like a BK stacker. That was my favorite.
BK stacker with the stacker sauce. Then everything you ordered from Burger King as of five years ago
was cold. What happened? Did they just like get rid of the microwaves? Did they get rid of their heaters?
I have not had hot food from Burger King in five years. That's an accurate actual statement. I have
not. I haven't been there granted for very many times but the times that I have been there it has
never been even warm. I don't know why that is. Now that happens at McDonald's not frequently but
it does but not to the extent that I've saw it at Burger King. Fine hot. Um well okay let me think
about this. Okay if you put your hand like on your ass right now. The heat like coming off your
ass right now. I would do I would consider that like like I would consider like McDonald's like
warm. Like that's like fast food warm to me. Like like put your hand on like your belly like on
your stomach. Just hold it there for a second. That's like okay like when you feel the burger
in the wrapper that that's edible. That's edible. Like kind of hot. Do I kill these things? What the
fuck are you talking about? Like luke warm. Just like slightly warmer than room temperature is how
a lot of fast food comes. You just made thousands of people you just made thousands of people touch
their ass. Well no I just mean like your body heat. Body heat is like a respectable fast food
heat. I'm okay with that. I'm not touching that. My ass is not wrapped up in a hamburger.
You supplast a fun thing. Like my ass is not your ass is no you're not gonna eat your ass in a wrapper.
Before he gets up come on. This man can't beat a children's game. Do you see how much chaos
is happening on the screen right now? Even more of these. All right let's get the big guy first.
All right wait clear it out. Big guy first go. Fucking read the screen. I'm getting rid of the
big guy first. I know I can see the icons. What are you talking about? Shit this this is no longer
my favorite movie. This is not my favorite movie anymore. Oh give me a break come on. Okay I got it.
You can't die in this game. Who cares? Star Wars diaper check? It's not full. But um what?
What's wrong with me today? What am I doing? Why am I saying these things? No. You're a piss baby.
Okay I thought that was a lightsaber and I was gonna say that's a very strange lightsaber.
Hey you little piss baby. All right get it. Two percent. 10 out of 160. This is a cool game.
Now I understand why this won the 2.5 billion dollar erasure screen. I get it now. This is why
you wanted me to play this so bad. Empire Strikes Back. Escape from Echo Base. Oh shit we're on the
ground now. Links are now accepted. Well not yet. Let me get to uh an episode after this.
By the way what's up? Like they're like brother and sister right? And like while we're like in love.
It's fucking weird. Oh it's Han Solo. Oh this is not Luke. I thought it was Han Solo.
Favorite movie. Yeah but I like I don't know whatever. It looks like Luke. It could look. It
could be. I was in the movie. I haven't seen it. I've not seen this movie in probably 10 to 15
years at least. Who can open this? I don't know what to do. We played Battleship. I'm thinking of
Battleship. What a fucking pog game that is. Nobody plays it anymore. Have you guys noticed that
Battleship is not cool anymore? Nobody plays it when it's like one of the most interesting games.
You know what I really really really hope to god happens and I'll be the one to start it if I have
to. You know like chess took over Twitch. You're like Among Us took over Twitch. When is Battleship
going to take over Twitch and be a huge thing? I'll do it and actually I'm very happy that chess
got very popular because that's a game. That's a game for brains and it's really interesting.
Where do I go? I can't pick up the I cannot pick up like the sesame street play telephone
machine thing. How do what do I do? Build. Build Legos. What? Well I don't know I could take. What?
I thought it was just whatever. So let's go. Build. Build. Build. What do we go from here?
Oh one two three. It's a metal melter. How come there's been no Star Wars RTS game with like Jedi
and stuff? Has there been? There was but what happened to it? It's been multiple. It exists.
Yes. Did it age well? It's still good shit. Is it really? People still play it.
Yeah maybe I'll play it. Is it run on new hardware? It's on Steam. Is it really?
I'm gonna have to check this out. Oh I missed a blue. Off screen. Can't even get me. Rebuild it.
Wait get the blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue. Blue.
E-sports. Cheater. All right I'll get the right side you get the left side.
Left side. I think we just move. Rebuild. Barrier. Barrier activated. Barrier online.
Why did you say that? Barrier? That was an Overwatch joke? Well it wasn't an Overwatch
joke. It was just I said a thing from Overwatch. If it was an Overwatch joke don't you think I
would have been like hey remember what Overwatch would look like? McCree goes like a shadow.
I just said they were lying. Didn't do anything. What does this do? Oh sick. I thought that was
Worf from Star Trek. Oh C-3PO. Finally. We're dead. Skeletons in a kid's game?
Heck. All right we need another person. Where's another person? Where's the next person?
We're missing somebody. Wait can C-3PO open this? C-3PO come here. Okay that's the button. What
happened to him? Oh shit. You can't control that? Move. All right get that door open. Wait okay I
was gonna say he doesn't have any hands. Can he open it? This is kind of this is sad. Can we get
him his his body parts back? Oh it's an ambush. You did this but I will deny that I did. All right
rebuild. I'm gonna get on that gun. We do oh I need a Jedi for this in free play and his suffering.
No. Oh wait coins. Move. Coins. They did a good job with this game. That's good. I like it. Yeah
they are they're those little buttons. Doesn't this make you just want to buy a big Lego set?
Dump it out on the counter. Look at it for a few minutes and look at the instructions
and then put it all back in the container and put it in the closet and never open it again.
What happened? Oh I gotta break that. Wait give me this. This makes me want to play Luigi's Mansion
3. Did you guys watch that? All right one in the chat if you would actually watch me play
Luigi's Mansion 3 and I think that would be like a POG champ stream. All right let's go play the
first one instead. Yeah it's not very POG. Really? Damn adaptive difficulty. What's going on here?
Let's get out of here. Get together. I love the first one so much. All right for Nintendo
Switch week that's something that I should do. How do I get him up? Uh how do I get C-3PO out
up there? Is he like his own little car? Wait he has his own little car. Wait C-3PO come here.
No wait. Where'd he go? Is he gonna be up? Oh play Mario. Yeah this is gonna be a Mario week.
I'm gonna play Mario Super Mario Super Mario. I'm gonna play Mario Galaxy 2. I've never played
that before. I'm gonna Mario Odyssey. I gotta play Mario Odyssey as well. That's another one that
you'll see probably pretty soon here. We'll go through all the good Switch catalog games that
I never really got to. Hold on that's a lot of blues over there. I played Mario Maker. I played
Mario Maker one and two. Oh what? I also want to do Mario 64 slide levels. Heard that exists as
well. Do I have to jump on these? All right I got one. I have the same anger in Mario RPG when you
try to get the frog coins in the river. What about Zelda? I don't know about Zelda. I never was a
big fan of Zelda. I liked Ocarina of Time. That's kind of it. He's a dive? I'm just losing them as
I get them. Yeah I'm trying to touch the buttons. It's a lot harder than it looks. It's not very
much handling power here. It's children's game. It doesn't mean it's not designed to do more.
Hey. Who said sit down? Shit. RTX on. This company. Yes. You got it. Step on it please.
Developers developers developers developers developers developers developers developers
developers. I miss like the meme ability of Steve Ballmer. Oh it's Chewbacca. Chewy. Chewy. Is it
weird that the Han Solo's Chewy has the same energy as Walter White's Jessie? They both sidekicks.
Yeah that's I guess that's true. I'm gonna step on the other one. Chewy we have to cook. Yeah over
here. No no no don't block it off. Don't ruin it. Good. Now I see why uh co-op with this game makes
a lot of sense considering that yeah there's a lot of things that would go faster with two people.
Wait what? Points. Don't block it in the I did it. I ruined it. No I didn't. Do we get mounts?
This is a switch? All characters except droids can ride creatures. This is awesome. Do they have an
attack? Yeah but you can jump super high off of them. It's a one percent drop. Dude I got it. It
only took me seven thousand attempts. Wait turn it off. How do we turn this shit off?
I'm weird that I have to do here. Oh it's destroyed. He didn't move. You're on fault.
All right get on the mount. Can't fight on the mount. Wait Chewbacca can rip their limbs off?
A little morbid don't you think? Did he do that in the movie? All right somebody came down.
It's referenced in episode four. Oh that's a neat little easter egg. Can we get in this?
This is the Millennium Falcon. How do I activate it? Stop protect me. Shit's ready to go.
Oh there he is. This is where Obi-Wan and him no that's the other one.
They're thinking that's Luke. They're just like why do they oh level complete. Yes you unlocked
Han Solo. Princess Leia. C-3PO. Chewbacca. Are you a true Jedi? No. Is Kit Fisto in the game?
Is he actually unlockable? I'm not that I care that much but I do. Play episode three.
Episode three. Episode three. Episode three. Go to episode two and three.
Hold on I'm in I'm I'm like halfway through um Hoth. Stop being so Hothal.
Am I flying this? Where am I? All right gotta get 16 lasers. I just read that in the chat.
Nobody said that. That's what really would happen. Doesn't matter how good of a pilot
you are when there's like 6 000 ship shooting in random directions you're going to explode.
Wait is that a true mega lull right there? The Darth Vader theme song. Only four more where are
they? The last ones over here. That's the 34 by the way. I know how old I am. You don't have to
remind me. Where are we up to? All right that doesn't even look like Chewbacca. That looks
like cousin It from Adam's Family. All right just dodge the asteroid. Watch out for that asteroid.
All right right now inside of this ship everybody is fucking throwing up.
Because organs are out of their mouths. Even just doing that. Um how do I blow this up?
Zero gravity. Doesn't matter. There are bombs to get apparently. How do I collect them?
Any button? Oh give me it. Eat shit. What? Okay it worked. It's hard to control.
This is too intense for a kids game. There's violence in this you're right.
There's violence in this. No violence in my kids game. Only violence that I want. My kids programming.
Dappy duck getting his face blown off by a shotgun. I have to do that again. All right I'm going to
try to collect like a few of them. That's two right there. All right just go. Fuck. Can I get them back?
I can't get them back. A lot of space missions in this one. Not enough lightsaber fighting.
That's why I return to the jedis better because there's way more lightsaber fights.
That's how I determine how good of a star wars movie it is. By how many actual lightsaber fights
there are. And you love it for so free. Yep and again let's be honest with the franchise.
The lightsabers are the only thing holding this thing together. Without the lightsaber sound effects
no one cares. What about the Mandalorian? Yes I stopped caring about the Mandalorian
after the fourth episode. Haste and point. And then I picked it back up again. Did I just die?
Episode one two three. It was like all right I'm into this. This is pretty cool.
Soundtrack is incredible for the Mandalorians. I get one of the best theme songs of any new show
in a very long time. But I don't I after like episode five they were just doing the same thing
over and over again. There's no lightsaber fight. This is double score zone. I leave. Oh shit I got
him. I liked the Mandalorian. I didn't love it. I really enjoyed the first half. If I can get more
of those bombs. Episode seven and eight are the best. Season two episode two is the best. Season
two is really good. Should I give him more of a chance? I'm seeing a lot of no's. I got shot at
the midair. All right there's something to blow up right here. Secret. Check out what my dog does when
I give him a bone. Hey remember when I said that I think that the Mandalorians like does the best
new Star Wars content in a decade? Remember when I said that? I said that like after the first two
three episodes. I just lost interest. I just did. I just lost interest. I was like I was like oh
this sucks. I didn't know enough lightsabers. Not enough of this. Not enough. No I just like lost
interest. The Millennium Falcon sure has a lot of lives. Lightsabers are dumb. They are not. You
like them. You're up gaslighting yourself. I do. I do. I'm telling you I do love the
you guys are telling me that I don't watch the Mandalorian and I just don't. I did the
the you don't know what that is but I'm the one that lost interest. Unbelievable.
That was sort of obvious. I apologize. That was kind of Peter Griffin.
Oh man. Stop talking over cutscenes. Oh whatever. We saw baby Yoda on your Reddit shelf.
I like baby Yoda. Reddit shelf. Reddit shelf. Oh Normie. Now all of a sudden I'm Normie. Oh I like
oh Mandalorian. I lost interest in the Mandalorian. What the fuck? Fuck you. What are you stupid?
I think baby Yoda was like really cute and fun. Normie Reddit shelf user. We've got a Normie.
Normie alert. So if I don't like the Mandalorian I'm an asshole but if I do if I love the Mandalorian
I'm a Normie. Is there a middle ground? This guy likes Home Alone 2. I love Home Alone 2. I love
both Home Alones. I think they're fantastic. I would love to watch them on stream if I was allowed
to. I find them they're required reading for this stream. Home Alone 1 and Home Alone 2 are required
reading for this stream. If you haven't seen them you have to go watch them. Home Alone 2 is terrible.
Don't know. I mean it's not as good as Home Alone 1. Just like Gremlins and especially Gremlins 2
is required reading on this stream. If you do not like Gremlins 2 and you are watching this stream
right now and you you're like here I can't I can't believe that. I don't I cannot there's no way I
could believe that. When like Hulk Hogan comes and like tells like the Gremlins when he's in the movie
theater like cut the shit because they fucking with the projector. How could you not like that?
It's like it's hysterical. You ruined it. That's like one of five thousand gags that are in that
movie. I'm not a powerful force user yet. I can't lift this up. Was that a bat? I kind of like this
level. I like the scenery. We're about to meet Yoda. That's not Yoda by the way if you're curious.
That's Yoda's like goofy cousin who's like a tax accountant or something. Wait can I get that?
Dove head first into the poison. Wait R2. R2 can you get that? You can't.
That was the sounded like it was starting. Where do I go? Wait Yoda go get that. Yoda you have to
be able to do something. Not Yoda. Um R2-D2. What am I supposed to do? R2-D2 can hover?
You know I don't know that because I didn't play for more than five seconds with R2-D2.
Okay good. Good to know. His favorite franchise. No I didn't say that was my favorite franchise.
Did I? What is my favorite franchise? Uh Niners Drive-Ins and Dives. Come here. Nice.
Classic song. This is the Luke theme. You know I was in the theater and they played Luke's theme.
Just started fucking screaming.
He's just a little giggling. It's Mr. Bean. Mr. Bean. What the hell? Am I supposed to do that?
Wait fix this. If you want to know my secrets, kill that droid that you're with. I can't. He's
R2. He won't be learning anything then. I'm sorry dude. What was he teaching me? How to lift up
things? I'm not strong enough. What was he doing? I don't know. I don't know how to do math anymore.
I think I stole that from somewhere. Where did I steal it from? Me. This family guy when Chris
sticks an army figurine up his nose. Okay so those of you guys that didn't see this, I'm just gonna
say it because like I find it to be funny and I don't care if nobody else does.
In pre-stream chat one time we talked about like doing family dinner too but the only difference
was it was just me and a bunch of actors dressed up as family guy characters and I was Peter
and we just it wasn't even me it was just the family dinner but we were just doing family guy
and there would be like pre-recorded videos of like cutbacks, reference callbacks to like cutaways
so it would be it would just be it would be the same thing like family dinner too.
It's still us but we're also kind of like the Griffin family and it would be unbearable for
you for like fucking two or three hours and we'd just be like oh that reminds me of the time like
it would be me as Peter Griffin but it's me it's not I'm not I'm not actually being Peter
Griffin I'm Jeremy Albertson. I got real close to pulling trigger on that one. All right Yoda come
here. Did Yoda just kill me? Oh all right Yoda come here. Get on me. We fly? Wait I have Yoda's
okay when I wear Yoda on my head I get extra power he's like a he's like wearing a piece
of tin foil he's like an antenna. Yoda can you move like a little to the left? How do we how
do I do anything? Not even my favorite movie anymore. Can we touch this? Why would they have
bats in there? Why would you keep bats in here? R2 can fly. Yeah I know R2 can fly but I mean
how that seems like too far for him to go. Wait he can he's he doesn't die from the poison.
I'm gonna get copy striked. I'm not whatever I'm not gonna get copy striked.
Humming the Mandalorian theme song. Like he's humming a song. Don't ever listen to the radio
ever again. Listening to the radio is illegal. All right I got it. Based and poopy pill.
Thanks I guess. Well how do I get over there now? Wait what? R2 you didn't even do anything you
just like gave us get off me. Oh shit just killed Yoda. Yoda I'm sorry. Yoda never ending like
torture device for Yoda. I'll help you. I'll get you up just grab my hand. Um I don't think
I don't think I can actually help him. Help him R2. Get in the way so he bounces off of you.
How did I get soft locked in this game? I don't understand. If I run too far away he won't
he'll have to get spawned somewhere else right? I'm just trying to go far enough away where he
gets pulled. Why can I not walk? All right he'll get pulled eventually. Pull him. Pull back. I
think I actually have to restart this. And R2's just over there like oh what a bunch of
fucking idiots. That's over I have to restart. Restart. I can't switch to Yoda. Episode four.
Look we're only like a few episodes later. Come on. Hey Joe it's Star Wars. I can't skip the cut
scene. Stop saying that. You literally did not need Yoda for that part. Didn't? Watch out. Can
someone tell him? Tell him what? All right speed run. Just get to Yoda. Get the get the coins too.
No just go. Yoda percent. No no don't have this happen to him now please.
Jump out. Those are some pretty good fucking moves. Watch out episode four. I couldn't get
past the Death Star level. Well you were eight. I'm 34. I don't think I'll have that much of a
problem. Can we cut to me like raging and I can't do it. Oh you're not dead. I'm gonna let this play
out for a second because uh this is just chasing around a fly in the house. Why is it still alive?
God. A plant. Right I just. Latch on man. You're making me look really bad.
You look terrible. Stupid dog. You make me look bad.
Oh courage. You can do better than that. What is that accent? I'm getting showing up. All right
new year's resolution. No more screaming. You guys understand? No more of that. No more screaming.
I'm not gonna scream anymore. I'm just gonna chill. I'll be just hanging out playing a game.
Just chilling. No more yelling and like. Like no. I'm done with that. No more.
Kids eat this shit up don't they? No emotion. No. All right no talking. Do you think I can do it?
No talking for five minutes. I can't say anything. No speaking for five minutes. You don't think you
think it's possible? Okay at three at three hours and 52 minutes on the stream I'm gonna
not talk for five straight minutes. Okay here we go. I have to talk. You know when you watch like a
gameplay walkthrough of something that you're stuck on and you find a channel like this that
you're just like skipping through this person's like two hour long video which is like dude what
do you fucking how do you do this? You're doing terrible. I just want to see what what the next
puzzle part is and you can't you can't even do it. This is a walkthrough. All right this video has
four views. You if you were looking for that if you were a kid and you were looking at how to beat
this part after you just leave you'd be like all right well I guess I'm gonna figure it out on my
own. I need Yoda back. Somebody said gaining viewers. That you know what that was actually
kind of nice. That was like a talking break. How do I feel? That was pretty good. It's like
this is quiet for like 10 almost 10 minutes. That felt that was like a nice break. Do that more often.
Those two minutes? No it was not. I started doing that at 352 on stream. I gotta get him up here.
I have to put Yoda. All right hey get on this. Get on that. No what the fuck? That's not what I
wanted to do. Why did he just why did Yoda jump all the way back there? I can't lower this. I need
Yoda on my head to lower that but R2D2 didn't go on it. It's gonna be in the walkthrough? Yeah.
I'm not recording my mic. I'm capturing the game only. I have it split. I have uh the audio split
so it's not capturing my fucking voice. All right let's go. Editors do the right thing.
All right R2 get over here before I scrap you. Get on it. All right R2D2 go on that. All right
R2D2 go on that. How do I jump with R2D2? Let's jump. Start. Okay it's five on the d-pad.
What? What the fuck? You have to move with me. All right but how come he won't go on that with
the computer controller? I don't understand. This walkthrough sucks. All that matters is you just
skip to the part that you need to see. All right go on there R2D2. Who? R2D2? What? R2 what the fuck?
This sucks. This is so like this. They didn't do it good enough. What do you want me to say?
Okay what do you want me to say? Throw the controller into the ground. I have not any
trouble at all for four hours until the stupid swamp level. And of course, of course it's a
swamp level. All game developers. I don't care if it matches the fucking scene for scene of the movie.
Don't do swamp levels ever. They're all terrible. Make it concrete. I don't care if it matches the
movie scene for scene. Make it like grass. This is the walkthrough? Oh shit it is. That's right I
forgot. All right I'm supposed to not laugh this hard today. Watch a walkthrough to make
my walkthrough. No don't kill me. R2 get on that. I can't switch to R2 because I you don't
understand. I don't have two people here. Okay R2 get the fuck on that. R2 get on. Don't spawn
any fucking bats. Why won't he go on this one R2? Stand on that one. What the fuck is he doing?
What is he doing? Why won't he jump on this one first and then this one? That's what he's supposed
to do. Switch to R2. What if I switch back from R2? Okay I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I
get it. I get it. Fuck the goddamn swamp level. All swamp levels suck. If I ever make a video game
I'm gonna have the swamp level be first. The first level in the game and then what happens is
the swamp level before you even start it's like here we are. We're at the swamp.
Everyone loves these. Then you get to start and then a fucking nuclear bomb drops in front of you
and it's just and then you do skip that level and then like a portal opens on the left and it's
like oh it looks like we can't go this way through the swamp. Let's try this portal.
What the fuck? I get hit twice. Why? Seriously I get hit touched twice by bats and Yoda
fucking yeets off of me. I'm so bad right now because like this is I hate this thing.
Why are there even bats here? What's the point? This is children's game. Quiet.
Shh. I'm fine. Everybody relax. I'm so tilted right now and I have to calm down.
This is not hard. It's just stupid. It's very dumb. It's that this I loved I you know episode
five is not in my favorite fucking movie anymore. Episode one was way better.
Okay those of you telling me to to change to Yoda I want if I change to Yoda if I don't
that little can guy if I change the can guy right now Yoda jumps off my head.
You stand Yoda get over I mean what if they're both little lower all the mushrooms and then
short the mushroom lower both switch to r2 don't jump off me all right I got it I got it I got
I'm gonna I'm gonna do for I'm gonna go for it okay so tomorrow we're gonna be trying to get
Darth Vader um Darth Vader is a tough guy to unlock it was easy I know I just didn't hate this
I hate swamp swamps just fuck me up and they make me angry swamps just make me very angry
light town no I don't swamp stupid I don't never want to see a swamp ever again
Yoda's dead whatever he's too slow yo come here what the fuck is in here what why is there a
tractor in here there's a tractor I don't remember there being like a John Deere kids toy tractor in
this fucking stupid movie I just called this stupid movie it's not why is this here
oh don't get locked in switch to yoda switch the can I have to look
minus twos how have I gained viewers during this what are you still doing here
okay who do I gotta be uh what do I do now oh look Yoda's just on the tractor
is he actually how can he go this way
on the tractor come on Yoda you can do it can I uh grapple toy Yoda oops I can't grapple
what are you doing great music cue Yoda crashed the fucking tractor have I
it's pretty good oh let me get this shit off of the screen go bats look more bats
well hey well what the fuck are you dying for I was standing on the button
there's not enough room for three people here we take up the whole bridge I'm trying to grapple
I'm gonna I'm losing my mind I think I really think I'm like I've changed games no man not
right now no that's not gonna happen tonight oh shit r2 where's r2 r2 what are you doing the thing
is you know all of you know that that's not on purpose it's just like hard to see what the depth
is because like you know that I'm not doing that on purpose I know you do this pretending is
exhausting oh um the last like three the last three days in a row I've just it's just been oh
shit what happened Darth when did this happen when Darth Vader show up in this movie sacrifice the
droid oh he's what's wrong with him all right Yoda get in here no I'm Yoda versus Darth Vader
this is the fan fiction we all wanted this shit never happens in those movies get up all right
Luke lift me put this back together uh Luke come here lift me up throw it over there all right let's
get up no put it back I need another one put me this one all right let's go hey all right let's
embarrass let's just absolutely embarrass the fuck out of him blast hit from r2d2 he's dead we killed
him he exploded nice work everyone this is a long level I always just feel like that because
it took me like 30 minutes to do a children's puzzle probably that something under here
oh what's this what is this a weather a weathervane what is it ridges up let's go go boys
get that bat come on r2 perfect opportunity for you to show up how do you mean I'll play as Yoda
I thought Luke was bald for a second finish it right now what was the point of that
either side let's go dude imagine being Yoda yeah I know it's pretty cool
stop using Yoda he sucks he's really slow I mean I get to play as a Yoda though build it whatever
it is cannon bats are too op in this game get storm troopers just literally sitting on their
ass and all it takes is a bat to touch you once or twice and you just explode r2 excellent work
now we got this take it out this is it this is where we take the thing out of the um
we take the plane out we need you order to help Yoda you do it you know what I could go for right
now a huge soft hot pretzel big one what the fuck is that that's Obi-Wan all right we're almost at
the end of episode five unlock all I'm not gonna unlock all all right we got one more after this
right or is this the last one please god I'm so high right now well click the x in the corner
sit down take a few deep breaths have a glass of water and just relax
here comes Darth Vader all right what happens to this part of the movie this is the part where he
goes this is the Lando right come here R2 come here wait he can't put Legos together when he
said there's a red brick where I don't see a red brick is there a red brick I don't understand
where's the oh that red brick that one I thought you said somebody said was behind the x-wing
can't even go over there I don't think I can get that how do I get that you have to be in
pre-play right okay well here we are again you get to do this again you can crash the
tractor I will what the fuck I think I was already dead this is what I'm talking about
this is my favorite I like the lightsaber fight no swamp levels we leave you hover over there
and get that whatever I don't care I don't even care streamer confused by glass hold it out
excuse me R2 ding where's the ding I love when I get to play this game and be a hero
okay shoot shoot the door shoot the door not done oh shoot door let's go only bounty hunters can
access these areas not fair go to Lucas raid what seriously stormtrooper mask can you get one too
R2 can you get a stormtrooper mask oh here he is again Darth Vader all right I don't know what
that is but activate it you two fight R2 is going to do all the weird work here scripted
it's just scripted you gotta let hold on is it scripted all right attacking him what does
this even do this puts the gas up can I jump off off the gas wait wait whoa whoa whoa he's
like he's dazed what's wrong with him all right so just play as R2 and just wait till he
Luke hunt get him on there stunning spawn camping your own son why is he not stunned
wait there are two put together quick before he does anything I'm naked I thought I just
looked was naked with a loincloth on all characters except droids can use this
and operate the crane now get over there now activate that for me what is this
you can't like touch that can R2 touch that I have no idea what that is for your armpits
I would rather never mind wait I don't have I'm not a stormtrooper I need my stormtrooper helmet
go get it chat is fucked up today well look I'm gonna listen yesterday there was a two and a half
billion dollar bet they're a little rowdy okay I better running away from me R2 um this is why
you have two players all right let's go R2 hurry 800% toxicity tonight R2 R2 R2 hurry the fuck up
what are you doing oh let's go come on R2 scary it's so scary here we go final boss
force push yeah be a shield for me please streamer when you want killed all right I want
everybody to act in the chat right now like this is fucking crazy like holy shit I can't believe
he's actually gonna do it do it for like a few minutes here go ahead I'm fucking nervous though
like this for the first I've ever been in the game fuck come on come on come on up up up up up
up up come on man I gotta like shake my hands a little this is like the hardest fucking fight in
the game come on I have one life left no bad start really bad fucking start fuck it's okay
sorry sorry it's okay it's okay if I do it first try that that's gotta be some kind of I don't
know I don't think I've ever seen anybody do that before I'm gonna be quiet for a little bit guys
because this is like yeah I'm not gonna really talk that much in the next few minutes fuck
get in there get in there push this and then get him up there come on go go go go go go go go where
I have he's got half health half health last time I got here he was at like one heart further than
this all right stop one fuck perfect parries it has to every parries to be perfect I'm not
gonna be able to do it if it's not perfect no fuck no no what the fuck no no oh so stupid man
so stupid when they when when you get a spawn behind you like that it just and you can that's
so stupid I can't fucking believe it unbelievable look at how look at his hearts too he was a full
heart lower than he was last time what was it four and a half hours all right get over here
he went into the screen during that it must have been like it's a fucking kids game man
what are you doing you can't like beat darth vader are you over the age of eight a ton of
people left during that did they really did they I don't see it all right r2 get on that
oh hurry you handle the heat done 500 people left no that's all right maybe we'll see them again
pretty good e3 acting fly over there what are you doing
holy shit I just decapitated that guy oh no it's vader let's go you want to fuck with me fine
wrong target whoa he's here r2 get over there quick oh r2 carries the franchise not really
that's it that's not it wait wait we're talking purely kids because that's different depending
on the age group r2 d2 carries the kid crowd and so does Chewbacca but I would probably say
the adult crowd like who carries the franchise for the adults probably Han Solo that's definitely
Han Solo I can't even see I get him oh shit get that in double jump I'm losing tons of money I
don't care do a ground pound feeding the enemy team uh an r2 dude what I don't get it what's
going on am I stupid okay let's go let's go the ultimate in fall jokes have been today
that's not even fair I'll be honest I kind of clocked out too like 20 minutes ago I kind of
clocked out in this game but I still enjoy what I'm doing give me that you get it no that's so
stupid I switched to him right when he fell down so I lost the money down zero stud Andy
whatever activate that while I go do work of course not oh that's a speed droid this is the
best strategy this is just this is doing the running boot in battle toads are you you know
it's really weird about this I forget what happens after that I can't wait did he just groin hit
okay um does that happen in the actual movie you like fucking pro skater groin smashed
like ball bust all right this is the final level of episode five this is it this is the big one
because when I blow up the Death Star or whatever happens at the end of episode five nothing
happens oh yeah the ending of episode five sucks right isn't it just like you'll never get out
you're here forever and then it's over right when does he get turned into a piece of wall art
oh it's right now it just looks like he full body scanned himself in the office printer scanner
combo this is just like bare ass all right let's go land up with c3pio he's a quick builder quick
building I like it quick building oh it's Boba Fett everybody's favorite character
oh wait wait wait wait who's the force anybody a force user here no you're just like dps your dps
your dps where the fuck is the support where's the where's the force user we have three dps here no
tank no fucking healer stupid you can activate Boba I think you probably would just stand back if
you saw a guy do the cigar yeah he's like he's got it under control I think all right let's
switch to Chewbacca Joey you did have a cool ship I forgot about that shot and I would wait
for the helicopter there's another one of these somewhere we got to activate all these we droid
we got a droid but that was a that was almost a quadruple slap sorry we got a droid no we need
to c3pio all right stop I think I think I think whatever go shit shit I need to do what do I do
I need to okay let's go this way I kind of turn that what do I do about that
right isn't this the way we came this is the very beginning of the level oh I thought it was gonna
be r2 no not that way no which way r2 all right we have to move this all right plug this in
let's fucking go what's that do for us oh it's a droid aha yes yes yes now we can open some other
doors let's go follow me let's go you not you you put your eyes into that thing and turn it on
the stormtrooper helmet on on chewy all right fine all right watch out everybody move like I
didn't even know he died okay let's go no my helmet can't move these oh no he's a bear he
really is just wild why do we think having a wild animal around was a good idea he snapped
build build build build build I got it car let's go wait crank it who can do this
oh me I can do this who the somebody just came up with me it was me Lando that's a good tactic
there's the helipad I got 20 000 I'm doing all right I'll break the crane pick up the droid oh
okay got one droid put you over here the other droid come on three field let's go all right how
do I get them up here oh there we go all right let's move elevator down look at the droids I
feel like I'm just kind of fucking with them right now see freebo come on oh oh what's this oh droid
come here this is the time for r2 to shine beautiful what happened to this bump what's wrong with this
guy oh I okay I got it let's go three peel it's safe ow all right what do we do here we're going
to move puzzles around I need three PO shit I need to move this this way I can you fit through
my god I thought that wasn't movable I love his recovery move it's awesome
it's the last uh pylon hit it up wait that's three out of three aim over we'll kill no who
is a double jump do you have a double jump no do you have a double jump Chewbacca I don't care
all right let's get out he hates the game he fucking hates this all right draw straws who's
going to go first okay once twice three shoot oh I'll beat you oh once twice three shoot
rocker wins again once twice three shoot oh sorry three PO wins he had rock lost a hand though
the two droids once twice three shoot oh it looked like it was r2 r2 wins
r2 I need you to come over to the steam room this is relaxing good put that bridge up there it is
all right two people stand here and we need two people to stand
over there somebody pull this it's one remember you're so fucking smart sometimes I can be
you know broken clock is right at least twice a day hey Chewie let's get the heck out of here
oh oh no enemies he's just good he's got genius level IQ got 20 000 bits I don't want to lose him
okay um somebody clip right now like clip right now that stormtrooper was in a bikini
what was that am I crazy it was a beach trooper that's actually what they're called
that was luke he just had a little shiner we got a link hold on there it is I did I win
is that how the movie ends super story what does that mean nice finish story are we hiding
it was like the toothpaste dentist droid thing from the adams family all right that was cool
that was episode 5 12.5 completion rate you have unlocked I can't even like fight in here I don't
understand what is this new toy unlocking Indiana Jones I did didn't I all right hold on this is
apparently a very important link I need to look at I'm probably going to call it here okay this is
gross gross I mean I don't even look like this this is not what I'm going to look like
I don't I don't think I'm going to look like this that's just weird right that doesn't look
anything like me those are all wrong this one's correct in only two weeks that's all it takes to
get a massive dumper all right I'm out of here no way this one's really good too okay so let's go
how much have I shaved off of the debt 30 40 million right 20 million for the um the noise
10 million or it was 20 million I shaved off 20 million hey the egg thanks to the 10 community
subs thank you egg it's 10 pog subs thank you the egg frog man also gave five community subs
thank you also the zat zuck irl also gave 50 earlier 5 000 bits to be exact thanks for the
gigantic bit drop zat zuck here but not everyone in chat has necessarily agree with these terms
but I made it and I think it's funny oh Jesus okay this is long let's see hold on what are all of
these there's a there's some of these all right let's go over okay how to clear debt all actions
can only be monetarily redeemed once 35 million show auto on cam for at least 10 seconds okay I
can do that 500 million show your two whole feet on cam unadultered for at least 10 seconds
cross that one off uh 800 million play streamer sim again but with face cam on for at least four
hours really 800 million shaved off the streamer sim stream again that's a lot a whole billion is
eat one entire gallon of mayonnaise on stream cam must be on and showing you eating said gallon of
mayonnaise this is really bizarre ransom demands it's like sorry uh can you let everybody out of
the bank here are my demands show auto for 10 seconds show your bare feet in front of me
play streamer sim and eat a gallon of mayonnaise and i'll let somebody out uh stream one this is
for 1.5 billion stream yourself going to a real general physician and get your height accurately
you agree to that one you agree to that one that's you want me to accurately measure my actual
accurate height to shave off 1.5 billion of the 2.5 billion it can't be an actor it no it won't
be i will make sure it i will accurately i think a lot of you guys are in agreements for that one
jog five gate raids and do an actual fat fuck irl stream with the voice and the cam on what's the
voice clear the debt completely is the dump truck emote debt clear an entire chat zerk's off
zorn stream oh that no i can't drink that many gatorades i'll throw up if i can shave 1.5 billion
off by doing a full-on true accurate shoes and socks off feet on the ground i'll kill two birds
with one stone there i will do it to shave off that 1.5 billion okay this picture i swear every
time i look at it just makes me laugh all right uh i will see you guys on let's say monday thursday
thursday or friday keep an eye on the sus either thursday or friday check the sus tomorrow same
time around like one or two p.m pacific on thursday or friday more likely thursday but in case something
comes up friday maybe two bug snacks i don't know what that is all right i'm out of here let's take
a look at subs tonight that was uh did i hold on did i shave any money off at all by doing this
stream this was a like 2.5 billion dollar they chose this how much got shaved off for this
something or i had to be something nothing zero oh this is part of the deal right okay it was a
chat choice and a bunch of other demands right okay i see now you're right i actually you know
i'll be honest with you i think i think that's i i mean i think i want to play that again and
like do the rest of them that could be a really really good just when i have nothing else to do
just play that i'm not saying that's going to happen the rest of the week but i'm just saying
it it's a good backup to be like you know what i didn't do episode six let's go six day rule
yeah you're right keep an eye on that thanks all for those subs and talking is hard today
thanks for all the subs guys thanks for all the support as always i want to check on that
that rts as well yeah i do want i want to check that yeah we're gonna raid uh we're gonna raid
nova tonight and i'll tell you why uh nova is playing uh assassin's creed valhalla and i want
you to tell me if the game looks any good i want to know it's been a long long time since we've uh
shown ourselves i know it's been a while really funny dude really good guy go check him out if
he apparently is playing it on the hardest difficulty it's an ubi soft game so you know
you know what to look for it'll still look like it's made for children ubi soft i'm just looking
at who's streaming right now and i'm like wait assassin's creed valhalla let's take a look at
that all right goodbye good night everybody see you in a couple of days two or three days
i just like clicked the wrong thing like five times all right goodbye