Hey, what is going on, everybody? Turma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Spy with the Ambassador, the Kunai, and the Dead Ringer.
My typical Spy setup, a lot of you guys know that. This video is going to discuss the Spy.
It's gonna be kind of a casual commentary, I'm gonna sit back and talk about things, relax, drink a few Dr. Peppers, you know, crack one open.
If I had one, I would, but I have one already open, so that joke does not exist because I can't make it.
But I want to talk about the old Spy. Those of you that will remember, and I don't know why I thought about this.
When I was getting this gameplay, I thought about it because there's a couple of instances where my knife comes down really quickly and I was like, you know what?
Wasn't there a time when the Spy didn't have that? And there wasn't. For those of you that do not know, the Spy's backstab animation never was like this.
It was never this quick a few years ago. Actually, it was probably more than that.
But it was when the game came out. When the game came out, and maybe for like six, seven, eight months after the game came out,
the backstab animation took almost a full second to complete. You brought the knife up, and then you brought the knife down.
It was kind of slow in comparison to what it is right now, where it's almost a quarter of a second when you stab somebody.
It was much longer than that. I'm going to put a link in the description here of what it looks like compared to what it looks like now.
I'm old. Seriously. I thought about this, and this change happened when I was in college.
It's almost four or five years ago now that this change was made.
I remember sitting in my college dormitory and being like, oh wow, they changed the backstab animation.
I'm young and fun and young and good looking. Fast forward a little bit. I'm an old shithead.
I'm just sitting here drinking Dr. Pepper's five years later. I really can't even believe that it's been five years since that change.
This is also kind of around the time when they added the compression blast to the Pyro, because the Pyro never had the compression blast.
I'm just going through all these changes in my head and thinking to myself, if you were to tell me when I was in college,
all this stuff is going to be hats. There's going to be new backstab animations.
Pyro's going to have a thing that knocks people away with this compression blast.
If you told me all this stuff, I would say, what the hell are you talking about?
TF2 is just like a fun multiplayer game that I play online sometimes.
I would have never believed that this would have turned into the TF2 Hat Combat Simulation Virtual Reality Burger Boy 2012 Emperor of Earth.
I would never have been able to guess that.
So what's the point here? Why did I make this video? What's the point of me making this video?
The point is, from right now, July 22nd, 2013, where is this game going to be five years from now?
In 2018, if TF2 still has an active community, if they're still making updates, or if TF3 comes out, what the hell are they going to do?
How are they going to change this game even more than they already have drastically done it?
And I don't think anyone will ever be able to foresee it, because nobody could foresee that there was going to be a hat economy.
Who the hell knew that was going to happen? Who in their right mind could have ever said that TF2 was going to have a hat economy?
What? What are you talking about?
And it interests me for a very specific reason.
It's because when you get older and you look back at the games that you've been playing,
and you look back at the games that have been out for a very long time, that have undergone huge, drastic changes,
and you can remember back to when the game was completely different,
it's kind of sad and kind of a little depressing, but it's cool at the same time,
because you get to see from the beginning of a game's life to where it's currently standing,
and you get to see all the changes, all the things that happened, and it sort of reminds me,
now we're going a little bit deeper here, but the console generations.
I've been alive long enough to see all the console generations,
all the way back from the Atari almost, the regular Nintendo, the whole Super Nintendo, N64, PlayStation 1,
all those generational changes. I've seen everything.
And it's crazy to think about Team Fortress 2 has gone through just about one and a half console generations.
I mean, it started during the midst of the Xbox 360 and the PS3, the prime of those two consoles,
2006, 2007, everybody had one, everyone was using one,
and we're going to go into the Xbox One and the PS4, and TF2 is still here, still actively played.
So it's done its own, in quotes, console generational leaps, if that makes any sense.
And I truly do wonder if TF2 eventually, if there is no TF3,
if they will do some type of source 2.0 port, because I'm sure a lot of you guys know the source engine,
the new source engine is currently being worked on.
So a world where we would see maybe another generational jump for this game, Team Fortress 2,
is a complete graphical reworking or a port to the new source engine.
I don't know if that's going to happen. It's obviously just wishful thinking at this point,
because who knows what Valve's going to do with this game.
Nobody knows, but that's really where I want to take this video.
I just want to wrap it up here, guys.
A quick little casual commentary about the spy and then transitioning,
kind of going off on a tangent about consoles and stuff, but that's going to wrap it up here.
I'll see you guys all next time. Thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it, and I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.