Yeah, I'm here. I'm here. This dude hates sorcery. I don't hate sorcery.
I don't hate sorcery. Why'd you get, where'd you get that idea? I mean you thought there was
gonna be sorcery today, but you were wrong and so was I. And there's a reason for it.
Reason number one, to be very clear. Uh, I didn't want to play it for like an hour and 40 minutes.
Reason number two, pre-stream chat decided, they decided, not to do it today.
It's like 150 people guys. Pre-stream chat wanted their, their own sorcery stream. Its own stream,
not just like a couple hours. And the new Hitman map came out and what is this thing popping up
on the top of my, what is this? What's this new thing they added? I keep seeing the different subs
pop in and out. I don't like this. How do I get rid of this? How do I get rid of this activity feed?
I don't want this activity feed. Anyways, uh, yeah, sorcery will be its own thing.
Uh, we're also going to play multiverses today in a sponsor segment. I fucking love that game,
by the way. While I was kind of sick, I was been playing it on my Xbox. Shhh. I'm just sitting
there sick playing it on Xbox. Xbox Andy. Yeah, guess what? Series S. What's wrong with it?
It's everything you want in a console. I actually believe that. The Xbox is a stinker. No, it is not.
The Xbox Series S is actually really good. You get the game pass on there. You can put on YouTube
and Twitch. It's like a media box for me. It's not a console. That's literally your worst take.
I just made that up. I made that person up. No one said that. I combined three messages.
Somebody said, that is your worst. And then somebody said, I'm getting takeout tonight.
And I just combined them to make my narrative make sense. Anyways, uh, Hitman has a new map.
I played all the Hitmans, obviously. So we're going to do this. I'm feeling better. A lot better
than I was a week ago. So I think I'm all right now. For those of you that were curious, COVID
kind of came through the house a week and a half ago or so. And then I got put into a colitis flare
up probably because of it. I'm negative for COVID, but I have this colitis problem. So, but that's
getting worse. That's fine. That's not out of the ordinary. I know how to deal with that,
but we're good to go. Anyways, let me tweet. Give me one second. I got to make sure I get this right.
One sec. Hey, I'm back. All right. So let's do the Hitman map. I haven't played Hitman since Hitman 3
VR, which I wasn't a big fan of. In fact, I was very, very adamantly opposed to it.
Must be a long ass tweet. No, it wasn't. I just, I had to go grab, I had to get something.
All right. You guys ready for Hitman? You guys good for Hitman? Okay. Is the new map any good?
How does it compare to the rest of the series? Am I going to like it? Am I going to hate it?
How is it? Be honest. Don't sugar coat this. Is it all right? No idea. I mean, it literally came out
like two, three days ago. So maybe you don't know. All right, let's go. What's my title? Oh,
it's all right. That title's fine. It's another concrete level. It fucking better not be.
I actually mean that. It better not be. Is it actually? Better not be. That's fucking loud.
All right. Are you guys ready? Destinations. It's this Ambrose Island. Is this new one?
Are you guys ready for this? Should I turn it up? Should I turn it down? Handsome.
Go away. Red Andy. My skin is tinted a little orange. So what? Fuck off. I have like red,
I have red, rosy, red cheeks. Fuck you. All right. You got a problem?
Then speak it into the speaker. The Ark Society's annual.
Are all these people dead? Which should give us ample time. Mr. Gray has an off the books
request. Perhaps you should explain. I actually don't know. No crest.
Spoilers. My best fixes. It's Hitman three. It's your fault for being here.
The militia literally hit man three to cease all attacks on Providence.
Stand by and crest and his men reinventing themselves as a glorified gang of international
thieves. They specialize in ruthless spectacle, heists, zero regard to collateral damage.
I've seen the man's file. What did you expect? It's not like I had much choice.
Seeing as all my best lieutenants were killed by you too.
Crest is a rabid dog is my responsibility. Shut up. You don't care. An isolated harbor
north from the Strait of Malacca. Coincidentally, one of Wazir's old ports of call.
According to my intel crest and his men have joined forces with the local pirate syndicate
to raid a passing tanker. His goal control unit for an ether core being covertly shipped abroad.
The satellite is a node in the company's most secure cloud storage network.
So they would bear a fortune to preserve its integrity. What is Crest's end game extortion?
Money. If I had to guess, we don't have the luxury of a full investigation for us to move
against the constant. We need Providence to think the threat is over and lower their guard.
Another militia attack on ether will raise alarms. I agree. 47. You'll need to eliminate
Crest and destroy that control unit before we lock the militia out. The satellite cannot fall into
their hands. We'll need a cover story for ICA. I only need one grenade and I'll be able to do it
easily. The syndicate already has an active ICA contract on her head. Take her out and
we'll even get our expenses paid. Well, I never had you pegged as a rebel. I'm warming to it.
Are you eating toothpaste? What are you talking about? 47, seeing as I know Crest,
I'll provide field support. Meet you out east. Sounds like a plan. 47 out.
You hate it. Go again. Fucking relax. I haven't streamed like a week. Sorry, guys. I have a lot
of energy right now. Um, hold on. Uh, I gotta turn this back on and ask me what happened. Hey,
there I am. All right. So we need to, uh, we need to, we gotta kill, kill, kill. I haven't played
Hitman in a while either. What's with the toothpaste stuff? I don't know. Why are you asking about
toothpaste? Can somebody fill me in on what the toothpaste thing is here? It's toothpaste joke.
I don't get it. All right, let's go. Uh, I, I'm going to do default Andy. That's fine.
Neutralize the satellite control unit. Easy enough. You know, I, I keep avoiding on,
I feel like this is a YouTube embedded video. Is it? It is. Okay. I thought that was,
but how do I go? Okay. Play. All right. Let's go. Let's go. It's been a while since I've
turned a computer on. I'm not fucking around. I've not turned this computer on. I have not
turned on the computer in five days. I think that's accurate. All right. Professionals fine.
Master. Why is this on master? Who did that? I didn't do that. Is it weird that I actually?
No, we're not doing master. No way. When did I put master on? Try master for one life? No,
I don't think so. Just in time. It seems crest didn't disclose the true object of the heist to
his partners. Okay. So Acre has seized one of the satellite control units, key cards as collateral
until they can renegotiate. The militia have set up camp near the remains of a colonial outpost.
Both crest and the control unit should be nearby. You'll need to destroy the unit itself or render
it inoperable by retrieving both key cards. Give me a grenade crest. He'll have given his to someone
he trusts, but Acre is less inclined to delegate. She should be in the pirate place when she's not
out among the locals. Okay. I provided you with a GPS tracker. Activate it when you're done and
I'll initiate extraction. The sooner we finish up here, the better. All right. Sounds easy enough.
I thought it was like a superhero costume. I was like, holy shit, I have like a superhero costume on.
Okay. How are we doing? We effing? It's going to happen. Unfortunately, I have to deal with it
for now. Okay. Eliminate, eliminate, deny access to the surveillance satellite,
destroy the satellite. Who's this guy? All right. Let's get over here. It's like an island.
Am I allowed in here? How's this? I'm not trespassing. What? I'm just going to the freezer.
This is just weird. Okay. Is there anything I can do in here? Wait, fish. Got it. Can I take, wait,
what's this? A fishing line. Okay. Might be useful later. All right. We're good. All right.
Let's go. I'm not, I'm not, I'm not going to, I'm not going to. These are the targets. No, what? No,
they're not. Not even close. Destroy satellite control unit. Do I have to do that or can I just
throw a brick through a window and hit the person in the head? Stop saying teeth. I don't know what
that means. I'm going to go this way. What do I have for weapons? How do I open up my menu? Is it
tab? Holds a button. What's the menu? I, yeah. Okay. GPS tracker. Coin. Gun. All right. Let's go.
I forgot how pretty this game was. Okay. Right over here. That's the first target. Should I
change disguise? I'm just kind of a guy in a scuba outfit. Is that weird? Is it weird for me to be
look like this? Is this weird? You too? No, this is not weird. Why do I have music? Holy shit. This
guy's got a whole studio in here. I got to get in there. This streamer. Please go away from me.
How do I get in here? Why can't I go in? I can't climb in this. I have a lockpick though, don't I?
Let's put the gun away, please. Don't I have a lock? Yeah, I do. I don't have a lockpick. How?
All right. I need to find the key. I need to get in that streamer room. Pretty much how I do
fishing as well. How many of you guys go fishing and just cast into the water and just reel it
back and you're not even trying? You're just humoring the one friend that actually wants to
be there. Okay. I don't know how to get in there, but is there Intel over there? No.
Okay. All right. This person's right over here. Wait, what's that?
I'm making sure I have a lot of stuff too. What is this? What? Is it arm wrestling?
Okay. I've seen these videos before. I've seen. Let's go. You want to fucking go?
Hold on. I can't save right now? Next round. Let's see. What happened? All right. I'm ready.
Ready up. Wind up. I don't get it. Do I have to tap? Tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap. Okay.
You hurt his hand on my face. Why am I making it out of cement? All right. I'm going to get
this guy right here. See you later. I killed that guy. I legitimately, I think I just killed him.
Come on. Get up here. I have to go through all of them. Okay. Should I just drop him? Shut up.
Why don't you get up here and show me? Wait, this is the guy.
I hope I can do it to him. So now what? I get to be friends with this guy?
Can I save the game? I would save the game. I can't save it. I have to just do this until
I can stop. Okay. Is it going to like cut to the next scene where every single person in the town
has a red hand on their face and I'm like counting hundreds? I don't understand. How many more times
do I have to do this? What the fuck? Why didn't they shoot me? Why didn't they do anything?
I'm so confused. What? Why didn't they do anything? I don't understand why they didn't do anything.
I literally aimed the gun and shot the guy in the head and everyone was aiming at me.
I'm going to do this to everybody here. I'm going to hit every single person here.
Should I? Krust appears impressed and has requested to talk with you. Oh wait. That's me
talking to me. What's up? I guess so. I want to talk to you about something in private.
Nothing sinister. There's no hard feelings here. I just have an offer for you. Come and hear me out.
That's all I ask. Are we going to go with a bodyguard? Hey, are you the guy that can
clearly kick the shit out of every bodyguard I have stronger than all my men? Come over here
in private with me alone. I'm the wicked rich guy. Why would we do this alone? Should I just
do it now? Oh my god. There are two bodyguards here. I was about to strangle them.
Bro, you're going to stand right next to the red barrel. This guy was talking shit earlier
about cartoons. You're in one right now. What? You're standing right next to the red explosive
barrel. Okay.
Punishment someone who could be an inside man but won't buckle under intense interrogation
if he's caught. I'd do it myself but my time and expertise would be better spent covering our tracks
and you've shown me that my guys aren't up for the job either. Smoking next to a red cartoon
barrel. I can hold my own. Excuse me. Why was he itching his wrists? That guy was itchy.
He didn't even. Why did it not explode? Hold on. Why did it not explode? He was just itching his arm.
Hollywood about it. Hold on. Come on. Your attention span can't be that fucking.
I'm gonna hide. I can't even. Where am I going? What happened? Should I do it for real? I gotta
do it for real. I gotta do it for real. I have to do that mission for real. Let me do it for real.
I'm gonna do it for real. I'll do it for real. I'm gonna do it for real. All right. I'm gonna do it
for real. For real. For real. No more fucking around. Could I have poisoned his cigar or something?
Certain prominent individuals, government facilities, big targets. But that means big payouts.
I'm looking for someone who can take a little punishment. Someone who could be an inside man.
Okay. Buckle under intense interrogation if he's caught. I'd do it myself but my time and
expertise would be better spent covering our tracks. And you've shown me that my guys aren't up for the
job either. I need someone I can depend on. I can hold my own. I know we only just met but you have
this quality to you. I can't really pin it down. It's familiar but alien at the same time and
your face. Don't take this the wrong way but it feels like if I looked away for a minute I'd
completely forget every feature. You might be my missing piece here. I don't need or want a decision
right now. This is a life-changing choice. I know we just met. It could be the start of some big
things for you but there would be no backing out. I don't need any more disappointments. Make sure
this is what you really want. I'll be here for a few more days at least so
no rush. I'll think about it. What happened? What's going on? Can I say yes? What was that?
No fuck you! I wanted his outfit! No shit! I wanted the outfit. Oh god damn it. I swear to god.
Government facilities big targets but that means big payouts. Just puncture the barrel.
Someone who could be an inside man but won't buckle. Yeah I'll do it. How do I say I'll do it?
I'd do it myself but my time and expertise would be better spent covering our tracks.
How do I say yes I'll do it? You've shown me that my guys aren't up either. I need someone I can
depend on. I can hold my own. I know we only just met but you have this quality to you. I can't
really pin it down. It's familiar alien at the same time and your face. I think I have to go
find him again. I don't take this the wrong way but it feels like if I looked away for a minute
I'd completely forget every feature. But if I go get a different disguise won't he not know who I am?
If you want a decision right now this is a life-changing choice. It could be the start
of some big things for you. Okay no backing out. I'll do it. I don't need any more disappointments.
Make sure this is what you really want. Yes. I'll be here for a few more days at least so
okay. All right so I was fine. I freaked out. Okay sounds good. Yes I'll do it. So now I'll
just have to go talk to him again. Thank you. All right goodbye. I need to find out what that is
right? Like what's going on here? Is somebody in this house moaning? Why? They're in there.
Am I allowed to go in here? We can't enjoy the fucking movie. Why? We can't hear anything.
All right let's watch it. Turn off the projector. You need to.
What happens if I do this?
You know you weren't even watching the video. You weren't even watching the video.
Dangerous fucker.
That guy got out of here quick. I don't have a disguise on. Why did Peter Griffin just come in?
That's just fucking out of place. Hey Loish remember that time. I'm in trouble. I gotta
get out of here. That's the guy. That's the guy. That's the guy. That's the guy. That's the guy.
That's the guy. That's the guy. That's the guy. What was he doing outside the door? Holy crap.
Don't do it. Don't open it. Clueless. Wait is this the guy that was in here originally?
You're not going to sit down and watch the YouTube video right? No you're not going to
come back and watch the YouTube video. It's just smoke. Did I win? I have to wait. There's
another person to kill. I dropped my cigarette. It was in my mouth and I dropped it. Somebody help.
My cigarette hit the ground.
Did she just puke? I have to get out of here. I have to get out of here.
I have to leave. Alright everybody get out. I wonder what he's going to do. Does he remember?
You remember me? No fuck. No I'm back in this stupid. Alright I'm going to do it for real.
How do you jump? I gotta do it for real. I gotta do it for real. Do it for real. Do it for real.
I can't help it. It's like fucking Grand Theft Auto. Alright so I gotta go back and talk to that guy.
Okay yep yep yep yep yep. So I gotta go talk to that guy and say I'll do it.
Ready to go up here? Yep alright so he's over there. Newspaper I'll take it. I keep thinking
somebody is hitting me in the fucking face in real life. That's hitting me in the face in real life
every time I hear it. Okay so are you? It's in. Oh this is. Oh. Hold on. Getting them both in place
would certainly save some time. Okay so should I go to the meeting? I'm using the light to signal
for Crest when she wants a meeting. The light. It shouldn't be too difficult to exploit that. Okay.
Also known as Akka, leader of the pirates. She should be carrying one of the key cards for the
control unit. Okay. Is this weird to do this? Probably. I mean is it is this is it weird to
do this? I mean it's kind of odd but is it really gonna get me in trouble? Alright I'm gonna go
talk to that guy. He's like come find me if you want to actually do the thing. Alright let's go.
I want to do like a fun mission. I just want to throw fish at people. God damn it. Okay this is
interesting. Whatever this is. What's going on in here? There's always a chef. Have you guys noticed
that? There's always just the kitchen with the kitchen knife and the chef where you can
poison the meat. Really? Oh this is I guess I'm not allowed. You don't. He didn't seem to really give
a shit. Okay. What can I do in here? Can they see? What happened? I need to get a disguise or just
say fuck it and not go in. There's not a good opportunity for a disguise. Where's my coin?
I have this mission going already. Let me just do this one. This seems like the best idea. He's
like come find me and tell me if you want to do it or not. So let's go do it. I just walk up to
him? Alright I'm ready. I'm ready to do your fucking weird mission. Alright I'm ready to do
your the mission. What do you need to examine the pores on my face? What is this? Are you checking
me for weapons? He's clean. There's definitely going to be a place I can say yeah I'll do it
right? Where are you going now? Subdue? No I'm not going to subdue. That's such a simple way to do
this. He said I need a man like you to be able to you know fucking take you know pain or something
right? Whatever he said. But the last like two or three straight minutes I've been larping as this
guy's security guard. I mean I there's got to be a way I can activate this right? That was the chance
to kill him. Oh but I thought he wanted to make join me like me we join oh now he's back watching
the slap fight again. What if I do the slap fight again? Let me impress him again. Hey remember me?
I'm the slap guy. What? That was your opportunity. Um alright so let me I gotta go to the meeting.
I don't even care about winning. Wait Intel he's checking in with the military base regularly.
All right I need a military outfit. I need a military outfit. How do I get? I'm going in here.
Where is he going lol? First time viewer fuck. Everything's kind of on the open.
All right I can go in here. Kind of. All right I'm gonna wake this person up and I think they're
gonna open the door. And this is going to be something in here I can use. Okay I have so many
items. Okay now you come open the door. No don't get back in bed. Oh my god it's military person.
I can. Oh shit. Hey hey hey it's one of those guys. Come investigate over here. Hurry. Why did
I turn the fucking vacuum cleaner on? Who's shooting me? What? Who's shooting at me? Excuse
me? What? Why? Who was shooting at me? From what direction? Are you? What are you talking about?
Genuinely who was? There's nobody behind me. I don't give a shit. I don't care. This is a hard
mission. I don't give a shit. Turn the vacuum off. It's gonna make me fucking scream. Okay go in the
vacuum room. Turn it on. Okay get. Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine.
Here we go. Vacuum. Good. Okay let's go. Now I'm gonna go to that meeting right? I have to steal
something. Oh no I'm not doing that. How far away is that? That's so far away. All right let's get
this guy now. You're going to the toothpaste convention. What's with this? What's with the
teeth thing? I don't get the teeth thing. I have an idea. Nobody can even see me right now. I actually
don't think they can see me. Oh yeah they can. I thought like metal gear solid you know. There's
like the window where they can't see. Okay what's that? Hold on. This is a water pump. Repairs on
Chris's boat are held up and it doesn't look like they're going to happen anytime soon. Perhaps the
local mechanics could use an extra set of hands. Okay. Okay. Do you need some help?
I need a screwdriver.
How do you guys not have? How is that not a screwdriver? Oh there's a wrench. No it's a pipe.
Is there no wrench in here? A crowbar? Use cell. How is there no wrench?
I just like what the fuck am I supposed to do? I mean where's the wrench? I love throwing car
batteries. We already went over this right? How many car batteries would it take to actually
electrify the ocean? That's far away. Not really. A signal light on the radar tower. So when does
that happen? Should I just go? Hold on. So what they're gonna flash a bat signal and I'm supposed
to go to the meeting? I can trigger it. Oh let's go do that. What's the best way to get there?
What do you want? What of it? Yeah. Yeah. What about it?
What do you find? A coconut? I has asked 47 to fetch her a coconut. How quaint. But who
knows what may come from doing a favor for it. All right let's go get a coconut. Coconut right
here. How do I get there? Do I have to climb this? Can I shoot it down with a gun? People are not
gonna freak out about this right? What the fuck? Huh? What the? Okay um that's not how you get them.
Oh what the fuck? Oh what? Were those not coconuts? They definitely were. Okay where would I? Okay I
have to destroy the control unit or yeah I'm gonna destroy it. I'm not gonna go get fucking
access keys. No thanks. Let's go destroy it. I'm technically allowed in here. Where's that camera?
They don't care. I'm allowed to be down here. I'm in the uniform right? Okay never mind. Really?
What are the weird cartoon objects do I have? It's only two. That was louder than anything else
I've done so far. Can I hide them anywhere? Not really. Bring the fish back. What's quick save?
How do I quick save? Whatever somebody comes down here they come down here. Five. If somebody comes
down they come down. Whatever. What am I gonna do about it? F5? All right let's go. While I'm
allowed down here. Fire extinguisher? Okay I gotta be careful. That's the control unit. You'll need
to either destroy it or deny access to keep the ether satellite out of the militia's hands. Oh
fuck. Stop talking to me. Holy shit there's a stalactite. I have to stalactite somebody right?
I got him. When you're like on a security job and one of your co-workers gets killed by a stalactite
you're not gonna you're gonna go investigate that. All right what is this? Fuse? Oh screwdriver thank
god finally. Oh it does it's an accident. He found the guy. X. Hey uh like Joey uh there was another
accident of the stalactite. These were sharp and small. Oh this person's coming to the generator.
Just slowly clear this whole remote. That'll make a ton of noise. I don't want to do that.
Let me uh let me piano wire this guy. Dude I'm gonna set these motherfuckers up. I'm gonna set
all five of these guys underneath the stalactite. So it's just like they were all sitting here
having a smoke break and this giant stalactite killed everybody. Perfect. A tactical shotgun?
Hell yeah. Yeah you've you've you found something. No one's turning the generator off. Only two more
people that's it. He's gonna hear the generator. Actually you know what? Fuck it. Some punk kid.
All right I've successfully infiltrated. Okay hold on. No one else is here right? Laptop files.
Crest wasn't planning to sell the control unit back to them at all. He was going to use the damn
thing. I suppose I was selling him short. Okay. Can I take the rack? Did I do it? Safety is on.
What do you mean safety's on? Oh let's go. With the control unit in pieces the satellite's no longer.
Let's go. That's one problem taken care of. All right hell yeah. Let me get some uh extra stuff
though. There's all kinds of like goodies here. All right not bad. Now I'm gonna go turn on the
bat signal. Anything else I can do? That's it. All right let's go. So from here I'm gonna go
drop disguise. Oh I'm gonna head this way. Get out of the cave. You need to kill the witnesses.
They're not gonna get up. Those other two people will be dead far before I have to do that. It's
not coming this way right? Yeah these guys have the two targets will be dead before they wake up.
And even if they do wake up. What you woke up in a cave and four people died by a stalactite. Does
that really matter? I'm gonna be fine. I need to get rid of this. Don't aim the fucking gun. Throw
it. How do I get rid of the gun? I don't want two guns on me at all times. Okay let's go do the bat
signal. Z? Okay that's fine. All right that's better. All right let's set up the meeting.
I should be allowed in here right? Aren't I like personal private security?
Please don't search me. All right you guys remember in the mask when they're like freeze and they
start going through his pants and there's rubber chickens and clocks. I this is a lot of stuff to
have to get rid of. I need to be a pirate. I have a pirate disguise literally right over. Okay well
I'm gonna go get it. Lock the hole in the sand castle? That seems just kind of set for. Let me
get the pirate costume. Okay I thought one of them got up. All right so now I should be able to get
in there. Why is that evil? All right that person can see through. Nobody else can right? No we're
good. All right we're here. I want to turn that thing on. We're good. Oh oops. Do you stay this
way or can you please turn? Fucking camera. Don't take my picture. It doesn't really matter. What
the fuck? Huh? I thought I had a crowbar. I don't care if I get seen. Doesn't matter. Yeah. Oh my
god. Can I get in there? Don't say that. Friend of yours. 47. Don't. Why would you say that? Mr. Smith.
47. Real thin ice with interval. This assignment was supposed to be a gimme. Tag along undercover
on some tankers. Monitor the crews for any suspicious contact with pirates and sportsmen
investigations with whatever info I found. Should have been a piece of cake. Do you need some help?
Yeah. Haven't heard any keys on their leader when she comes by. If I had to guess I'd say
she's keeping them somewhere private like an office. An office. If you can get those keys
and open this door I can get myself off this island. Got it. Okay. Turn up the volume. Okay.
Is that better? All right I need to find the keys. They're probably in an office. I don't
whatever this is I'm touching it. Turn that off. Turn it off. I don't know what I just did. Turn
it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. I'm sorry. I don't know what that does. I can't turn that off.
Did I fuck it up? I think I screwed it all up. I messed the whole thing up didn't I?
All right I gotta get I gotta knock these guys out and then use the printer or whatever that is.
Oh my god I have so much stupid bullshit in my inventory. I don't even I whatever.
I need something quiet. What's the quietest thing I have here? Probably a knife or this.
The fish is quiet. The fish is not quiet.
What does that do? I don't even need to be in here. Is there a key anywhere?
There's no key here. It's probably upstairs. I'm gonna stay over here right? Probably up here.
Oh shit. Okay let's go go go. What do we got? Notes. Intel. Rough accumulation of intel about
Crest and the militia in addition to because calculations about the value of the satellite
itself where notes outline what Crest stands to gain from blackmailing ether and their clients
with its data. Wow. There it is. Got the key. Holy shit this this thing is insane. Um throw this
out the window. I got the key. Was there anything else in here that I needed? I've got the key.
I'm gonna drop down. All right let's go. Now what? Who the hell are you and what were you doing on
that tanker? If you don't start talking I'll cut one of those ears of yours off. Whether or not
I know who to send it to. Hey you. What happened? Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait.
Now all that's left to deal with. What did I do? Crest himself. I'm gonna get the fuck out of here.
Like I said Carbat. I fucking electrified everybody. I gotta get the fuck out of here.
Did you drop anything? An access hub? Key? Wait hold on. Open this door.
Are they coming in? No we're okay. Data entry and I don't know. Whatever. Go. Get out.
Fuck. No no no no no no no no no. I don't. I don't. I don't. Just come in and investigate.
Do whatever you need to do. Bye. Don't shoot him. Just run. I'm good. Save it. That is not how you're
supposed to do that. Okay so that leaves us with the bat signal. Kick bag of bricks? The signal's
lit. Their meeting should start soon. Am I gonna kick a bag of bricks on this guy? Here it comes.
That guy doesn't know the meeting got cancelled. He doesn't know that um that I killed like all
the people down here. He's no idea. This guy has absolutely no clue. Shit he's gone. What is this
guy doing up here? Did I get him? Okay okay okay okay. He's coming. He's on his way. Dude I could
probably just go like. I'll do it the right way. I'll do it the right way. I'll do it the right way.
Relax. So this just dropped down here. Did they actually even walk by this? Where's he going? Wait
where are all the dead bodies? They got rid of all the dead bodies. What distraction. This guy's not
up here is he? Oh there he goes. Is he leaving? Investigate that. How far can I throw something?
See what the hell that was. The meeting is not in the tower. That makes sense. You're right. Why
would the meeting be in the tower? You're right. Yeah that's weird. Oh well let's just kill
whoever this is. What was I thinking? I don't know. This seems like a secluded place.
Now fuck that. When Commissioner Gordon does the bat signal Batman goes to the bat signal on the
roof. That's how in every single movie. Every single tv show. I have a sword now. All right
whatever. I'm just gonna go kill him. Save it. Where is he? I'm gonna go slash this guy with
a sword. You know what I mean? Like who cares? Shit it went the wrong way. Come on. Really?
Metal worker? No. Oh hi. Hello. All right let's go this way. That's probably an escape route right
there. All right fuck this guy. I've had enough. I'll get him alone here. He goes around the corner.
When he goes around the corner I'll go for him. I mean this is way more. This is way more hilarious.
Quarter out of my pocket. Fuck off. What what's so weird about that? What did I lose? What are you
talking about? I took a oh actually thank you. I appreciate that. Usually people would just be
like you know don't give a shit about somebody dropping something. I really appreciate it. Thank
you. You thought I was gonna hit him in the face with the battle didn't you? I would have if it
said uh the text came up but it didn't. Stop. Just focus. Oh shit you wanted a coconut. What do I get
one? Where do you actually get a coconut? I want to do that. How do you actually get a coconut?
Or something. No. I wanted to hit him with the. I wanted to hit him with the with the pad. I want
to hit him with the board. I was waiting for. I don't know. Why can't I hit him with the board?
I'm about to just throw it at this guy and run. You know what I mean? I might as well.
The exit's probably right here. This is crass. What's your status?
I don't care anymore. Whatever. I genuinely don't care.
That's that. How do I get this guy alone? Enable your vaude. It should be there.
I don't. How do I get this guy alone? Shoot him from the tower. That's easier.
I was throwing a fucking knife in his head. That's crest taken care of.
And that's that. The rest will pick up the pieces. It's time to go 47.
We need to secure the area. I'll see you soon. For your own safety. Do you understand?
Don't head in the game. Get your head in the game. Anybody copy? No sign of any pub.
You're supposed to be guarding stuff you lazy prick. I had to do it. You know I did.
I had to do it. I had to do it. I had to do it. I had to do it. I don't care if I failed the mission.
I had to hit that guy in the face for the video because they're going to edit the video right
when I hit him in the face. It's going to cut to the next clip which is coming up here shortly.
That's crest taken care of. And that's that. The rest will pick up the pieces.
It's time to go 47. I'll see you soon.
That was scary.
Someone's fighting a gun. Help me. What? You're talking to me?
Wait. Wait. Are you asking me for help? I'm so confused what happened. I don't care. What was
that? 47. That was a Homer Simpson scream. All right. I got 20,000 XP and oh okay. Unfortunately,
unfortunately you got one star. Zero actually. That was kind of a fun mission. Oh all right.
Cool. That was kind of fun. New personal best. That's the first time I've ever played it. All
right. Was is there any? Is this the only DLC map or is that it? Are there any more DLC maps? I just
want to see what the sword looks like when you hit somebody with it. See you. That's
brutal. Okay. Is there any more? It's quick. It's very quick. Does it kill instantly? This is not
knocking people out, right? It's fast and it kills people. That's kind of crazy. All right. Well,
that's fun. Let me see. Anything else to do? Otherwise we'll play some multiverses. We'll
move to multiverses after this. Play the scary card game. I did. I played scary card game. Save
the guy, the people, people in the cage. It's over. I do art of wilds DLC. I probably will eventually.
But like I heard it was kind of a little too puzzle based. I heard I wouldn't be very bad at
it. I heard that I would not have fun playing it. That's what I was told. Fuck the plank of shame.
Art of wilds DLC. They lied to you. Okay. All right. Let's let's do multiverses. I'm ready to play.
I've been kind of obsessed with this game. This is also going to be a sponsor segment.
I've been playing this game a shitload on the couch sick on my xbox. I'm ready to game. That
was fun though. What about, so VOD is still private. Why? Why does twitch keep changing this
shit? It shouldn't be. Let's see. Hold on. Yeah. Why is this not published? I changed this setting.
I changed this setting like three days ago. What the hell? If I publish this right now,
will it actually go through? That's kind of annoying. Publish this. Okay. Is it there?
Please confirm with me that you can see it. I hope so. Yeah. I went into my settings and I
changed this already. This has already been changed. Where, what is it? What is it under?
Stream settings. Store path. Always publish VODs. Dude, I did this already. Why are you doing this
to me? Okay. That's whatever. All right. Let's do multiverses. Let's open it. I'm gonna do a quick
BRB for one second because I need to set up a chatbot and stuff. So give me one sec. Gonna be
playing a lot of LeBron. LeBron is really fun. Really good. I'll be right back.