Hello, how are you? How is everybody doing today? Today I think I'm going to be
playing some Nancy Drew and also Diablo 4. How you doing good? Starting off strong
on this one. Starting off strong. No, I'm gonna slow it down a little bit today.
There was a TikTok voiceover. No, go full speed. How many stream points do I have?
Stream points? Like channel points on my own channel? Do I even get them? Introducing
channel points. Watch German 985 earn channel points. Unlock rewards. I haven't
even clicked the button to begin accruing points. So I guess the answer is
zero. Wouldn't I be... Oh yeah, me getting my own currency created
from my own channel from me? I feel like that's contributing to... I don't... No, I
don't want to do that. I would want to make sure... I would want to take away
from myself from having that many points. Fake fan. Some kind of currency thing.
Dude, just click it. I don't want to click get it get started. I don't want...
When I click... If you click get started that just to me tells the computer like
alright I'm ready to do this now and I don't even want to do it. You know what I mean?
I don't want to click get started because I want to finish it the second
I click get started. Like the title? I mean it's true. Scared of commitment. I'm
scared of committing to things that I don't necessarily really care that much
about. I understand. I said steam points. God damn it. Why does this happen to me
every day? Your balance on steam. I don't know. I don't... I don't know. 200. There you go.
This is my balance. 200. A lot. 200 points. That's a shitload. No, not your steam wallet
balance. That's not accurate. I'm just made up a number. I feel like that that would be kind of
a lot of money to have in a steam wallet. Wouldn't it? Like 200 plus dollars? Maybe not. It's
depending on how many games you plan on buying. But anyways let's talk about what's happening.
Okay. Let's talk. Today we're going to be finishing our Nancy Drew homework.
I feel like the Diablo 4 server is... I played it... I have to confess. I played it a lot last night.
Ollie and I played it a lot. I made another character and I just kind of... kind of went...
we kind of went nuts without us. Yeah. I did. I did. But I can tell you that
I enjoy it. I think it's fun to play. And I'm hoping that the game is searching to how to stay
fair. It's searching. They're trying to come up with a way to say be fair about it but also not
too involved. Don't let them think that you care that much. That's what's screaming through my
brain right now. So what I want to tell you is I want to play as the Necromancer. That'll be the
way that I really tell if I'm going to play it or not. But I do like... I like it so far. I don't
know how deep the skill system is really going to go. I don't know how deep the itemization is going
to be. But if Necromancer is fun, I will probably be playing it. That's it. That's it. But today is
the last day that it can be played for this week. So the plan is to do Nancy Drew for a little while.
Maybe get to the end of that. Maybe get however far enough the end of there that I want to,
you know, play it. And then move on to D4 for the rest of the night. Just chill because I think it's
turning off at midnight. Is it tomorrow at midnight or is it tonight at midnight? Because I still want
to play with these sorcerers. 3 p.m. on Monday Eastern. Okay. So there's plenty of time. And then
Resident Evil 4, I'm going to play it essentially until I beat it. So that's, I believe... Is that
the 23rd at midnight or is that the 24th in the middle of the day? I asked this in pre-stream. I'm
curious if anybody knows. Is the Resident Evil 4 remake coming out like in the middle of the day
on the 24th or is it going to be like a midnight release on Thursday? I don't think anybody really
knows. He didn't even listen to our answer. It's just out when it's out. Yeah. Well, whatever.
Whatever it launches on the 24th, that is when I will be getting ready to play it. Apparently,
the remake, as of all the reviews I've seen, is stellar. It is getting unbelievable reviews.
Some of these outlets are giving it a 10. This is getting tens. So I don't want to say that,
like, okay. Am I? I don't want to say it, but I'm going to say it. I gave the Resident Evil 2 remake
game of the year when it came out. Is that going to happen again for another Resident Evil remake?
It might. We'll see. That's funny, though. Oh, Bat Chest stellar reviews.
All right. I am going to open up Nancy Drew. I might not put the camera on. I've been doing
no cam and I've been liking it. We'll see. Maybe we'll turn it on a little bit later.
We'll go cam camless for now. Don't worry about cam. Yeah, no, I know. I know nobody here is
pressured me to put it on. Don't worry. Just last night was kind of like I was feeling it.
Let's put it on and just fuck around. It's going to happen a lot. All right. Nancy Drew.
Does anyone remember anything that we did? I'll be really honest with you. Not last night. You know,
my sense of time is so fucked up. We were going back and forth between Nancy Drew and Diablo that
I kind of don't even remember what the hell we even did. Hey, I tried to do the cat puke noise
and it just makes me sound like I'm burping. Any tips? I do not recommend anybody attempt that.
Don't try that at home. You should not. Don't try this at home. Okay. I need to make I need to put
like a huge disclaimer up somewhere on the stream that just don't ever try anything or say anything
I say ever. Don't ever do any of this and don't watch and don't comment. Don't subscribe. Don't
be here. I should probably put that up, right? Don't ever say anything that I say. Don't ever
do anything that I've done. Don't ever attempt anything I've done. Don't ever watch. Don't
subscribe. Don't donate or anything. You know what I mean? Just probably like a disclaimer.
That would be such a fucked up disclaimer. All right. Don't watch. Just put it at the bottom
of the screen. Hold on. I got to think of like a huge paragraph though. I should have thought
about this like an hour ago. No, I'll do it another day. All right. Nancy Drew, what do you got?
Hopefully it's not too loud. How's the audios? All right. Don't attempt anything you see. Yeah,
but people that are coming in and seeing that pinned are going to think I'm about to like
backflip off of a building or something, right? Like that that you get that warning before
something crazy is about to happen and they're going to be really disappointed when it's just
Nancy Drew. I'm not going to do anything. That's a warning to me. To me that is something dangerous
is going to happen at some point. He's going to turn his cam on. He's going to get like attacked
by a bear or something. All right. Anyways, what I need to focus. We fished. We put the line in.
We did the fishing mini game. I couldn't keep one, right? I snagged a log. There goes my line.
Can you stop being funny for a minute? I need to pee. Um, well, I think funny is very subjective
to people. So you, you might've thought that was really funny would just happen, but somebody else
might not think that what I just did was funny. And you two need to come to some common ground
of what you think is funny with for me because, um, it's very subjective. So I think you could
have made a lot of people very upset with what you just said. I need a container for the fish.
It's a comedy committee. All right. So I got it. What the hell have we been doing?
All right. What the hell happened? The wolf, right? I remember the wolf. I remember this guy,
the avalanche. We reported the avalanche. I remember that we had, we cooked dinner. We cooked
lunch for people. I did. I have access to the snowmobile. So I got to track down the snowmobile.
This is Nancy Drew guys. Beyond centrist Andy. Really cold. How do you go? Wait, wait,
beyond centrist Andy. What? Wait a minute. That's not correct. Wouldn't beyond centrist Andy be
like not in the middle. That would be beyond the middle. So I can't be,
I can't go too far centrist because that means I've got, I have to go somewhere.
If I don't get warm soon, she's going to die. She's going to die. Why is she, what's happening?
Turn around, turn around, turn around. Where am I going? Turn around, turn around. Nancy,
turn around. I used to go lake. No, this way. I'm walking wicked stiff too. All right. There's
this snowmobile. Let me go inside and warm up for a second. Warm again. This is an unhinged
stream incoming. No, it's not. No, it's on the Z axis. You're still a centrist. Z axis.
What? I want to go. What? Okay. It's 7 a.m. Hold on a minute. Sure. Am I being put into time out?
Is this time out? Get in there and, and, and stay, stay there for a while. What? Wait,
what are we eating? French toast. I didn't tell me how to make French toast. I thought I only
know how to make hamburgers. How do you make French toast? I didn't get a tutorial. Oh, hold on.
Yes, may order French toast. You hear the cook. Are you just waiting for breakfast? What is French
toast? I don't know how to make this. What is this? Where's this? Where's the step by step
instruction? I would just drink an orange juice and walk out. I would take the, the yogurt in the
sitting in the ice, which always freaks me out. But, you know, whatever. Like I know that when
the yogurt sitting in the ice, I kind of feel like I want that in a, I don't, I want it in the fridge
because it's like yogurt. I don't want it left out because what if like the top part's getting cold?
I mean, the bottom part's getting freezing cold. The top part might be at like room temp. I don't
know. Anyway, somebody is asking, do you know how to make French toast without the book? Let me,
let me see if I get it right. Okay. It's two pieces of bread and you dunk the bread in egg,
in an egg wash. And then after you soak the bread in an egg wash, you put it on like a pan
and you kind of cook it. And then you put, I don't know, like cinnamon sugar on it. I don't eat French
toast. I don't really like French toast. Why would I know how to make this? Why would I care
about making the food that I don't eat? I don't eat French toast. Why do I care? I'm not a sugary
breakfast guy. I'm a savory breakfast guy. Eggs, corned beef hash, bacon, sausage, toast, orange
juice, a shitload, a huge, like a 32 ounce glass of orange juice. I'm talking like a fucking thermos
that you would take if you were going hiking for like three days. That amount of orange juice.
All right. What do they want? Okay. French toast and Canadian bacon should be cooked on the griddle.
Omelette should be in the frying pan. Make sure all food is thoroughly cooked before removing it
from the griddle or pan. French toast and omelette should be golden brown while Canadian bacon should
be lightly browned. Making an omelette, simply add any old, any, when making an omelette, simply add
any extra ingredients to the pan of egg mixture. Fold the omelette over, whatever. Okay. I'm just
going to, they're going to get what they get. How many pieces of French toast? It's two, right?
Is it done? How do I pick this up?
Fanning through the book with a piece in my hand. Oh, that's not it. How do I put this down?
What? Okay. Honestly, how do I put it down? One French toast. I put this ingredient down.
Okay. There's French toast. Beautiful. Three Canadian bacon. Okay. I flip it.
Do I, why is this not cooking? Is the oven on? Oh, okay. Three, one omelette and then you want
spinach, two bacon, one bacon, two spinach and two green peppers. All right. Omelette. Where's the egg?
Okay. And then what? What do you want? Fuck. This is wrong. Three. Okay. One bacon, two spinach,
two green peppers. What is this bacon? One bacon, two, what is this spinach? One bacon, two spinach,
two green peppers. Okay. Hey, come on. We're hungry here. I'm going. I'm working. Okay.
Order up. Order up. Three French toast, two Canadian bacon. That's all you want.
Imagine waiting hours for French toast. Imagine forcing somebody that doesn't know anything about
how to cook meals from more than one or two people at a time and not being a chef. I'm a fucking
detective at a detective agency telling that person that they need to be the chef
for an expensive lodge. Order up. I can tell you one thing that that would be pretty dumb.
Are we sure that it's, am I, am I wrong here? Okay. Two French toast, one omelette. Let's get
the French toast on there. And what do you want in it? Spinach, cheese, three green, three olives.
Spinach, cheese, three green, three olives. Spinach, green, three olives. I don't remember.
One spinach, one cheese, three green peppers. Ah, what? Oh my God. I'm fucking so mad right now.
You don't bring me here. I don't want to do this. I don't want to do this. What if, you know what?
Who cares? Does it matter? I don't know who cares. Just French toast. Just eat it.
One French toast. Everybody wants French. Just make, I don't care if it sits here. I need one
French toast, two, three, four, five, six, seven French toast. So one, just fill the whole thing
because it's going here. You wanted one. You wanted one. You wanted one. You wanted two.
You wanted, ah. Oh my God. This is embarrassing. This is embarrassment. I fucking didn't get it.
All right. I, I don't want to be here. I don't want to be in the kitchen. I don't want to be
in the kitchen. I don't want to fucking be here. I would never do this and I would never do it.
Nancy, you need to cook for like 10 people. Good. Hire a chef. Thank you. One, one, two.
Oh my God. If I just press a goddamn button. All right. Two, three, four, five, six, seven pieces.
Okay. So it's two and then three. And then it's two. Single task Andy. I don't want to mess it up.
This game, guys, this game came out when some of you guys weren't even born yet.
All right. Give me, give me a minute. All right. Three Canadian bacon or five, six, seven. All
right. So let's do three. And then, okay, three. Okay. So this three here, why does this take so
much longer than anything else? But I feel like this would be the fastest thing to go. Okay.
Then two Canadian bacon, five, six, seven. This is two, three. How many people here weren't born in
2007? Is that when this game came out? I apparently have a lot of 10 year olds here. I didn't think
about that. How many does it want? Three? Stop making me laugh. You're fucking me up.
This whole channel is 10 year olds. All right. Two more. Dude, 2007 was 28 years ago. Aware.
All right. Now we do the complicated shit with the omelets. One omelet. So this person wants a
fully, this one person wants a fully loaded omelet. One bacon, three spinach, three cheese.
I would put the cheese first. In my opinion, the greens and vegetables is after. This is throwing
me off. One bacon, three cheese. One bacon. One, two, three. Three spinach, three peppers, one olive.
Here you go. What the hell do you want? One bacon, one spinach. What the hell else do you want? Two
green, one olive. Order up. All right. That's all you wanted, right? Omelets kind of suck. Yeah.
Actually, I'm not a big fan of omelets either. To me, omelets almost feel like they're too much.
Order up. I don't know why. Sounds like we've eaten a whole omelet. Just kind of like,
I can't, I can't really do it. All right. Two bacon, two spinach, one green. Two bacon, two spinach,
one green. What else do you want? Two olives. What do you want in here? No omelet. Okay.
So you're done. Order up. So you want three spinach, one cheese, two green, three spinach,
two, wait, two green, one cheese, two olives. Wait, which one is this one? I forget.
Which one is the, who got, who got this one? Who got this one? This is this person's, right?
Order up. Okay. Good. And then no omelet for you? Order up. We got it. We did it. Finally. Cheese.
Okay. So I think we're all right. I think we did a pretty good job. We're good. So now what
were we doing? Oh, the snowmobile. Let's get the hell out of here. Move. Can't you, how am I driving
this on this? Doesn't it have to be in snow? What is going on? Oh no, Nancy's dead. Wait, how?
Oh. Have I fired? Oh no. Okay. Well, now we know what happens when you just hold the
pedal down to the floor. Honestly, to crash that many times as violently as I, Jesus Christ,
to crash that violently, I feel like the car needs to be made out of magnets or something.
And it just pulled me around. Um, what is the hit box? What are you in there? Oh, okay. I think I
made it. The sign's not buried. So I guess there hasn't been an avalanche. Okay. How do I put the
key down? No, I want to put the key away. Why can I spell avalanche right now? Okay. I'm not looking
at chat. Avalanche. A-V-A-L-A-N-C-H-E. Avalanche. Correct? I didn't look at chat. I promise. So
maybe I can't, I guess I can't do anything here. It just seems any secrets are up and up here.
You should do a spelling bee. You know, a streamer spelling bee. Like, yeah, that would actually be
pretty funny and just pick wicked, easy fucking words. I guarantee you we would eliminate half
the people. I, cause you know why I know that? Cause I know I would be eliminated by spelling
like a simple five-letter, four-letter word, like five-letter word. I don't think you even
need to go up to like seven or eight letters. I think everyone would get eliminated after like
the fifth. So what, what, what did I do wrong? Is arrow pointing me back to the lodge?
Like where is this moment to go? I need shoes. Oh, I probably do need snow shoes. That's all right.
In the play testing for this game, people probably got lost. I probably need snow shoes. Okay. So
then now what's, what's the progress then? What's the progress? Much better. I was really cold.
Tell the guy there was an avalanche. I did. Oh, I was checking to see if there was an avalanche.
And now we have to tell the person downstairs, whoever that was, that there was not an avalanche.
Now I remember. Sorry guys. I was playing like Diablo four every 30 minutes. I don't even
remember what happened in Diablo four. And I played it again too. It was pretty cool though.
All right. Where is this dude in here? Where the hell are you? Hey, I did.
No avalanche. There's your snowmobile key. You make a report to the eye cup. Um, I see, uh,
and then after the, after that, I think there's a, um, I think after there's a U and then after
that, there's what, uh, A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P the 16th letter of the alphabet, which is
P. I think that's how it's spelled. I think I got it. Wait, what? Oh, what do you got to tell me?
What did you tell me to spell? I forgot. That's okay. I'll call him. What else do you want?
Oh, I'll call them. Okay. I'll get out of your hair now. Good. What? What you need. That's all
the questions I had. Should I call? I probably should call anyways. I think it's just call
anyways, right? I want to go this way. Well, that kind of blew it all up to me. Now what do I do?
It's not the snowmobile. It's not the avalanche thing. So now what? We've been here. We've been
here. We've been here. We've been here. We did this. Wait. Yeah. We know we did. Maybe we'd know
we didn't do this. Did we go look in people's rooms again? Okay. I guess. Okay. What's the area
code though? Cause I want to call that. Why would it want this number here? If it wasn't supposed
to call it five, five, five, it's four Oh three. Was it four Oh three five, five, five, two eight.
What was it? Two eight, two eight. Hurry up. I, it's going to go dial tone on me. Two eight,
two eight, two eight, two eight, two eight, two eight, two nine, three eight. Oops. Your call
cannot be completed. Four oh three, five, five, five, two nine, eight, three, two, three, eight, three.
This is going to, is anyone going to pick up? Well, I mean, I'm just going to, what are these?
What's the maximum amount of rings? Oh, so what's that ring? Two, three, eight, three. It was wrong.
Two, three, eight, three, two, three, eight, three. What? Uh, what about three 12? Oh yeah.
God damn it. It was the first one. No, I want one. Okay. So we'll just say,
called, called Joe. There's no Joe. Joe mama. Ban everybody writing that. I want every,
every single person writing that right now. I want them banned from the channel and I want them
permanently five minute banned. And what that means is that you do not get unbanned within that
five minutes. So like, it's really funny until you get permanently banned for five minutes.
I don't know what the hell to do. There's the laundry bag again. I guess I'll just take it.
I need like phone numbers on here. All right. So I'm just going to go, but I need to find,
this is a granny like, although not really granny like means that I'm being pursued in
this house while I have to do all these things. Yeah. This, this predates a granny likes the bed
used towels clean no later than noon. Okay. I already, nobody's even using their room.
Is there nothing in here? There has to be something in here, right? This one has been locked.
I can't get even, I can't even get into this one. Who's in here? It's vacant. Oh, that's why.
But yeah, it's because it's vacant. Well, that's great. All right. Well, well,
let me see if anybody else has anything I have to do. I got to do everybody's bed.
All right. Fine, fine, fine, fine. There you go. Okay. There's four rooms that need it today.
What's this? Oh, interesting. This room is studying wolves. Hmm. Why, why do you have
this book? Okay. And you're a sculptor. Interesting. Who's in this room? I can ask
a few questions about that. I think who is in this room? Okay. This is who the hell's in here.
Oh, Lou. Okay. Lou Talbot, Lou Talbot. Interesting. Okay. Did they make this? Is this a children's
game? This is the person that had the wolf book in their room. The one to be like, you are like,
you like wolves. Yes, I do. And you did it. Yes, I did. Is that like the smoking gun in a way?
I have to imagine in my feed. Okay. Give me your laundry. Nice. I can't get into anybody else's
closets unless, wait. You forgot to put all the laundry in that bag. No, I got it all actually.
Are there people down here now hanging out that I can talk to? I'm just going to call Lou on the
phone. Nancy. Hey, got a proposition for you. Since Lou hears two chicken to go mano a mano
with me out there in the ice fishing shack. Snowshoeing is my thing, dude. Besides, it's
animal cruelty. Oh, you're Lou. Give me a break. You ever been ice fishing? I have. As a matter of
fact, I have. Excellent. Here's the deal. I need some competition. So I want you to go out there
and try to catch a bigger fish than I caught yesterday, which means you got to catch a two
foot northern pike. Now it's a bit of a hike out to the lake, but the shack is solar heated.
I already did this even from first. So what do you say, kiddo? You game? Anything to make
your guests happy. Atta girl. Well, I'll let you get back to beating Lou. Do I need a place to
keep it or no? What's up? So you go to school and talk to me here? Yep. University of California,
Brea. What degree are you working on? Master of fine arts. Hmm. What's your favorite medium?
Cool. So what's your favorite medium? Holograms. What is this? Like the Spanish Inquisition.
Hey, give her a break. She's just trying to make pleasant conversation. Oh, right. Um,
my favorite medium, dirt. Dirt. You paint with dirt? I create works of art by manipulating
naturally occurring geophysical substances like dirt. Oh, sometimes I just use my hands,
but most of the time heavy machineries. So you're blowing up pieces of the earth.
No, what do you understand? You're like throwing grenade. You're like burying grenades and like
taking great to be misunderstood. FYI, Ralph Waldo Emerson said that. Yeah. Yeah. You're like
using explosives to create art in like out in the wilderness or something, right? I think that
might be what it is. Is this your first time at the lodge? Yep. My car broke down on my way to
Lake Louise last summer, pulled in here to wait for the tow truck and figured it'd be a cool place
to visit during the winter. So here I am. Well, good luck. Well, let's go catch the fish. At least
that's the way we know we have to do. I can't wait to have to play somebody in this because
you know, I'm going to have to and I don't want to. No need to go in there till it's time to cook.
I already went over this, but this is from the oldest RPGs. Like D&D taught us this like almost
a hundred years ago. People are good at stuff. The whole the whole reason for like a party system
is because everybody's good at different things. I don't want to be the chef. I don't want to be
the manager. I don't want to be the performer at the fucking comedy club that's down the street.
We all do the things that we're good at. That's why if RPGs have taught us anything. All right,
how do I get back to the lake? Is it this way? Call the avalanche patrol? Uh, I was going to,
but that guy said he was going to do it anyways. You are literally a performer at a comedy club.
You don't see me cooking, do you? You don't see my like unbelievable chef skills. No, you don't. You
don't see me. Um, you know, I'm not, I can't, I can't really let him cook. Let him cook. No,
you don't really want me to. What about the egg salad? Well, the egg salad only requires a very
small amount of cooking. Go back to chicken ridge and risk getting caught in another avalanche.
I don't think so. All right. I, I need a map. Go back to chicken ridge and risk getting caught
in another avalanche. I don't think so. I'm not going out there again. I figured if I spun her
around a few times, she wouldn't know where she was either. It's like, I'm not going back there.
Oh yeah. Actually, you know what? You've spun me around enough times. That actually seems pretty
safe. Let's go that way. No more avalanches for me. Thank you very much. What was that lake? I feel
like I got lost accidentally and found my way to that lake. You were literally on a cooking stream.
Yes. Yes, I was. Would you have eaten any of the food that Charlie and I made? Okay. So what,
what's the point there? Aren't you making the point for me? I need to look at a map because
this is, Oh, here it is. I got it. Too cold to go any further. Oh, come on. All right. I got it.
It's the skating pond. It's the skating pond. Is it get in the house? Oh my God. I just clicked off
of it. Much better. Okay. It's really cold. Go right back out here. Is it the skating pond
past the skating pond? Save the game. It was, wasn't it? I don't remember. No, it's not. It was
like a weird, it was like a shack. And I remember being like, how did I even get here? It's past
the snowball fight area. It's not that way. Which way? I better not follow this trail until I know
for sure where it goes. Nobody remember over here. Oh, Oh, nice hit. Nice job. Oh, look out. Oh,
it got me. You let me bite. Now let me bite. Now get out of the way. I'll get out of the way. Get
out of the way. Thank you. It was fun. Very fun time. If I don't get warm soon, I may not make it.
All right. Well, hurry up. Okay. Catch the fish. It looks like someone came in here and just
wrecked everything, including the fishing gear. What? So much for catching a two foot northern
pike. It's definitely one of the two of them then. I can't fish. The tackles ruined. There's
somebody one step ahead of me. It's one of those two. Left behind by whoever trashed this place.
Birds of the Southwest. Okay. All right. Calling that. Get me out of here. Uninstall Diablo four,
please. I'm starting to get really cold. Why? It's Lou. It's definitely Lou. Somebody left me a note.
A note. Nancy Drew. Hmm. I really like playing snowball fights with you, but I'm afraid you
won't want to play with me anymore. If you play with me and win, I'll give you my top secret way
I can... Oh, this is a little kid. Nevermind. I thought this was like a mastermind criminal or
something. I'll give you my top secret way I can stay out in the cold for so long. Wait, wait.
Ready. Secret. I better not follow this trail until I know for sure where it goes. Wait, where?
Dude, this voice. What did you just throw at me? I didn't even see it. What did I even get? What is
that? What the... No, I don't want to use it right now. What is that? I didn't want to even take that.
What drugs did I just take? What did I just take? Did I soft lock myself or something?
Was it a hand warmer? Why did I use it? What just happened? All right. Let's make the call.
202-555-7237. Damn it. Two... What is it? 202-555-202-7237. Interesting. So, hey. Lou? Where's Lou? Lou?
Who? Has he been here the whole time with you?
What? You're kidding. So my gear's ruined? Yep. Completely. So much for our little fishing contest.
Wait a minute. Ollie ice fishes. Go ask him for a hook and line and don't take no for an answer.
Oh, okay. I'll see you two later, okay? Where's Ollie? Who's Ollie? I don't know who that is.
I've just learned these two people's names into long term memory like five minutes ago. So,
actually, I don't even know who the person on the right is. I'll catch you later. In real.
If you told me, Jerma, I'll give you a million dollars right now, tell me this guy's full name.
I wouldn't be able to do it. I don't think I wouldn't be able to do it. Even if you said it,
I'll give you a million dollars. I have no... I don't know what his first name is. I have no idea.
I know this is Lou. It's time to serve lunch now. Not time for kitchen duty yet. Okay. So,
I need to go find Ollie. Who's Ollie? Is Ollie this person down here? It's two people down.
This is Ollie? I'm glad for the chance to talk once again. There is something I must explain.
Sure. There is? What I said before about wolves, it is because my grandmother was killed by wolves,
killed and devoured. Okay. Are you serious? Years ago, when my mother was a little girl,
her mother, my grandmother was on her way back from the village on her motor scooter,
which was and still is the only means of transportation most Fredonians can afford.
It was January and the sun had just set and it was dark, very cold. There were thousands of
wolves in the countryside that winter. At night, they would roam in huge hungry packs. My grandmother
was halfway home when she came upon a young man waving from the side of the road for her to stop.
Wait a minute. He too had been on a scooter, but his had broken down and wolves were gathering
all around him, preparing to attack. My grandmother, of course, stopped and he
leapt on behind her and they took off down the road with the wolves, dozens of them
chasing after them. But with two people riding it, her scooter was slow, much too slow and the
wolves soon caught up with them. When one of the wolves seized my grandmother's boot and its teeth
and started to pull, instead of helping her, the man pushed her off the bike. It instantly gained
speed and he got away. My grandmother, set upon by the wolves, did not. If she died, how do you know
that's what happened? If she died, how do you know that's what happened? Tormented by guilt,
the young man eventually confessed. He went to prison for several years and the wolves were
hunted year round until the countryside was rid of them. But the damage was done. I don't think
that's what happened. Yeah. You ever see Lou Talbot when you're out there training?
Ever see Lou Talbot when you're out there training? The college student?
Just yesterday I had to slow down to avoid colliding with him. It ruined my whole session.
Chantal would like to use your name and picture on her website when she gets it.
Would that be okay? I'm sorry, but no. Guilty. Oh, well, so much for that. I have disturbed you
long enough. Kavicinaya. We've got some more info. Why do I feel like this is in slow motion?
I'm hearing slow motion artifact sounds. Does it sound like that? What you need? Someone went
into the ice fishing shack and ruined all of Bill Kessler's equipment. Someone went into the ice
fishing shack and ruined all of Bill Kessler's equipment. Probably some animal loving eco
fanatic who figured it was time to save the fish. How am I going to catch it? Problem is,
Mr. Kessler still insists that I try to catch a two foot northern pike. Say no more. There's
my tackle box. Oh, yes. Yes. Me into competing with him, but I can't very well do that when
you've got my hook and line now, can I? No, I don't suppose you can. What else do you want?
That's it. That's all the questions I had. By the way, you dumped the laundry bag before all the
rooms were cleaned. So I put it back up at the front desk. How is that even possible? I don't
even care. If that's not game breaking, game progress breaking, I'm not doing it ever again.
I don't care. Yeah. OK, come on, kid. I feel like this is Groundhog Day and I have to do this every
day. Eventually. See, I've gotten so good at this because this is like the 5000th time I've had to
do this. I love this voice. I want to hear more of it. I like it. I like this voice. It's cute.
It's like imagine. It is really, really cold out here. It sounds like Cartman. All right,
let's do what we were supposed to do an hour ago. Close to two feet, right? It's Dark Souls 2.
It does it. You'll hear it again. Just you'll hear it. It goes. It goes done, done, done,
done, done, done. It does it for one. It's one part of the song. Not this part. Yes, it does.
Just wait. Never mind. It goes done, done, done. And then that's it. It does it for one part of the
song. I mean, I'm like I'm a I'm a plastic beach fan, so I guess I have one of my favorite albums.
Rats too small. Also, I vodka pineapple. It's super good. It's not a whole lot of
bullshit. Yeah, I don't, you know, that's what I drink. Oh, no, that one looks pretty good.
Rats too small. That was that's it. Oh, come on. There was that won't do.
Shit. It's not. It's not that one. There we go. Yay. Northern Pike fishing for me.
Gameplay resident sleeper. Hold on a second. Somebody resident sleeper, Nancy Drew.
Wait a second here. OK. OK. All right.
What did he fucking throw at me? Oh, my gosh. Whoever threw that ice ball at me must have set
off an explosion that shattered the ice. Huh? My jacket's gone. No wonder I'm so cold.
What? You're the worst detective I've ever heard of. I need to make it to shore by jumping from
ice floe to ice floe and put on that coat. Wait, Nancy. Nancy, somebody. Oh, hold on.
What the hell is happening here? How do I get over there? How do I how do I get over there?
What? I can't reach it. There's no I didn't know you could go diagonal.
Those weren't even touching. First of all, I don't know. Let's come. I need to talk about
this for a second. Nancy, if somebody throws a snowball at you and then the room you are in
explodes, it wasn't a snowball. Like, oh, no, if somebody threw a snowball at me and something
blew up, I must have caused an explosion. I don't what how am I supposed to do this?
What are we trying to do here? That is what OK, I have to step on this one to be able to get up
there. I understand how it works now. We just got to get over there quick. What's going on?
Come on, get up there. Spawn one up there. Is there a rhyme or reason to how this works?
Because I stepped on that one last time and it spawned one up here. This is just RNG. OK,
so if I go diagonal, then it spawned that over there. What if I go diagonal again? I think the
idea to make it so you fill in these so that it has nowhere else to go makes the next one
over appear or disappear. I think it's random. Is that one? OK, then OK. I can't use the heat
pack. It's almost there. All right, just make my way over there. Come on, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on, do it already. I'd be freaking out if I were you, dude. I'm all right. I just don't.
Is there a pattern? It doesn't feel like there is. If I go down, what happens?
It takes that one down. I go up. It takes the one above me. If I go down, will it
reappear? No, it won't. So what if I go left? What if I go right? OK, left again. Up. OK,
all right. Wait, wait, wait. I think I'm starting to understand what's going on here. All right.
All right. All right. OK, so what is making it? So why did that spawn down there is the opposite
side? I don't know. I diagonal down left middle. No, it's definitely not random. It's OK. Well,
how do I know if it's going to move one or not? If I go down, it takes someone below
where I land. If I go up, it takes below. If I go left, it takes the next one to go right.
Diagonal is nothing throwing me off. Is that it? Did I get it? I think that's it. Is that it?
Fuck you. The blocks of ice are laid out in a grid pattern with horizontal, vertical,
and diagonal rows. If Nancy moves along a horizontal row, then random ice flows in that
row will appear or disappear. She moves in a vertical, then it will be ice flows in the
column that appeared. The same applies. Is this pre-recorded? No, it's just because you know
what I was about to say to you. I stopped myself. I stopped myself from saying. Have you been on this
for an hour? No, I just don't. We're fine. All right. I am starting to understand. So I want to
go diagonal because I want it to hold on. I want to like fill in the next diagonal spot, right?
I go like that and it'll have to. Okay. Fill it in again. Do it again. Fill it in.
It's just so cold. The ruin one lets you place one. Yeah. Got it. I don't know whose this is or
why that wolf left it here, but at least now I won't freeze to death.
Whose jacket is this? I feel warmer already. There's a note in one of the pockets.
Swear word. Since I can't go back the way I came, maybe these tracks will lead me to shelter.
Beautiful mountain range. Beautiful mountain range. Avalanche ridge. Not exactly reassuring.
At this point that I look up, I cup my hands to my mouth and I go
just fucking wait and see what happens. The snow's so deep. I'm sinking up to my knees.
If I want to follow those tracks, I'm going to need some snowshoes.
Oh, I know where to get those.
Reuse joke do better. There's like 10,000 people that weren't here when I did that like two years
ago. Stop it. What's this place called? Avalanche ridge. All right. So I got to get the
snowshoes to go to Avalanche ridge.
What? No, get. Wait, eat the thing. Eat the hand warmers. I don't eat them, but
hypothermia claims Icicle Creek lodge employee. What? Avalanche ridge. Not exactly reassuring.
Ski tracks. Probably Yanni's. I bet if I follow them, I'll wind up back at the lodge.
I was right. Nobody's going to look out the window and see Nancy Drew is like blue
with icicles all over her face and shit. So come on. Was nobody aware? If I don't get warm soon,
I may not make it. I feel warmer. Lunchtime. I got it. I got this. Don't worry. Oh, wait,
somebody's sleeping. Well, who are you? Well, keep it down. Somebody's sleeping over there.
Uh, I'm Elsa's replacement. Oh, the new maid. Thank goodness. I was wondering how much longer
the owner expected us to endure these conditions and still pay full price. I'm trying to learn
everyone's name. What's your name? My name is Guadalupe Comeo. My friends call me Lupe.
So I should call you Lupe. I hardly think so, dear. Yeah. I don't even know your name.
My name's Nancy Drew. Wonderful. Now be a doll and clean my room first. It'll hardly take you
any time at all, especially compared to the other rooms. The other guests are all men, single men.
Well, I'm happy to report that I've already cleaned your room. Excellent. What are you doing? I hate
to sound nosy, but what are you doing? Birds. I'm watching birds. That's what I am. You see a bird
watcher. Sometimes I go outside and watch and sometimes I stay inside. It all depends on what
the birds feel like doing and what I feel like doing. She fucked up the, she fucked up the
shack. That was the bird newspaper with the number on it. There's a bird magazine. Hmm. So that's
what brought you to Icicle Creek Lodge, the birding? Absolutely. The place is a veritable
birding paradise, even in winter. In fact, in the short time I've been here, I've seen hawks,
eagles, orioles, cardinals, jays. I was just going to say, oh yeah, name three birds.
I should have said it. I was holding it until the conversation was over. I was right about to say,
oh yeah, name three birds. That would have been really funny. I was holding it because I didn't
want to talk over the conversation. Well, okay. Well, you named three birds. There you go.
Have you met the other guests? I've bumped into them at one time or another. Yes, I don't spend
all my time in front of this window. That Yanni fellow, he's very talented, but extremely intense.
His whole life revolves around being the best in the world. As for the two who are always sitting
across the way playing that silly game, the older man, Bill Kessler, he's no deep thinker,
but he's nice enough. But the other one, that college student, talking to him is like trying
to converse with a giant turnip. You're hiding booze in there? You're hiding booze in there?
I almost prefer talking to the handyman, almost. Okay. Anyone that intent on destroying something
as glorious as that wolf is hardly worth talking to. I'm just gonna say it's a little quiet.
You can turn it up. Let me know if that's better. Have you seen the wolf? Have you ever seen the
wolf that's been hanging out around here? No, not that I'm looking for it. Of course, Yanni
occasionally skis by, and that dullard, the student, I see him snowshoeing occasionally,
but I've yet to see the wolf. Have you seen it? No, you see, I have. Yeah, up close and personal,
as a matter of fact. How did it act? Was it aggressive? Did it look injured?
You seem to really want to know a lot about this wolf, even though you claim to not really care,
and you're hiding booze in those binoculars. I don't think I fucking don't know.
Actually, I think it may have saved my life. Really? Of course, its behavior does suggest
that it's had contact with humans before. Have you told anyone else what you just told me?
No. Good. Don't. You see, I'd like to see this wolf for myself, and I don't want everyone else
going after it and scaring it away. Okay, I have to tell everybody. There's no telling what that
trigger-happy handyman might do. So it'll just be our little secret, all right?
No. No. No, because I'm not going to end up with a kitchen knife in my back in 10 minutes.
I'm going to tell everybody. Do you want a book about birds of the southwest?
I might. Why do you ask? Hmm. See, I just like, just totally just throw this whole thing under
the bus and just be like, well, because I know what you're doing. I know everything. And I know
there's booze in there. Because I found a piece of a book cover in the fishing shack,
and since it was about birds, I wondered if it was yours.
No, it's not from any book I have. I've never been in the ice fishing shack, so how could it be?
Yeah, but it forgot the whole part where I walk up to the window, get out a cigarette, like,
start smoking the cigarette and telling her about the magazine that I found in the shack.
Well, there was a magazine in the shack that had a lot of things about birds in it, and
well, I mean, not too many people around these parts really love birds as much as some people
I've talked to recently. Have a good afternoon. And I make loud fucking walking sounds. There's
like jingling on my person, you know what I mean? Just like, ching, ching, ching. I make noise
whenever I go anywhere. Good luck. Good luck with your birding. Au revoir.
Yeah, if I was a... Sorry, let me get my fucking 200-caliber sniper rifle I dropped on the ground.
I wonder what you're doing out here.
Okay, well then where did this just come from?
It was probably lying there on the floor all along and you just happened to kick it into view,
that's all. This did used to be a hunting lodge deer. I wouldn't worry about it.
Yeah, I'm telling you, if I was ever a detective, I'm having, I'm putting a bunch of coins in my
pocket. I'm going to walk around like a tambourine. I'm going to make sure that, like, I'm going to
wear, like, leather so it makes like... I'm going to be fucking loud as fuck if I go anywhere. I'm
going to be making all kinds of noise. Like, I'm going to lean down to stretch and look at, like,
where the body was. Yeah, interesting. Light up a cigarette. How'd they die?
Sure, am I just going to accuse this? Am I going to accuse her of this?
Worst joke? Why? I thought it was humorous.
You did it because you're a member of the Run and Grow Free and you're trying to protect the
wolf at any cost, aren't you? That's why you have that magazine in your room so you figure out how
to keep Olly Randall from shooting the wolf. These are both the same thing, aren't they?
If you didn't find this bullet, it would have ended up in your back.
I don't want to see anything happen to that wolf either. If you belong to Run and Grow Free,
just tell me. I'm good at keeping secrets, believe me. You're right, I am a member of the Run and Grow Free.
I'm a detective, aren't I trying to... I did make sure that brute would miss if he took a shot at
the wolf, and I will do whatever it takes to protect that beautiful creature. Hey, we're talking
about a potential crime that's being committed, but just tell me. I mean, just tell me the crime
you're committing. I can keep a secret so you're undercover. So you're here undercover? Yes.
What are you going to do next? What are you going to do next? That's all I'm going to tell you, Nancy.
And if you really are concerned about the wolf's welfare, you won't repeat any of this to anyone.
Let's not talk anymore, Nancy. People are starting to get suspicious. R1, R1, R1, R1, R1. Hey, hey,
you wouldn't believe what the fuck is going on in this lodge. Wait, can I talk to you?
Nancy, hi. What the heck happened out there? Actually, I'm not quite sure. I walked out to
Icicle Lake to see how you were doing in the fishing shack, only there wasn't any fishing
shack. There wasn't even a lake. The ice was all busted up like somebody dropped a bomb on it.
All I know is... I wouldn't want to be told any of this shit. I walked outside and someone knocked me
unconscious with an ice ball. The next thing I knew there was an explosion and I was on an ice
flow in the middle of the lake with no code and no fish. Somebody decked you with an ice
ball and blew up the lake? Holy moly. The good news is you're okay. The bad news? No more ice fishing.
I mean, I don't know, if like a detective came up to me and was like, hey, hey, listen to all this
shit that's going on. Hey, by the way, I know it's her. It'd be like, who? Oh, hey, the lady by the
window with the binoculars. Watch the fuck out. It's like, oh, but the arrestor, what are you
talking about? Yeah, by the way, hey, just want to let you know, she dropped a bullet. What? Yeah,
shut up, don't do that, I'm not supposed to tell anybody. You're not a cop. Oh, no, that's right.
I'm just like an investigative enthusiast, right? What is Nancy Drew's, what's Nancy Drew for a
career? You're literally like 16. Nancy Drew is just like a teenager. Oh, she's a true crime
podcast fan. Oh, since Mr. Talbot isn't here, could I play a game of fox and geese with you?
You bet. Have a seat. Here are the rules. Oh, no, I don't want to do this. The black piece is the fox.
The goal of the geese is to corner the fox so he can't move, while the goal of the fox
is to gobble up geese so that they can't corner him. The geese can only move forward along a
line to the next point, either directly forwards, diagonally, or sideways. You gotta slow down. Same
thing for the fox, except when he's next to a goose that has an empty spot directly behind it.
He can jump over it. Gobble it up. Right, gobble it up and remove it from the board. Dave. Just take
turns and play until somebody wins and somebody loses. Dave, I just found a bullet on the ground.
I don't want to do this. No, I don't. I really don't want to do this. I don't. The goal is to...
Let me read this for a minute. Okay. The goal of the geese is to corner the fox so he can't move.
The goal of the fox is to gobble up the geese so they can't corner him. The geese can only move
forward along a line to the next point, so the geese can only move forward. They can't go diagonal.
No, they can go diagonal, but they can only move one space, except when he's next to a goose that
has an empty spot behind it, he can just brute force the puzzle because it can't be that hard.
You bet. What team am I on? Shit in my... No! Can't restart. I don't... I take these things.
If I walk by and there's a puzzle like this being played, I walk right by it,
or I lean over to two people playing it and I go, oh, interesting. You want to play? No, no,
no, no, no, no. You guys are doing pretty sick. You guys are good. I don't play... I would never
play this. I would glance over and say, cool, and then I would never talk about it ever again.
Whatever. I don't... It doesn't matter. There. Now you... Okay, I have to restart. I gotta back away.
Okay, if we start over. Oh my god. Okay, what is the... What's the... I don't know. I know it's about
patience and I have none of that. Watch this spot down here. All right, you cannot go anywhere. I've
got you locked right here. Actually can't do anything. Cannot go anywhere. Now we close it in.
Slowly close it in. You can't go that way. All right, if you go up, you could take that out. If
you go up, you... All right. Slowly close it in. Okay. Okay, now... No! Oh! No, no, no, no, no, no.
I got it, I got it. Sorry, sorry, sorry. I don't... I fucking don't know. I fucked it up. It's okay.
You actually can't go anywhere. Okay, now... I got greedy. I win. I win. Not yet. I need to...
Did I win? But will... I think he'll just jump it. Won't he just jump it? Oh my god, what just
happened? I fucking hate this. I want to delete this so bad. I would flip the table at this point.
I don't know what just happened. I fucking hate this shit. I never play these. I avoid these like
the... I avoid them because I don't want to play these. I don't like... I don't play checkers,
I don't play chess. Everyone... I've had people ask me, oh, are you interested in playing chess?
No, zero. It's a big brains. A lot of brains involved. I'm not saying I have a small brain.
I'm just saying a very particular brain that does particular things pretty well. This is not one of
them. I had it. I... Dude, I know I had it. You know the guy who stabbed that? Don't save it.
Just quit and just start over. I hate these fucking things. It's not even hard. It's just like...
Yeah, I have to sit there and just like... I thought I just won. This game is best for an
ages nine and up. Yeah, I know at the age... I know the rating it has. Now I'm just fucking tilted.
I'm just... I don't want to be doing this. Okay, if we start over. Where's the part where I could
like sprint wicked fast for a few minutes? You know what I mean? Like where's that part?
I had it. I know. I just don't care. I just want to flip this. Fuck out of here. Now you're stuck
here. Now you're stuck here. Now I can bring everything down safely, right? Yes. Now I can
go down. We're good. Now this is where I screw it up. If I go down here, can't go left, but he can
go that way. So let me think about this. If I go down, it's going here, which means I had... This
one has to be here, right? I'm just planning this out. So if he goes here, I don't... So then this
one needs to be moved as well. We don't want to give him any opportunity. This means he cannot
go diagonal from here. So if I go down with this one, he can jump it. If I go down with this one
right now, he cannot. Save it right now. Oh, nice. So let's see what happens. Okay. I'm scared.
No! I saw it. I saw it the last second. I hate these fucking games. No, it doesn't let you cheat.
It doesn't let you cheat. It doesn't let you cheat. It doesn't... Oh my God. Why did I...
It's one little mistake. Just fucked the whole thing up. I hate this. I don't want to do this.
What went so wrong there? God damn it. Fuck you. I would never bring this to Friday night game night
ever. Where you going? Why are you doing that? Why are you doing that? Why are you doing that?
Why is he doing that? He can't go this way, right? Can he go this way? He cannot go this way. Can he?
No. No, no, no. Okay. Oh my God. I can't... Oh my God. I can't do it. I don't think I can do it,
guys. I don't think I can fucking do it. I think I have to literally get a save file from some fucking
random ass website. I fucking hate this more than anything. I hate this shit. I hate this shit.
I can't play these. I can't... I just don't have the... I just don't have... I could do it and I'm
going to shut the heck up and I'm going to beat it right now. Start the timer. We're not sitting
here anymore. I promise. All of you that are sitting there that are thinking, I can't believe
this guy... I can't believe this guy drives a car. I got you. Just relax. What would this have to do
with driving a car anyways? It's not like you do this when you stop at a stop sign. I can't do
anything. He's stuck. I can move this here and it's safe. No, I can't do that. Okay. Wait a minute.
What if I put him up here? No. Should I put him up there? Worst gamer moment. These things are
annoying and hard. I guarantee you. You sit... 90% of you down. You ain't going to beat this in five
minutes. What should I move? I just... I'm so paranoid that I'm going to just miss something.
I wonder if the other guy got up because he was kicking his ass for three straight days in a lodge
and that's all you guys can do is sit here. Oh my god. I can't even see it. I can't even comprehend
it. My brain is not wired to be able to understand how this game works in every single facet of it.
This is like the one... If a bomb was going to go off, get me out of this room. Don't give
this to me. It's not going to happen. God damn it. I fucking want to get out of here so bad.
Okay, we start over. It's so... It's not hard. It's just there are so many places to screw it up.
All right. I'm going to get it this time. All right. Trust me. That's safe. Everything is safe
if I do it here. There's nothing. You can jump over here so I can start closing the gap here.
As long as I move this and then the other one right behind it immediately.
Okay. You're stuck here. Same deal. Wait. I got to be aware of this. So move... What should I... I
don't know what to do first. Putting this here is free. It would ruin everything. So moving this
would have to see what he moves. If I put this here and he moves diagonal. I don't know. Maybe
I should move one of these down. This one down because then he has to go up and then from here
you've got nothing. You've got nothing. You've got nothing. So I can safely move this here
or this forward. You've got nothing. Okay. You've got... You've got nothing. This is coming down.
You've got nothing. This is coming down. You've got nothing. You've got nothing here. There's no
diagonal to here. So I can move this. You'll come down and you got nothing. By the way. You've got
nothing. All right. Now we come down with it. Right? Come down with this one and down with this one.
You've got no... You can't... You literally can't go anywhere. So just bring these ones down
where I can. All right. Now what? Now what? Should I try to do what I did before and just keep them
down here? Is that the right play? Keeping them down here. Is that the right play? All right.
We're solid right now. Actually has nowhere to go. Now I don't want to mess this up. And I'm going
to if I don't... I'm going to mess this up big time. If I put this one down then it's bad.
This one comes down it's over. This one comes down it's not over. If I put the middle one down.
If I put this down and he goes to the diagonal. I'm in trouble aren't I? I could have one move
to bring the one down which should save me. Right? Middle coming down blocks everything he's doing.
Now he can go... He can only go this way so I can block that here. Wait a minute. Hold on. Wait,
wait, wait. Block that. He has to go back down. So he ends up here and I have these two. So you
end up right here with two here. He can't... If I go down then he'll go that way and I'm going to
bring another one down. Should I... Okay this one or the middle one? I'm not sure because I think
it's both scary. Or do I bring this down again? But that will I think open up too many opportunities.
I think I'm bringing the right one down. Okay. Then I'm bringing this one down that blocks him
so he can go right. He's going to go right. I'll block that. He's going to go right again.
I don't... I can't block it again. What? What? Hey what happened? What? What? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Excuse me. What's going on? What just happened? Why did it move? What just happened? Okay we're
fine. He went up. Bring middle down or do I bring this one down? If I bring this down here
then he has to go right. This is... I think this is correct. So many people don't know.
I don't want to mess this up. I swear. This one going down or this one come down? Bro he's
stupid. I just don't want to mess it up. I just don't want to screw it up. The top one,
this one comes down. That's what I was thinking. That's correct, right? Yes. That's what I would
have done. All right. Now I can't come down. I can't come down. We just have to start moving
other stuff down because if I move anything it's over. This has to come down. He's now...
She's trapped here. He can't do anything. This comes down. Ah! What? I'm safe as long as I'm
going to get everything in the right spot. If even it comes up here I can't... All right. Bring
everything down. Okay. All right. Now this comes down. If he moves to the right then I block it.
Right? Blocked. Blocked. Blocked. Wait. He's gonna move down. If I move this then he'll be
able to get that. Blocked. Blocked. Blocked. Blocked. Okay. Blocked. Now. I got him!
What just happened? Did I lose? Did I win? Did it take too long? He fell asleep.
It was optional. You have to win this three times. No, I don't. How about another game? No.
It's three games. No, it's not. I don't remember any of that. I would just watch the VOD.
It's just a side game. No, it's definitely not seven times. It's just optional. Well, I thought
he was gonna give me an item or something. All right. Well, now what the hell am I doing now?
Oh, now what? Well, sorry to bother you. You want to talk? You know where to find me.
Whatever. Well, okay. Fine. Now what? Oh, it's time for dinner. Oops. Oopsie. Um, okay. This is fun.
This is a fun game. Hope everyone's having a good time. I'm having a good time. I need to cook.
Where's the door? I have no object permanence. Nancy, Chantal's calling. Again?
Lunch. I'm never here. I'm never here to cook food. Oh, God. This is elaborate.
One salad with a bunch of bullshit in it. Oh, my goodness. Okay. What is salmon and or a salad.
Cook salmon on the griddle and remove when it turns bright orange pink. Put extra salad ingredients
in the salad bowl on top of the lettuce. All salads are to be topped with the Lodge's famous
Icicle Creek ranch dressing. What if somebody doesn't want ranch dressing? We just put it on
everything. Why would I? What if somebody says don't put any sauce on it? Do I say? I don't
care. I saw it comes. What do you want? One say, let's get this right. One salmon. Okay. Now you
want three egg, three. I'm going to have to look at this like five times. Don't want any anchovies
and no croutons. Three egg, three yellow peppers. Does all salad have lettuce? Which one? This is
lettuce. Does all salad have lettuce on it? Yeah. Okay. Three eggs, three yellow peppers, two
tomatoes. Three eggs. Dude, that's a lot of eggs. Three yellow peppers. That's kind of a fucked up
salad. Two tomatoes, two spinach, three carrots, three cucumbers. Okay. Here you go. Salad. Enjoy.
Order up. What do you want? Two salmons and then one salad with two egg and then a bunch of other
stuff. Two eggs, one yellow pepper, two tomato, two spinach, one anchovy, three carrots, three
cucumber, two croutons. Order up. What do you want? One salmon and one salad. What do you want on it?
Two egg, three yellow peppers. One, two, three. One tomato, one spinach, two anchovy, one carrot,
and three cucumber, two croutons. There you go. Order up. Just want a salad. Two egg, three yellow
peppers. I can't remember this. Okay, we're good. What do you want? Two egg, three yellow peppers.
One, two, three. Two tomatoes, two spinach. Okay. One carrot, one cucumber. Easy. And then three
croutons, right? Yeah. Order up. Are you de-boning the fish? No, I don't think so. All right. Two of
these. What do you want? Do you want any of that? All right. What? Put four on. You're both getting
salad. Yes, they're both getting salad. I put, oh, what just happened? All right. They're both
getting a salad. Did I just frisbee that? Where did that just go? All right. You're both getting
salads. You both want one egg, two yellow peppers, both two yellow peppers, one tomato, two tomato,
three spinach, one spinach, two anchovy, two carrot, one carrot. What was it? Three cucumbers,
two croutons. Two cucumbers, three croutons. What? Three cucumbers, two, um, what? Okay. Yours is done.
And then you wanted two. Order up. We're done. We're good. Okay. Very nice. Now I did that.
Everything's good. We were in the middle of trying to figure out what this is. Okay, we've got a
okay, it's a four. Wait, what's that? No, no, no. What is that on the wall? On the wall, on the wall,
on the wall. Come on. You're not going to do this to me right now. Come on to the wall. What's that?
No, we're in Canada. All right. What's Canadian? Canadian, um, hockey, maple syrup, um, trees,
mountains, snow, poutine. All right. We're good. Who cares? When do I get to go to sleep by the way?
Hmm. Should I go upstairs? I feel like people are in their rooms now. Let me see. Right. People in
their rooms or anything? No, I don't get it. We can name one human being who is not yourself. Um,
anymore? Why am I stuck here? What's going on? What do you want? You messed with my rifle,
didn't you? This I got to hear. What? Excuse me? This fact just came for you. It's from the
wacko left-wing wildlife gang that paid you to screw up my rifle so I'd miss that wolf.
Talk to me like that. I'm leaving this place right now. Good. You just got yourself an escort off
the premises. What happened? Hey, wait, wait. No, I'm the detective. Come talk to me. Wait.
I'm not going outside now. It's too cold. What the heck? That's for me. What? Nancy, because of that
Neanderthal of a handyman, I've been forced to return home. Please call me. When it comes
to the white wolf, there was much for us to talk about. All right. Let's call you on a secure line.
Two, one, three, five, five, five. Just do the two, one, three part. Two, one, three, three, two,
six, four. Two, one, three, three, two, six, four. What was it? Two, two, one, two, one, three,
three, two, six, four. What? Hi, this is Nancy Drew. I'll call you later. Oh, no. Call now.
What was it? Three, three, two, six, four. Still not there. Still not there. She just left. Give her
a few minutes. What am I going to do for a few minutes? I got to go talk to that guy.
Walking around. You hear that? Who's walking around? What you need? What's going on here?
I couldn't help but overhear the argument you and Miss Camille had. She messed up my
raffle so I couldn't shoot that wolf. So I tossed her out, told her to take her little crusade
somewhere else. Tell. Have you told Chantal that you threw her out? Chantal that? Not yet.
She's not going to be happy. But by golly, that woman was a menace. Anybody who deliberately
sabotage a man's rifle is capable of anything. But at least now I know why I miss that wolf.
And like I told her as I was giving her the bum's rush next time, I won't miss.
Oh, that's why you missed. Thumbs up some major copium. Oh, hasn't your rifle been?
I'd better get back upstairs. If you need anything, just holler.
Copium. Yeah, all of you guys would be saying no skill issue, skill issue.
All right. Can I call her now? Was it three, two, six, four? Still not there. So now what do I
got to do? I can't leave. I'm not going outside now. It's too cold. Call in the morning maybe.
Can I just go to bed? I feel like there's not much else I can do right now. Call 1555 Mystico
and prepare to be amazed. There's not even enough numbers on a keypad to type that in.
Whoever came up with that jingle. What are you talking about? Go call it? There's not even that
many numbers. That doesn't make any sense. What was it? Mystico, 1555, 1555, 1555, 1555, call
it. What is it? 1555, M, Y, S, T, I, C, O?
Who dares disturb the concentration of Mystico the Magnificent?
Um, I'm sorry. This is Nancy Drew. Nancy Drew, I see your future clear as tape.
I see. That's too many numbers. And a dark figure named Bruno. Bruno. Bruno? But beware,
Nancy Drew. The wolf will only lead to danger and intrigue. Cool. I mean, yes, Mystico.
The Magnificent. Huh? You're supposed to say Mystico the Magnificent.
Oh, right. Yes, Mystico the Magnificent. So Nancy Drew, what secrets from the beyond do you seek?
A hint. What do you think I am? An insurance salesman, a pair of underage
detectives, a star-struck teenager, a watch the police officer, an elderly housekeeper, a parrot?
You have incurred the wrath of Mystico. From this moment forward, bad luck shall creep behind you
like a malevolent shadow. Don't say that. Mystico has spoken. Now, why would you say that to me?
What the heck? Do that? People sad. Well, I'm just going to go to bed. Isn't this my room?
This is my room. This is my room. Where's my room? This is my room. Which one of these is mine?
Isn't it this one? It's the one that's locked. If you put your face cam on, we'll tell you.
You would like me to turn my face cam on, wouldn't you? Check my items.
Okay, I need to call her in the morning. It's this thing. I haven't seen any of these. I don't
know what that's trying to tell me. What is this? Oh, that's the fishing toolbox. I already did that.
Here's the bullet. I already called this. This is the book of things going on. I don't know.
What about her room? I'm going up to her room because, okay, she just got like kicked out,
right? Maybe she left something behind? I don't know. What was the word I said again?
Oh, lolly. Did he leave something behind? I mean, it's 730 at night. It's getting kind of late.
I can't leave, so there's got to be something I can do here. This is weird, too. What is this?
Why does it want me to look at this? 730 isn't late. Well, it's late enough where I can't leave
the lodge. I need to get the snowshoes. How do I get the snowshoes from him? I don't get it.
I can talk to this guy again.
Do you have no other dialogue? No. What about the sauna? The sauna's just hanging out here.
Is there anything I can do with the sauna? I don't know. What's this for?
I don't know. Lala or pre-recorded. That's the worst way to get me to do that.
Save the game. This is the first game that I ever played. It's a good one, so I can't leave.
So I have to call that number. You're just not available. Go to bed? I can't. I can't go to sleep.
Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat.
Oh, it's closed, though. What do I do? Are these symbols in the... Wait a minute. What about that
device that's sitting on the table? Where is it? With the wolf face and this thing. Have I not
figured out what the hell this means yet? I have to know what is going on here, right? I have to
know what this means. What is this? You know what I'm saying? There's nothing under the table.
What about that symbol note? Yeah, but what... Okay, is there... Do the animals have symbols
next to them somewhere? I think it means... I'm not reading that. It's the Saga of the White Wolf.
Don't forget. Yeah, I know. So what? What does that mean? What does that mean? Why are you saying
that? Why are you putting that in quotes? Don't forget. It's the Saga of the White Wolf. Why are
you saying that? What's that? Is that a book? Is that a book up here? Where are the books? How do
I go to sleep? Skip. I'm trying not to spin in circles. Go that way. Who had that book? Saga of
the Winter Sports Monthly. The Call of the Wild. That's not it. I thought this was going to be it.
Where is it? It's the Saga of the White Wolf. Damn it. I don't know where to go. Engineering,
geology, machines. Wait, what was that crumpled up piece of paper? It's all totally unfair and
I'm sick of putting up with things that aren't fair. It's his fault, her fault, their fault,
but I don't have what's rightfully mine. They are thieves and it's an insult to have what they
stole from us waved around in my face. I could throttle them, both of them, for what they did.
Justice shall be served one day. One day I will have justice. Whose room is this? Pish one? Pish
Pish is who? Bill Kessler. Okay, Bill, that's your room. Snowshoes on the ground? Are those snowshoes?
I don't think I can look down and get them. Other room? Those are slippers, dude.
Just get out there in slippers. God damn it. Where am I going? Okay, I need to fucking focus
for one goddamn second. The same shit happens to me in Myst when it's just pictures. Instead of
actually moving, my brain does not let me put it into memory. This is Bill's room. No, this is my
room. Whose fucking room is this? Where are the snowshoes? Get them. I can't pick them up. I can't
touch them. No stealing. I've been walking around in a simulated hour. Please lala into your
microphone. Need to check the den? What the fuck is this? What are these? Snowshoes. I thought
these were tennis rackets. Wait a minute. Do I have something here? What's this? How do I get that?
Heat and moisture sometimes cause the door of the sauna to stick. Periodically check to make sure
that no guests are inside. What? That sounds pretty bad. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
She was full of shit. There are no eagles in the winter. There are no orioles in the winter.
She's a liar. Not watching birds at all. There's booze in that. Don't we already know that she
wasn't bird watching? She told us. Interesting. That's right. Good detectives always stick together
by the tens of thousands. So, you know, you know, I'll work on a case with me to get there. Imagine
being a detective and having fucking twitch chat. Oh my god. What a fucking nightmare. All right. I
need to figure out how to get these. It's a four digit code. What's the code? Like is it a number?
It's numbers. Okay. You know, I've seen, I've seen this number in the chat. Drew Crew spammed this so
he opens it. I think this is cheating. The Drew Crew wants me to hurry up and finish this. I mean,
I'm, I'm, I can't pretend like I haven't seen the number like a thousand times.
Everybody's writing this. It's four. It's. Oh, now they're fucking it all up. Okay.
Drew Crew spammed this so he sees. It's not even real. I'm going to get it on my own. Okay. And by
on my own, I mean, I want you to help me get there. I'm going to ask you a bunch of questions
and I would like for you to answer them. I am the detective. I'm asking you. It's time for your
questioning. You've looked at that dog breath. I feel like that sometimes. Oh, check on somebody,
dude. I think the balls are stuck to the bottom. I think we're okay, man. Nice talking to you.
Been real. What's up? Nice talking to you. Ditto, dude. It's something with this, right? But I don't
know. I need the snowshoes. I got to figure out what that because this is telling me what the code
is, but that where are their numbers? Are there numbers somewhere that I've like with symbols
next to them? Cause I don't, I don't know what this would be next to the numbers are on the note.
This is not, these are symbols. It's mirrored. What are you talking about? This is a four,
a one, an eight, a nine. What do you mean? It's mirrored. How does he not see it? It's guys.
Hold on. Seven, nine, one, four. But I know, but I thought this, but I'll buy it. Hold on a second.
Hold on a second. I get that. But what I'm looking for is I see this shit all over the place. I see
these. Hold on a minute. Like I saw, I saw like this triangle and I was like, okay, triangle,
maybe that's like, hold on. I'm looking for symbols that I have a number. I forgot this game was made
for children. Okay. Well not adults too. We can enjoy these for everybody. What was it? Seven,
one, seven, nine. What is it? What is it? Seven, nine, eight, seven, nine, one, four. That's not
correct. That's incorrect. That's incorrect. You guys don't have it right. Seven, nine, one,
four is incorrect. Seven, nine, one, four. Four, one, nine, seven. What's happening right now?
Because I don't think this is right. You guys are all wrong. Four, one, write it correctly. Four, one,
that's not correct. You guys got it wrong. Seven, nine, one, four. Drew. Yeah. The Drew crew has
failed. Keep it in mind. That's a shoelace. Seven, nine, one, four. So what's, what's going on here?
Is it like an accept button? Press enter. If that's for something else then. Well,
shit. That might be for the suitcase. Maybe it's backwards. Yeah. I'll put it in. I just did it
backwards too. Maybe a year. Not like 19, 1940s, 1947. Would it be a year? I don't know. I don't
know. No, it's definitely, that's for something else. Read the plaque.
Snowshoes owned and used by Trapper Dan in the early 1900s. Right. That didn't work. What about
1974? No. What about seven? Hold on. Seven, six. No, that's not going to be a six. That's nine.
Oh wait. I'm going to call the number. Still not there. It's a six. Oh my God. I'm dying. You think
it's a six? So it would be seven, seven, six, one, four. Time that person up for one second.
Look at the wall. Oh my God. Hold on. Trapper Dan started construction of what is known today
as the Ice Creek in 1894. It served as his center of operations until the winter of 1921.
When he vanished without a trace in 1934, the lodge was purchased by Abe Wentworth who maintained
it as a hunting lodge until, okay, 1894. 1934. 19, let's just write 19, 19, 1934. 19, 1930. I don't
know. 1980. You're wrong. All of you. All of you are wrong. Seven, six, six, nine. You're wrong too.
At some point, who's coming over here and going, Nancy, what are you doing over there?
Call the number. I just did. You have to call Tino. What the fuck? Tino, are you awake?
I need help. I think that'll do it. Thanks, Tino. Can't I just be like, what's the code for the
snowshoes? Cause I need them. Why is this so difficult? Can I, can somebody get me snowshoes?
Hi, Chantal. It's Nancy Drew. Not quite yet. This is a lot of questions. How come the entries for
last year were deleted from the guest register? That's what the computer says. Contents deleted.
Well, I didn't. Okay. Ollie's daughter? Has she done other things like that? No. I think that's
only in movies. Besides, pretty much all this person had to do was press the delete key.
Maybe it was on the kid? I'd like to know more about the accidents. I asked Ollie, but he said
you said he wasn't allowed to talk about them. The guest server. Okay. I'm not listening. I'm
not paying any attention by the way. But the only incidents that you can be sure were sabotage were
the tires, the phone wires, and maybe the explosion in the bunkhouse. I gotta send this. I gotta do
the survey. Where's the survey? I better get back to work. No, I had to go. No, I had to go. Don't
one-up me. Don't one-up me during our conversation. Hey, I'm wicked busy. You got a lot of stuff going
on. I'm out of here. Oh, I'm actually wicked busy too. Yeah. I was just about to leave. No, I was.
You weren't. I was about to leave. Okay. How do I fill out this survey? Is it on the computer
or something? Like where's the survey? In your inventory. No, it's not. What kind of weird social?
I'm just kidding. I don't actually think that. Or does he? All right. So I don't have this thing
you're talking about. Let's see. Get the guest survey. I was, when I just talked. Give me the
survey. Hi, it's Nancy Drew. Yes, but he said no. Darn. I can't. There's nobody. I just talked.
There's no guest. The guests that are in the lodge now. Did any of them stay here last year?
About Tino. About Tino. I'm not totally comfortable with the idea of consulting with him on this case.
Okay. Do you know what he did when we were on that train trip Laurie Gerard arranged?
Understood. Anything else? No. I better get back to work. I have to get going too. Go outside? I can't.
It won't let me. It's too cold apparently. Carrying this laundry bag around is a pain. I need to dump
it down. Why do I have the laundry bag at 10 o'clock at night? Who told me to pick this up?
If I go outside now, I'll freeze. I can't do anything. Go to bed? I don't think I can go to bed.
I'm just trapped. I can? I was in my room and I couldn't click on my bed.
Get me the hell out of here. Which is, which my room again? I better wait until this do not disturb
sign is gone. I better wait until this do not disturb sign is gone. Where's my room? This is my
bedroom. What just hit me in the head? Why is it, I woke up at one o'clock in the morning?
Now it's 1 p.m. I missed, I missed serving breakfast. Oh god. Just hold on. True though.
How often does that happen? All the time. I gotta, I gotta go to food. As long as it's not time to
cook, I might as well stay out of the kitchen. All right. Now I can finally leave. I'm gonna call
that number. What was it? One, three, three, two, six. I've memorized it by this point.
Ms. Camillo, hi. It's Nancy Drew from Icicle Creek Lodge. Yes. Well, Ollie hasn't succeeded in
shooting or trapping it yet, if that's what you mean. It scares me. The wolf scares me.
When I was trapped out on the lake without a coat, it dragged one to the shore and left it there for
me. It may have sensed you were in trouble. It is? Wolves and humans simca dog may mask that reason
no matter how sociable the wolf may appear. Instinct can at any moment rear its ugly head
with devastating results for any humans involved and for the wolf, especially for the wolf. It
will have simply been doing what comes naturally. Don't go up to wild animals like it's a Disney
movie. I think we've, I think we could all agree on that. So the fact that this wolf doesn't seem
to be that afraid of people could lead people to think they don't have to be afraid of it.
He's so brave. Oh, shit. I get the picture. I was talking about throwing raw turkeys to it,
right? That's my bad. Yeah, I was talking about somehow giving it raw turkeys and stuff, right?
I was like, oh, I'll just throw raw turkey at it. Yeah, that's a good idea, Jeremy. Bad idea.
Are you the one who wrecked all the gear that was in the fishing shack?
Yes, I have to bring the stream warning back. Oh, yeah. Do not attempt anything you see or hear
here. All this is to be never attempted. It's a it's a stream based around comedy and there's
some things that you hear that you do not be said again or to be attempted. I forgot about that.
Yeah, I got to have that like take up the whole entire it's going to be a watermark across the
entire image. When you were here at the lodge, how come you had a magazine that featured
in your room? You know, actually, nevermind. Why didn't you just come out and tell the people
at Icicle Creek Lodge that you were there to protect the wolf? I didn't even ask. I need to
get back to work. I'm getting back to work. We're sorry. Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
Please check the number and dial again. Recording. Now I can take the test. He's saying hi,
it's Nancy Drew. I'm glad you called. Actually, it was more like Ollie threw her out. Well,
hold on. Hold on a second. We just spoke and what I can I can just accuse. I can just accuse
automatically. Now call Tino. Bad friend. Yeah, we just became really good friends. I can now.
Yeah, but don't betray. Don't betray. I don't think so. We don't know the only we still have
to come up with proof. And now that's it for now. Now we call Tino. She gets us the survey.
I think that'll do it. Nevermind. All right. Now what the hell do I do? What do I do now?
You have to go back to Avalanche Ridge to trigger her recognizing she needs the shoes.
Didn't I already do that? I already did that. Yeah. She was like, oh, I can't go anywhere
further without snowshoes. And I kept walking and she died. Go to Avalanche Creek. You die.
You died. Avalanche Creek, not Ridge. Where's Avalanche Creek? Avalanche Ridge. Okay. Now
the snow so deep I'm sinking to my knees. Okay. If I want to follow those tracks,
gonna need some snowshoes. Turn around. I need snowshoes. If I don't get warm soon.
Oh my God. And now I'm gonna die. I don't have any more hand warmers.
I feel warmer already. All right. Now where do I get the snowshoes? You. Now call. I need snowshoes.
Where do I get them? It's Nancy. Listen, I think I'm on to something, but I desperately need
snowshoes. Could you give me the combination to the lock on the display case so I could use
the ones in there? Sure. What do you want me to do? I can't believe it. I'm just gonna write
random information. Sounds good. Excellent. As we speak. Great. I just hope the questions aren't
too dumb. Got it. Good. Okay. Nothing else to report. Don't let me down. Which side of the bed
does S get up from? Yeah, Pluto. Didn't answer. Actually, I was supposed to spill coffee on this
one. Neptune. This is two states. I don't know. The right side? What side of the bed? Left? I
don't know. And then left? All right. It's filled out. Done. That was fun. Backs it over. I can't
send this yet. First, I have to call Tino and tell him to turn his machine on. Turn your machine
on. I sure am. Huh? You bet. I better go. God damn it. I have to go interview people now.
Speedrun. They're not even here. Who do I need? I need to, okay. G, C, L, T, B, K, and Y, V.
Let's go talk to Bill down here, right? Before I forget, Chantal called. Told me I can answer any
questions you might have about those accidents after all. Guess she changed her mind. Okay.
How do you explain what happened to Carl Jenkins, the former guest who slipped on the stairs and
broke his leg? Can't explain it. One minute those stairs were clear and dry. Next minute they're
slick with ass and he's lying at the bottom of them. What's going on with my game? Okay. You're
positive they were clear and dry? Yep. Chipped every bit of frozen snow off of them. Oh, they
have the answers in the chat right now. You ask me. Fuck it. I don't care. Somebody ice those stairs
down on purpose because it wasn't nothing I did. No, sir. No, sir. I'll get out of your hair now.
By the way, you dumped the laundry bag before all the rooms were cleaned,
so I put it back up at the front desk. He's cheating. Yeah, but this mission is literally,
I just have to talk to people and get their answers. We can write, I already know them.
What is this? Do I have to spell the whole thing out? It's that, right? I don't care. I genuinely do
not. I don't care. I know people are saying, oh my God, what? I can't believe you're cheating
right now. This is, this is going to take us like an hour. This is like a gigantic fetch quest. I
don't care. I'll copy somebody's paper. This is the kind of stuff I don't, you know, this is,
I don't need to do this detective work. We already got detectives here. What planet was this one?
Just search the rooms. I just, I just pretend I did. I'm disappointed. I, I, I'm telling you,
you're not. I know you're not. You're not disappointed. I know you're not disappointed.
You cheated not only the game, but yourself. I know. That's fine. You can, don't spam that
for at least a minute though, cause I can read. Why are you even playing this game? This is the
only time I've done this. This is the one time I decided to do this. You're letting down the
Drew crew. The Drew crew. I, I'm just, I mean, I'm just saying that we have revitalized the
Drew crew the last couple of days. Yeah. There's no way it's disappointing. All right. Let me get
this right. All right. So that is earth. Wait, what earth? No. Okay. Lou is Venus. Okay. Yes.
Okay. Okay. Wolf. Yes. How many people is that? That's probably people mad at me.
It's all right. Okay. Okay. No. Okay. What is this one? That? Okay. I didn't get any of these
right even accidentally. Hey, look at that. I did it. All right. Yeah. Let's fax that over.
Turn yours on. I sure did. You messed it up. Oh my God. What was wrong with it? Oh, wrong club.
X. I know. Do it over. Not in Venus. So somebody was lying to me in the chat. Planet X. You know
how painful that would have been. All of us know that we want to avoid me opening the same three
doors 10 times over the course of 40 minutes. Right? I mean, I'm just telling you. Yep. Just
saving us a little time. No problem. I think that'll do it. That's both right. Right. Is it
because I like have, is it capital and don't do capital letters? Maybe Angeles earth earth
isn't random. I spell it wrong. It's Planet X. You're doing the shitty lying voice. No, I swear.
I promise you. I'm looking at a screenshot right now. Is this correct? This is wrong. Spelling,
spelling, spelling. You have to say Planet X. Like that. Planet X. Yeah. Let's try that. Yep.
Okay. Come on, man. What the hell? But Bill Kessler likes to ice fish. Guadalupe Camillo is the one
who likes to bird watch. Yanni Valksdaya is a champion skier and Lou Talbot likes to snowshoe.
That's right. But you were kind of right. I mean, you did pretty much describe everyone at the lodge.
There we go. Finally. Finally. Yes. To the display case. What is it? So what is the point
of that paper with the seven and the four? What was that even for the mirror? That does it for now.
I mean, these damn things did it. I did that number already, but I had to do all that bullshit
first. Okay. I got the snowshoes. Now we're going back out of the ridge. I'm going to walk on the
ice. I'm going to go get a, let me get the hand warmer. Thank you. Thank you. Okay. Now I have to
go not that way. Not that way. Not that way. This way. Snowshoes. See what's really going on here.
Now what's really going on? What happened to my snow thing? I just took it. Are you kidding me?
I just guess I saw off lock myself. What's going on? I'm starting to get really cold.
I can't stop shivering. I need to get in out of the cold. Looks like some kind of house.
Could someone be living? Hello. Is anyone here? Fuck. Wait a minute. No, no, no, no, no, no.
This is it. What is it? This is definitely it. It's what was it? Mirrored seven nine. All right.
We're in a weird book. The rest of my life by Julius McQuade. I'm not reading all this.
I'm not reading all this. No way. I don't know. It's too long. So once I get her attention by
saying her name, I can give her commands. I got to pick this up. Maybe I'll write in it.
Okay. Now I miss somebody. I feel like I'm hiking around. I have to write to somebody,
even it's my cell phone. Maybe probably not. I'm tired of writing these down. Tired of feeling
caged like an animal. I spent 40 years of working with three hours. The train will reach
Edmonton. Maybe I'll get off. Maybe I won't. I don't know. The next day I woke up in my tent
to the sound of distant gunshots this morning. Later I found my wolf pup is all by herself.
Stuck in a lunch. I figured out the hunting got him and mother since she was nowhere else around.
And since there is no way whatever extra extricate herself, I started shopping through the brambles
to free her. It took me a while though. And I was talking to her all the time, trying to keep her
from struggling and hurting herself. So what I was really doing without meaning to was
imprinting my voice and my scent on her brain. Because at first she went racing off, but then
later I noticed that she was following me. Even now she's sitting about 20 yards away,
despite my campfire. Just watching me. I haven't fed her. I avoided touching her while I was cutting
her free from the brambles, yet she's there. So since this could be the beginning of an
inter-sting relationship, I thought maybe I should take some notes. Old habits of one indeed,
whatever. A week went by. The pup whose coat is pure white still shadows me wherever I go.
Every day she narrows the distance between us, which has been reduced to about 20 feet. If I
get any closer she runs. Another like month went by. The pup which has been, I've been calling,
now keeps no less than seven feet between us at all times. Distance which I am happy as well. I've
watched her hunt for food, have seen what she can do with her teeth and jaws, and have no desire
to even encounter either on a personal basis. I have revisited the urge to feed her, to make her
in any way dependent on me, but I do talk to her. I can't help myself. I've discovered that talking
in a very basic human need, way, why, is a first listens and I don't know, but then she's something
happens. A month went by. Snow has began to fall. I've moved into an alarming dome storage,
but I found it's a little too close, but I don't care. All right, so the dog had a friend.
Hey, are there any plumbers in chat? I took apart my shower head and now I'm confused.
I've been there before and it sucks. I've actually been there before and it kind of sucks,
trying to figure out what to do with it. Yeah, I've been there. I've been there, man. It sucks.
Just, I don't know, at this point, just turn off, turn the water off and just call somebody
that knows what they're doing. That's what I do. Like it or not, I've become hers. I'm not at all
sure which, while she is never underfoot, referring to remain at least three feet away from me most
of the time, she does permit and occasionally seeks out a friendly pat or two on the head and
shoulders. Although like most dogs, she doesn't seem to consider my touch to be any kind of reward.
In fact, I sometimes feel that by letting me pet her, she's rewarding me. Like three months,
four months have gone by. With the coming of the spring, I fully expect Isis to take off one day
and never return, but so far that hasn't happened. She appears for hours at a time. No doubt to hunt,
but for some reason she always returns. Another month. Last night, a wolf started howling in the
distance. Isis sat bolt upright, jolted, and listened to my hand she was shaking when howling
ended. After a moment, she lay back down and went back to sleep. I suddenly realized that she's not
going to leave. Even it was either the wilderness or me and incredibly she chose me. This is like
another year. Isis is by far the smartest animal I have ever seen by watching her carefully and
reinforcing the commands. I could have just turned to this page and said that I can give
commands. Down, forward, jump, stay, bark, paw, left, right, around. I can give Isis not just
one command, but many commands chained in a row and she'll carry them out one by one in order.
I start with a chain of commands by saying Isis and I end the chain by saying go.
Ability to sort objects by scent. There's nobody reading this. She has an object in her mouth,
she'll sniff, then drop the object near another object that has the same scent.
Pinevale Hospital. Okay. Uh oh. Sit, sit, sit, stay. Where's the turkey? Where's my raw turkey?
Isis, stay. Okay. Isis, jump. Jump, paw, left, right, jump, down. I'm going to stop here.
Isis, jump, paw, left, right, jump, down, go.
Jump, jump, down, down, left, right. I'm going to stop here. I can't do the Konami code.
Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump. I'm going to stop. Isis, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump,
go. Wow. Bark, bark, bark, bark. I'm going to Isis, bark, bark, bark, bark, around, around, go.
So stupid. Why are we doing this? I mean, this is a really smart, intelligent dog. It seems like a
really great animal, but like, what, why am I, am I going to go out this way or what? Forward,
Isis, forward, forward, forward, forward, forward, go. Okay. So now how about, okay. So left, left,
left out the door. Okay. So left, left, left again, left, and then forward, forward and then
down, down. Like, what does that do? Isis, left, left, forward, down, go. Who's left? My left?
No, that's, that's okay. That's Isis's left. So right. So you need to go right, forward, down,
bark. Okay. So I think I want her to go out here, right? Get rid of this. Right, forward, down.
What does that do? Isis, right, forward, down, go. Right, forward, down. Wonder what this is.
Looks like there's a phone number on it. Call it. This is just practice. Oh, what's that?
This indentation looks just like the one on that plaque in the lodge where that missing Rex
bone used to be. A little bro distracted by Bop It. Okay. Well, that's, I guess that's how it is.
If I try to walk back to the lodge now, I'll freeze. I better stay here for the night.
Nancy, you forgot about breakfast. You forgot about lunch. I have customers.
That it? I think that's it. Let's go back. Thanks for being a good dog. Another explosion.
What the hell is going on out here? It wasn't the dog. The dog was with me. The dog was with
me the whole time. Do vertebrae employ this furniture to provide wings for muscle attach
missing otherwise in excellent condition. Big money. Possible urgent sleutlinosis of a new
species. This thing is important. Owner clueless. Says, says came with lodge probably excavated by
builder aka rapper Dan. Which search of immediate vicinity private property yielded possible
sauropod scapula take to lab for precise ID. Must figure out how to look for and excavate
other species in secret potential gold mine. These are just Trump tweets. Order clueless.
Okay. Well, so that's the bone. It's okay, Jerma. I get it. So, all right, let's go get that thing.
Wait, I got turned around. Which one am I going? Wait, yeah, I'm going the right way. Am I going
the right way? Yeah, okay. We're gonna check out that bone. Ah, much better. Who's this from?
Uh oh. Meet me in the sauna in the basement. I have some interesting information for you.
Well, I- Sauna sounds good to me. I'm not getting locked in the sauna. That's not gonna happen.
That's what's gonna happen. So let's prepare. Where's that? There's like a, where is it? There
it is. I need to, this is like worth a lot of money. I gotta pick this up. There's no way I don't
get- I'm gonna get closed in the sauna. Okay. Who is it? Hello? Anybody here? I'm gonna go in.
These weren't here before. That birthmark below his eye looks very familiar. Wait a minute.
Oh, somebody locked me in. Is someone out there? The door's- I'm getting really, really hot.
Well, we're dead. I can just get cold water running through these pipes. I'll be okay.
I don't get these pipes adjusted soon. I'm not gonna make it. Hold on. Not much time. I've gotta
get these pipes lined up now. What's the right? I don't get it. What's, where's it coming from?
Where's the water coming from? Is someone out there? This is really great. Finding of Isaac
music. I'm getting really, really hot. Okay. All right. So what the hell's going on here?
Do I have to connect everything? I can't take this heat much longer. Oh, that's impossible.
I don't get these pipes adjusted soon. I'm not gonna make it. What the fuck are you doing to me?
I don't have much time. I've gotta get these pipes lined up now. What the hell? This goes so fast.
Is someone out there? The door's- I'm getting really, really hot. This is a
bullshit puzzle. This is a bullshit puzzle. I'm running out of time. I've gotta do something fast.
Oh, you piece of shit. That's so awful. That's it, right? Go, go, go, go, go. That's gotta be. Why?
I've gotta get these pipes aligned before it pass out from the heat.
Every single one has to be connected, the whole thing. I can't just have one space.
I don't have much time. I've gotta get these pipes lined up now.
How the fuck am I supposed to do this? I got it. I got it. I got it. Watch, watch, watch, watch.
I have to make a closed circle with the first part and then go up. This shit is bullshit. This is
bullshit. Hey, is someone out there? The door's- I'm getting really, really hot.
No, stop.
Dude, stop doing that. This sucks.
Stop it.
That was horrible.
Trying to kill you.
Say, you look kind of bedraggled. Are you all right?
I'm fine, and I'll be even better after you and I have a little talk.
Yeah, that's me. When I was a kid, this place was practically my second home.
My late grandmother, Tilly Wentworth, used to own it.
Great. Why did you not open the door when I was dying in the sauna, screaming? I think that's
the first question we ask after we get the police here. You know what I mean? That's the
number one question. None of this other shit matters. Was she the reason you wrote that
letter I found crumpled up in your room? About two years ago, just before she died,
my grandmother sold this place to Albert Mowikwe without telling anyone in her family.
From what I've heard about Mowikwe, I'm pretty sure he bullied her into selling.
I think he cheated her, and he cheated us, and that it's high time somebody-
Taught him a lesson by, say, putting Icicle Creek Lodge out of business?
I had nothing to do with that explosion, loose window, the food poisoning, the icy stairs,
none of that stuff. You ask me, it's karma. The Mowikwes are just getting what's coming to them.
How about another game of Vox and Geese? How about another game of Vox and Geese?
Now you're talking. Have a seat. Ready? Okay.
Actually, I changed my mind. I don't want to play right now.
Okay. So what can I do for you? Since you used to spend so much time
here, do you know if there's a way to get into Trapper Dan's needle?
You know that pyramid thing on the table over there by the entrance to the dining room?
If you fool around with it until nothing but pigs show on the outside, this compartment will open
up and inside will be this round magnetic thing that used to be Trapper Dan's special master key.
Just hold it up by the needle and a hidden door will pop open.
Are you telling me that I did every animal besides pig? I did at least two of them,
and just said no. But that was the solution. I would have beat the game.
If it was all pigs, it would have opened and I would have got the key to that tower and I
would have beat the game four hours ago, five hours ago. Why did he need a special master key?
Who knows? I mean, let's face it, living all by himself way out here in the wild
winter after long dark winter, Trapper Dan was probably stark raving bonkers.
Two days ago. And we wouldn't have all these lovely memories. You know, that's true.
I better get going. Okie dokie. That's a good point.
Okay, so let's go do that. Although that would have been kind of funny.
Okay, all pigs. So what is right before pig is wolf. We have to get these all to be wolf.
Thankfully, I already did this puzzle a lot of times. I already know what to do.
Okay, now we go like this. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine.
That's fine. Okay, thankfully, open it up empty. If there was a special master key in here,
it's gone now. So what was the point of that? All for nothing? Really? Wake up. He's not in there.
Huh? Oh, now what? I opened up that pyramid like you told me, but there was nothing inside.
There wasn't? Oh, well, I'm afraid you're out of luck.
What? Could that magnetic key thing be somewhere else?
You know, Grandma Tilly once told me that if you turn the top of the pyramid 45 degrees,
then fill all the boxes on the outside with one kind of animal, then another kind of animal until
you do that for all four animals. She said if you do that, you'd find a journal in there written by
Trapper Dan himself. So just do every animal? Did you ever read it? I was a kid. What would
I want to read some crazy old coot's journal for? So go there and turn it into an animal and then
another animal and then another animal. Now, what is this? What does it want me to do? Do I have to
get it all the rows like this? One, two, okay, hold on. So one row of raccoons, a row of wolf,
row of pig, and a row of Mises. I think that's what it wants me to do. So to get this correct,
we need to line this up. So it'll always be. So what is right before wolf? This has to be
that. What is right before pig? That. And then right before this is raccoon. So if we go like
that, that's correct. But it has, okay. So that's good. So this, this, don't touch this line. This
line is, this line's fine. Okay. Pig. Oh, I messed it up. It's all right. Oh shit. You're really going
to fuck with me here now, aren't you? Okay. You're ignoring chat. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
please, please stop, stop, stop. What, what, what, what, what, what am I doing the hard way?
Just do it. Okay. All right. I'm working on it. Yeah. Yeah. Oh fuck. No. Oh boy.
Okay. I got to, I messed it up. The whole thing screwed up. Okay. I need to think about this for
a sec. It moves everything around it. I got to get all these two. Oh, this hurts my head. This
hurts my head. This hurts my head. You got to start. Okay. So you get corner and here. Oh fuck.
Oh man. I think you have to start on the corner. All right. Get everything to, what is it?
Everything has to be, everything has to be raccoon or at least close to it. This should do it.
This get all these to raccoon. Okay. And then this should do that. I should do this. Close. There it
is. Yeah. LOL. The D for beta is over. Oh, oh well. Daniel Weissnitz, better known as trapper Dan,
a hi-he-ho-ho to you for discovering my hidden journal. No doubt you already found my magnetic
key that unlocks my needle and the rooms. Keep my secrets safe, especially from the Mounties
and those rascally squirrels, evious varmints. One thing's for certain without an intelligent
creature that can crawl through small spaces such as my beloved Mary. You won't be able to
use my vaults. I fixed the vault passageways so you can see if your animal is dumb or smart by
getting lost in the vaults. Make sure your pet can jump as there are pits in there and has paws
or hooves to make the move the levers. The first thing you need to do is crack my cipher below
or just follow the moose, wolf, raccoon, and Mary. Looks like the rest is in some kind of code.
First thing you need to is to crack my cipher below or just follow the moose, wolf, raccoon,
and Mary. I think I get it. I don't. What are you saying? What is this? I have to do this?
More of this? Any combination will work. Can't find Mary? Well, try pulling on that rope above
the vaults. It'll open a surprise at the end of the hallway on the second floor. Keep it taut.
Mary always helped me with that one. She got through the maze. You just need three more
keys to open the keyholes. Oh my goodness gracious. These are the locks on the doors
that need to match the animal that need to. This thing is made out of stone. What did this shit
say again? Oh no, this. No, where's this guy's journal? Isn't this it? Where's the journal?
So the raccoons need to be the pigs. So the pigs need to be in just like the order. So raccoons
go in these two slots or something. I don't really box in the geese. Is this this blue? All right.
These are the hotel. Okay. So blue, red, white, green, blue, red. Please remember that for me.
I have to go do this to the rooms upstairs. Blue. I already forgot it. I already forgot.
Blue, red, white. Blue, red, white. Blue, red, white. Then green, blue, red. I did it. Now what?
Oh my goodness. This is one of those games where you can click out of the window accidentally and
it minimizes and re-changes all your resolutions. Wrong order. All right. Looking straight down
this way. Left side is blue. Like I'm talking like from me forward. On the left we've got blue.
Blue, red, white, green, blue, red. So blue, red, white, green, blue, red. Go to the end of the hall.
Start at the end of the hall. This isn't an emergency. I better not open it. Okay. So we've
got looking this way. Starting at the fireplace. Blue, blue, red. Okay. Blue. Stop. Oh my God. I
hate it. I hate this. I wish I could just move. This side is. So this is blue. What was it? Blue,
white, red, and green. Infinite content omega low. Hold on now. Blue, red, white on the right side.
Blue, red, white, green, blue, red. Blue, red, white. That's what I was going to say.
Green. No, close this door. What just happened? Where am I? What am I looking at? Turn back around.
Green, blue, red. That it? I don't know if that did anything. I'm taking a picture of my fucking
phone. I don't even care. I'm literally taking a picture of this on my phone. That's it. That's
what a normal, sane human being would do. We'll just take a picture of this. Here it is. Got it.
Done. Go. Got it. All right. From the fireplace, we've got on the left side, green, blue, red.
Stop turning around. On the right side, it is blue. Okay. Next, we've got blue and red. Blue on left
side. Close that fucking door. Red on this side. The final hallway is red on the left side. White
on the other side. Done. I got it. What is going on? So this should be white on the left,
red on the right. It is. The middle should be red on the left, blue on the right. It is.
Blue on the right. And the final ones should be blue on the left, green on the right. What's going
on? Yeah, I did it from the fireplace. Looking like from the fireplace. From the fireplace,
it's green, blue, red on the left, and blue, red, white on the right. I'm looking at it right now.
What about the fireplace? Check the fireplace. You have to turn the fireplace on. Do I? You need
to put fire in the fireplace. You did it right. You have to do something else. So, okay. Okay.
I keep mistaking this for the... Okay. You use my vault. Make sure you... Okay. Make sure you have a
dog. Right. Okay. Three keys. I did that. So now that's done. Throw all the books into the fireplace.
They're pretty useless anyways. So now, the raccoon? With this? Is everybody else as lost as I am?
Okay. As for the rooms, well, you'll just have to bust down the doors and remake the key.
Crack my cipher below. Can I just crack this code? I kind of want to hold this up too.
Because I have, like, the translator app. Like, take it or something. You know what I mean?
Yeah, what's this code? Cipher this code. I don't... I don't know what this is trying to tell me,
though. Like, very obviously this is that pyramid. And they're talking about this is where the raccoon
was placed. So the left side, most left side on the left was a raccoon image. It's telling me to
do whatever this is. And it wants me to spin it around. Go play the game of geese and fox.
Did I already do that, though? Do I actually have to play that with this guy? Hello again. I'd better
get going. Okey dokey. What's up? I'll catch you later. Can't do it. Hello again. I'll see you two
later, okay? See you later. Any combination will work. What's up? Oh my god. Nice talking to you.
I just wish there was a different button I could press to, like, leave instead of having to go to,
like, this magic five pixel area at the bottom of the screen. Yeah, what... what is this even
talking about? My vaults? There's, like, a whole underground world we haven't been to. It's a maze
underground, apparently. Do I have to go back to where that needle is and just go... just go there?
Those are the pyramid clues. Any combination will work, but I don't... it's a raccoon. But I don't
like spinning around with a weird fucking line in the middle. What does this even mean? If you wanted
me to spin it around, why would you draw a line in the middle? Is this a letter? What is this?
And then I thought this was a lobster until I realized it was the moose. So but where do you...
why is there... and there's, like, a slice of pizza here. Is this a pig? This is a pig. So this is a
pig's face here. What's this? What's the... hold on. Let me look at this pyramid again. There ain't
any geese! There's no goose! There's no ducks! Why am I secret hideout? Fox and geese, there is
a pig, moose, raccoon, and a wolf design on the fox and geese game table. Well, I would love these
assholes to get the fuck up from the table so I can look at the stupid thing. I can't look at it.
This needs to be lunchtime, but I can't sit here. Apologize to them. No! I'm not going to.
I'm just gonna go. I'm just going to bed. I'm just going up there. I'm gonna hit the button
fucking 10 times in a row. Wait, something on the bed. That's not... get out of my fucking way.
I have to walk up here and turn around. I want to look at the table! All right, I'm getting
tantrum-y here. Take the... someone's telling me how to do the code. Take the first line. Take...
okay, hold on. Take the first letter of the first line, then the first letter of the second line.
The second letter of the first line, then the second letter of the second line. What? The first
letter of the first line, and then that's first. So it's first things first. Dude, you have to
write this out. I have to actually write this down on a piece of paper. Hold on. First... oh,
somebody has it. First things first. Locate my secret hideout up in the mountains. It's so secret
you'll probably never find it. But if you do, find my Rex bone and use it in the wall of my
hideout. That'll open up a secret lock. You could have just said that in three words. Dan,
whatever your name is. My secret hideout up in the mountains. Find my Rex bone. That didn't help at
all. Find my Rex bone? Wasn't it telling me that this shit was made out of, like, Rex bones?
This thing right here. Yeah, so what the hell? Go back to where you met Isis.
I have to go back to fucking bed, first of all. Okay. I feel like this game has gotten very,
like, convoluted in the end. Go to my magical pyramid and press the button on the top and then
do a bunch of weird shit. And by the way, decipher my thesis code. If you can't do that, get a bone
and put... I'm trying to find... Where is this bone? You miss serving breakfast? I don't give a shit.
These people go order takeout for all I care. Why is he so mad? What happened? I'm not mad.
I'm frustrated. Okay. So now where is this thing? Under here? Maybe I can use Isis and her incredible
sense of smell to figure out who owns the notebook I found outside. I already know who's it is. All
I have to do is get something from each of the people at the lodge. Something that each of them
has touched. Then let Isis figure out which of their scents matches the scent on the notebook.
What? I don't even know what that means. Forward. Isis. Forward. Go. And smell this.
How do I get the dog to smell this? You do not have to hand it. Okay. You use a guide book.
This shit's empty. It's empty. I can't get it. We have a Vinny raid coming in right now. Vinny,
I'm having trouble. I'm having trouble. I need help from the Vinesauce community if you can help us.
Trying to figure out playing Nancy Drew right now and I'm stuck. Thanks for the raid. Welcome.
Having a little bit of trouble in the game. Somebody says there's a couple of key things
you need to find if you actually want to progress. What you need to look for is some
good old-fashioned values. It's a family guy routine that they're doing a family guy joke.
I read the rest of it. I'm not going to read the rest. Translate the rest of the words.
That looks like a Geiger counter. What? What a weird. This measures radioactivity.
I wonder if Isis found it outside somewhere or in here. Radioactivity. There's a number I could
call on this weird thing, right? Okay. I can call that. Um, leave. Right. Right. Isis. Right. Right.
Right. Right. Go. I don't really know what the game wants me to do.
Smells stuff. But how do you smell this? Bark. Bark. Isis. Bark. Go. Smell this. I don't. I need
to put the bone here, but I don't have the bone. Somebody stole the bone. I don't know who has the
bone in their possession. Did they ever expect children to do this stuff? How? Even with an
adult's help, I would, I would have been like, like son or daughter. Now close that game.
No, open up, open up fucking Nickelodeon. You know what I mean? Like, get off of this.
This is too much. Get off of this. Go watch Rugrats. You did choose senior difficulty,
to be fair. Yeah. Cause if I picked the other difficulty, everyone would have made fun of me.
Tell the dog to figure it out. I feel like this hole just, can I tell, can you leave?
Can you leave the hole? Like, this is very clearly saying, Hey, look, there's a space.
The dog can fit under here. There's no way that's not what this is. No way.
Very cute, but didn't do anything. Wait, someone's got a solution. Go back to Isis at the shack,
pass Avalanche Ridge, exit the lodge, go left. I'm at this point. I'm just going to listen to you.
I'm going to listen to you. Go left, left at the corner of the lodge, left again. So go left,
the left, left at the corner of the lodge. Wait, what's happening? Go right by the lodge and left
into the sus space. You're not helping. I already had the shack. Oh, that was the shack. Wait a
second. I need to, I'm going to uninstall this game. I swear to God, it made me drop. I just
dropped my chapstick on the ground and I'm pissed about it. Okay. I'm at the lodge. Go left. No,
I can't go left. Exit the, exit the lodge. I can't even turn around. Okay. Exit the lodge. Go left.
I'm going to follow this. I don't apply it every 30 minutes. I apply it every hour or 30 minutes.
Okay. Left, left at the corner of the lodge, left again at the next corner. No, the, no,
not the shack, the, the, okay. Not the shack, the lodge, the actual lodge where I came from.
Wait, didn't I already come back here? It's just, it's telling me to go back to where I just was.
Go back. Yeah. Why wouldn't it go back to ISIS at the shack pass ridge? Exit the lodge, go left.
Wait, what are you talking about? I just did that. I need to read this. Go left at the corner.
After the avalanche sign, you use the snowshoes. We already did this. Go forward until the shack.
Give the notebook with pictures to ISIS. Why? I was just, I didn't read the whole paragraph yet.
All right. My game is alt tabbed. Warm again. I don't want to say it.
Give her the notebook with the pictures. I didn't, I try that already. Did that already.
We did this. It just didn't do anything. It's one of those games where you have to do A, B, C, D, E,
F, G, even if you have G in your inventory. We just saw it with the stupid survey thing.
Here's the notebook. Smell that. It doesn't work. I can't even pick this up. I have to talk to
everyone in the main lodge. I don't even know what anything smells like. Like, what is this?
Hold on. This is funny. Okay. Somebody asked chat GPD. Great. In Nancy Drew, the white wolf
Icicle Creek, there's a puzzle that involves snow wolves and triangle puzzles. To solve this puzzle,
you need to first collect all the triangle pieces scattered throughout the game. Once you have all
the triangle pieces, go to the room with the wolf display and arrange the triangles to form a wolf
picture. This will reveal a hidden compartment that contains a snowshoe. Use the snowshoe to
traverse the snowy area. Well, that's not accurate. That didn't help at all. So we've got to go back
to the lodge and get things, ask people for stuff that the dog can smell. Why would I do that? Okay.
This is actually a Wind Waker quest. This is actually driving me crazy. It's going to get dark
soon and cold. I'm going in. Going in where? I feel warmer already. Let's get Luigi'd. Go to
the basement. Go to the workbench and get a red rug. Everybody's just telling me the solutions.
I mean, they're kind of, I mean, come on. Go to the workbench. I'll let you get back to work.
See you later. How can I help you? I hear that a major cross-country skiing competition may be held
in this area in a couple of years. This is very true. The towels in the rooms, the laundry.
I also hear that you can be pretty imaginative when it comes to gaining an edge on your competition.
I told you about the bomb. My competitors will stop at nothing to defeat me. I am forced to seek out
and exploit every possible advantage open to me. I take no pride in some of the things I've done
to bring victory to my country, but I have no choice. I would love to stop clicking out of the
window. I have disturbed you long enough. We'll talk again, I'm sure. Okay. I need to,
there's just a certain order to, this is a granny like. I'm conceding that. This is a granny like.
I didn't think it was, but it is. Everything has to be done in a specific fucking particular order
or it won't work. It's a granny like. And I'm being chased by my own embarrassment from the chat room.
That's what's chasing me around these rooms. Laughing at me, pointing at me. You're the granny
in this situation. It is a granny like. I would love to put the bullet down.
That's all the questions I had. Good. I would love to put this down, but I have a full,
full fucking inventory. Oh no, I don't. Relax. Relax. Everything's fine. There's no problem.
I just keep clicking out of this stupid thing. Please give me the one correct route to go up
the stairs. Oh my God. Okay. Okay. Cool. I made it out of the basement. Now what?
He's having a meltdown. It's getting there. Do I have the laundry bag in my gigantic inventory
of old notes that I didn't even know why I'm keeping any of these? What's the point of me
holding onto the shit in my inventory? Why do I have this? Throw it in the trash. Throw this away.
I don't need it. Throw it away. I don't need it. Get rid of it. Throw it in the trash. Where's the
trash can? Fucking laundry bag. He's losing it. I am. I should have picked, all right. If I haven't
played a Nancy Drew game ever again, I am picking the, the children, whatever the, the, as whatever
the, I'm picking like the junior detective mode. I ain't picking the senior detective mode that
back in like the mid 2000s that was telling you, Hey dude, this is going to be, this is going to
suck. Don't do that. This is like not even, this is higher than parents difficulty. This is bring
this to school and give it to your teacher difficulty. This is your teacher's going to look
at it and go, I don't fucking know what this is. Go sit down. Okay. So we're going to go to bed.
We're going to wake up at 1 AM. Apparently I got it out. I feel fine. I can't go in. If I unlock
the door and someone's inside. Yikes. It's why am I waking up at one o'clock in the morning?
Why is that happening? Can somebody help me here? Why am I waking up at one o'clock in the morning
every day? They don't need their rooms cleaned anymore. Okay. Take all the laundry. I think I'll
keep one of these washcloths. Okay. Good. Good. Excellent. Very nice. There we go. Okay. Now let's
keep going. Excellent. Very cool. Very good. Okay. I've got these. There's one more, right?
No, that's it. That's it. I've got the three that I need. You're not making the beds. I don't care.
They're going to fire me anyways. I don't care. This one's already done. All right. So I've got
these. Now I have to bring this to the dog. I believe these are the only three. Please get out
of the room. Nancy Drew killed Diablo. Now I missed one. What am I missing? There wasn't one in the
other room. No, I don't want to give. This is my room, right? It wasn't any in one of these rooms
though. I need the other. Oh, I need to go to the workbench, right? That's where you get the other
that dude's rag. You're losing viewers. That's fine. Sorry. It's okay. All right. So now this
I need to drop this laundry bag down the chute upstairs. No, I don't want to do that.
How do I put this? Put it away. I don't want to carry dirty laundry around all day.
I should get rid of this bag. I'm going to kick this door. What? What's going on? I should get
rid of this laundry bag before I forget. Hi. How do I get his? I need his. What you need.
I'll let you get back to work. By the way, you dumped the laundry bag before all the rooms were
cleaned. So I put it back up at the front desk. How do I get his? Go upstairs, enter and go to
the moose head, right? Click on the moose's eye, take the moose disk with the radio. This is worse
than a granny like go upstairs to Yanni's room, enter and go to the moose head, right of the door,
click on the moose's eye, take the moose disk, look at the radio, click on the radio. And there's a
foreign somebody's talking and then talk to Yanni in the basement about the radio. Jesus. What the
hell is this thing? It's a third room on a moose head. Oh, give me a fucking break. If something
tells me this radio belongs to Yanni and if so, why is he hiding it? Click on a moose's head to
get it a key item. Now go, Hey, what's the radio in your room? Okay. Now let's go talk to you about
the radio I found in the room. How can I help? Hi. Why do you have a radio hidden away in your room?
You've got the disk. How do you know about that? When I got done cleaning the moose head, that
compartment was open. When I looked in it, there was the radio. Now you answer my question. I use
that radio to communicate with my coaches. It's a special radio. It scrambles the signal so that my
competitors cannot listen in. How did you know there was a secret compartment in your room?
The first night I was here, I searched for bugs. Something which, due to the cunning of my
competitors, I've become very good at. I discovered that by pushing on the moose eye, a compartment
opened up. What I don't know is, did you really open that compartment by mistake or were you up
to something else? I'm a detective. I'm a detective. I'm a detective. I'm a detective. Shut up.
I'm no spy, Mr. Volksteyer. I'm just very observant. Who else have you told about the radio?
No one. I believe you, Nancy. So if I find out you're lying, both of us will be very sorry.
Okay. You're busy, so I'll let you go. Hold on, I'll be right back. I gotta get the crime disk
from out of whatever that was. I'll be back. Hold on, just be right back. I'm going to get the crime
disk out of your room. All right, now where is it? Did I get it? Okay, got it. All right, now show
him the crime disk. Okay. Make him take off the wetsuit. How can I help you? Do you have any proof
that your competitors are out there spying on you? When one has enemies, it's prudent to assume that
they are always close by. They are here, Nancy. Make no mistake. Okay, can you imagine? We have
a conversation here. I found this hidden radio up in your room. You did? Oh, well, that was nothing.
Why were you in my room looking through my things? Well, because I was, I'm a detective.
I'm trying to find like a killer and who's trying to kill people and shit. Oh, don't do that again.
Okay. Yeah, I won't. And then I turn around and I fucking sprint fucking stairs and they,
and he hears above him me running up the other fucking stairs. Are you chasing, am I getting
chased? You're busy, so I'll let you go. That's how fast I was going. Okay, so now I can take that
thing. What you need? I'll let you get back to work. If you need anything, just holler.
Everything's good. We're fine. Okay, so now where do I take that thing? This goes into,
it goes into a slot. Is it fire? Fireplace? Really? You need to look for the shotgun behind the front
desk. There'll be a buckshot under the rug. Shut. Come on, man. The fire necklace will tell you all
you need to open up. Sly raccoons hiding place. Just don't wake up in the, yeah, this is very
helpful. Don't wake, go back and take a look at the fire necklace at the display table. Take note
of the colors of the disks. Go back up to the guest rooms. Look close to the colored wedges above
the doorknobs. Yeah, you're a click. Look at the picture of the raccoon between. Yeah, I would never
would have clicked on this. I just wouldn't have. I never would have clicked the random painting on
the wall. I never would have done that. Okay, so where, how do I get the pig one? This is the pig.
How do I light the fireplace? Go talk to Lou. You know what's so funny about this? There are about
17,000 people here right now. I bet you at least 12 to 13,000 of you have the guide open on like,
you have like the game facts open and you're all just sitting there going, how are we going to just,
how do I make sure he reads this? I think two or three thousand of you just gave up and like are
making food right now and you can probably hear me from across the room. Maybe you put me on the TV
and you're like, you know what? I'm, he's not going to finish this in like the next 20 minutes. I'm
going to make like a steak and I'm probably talking to you right now. You may, hopefully the steak is
good. Hope you cook it well. Well, not well done, but well enough for you to enjoy it. And then I
think like a couple thousand of you just left and they were like, I'm going to bed. So for all of
the 12,000 of you that had the game facts open, I appreciate it. Now we need to talk to Lou. One
person has it open 12,000 or just copy and pasting the one person's answers and changing
one word to be sus. That's also true. You're right. A lot of you are not helping at all.
You're copy and pasting the real answer and then adding like, and then you poo poo all over and
then you pee pee. And then it's like, okay, well I've read that one. I didn't, but you know,
I did read it, but I didn't say that I read it until right now. Lou. Yeah. Well, good luck with
the game. In real moose, the moose, the moose, the moose, the moose. I can't already have the
moose eye. Why are you telling me to click on the moose? I already have it. How do I talk to Lou?
Hello again. I'll see you two later. Okay. I haven't served food in three days. What's up?
Nice talking to you. Ditto dude. I'm going to sneeze and I'm really sorry. Wait, I need to do
this. Come on. I wanted so badly to get that. If it's back, I'll do it. Damn it. I want to click
on this one. I can't even click on it. As long as it's not time to cook, I might as well stay out
of the kitchen. I can't click this one. Um, someone's talking about like element ring strategies.
Mm hmm. Things are not going well for stripper. German 95 has been having a little trouble in
Nancy Drew playthrough. I do not have the bone yet. I can't open it. I'm going to call this number
three, three, four, five, five, five, seven, six, two, five. What is this? My name is Nancy Drew.
I'm staying at the Icicle Creek Lodge and I recently came across some kind of device that
had your phone number on it. Well, it has a spike on one end of it. And well, actually this,
I mean, someone's dog was using it as a chew toy. She must have found it outside somewhere.
You know what it is? What's a geophone? They said it sounds like a frog detective voice.
OK, so I got to go take the radiation device. When you say seismic waves, are you talking about
earthquakes? So to put the geophones to use, you need to blow things up. So if someone were
looking for valuable mineral deposits, they might use geophones to do it. Types of mineral deposits
are likely to be found around the Icicle Creek drainage. Good word. What do you know about
dinosaur bones? What do you know about dinosaur bones? That's not the one I wanted to click on.
Are dinosaur bones good for anything? Delete that part of the stream. Just rewind that and delete
it. I came across a Geiger counter. What can you tell me about them? How am I able to bring that
up? Do you know what range of radiation is unsafe? All right. In other words, if I'm doing a high
reading on my Geiger counter, it doesn't necessarily mean I'm an imminent danger.
All right. 990. 990 frequency. All right. So that's cool and all. So can I turn the radio station?
Or this is 990. It's the radio. You sound sad. Yeah. I just wanted to. You don't. I can't. OK,
turn it to nine. I don't know what this is. There's too many moving parts in this game.
I have. Should I bring this stuff to get sniffed? Look at all this shit in my inventory.
How do I get this open? I can't get it open. I need to talk to Lou. Every time I talk to Lou,
he's sitting at that game and he just goes, talk to you later. A to B, B to C, C to D, D to E,
E to G, G to X, and then Y and Z. And you go 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. And if you go from 1 to 4,
what's going on? Somebody's like radiated here. Turn around. What's up? Nice talking to you.
Ditto, dude. I can't talk to Lou. Lou doesn't do anything. The bear? What about the ram head?
How do I get it? I need a ladder. I need a ladder. The door colors are wrong. Go check them.
No, they're not. I wouldn't. I wouldn't really get the raccoon one if that was the case.
Why is there a radiation mechanic in a Nancy Drew game? Oh, this game is fucked. I need to
turn the fire on. So I need to somehow get whatever. This is the pig head. I got to get
the fire to turn on, but I also have to get the ram one too. So I need a stepladder or something.
Have I not beaten this game yet? I don't know, because the game is fucking goofy. So this is a
goofy game. This is a wacky game. I could maybe go back and have the dog smell this. That's the
only thing I can think of right now. Understand anything else. What the hell am I supposed to do?
Just do that. Why do you pick the hilarious difficulty? I didn't mean to. It was only it
was this or easy. See what the dog says about this stuff, which I view left of the stream in
the last 20 minutes. He came back to check on us. The dog talks. That's a kind of bizarre,
by the way. So you missed that, which is very weird when it started talking.
I mean, I don't I don't think it should be like an Elmo voice. It was off putting and weird when
it was like Elmo was like high pitched kind of Elmo voice. I'm surprised I actually decided to
give it that kind of a voice. All right. What do you think about this? I shouldn't give Isis that.
I should give her the notebook. You gotta be fucking kidding me. Looks like it's not Yanni's
negative for Bill Kessler. The sense match, which we got those notes belong to Lou Talbot.
Good dog. Hey, Lou got a bone to pick with you, Lou.
Everybody laugh. We just sneaking with our jokes like that. I was going to walk in with the notebook
in my hand, holding it straight up. He's like a cigarette too. You know what I mean?
Just walk right in the front door. What's it say in the first passage here? Oh,
two vertebrae employed as furniture, but your fried wings for muscle attachment.
It's quite the notebook. Just be talking loudly about it.
Now where would I be able to find the owner of this notebook? I wonder warm again. Now what?
What is this? Lou Talbot charged with trespassing, vandalism and theft. I have a plan property,
creating a piece of earth a texture inspired by maverick artist Poppy Dada of keeping the
dinosaur bones dug up on the process. Dinosaur bones. Hey Lou, can I get your hand with
something in the kitchen? Oh, he's gone. Not time for kitchen duty yet. I feel like it hasn't been
for days. Let me in here. That just hurt my fucking head. I did too many and it hurt.
Why is that so loud? Okay, so now I call somebody. I mean, I know that I need to talk to Lou,
but Lou is not here. Do I just have to go to sleep? Can I get that ladder? Thanks for taking the time
to talk to me. Come back anytime. What you need. I'll let you get back to work. Keep me posted.
When you make the scavenger hunt too hard, the kids can't do it and you just have to keep telling
them where things are hidden. I should put on a coat before I go outside. I don't know where the
egg is. Well, did you go up and press the face of the ox up in the bedroom? No. Well, after that,
did you take the Geiger counter out of the wall and then find the radiated banana that I put
under the sink? No. Well, I mean, and then after doing that, did you look down the third drain of
the fourth toilet in the house? I just want to collect eggs. I don't want to do this. Well,
you must be a dumb kid then. Let me show you where everything is. And I don't even fucking know.
All right. It's the banana. I like open up the banana, peel the banana and then there's a code
written on the peel. No, it's not. The code's not on this banana peel. No, I must have written that
underneath the desk. I don't, it's not there either. I don't know where your eggs are. They're gone,
kid. They're fucking out of here. They're gone. I ate all the eggs. I ate all the chocolate in them.
That's what happened to them. Okay. I need to talk to Lou. I feel warmer already. I'm just going
to fucking bed. Mr. Green, are you all right? No, I can't get out of here. I'm fine. Stupid Easter
eggs hunt anyways. When I was younger, we did money hunts. My father put six grand in a brief
case we hid it and me and all my siblings had to beat the shit out of each other and find it.
He hid it in one place. He gave us all different clues that were wrong. We had to come together
and put our pieces of our clues together, but it never worked out that way. We just beat the shit
out of each other. I don't talk to any of my siblings anymore either. There he is. What's up?
Can I have the Rex bone that you took from the plaque? Do you think I could have the Rex
bone that you took from that plaque by the display case? Dude, what makes you think I took some bone
from some plaque? Don't get smart with me. Because you referred to it in your notebook.
He's losing it. I'm fine. Someone who has a really good nose for such things is positive that it's
yours. All right, here's the deal. There's a lot of people out there who collect stuff like fossils
and dinosaur bones, okay? They pay big bucks for them. And it just so happens paleontology is kind
of my thing. This guy's drip is atrocious. I disagree because this reminds me of Scott Cyclops's
drip, which is the blue with the yellow thing that goes across. That's Scott Cyclops's drip.
I like this. Don't call this bad drip. It's the same outfit.
You want the bone from that plaque? Go ahead and take it.
Okay, dude. Excitement's over. Who's move? Okay, dude.
That's awesome. Okay, dude. All these bones. Lou's been a busy guy. Okay, dude. Here's the one I'm
looking for. Give me that. The Rex bone that's missing from that plaque. It is. Now let's go do
it and solve the mystery. Did I call anybody? Crumpled paper under the desk? I think we already
called that number. I lost my phone. Can you call it for me? Yeah, yeah. Give me a second.
It's ringing. It's in the room somewhere. I can hear it somewhere in the house. Can you hear it?
Check under the sofa. Like just look under the bed. Yeah, somewhere in here. I don't know where
your fucking phone is. You're sitting on it. I'm not sitting on it. I already looked. I still don't
have the other coins though. If you don't need it. I'm not sitting on it. Do you want me to call it
again to see if I'll prove I'm not sitting on it? I'm calling you right now. I'm calling it again.
My service. Hold on a second. My phone's fucked up. All right. It's ringing. I don't know where
it is. It's not underneath me. Oh shit. It's underneath me. I just set up. What do I do?
What do you want to do with this? I was sitting on it. Fuck. All right. I gotta. That's weird.
I was kind of muffled before I picked it up from under my ass. But I don't know. I don't know what
that was. But, um, that's pretty. I guess we just did that. This one. Oh, that just happened.
Fucking door. There it is. So I can rearrange these by continuing to drop the tile that falls
out the bottom into one of the columns at the top. What? The question is, how should I rearrange
them, match the symbols and line them up in rows of three? Maybe. Oh no. It's the shit again.
It wants me to do all this weird shit. Can I change the difficulty right now? I gotta put
all the coins in. Don't I? No. Wait. What is it? Okay. Wait. No. No. Having a tantrum. Um,
so there's an extra one here. The question is, how do I, I gotta get rid of the extra one.
Putting it in. Like it's just stupid ass puzzle. I just don't know the order. It's just, I just
don't know what order I need to do this in. I'm just so over this. I'm just over it. I would
smash this thing with a fucking hammer until I got it. Well, how many are in this row? The order is
beside it. I know it's fish owl bunny, but this one stupid ass duck is ruining everything for me.
Only the answers were in a book. Yeah. I can't, I have to like leave this to open up the book.
It wants me to do this first and that's all fine and dandy, but how do I get rid of this stupid
duck? I need to get the fish to be like the next thing coming down like here. How do I get it out
of order? Like on the bottom row is if I'm going to, I have to start moving shit around. I'm going
to get all this. It's going to get all messed up because it takes so many coins out. Whatever.
I'm just going to fuck the whole thing up. I just don't, I don't know how to get to the solution I
want to get to. Is that it? No, it's not. God damn it. Range two columns at a time. Uh, I'm just,
I've been playing this dumb ass fucking children's game for five hours. Where am I going with this
one left? I didn't, I didn't even know you could fucking do that. Are you kidding me? But that
doesn't help. Crazy how not hard this is. Well, it's not hard when you know exactly how to do it.
I don't know how to do it. So it's not easy for me. It's hard for me because I don't know what I
have to do. I mean, I get it, but I'm running into a wall in my brain. That's why puzzles exist.
All these symbols and shapes and placement. Like I could sprint a hundred miles per hour in five
seconds. You give me a ball. I could hit that fucking ball hard. I can do anything else with
this. I need to reset it. The game won't even let me leave. It's like, no, dude, you're here.
You're, you're stuck here. Yeah. I know what it's supposed to look like. It's supposed to be fish,
owl, bunny. I'm about to just let you guys do it while I watch fucking SpongeBob on another
yellow monitor. Let me see if I can get it. Let me try it one more time. So bunny, bunny,
fish fit. It's just like, it's like knocking shit down. I can rearrange these by continuing to drop
the tile that falls out the bottom. I hate looking at this. Columns at the top. Then everybody get
that way. We look at just a shitload of symbols and you just can't anymore. They all just meld
together into one picture. Like this is all melding into one image. They're all, it's all the same
picture. It's all literally the same photo. I can't move them around. They're stuck here.
Maybe Dave can help. I almost feel like I want two coins at the same time, but I can't, I can't get
that. He's going to end the stream. I'm not going to end the stream. It's like a slight. Yeah. It's
all the slider puzzle dog shit. All right. Slider puzzles are problems too. I wasn't going to get
angry today. Slider puzzle. Oh God. No, I can't do a slider puzzle. Oh no. You know, when we were
younger, we didn't do slider puzzles. We went down the slip and slide off on rocks. Yeah. None of
this smooth fucking grass bullshit. Let me look at this again. Reset the whole thing. So I can
rearrange these by continuing to drop the tile that falls out the bottom into one of the columns
at the top. I know how it works Nancy. How should I rearrange them? Match the symbols and line them
up in rows of three maybe? Nancy. Hold on. I'm going to click that out of the window. You want
the bunny on top. Yeah. I, you need the bunny on top. Always keep the animal tokens next to each
other. That's the theory. Oh, I've got wicked bad diarrhea right now. I'm just, oh, I'm sorry.
Stomach is like fucking like a wicked bad diarrhea right now. I think it passed. I think I'm all
right. Yeah. I think I'm good. Get a good look at this. All right. The duck definitely has to go.
If it were me doing this, I would probably put the duck second row or the first row. I think
now that can go to the right side because you want to make sure that that's in the middle now
and then that goes on the left side for me. I would put this in the middle and this is going
to go up here and then on the left again, I think, and then probably back up. But I would
say probably on the left side and the left again and then maybe on the right. No, I would say
probably the middle. I think that's correct. Maybe the right left side and the right side
and the left side again. The walkthrough is different now. How, how, how, how would you
fucking do this shit? Look at all this and look at this mess. This is a fucking mess. I'm cheating.
I don't care. I'm literally cheating right now. I hate these. All these games that have just slider
puzzle after slider puzzle. I would, I would know just give me anything else besides this.
I can't even follow the guide. It's happening so fast. I'd rather eat my own hand than do a
slider puzzle. Okay. This goes here. So I can rearrange these by continuing to drop the
this is like the worst. This is my least favorite way to play a video game is these kinds of
puzzles. How should I rearrange the game? Just crashed. Stop fucking with me. Match the symbols
and line them. And I lost my place in the video slider puzzles. Okay. Goose goes first and that
goes on the right side that mine is different than the walkthrough. What, what's going on?
Is it our, is it random? The walkthrough is going too fast. This is not, I put, why did I put this
on a hard? What was I doing? It's Nancy Drew. Do I really care? The tile that falls out the bottom
into one of the columns at the top. Question is how should I match the symbols and line them up
in rows of three? Maybe if I was in bed with my iPad, I wouldn't care. I would be doing this,
but I'm, we're not in bed. I'm not, we're not in bed. We're not there. That no baited me.
It actually baited me. This is not supposed to go here. They put the, they hovered over here.
And it was like, Oh, no. And then they moved. What the fuck? Christ, man. So I can rearrange
these. I know how it works. Stop talking. That falls out the bottom into one of the columns at
the top. The question is how should I rearrange them? Match the symbols and line them up in rows
of three, maybe. I'm going to laugh if this walkthrough takes a wicked long time to do this.
That was the one that, okay, that was, don't, I got to, okay, right here, installing. I don't think
they know where to go. Yeah, they do. How long does this take to do this? I hope I'm doing this
right. Cause this is long, man. This is a long time. I'm going to imagine if I did this and it was
just like a fuck you germa at the end and this doesn't, was supposed to doing anything. I feel
like that could happen. Come on, man. Come on. It has to be getting close. It has to be right.
I'm going to miss a step. Just pay attention. Why does my back hurt? This is not ending. How
much longer? When do I get to leave this? Okay. I think it's close. I'm just following what it's
doing. I'm just following the walkthrough. I'm following the walkthrough. I promise. I got it.
Bingo. All right. Bingo. Scary. A little creepy. Looks like the map to some kind of maze. Christ.
Where am I right now? I'm taking a picture of this. No, nobody, no human does this without a
fucking photo. Um, where am I right now? Here or here? Do I know where I am? Follow me. I wonder
if she expects me to do something. Um, I want you to go. I want you to go. I don't know what,
I don't know even what direction I'm even facing. What direction are we looking? Around ISIS, around.
This map is meaningless unless I know what direction I'm looking. What? All right. Even
the dog doesn't want to do this. The dog doesn't want to do this either. All right. So let's just
let forward around. Around. Forward. Forward. Forward. Forward. Let's just see what happens.
ISIS. Around. Forward. Forward. Forward. Forward. Forward. Go. I just want to know what I'm even
looking at. Forward. Forward. Forward. Looks like some kind of gate is in her way. Um, forward.
Forward. Hold on. Forward. Forward four times and then right? Right? Forward. Right. I don't,
how many commands can I even queue up? ISIS. Forward. Forward. Forward. Forward. Right. Right.
Go. Your dog is a rudimentary computer, bro. Looks like some kind of gate is in her way.
I did forward four times. One, two, three, four. There are four dots. What are you talking about?
Forward. Forward. Forward. Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. I'm going to stop. ISIS. Forward.
Forward. Forward. Right. Right. Right. Go. You start on the first one. Forward. Forward. Right.
This dog is not doing the correct thing. Is it, will it go until it hits a wall? Forward one.
Forward. Then right? Right. Left. Left. Forward. Right. Left. Right. Forward. Right.
Okay, well there is, I can't go past the gates. I have to get to the jump over the gate. Okay,
what if, okay, forward jump? Forward. Jump. Jump. Let's just see what that does. ISIS. Forward.
Jump. Go. You start at the first dot. Yeah, well then why, why did, why did the dog go five dots?
I said three forwards, not five. I said forward once here. Okay, you just go until you hit something.
I, can somebody please explain to me what on earth is going on right now? Is it four circles is one
forward? So would it be forward, forward, jump? Forward. Jump. ISIS. Forward. Forward. Jump. Go.
Every intersection is a command. Will I end up in the, whatever this is in the middle here?
Looks like some kind of gate is in her way. Forward. Right. Forward. Right. Does that actually
work though? I feel like this is not working. Forward. Right. Go. Forward. Right. Okay, forward.
Right. Forward. Jump over the hole and then pop. Forward. Right. Left. Right. Jump. What about under
the gate? Down. Each command is an obstacle. Forward. Right. Left. Right. Jump. Forward. Left.
Right. Left. Jump. ISIS. Forward. Left. Right. Left. Jump. Go. Why'd you just do left? Somebody said it.
Right. Left. Not. Right. Chat is moving so fast. I'm sorry I got the one guy that gave me the
fucking bogus directions. Looks like some kind of gate is in her way. I can't even take it anymore.
Forward. Right. Left. Right. Jump. Go. Forward. Forward. Right. Left. Right. Jump. Go. ISIS. Forward.
Right. Left. Right. Jump. Go. We're losing respect for you? I don't think you are. I think everyone
can look at this and go, this is kind of fucking cheesy. This is cheesy. This is like a stinky
cheese. My respect for you went up actually. Yeah, thanks. Now what? What did we just do to the dog?
We beamed him up into outer space. Now what? Okay, that was just Liam Neeson jumping over a fence
with 12 cuts. I could have just walked up that easily, right? Like we didn't have... Now where
am I going? A moose, a wolf, a raccoon, and a pig. The same animals Trapper Dan mentioned in his
journal when it came to getting into his needle without the key. I'll bet that's what's behind
this wall. A room below the needle. Next thing I have to do is get each of these panels open.
Bro, what is this game? I have to get all the panels open? Where's the dog? Oh, I have two
coins. Okay, what about right? Oh, hi. Good job, I think. And then no nine-year-olds beating this
game. Nine-year-olds gonna cry. They're gonna get to a point they're gonna be crying because it's
just... A nine-year-old will cry. No way. Should have picked the child. Should have picked the
children. Fucking difficulty. Okay, I need to obviously flip up all these switches and have
all four of the infinity stones. I need to get all of the stones and then come back here again
and then do all this bullshit again. I mean, that's what I have to do. That's what I have to do.
I have to... I can't do this. This is a punishment. It kind of is. Okay, this four switches in the
tunnel. But I'm gonna need the four horsemen of the apocalypse. I need the other two coins. Oh,
it's too late to walk back to the lodge now. I'd better spend the night here. When you make the
dog pull the rope, you're on a timer. You have to run back to the lodge and get the pig token and
the pig head. Is that accurate? Because if it is, I cannot understand how that would be a thing.
That's not accurate. Oh, that can't be right. The timer is reset now. Do I actually have to do this
again? A whole day went by. I slept in the shack. The timer reset? Did the timer actually reset?
No way. Do you have to beat the guy at that coyote game three times now? No, I don't.
You're making it up. Nancy, what is going on? Nancy, what is going on with this one?
Why is there a sleep mechanic in the game? You know what I mean? Like, why is there like,
go go to bed and reset stuff? No, why is it? Why do I have to do people's laundry? What's going on
in this game? I'm not even here. I'm about to watch the rest of this on YouTube. And by this,
I mean, they just like what happens at the end. Chantal's on the phone, Nancy. Oh my god. I don't
stop being a negative Nancy. I can't believe I actually have to go back. Chantal's counting
on me to get those rooms cleaned. I should go do that. Is there a why is there a clean the rooms
mechanic? Why? Nobody wants to do what I'm doing right now. I don't want to. I want to solve the
fucking murder mystery. Why is there a go up and clean the room mechanic? What is this for? I don't
care. Fuck off. I don't care. I'll close it. I'm not going to even go over there. My jacket. I'm
getting a definite feeling I'm not wanted here. My jacket. Okay. I know who did it. We already
we've done this for like an hour and a half. Is there a room done or what? I think I'm good. I
need not just leave. I don't get call me again. Why is she not wearing the jacket? Yeah. I do. I
actually have to have the dog pull that and run back here. I really hope that's not bait. I can't
go anywhere. I still haven't cleaned all those rooms. Oh my god. I do. I have to actually do
the laundry too. This late in the game. You're going to maybe do the fucking laundry. I'm pissed
right now. We're like moments away from solving the mystery. Make sure you go clean the rooms
and shit. Let me finish the game. I don't want to cook lunch and go clean. Why? What earth do I
have to do this? I'm livid right now. I click too fast and the game operates on six screens in this
hallway. I don't even know if I'm getting it all. I'm just trying to rush because this is a crap.
This is a crap part of the game and we all know it. Why am I reviewing this old Nancy Drew game
from 2007 like it came out last night? I don't know and I don't care. Much better. I'm really
cold. I can't. Get me the fuck out of here. The pig head thing is not bait. My wife plays these
games and is very upset. Also the wolf token is in the basement. I really actually have to do that?
Wait. You should back down here. What's happening right now? Okay. Okay. I was going to say I'm not
going to do that again, right? Okay. We need to have him do all the levers so let's just get it
over with. So with that being said, we need to do all the levers. We need to get it over with.
Apologize to his wife. Why? Because I said this game sucks? I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
I'm kidding. Relax. It's a joke. I could never say that about the Drew crew and Nancy Drew. Come on.
I've just eaten at least three pieces of this chapstick in frustration over the last hour and
25 minutes. I would never say something like that about the Drew crew. Speaking of the Drew crew,
they could give me a quick hand here. Just give me the exact combination to do all this.
Speaking directly to the Drew crew right now. Just give me the exact combination.
We all know I don't want to do this. We know you don't want to do it either, but one of us has to.
And we all know it ain't going to be me. I'm busy looking directly into the center of the screen and
not moving my arms. Everybody else do it. Show us the map. I can't alt tab this game either. That's
the problem. Wait. Here's the combination. Oh shit. Somebody actually has it. I can't even bark.
It's so easy. This really isn't. It's easy if you like, I've checked out. I clocked out like 30, 40
minutes ago. I'm not kidding. Like it would be easy if I like looked at this map and was like,
oh, like one, two, three, five, two, four, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12. I checked out.
I checked out like 30 minutes ago. They took bark off this too, which I wouldn't you check out as
well. I fucked up my shower. You should have called somebody. Okay. Forward. Forward. Left.
Paw. Forward. Left. Left. Paw. Isis. Forward. Left. Left. Paw. Go. Looks like some kind of gate
is in her way. That's not right. Forward. Right. Left. Right. Jump. And then I have to run out.
Do I have to, I probably, do I have to do something else to get those bars to move?
Or was it forward. Right. Left. Right. Left. Right. What was it? Forward. Right. Left. Right.
Jump. Isis. And then I have to run out of here. Right. Left. Right. Jump. Go. You've opened the
red gates. You need to win the Fox game on those three sides. This game was not for kids. It
wasn't. There's no way it was. I played it as a kid. Yeah. And we all know you gave up after the
first explosion. You were like, whoa. All right. I'm doing something else. Pull it. Now run. Go,
go, go, go, go, go, go. Go, go, go, go, go. Hurry, hurry. Mom's never going to let him play Diablo.
I think I'm conceding that I'm not going to be playing Diablo tonight because this is the whole
stream. It was fun though. I had fun. I hope you guys had fun. It's been a great time.
As frustrated as I've been at some of this. No, the slide puzzles. No, the slide puzzles get you.
They really do. No, I'm having fun. Everyone at the beginning of 2020, I can handle anything.
2020, nevermind. Is it just me or has 2020 felt like one long game of Fox and Geese?
That's from the official Nancy Drew account. What? That's the official Nancy Drew account said that.
They made their game harder than Dark Souls and Dark Souls wouldn't even out yet. So
they were the original Dark Souls. Much better. I was really cold. Okay. Oh no, go, go, go. Don't
talk to, don't stop and talk to Chad for a second. Oh, I need to play. Well, sorry to bother you.
Don't we play this? Now go into the basement. Okay. What's, what's going on in the basement?
It's gone in case you didn't know. Just up and left. Oh, Chantal's not going to like that.
The good news is you don't have to do the cooking anymore. I can handle it from here on out.
Thank God. I'll let you get back to work. By the way, you dumped the laundry bag before all the
rooms were cleaned. So I put it back up at the front desk. Oh no. Let's see. Do I really want
to go outside without a coat? I don't think so. I can't go outside. Not without a coat. It's too cold.
Let's see. Do I really want to go outside without a coat? What do I do about that? What's radioactive
right here? I need a coat. Didn't I, I didn't, I didn't click on it. I had, do I actually have to
get my coat on? I did. I clicked on it. It was a note on it, but I didn't pick it back up. I thought
I did. Where's my coat? This isn't even my room. This is my room. Where's my coat? There's, there's
a reading here. Yeah. It's this, it's this thing right here. 13. See the reading at the bottom left.
Go down to the main floor. Go right and go left side of the kitchen door. There's a high reading
by the dinosaur bow and stool decor. Go down to the basement. Go forward after they get another
high reading. After the stairs and the cellar door, face the stairs and get the highest reading.
Wasn't I just, I was just, I was just standing there. Do I have to get a reading from everything
that needs to be read before I can do that? Click the bottom stair. What in the, do I have them all
now? I didn't know. One, two, three, four. I got them all. All right. We're almost there. We're
almost there. I have to beat this guy three times. This is going to be a nightmare. I'm just going to
click in random places until I get it. I'll put up like a family guy clip compilation or something
in the corner if I can't do it. Please just leave me alone. I'm just, I'm trying to literally walk
up the stairs, but I have to walk in a full circle to go up the stairs. No, I have to go to, I have
a sleep cycle. Go to bed and wake up and play the guy. It's too early. Go back to bed. Get, get,
get, I wish I could just click on the room. Where is this guy? Where is this? Why would he never be
here? Why would there be a code, a line of code where he wouldn't be sitting here? It's 3 PM.
Go back to the mines. Back to the mines. I have all the tokens, but all I, I can't,
I need to open the gates, the red gates. If I don't have the red gates open, I can't do anything.
So how do I get the red gates to open? Play this guy three times, but he's not even here.
Do I have to go to bed until he comes back? You don't have to. Oh my God. You don't have to.
All right. Well then I'm, all right, I'm going. Got all the coins. So you have to play the game.
Well, they didn't code him in to be there. He's not there. Something tells me I shouldn't be
making this much noise. Not when I'm walking in a place called Avalanche Ridge. Where are my shoes?
You should play something else. I feel like we're in way too deep and we were in way too
deep after I said I would play this today. I haven't completed a Nancy Drew game in two or
three years. The lanterns in here are basically just rocks hung in cages. I wonder what makes
the rocks glow like that. I don't know, but I wouldn't be breathing in that deeply because
it's like, apparently like it's radiation. Next thing I have to do is get each of these panels
open. Glad I just came all the way to do that. You actually have to beat him three more times.
Why is he not just sitting there? If that, if that is like a core
thing you have to do to beat the game, why would he, how would anybody, he needs to be sitting there
at the table ready to play. Not, not there and not sleeping. He needs to be sitting at the table.
Dude, you got to get out of there. The uranium is getting to your brain. All right. Let's go back
and play. I can't believe I have to play this game three more times. Yeah. I've got the pig token.
Set your alarm clock to earlier in the day to bury these games in a fucking landfill. Like they
did ET warm again. How about another game of Fox and Geese? How about another game of Fox and Geese?
Now you're talking. Have a seat. Ready? You don't mind if we at least little pig I found. Do you
mind if we use this little pig I found in place of the Fox piece? Fine by me. And now what? Now
what do I have to do? I have to corner. Well, I have to have to in different directions.
Heard the pig by surrounding with a geese squares. Good luck. But is this just the same game or is it
different somehow? Do I have to corner him in this corner over here? You've got to be shitting me.
You're going to be shitting me. There's no way there's, I actually, you have to do this.
All right. I'm going to move them over to the raccoon and I guess this won't be that bad. It's
going to be bad to do the pig though. Put him in the pig corner. Dude, this sucks. Okay. Oh my God.
You know what? You know what? I'm about to pull a plug on this. This is, this sucks. Okay. Have we
start over? I have an ad. Hold on. Give me 10 minutes. This looks so, so fucking annoying.
Okay. This sucks. I'm going to have to take this physically forever.
No, family guy has brought to you in part by that commercial you just saw.
Why did they pad Nancy Drew to be like a nine to 10 hour game? Like they got to the end here
and instead of just ending the game, they put like a two hour padding on it. Why? Why is there,
why do I have to, why is there at least a 45 minute to an hour padding on the final part of the game?
I don't remember the other Nancy Drew games doing this. You know what? I'm not,
I don't care about a guide. We're doing it my way. Now get up there. I was right there. Get me. Shit.
Is the mic off? No, I'm just really trying to focus because I don't want to lose this because
I almost got them up there. Here. Nobody knows what you're doing. I'm, yeah, they do. I'm trying to
trap the pig up here. I'm kind of, I'm this one maybe just to get it in here. No, no, no. Back,
move it back. Got him. I got him. I got him. I got him. All right. He ain't going anywhere. I got him.
So then this is go in the middle. It can't get me from anywhere in the middle. I will be able to go
up when he does. Now I'm not getting cocky because he's probably going to go, he's probably going to
go down and then I'm going to move the one that's left up. All right. That's, that's still good for
us. We can trap him here. That's even, that's better for us. We're good. I fucked it up. I fucked it
up. I ruined everything. I ruined it. Didn't I? Fucked it up. I fucked it up. I'm good. No, I'm good.
I got him. I win.
But this time I want to use a different one.
I want to replace my, wait, do I want to, was it, do I have to use a different coin?
Why can I not use a different coin? It's just the pig pile you use.
Oh, I thought it was like pig went up there, raccoon coin. Okay. So it doesn't matter. All right.
Well, let's just even get them over here. Are we quiet? Did I do that before? What? Oh, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Stay over there. Stay over there. You're, we're good. Stay over there. I just won.
I just beat him. I just beat him. Hold on. He's over here. Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
God damn it. He can get out. I can't block him. You went in three moves. I don't know what those
moves are. I know I can, but give me a hand here. I don't want to fuck around. And one in the middle
is what I want to do. Okay. So where do I go? Middle one, middle down left, right? Middle diagonal left.
All right. So, this thing's dead. I can't move anything here. This is, he's going to get out,
move it back. Nah, he's going to get out. I guess I'm going to try to do what I was doing before and
just get him over here. Okay. Now get out of here. There we go. Okay. I'm in such a bad position,
though, to try to get him to, I'm just going to start moving shit. Like I have to. Okay. Move
forward this one. Good. Don't go that way. Do not go that way, please. Thank you. That's fine. This
dude can't be fucking safe. Yes. Dude, I, all right. For those of you that don't know, I have to get
him in each one of these stupid ass slots. They tweeted about this. This was a meme to their
development team. They even said, wow, it's like, well, really it wasn't fucking, wow,
it was something, wasn't it? They are, they did that. The game devs already told you that this was
a long ass, stupid ass part of the game. Okay. I'm just participating. I don't know. Hold on.
He needs to go back up. Actually kind of good, I think. I can't go that way. Get up here. Build
the edges. Yeah, but he only moves into, he won't go up there. See? Like get the, stop going. He
goes back and forth, back and forth, back and forth. Just go up here and try to kill something.
Because if I put this down here, he's going to go up here and then he's going to go bunk, bunk, bunk.
Don't do it. He's going to go down here and he's going to jump me. If I go right here, he's going
to go back to that one and he's going to jump over my ass. He's definitely not going to go into the
corner. I mean, this is, I could just see what he does. He's going to move backwards. I got to get
this, I got to get a piece down in the corner. Why is he doing that? Wait, no, no, he can't go
that way. He can't go diagonal. Can he? Wait, I think he can. That's freaking me out. No, he
definitely can't. Okay. Okay. This is in the right spot. Go back up there. All right. Now let me see
what happens if I do this. Okay. He'll only go there and there. If I move this down here, he's
going to move probably down, right? He's going to jump that. This has to come down. Damn it.
Because if I block this and he jumps, he does a double jump. I don't, I don't know how I'm going
to get him to stay over here. Cause it seems like he has an escape every time. Sacrifice a middle
piece to make him jump into the corner. That's not a bad idea. Put this here and just make him
jump over here. I guess I could do that. I hope it's not going to be a problem, but I guess we're
going for it. Okay. Now, now he's trapped in here. There's now nowhere for him to go. He could go
this way if he wants to, which, okay. So hold on. If he moves to the left, he's going to jump this
or down. I need to block this. He's, I mean, he's going to go up, stop and look. I know,
but these games are so just, it's just brain mush. The experience, the bottom piece, like this one,
he's, he's going to jump up. They just, somebody had a bet in their game studio. Like,
can we make a Nancy Drew game, a 20 hour game? No, impossible. I'll just make them do this five
times. Oh, done. We did it. He can jump this. I have to block this or he's gone.
Okay. Now he can't move diagonal. So if he goes down, he could jump to the left,
but that's fine. Cause I can move this here and I think we got them. Not quite. I don't know what
to do. Ah, you beat me. Another win. Another set of red eyes. All right. No, one more, one more.
I took it to this one more time and we went, okay. If we start over, get in there. Why are you doing
that? Get in there. What the fuck did you just do? What did you just do to me? What did you just do?
Get over there. What's happening? Okay. If we start over, my fucking God,
this is the stupidest fucking thing ever. Kidding me, man. Like, it's just like, I, who won?
Nobody wants to do this puzzle. I, I guarantee you, all of you that have ever played this,
probably saw this happen and you went, Oh, fuck. No. Who wanted to do this? I don't even know
anybody that would even make this. That would say, you know what? I want to do this five times.
Who would ever want to do this five times in a row? Unless you download the Fox and the fucking goose
game. That's like what I'm trying to do. That's what I'm doing. Like who wants to play this?
Besides people that actively are looking to play the Fox and the goose game. It was so close too,
but it's just, God, hurry off. Wait, you can't go that way. You, where was this one? Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's one o'clock in the morning. What happened? Oh my God. It's 1 a.m.
I must got you, you motherfucker. Go that way. You're in trouble. I must got you, you motherfucker.
That's the correct play here. What do I do? Top one. Can you screw me if I move this here?
As long as I move this and then the one right next to the right. If I go this one here and then this
one here, he can't do anything, right? No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm seeing a lot of nos. He'll take
the piece above it. Will he though? He doesn't have anywhere to go. I think that's correct.
Yeah, it is correct because now that's fine. I can sacrifice that one. Now he's in a bad spot.
Oh my God. I couldn't hold that one. You can't. Wait, wait, wait. He can't go this way. He can't.
He has to go left. Fill out the corners. Wait, wait. I know. I just have been doing this for
so long and my brain is having problems. I think it's fine. This moves here, right? Or do I just
try to block him now? If I move this here, he has to go left. Block the middle one and then take the
top one, top left. This one goes top left now. He can't go anywhere. He really can't do much of
anything. I win soon. Give me my token now. Another set of red eyes. Give me my token right now.
That's it. I win. This game over. I thought the building was on fire. Let's go. Let's go. All
right. Let's get out of here. It's like I was convinced that the building was on fire. Way too
cold to go out there now. I have to do it one more time? No, I don't. I already beat him once.
No, no, no, no. It's only three. It's only three. It's not one more. They all have to be red. Yeah,
no, that's the one guy. Okay. No, we're good. This is kind of a lot of guys. I'm getting up
bright and early in the morning. How do I make this? What time I wake up? Right there. Fine.
No, not 12 a.m. Oh, that sucks when you do a.m. instead of p.m. I've been there before. Your whole
life comes crashing down because you've been awoken very rudely and sometimes it's not really,
you know, you can't go back to bed. So then you just screw it for the rest of the day.
It sucks. I've been there before. All right, let's go. Time to see the conclusion of Nancy Drew.
Wilderness of the wild white fox. The title is not correct. Yeah, the title is not correct.
I get this still. Oh, my God. There's a lot of people still here at one o'clock in the morning.
Hey, well, we're good. We go till we beat it. I, you know, even if I have a few complaints,
the game was probably a nine point five out of ten. And then when we had to do the four games of
reverse, whatever the hell that is, brought it down at least two letter grades at least.
Now we get to have this fun. Let's see. So I got a picture of it. I've been like screaming,
too. It's been it's been kind of a wild stream. Sorry about that. Today was going to be like a
chill day. No cam. Sorry. We'll make up for it next time. All right. Here we go. All the gates are
open. So we just need forward, forward, jump forward. So forward, forward, forward, jump.
Let's try it. Four, four, four, jump, Isis, forward, forward, forward, jump, go forward,
forward, forward, forward, forward, forward, jump. Oh, forget it. Four, four, four,
jump. Isis, forward, forward, forward, jump, paw, go Australian hours. Yeah, I'll tell you there's
a lot of I look at the demographics of the channel. There's a lot of people from Australia that watch.
I actually think it's like the third or fourth demographic highest. So hello Australia, Asia too.
Yeah, but just just pure demographic wise, Australia is I think number three or four.
You stream at great Aussie hours. Well, that's good. So that was one. OK, now the other ones
looks like left, left, paw, left, right, paw. Let's try left, left, left, right, paw, Isis, left,
right, paw, forward. I think I think Isis goes forward already. Does it account for the first
intersection? It doesn't. OK, so forward, left, left, right, paw, forward, left, right, paw, Isis,
forward, left, left, right, paw, go. I go right because forward, left, left. Do I have to turn
that corner? I think is what I this is left is left, right. What happened? Forward. Do I not need
OK, so that that corner on the bottom doesn't matter. So it's just forward, left, left, paw.
You don't need to go right. OK, so forward, left, left, paw, forward, left, paw, Isis, forward, left,
left, paw, go. There's no intersection there. Yeah, that's true. Why is the cave green? That
would be all the radiation. And I wish I was making that up, but that's actually what that is.
All right, one more. This looks like it's forward, right, left, paw, forward, right, left, paw. No,
wait, forward, right, forward. Technically, that's an intersection. What about jump? Oh, there is a
jump, right? Hold on. So it's forward, forward, right, right, jump or forward again? Forward,
jump, forward, right, forward, jump. I think, yeah, I think I have to say it. Yeah, I think I have to
or jump, left, paw, left, paw, Isis, forward, right, forward, jump, left, paw, go. I think that's right.
Forward, right. This is an intersection here. So forward again, jump over the hole,
forward again, taking a left paw. There it is. That was fun. I like that one. I just didn't like
opening all the gates with the convoluted way to do it. I just gained a leather grade,
one half leather grade. Drink some water. I have been, I'm hydrated, don't worry. All right,
that is it. It is now time to go open all this shit up and finally see what's going on in this
world. It's time to party. We like, we like to party. Skiing guy and Lou, both of them,
they both did it. You see, Brea, this bag must belong to Lou. Oh my gosh, it's full of explosives.
Lou is the one who's been making those craters. He lied to me. He has been looking for dinosaur
bones. Nobody behind me. I'm gonna hear clap. Hello. What is this guy doing? Nancy. Yanni,
what are you doing here? I was skiing, but when I passed the needle, I saw that there was a door in
it, a door which was open. So I took off my skis to look and now I'm here. You didn't have to play
reverse heat for four hours. What do you mean? All I know is I found a bag, Lou Talbot's bag,
and it's full of explosives. There's just a door to come down here. Who is the one who has been
blowing up things? He is the bomber. He's been excavating dinosaur bones. He may be responsible
for a lot of the other stuff that's been going on around here too. You must stay here and guard
the bag. I will ski back to the lodge very quickly and tell the handyman to call the authorities.
This guy's full of shit. This guy's full of shit. This is very clear. Yeah, this is the villain.
There's 990.
A person who's been wearing that snowmobiling suit and blowing things up
is Yanni. Geophone data. Uranium. Oh my gosh, he set the timer.
Oh, there was just a door. We've got to get out of here. I was skiing and I found a door and I
walked in it. No, it would have been more believable if you told me. I had to play that
old man at that game that he played to beat him four times. It was very tricky.
You don't say I found a door. Like, buddy, I've been looking around this place for three weeks.
Get away from me. Snowmobile race. I hate that I can see all the gross shit on my monitor.
No way. We both just did that. You know, you have those moments where you just go, man,
I sneezed like a month ago and it's still right there, isn't it? What the hell? Where are you
taking him? Get over here. This is so stupid. Oh my goodness. Can I cut across somewhere, maybe?
I don't know. Yep. That's the play. All right. If we go past there again, I'm going that other way.
I'm trying to cut him off. God damn it. Oh, no. Oh my God. That's a Wario screamer that was.
Lying there in the snow, defeated, Yanni owned up to everything. He tainted the potato salad
with bad mayonnaise. He iced down the back stairs. He opened a gas valve in the sauna.
He blew up the bunkhouse using the clock he took from Guadalupe's room. And he left those pictures
of Bill Kessler for me in the sauna. Although he swears the door got stuck by accident in order
to cast suspicion on someone else. He did all this because he wanted everyone to leave Icicle Creek
Lodge. Why? Because it turns out that he was actually spying for the government of Fredonia,
which had sent him to Canada to look for uranium. Apparently his superiors hoped to secretly mine
what he found and smuggle it back to Fredonia. What they planned to do with it then, even Yanni
didn't know. But he insisted that he never meant to hurt anyone and that he really was the best
cross-country skier in the world. Unfortunately, he'll never get a chance to prove that now.
Chantal has barely been off the phone since she got back to the lodge. It seems that Yanni
Shenanigans made the nightly news, not just in Canada, but in the States. And as a result,
people have been booking stays right and left, much to her delight. When I told her and Ollie how
Isis had helped me, they were truly amazed. Hopefully from now on, Ollie will think twice
about pulling out his rifle every time he sees a varmint. As for Isis, Guadalupe called me that
very night and told me she'd found a wolf sanctuary that could take her. How could you tell from the way the
volunteers from the sanctuary treated her when they came to get her that she'll be in good hands
at her new home? But still, it's sad that through no fault of her own, she could never run free again.
They said it's possible that she might someday be released back into the wild, but not very likely.
I'm going to keep my fingers crossed anyway. I told you. I had it from the very beginning.
The dog was good. I told you that. You've been awarded the title of
Dear Detective for Superlatory Sleuthing. Got it? All right. Best suggested we head to New Orleans
for a short vacation. I thought it was a great idea. The French Quarter, fantastic food, awesome music,
friendly people, but all it took was one little side trip to check on a friend of Ned's and suddenly
everything got very strange. A recent death, a musty old mansion, a disturbingly odd curio shop,
a garden where only secrets seemed to grow, and something as ancient as it was terrifying.
Join me on my next adventure, Legend of the Crystal Skull.
I would, Nancy, but unfortunately I'm going to need a shovel to dig out all the buried copies of the game.
So I did say that that was cute. I liked it. That was cute. It was worth playing it. I'm glad we did it.
It was a lot of fun to be had lots of funny things. We talked about lots of interesting things we did.
I liked it. Nancy Drew and the Icicle Wolf of Icicle Creek. Just move those words around.
To where they belong. So next time you'll see Nancy Drew. Hey, did you really think you were
going to get a Nancy Drew game today? Yesterday? Did you think you were going to get a Nancy Drew
game? There's no way that you thought that. And we did it. So I have like 30 of these.
So we can do another one eventually. And it's fun. You skipped half the game. No, I didn't.
Half the game was the reverse again. Yeah. With that, I'm going to, I'm going to call it seven
hours. I think that's a good place to stop. So I'm trying to think of what, is there like a
post credit scene? You scummed at checkers. Well, I scummed at the coin swap machine thingy. That
was fun. I had a great time. I always have a great time when I play these. As long as you guys are
having fun. As long as it's fun to watch and fun to be a part of. That's usually how it works.
All right. The next stream is going to probably be probably the Resident Evil launch.
When is that? Two or three days? 23rd, 24th. It's probably the 24th in the middle of the afternoon.
Because what's probably going to end up happening is I'm going to play that
just until it's done. I imagine that's going to be probably like a Friday, Saturday, Sunday ordeal.
How long is Resident Evil for? It's like 15 to 20 hours or something, right? Somewhere in that
range. Maybe a little bit more, maybe a little bit less. So that's what we'll do.
I will see you guys again on the 24th and we're just going to go until I beat it for two or three
days in a row. That seems like the next logical time for me to come back. Plus that also gives
me the opportunity for the next few days to get some Grotto Beast stuff situated because as of now
we're starting to kind of come out of this pre-sale period and there is a couple things to make sure
go off well. You'll see very soon. I'll see you guys on Friday. Thanks for watching. Friday,
Saturday, Sunday probably or at least starting on Friday and we're just going for however many
hours or days it takes to beat Resident Evil 4. And actually the next time you see me I might have
something interesting to tell you or show you perhaps. We'll see. Maybe. Soon. We'll see.
Maybe. Not guaranteed but maybe. Alright everybody, see you later. That's the wrong thing. Hey,
there it is. Thanks for the subs everybody. Thanks for watching. Thanks for supporting the stream.
Kind of unhinged today but I think Nancy Drew just kind of pulls that out of us,
me specifically. We'll see you again. I'm very excited for Resident Evil 4. It's getting really
great reviews although I mean it's a remake of the one that already got really great reviews
but this one's getting very good reviews too. Making a remake could have the opposite happen
where it's not as good as the original but apparently this is incredible. Most outlets
are giving this high nines even tens so I'm very very excited because I love the fourth game.
I've played through it many times at least three or four times many times. We'll see how it holds
up. I'm very excited. The Resident Evil 2 remake was incredible I'm sure. Yeah we talked about it
in the very beginning of the stream. It'd be kind of funny if because I gave Resident Evil 2 a remake
game of the year. It'd be funny if I give this it was just two remakes in three years getting
game of the year for me. Alright let's raid somebody. I want to you know what I want who I
want to raid. Let me bring up their stream. Let's get a raid going. I want to raid. Oh let me see.
I want to raid Seadog. Seadog VA. Seadog's currently doing a charity cycle-a-thon from
Nagasaki to Kumamoto. Big charity cycle-a-thon. Go say hello. Connor is an awesome dude. Seadog go
say hi. Charity liker. That's right. I'll see you guys later. Thanks for watching. Take care
yourselves. Bye bye. Oh also we've got a few coins to spare. The donation the goal right now is 150k.
It's currently at 132k. So if you got some spare coin you know where to put it. See you guys soon.
Take care. Hey you hey we can get this to 10k. We can get this to 10k. Let's get a 10k raid on
charity stream. Come on let's do it. We can get this to 10k. We can do it. Let's do it. We can get it to 10k.
Come on. Go go go go go go go go go go go go go. If we don't it's fine. Come on go in.
I think everyone just left already. It's all right. All right see you guys later. See you on Friday.
Have a great night. Take care of yourselves. Goodbye.