Well, the guy in the striped shirt's a real cocky asshole, huh? I wonder how we're gonna deal with this situation, hmm? Could you guess? We're gonna fucking...
You're holding one, and here's holding two, and then here's your holding three.
Damn! Oh, alright, alright, that's two. That's double points, right? Alright, I'll take it, I'll take it.
Now, I'm gonna smash up somebody's cock, or I'll just miss. Hit the fucking car!
No, I'm sorry! I didn't mean to! I'm dead!
Let's get this shot lined up. No more messing around, we're gonna play golf. That was the wrong club. I didn't mean to use the sand wedge on the tee.
Step aside, my boy. Let me show you how a real golf pro does it. Yes, watch the ball gracefully fly through the air. 225 yards. That's a new record for me. You should probably take notes.
So this is, uh, this is what you're supposed to wear to the golf course, right? Like a dress? You're a joker! Call the cops, yeah, go ahead, try it.
She's actually gonna call the cops. Are you kidding me? What? I seriously have a star right now because I'm wearing a dress.
I honestly cannot believe that there's police swarming this area right now because there's a man in a fucking dress. Like, really? This is like, this is illegal? It's this illegal? To wear a dress? I'm not putting one on ever again.
That means I put a dress on, but I'm just kidding, don't worry.
Alright, let's do this. Let's go golfing again, my friend. Where'd you go? What? Alright, let's get in. Get on in here!
What the fuck is happening to this guy? Is it like another dimension? Is he right? Can I run him over?
This guy is in like the stomach punch dimension. Can I? I'm not doing that!
I'm not doing that!