Hello, welcome to another edition of Jeremy plays something and we go what the fuck today's what the fuck moment is
Vistra cleanup detail. All right that over here stream detective. Yeah, and I'm sorry to say
Today is gonna be a short stream. No, no before anybody gets angry. Just what wait, hold on
I need to make sure that the Christmas stream is taken care of I need to get packages ordered
I need to get paper and the people that are involved with the project need to be brought up to speed and
It's a whole ordeal. So to make sure that I can get that going
I've already been doing it kind of today and the day before yesterday
So the reason why there's a short stream today is because of the Christmas Eve stream
So here I'm gonna give you the plan for the next few days because this is kind of the holiday schedule, right?
I got to go to the doctor tomorrow. So that really has nothing to do with it. But the appointment is
In the afternoon, so I can't
Stream really and it gives me another day to make sure everything can get done. So one two three
Here's the schedule for this week. Nothing tomorrow stream on Saturday. Nothing on Sunday
Christmas Eve stream on the 24th and then two days later, I'll see you again after the holiday
So I'll see you guys probably on like the 26th of the 27th end of the stream voice
already
No, I mean short as in
less than four hours, but more than two, you know, I mean and
to continue to talk about this because of the nature of the packages and
The secret Santa chat suggestions, I got to get this shit ordered
So well, you really only have another couple hours for any suggestions
If you have any suggestions on what you'd like me to open on the Christmas Eve stream
And I'm gonna break down the rules one more time just because I think
There are probably plenty of people that may not know what I'm talking about because they literally only brought it up yesterday
So Christmas Eve, I'm gonna be opening up presents from you guys
But I'm going to be buying them. I'm not gonna be buying them a third party will be purchasing them
I don't know what they're gonna be
I don't know what they are your suggestions in that just is the discord channel by the way only up to three suggestions per person
Nope, nobody buy it. You don't buy anything. You just give an Amazon link that has a primable
Shipping and the mods are going to determine if that would be fun to open or if that would be something that they would want
Put on the list up to $50 per suggestion. No more than that. No live animals. No sexual stuff
No perishable items. They're your criteria. So no, you're not gonna it's not gonna happen. That's why the mods are
Responsible for selecting what they determine to be worth opening. I guess
Basically everything hold on. So this so nothing exists. Nothing in the world exists besides bugs
rats like dildos and
Like sandwiches, are you sure are you sure about this? Nothing else in the world exists. There's no other items. Anyways
We're gonna play this or clean up detail
Forget it's a just chill game to relax and hang out and play for a few hours
Well, then I figure out how I'm gonna get this whole thing put together for Christmas Eve
So let's just get over there. What do you say that up should already be
Captured. Hey, I think it is. This is not Shrek that I didn't say we were gonna play Shrek immediately
I never said that Shrek was gonna be played immediately
Shrek is is
Why the fuck did I say that last night?
why did I say I was gonna play Shrek last night the one where explicitly he talks about a
Certain thing a certain
sexual
thing
The first sentence of the game and I'm gonna play that on stream
I'm gonna have to like you know, here's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna
He talked like the first sentence of that game was he was talking about like oh, yeah
I'm gonna like put on a jacket. Yeah, it's cold outside. I'm gonna put on a jacket
You guys know what I'm talking about. Don't pretend like you don't. All right work assignment. I've
Split screen solo. Let's just do solo
Alone and scared. I played this game years ago a long time ago so long ago
Clean up speedrun
Worksite, holy shit. I think there was only one place to clean up
Save file. I don't have a restore. All right game rules
disable sniffer
Time limit and footprint limit. All right. I think that's fine
Let's listen Athena's wrath
average length one hour and 30 minutes
Holy shit, these take a long time three hours Wow, okay
Ever stream blank hour and 30 minutes play the Christmas map
I haven't purchased but I think I might need to open it, right?
I always found myself much slower than the average time. It's gonna be five hours. Oh shit
Shrek Shrek is walking shadow warrior map. Yeah, I have that too
Let me go pull on a second
Switch game DL switch between this or cleanup detail and its various spin-offs
Okay, here we go. So Santa's rampage shadow warrior house of horrors or the Vulcan affair
I think I'd have to do the Santa one, right? I
Guess we'll try. Do I need to know is this like advanced techniques and stuff?
Well, okay. Here we go. Which would you like to apply for?
assignment, okay
Santa's workshop
Two hours. All right. This is perfect game rules footprint
Whatever, that's fine. All right
Christmas I'm ready
Start work. No footprints. Why no footprints janitor age 23 occupations station engineer
the tar the tragic events that unfolded at this workshop must be
Post in no way deter you from performing your duties in a manner befitting the company's reputation
Your work here entails cleaning up the horrific aftermath of mr. Claus's unfortunate breakdown. This is the obvious slaughter and any broken items
Please conduct yourself appropriately as assignment will reflect upon your permanent record. Wait, what happened in here?
Failed to follow company guidelines and regulations. You may find yourself without a job
Once I'm just complete the corporation will take ownership of the workshop and any remaining items. Okay
Let me turn the sensitivity needs to come down. It definitely does
Controls sensitivity, let's get that down to like
That not that didn't really change anything did it?
menu sensitivity
Sensitivity, how low does this have to go? All right, that feels fine. All right, so
I have to clean up
personal log
Alright, so I don't even know the controls. Oh my god
Is this person still alive?
Okay, how do I pick him up? That's not how you pick people up. That's not how you pick people up
Okay, now what do I do with them? What is this? How do I like use items? No, I'm not gonna put him in the fire
This is scaring me. Okay
Wait, these presents are fine. All right. Let me look at the controls
Should have played the tutorial. I really should have this so much here. Okay, should I go play the tutorial?
Do I like have no idea what I'm doing? Hold on for a game pad
Forward interact is mouse prop and hit is mouse to mop is one hands sniffer is three additional tools
All right, I'm gonna go to I don't know what the fuck I'm doing
So I need to like I didn't know how to like even play the game. Is there no tutorial? I closed the fucking game
It's all right. You just clean up
Why is everybody telling me to do the is there even a tutorial clean up this one? You just clean that's it
But there's no other that there's no
Mechanics that I need to know you just clean. Is there no tutorial there isn't a tutorial
There's no tutorial. Why did everybody tell me to play the tutorial to just clean? Oh
Fucking god damn it. All right, whatever. Here we go. I'm ready. All right a game rules. These are fine
All right, this is an easy game to flip
I know but I don't know how at least like at least five one guys told me to do the tutorial
All right, I got it. Oh now I'm on fire. I need to get a bucket of water
This shit is so dirty now. I think where's the water? I need a bucket of water. Where do I get a bucket of water?
What is this? All right, I gotta find water. Do I have like a water? Can I like order it from my fucking menu?
What the fuck is this?
Why do I have like a ghost detector? Oh
Okay, the slosh automatic. Oh
There we go a bucket of water. So now I go like this
Look at that. Oh my lord. All right, I get it now. I get it. I
Remember and we don't have what do I do the bodies? Is there something I need to do with the bodies?
Do I actually have to burn them? I have to burn them. Are you sure I feel like that's wrong
Hey fuck this Xbox. I think I blocked the door. Oh
All right, what do I do?
It's too bloody I need more water does this work more doesn't work faster. All right, come here put you over here. Oh
I feel like you guys are just making me do that. I'm not supposed to be doing that. Just put everything in the fire
Okay, everything can go on the fire. That's how you clean the whole house. Okay
This is dirty. What do you do with the dirty shit?
Okay, I need another one. All right, get out here. Oh and knocked it over. No, I want to give you it
All right, come here right here now. It's clean now. I'm tracking footprints everywhere
Is this why everyone told me to turn it off?
How do I clean my feet?
How do I cook? Okay. All right. I got it clean them. Okay
Wait, what's that? What do I do with these?
Can I get like a wastebasket? How do I get like a trash can? This is is a trash can don't like don't tell me
It's not it just has water in it. Okay. What's this ice cold?
Is this playing music? How do I make it change songs? How do I make this change music?
All right, I need to turn this music off. All right, here we go
Set it on a safe place. Is there how can I rotate something? All right, how do I rotate?
All right, how do I press the button?
E
Hold left click the screen. Ah, I got it. Okay. All right, stop. I gotta clean
There's a cursor. Oh
What the this is so tiny. I didn't see the cursor. I thought I had to press the button with my finger
No, they all start the same way. All right whiskey and a shotgun. Sure. All right, give me my where's it?
All right. Let me I gotta go. I'm gonna go corner. That's how you clean a real house. You go corner to corner
And you got to bring the bucket with you so you don't get it anywhere. All right, I'm gonna go corner to corner
Start in this corner
Sorry
Make sure it's all clean in one corner
Watch your feet. This is the tactic because then you don't step in where you've already cleaned
And you don't have to worry about anything else. So I didn't know you could do that
Presence are fine, right? I don't have to get is part of the cleaning. How do I get that?
How the fuck do I get the kite up on the on the ceiling god, what do you mean gun?
What am I supposed to do with the gun? I can't use it the FOV. It should be 90 when we turn it up
Anything over like an 100 is puke inducing. All right, so this corner is done
Wait, not quite. What's that thing? What a load disposal bins. Ooh, wait, how do I get one? So this is where trash goes
All right, how much what do I do with this afterwards? I have to throw that in the fire afterwards. Oh bullshit. No, I don't
Okay, make sure how do I see? How do I stand it back up?
Shift how do I turn it?
Turn this I got it. Okay, so you can't just smash into stuff. I get it. God. Oh, okay
I can hold left click and just turn it on easy. All right. Can I get the fuck out of this corner? I
Almost got the okay. Remember the technique is corner to corner. I have to be careful
Alright, so I have to put these in here. Is that the do I get more points if I do it like this in footprints?
There's nothing even in here. This is dirty. No, it's not. What's the what are the shells coming from?
Why does this thing have this thing's on a shotgun? Oh, never mind. It fell out before. Okay, here we go
Don't step in any blood. I gotta get to the front. This is fun
What if this is kind of like a house flipper, but you don't flip the house. You just clean it up
This is fun. What was this something wrong with how I said that?
You don't think this is fun. I think this is fun. It's fun. Can you do my house next?
I don't even want to answer that because I don't think I'm good enough
You know, I mean, I'm not sure you want me there
It'll take me like six hours to clean one room in your house
All right. What else is in here? All right. Well, that's pretty brutal
Happy Christmas. So these are as if that doesn't do it. I
Call it another janitor. Yeah, too
Okay, so age 19
Careless work ethic of your predecessor led to their death shaving the company required that you is a substitute this opening immediately
Perform your duties in accordance with the company guidelines and regulations
Or be replaced your parts will be valid. Why would somebody do that?
I'm gonna just take fucking live dynamite throw it into a fire and does it work is my last words. Oh
Fuck okay
Is that me
Hold on I want to like do it again though. I'm gonna get a good distance. Fuck it. Let's go ready
What are we doing over here? Oh
shit
What was that? There was another explosion. Oh, no, what?
What was the other explosion?
No
This is cleaning up haven't even seen game of Thrones fire. Oh fuck
This is the I'm cleaning
Give it to me. I want it. Okay, so I did it so now I have to have to restart the level
Do I have to do I have to restart the level? Yep. Yes. No, I could clean it though. Ow. Oh
Shit that was his head. I get I can clean this up. Look I have to clean it up anyways. Oh
What a funny explosion stream. No now that's over
Alright, I'm gonna know. I know I don't get to go back. Did you see that buddy explosion?
Ah
Okay, let's like all cleaning techniques. You gotta start in the corner
Give me this. I need a mop up here two hours average. I
Don't know what the fuck I was thinking. I want to play this game again. This is I like this game
I didn't even give it a real chance before but what if this is fun? I feel like I'm a comp was this
My god, that's this is terrible. This is actually fucking awful
Get in there. Okay
Okay, that's fine. Let me take care of this first. Oh
Whoa
Then I'm gonna dump this in the means in the so this is kind of like bagging leaves, right?
Don't tip it over. I want the arms you then you go dump the leaves where is that a person inside it is
Tip joke incoming. No, it is not
I need to get it all concentrated in the same place and then I can deal with it. So that's it
No, there's a couple more pieces in here. Come on. Get it. They're like a crouch. What the hell? Well, I
incoming spill
No, I'm getting them in a concentrated location because then I can dump them because I don't want to have to come back up here
for bodies, right so
Only one more
All right. This is the last body here. All right. Here we go. Is this too heavy?
Slow slow slow. What the fuck did I just walk over? I don't even know what happened. I went over a speed bump
I can't see am I going the right way? Yes. What is going on? Okay
All right
Get him over there. There are too many in here. It's alright. Come on. Get out get out
Yeah, it's like dumping a recycling bin. Okay burn the box. Should I have done that?
Put out a new song with the stuff in it. Well, whatever. It's fine. Okay, so that I now I'm gonna get a clean
Bucket and that's gonna go up here and then I'm gonna start the actual this is gonna be
Completely clean. Oh, I forgot a guy over there. Whatever read the notes on Santa's desk
What about the flash drives? I need another
This is gonna take forever. No, it's not
No, how about this? I'm not gonna turn the stream off until this is clean
You understand this is gonna be a short stream, but I don't know
Might be longer than that now
Okay, I gotta get the blood up there. I gotta make this orderly too. All right, this is dirty
Well, I gotta get rid of this. I can put it back here, right and then
What came what is that? Why did an arm come out?
Do I just burn these?
You just burn everything I didn't I thought I like could put it up there in and exchange it for a new one
Okay, that's fine
I'll deal with that one later
No footprints. Okay, it's so dirty up here. All right now, let's
Let's go past
The I am good, right?
Come on what everybody hated that one? Very funny. Nobody liked that one. Nobody thought that was funny fine
I'm never making another joke ever again. I don't know that
That guy clips through the wall
Can he honestly not see the USB sticks? Yeah, but what am I?
So what about them? What do you want me to do with these?
I don't know. What do you want me to do with them? Everyone's saying USB USB. Is there a computer because this thing?
Is this a computer?
Please swipe your card and pull the crank. It did not put gum. Okay. Oh
Okay activate as your janitorial work here met the requirements of the company
Oh
No, I'm not done yet. I was just checking the machine
I wish I could do more for my company. Give me some paperwork to fill over extra marks
No, I'm just checking out the machine. So how did I how do I get that to work? I just put it in it disappeared
I did oh
Okay, can I pick this up? Okay. What was I doing? Oh, yeah up here
All right. Oh, the top is gonna be done very very shortly. Just to rearrange get this off here
I'm just gonna get everything down there. So it'll be fine. Now. What about the pro? Okay. Hold on. What is this?
Hello, Miss Dana. I don't want any more stupid books again
You must give me the new ultra mega water blaster assault cannon and I want the big
Times times five one so it'll be bigger than Kenny's one
I'm gonna fill it with acid from my daddy shop and spray down old
Mr. Quouch's car that teach her for calling cops again. I don't want to see that
And I want to fucking I've no no, okay. I gotta get that to the police. Oh
Thank God. Okay, like everything that's incriminating. I need to keep right here. Thank God
Shit can I get it in from down here? Nope, what is the fuck is this? What is it? Why you get I want water
My god look at the floor we're not down here yet. Okay, relax
We're not at this part yet where do remember even you start cleaning clean
Corner to corner, okay
Don't stop fucking hitting stuff. Okay, all the elves are all gone from up here
I need to go clean up this way watch the ground. Okay, there's no blood over here. I
Gotta put the presence back up on the table because actually no no, it's dirty. So let me ask this one more time
Do I need to throw the presence away or do I keep the presence where they are, you know I'm saying keep them
Okay, so it looks nice. Why would I I don't know because I don't know they might be bodies in there
Just Santa. I was good this year. So I want a pony and a bike and a new clarinet. Okay. Well, this is not incriminating
We need to save all the incriminating one Santa my parents say I was good
So I could write to you and ask for stuff
So I want the new super turbo jet racer car with all the extras. Also, I want lots of chocolate and the y-pad
Oh my god, that hit me right in the face. Okay. Now we're gonna make the presents look nice
I don't okay. I gotta stack these in a nice way. No, I gotta sit you in the corner over here
Whatever. Okay, set these back up presents back on the table. All the blood is gone. Is there any blood underneath?
I don't think there is it's a little bit. Is that blood? No, it's a shadow from the gun. Okay, not bad. Wait
Okay, take a look at that nice and clean we just need to take this stuff down here to throw it into the
fire trash
Use the sniffer. What is this thing trying to tell me? Uh, what does it mean?
What I mean is there I need the wood planks to go over that hole. Are you sure?
Uh, is the guns hold on still it's I want to test something here. It is the gun
It's detecting all the blood below me. Okay. No, no, no, we're fine. There's blood on the ceiling
Put it put it. I'm not even gonna say what you just said. All right, this is done. What is that? Oh, all right
I don't want to make sure I don't track any steps. Come here one detects blood and gore the other detects trash
Okay, I feel like I kind of need to get close to being clean because I mean I will I am
Have you detecting anything in the room? So I need to clean this up first and then walk around with the ectoplasm gun
This is dirty people are asking. Why am I doing? Wait, does that work? Hold on a second. Does that work?
No, it doesn't get what are you giving me? I don't want this. Why is it cooking food for me?
I don't want like a fucking filet mignon. Give me a what are you giving these to me for? Why is this here? No
Why did it spawn die? This is the water hole. What that's supposed to get water buckets out of that thing
Put the dynamite in the water. I didn't have any buckets of water
That's why I was calling for them
I thought you could dump the buckets of water onto the ground to make the ground clean
All right, the careless of the janitor for the careless with like an ethic of your predecessor. Let it at death. Yeah, it's a shame
Okay, let's hope I don't get a fucking with a dynamite in the water machine
No, just more fucking stakes
Why are you doing this?
Can I get a bucket of fucking water?
All right, get off
No, I don't want more water
Give me
Okay looks pretty good so far get this shit out of here. My computer's like running. Oh, I need that. I need that
This is how you get extra points, right? Two steps forward. Oh what there was no blood in there
I was gonna say two steps forward ten steps backwards speaking of steps
Ruining everything and I like throw this in the air
Not smashed all that needs to happen is I need to get real close to pick this up and the hand has to fucking
Grab me. I don't think I'm getting this ever. No, yes, I am. Let's clear the stairs off. All right
More water, please. Oh
Like a brain matter
Water what the fuck is going on? How do you even produce this?
No, now that is dirty the water fuck am I doing something wrong?
Finally, the machine is dirty. Well, how would that explain why there's dynamite in the machine?
Fucking god, damn it. It's fine. There's still what yeah that machines real dirty. That's why it's spawning
Dynamite. All right. Here we go. Oh, this is really dirty
Cool. This is oh, this is dirty
And you put on the ceiling. It's not spawning dynamite. What am I talking about? You didn't see the explosion
All right upstairs is done. It only took like two hours
Not the ceiling. Oh fuck
Dammit, okay, make sure I think I got it all what the hell is this trash? All right. I gotta get rid of whoo. I need that
Well, all right, so I'm sorry I didn't know that was gonna turn into a fucking Simon Belmont item
There's a Castlevania. Holy water. I didn't know that was what was gonna happen. I thought it was an LED. All right, the machine is clean
Yeah
I'm gonna clean the machine and then let's see if your guys theory is correct. Okay machine is now clean
Whatever fuck. Okay. I have a clean machine
Now, let's see if if I get more body parts
So it was bullshit doesn't matter if the machines dirty or not that wouldn't produce. Why does it keep getting worse?
Am I getting bad grades or something?
Okay back up here. This is done. No more blood on the ceiling pick this shit up
Yeah
Okay
Now I didn't need a new I did a new bucket of water. I'm sure you didn't want an arm now
Well, I'm overwhelmed. I'm okay. I'm done. That was fun. I'm just kidding
So what I don't even start I don't know even where to start with this. What are all these buckets doing down here?
Oh, I don't know what to do. This is so much
It's so much that it's overwhelming to me corner to corner just like my true strategy
Okay, let's do this. Correct. I'm gonna burn the buckets
I'm starting from scratch. I don't even care what that is. It's just it's in my way
Fuck the stools. I don't I just need space
Get over here. No, I need that nice. It's this too many things in there all presents are gonna have to move into a corner
There's a radio. Yeah, I got ridder. Okay. No, there's more buckets. Can I like put these in here?
What happened? Oh, all right. I get it. I can't so what happens if this goes back in there?
Let me just I'm testing something. Hold on. Does this take the trash as well?
Okay, you have to burn it, but I didn't know if you could fill it and then bring it over there and it like
Oh, thank you. It sucks it back up and empties it without having to dump it into the fire
Okay, here we go. This is new. He's trying to tele-frag himself. I mean not really
I didn't know if there was an in a quicker way to instead of dumping it into the fire
Corner to corner. Let's go. I do need that though. No, so I don't even care what it is
I'm not if it's a present who gives a shit. It's going into the trash
Fuck well, that's to go up there. Perfect about this. This is oh my god. Damn it
Nothing fell out. It's so easy just to accidentally. This is just look at this physics thing the game
What does this stuck on? On the hat?
Okay, I just it's flat man. Just what am I sitting this on? What's wrong with this? A bullet?
more body
parts
Yeah, I'm sorry that gets caught up in the crosshairs. I don't care if it's a nice candy cane. It's going to the trash
It's not my job to have to worry about what can or can't be thrown away right now
The fuck is this thing? All right body parts in in
In all right, we're pretty we're kind of full
All right, I got it
So do I leave that in there
Or do I don't understand? Do I leave the incinerator in there or do I have to take it back out?
Just leave it in there. Okay. I didn't know if I was
That's fine. I need another one. All right. Now I need a bucket of water joint
Look at that, you know, if I think I was gonna get anything done today, did you?
Zero progress look at upstairs. I did all of upstairs already. I took care of upstairs. I got started down here
This is how long it would take me to clean an actual house
I'm gonna here's where I'm gonna store all the flash drives over here in this corner one small part of the map in an hour
There's not much left
Fucking footprints. I need more water. All right. I need to how do I reliably dump this in the fire?
I think yeah, I have to just put it in the fire. I can't do anything else with it. All right now I've got a flow
Now I got a fucking flow
This but bought downstairs here is gonna be a breeze
All right, what time is it right now?
I've been streaming for an hour and four minutes. I
guarantee I
100% guarantee that this area down here will be
Immaculate in exactly 20 minutes
Okay
So at exactly one hour and 24 minutes into the stream. It's going to be immaculate down here. Go
Check this out. I got a fucking better idea. I know what I'm gonna do
Watch this. I need like five of these. Okay, that's good for now one more
Here we go. Fuck. I still got it. It's fine. Nice spill joke. No, not everything is a spill joke
Time check I don't need that one. It's fine. I got obviously that's even two minutes
Relax. I got this ten minutes left. No, I have like
Seventeen minutes left that bring this closer. Don't waste any time with the incinerator thing. There's no reason for it
Okay, candy can't get in there all things must go once the blood is gone. It's just a matter of getting three incinerators
Dirt, okay
Getting there. I'm not gonna lie. I would probably sit here with my mouth open and play like the ten hour long level. I
Really would
Is it too early to call this game of the year?
No, no, not too early. It's fucking two weeks till the year's over
You know what? I mean though. Is it do one of this come out like five years ago?
I'm a couple of years too late. Well, can I amend my taxes from two years ago and make sure that I put game of the year?
2015 as visceral cleanup detail. Is that bad? I put that off my taxes
Yeah, that one was on purpose because I thought it was funny
That's just gonna shoot does the gun shoot if it's in there. This is like a cartoon. This is like a cartoon
That's gonna go like
Right
Okay. No, it's not
Where was the blood where the blood come from get rid of the oil? How am I gonna get that? Okay, good clean no blood
little bit of blood
All right, almost there. Oh my god. I got about 14 minutes. Oh
Dear not gonna track this around. I don't care. I don't care
Dick I need to bring this over here
Come here get over
No, I forgot there was that much shit in it, it's all right I got 14 minutes
What the fuck it was on the table it was a perfect shot perfect shot
Oh
Am I mad?
Just get the furniture out of the way temporarily. I can set this up later. It just gets in the way. It makes me trip
Holy shit those
Okay. Okay ground is almost clear. Okay ground. I just gotta run around
This stuff in here. Okay, sit right here. Oh, no, there's so many. Oh, no
Okay, just the floor has to be cleaned for this the challenge to work
Okay, don't these footprints are killing me
Skip rid of the large debris. It's a lot of it over here. I need I need another one of those
Give me another one. Hurry. Hurry
Hurry, why am I saying it like that? Hurry. Hurry. What accent is that? Hurry?
What's hurry slow down? I think I got plenty of I have plenty of like four minutes. No, I have way more than that
I have like yeah, I have ten minutes
Come on. Hurry. Okay. Is there any more debris? There's lots of debris. What am I talking about?
This is all from the explosion. This is not even my fault. I think that's it. Any more random debris. Yes random arms that came up
Well, this got dumped
You got to move out of the way man all of you
Cuz I got more I got more things to dump
Okay, just get it in the trash who cares two buckets. That's the third one. Just put it here
It looks like I just started
Well, I can assure you I didn't just start. All right, that's enough
There's only a couple more things and then I got to just
Furiously mop dump it. Wait, wait, what is happening? Love a clean shot. Oh
Got it. Okay
What's next? What's next? What are you doing now? Where did this come from? What was it in? Huh?
Come on. I fucking guaranteed. I
guaranteed
You know, I have to it has to be done
No, I got I got to place these
These have to be placed strategically
One here one in the corner
One here. Here we go
One two three action. Come on. See the strategic triangle that I made
I'm never away never never five feet away. Okay, let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
I'm fucking amped up right now. I had two sips of a Red Bull earlier right here. Come on. Come on
Dick you dickhead dickhead. Not everybody's a dickhead. Fuck you game. I'm
Look, come on get back into it. I need it all got it went to hell when I fucking
Shit over here
Watch it watch it watch it watch my watch my pads my pads are getting on the ground. I could still do it
It's still close
Here we go corner. I'll clean it up. I just got to get the shit in here
Get in give it a little shake. Sometimes I didn't put him in
How did you not get my fucking god? Give me a break. Fuck the presence. They're not necessary
Just get rid of them. Who cares? It's taking longer to fill this then to
Come on, how much time I have four minutes. I can't even put the fucking presence in there. It's gonna be close
All right. Any more stray stuff around here. Don't you dare fuck that up? Okay, come on. It's so dirty over here. Fuck it
All right, watch the feet good. Okay, we're almost done. What's left two minutes? Oh
No, there's too many. I need one of those incinerators. Come here
Don't step in the blood. I got like 30 seconds. It's all it's gonna be clean
It's it'll be clean, but there'll still be like some debris, but it'll be clean
It won't be bodies and it won't be blood 20 seconds. Okay, what else is anybody body parts? Okay, hold on
All right, wait 10 seconds 10 seconds 10 9 8
7 6 5 4 3
Fuck you game bullshit. I'm so pissed off. I had it. It was close. I
Love this game. Oh, it's so much fun
Okay, it was clean. Look at how clean it was before I fucking panicked. That's pretty close
Let's get a bird's-eye view. Come on forget about see that one right there that one right there that one down there
They weren't there. I had the presence stacked. I just I knocked over the bucket. That was pretty clean
Now I can slow down. I did the whole thing in almost 20 minutes. Come on. I'm not gonna get at least one
Bogjam
You guaranteed and I did do it. I did clean it but I so when the timer went up, it was clean
There was no blood. There was no debris when the timer went up
It was it was fine. But the problem is after the timer when it was clean
I didn't tell you it wasn't gonna be fucked up after the timer goes up
So the timer goes up and I got I knocked over a couple things after the time went up
A few pieces of debris some blood went on the ground. Stop burning Christmas presents. Shut up idiot. Liar. Liar idiot
so why did I hit blackjack like four times in a row with the
the dumb
I was gonna say grenade dynamite. I can't even think I can I not even diddle a simple procedure
Just the timer is up
All right. Now I can just slowly take care of the rest and then we're gonna move on to I don't know
What do I move on to the spill joke isn't funny stop doing it
I got some really really bad news for you
He's not pretending
I just I'm so I don't know. I just bump into stuff
Going a third person. Can you is there a third person mode?
I gotta have set this back up in a proper place in a nice spot right here on the table
That's good. Let's do
My crank in it. All right crank it alt f4 is third person. Is it? Let me try alt f4
Let me very clearly and I'm hitting space to make that. Why would I choose space of all things? So, let me put these
I'm trying. I'm trying to keep track of these
All right
Presence, let's just clean this up wall blood
Fire put that what's still in there. Stop burning everything. I'm not burning everything
Just the things that I don't feel like walking 10 feet to my left or right if I have the urge to
Take a stool and walk it this way. Then I will
Does that boom box have doom OST? It does not I'm pretty certain it does not
No, put this on the table
So I'm just learning right now that if you just left-click it puts it straight like the correct orientation that it was supposed to be
Right. Well, that took me a long time to figure that out put on doom
No, I'm not gonna cave to put the doom soundtrack on
I'm not gonna be the guy that gets pressured to put on doom soundtrack every three streams. I
Want to do like I want to do like color coordination. Oh
That's okay
Fucking immaculate is what this will be
Do it vessel. No, I'm not gonna do that
I want to put on the songs that I want to listen to and one of them is this one
Look at how nice that looks over here. No scratch that now. Look at how nice it looks over here
You do it every stream. Well, don't you understand? I don't want to be I don't want to do that. Come on
Don't make me put on the doom OST. I'm gonna have some self-control. I'm not gonna do it. Just put
I'm I don't want to put on that either. I don't want to put on the dancing grandpa six-flags song
All right, what happened to that guy dance? Oh
Probably that guy was supposed to be like a hundred years old. That was like 30 years. That's like 15 years ago
That's too bad. I wish that guy would come back
He was a cool mascot. I know it wasn't an actual as a guy with like a prosthetic face on
Do you think I'm that stupid?
Do you do you do you think what am I some kind of maniac?
All right, look at this mess spill joke incoming no, that would have been a perfect opportunity
You see if I was like, do you think I'm a fucking idiot? Oh
I didn't do it though. That was a perfect opportunity for like the YouTube edit right there
You know I'm saying like I go on that whole rant that whole
Whole
Anyway, you guys think I'm stupid. Oh
God next scene
Perfect. Oh
How did this get up here? What the fuck? He's trying to distract us from the doom. Ost. Is it working?
I'm not gonna play doom. Ost. You gotta have some different you got some variety here
Maybe I'll put something else on but it's you gotta have a little bit of variety here
Katamari I we listen to Katamari already more than once
Okay. Now, let's get rid of the buckets that are here
Hotline Miami. Ost. We just heard it. You just heard the whole thing two days in a row
Give me another
Persona 5 ost
No, I don't I haven't played persona 5. I don't want to listen to the ost
It's gonna give away like some secret characters
Stream it for a hundred hours
Crypt of the no, I know no no
sponge Bob
Yoshi's Island. Ost now, that's a good one. That's something that I can get behind, you know, I can get behind that
Are these sounds too loud or is this fine? Am I being overpowered by the loud noises?
Hold on a second. I don't want to fuck that. Hold on. Let me save the game because that would be bad if something happened here, right?
Okay, right there play the Seinfeld. Ost
Seinfeld doesn't have what it's like three songs. There we go. Let me get this in the right
Volume level that's another that's not a bad musical level. I don't play I think it's fine
Yeah, and it just needs to be in the background just something that's just okay. Hold on. Why are we getting resident sleepers for this?
Resident sleeper. I wonder why is it because you're sleepy. I don't get it
Alright, there you go. What happened to this? So comfy. Yeah, this is a comfy
Soundtrack, that's for sure. I don't really get out of here. You dumb. I okay really I'm trying to get comfy here
I don't want this bullshit. I can't wait to get the
The song that goes I
Bring this over here. I'm done with this room pretty much. I do need to reorganize
Get out of the okay. I'm gonna put everything up in the air. So I don't accidentally spill joke it
That's Yoshi's Island. Not Yoshi's story
No, that's just she's that's where it came from
That song came from Yoshi's Island. That's the stage select and you'll know because here it comes right now
Never mind, that's not it
There's this table's dirty. All right, I gotta make sure that I did not pick like a 10-hour version of this one song
No, I didn't it's stopping. There we go. Here it comes. You ready?
Here it comes. Come on. Do it
Okay. Well, this is the ocean level
Now this is the title screen
This is the person didn't press start yet. Whoever's playing this guy's stuck behind here
How am I gonna get this person out of here? This is not good. Nothing. I can't do anything about that
I can't move the shelf. Well, whatever he's now he's a display. That's fine. Okay, let's see ceiling. Oh
No, fuck that chrono trigger is the chrono trigger OST is going on next
Yeah, let's get this back up here. All right looks good. I don't think I see it
All right. Now is the opportunity where I can let's clean this up
Put these chairs back where they belong
Get the presence move them over on this table for now
How is this different from the house game you played earlier house flipper? Well, this one is gruesome brutal
Murder scenes as you have to clean up house flipper is you put up new walls? I don't put any I just have to clean
That's all I gotta do here
This is the first cutscene. I remember this
This is when it introduces Super Mario in the diaper. It's really loud
How do I how am I gonna get this miss an elf over here? Fuck that would have been awesome
Finally, what do you mean? Finally?
fucking finally
Finally, he found the elf
What is this noise? I hear
What are these sounds I seek?
How many people are in the street? Oh, that's perfect fucking here comes the musical intro
And like all the actors are fucking running around and like wind is blowing them
This is the ensemble intro to any musical you will ever watch. It does not matter
Just listen wait for the this part
Here here it is here it is this journey high right now. No. All right, I'm gonna relax
Like this guy's on drugs. He has to be
What's this guy on fucking drugs?
No, don't take drugs. Well, I mean I do but ones that are prescribed by a doctor
Yeah
Oh, no, are you gonna explode? What do we do?
Wait, oops
Candle, okay candle
Uh, I can't like transfer it bring the tnt closer. Yeah, but
That's dangerous. I gotta go far for that. Damn it fucking
Yeah, no, I just I can't light it from far away. Whatever. Welcome to the scene
Use the candle use the can't can't do anything. I almost just said the f word. I'm just said the f u c k word
This is okay level. This is cool
Youtuber funny moments clip don't tell me about youtuber funny moments
Have you ever seen?
my modern warfare 3 video
hysterical
Remember remember when I went
Get the fuck out of here. Hey, oh, look at that. I look at all these lols
Remember that
How about this one?
You stupid fucking idiot
Remember that one? Whoa, I thought my monitor just broke. So did I
All right, no more dicking around I can't one step backwards two steps forward three steps backwards
That's been this whole entire stream so far
Is there somebody in here?
Or there was whatever the game has text to speech chatting text to speech chatting
How how do you do it type in the chat?
Yeah, that is that's a tuber game on that's
Type in the chat
You have to enable it. Oh, how do you type audio shit for brains?
What you don't think that would be under controls like toggling like a control what?
t
great t
What?
Yeah, it's not stuff to eat remember this one's a ha ha ha my rocket copters wishes
I remember that when let's do it every video
So
I'm serious every single video i'm gonna put that in my funny moments
Oh fuck was five jump egg roll
Got him how many more hits
The big loopy guy with his clown pants
Wtf, how does it sit on a stab yak favorite game from snes?
He's blinking
He's close
Who got him?
Oh, this level is dm7 believe the mushroom and go dizzy
All right, that's enough
Say germacraft
No, i've that's something i'm not going to say
Stop, it's not a mess
Hello ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of germacraft the terrarium is where I play minecraft now
There's gonna be some food
What
What are you talking about? It's gonna be some food
All right, the text to speech is over. I'm turning it off
I gotta get out of this fucking room
Fucking he oh he swears
What's wrong with me?
No, it's not on there. Why do I think it's on there?
All right, give me the incinerator thing
Give me a new one. I want a clean slate. I don't even know what's in there
This room is done
Let me pull out the
the meter
What is up here?
Oh right there
Is that it? I think it's detecting the shit downstairs
You finally noticed the green poop it's called the sniffer get the names right
All right. I'm gonna move on
This room is pretty much done. I'll figure the rest out later
I need a new bucket
Let's get rid of the old buckets. Wait a minute. That's not a red lamp post
Now it is
End of the stream voice not even close
Oh my god, why am I doing that?
I have the memory of a fucking goldfish
I'm gonna pick this up and put it over here. Okay
That thing no longer exists
Has it been more than five seconds item doesn't exist anymore
Two will be fine. I think
Okay, don't knock that over two will be all right
Now I need to get one of those
trash compactors
What is this?
What is this? You just
This is the bat I think it's the bat
Was there bat in that game? I don't remember who that was. No it
Bowser Jr
A boomer game
How dare you say something like that?
Yoshi's island is
Is is the history of all video games? I need
Oh, what do I need?
This is an achievement that said 28 000 of something. I don't even know what it said, but that's a lot
There's no blood over here. This thing's pretty clean over here
What the fuck happened in here? Did the grenade come in here?
I think so
That's not gonna fit like that. I'm gonna have to do individual pieces of wood
A grenade walked in here
Yeah, so I mean like what the fuck
Get out of my space, man
I need to get this is not gonna happen
It's too clunky
too clunky
Too clunky
How am I gonna get all this out of here? I think I have to make another pile no
Give me the bucket
I think I have an idea
It's kind of that's not a bad idea
Just knock it all in the corner over there
Now that loosened it up. That didn't do anything. I need to hydrate
Um, it's been two hours
I'm all right
I drank I already drank a lot of water. I'm all right
Appreciate the concern
Fuck you. Did that really just happen?
That's mopped up
Nothing else in the corner. I don't think
except for the table
This water is absolutely filthy
Time to get rid of this water
drink drink drink
fine
There's extra like fucking protein cells in there. It's the bonus room where you spin the wheel
Okay
Why do you just have to ruin everything with the meat here?
Is this clown music? I mean it technically is clown music carnival music
Technically
All right. What are we at? We need
I need to get the stools out of the way
No, it's just it's just brush
Pick up the bodies after just it's spelled. You got a brush
Because then I got a clean slate and it's just picking stuff up and moving stuff around
Just don't hit the bodies because it spreads blood like that
Debris is fine. I can just mop around it
Debris and blood is more debris
Now it's time to actually pick shit up off the ground
This is super mario gets the star
I don't know what the fuck it's doing in a yoshi game
All right. I think I can bring in a barrel
Because yoshi is part of the mario universe
Oh, yeah
Nice ad
I can't even see the sour please gift. Yes, I can
I told you my new year's my my new year's resolution is i'm going to download better twitch.tv
These are just too big. I gotta go by themselves. They can't fit in the box
But hey that there's the joke though guys because new year's resolutions you never do them
All right. I think the rest can fit in a box
Yeah, give it to me. This is the final boss, right?
body parts
This is going pretty smooth
These old electric guitar song the sounds that like
You know how long it probably took somebody to find or make that electric guitar sound
Sounds like a mega man
Well, they are from the same era
Not gonna fit but I will try to balance it
Don't have this guy
You know what I mean fortnight they don't have this kind of music in fortnight
Why does everything relate back to fortnight?
Because I believe at this point there are more followers to the fortnight
twitter
Than members of christianity
So, I mean it's pretty relevant
Jesus fortnight. No what i'm saying is
Fortnight has become so big
It's like minecraft times five
How many followers does the fortnight twitter have i'm curious and this is just the twitter account
six and a half million
How many how many people follow christianity?
like eight million
four million
It's like it's like probably a billion. Fuck. It's like two billion people
All right
So i'm gonna do a google search is fortnight more popular than christianity
fortnight
Yeah, only 6.5 million people
Follow the twitter, but how many people have installed the game?
Somebody give me some facts on that how many people have installed fortnight. I'm talking across mobile. I'm talking on desktop
over 200 million
Okay. Oh, we've been new ost new ost. Hold on
Chrono trigger, this is a good one. This is a really good one one of my favorite games ever made in case you're curious
Resident sleeper on chrono trigger what chrono trigger is an awesome game
Oh, I mean you that's a real quick way to get fired from chat
Anime game. It's not it's not an anime game. It is what do you mean? It is. Yes. It is. No, it is not
Just because toriyama did the fucking slides doesn't mean that it's an anime game
Fuck that i'm taking up later. All right, i've made no problem. Yeah, I have look at this turn it up my pleasure
Is something oh no, okay. I thought the game crashed here's a fun fact about chrono trigger and uh a stupid dumb
moronic fact
Uh, they've re-released this game probably twice the amount like probably more than skyrim
Just make another one
Do it
You you had fucking god. Damn it
just make
Just make another one. What's stopping you? You know chrono trigger and chrono cross. They're such everybody loves them
They're like more loved than final fantasy seven
But let's let's bring the final fantasy seven three times
No, no, no, don't do it. There's only been two chrono games
Make another final fantasy
Quick do it rich 17
Oh my
I'm so i'm so flustered right now for a fucking chrono trigger
They had an opportunity. They had it trademarked
But they were like no, you know what oh
Hmm
Okay, I moved it over there. So it is
Chrono for smash
I don't know if that would ever happen. Isn't there a bunch of weird legality around the entire chrono franchise?
Not like five people tied to its inception and like that's why it's impossible to do anything with it
Just think this one's fine. What's wrong with this one? Nothing. Whatever
they made
Yeah, they yeah, they made fortnight instead of uh chrono break
Chrono cross was messy
But it was still a great game
You wanted something crazy about chrono cross
Why that game was so fucking cool?
they were
Playable characters and they're more than I think like 45 playable fucking party characters
That's just I mean, it's it didn't suck. It didn't suck. It was messy
It was messy
But it didn't suck
It really did suck
yeah, but if they had if if chrono break tied the whole series together and they made like a
Bring back like chrono bring back frog or you know, glen spoilers everybody. Sorry
Boomer rose tinted glasses. No, no, no, no, no go play chrono trigger right now
Do it right now close the spring
It's on every platform. Don't worry. You'll find it type in what platform is chrono trigger run for me
Chrono trigger is one of the best games ever made
Just do it right now. It's gonna take you like 30 or 40 hours to do
Put it on your christmas list. Don't worry. I just threw this in the
Stream chrono trigger, I I know I can't
Boomer streamer thinks the game he played when he was five is a good game. Oh, you guys have no idea
You have no idea. Come on. Are you serious?
This game is a cloud. The story is wonderful. It was about time travel
And like fucking up the future and fucking up the past. It was oh it was perfect
Anime plot this shit predated anime. This was like 1994
It predated all those terrible netflix original animes guys. Come on
Oh, no, here comes the chat for anime netflix. I mean i'm joking but you know what I mean
Yeah, what animes did we have back in like the 60s and 70s? We had speed racer
And then like dragon ball was made in like 78
And then chrono trigger
the pokemon
And the cura came out and that would mean that was wild
And then minecraft came up and changed everything
Whoa
A new item
What is this? I don't understand what this does. Is this just a better mop? This thing sucks. Am I using this wrong?
Broomer, I know it's a broom
Stop calling me broomer. Did anybody say that or did I just make that up?
I don't know. I'm like i'm having a paranoid moment here
No one said that
All right. I gotta pay attention. I have
He thinks he's streaming again. Jeremy, you gotta wake up. You think you're streaming
Compact broomer
I'm just so clumsy. I don't do this in real life. Just because my video game character has like a fat stomach
Okay
I think this room is pretty much good. Just a little bit more cleanup and we can go down to the basement
Wake up. Jeremy. It's been five years. I mean you I saw you in the other chat doing that a year ago
You know, I think i've seen you in that in another chat doing that. It's part of the dream. That was part of the dream
Get out of my fucking way
Who's the first person to call me a boomer? I really wonder
Who started that?
Yeah
How many tickets did you guys get when you played this level?
Max stack. Yeah, maybe the soundtrack alone will make some of you, uh
No, i'm not gonna keep pushing that i'm not gonna keep pushing like the boomer millennial thing. It's a great game
It's got a great soundtrack
Made by some of the most brilliant minds that are still making games
In the industry somebody said this the soundtrack the soundtrack is very meh
I want that person banned for life
Yeah, if you don't know what a lifetime ban here is
10 seconds the zoom beanie ost is better than this
Are you okay? Is the streamer taking drugs or is the chat member taking drugs? I'm not sure. No, I am sure
I'm not on drugs. So let me you know what I was going with that
Oh my god, god damn it. I don't take any drugs
Unless you count like Tylenol or caffeine
Sometimes this one was perfect. I think it's just music. It makes me really productive
Jenga
Oh, there's the magician inside that uh, little tent area. I don't actually know that this is uh,
This is the robot that you have to beat up for tickets
I love reminiscing about this game
Yeah, it's el gato
I said it's the robot that you beat up for tickets. I know what it is. I've played i've beaten this game 30 times
Is for as many years i've been alive beat it on stream
Maybe I would one day
but turn-based rpgs on twitch
I'm not sure how uh, i'm not sure how people will take that
I feel like it's a very like you got to be like known for that, right?
How many of you guys would want to sit through a me to play a full turn-based 60 hour rpg?
Really sure
Are you guys sure I played octogen for two days and you guys were trying to fucking
scream in my face
Don't octogen was fun. It was
That was a fun little game
All right. I think we're good in here
I'll do a final check later
See any of the blood down to the basement we go after I burn
If people watch fortnight, then people will watch anything
Yeah, but you understand like you guys
Don't want to watch fortnight
Oh god. Damn it. I don't have any water
No, not my gifts. Oh, come on
I just did this room
No, what the hell?
uh
This room is completed
Are you saying we wouldn't watch you play fortnight? Yeah, maybe it's like a joke for an hour
If I turn the stream on tomorrow
Oh, hey guys
So i'm going a different direction with the channel here. I'm gonna be playing fortnight three days a week
75 percent of you would leave
We've already talked about this
You know how many fortnight channels I already exist
What do I bring to the table?
Whoops, I got a headshot in the very beginning. I was player number 97
I'm out
You know, let's do that like 35 40 times
I can't believe this happened
I'm not gonna be better than everybody that plays
I don't i'm not like i'm not into br
It's uh, it doesn't doesn't do it for me
But what how else am I supposed to abbreviate it?
Burr
Royale
Battle royale
I guess that's not too hard to say actually never mind. All right, no more
Fucking dynamite
Come here. Come on. All right. Good. No more dynamite, please
fresh bucket
Play fortnight play fortnight play fortnight
I would never play fortnight
I just it's not it's not I know I understand. It's fun. It takes well, I don't know if that's true for me
If you think it's fun, i'm glad you do
But that's I can't I can't play the other games
It's it's actually fun
Hey, you didn't tell wow. Yeah, what a dumb boomer. He can't even make a fucking present bridge. Oh, yeah
Why am I accepting?
That like the boomer word
Why is that? Why am I saying that now? What have you guys done to me?
Okay
We're looking pretty good
All right. So basement it is what is down in the basement? We have that's not gonna take that long
We're getting close to being done a lot of bottles a lot of broken glass don't come down here with bare feet
That's a reindeer
Is that throwing these down here? I don't have a doormat, but this will work, right?
Get off of me
Why?
Okay
Hmm. How am I gonna do this?
I have to bring the trash down there. Forget about the water for now. Give me one of these
Again, do it again
Start from the back
Uh, maybe I should uh, yeah, I want a bucket too. Wait
We don't even need this anymore. It's not playing any music
Am I gonna play classic wow?
I don't think so
I just got big burnout the day the funk died
Oh, it's because I broke the boombox. Okay
We got our own boombox. Don't worry
Okay, would you guys be upset if I played this game way more?
because
I this yeah, I I like this game. I think I want to play it a lot more
It's something very therapeutic
And we could talk about fortnight
That went in my eye that went in my eye
Am I wearing glasses? I hope so
All right. We're gonna put these
up on the stairs
Get them all in the same place. So I don't
view down here
Safety goggles up, please
This is getting kind of full. Let's give it a little shake
Okay, that's better
Because now I can still fit stuff in it
We got a reindeer body
I'm gonna have to shake it another time
There's a battle theme battle theme. All right. I don't want to track dirt. Hold on
Got a lot of glass noises. Ah, it's all right. This is a really weird ride for this guy
Okay, I didn't track any dirt. What are you talking about? We're good. All right. I need another one
Press shift to walk. Oh just like that
crafting game
What the fuck was that? What the hell happened? What? What the fuck?
Alcohol in the bottles. I thought they were empty
This is uh the castle that's not gonna fit what is it a reindeer head made out of molotovs?
Is that thing gonna be fine? All right anymore reindeer
Antlers. Yeah, I gotta get rid of these. We're not gonna fit the box
I'm making a mess
Well, I have I have to make a mess first down here before I because these are gonna I have to take these one by one
They're not gonna fit in the box
And i'm trying to jump to not track this blood everywhere
Which i'm not this is the last piece
All right, let's get
Thank you for that
I want two buckets
Thanks again. Appreciate it
Thank you
Oh, i'm sorry. I bumped you
Now I need a box and this should be good because i'm gonna do one on either side
I don't even need a box. I got one right here
Where did this come from? When did I bring this down?
Okay, reindeer chunks
Okay
I think that okay, that's already done for me. See
that bucket's already full so we're gonna
Stick with that kind of theory here and just put fill these buckets
and then we have
Smaller amount of things to take up
Let's see if I can stuff him in here
No, just put him in the big one really fit in the big one
Upside down get in all right. That's as good as it's gonna get so you can fit in here. What is all this?
I'm gonna do another run here
Yeah, take it up
Yeah, well, I gotta come back
Give me another one
I can see the finish line. So can I
This is a lot
More fun than I remember it being a long time ago
That this is i'm having a great time. I really am
Any of the dangerous stuff up here? No, this one's pretty much done. I will have to i'll go through and check the uh the ecto
thing
All right
I need another box
Play simpsons hit and run
I will
Not now
i'm cleaning up
Something okay almost ready for the mop and I get two buckets down here
Just need to bring up the last bits and pieces
Give a shake
Good make him play the contra ost
Contra
Why contra?
So this is it after this I just mop up and make sure everything's done
What was the estimated play time for this one four or five hours? I did it in like three
What the fuck?
Okay, and we just got the little nerf pellets. I gotta bring this over here. It's gonna be paying the ass
Right there so now i'm gonna I can turn and just be real real clean about it the boss fight
But not a real boss fight. This is like a a mid-level boss
Not to be confused with a real boss. You'll know what that is when you hear it really
Uh, where'd it go? Okay. Well, whatever it's time to stop mopping
back wall
This would be so clean. I'm gonna get an a plus
That one's dirty
All right. Next one
This is really bloody down here. It's gonna take a while
This is a frog song
Unless you that are curious. Why am I the dj?
And coming up next we have frog song from uh chronic trigger
This song played when anytime frog was on the screen
Coming at you soon here. Uh
kxw 9 1 1 4 5
frogs theme
905.3 the rat you're listening
Don't spill i'm not gonna spill ready
Uh-huh
Hey, look, we won. This is a victory theme
I need a few of these
I forgot I had this here. It's all right. I packed it so well then nothing's gonna fall out
uh fun fact, uh, that was frogs theme turning into uh victory or uh
Hold on the court. Uh, I need to get everything empty from here. Let's take this because this is just one bucket
I was holding shift and
This whole thing is dumping out god give me a break
Oh
It's because I was holding shift and I was being careful. I should just fucking walked out
so if I was doing a speed run, uh speed runners of this game if that just happened would you would that be like a
fuck reset moment
And the reset would be really quick too. It would be like
And they're starting again. It'd be like click click click click click click and do game
All right. Um, let's get this out of here. I'm walking. I'm not running. I'm walking
All right, give me another one. Give me another bucket. I want two
Give me another
Incinerator
And I have to use this right now because of this stupid shit here
They give you the zombie parts. I just want a thing to put people in
The finish line it is inside. Nobody said that but the finish line is in sight
Stop the stream. I'm trying to eat
So good luck with that right now
still eating
That was real. I don't know why I'm sorry about that
I'm sorry
This just think of it like this this is just barbecue
See that's barbecue sauce. This is like a nice spare rib
Well, there's like a chunk of brisket. Just think of it like that
See, this is spare rib
Okay off screen like look at it off screen if I told you that this was forget about where we can see the hand right there
If I told you this was like a nice barbecue spare rib right now. Look at it like right there
You wouldn't be able to know what if you were vegan? Well, then you wouldn't be eating it. Anyway
It's the courtroom part two. All right. I fucked this all up because i'll be an idiot
I'm just in one of those moods today for some reason
All right, let's take this downstairs
People are eating
Well every time there's something gross on the screen. Just look away
Yeah, can I just put the whole fucking bucket in there?
All right. Oh, can I stack the buckets in each other? I gotta weigh it down. I'm walking
Okay, watch out for this watch out for that perfect. All right, let's go back to what I was doing down here
It's a new bucket of water
And then I can do the final pass through that's got to go
That's gonna get me points docked if that stays down here
Uh, just you stay down here for now
This is in the future as it happens and get to the future
All right looks pretty clean back here except the bucket. Okay
Right, that's there
Uh, how am I gonna put these in a container to bring up? Is that all the bring this out of here?
Just put it on the table
What are you this can go in there too?
Get another box over here that I don't need actually yeah, I do I need to put the
Flash drives in there. What's in here?
Oh, right. Okay
Uh, i'm gonna get rid of this now that leaves me with this
to put
Some small remaining stuff in like these flash drives
And i'm gonna dump them in front
the front door
That's gonna give me some points
Okay, where's that bucket?
This is too dirty
Yeah
I can't put the bucket in here. Shit. It's so I gotta walk back
I'll clean it up later. Don't worry
We're on crunch time here now
If I spilled this i'm gonna be very upset
See that doesn't count. It's inside the fire
What else is down here?
Okay
Need to get this out of the way
There's no more items
I need a bucket. Hey, look, it's a bucket. I need it right here
Only the final room is the entryway and then I can clock out
I'll dump that in there. Just turn it upside down and i'll throw this away
I can't
I jumped over it. See? All right, here we go
Uh, i'm gonna leave that one for trash
Because they're probably stray trash
Where's my bucket?
I did it. I didn't spill it
Okay
Down here and then just clean up the blood and that should be it
And I can do the final room
Hopefully there's not that much where I need a second bucket, but there probably will be
It's already getting a little dirty
Shit, i'm gonna need another bucket. Ah
Or am I?
Hmm. It's yeah. Yes, I do
Give me another bucket. Am I ever gonna play mother of three?
earthbound two
Earthbound was mother two, right?
Uh
Put this in here
Oh, by the way, there is I there's dynamite in there. Yep
Goodbye
Is that uh, it's not a controlled blast though. What the fuck what?
On the table I knew there was dynamite in there but the one on the table to the right
I knew there was dynamite in that one. That's why I did it but I thought
How are you supposed to get rid of those?
Script a joke. No, I knew there was dynamite in there. I said it as I was walking up
But so if you put dynamite in the water, but then what happens when you throw that in the trash?
Okay, hold on if you put dynamite
In water and then you put the dynamite into the fire. Doesn't it just blow up?
Just don't throw it away. No, it doesn't it doesn't no. I knew I put the dynamite in that one
I just didn't know if it was gonna
Set off the why am I putting this over here?
Not a controlled burn in the trash
Why would that happen?
No, he fucking scripted it. Oh, it was scripted
See he knew that was gonna happen and that's why he did it
Notice the frame notice the frame right before he puts look I froze it here
Notice the frame right before he walked forward. He glanced to the right a little
To make sure that he was in line of sight for the other explosion
And what he did is he then he made sure he was close enough
And then he stepped a step to his right to make sure he got blown up. I I recorded it and I saw it
uh
Got five community subs
by chungi
Thank you for the five community subs
He admitted it
No, I didn't I was pretending to be somebody
That was pretending to think that I did that on purpose
But did he?
Uh that and that's an anonymous gifter
10 community subs from
nobody
from anonymous
Whoever anonymous is thank you so much
Thank you for the 10 community subs. Thank you for uh, and then chungi came in with another five. That's 10 from chungi here
That's 20 community subs in like 30 seconds
Thank you
Thank you to the both of you
All right. Hold on. Hold on a minute. Let me uh, hold on. Yeah, let me script out something here
Make sure I get this like, you know, I got I have to sit her in that plan this
It's okay chair. Oh fuck
Uh the spaz and jammy both giving up five community subs. Thank you both of you guys
Thank you guys both of you
You guys are awesome
script scripted subs
Oh my fucking god, oh no
Oh god
That's
That's 20
20 community subs from basic feral my god
that's a lot
I've actually I took a look at some of the uh
Some of the community subs that people have given some people have given almost 100 more than 100 community subs
That's fucking crazy. Thank you guys. Thank you. Oh man get in the clown car 10 community subs mo five community subs
What's that? Almost a hundred?
You guys are you guys are very kind. Thank you
the spaz another five
Five community subs from spaz
What else do I need to clean? Do I have to pick up the bird's nests?
It's going too fast. I don't know if it was who was picked
pilot guy five community subs
Thank you
I wasn't looking at I was looking at the chat because there's a lot of fender. Uh mcbender for five community subs
Pilot guy giving up five fender mcbender five
Oh my goodness
Oh, it's the best song. This is robo song. This is this is my favorite character in the whole game
Lula, thank you lula for the five community subs
That's oh look at how many fucking darts are down here cozy. Thank you cozy brother for the five community subs
Oh lord
This is just rick roll. Yeah, and it sounds pretty similar, but it's not it's not that song
It's not rick roll. Uh, this has just been ruined for me
Uh, thank you spaz for the five community subs
fuck I know
We phone
Why is this the rick astley rick roll song?
no
Multi trip thanks for five community subs
Five subs from multi trip five subs from from we phone
Did you really not know? I mean, I I thought about it
Where's mine? Maybe one day if you're somewhat generous person from chat
But thank you guys. That was fucking crazy
It really is
Spaz five more subs from spaz
Got it
Spaz gave a shitload. There's so many of you just gave so many subs
Okay
Blood on the bird's nest
Not anymore
This is pretty good
Chungi is back
with more
Attack of the hawk five community subs
Holy shit. All right. Don't blow this up. What do I do with this?
Can I like what am I gonna put it? Okay, I'm gonna put this in the water because it's an explosive
What?
Oh my thank you spaz for five community subs
Let's get the shit out of me
Oh my god, just get rid of it
Thank you guys for all your subs. It's so many
It's so fucking many
You guys are something else. Thank you
All these subs and all he manages to do is rick roll and spill jokes
You got to take the joke off of it. Can't it just be a spill?
Does the joke have to be on the other end of that? Is it can't it just be I spilled?
What?
I was just like I was just like lost internet there
I think I laughed too hard. The internet wanted to turn off doctor. Thank you doctor mo thord
five subs
Spaz five more subs. I can't even keep up with it. You guys have given so many. Thank you
I don't know what to say anymore. You spend a lot of money a lot of you guys
Step up again
What?
Is it the end of time?
I'm still why am I still dictating the soundtrack of chrono trigger for you guys? Just play the game
It's one of the best games ever just play it
All right, what's left?
How's this one? This is uh the end of time. It's uh plays quite a bit in this series
What am I like a song review channel?
End of the stream voice. I have to finish this level first
Oh that okay. That is the end of the stream voice. You're right
Okay guys, so um, I think uh
well, uh
Okay
by the way, I want to make sure everyone's aware that the uh, I hope you got a suggestion in
For the secret santa chat secret santa christmas suggestion
because the polls
Well, not the polls the suggestions in that discord
Are are now
I think pretty much officially closed
Somebody said I forgot i'm sorry, but I really have to get stuff ordered for christmas eve stream
So really can only give about 24 hours or like 30 hours or so of time
Why did I just put that present in the fire? I don't know. What's this?
It was my birthday friday. Mommy got me only 23 presents and a soccer field cake
I hate her. I said you were better. I want 23 steak pies 12 ice creams 18 trays of reindeer chocolate three big
big boxes
A fudge a pair five computer with conscription three brown
And an intend night a nitro genie whatever fuck off
This is the trainer stop. I don't okay. I'm not gonna tell you what another song is
But I love this song though. It's blood on the door frame. I'll take care of that
Where I think that's it?
The other door
This is not a door
You should have said the exploded wall door
Door
All right. We are close
so close
Is only
Grandpa's study the grandpa. Um, what the fuck is this place?
I don't know. Watch this
Molotov cocktail
No, apparently not the mt. Is that the problem?
That one's still there
All right, what can I
No, it didn't do anything
That's water in there spaz gave another 10 community subs
You have to be reaching some kind of extreme level here
Next slide, please
I think we're running through like a rough patch right now. Sometimes it happens. It's eggnog. Yeah, but eggnog is
Alcoholic is it non-alcoholic eggnog?
But yeah spaz that you've you've given so many
Yeah, sometimes you get a rough patch. The internet was fixed
uh
Like a month or two ago
But sometimes it still does happen. Sometimes it's a little dip that lasts probably five to ten minutes and then it smooths up
Usually unless something else went wrong, but I don't think so
All right
I want a new playbox 180 and a new y-phone 732 s and the new racer man car driver game
I also want a new bike because the one I got last year is dirty and I want a new windbreaker air rifle too
I've been so good and I want these is this eggnog thick and slimy 100 foreign
uh
Wonders of pride and I don't understand
That it's another no alcohol on this
Happy christmas this year. I want a new
Dear too long
I have in my possession video footage of you along with your gang entering one of my premises via the fireplace
The footage also shows littering and you personally removing my valuable property milk glass and confectionery items
At present i'm preparing to forward this evidence to the local authorities unless I receive compensation from your organization in the sum of no less than
100 000 dollars
I've generously decided to give you until monday to complete this transaction or face the consequences
Mr. Claus it is with a heavy heart and dwindling pocket that would regret to inform me that you are being sued in the amount of 250 000
Dollars the claims are as follows destruction of property damages emotional suffering public disturbance and obscenity
Apparently your reindeer had defecated across a house or houses as they passed by the area
Where was I keeping these to make sure I had them right here
Mr. Claus you'll tie greeting for squads and represent a select group of people with great gift-giving ambitions
Oh boy
uh
I'm in jail again and need bail money. I was caught
whip
What the fuck are these letters?
It's great regret that I find myself forced to write this correspondence once more as our investigation determine the atrocities conditions
When you force upon elven brethren must cease immediately the low pay the incredibly long workdays the lack of holidays
It's inhuman if we go to if we at the union do not see a radical change we'll be forced to pursue legal
Channels and then sir you shall see the full fury of the elves
Is not so small
invoice your total for this month comes to toys 953 000 dollars
Five million for electronic devices 35 000 for shipping
Streamer hates unions. What? No, I was I was looking at the
They said they were coming after me. So I wanted to just burn it
Oh
No, stop it. I
Stop it cocks. I know really
You want to get over this like weird internet hiccup you got going on right now for some reason
I need a box in here. I kind of ruined everything over there. All right, I need a box
Hey, uh, no, i'm not gonna do it. I'm i'm gonna break up. I'm not gonna say the b e t e r
I'm not gonna say p e t e r
I almost did it. I was going to say it. You're right. It was close
This is your favorite song from a corner trigger
The whole soundtrack is great
I'm not gonna what's spider-man's real name?
p e t e r
p a r
k e r
How am I gonna get under there? How do I get under there?
I can't get that bullet that's over there
Is this alcohol?
Yeah
There we go. Nice
Short stream by the way, I know I gotta get like I gotta get this shit ready and ordered and everything
i'm not
live tomorrow
get
What is it hitting?
Just take it and get rid of it. Yeah, i'm not gonna be around tomorrow
I'm gonna spend pretty much the whole day
I got doctor appointment and then I want to get shit ready for tonight and then get shit ready tomorrow and make sure everything is
Ready to go completely
for the christmas eve stream
You'll see me again on saturday. Oh my god
Don't be dynamite. Okay, I can handle that
Does that mean
Okay, whatever
They really just don't want me to be able to end this do they
The sub notifications are still going
There was so many
There was so many subs
All right. Don't make the same mistake you make every time
Just place it on the table
There no explosion
Yeah, the the
The subs were out of control
All the community subs all the subs that this channel has so many subscribers now. It's fucking crazy
Honest to god
Thank you guys
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
I'm gonna have a lot of uh extra points to give out here
And speaking of subs five more from spaz
my god
Thanks, dude
I gotta get under there
How do I get under there?
Do I have to baseball swing?
Oh, look at that figure it out never answered my mother three question. Well, I have to play
mother one and mother two
Before I play mother three
Yeah, I know who lucas is because I made him in brawl
Get get over here
Let me know I didn't this I did
Did I get it?
Ah, it felt really good to get
I gotta go around
Come on
Did I loosen it?
Oh, it's like getting popcorn out of your teeth. Come on
go
Got it
Where did I?
nice
And what do you do? You put it back in your mouth and you ate it
Somebody know what that is
Come on. Somebody has to know what that is. I'm waiting for someone to know who is who's if that is
Are you serious?
None of you. Wow
I'm surprised
That was george carlin
Are you guys saying who?
Oh, i'm right collect
It's a meme song
Why is this a meme song? What are you talking about?
meme song
George rr martin is the guy that will never write the whole story of a song in ice and fire
song of ice and fire
He's thinking of two different people
Oh my god
Well, you see it's almost done. You see what what what tyrion wants you wants to split the thing is let me tell you something
Uh in about 10 years
I by the way, I write with one finger
Get in the clown car. Thank you for the 10 community subs
10 more from getting the clown car
Well, you see that's the thing is
I I just
I I when I write I usually write very slowly and it's it's
It takes me about four months to write one page
And that's okay, but as you know, I just love what I mean
He's
That's not owen wilson
I mean it kind of is
Don't hit that that's gonna explode sit up here
You say well, wow. The thing is when I wrote that book
What the fuck
No, what's going on with my internet? Why is it doing this again?
Cut it out cocks. It's not funny anymore
Okay, this is dirty
I'm looking over at obs to see how many frames i'm dropping
Because I need to know like I can't even see after I have to alt tab
All right. That's good to go. This is pretty much all done
Always funny spill joke. It's not always funny
What did I just knock over?
I don't know. I think that's good
I'm sure the bookcases are all clean
Norway is fine. This room is done
Let me just set up
All right. We're done
Let's get this out of here
And then i'll double check
Okay basement. I love this comment basement stable bright wall
You got it
I'll get it
Right click the painting what painting
This painting
I don't what do you want to do that for that's a fucking way did that come from did I just spawn that?
With hands what do you do anything?
Where did this come from the painting? That's a poster
It doesn't do anything
Okay, I need to dispose of this
So we got water
Right here
Here we go. Ready
What what the fuck was that? Okay, so this is not gonna light on fire. You guys told me once it's in water
It can't be lit on fire
Right
Okay. Thanks for the lie. Thanks for lying to me. Appreciate it
Thanks for the lie
If you put it in water
It won't it's you throw it in the fire and it's fine
That wasn't just one guy. It was like 40 people
That was 40 guys
Keep it in the water
What?
I I drenched it. I dunked it
How do you
Whatever. This is done now
What is going on? Why are they spawning?
Okay, well
So you're telling me
See it is now impossible for this to light
Keep it in the bucket and then put the bucket in the fire
What the hell was that?
Did it work?
It worked. It's gotta stay in the bucket. No, i'm not
I'm gonna just put the fucking dynamite in a box and put over under the tree
It fell out of the bucket
That doesn't matter
That does not matter at all
Why did I turn into a broom?
Where does this broom come from?
What the hell is this?
What is that?
What is this thing?
Whatever, okay, if there's another stick of dynamite in here i'm gonna be fucking mad. All right, we're good
Okay, i'm done. I'm I just need to clean up a little bit more. No more random spawns of dynamite
I gotta get rid of my old body
This is just like diablo 2 man, except I where's my gear?
Whatever one of you guys went
Remember when this only took two hours?
Yeah, I do
I didn't remember you paper watch father members
Hey, do you guys remember when
It's with heavy heart and generally probably that we inform you that you all were being sued. Yeah, whatever
That joke ran out fucking like a year ago
Use the tnt on the wall for a secret room
Well, I don't have any more
We were done a long time ago
And then just keep I keep fucking it up
Hit the rock painting with mop
The rock painting
All right. I I you can't think i'm that much of a fucking dummy
Use tnt on the broken wall to fix it
What
That's not real
What the fuck anymore? That's cool. There's secrets
rock painting
Okay. Now use what the fuck? Okay. Use this now on so much dynamite
Where am I using this?
dynamite the cellar door for a secret room
And how am I supposed to get this down to the cellar?
This is going to blow up my face before I go down here wall in basement. Which wall?
lantern
Use the lantern. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Hold on
So use the dynamite on this door here
Okay
How do I pick it up? Can I pick this up? Can I knock this up?
Get another lantern
You can I can molotov that
Just hit the dynamite with a broom
Are you sure? Oh my god, i'm scared
Holy shit, they weren't lying to me. That actually works
Uh, it didn't do anything
The model had blow up the door wrong wall
It wasn't in the right spot. Got to use another one. I don't think so. I ain't gonna get fucking derailed
ball tennis ball
Ah
I'm gonna do it. It's a red spot. Where exactly do you want me to put this?
Right there there red spot. That's blood
That's blood right wall. Why am I doing this right there right there right there turn on the click map
No blue spot blue spot
This is blue. Show me right over there. Is that what you're talking about?
Okay, i'm fucking out of here
Isn't this secret fucking blow up the door bullshit?
And now look what you made me do. Oh, all right. I'm done. I'm cleaning up and i'm i'm gonna put the
SD cards into the slots and then that's it
That's the oldest trick in the book
I don't know. This has been out for like a couple years. You guys might know secrets that I don't know
That's very possible
All right, we're close
Why would there be?
An unlit tnt if there wasn't a secret. Well, because didn't I already blow up the wall already?
Why would I throw that?
Why would I throw it like that like immediately?
All right
Save the tnt for the santa fight
That has to be bullshit, right? All right broken bottle
We're almost done a couple of streaks. I'll take care of that
Ah
I don't know why I don't know what that was
I immediately did not know what I was doing. Oh paintball
I'm gonna i'm gonna tidy up the place a little bit make it look nicer
So I get extra points
All right
This room is good to go. This is nice and cleaned up presents are up on the table
down here
Let's pull out the meter
How would you not pick this up?
This one's done
Wait, wait, wait
Right here. There's an elf in the chat. What are you talking about? Wait a minute. What's the problem over here?
Look an elf what no don't hit that. I think I got it. There's an elf up on the shelf. All right, is that it?
Come here come here. I got you
Elf on the shelf. That's what you guys are referring to. Okay, I get it
All right, is that it? I think that I think this room is clean. It's a blood on the ceiling
It can't be clean while you're in it. What was that? I just saw a drip what just dripped. Did you see that? Am I insane?
Okay, all right done. Take a look perfect clean
Satisfied same thing with this room. Let's tidy it up. There's still blood in there. No
I ain't blowing up any more walls with dynamite. You ain't gonna get me. I'm not nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
yeah, uh
we got a problem with the
The boy who cried wolf here there could be something really important, but all I'm gonna hear is throw dynamite
Throw dynamite at door is all I hear. I gotta get there's a lot of blood in the ceilings
I'm not tall enough to do this. How am I gonna get that? Is that even possible to get? I don't think I can get this
Are you kidding me right now?
Yeah, and there are my stools. Did I burn them? Yeah, who said I couldn't do it, huh? Right click that what that's what I'm doing
What are you talking about wet the mop?
What do you wet the mop? God damn it. I need to get up there. This should be it
I don't care if I have to do four I'll get it because then I can get up there
Well, it's gonna be one more. It's gonna have to be four get a present on there, too
Okay, I'll jump from here up to there and then I should be able to get it from here
Press tab to extend them up
You fucking guys give me this present. What are you doing? Get on get
on there
I'm gonna get on this. This is cuphead level journalist gaming
No, it is not. This is fucking annoyingly hard to do
cuphead level
Journalist gaming how dare you say something like that to me? Got it
I'm just gonna say it ain't gonna happen, but I could do four right there use the middle table
That's the one I was just on the one I was just on I couldn't reach with three
I gotta get to four. This is one of the other best songs. This is the the the epoch
What there could be a little bit of blood on the ceiling now, it's time to go there you go ready
I got it. It's gonna be four
One two, three, there are enough stools to do four wrong way. That's the one that's gonna be four right in the middle fuck
One two, three four. Oh god. Damn it
I
Just need to get these I have to approach from this way
I got laughing gas what do I do? I just need to get
All right, one two one two three. Here's two. No
Oh
This is fun, all right one two, I just gotta get this one up here
There's the one two three
Am I gonna have enough stools to do this dumb shit?
Yep, I will. All right. I'm gonna go very slow with this. Oh my I
Can't even look this way. I have to just guess. Oh my god. I'm up. Okay. Where am I? That's one two
Holy fuck. Okay, go go go. I can do it fucking god
What what did you say? What did you just say? What did you say? Did you you said grab the ladder?
That's in the basement. What where is it? What are you talking about? Grab the ladder in the basement? Oh, I get it
I'm fucking throwing a bucket up there. Is that gonna work? I don't think it's gonna work
I is there a reliable way that I can actually get this cuz building stools. It seems not possible
Presence for the press to throw them off at the ceiling at this point
I'm willing to try that but I can't how is he still trying cuz I have to get that
There's so much blood up on the ceiling. How did it even get up there?
Wait, yeah, fuck this get this all out of here. Are you serious?
Give me like four of these. It's the surface I can tear. This is so much more surface area
He's I thought I just killed somebody over there. No, what are you doing? Okay right here. Can I jump on these?
I'm not tall enough. This is not gonna work. I have to be fucking tall enough. I need a stool
Okay, I need to get up there. Come here. Why can I not grab it? What the fuck?
I wasn't staying I'm standing on the other one. You thought I dropped it. So did I why is this not working?
Are you serious? Stop giving me this shit. What's on here? Get off
You're ruining everything. Where am I? What the fuck is happening? Why did I just what am I gonna do with all these buckets?
Having a breakdown. I'm having a breakdown
Get on
Don't fuck it up. What are you doing? Hey, you're a dud. I'm almost done. Almost just do one
That's how I feel right now. I feel like screaming like that. This is it one two three. Got it. This is it
Yes
Yes, what about over there? Is there any more? I don't think there's any more up here. I made a fucking mess. Oh
Shit over there. I think I can reach that just by jumping on one though. Oh, yeah, I got it
Thank the Lord
Wait, I did it. Okay. This is the I won the game music
No, did I get flood on the ceiling?
I didn't just do that. Did I I didn't just do that
There's no way I just did that
No, oh no, nobody saw
Oh
Burn it all burn it all I'm done. Just pretend you didn't see it burn it get it all over there burn it
Forget it. Who cares?
Get this fucking stool out of here. Get over here
It was all done and look at all this shit that has to burn and the stools have to be set back up
Well, what about the stools? Where are the children going to sit get them in there?
I can't fucking believe it two steps forward four steps backwards
Burn it all. I don't even see this anymore
You see this present? Yeah, see you later
Blood and fire. I'll get the blood in the fireplace. I know
I'm so disappointed
That's so unsightly. Oh so mad
Pick it up. Oh, we got married. This is the married song
What emote is that ha ha ha look at how clean it is in here don't do that in here
Look at how perfect it is. And look at how I fucked up this whole room. I was done. We were about to turn it off
Pick it up. I
Love this game. What a fucking joy
Hey, Merry Christmas everybody
Just leave
I've been in here for like four and a half hours. I
Can't just leave I have gamblers fallacy. I'm not betting any money. I'm cleaning a house
Getting there. Okay
Those splats came from
it's from
the little paintballs
Okay, so let's finish this up. What the hell?
Why what's it supposed to play mother three? No, don't fucking do that to me. Just put this in the trash
But any more of those
We are pretty much done after this is to get the little side room there I
Can actually get that by standing on a stool? I think yeah, I'm good. It's good. It's good. It's good
Don't worry about it go in. All right, we're close
Remember all the presents that were in this room
But the explosions destroy them all all right final pass through on this room is gonna be here in a second
All right, how we look? Oh, this needs to be picked up. See they look nice
I'm just going to put these down in the ground. Just they're just gonna sit here right there. I'm not touching them
They just display. Oh, okay. I think that's it. This room looks good. This room is looking better
Okay, what else?
Should I just get one of the boxes and just give me a box so I have to keep running back and forth
All right any stray trash, okay, maybe you should check the ceiling now. See things all right
I don't even need to look at it. All right good
Everything looks good except for that. There's a present under there, but it's okay
I mean the sniffer is gonna find the blood. I mean, there's a lot. I gotta dump this first. No, I don't
Hey buddy, I think you missed a spot on the ceiling there
Glass bottle. Let me check up here one more time. I did. Yeah, there's like explosions and shit
Put the wood in the fire who cares
Think that's good last little bit here. I think we're good the entrance. All right, don't worry
I've worked my way all the way back to the entrance. I think I don't know what this is. This is autoplay. Yes
Got it. Okay, clean up the eggnog and that's gonna do it fireplace. Yeah. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on
Look at that. It looks great. No, it only took us about four hours more than that probably
Okay
Basement last check in the basement. What what is this? Is this parts of the Caribbean? Yeah, it is
This is from Dead Men Tell No Tales
By the way, anybody watch Dead Men Tell No Tales and
Think the whole movie that you were watching Johnny Depp do a bad Johnny Depp impression. It's weird. All right
Entrance and then we're done. Forget about the one splat on the ceiling. Let the oh
Don't be body parts. Okay, good
Let's start our
You start our turn in you know our quest turn in hit the screen. What? No, I'm just checking it out
Come on get it. I'm gonna rack up so many points for this. Did anybody like how much would he get for doing this?
Why was that pitch shift down? All right, so let me
Let's not track dirt everywhere get this in here fill it up
Only no, it won't be long now. No, just a few minutes
And yes, I did say this was gonna be like a three-hour stream
But I got addicted to the game and it became like this is a lot of fun. I'm definitely gonna be playing this again
Like I'm yeah, this is now a clean houses channel house flipper DLC
What the hell was that? Oh trash and run out of space here
I think that's the only thing left and then it's the mop and then we do the final pass. I
Don't want it. I'm gonna get dirty shoes here. Oh, no. Okay. Now. This is Monster Hunter world. Okay
All right, just a little bit more and we're done
Perfect a final
Box to dump in the trash. I did it. He's actually blind. What are you talking about? What one guy?
It's over. It's over. It's done. Merry Christmas
What can I get this? All right, perfect. Nothing in here clean. Did you clean upstairs? Oh, yeah, what's wrong?
What's it? Why is it doing this? Oh cuz the fucking thing on the ceiling
Okay, it's done. Take a look at this clean house. Maybe what it looked like before look at it's so cozy
One shotgun shell. Ah, two shotgun shells you meant to say. Ah, okay. I think we're good. It's done
There's a stool knocked over where no, this is clean down here clean. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What's wrong here? No, it's it's like
We're great. It's like over here. Do I have to get rid of the TNT? Everything's clean in here. Whatever. Fuck it
All right, that's it. Yay. Merry Christmas, but do I get like a score? All right, let's go
C-minus no buckets. No random shit everywhere. Ah, oops. That's it. That was fun. All right clock out
I'm proud of my performance and certain it will meet with approval
I wish I could do more for my company. Give me some paperwork to fill up. I don't care
I'm I'm proud of my performance employment review project closure. You left Santa's workshop after carefully preserving every treasured
Christmas item there's a weird
Okay, as well as cleaning the workshop
Although you're not sure if you ever get over the horror you witnessed at least you treated the tragedy with a measure of dignity
With your holiday joy now forever lost you wonder if it was enough sure while the thought of maybe one day earning employee of the month
And picturing the shiny presence being treated with respect
Eases your heart the morbid look on massacre to elephant faces will haunt you for years to come
Okay
Assessment, what's my assessment? That's an a
Incident reports IR eight concerning Santa's workshop. What's an IR eight? I are eight
I didn't do paperwork
Blood spot on the door. So they give it you get a little office. That's cool
What happens if I fuck up the office you have to clean up my office? Oh, no, no, don't break this
I need this probably post office burns down a post service office in the North Pole is burned down following careless
Handling of package from recently restored Santa's workshop
What package said to contain a Molotov cocktail? What the fuck happened?
certificates, oh
That's cool
All right. Well, this is a lot. Oh cool. That's what the sounds that come from. All right
Well, I left a Molotov cocktail. That's not what I'm gonna save. This is fucking fun
All right. I gotta get out of here. That was a lot of fun, but I do have to go I have to
I gotta get this shit ready for Christmas Eve
We're gonna play this again. This is that I love this game. What a fun game
Time to I'm gonna go clean my house in real life. Yeah
Yeah, I was only supposed to string for like a few hours because I have to go do package
Ordering and to make sure all these things can get here. Thank you, by the way for all the suggestions
I don't know what they were but I'm sure they will be very very fun looking forward to it
Where was Shrek? I'll do that next stream. We're gonna play Shrek next time. I didn't think this is gonna take this long
I had too much fun dicking around. When is the stream? The stream is gonna be Christmas Eve
So I will not see you guys tomorrow tomorrow. I'm gonna be off
I have a doctor's appointment and I'm doing other stuff with the Christmas Eve stream and then I'll be back on Saturday
I might just play this again on Saturday. Well, maybe Atlas if it works, who knows maybe it'll get delayed again. We'll see
There's like seven or eight more campaigns that I haven't even looked at so but yeah, I've taken off. Thanks for hanging out
There was a shitload of community subs tonight. Thank you for those and
If we're gonna get to the bits, let's go back all the way back about four and a half five hours ago or so
Here we are right here
So I'll see you guys on Saturday
That was a lot of fun. Thank you sticks renegade for the one dollar. I found these berry
Beery kicks today and I was so happy. I haven't had berry kicks in 12 years
Also, my friend gave me French toast crunch cereal and I just realized the sell-by date was January
11th 2018 should I eat it the sell-by date that hadn't oh
Probably not. No, that's almost a year ago
That's gonna be stale as hell. I wouldn't do it. Lucky charms is my favorite cereal. It's I love it
Captain crunch lucky charms. They're great, especially lucky charms. I haven't had it in a while though
Mostly lost. Thanks for the one dollar bugs rats dildos and sandwiches is my next band name hashtag charity
If you missed the beginning of the stream, we're talking about things is not to suggest the mods pick
For suggestions on what I'm going to have purchased to open on stream. Hey Divis. Thanks with three bucks
No message. Just thank you Divis. It was P
Ah bonjour
I'm just saying bonjour to you guys. That's it
Deviant thank you deviant for the one dollar. Thank you. Swiggy swanky for the one dollar
This game is probably more traumatizing than that birdhouse story. I told a while back. I don't know why that was a pretty traumatizing story
That was a really traumatizing story on your
Zarathos plays thanks for the five dollars. They just say hi dad. Hello son. Thank you for the five dollars
Bonjour again, but I just want to say it bonjour actually bonjour Tristan gave a dollar. Thank you
Flank tank one dollar from flank tank. Hey, German. Just want to say I look up to you. Well
Let's just say I respect you. Sorry. Oh, I get it
bunny
Bunny, but thanks for the one dollar. Oh
fucking meatloaf again ma
That's supposed to be is that Will Ferrell?
Gaming hash. Thanks for the dollar 15. This is seriously the most I've ever laughed. Also burn buckets. I had a blast
That was those almost five straight hours of just oh man. I I loved this game
This game like on sale right now. Go get it. You don't have it. Why are the games?
I like the most where you do mundane chores. Oh house flipper. Definitely one of my favorite games
You just like put up walls and and paint walls and shit. Why do I why is this?
Because it's relaxing. Yeah, it just is
Thank you. Jamie for the one dollar German heart hashtag charity. Thank you Todd flower. Thanks for the one dollar local streamer cleaner burns
Nelves, oh, that's a gnome thing. Okay. Thank you bet three for the five dollars. Here's your fursona, sir
Oh god, thanks pet three for the five dollars
Good stuff. Thank you jerk TC for the ten dollars. Hi, can you clean my bathroom hashtag charity?
No, I don't I I would know I don't want to clean somebody else's bathroom. You like you like shit in there
You use that bathroom, you know, I don't want no I'll clean your room. I'll get I'll clean your oven
No, you got to clean your own like toilet. You know what I mean? I'm weird like that
I have to clean my own toilet and no one else can do that. What if I shit in my oven?
Well, then that would make you a very strange person. Well, thank you jerk for the ten dollars. Appreciate it
Freudian weapon. Thanks with the one dollar Freudian. You done good kid. Hey, thanks. I tried
Flank tank. Thanks for the one dollar. Also to those who know and care
HH was shut down
Dancing crab meme. I don't know. What is that? Hey HH
How Howard Hughes? I don't know what that is. Well, thank you
Thank you. Yodel man for the one dollar
Appreciate it
Stank goblin. Thanks for the one dollar death grips. No, I had we had to have video game music playing. Thank you stank goblin
Thank you sticks ready to get again for one dollar. I'm watching Seinfeld for the first time today from beginning to end
I've never really sat down and appreciated it. I love it so far
Well, I got news for you. If you like Seinfeld if you actually think it's funny
curb your enthusiasm is
In my opinion is a superior program. I think that I like Seinfeld. I I don't know
I don't like the studio audience thing though. I never have but Larry David in curb your enthusiasm is
especially
Especially curb your enthusiasm starts off kind of slow
You're gonna be like, this is not funny. You're gonna watch like the first four episodes and go. I don't like this
This is stupid. Don't don't do that
You got seasons like two through eight of curb your enthusiasm is some of the most hilarious television I've probably ever watched
Every first season of a TV show is weak. I stopped in the first season hypo
Yeah, but that that's what I mean. The first especially the first couple episodes is just
Like oh, there's like two guys kind of arguing with each other. That's like the whole episode. Okay. Well that
This so there's so much more after that first season, especially the first few episodes skip the first season
No, you can't
Is it on Amazon Prime?
No, I think it's on it's on HBO
If you have HBO now or HBO go if it is on Amazon Prime, that's actually pretty cool
It is well more reason to just watch it while it's there. It's a great show. Thank you
Blumpkin
So did I actually just thank you for the $1?
Fuck she's island athletic theme is the song you are looking for
Thank you so much, dude. Why did I say that? I don't know. I just have read the name. I just read I read name
Why I?
It's alright. Don't worry about it. It's gonna be fine
It's gonna be okay. I
Read name every name we rename no use brain
Whatever. It's okay. Thank you for the $1 though. Thank you sir rock for the $1 play hotline Miami to Shrek
Hashtag charity. I will just not right now. Not today. I'll play the Shrek
Merry Christmas
Pulled it off. Well, I mean I did I did say that at one point you do you're are you're all right?
And that was a disgusting video. I ain't linking that one in this chat
If you saw it good good you saw it. Hey, thank you, too
Freudian weapon again for the $1 Yoshi's Island is a classic for sure. Love the music. Hashtag charity
It is a very very good game one of the best for the old Super Nintendo Entertainment System
Ryan to Dell deliration
Ryan deliration thanks for the $5. They say whistle hashtag charity. I don't know how I just did it
No, it happens sometimes. I just can't I think my teeth are too big to whistle
That's kind of how I felt about it
You got good dental. Yeah
Hey, thank you, but thank you so much for five dollars and hashtag charity as well captain Morgan
Thanks to the $1. Do you dream of twitch chat? I've had dreams of twitch chat before
I've actually think I've had a dream before where I was sleeping just in my bed and I was just seeing
Kind of the chat on the right side of in of just meet like, you know
I'm lying there with my eyes closed like it's all it's all black and I just see twitch chat on the right and it's just
Like he doesn't know he doesn't know what the fuck. Oh my god. What an idiot somebody text him
Anybody have it like it was that just spamming and there were like 30 or 40,000 concurrent people there and
I was like wait a minute hold on. I had like an internal panic. I'm like, wait, I'm sleeping. They're watching me sleep
How did I delete the stream on now? I'm sleeping and then I realized what was happening
But that's probably the only thing that's happened because then I'm thinking about like it
What do I have any clothes on like how many people are here what's going on?
Why is the stream on him? Why am I why am I asleep? What what's going on?
But yeah, Freudian weapon again. Thank you for the $1. Honestly, I would watch you play through anything RPGs, especially
Maybe persona 5 someday hashtag charity. I don't think so
I've never played a persona game before and I feel like starting at persona 5 is the equivalent of
watching
like
like watching Star Wars
That's like watching the new Star Wars movie before you even know what Star Wars. I guess I'll watch this
episode 7
You can't really do that. It doesn't matter. So they're not they're not connected at all. They're all self-contained except for the first two
Oh, oh, okay. Oh, there goes the one of the reasons then I actually saw on the ps4 store when I was browsing
There's a persona 5 dance game because that's what I thought it was at first
It was like persona 5 dance in the starlight or something and I'm like what the fuck why people like this game so much
It's like is there like a
This is a RPG, but just like a dancing simulator. I thought that's what persona 5 was
Because it's persona 5 like colon. Here's like a little tagline. I was like, okay, that's that's persona 5
So how so there's a there's also I saw persona 4 like dancing with the stars, right?
Cuz I got really confused and I watched the trailer
Everybody's like oh you gotta play persona 5. It's got such an engrossing story. It's like such an interesting game. It's so great
Oh Joker, and then I'm watching this trailer for the people. It's like a
It's like a DDR. I'm like, this is what okay
But I guess I mean I I've seen persona 3 be played and it was pretty interesting
I never played him myself though. Hey radio video. Thanks for the one dollar German
We we will watch you whatever you stream because we love you
Those stuff like Chrono Trigger would be good for chill streams. Yeah, I know I probably will end up playing it
I probably would stream it. It's a great game
But alas, I would watch it. Well, that's good. I am monk
Thanks for the dollar 72 can't give subs, but here's some bits
turn my heart hashtag charity nobody is ever under any
obligation to buy gift subs or pay
It's solely up to you. You don't have to it's not like oh, I have to don't worry about it
Thank you so much for being here. Thanks for the dollar 72 all mew. Thanks for the two bucks epic janitor spill jokes
It happens so many times. Alright, so like help me some slack here guys
Do you really honestly think that I would have a good funny idea for a joke?
I'm gonna spill the bucket over
Accidentally, I mean, okay sure, but if that happens like two or three hundred times
Does it do you think that at like not time number 300? I'm like, here we go. Here comes a funny thing
I'm gonna do yeah, this would be funny when I do this after like 200 times
No
There are certain things that I maybe I would
Potentially not tonight, but yeah sure like when I'm playing red dead
Oh, I'm gonna try to like time it so I can like run into the train like right and we all know that that's happening
And I tried a few times and I can't do it, right?
But I don't like plan whoops. I tripped. Oh, I gotta plan that one. You're unfunny like that
That's the same thing to fall off the horse thing. I do you think I'm making a joke after 75 times?
It's funny because I played Red Dead Redemption 2
Like two nights ago when I wasn't streaming I was just hanging out on the couch and I fell off more times
Than when I was streaming and I'm a little laughing to myself going like man
If only people were watching this they would be like, holy shit
without us
Yeah, I maybe I would stream Red Dead again, but I'm just I'm having fun. Just slowly going through on my own
You betrayed us
No, I streamed Red Dead like five times
I played about 30 or 40% of that entire game on stream that into the whole thing, but I mean, it's a long game
He thinks we aren't watching
Hey, man, boy. Thanks for the one dollar. Here you go. There's a link here. Okay here here you go
We're gonna give you up, never gonna say no
Never gonna say goodbye
Never gonna say a lie or diss it. You've ruined my favorite song
Hey the spaz. Thank you for your huge amount of community subs and your five dollars here
It's a Christmas gift. I hope you enjoy all of it. Well, thank you. That's incredibly generous of you
You gave a lot of community subs and
$5 here. Thank you
Demonic cucumber. Thanks for the one dollar. Can you tell me the name of a cooking device specifically used to mix eggs?
an egg beater
Well, that was pretty good
Thank you verse seem know for the one dollar hashtag charity, thank you Ike turtle thanks for the one dollar
Hey, just thought I'd donate to my favorite top 1,000 streamer
Nice to see you finally made it to the B tier and that's all I ever need to be
B is perfect where it is
I'm totally cool with a B grade
Anyway, I'm excited about the crypto safe stream. Also that makes eight now
It's how smug hashtag charity eight what? Thank you. Ike though. Appreciate was this this is what I just did
Goodbye never gonna say goodbye never gonna say say say never gonna say
No, it's flat. Never gonna say there it is replace it. Somebody mix that in and replace it, please
Hey Garfield the Monday killer. Thanks for the one dollar
Hey, Jerem ain't the Christmas season just garfy spider-man has quite the year hasn't a great PlayStation 4 game and awesome animated movie and
A big role in Infinity War
What a Garf tacky little year for Marvel as a whole
Once upon a Deadpool is given a dollar of every ticket sold to charity to stop in cancer
Plus there was a heartfelt apt credit scene
with Stan Lee
Brought a tear to my eye got to remember the importance of comics and the guys behind him German heart. Absolutely
Stan Lee created pretty much almost every single thing you think is cool. So
Rest in peace, but thank you Garfield. That was very nice
Very nice comment there. Hey pop. Follow me. Oh, thanks for the one dollar
You can guess how this game would be pretty fun with friends. It's really easy to walk over each other's buckets
Aside from that I've been playing ashen in my impressions as someone who has never played a souls game are very good
If you ever get a hold of it having a friend with you instead of an AI really makes the experience Mary
Kerma German heart Santa hat. Oh
Man, if you like ashen, oh boy
If you've never played a souls game before
You you got a lot to go through
But I think ashen would have to sit sort of on the back burner
Because that's a big commitment. Isn't it? It's a
It's not is it a long game. Is it was it like 30 hours or something like that?
20 30 40 hours was it short 20 hours
Yeah, but I've probably sit on the back burner. I don't have any plans for it not in the immediate future, but it is always there
That's the one thing about great thing about video games
They're always available
So if it's ever like what am I gonna play next week? Hmm. I don't know what I'm gonna do. Oh, okay
Let's just dream ashen
Hydrate hydrate already did I did I did don't see look but thank you profile of you. Thank you cozy brother for the $4
No, no message just $4. Thank you
Bunny, but thanks for the $1. I have finals week, please
Yeah, you guys have finals week
Some of you've already taken them some of you still have to wait, but good luck
Mr. Pigeon. Thanks for the $1. Hey Jerma congrats on the news about the pregnancy time flies super fast
It feels like yesterday you introduced yourself
us
No, this ain't real. No, it's not real. It's not real. Don't this is a funny
Like he like he knocked the bucket over a hundred and fifty times, right? It's one of those
I forget what they're called again. Um
Yeah, it starts with J I don't know hey c4g
Thanks for the $1 if you hold a bucket under yourself and jump you can glitch off of it and fly
I missed that one. But thank you c4g
Thank you face in cake for the $5
There's another USB on the upstairs table you fuck now
You reax now you rearrange those last three words and you got now you're talking my language there. Fuck you table
Talked about that before the stream started. That's one of my favorite things. Thanks for the $5 face and cake
Thank you II dragon for the $5 hashtag charity. Thank you really appreciate it
Thank you bunny, but for the two dollars want to say thank you Jerma today was hard
Having a rough time with life, but it's always amazing to relax with one of your streams. You're amazingly uplifting. Hope to see you more
I'm really sorry to hear that you have in a rough time
glad you can relax and
Fuck around and chat crack a few jokes and hang up
That is what I care about number one, but thank you so much for the two dollars here. Hey the true
Michi, thanks for the one dollar. I bet you didn't forget that you said you will hit me up on discord eight months ago
well my brain I
kind of
Scatter it. He'll look into it. I've done that before
It's just I'm so bad
You know it took me it took me like there's like this guy in the stream and chat and he hangs out a lot
he was a college roommate of mine and
He's like he proved it. It was real and it took me like four to five straight months to remember. Oh, okay
And we taught we like actually talked so I am sorry. I'm very sorry
It's just my I scattered myself around and I lose track very very easily. It is not intentional
It's just sometimes like something else will come up over here. Something was come up over there
I have something else something will enter my brain and push out everything else and it's it's actually a really bad thing
But yes, I know
There are at least two I think there are at least one or two people that I do need to get in touch with so
I'm actually going to
Check exactly that when the stream ends. So it's okay. I'm just making it funny
I will be there in July 2019 to say the exact same thing
No, no, that's not gonna have it. I once I like remember and get on it. Usually I get on it
But it is one of my flaws
And I do apologize for it, but thank you for the one dollar. Thank you for reminding me
Thank you
knit and knit so
kitty
For the five dollars. Thanks so much for the stream today. Haven't laughed that hard in a while. I appreciate it
Thanks for hanging out. I had a lot of fun. It was blessed
Hey buster boy, thank you for the one dollar German. Just don't play mother three. It's such a boring game
You wouldn't enjoy it. Do we have a one guy versus one guy scenario here?
I think so because I think what did this is tough. This is 1v1 one guy
Hmm play mother three. There you go. I'm the second guy. I
Don't know if I would do enough three RPGs, I just I I don't know if I would do them on stream
I can't commit to that and be say yes y'all do mother one two. I'm gonna play earthbound and then mother three
What's the famous quote that I'm about to say right now? I'll look into it. I'm gonna look into that
PK fire PK thunder PK star storm
PK freeze PK freeze
PK freeze
PK freeze I
Still fucking got it
Peter Peter please
Peter Peter freeze
Hey attack of the Hank. Thanks for the two dollars
It's the zombie apocalypse. You can bring one character that has been in any of the German rumbles to join your zombie survival squad
Who do you choose?
Dr. Ocher is that a heart? That's a not a hard question
Timmy Tim tan thanks for the one dollar my sleep schedule so messed up at the moment that I missed the entire stream and
Only came in at the end at 4 a.m. Your streams are very good. You're the best streamer on twitch
hashtag charity
Having a messed-up sleep schedule always sucks. You just feel all messed up
Disconnected and everything and I'm sorry that your sleep schedule is a little screwy
but thank you for
Calling me the best streamer on twitch. That's I thank you. I don't really want to
I don't know if I want to agree with that because I
Anytime that I start to think that I'm the best. I'm the best on twitch
Then I feel like I would start to degrade in quality
I feel like I would be like that's it. I did it. I'm the best and I don't want to do that
I really really appreciate the fact that you think that but I
I'm floored that people think that there's so many people that stream here. There are thought they were like
How many people streaming right now and you think I'm the best on the whole site?
That means a lot that means a fucking absolute shitload this how many people streaming?
Seven so there are seven people streaming right now and I out of the seven
Thank you. I really appreciate that. I'm just glad you having fun. Hey seabear. Thanks for the $10
Leon is to Larry David as
Italics is to germo Leon is the best character
Almost every episode with Leon
Especially that's why I'm saying like when you get to pass like season six
It's like it's absolute
Hilarity Leon adds so much to the show and it just bakes everything everything is so funny
Step inside that asshole Larry. Oh
I'm gonna get out there eat garbage throw drop garbage. Well, that's classic
But thank you see beer for the $10
Thank you, Timmy Tim Tim for the $1 place slime rancher hashtag charity
I heard that's very relaxing and fun as well. Put it on the list
Hey get in the clown car. Thank you for your
bunch of community subs and
$10 exactly 13 minutes ago. There's no message here. Thank you for the large amount of money
Dr. Clay, thanks for the $1. He sprang to his clown car to his rats gave a whistle and away
They all ran like the down of a thistle, but I heard him scream as he drove out of eating ass
What yo Merry Christmas take care what that doesn't I don't know I don't understand
It was all that just to get me to say eating ass
He sprang to his clown car to his rats gave a whistle and away
They all ran like the down of a thistle, but I heard him scream as he drove out of eating ass
Yo, Merry Christmas. Take care. I did it with inflection that time, but thank you. Thank you. Mr. Pidgeon for the $1
I want to apologize for the fake news about the pregnancy play hit and run on stream
Shorty
Hashtag charity
Hmm. I have it. I've hit and run is behind me PlayStation 2 is right behind me. Hey bunny, but thanks for the $1
Germa, you're an inspiration to all of us and literally the reason I'm going to start taking voice acting classes
You always keep us happy. We couldn't ask for a better streamer. Good luck
Voice acting is a lot of fun. It's a lot of work
Take some time to develop. I wish you the best
Hey, I couldn't ask for a better audience. That's that's not couldn't ask for a better
Group of people you guys are awesome. And then finally here a clueless sniper for $1
Hashtag charity. Thank you so much right at the end. Let's go ahead and run the credits
It's gonna be a lot tonight. I wonder how fast this is going to roll. Oh boy. There it goes
Every day every time every time. Thank you guys so much. I
Missed one parfoil meal. Thanks for the $1
Second bit just something I've been meaning to say for a while
It makes me feel like an old grandma when I say seeing you move to Vegas
Rent out studios and follow your entertainment dreams makes me really happy
You seem so satisfied with what you are accomplishing and that rubs off onto your audience. Keep doing what you love
I'm glad it does. I'm glad it does. I hope you guys all have passions. Hope you all have
ideas
things that you want to do and
Try triumph if that rubs off on you then and apps of fucking Lutely no matter what it is
Doesn't matter what it is and I'm not even talking about just entertainment shit
I'm not talking about just like oh like being like an actor or like a
Writer, no, I'm just on all and out every single
aspect of your life
Whatever it is
Eating ass sure. Yeah, if you want to be the best ass eater in the world
Alright, that's go for it
Mood ruined
But that's Jerma's title. Yeah, I don't think you're gonna be able to beat it. Why am I still doing this?
Why am I pushing this bullshit? Hey double D
Thanks for the one dollar saw this Jerry big guy outside my window weird thing is I live on the 34th floor of an apartment
Building next thing I know he's walking into my walk-in oven. He's been trapped in there ever since hashtag charity plan
Because you see a button and you have to press it you hear a phone ringing and it could be anyone
But a ringing phone has to be answered. Doesn't it? I don't remember that movie
Now you stay right there and don't get out of that phone booth. Don't you move from that phone booth?
I'll do it. Look at all these subs. Look at all these names. Look at all these people that have subscribed you guys are fucking amazing
Thank you so much everybody. I will see you all on
Saturday, thank you for all your suggestions to the
Secret kind of chat Santa thing
That should be a lot of fun. I'll see you Saturday. We'll do something fun. We got a couple of options
Have a great rest of your evening. Have a great rest of your tomorrow. See you soon
Oh, hey meeting yeet
crookie monster the mass ray and oh
Thank you double D for that. I don't know. What did I do? Oh, I said somebody's name
All right. I'll see you guys on Saturday. Goodbye
Wait, dr. Clay got skipped for one dollar. I wasn't attempting to make you say anything
I was just trying to rhyme ass with Christmas. Oh
Okay, I get it now. All right. Good night everybody