Oh jeez, I've got so much work to do. Oh, goodness gracious.
I don't want to talk to him right now. Hello? Yes, I'm aware that I owe the reports next Tuesday.
Yes, I don't care. I don't want to talk to you anymore. I'm a professional fucking businessman
and I don't care. Good day. There's my files.
Okay, it's time to be a total dickwad. If you don't know how to be a total dickwad on TwoFort,
I'll show you. So what you want to do is you want to disguise as a friendly sniper.
Go out here, make sure you have whatever sniper rifle they have out. Pull out the dead ringer
and just pretend like you've never played this fucking game ever before in your life.
I don't, hey, where, where do we start? Where's the spawn? I don't, I, uh.
And then you come back here, go on in your uh, into your resupply and do it again.
Hey, I don't know what time is it? I've never played. Mom? Mom, how did I, how do you play
Team Fortress 2? Oh shit, the gig is up. The jig is up. No, it's not. And there's a dispenser here.
I can make this even worse for this guy. You thought you killed me.
What even just happened? Did I get backstabbed and then headshot immediately?
Or did I get double like headshot by like two or three different snipers? I have no idea what
just happened. You know, you got to mourn for these two gentlemen, two fort snipers. You got
to mourn for them. Dearly beloved, we are gathered here today to witness the, wait, no, that's wedding.
That's a wedding ceremony. I'm supposed to be doing like a funeral. Well, that, I fucked up
that joke. Let's keep going. They have a century in our intel. Are you serious right now? Hold on,
I got to check this out. How did they get this down here? What, who let this happen?
There's a century in our intel. How the, how did this happen? Is it, there's an engineer,
there's a teleporter down here too? You got to be shitting me. All right. See, that's going down.
I ain't letting this guy get away with that. Sniper's a good job, mate. Sniper's a good job,
mate. Sniper's a good job, mate. Get those direct shots. What's up? I'll take the intel, baby.
Oh, uh, right. Uh, I'm on the blue team. The blue team doesn't pick up the blue intelligence.
Sometimes I wonder. It's going on. We're, we're just going to go harass the hell
out of these snipers over here. We're going to get a bunch of Zatoichi kills.
Good evening. My name is Jerma. I suck so bad. It's okay. I, what is there a cent, why is there
a century there? Here we go. See you. That can be only one. How did I get covered in Jirardi?
That's what I want to know. No, I forgot. I already forgot that that century gun was there.
God damn. Eight, six, seven, eight. I look at where I am.
I made it on top of this thing. Look at how cool it is.
If that guy headshot me, right? If I fucking forget about this century one more time,
I swear to God, I'm going to flip out. There's nothing here. There's a century right there.
You don't have to protect this. I didn't, how did I not, did I hit the damn century?
That was stupid. That was so stupid. I think it just gave me diarrhea and that wasn't a headshot
either. I will get this guy. Can't see. I can't see. Don't you guys know how two foot works?
You can't just like walk in a straight line on the balcony. Dude, that's not how it works.
Look at, what if these people are getting destroyed? I'm going to prove to you guys
why that's a bad idea. You ready? Like watch. See? Do people not understand? Just watch.
Oh, hi. I'm going to walk this way on the two foot map. Ah, what do these do? All right,
before I go, I'm ending the video. Teleporter exit. Okay, cool. That makes sense.
Teleporter exit. Where are these entrances? Are they down here? Why? You're going to have to walk
anyways. If you go through that teleporter, you're going to have to walk at least some of them.
I don't understand. Somebody explain it to me. They don't even go down here.
Where do those teleporters go? What? All right, so let's go ahead and go over my loadout before
the video starts. We got the grenade launcher, the sticky bomb launcher, the half set Aichi,
the unusual, that's my patch, and the moomer smites.