Hello. Hello. I'm Andy. I'm Andy. I'm always a late Andy. I'm Landy. I'm Andy. I'm always late Andy.
I just like messed that up. Whatever. I practiced that for like 10 minutes.
I was in the mirror practicing that for an hour. Minus 50 minutes. Landy. Is this an ad?
Well, hold on. Not yet. Landy. We're gonna play two things today. We're gonna play Call to the
Lamb. It's out. It's out today, right? Or is it yesterday? Yesterday. Oh, spoiler. You know,
I don't want you to hear the music. Can you stream in an hour? I'm kind of busy. Well,
I was supposed to start an hour ago. Pre-stream chat knows. I made it three o'clock so I could go,
oh man, hey, I'm live at two. And then I had to make a few very, very important phone calls
and that didn't work. Hey, but it's okay. I only turned out to be like 12, 10 minutes late
rather than an hour and 10 minutes late. So it's a good thing I didn't make it two o'clock, right?
Now you're thinking with portals. No, but how you doing? Welcome back. Today, we're going to be
playing Cult of the Lamb. Like I said earlier, should be fun. I've heard very, very good things.
I've heard people say that this is probably one of the better games that's come out this whole year.
The Twitch extension works. It's just very, very slow. I'll wait. I'll turn that on another time.
Once it's like good to go because I'm probably going to be playing this again. I didn't set that
up if I had to because like they turned it off. They turned it on. They updated it. They turned
it off. I'm going to wait until it's good to go. Yeah, we're going to play that for a little while
and then I'm going to move to Two Point Campus, which is going to be a sponsored part of the
stream. So Cult of the Lamb not sponsored. Two Point Campus is sponsored. I'm going to do a half
and half today. This game is so good. I'm going in completely blind here. I can't wait. I'm going to
say my mic is what? Your mic is picking up the music from the game. It is absolutely not. Is it?
Hold on a second. No, it isn't. No, you're full of shit. Your mic is picking up several dangerous
pathogens. What do you mean? It's doing it? Hold on. What? What do you think? Wait, when I talk,
you can hear it. What do you mean by that? It comes in when you talk. Huh? Hold on. Wait,
we have to do a test. So you're saying that if I keep the microphone open and have the noise
gate not come through, you hear the music. What? Yeah, I don't. I have absolutely no idea why
that's happening. Hold on. Does it fix it? No, that's not even the right mic. I am so confused.
Funny mic. What do you mean? What do you mean funny mic? That's the webcam.
Hold on. What happened? Why is it doing that? I have no response to this. Hold on.
OK, I don't want. Tell me if this fixes it. Did that fix it or is it still happening?
Uh. It's not there, but don't ask. I just turned off literally everything.
But let me answer me this. You do hear it now, though, right? Scream into your webcam. OK,
we're good. I might not do face cam. I don't I have really I have I have unbrushed teeth today
and I haven't taken a shower or anything. So I look like a fucking just gross person. I don't
know. I might not have cam on today. I have a I have really unbrushed teeth. I'm just telling
you. That's a fact. I'm ready to play. You want to see what should we see what I look like?
I'm telling you, I have wicked bad unbrushed teeth. I know this sounds like an annoying thing
where I turn the cam on and I look fine. I look great. But I just tell you, oh, I haven't
showered. I haven't brushed my teeth. Everyone goes, oh, but you look so good. Right. How do I
look? I literally I just I like I woke up like this and I didn't change it. How do I look?
How do my teeth look? Literally no one could have could have. Look at my hair, though.
This is called my head was mushed into the pillow. This is like I'm sleepy. It's not balding.
Who cares if I'm if I bald? Why is my webcam flickering? Like there's a candle in front of
me. Guys, if I go bald, whatever, I'm almost 40. OK, if I go bald, that's a normal human reaction
to getting older is balding a little. Oh, I turn 40 soon. If I go bald, go cares. I made it a long
time with all this hair. I don't even care. You look good for a guy that's in a zombie movie.
All right. Well, it's coming off for now. If you're good, it'll come back. You have to be good,
though. Good, though. Oh, my goodness. That might have been the worst one yet.
That might have been the worst one in a decade. Hold on. I got to turn this down.
Why do my gohooks a lot change all of its settings? That was weird because this is
routing the wrong way. Whatever. It's fine. OK, here we go. Call to the lamb. I'm ready to play.
It should be fun. Your face came on. I will if you're good. You got to be good. You're aging
backwards and praise the lamb conduit to great power. Almost no sacrificial beast take heed
for a crown cannot sit upon two brows. All right. All you had to tell me there was x, x, x, x, x,
y, y, y, b, b, b, x, x, x, x, y, y, y, y, b, b. That's all you had to say. x, x, x, x, x, y, y, y, y,
b, b, b. This game was in the if you don't remember, this game was part of the Steam
demo day week, and it was one of our favorites. So I'm really glad to be playing it right now.
Where's this? Where's my precious streamer space? If you're good, you have to be good.
Azimala.
Vora stands the last of its kind, all others we have hunted down and put to the blade.
With this final sacrifice, the prophecy will be impossible to fulfill.
The heretic who lies bound below will be condemned to eternal captivity,
and the old faith shall be preserved. So I'm dead. This is the eternal being that's been chained
down here for centuries, over 200 years. Come closer, fear not. Though you are already dead,
I still have need of you. This foolish bishop thought they could keep you from me in death,
but instead they sent you straight to me. I will give you life again, but at a price.
All I ask is you start a cult in my name. Do we have a deal? Yes. Sure. And so it came to pass
that the Countess, once bathed in rejuvenating blood. I've never heard the rest of that dialogue,
by the way. I've always pressed click right after that part. All right, let's go.
X, X, X, X, Y, Y, Y, B, B, B. I forgot how fun this game was. This game was, it's like,
okay, it's kind of like Finding of Isaac, kind of like Legend of Zelda, kind of like Star Tropics,
kind of like Frickin' Morty. Not. Like Dark Souls? I would, I don't think so. Fear not,
I am Rattau. I was once a chosen vessel like you, but those days are lost to the winds.
I was sent to guide you. We are deep in the lands of the Old Faith and in grave danger.
My instructions are to lead you to safety, continue through the woods, escape lies ahead.
I will be close by. Sick. Is this your fucking house? Is this like Dark Souls? It's a little
bit like Dark Souls, a little bit like Frickin' Morty. I don't know why that's so funny to me.
That's making me laugh every time. I don't know why. It's a bad joke. Somebody in chat said it,
but it's funny. All right, that's my inventory. Where's my health? Is there no HUD until I need
it? This game feels amazing to play, by the way. If you haven't got it, I would suggest you do.
Wait until you decide if it's worth it or not. That's what we do here on Friday Gaming Vibes.
We check it out. We see if it's worth your dollar. Is Call to the Lamb worth you opening up your
wallet? Stay tuned and find out on Friday Gaming Vibes. Money, money, money, one coin.
It is yet. It is. I haven't bought it yet. I'm really excited. I'm a huge Finding of Isaac fan.
You guys all know that. So and there's been a lot of those kind of Isaac likes, I would call them.
There's been quite a few. I never really got into any of the other ones besides Isaac.
We've nearly reached safety, but look ahead. Another poor soul about to be sacrificed.
Rescue them and they would have no choice but to join your new cult. I remember this.
Almighty bishops of the old faith, we ask you to accept the sacrifice of this wretched soul.
Who interrupts our ritual and trespasses on sacred ground?
Is there a charge? Can I hold down? Probably not. Nice. This is a Morty like.
Hey, you know that that I think they're coming to multiverses at some point here soon.
So what if I play as Morty? Will you guys all leave? What if I play as Rick and Morty in
multiverse? What if it's like my K? What if it's a character that I just connect with?
And I'm really good with it. It's really my style. Play, play, play through style and everything.
Right. You're going to have to suffer or you won't, but you can just leave if you want to.
We've reached safety. You have done well. Red Crown will allow you to use those markings
in the ground to transport yourself great distances. We'll take you to a temple that
has fallen to ruin there. You'll be able to begin your new cult. I'll meet you there.
I don't think you guys would leave. I think a lot of you guys are full of shit.
I don't think you'd leave. You'd say you were leaving and just so like, in case the mods
wanted to see like check, you would leave the chat. You'd hit the X window and then open a
private browsing tab and come back. Just so you could tell your friends that you weren't there.
Right. Like, nah, when he, when he was playing like his Rick and Morty was pissed me off.
I left. You can check the logs I was in there. All right, cool. So now we do the town building
section. This was in the demo. Please select the difficulty and where you can change. OK,
so as a as a seasoned binding of Isaac veteran, is this is this a medium or a hard game? What
should I do? No one's picking this medium sounds fine, right? It's two buttons, dude. But somebody
had an actual like a good take here. Reviews say the game is is easy. So pick a harder one.
Do you is that as accurate? I don't want to know. Not very hard. Extra hard is not that bad. I'll
start with hard. We'll go from there if I want to. I can up it at any time or I can lower it if I
need to. All right, let's go. OK. This crumbling ruin is said to be the site of your new cult.
We have much to do. We begin by indoctrinating this poor soul into the warm embrace of your cult.
They get resources for you. Order this one to collect wood and stone. Come here.
Convert me to your cult. I will follow your teachings faithfully. All right, name. No,
no, no. Wait, I can just make it whatever I want, right? All right. How about, um,
aren't you, um, do Twitch integration? I think I'm not going to do it initially because I think
that it's they having problems with it. They took it offline for a little bit, right? And it's like
really slow. I'm definitely going to play this game more than once. I guarantee it. So we'll
turn it on another time. Uh, how about Bun Bun Bun Bob? I'm not going to name the character Morty
Bun Bob Sponge Bob. Yeah, Bun Bob choose form. Oh, oh, wait, wait. I got these because I got
the deluxe edition, right? Well, they can't be Bun Bob if they're not a bunny. That doesn't make
any sense. OK. OK. Variant. Yep. Freights on recruiting this follower immediately gain 10
faith and generates devotion 15 percent slower. All right. That's my first one. Whatever. All
right. So go collect, um, get wood. OK. Your cult will grow powerful, but your followers cannot live
on prayer alone that you need to eat. Gather necessary roots to build a cooking fire. Let's
you do meals. All right. Cool. So I need to collect. OK, let's go. I didn't chop trees down
like this. Germa, you're wormy. What do you know about me? You don't know me. You don't know me.
So don't say stuff like that. So I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Do I know you? Do I know you?
Excuse me. It's going to take way too long. All right. Look at all this shit to build. What?
There's a lot of stuff here. I don't want to mess this up. I don't want to mess. I don't
want to mess this up like I messed up my cookie run kingdom town. OK. I had a terrible, awful,
awful layout for that and I uninstalled it. Uh, it should probably be down here down here.
No, that's too far away. Um, right here is OK. I'll clear this out. iPad, kid. You can move
things freely. OK. All right. So they need to eat. Hunger of your cult can be seen at the top left
of the screen. When this gets too low, followers will begin to starve. I don't want that. Find more
food while crusading. Grouts that pass through foraging. All right. Plant farms to grow your
own food. Seeds can be purchased or found while crusading. OK, cool. They'll collect some berry
meat and then cook a meal. They plant the berry seeds. I'm not a fan. I'm not a fan of this game.
I don't think I'm going to move on like such a small, like low attention span. Like you won't
even do this little part here. OK, let's go. Cool. Now we must build a shrine. We need more
followers and more gold. Go crusade. Our mutual benefactor, the one who waits, has been trapped by
the four bishops of the old faith. Each of them guards a chain that binds him to the realm beyond.
We've conjured openings to their realms that is your task to track them down and slay them
so that he may be freed. Now go. There you shall find gold and willing recruits. And for those who
are not willing, convert them by force. Go. No, this game's fucking amazing.
Followers deposit resources here. OK, cool. Do I have to do anything with this person?
They just. Oh, wait, I can speak to Bunbob. Make demands. I'll figure that out later.
Dude, spoiler for season six. Rick and Morty. Oh, shit. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Yeah, I forgot.
OK, Jerry. I'm sorry I said that earlier. I know that like a lot of people were upset that I
spoiled season six. All right. Darkwood. Cool. So this for place to go. What are you doing?
What was that? Godly blood was spilled here to death. No longer wish to wait. OK, let's go.
Don't make this a Rick and Morty joke stream. It deserves better. I won't.
It's not I. I'm reacting to chat right now. It's nothing to do with me.
OK, cool. Well balanced blade dealing moderate damage. I didn't enter the lands of the bishop
Leshy. Those who do not follow the ways of the old faith will be destroyed.
Let's go. We need more gold and we need more followers. Oh, should I have health now? All
right. Don't mess it up. We're good. Three coins and some hearts. You're more of a family guy
streamer. Um, I don't know. Am I going to Luigi's Mansion this game? Am I going to cut literally
everything down and not some of the slowest player of this game? Meow. You will get stuff if you do,
but it's not a constant drop. So it's worth doing. So I should keep doing it. I'll keep doing it.
It's me stuff. Somebody said you're like something like the Sopranos. All right. Is this
stream more like the Sopranos? Am I the Sopranos of Twitch or am I the family guy streamer?
You're the George Lopez of Twitch. I don't know what that means.
Is that an insult or is that like a good thing? Do people like George Lopez?
I thought George Lopez is as like a TV show and as a comedian, right? I'm going to go this way.
You're the Big Bang Theory of Twitch. No, I am not. No, I'm not. That's absolute horseshit and
you know it. You just said that to make me mad. The card showed me once many lifetimes ago,
or is it yet to be? I've always drawn your cards, lamb. And yet this is the first.
You're the young Sheldon of Twitch. Okay. Take these cards and I will grant. I will draw another
each time we meet. When drawn by me, they will grant you a power. Power? Well, that's both known
and unknown. The cards will decide that. Okay. A heart offered, a vow made or receive double
the health when healing. What is this one? Is that a spirit heart? Why would I be the Big Bang Theory?
Nothing I say. None of the jokes I make are Big Bang Theory kind of jokes. When was the last time
you heard me talk about a like physicist joke or like a joke about the cosmos or something or like
a math joke? I don't make those here. I don't ever talk about that stuff. I hate that stuff.
All those topics I dislike. Is this a spirit heart? No. Yes. I'll take double the health.
That sounds better. You hate the cosmos. No, I'm talking about like math jokes. I don't,
I don't, I'm not a math person. All right. Goodbye. I think you're more the Frazier of Twitch.
No, I don't think so. No, no, no, no. That's incorrect. I don't want to die in the tutorial
zone. What do you mean true? Isn't Frazier like super intellectual and, all right, there we go.
I need health. Wired feather necklace imbued with the vitality of a bird.
Follower will have increased movement speed. Okay. Are these permanent? I don't have a follower
though. I have no health. Can I eat this? What if I, I'm going to die here. Let's get more food.
Is this medium? This is no, it's not hard. Oh, okay. It's a lot of vegetables here.
Oh, this is perfect. Okay. Oh, this is perfect. Oh, let me say this. Oh, this is, oh, oh,
sentence. Oh, sentence. You're the Lunchables of Twitch. Incredibly convenient. Tastes great
and can fit anywhere. Um, okay. That's, I'm very versatile. How did I not find any health?
No, I'm not saying that's what me directly. I'm just saying that in general, Lunchables are very
convenient. They, they, they, they don't, they don't taste bad. They're fine. And they can,
you can take them anywhere and nobody complains. If you, okay, I'm going to tell you right now,
if I were to be in a room, like a conference room with like 10 executives, it doesn't matter.
Like 10, like multi-billion dollar executives. And they're talking about, oh, this is what we're
going to do. This is, this is, these are the expensive cigars and cigarettes. We're going
to smoke later. Oh, was that a 10,000 year old Scotch? Oh yeah. Oh yeah. What year is that one,
John? If I was in that room and I pulled out a Lunchables and I opened it, everyone would hear
the tear and they would, everyone would fucking be obsessed with it. Everyone would want a piece.
They, they would all go, wow, you got Lunchables. Oh, sick. Everyone would be so happy. It doesn't
matter. Everybody loves Lunchables. And then one of the executives that do, oh shit, dude,
what a fucking psycho. He would be like, let me see, give me, give me. He would take the cracker,
ham, cheese, cracker, ham, cheese, cracker, ham, cheese, cracker. And everyone around him,
everyone's going to be like, dude, slow down, dude. Oh, he's going fucking crazy.
And he would try to get the whole thing in his mouth and we would all clap and laugh.
I don't know. I need help. You did that on stream like eight years ago. Did I do a
Lunchables stack? No, I didn't. I did. I literally did. What? Hold on. Was this Lunchables though?
You can't go in like that. Hold on a second. I think you can go inside.
Man is going to choke on stream. Stop. Why do I have no emotion doing this? What's wrong with me?
Here, give that to me. He doesn't take it out of my mouth, does he? Oh, well, that was,
that was actually like, if you're going to throw up your face, that was like,
I'm moving weirdly enough where it's going to come up. You can't go in like that.
I think you can go inside. Are they Oreos? Why would I do it
long ways by the way? What the fuck was I doing? That's amateur move right there. That was amateur.
What an amateur. You don't do it long ways. You do it, you move vertical. What are you doing?
What an idiot. I forgot where I would play. Whatever. It's fine. I forgot where I was.
All right. Fear not. Hold on a second. Let me move this back where it was. Okay.
I should allow fire still need you. Take what you have gathered, build and strengthen the cult.
This is how power is gained. Continue on undaunted. Each time you are brought down,
you rise stronger. You included the Oreos. I don't know. I don't know why I did that.
We were drinking. We were downing beers. That stream. Oh yeah. But still, why would you go
like horizontal? It's vertical. Okay. So I have, um, I make some more food. I don't have any
followers. So what else can I build? All right. I just gotta get back in there.
Should I cook more food? What do you guys think? 15% chance of pooping instantly. Um,
can I eat these? No, I can't. So they'll just be, he can just eat it whenever he wants.
Food will spoil by the way. Oh shit. Okay. Pop left to see how hungry. Okay. Well,
it's all right. All right. Let's go. Why run out of room in my inventory? Or is it infinite?
No. All right. Sick. That's a new weapon. Apostates cleaver. High damage and a little slower.
That is slow. This is a good weapon. This is an ungodly weapon.
Ooh, this is actually kind of fun. Regular sword is better. This thing has huge cleave though.
The small rooms. This is great. Don't hit me. Nice. Yeah. There are secret rooms,
tinted rocks, tinted rock secret areas, right? There probably has to be. The cleave is so huge.
What happened? What's going on? How can this be? You were put to the blade, lamb, as all your kind
were. And yet here you stand before me unrepentant. Crown his power. Could it be? But I am stronger
still. Turn tail and run little lamb. Mini boss? No, I think that's the main boss of the act.
All right. What do you got? Overall weapon damage increased by 1.2 times.
Almost as much as the Wii was stronger than the GameCube. Remember that? You guys remember
hearing that? And how much that pissed everybody off initially? The Wii was 1.2 times faster than
the GameCube. And people were like, what? And then it sold like 100 million units. I remember
reading that initial report and being like, you got to be fucking kidding me, Nintendo. What are
you doing? Mistake flop. Things going to be a piece of shit. And I think like, like a third
of all households on earth own a Wii. So I was wrong. Yeah, it's definitely worth that.
More damage. Hell yeah. Let's not get hit. Okay. And statue of the mighty lamb. Oh, cool. Okay.
I need a temple. Did it? That's cool. So this is just decoration. Are you ever right?
Okay. I was right about Bitcoin. I bought Bitcoin when it was a dollar and I sold it when it got to
a dollar too. All of it. So, you know, I was right about that, I guess. Thanks for the fucking
reminder. Always bet against Jerma. No, why would you? Excuse me. Don't ever bet against Jerma.
Don't ever bet against me. Cause you know what? I might surprise you. Hey, I might surprise you
today. You know what? I kind of want a compilation of all the times I've done something and said,
you know what? I think I might surprise some of you guys today. And then just show the me walking
into grenades and stuff. That damage is awesome. You're predictable. Um, I feel like I'm some
things I am, but a lot of things I'm not. Like if I was so predictable, when's the next time
I'm going to tweet. That's not a I'm live tweet. You know what I'm saying? Like when am I going to
tweet again for real? Go ahead and predict that thing is doing a lot of damage. Whoa.
Ooh. Crusaders blade too. Oh, let me try it out. It's faster, but do I want it? I don't think it's
worth it. Yeah, I'm keeping the act. That guy. You come far enough. My followers are willing to do
anything for me. Can you say the same of yours? I give myself to the cause. Oh, mighty leader.
By the blood of the great ones, destroy the red crown. I'm who see us. Whoa. Don't get overwhelmed.
Oh, now you're going to be my follower, right? Please spare me. Convert me to your call. I will
follow your teachings. Come here. And then eight, not eight, six berry bush seeds, 16 berries.
Um, I don't know what's better. Just the regular berries and, oh, that's a lot of money.
Nice. Very cool. You should have taken the seeds. Oh, well, I want to say, let me check this seeds.
Grow the berries. You goofy ass. Let it came down here. Hmm. I feel like this would be worth it.
If it was too goofy. Oh, I said goofy ass. What are you going to lose these? Uh, what mods? What's
going on? What am I missing here? Anybody in mod chat? What's what am I missing? What's going on?
It's a meme. They say, lol, I don't know. What? Uh, no clue. I'm lost. I'm just as lost as you are.
Actually goofy. Uh, don't tell them. Is it? I don't get it. What? It's a meme. It's a current meme.
All right, let's go for it. It's time to win. Wait, I can return to, oh, it's locked. Why is it locked?
Did I do everything? Oh, okay. Cool. Boomer doesn't realize his chat is all under 25.
Oh, okay. All right. Very good. My vessel. It seems I chose well when I kept you from death.
I'll be watching your every move. Do not disappoint me. Your viewer base is five to 10 at this point.
Nobody that's five to 10 years old is on Twitch. I'm sorry. I don't agree. That's no, that no, no,
no. That's not even, that's not even Fortnite guys. That's not Fortnite age. Stop saying Fortnite.
No, maybe if you said like 12 or something, that's not Fortnite. Nope. You know how I,
I am certain I am 1 million percent positive that because so I have nieces and nephews and I can
tell like what that whole age group cares about just based on the things that my siblings tell me
and things that I see my nieces and nephews do. I know what they're into now. And I'll tell you,
it's not, it's not Twitch. When you have five, it's not, you're not on Twitch.
All right. Let's bring this new person in. Please spare me. Anecdote Andy. Dude, when you,
I'm trying to think of like the world when you're five, you can't even fucking read at five.
You can't even read. What are you talking about? You just barely are like learning how to read
at like four years old, five years old. You're not like reading books. You could. Yeah. All right.
Sorry. All right. Yeah. Sam, I am. I do not like green eggs and ham. They're not sitting here
typing like omega low. Like streamers sucks in the chat. They're not here. They're not writing
like copy pasta paragraphs here. It's not how it works. All right. What do I want this person to
be named? How about green? Um, wart, rash, puke, punk, oil. Um, gremlin, gremel, gremel, gremel,
gremel, gremel, gremel, grimace. No, you can stay there. Uh, I like the color is fine, but this is
bad. I just five, this person doesn't have any good traits. Um, you go get stoned because I already
have somebody cutting trees down. Followers will either work or worship. Worshipping followers
generate devotion for you to collect, but to collect it, you require a shrine, build it,
statue, shrine. Okay. Um, I can, I can have, I have to put it here. Let's work.
Praise be your followers can now worship you. There's a new follower. Assign them to worship
at the shrine and collect the devotion. Your followers generated the shrine to unlock divine
inspiration. Oh, new follower authority. I kind of like authority authority. The pig with the hair
on recruiting follower immediately lose 10 faith yields 15% faster when sickened and in bed rest.
Okay. Go worship. So you collect this more followers worshiping at your shrine, the faster
they will fill up. The shrine is full. They will be stopped until it is emptied. Once you've
collected divine inspiration, unlock new buildings. Ooh, that's how you do that. Okay. Cool.
Um, all of you actually go worship. I can do this bullshit. You know what I mean? I can do this.
You guys do that. I can't do that. Come here. Anybody have food? I'll finish this. You go do
that. All right. I need a temple. Who wants coffee? Oh, there's still food here. That's fine.
All right. We're good. Oh, it wants me to finish this part. Okay. Take it. Divine inspiration
unlocked. Um, my God. Okay. Just turn in the path of exile. So what do I want to go from here?
Sleeping bags. Unlock. Oh, establish a temple. All right. Farm plot or sleeping. Probably farm.
Yeah. Farm plot. I need some divine inspiration. Temple. Uh, this will go down. Let's put it away.
Like down here. The music slaps. It does. Yeah. It is pretty good. Why are you ignoring chat?
Who said I've been doing that? Like on the right stick. Your Twitch integration. No.
Temple is center of your cult. From there, you will preach sermons to grow stronger and
perform rituals to mold the fragile minds of your followers. You need to maintain the faith of your
cult. If it falls too low, your followers will dissent against you and eventually leave. They're
ready to hear your word. Show them that you are their great leader. Preach a sermon.
Oh, okay. All right. Everyone come on here. I'm going to give you a classic Bart Simpson.
Rub it up, Deb. Thanks for the grub. Bart! Oh Homer, it's okay. Okay. Perform a sermon.
Drawing energy from your followers to bolster the power of the red crown.
Oh, stop. Give me a break. It wasn't the impression I was trying to do. It was the
cadence I was doing and the nostalgia of you remembering the episode. That's it. I wasn't
being like, okay, here comes my good impression of Homer and Bart and Marge. No, that was a
cadence for you to remember the nostalgic properties of the episode. Now you're going
to get timed out if you keep this up. They liked it. Performing sermons will draw power from them
and allow you to unlock new abilities, weapons, and curses. Followers with a higher loyalty level
will generate more devotion. All right. So we have to do this a lot. Oh my God. There's more.
Oh shit. Nice. What's your favorite 10 commandment? Thou shalt not steal. Leave my shit alone.
Do it again. Okay. God your cult. You need to declare doctrine so that they might obey you.
Turn to the lands of the old faith and seek out commandment stone fragments. With these,
you'll be able to declare new doctrines. Okay. What about thou shalt not kill?
Thou shalt not steal is like the first one I thought of. What are the 10 commandments
off the top of my head? Let me see if I can get this. Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not steal.
Thou don't, don't help me. Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not steal. Thou shalt not commit
adultery. Right? Thou shalt not. What are the other ones? Only three commandments. No, no, no.
Okay. Mel Brooks had this joke and it was an unbelievable joke. He's playing as Moses,
right, with the commandments and he goes up to all the followers that are out there waiting to hear
him. He comes back with the boy. He has the commandments in his hands and he comes over
with these three big slabs and they're all waiting for him to talk and they're just like,
oh there he is, Moses. And he walks up with these three halves and he's like,
yes, I have seen God and we have spoken. What I have for you here, the most important I have.
And he drops one of the slabs and it fucking shatters on the ground. He says, I have 15.
The thing falls, it shatters on the ground. Then he goes, oh, 10 commandments. Can we watch it?
Let's watch it right now. It's a classic fucking piece of comedy. It really is.
Let's just watch it. How long is it? It's like 15 seconds long. It's so good. It's
truly like a genius bit. You can't go in like that. I think you can go inside.
Okay, here we go. It's so funny. I shall give these laws. Hear me. It's given unto you.
Oh, it's so good. Like what were the other five? What were the other five? Oh, it's classic.
Like those must have been important, right? All right, so now we plant.
The volume was too low. Oh, it's all right. Those are DLC. Yo, dude, when we're going to
get a baby food stream? You're weird. That's a weird thing to ask. Okay, I can plant.
I can do actually farming now, right? Okay. Oh, shit. It's a bunch of grass.
Wait. All right. The farm's going to be over here on the left. Put it in a diamond shape.
Oh, come on. I ruined it. Did I do too many? Do a baby food tier list.
I don't know, man. That's one of those ideas that starts out funny.
And then in practice is like, I'm not comfortable right now. Like the baby sensory stream. That's
a funny thing to think of and go, wow, that's funny to think about. But doing it in practice,
it's like, this is making me uncomfortable. Okay, so water. This is sick. You actually
have like a whole thing like this. All right, so then add fertilizer. Oh, I need shit.
Do they shit? Are they shitting? No, no, don't clean it. Pick it up on sanitary conditions
that your cult will cause your followers to get sick. If a follower becomes sick, assign them
to bed rest or they could die. Okay. OOP vomit and dead bodies cause illness to spread quickly
throughout your cult. Cleaning messes and burying bodies will prevent the spread of illness. Oh,
my God, what? That was weird. Like immediate. Disgusting. Okay, so I need more. All right,
this is fun. Well, let's keep going. Everyone can, everyone's good, right? I need a deadly
sins tier list. You mean like in order of which one I think is the worst or the, well, what do
you mean? Ooh, no, it needs to be by full metal alchemist characters. Oh, come on. FMA characters.
Okay, the one who waits is pleased with your progress and wishes to grant you a crown ability.
Thanks. Hmm. Ooh, so there's a, oh, it's perfect, right? Hit it right in the middle.
That's fun. Enemies you slay will now drop fervor. Collect this to replenish your curses.
All right. Righteous anger earned by striking down non-believers and works like ammunition
for your curses. Fervor will drop when you slay an enemy collecting it refuels your curses.
You ever heard about the Bible story where the kids bully a bald guy and they get mauled by a bear?
I can't say I've caught up with my Bible history or Bible verses in a long time, man.
Okay. Ooh, old nuggets. What's this? It's time of day matter. I probably shouldn't be using that
on these guys, right? Do you drink shower water? No. I open my mouth with the shower water go in,
fill my mouth enough where it overflows from inside. I just hold my mouth open and it goes,
fill, fill, fill, fill, fill, and then goes over the sides. And then I spit it all out.
Ow. Oh shit. Okay. These guys are weird. Oh my God. I'm getting destroyed in this one.
I have to pay more attention. All right. I got to pay attention. Pay more attention, please.
You have good tap water. No, I don't, I wouldn't, I don't know if I would drink
the Vegas tap water. No, I don't, I'm not, I'm not into that. Go down. What's up here?
Oh shit. Wait, go back, back, back. No, I don't want to go there yet. How do I get over there?
Use the map. Oh, it's not, okay. It's not connected. That's why. See how the little thing,
the little tag on the bottom is not connected. I thought for some reason I couldn't get that way.
Don't you have a filter? Yeah. Still, I wouldn't, I wouldn't just drink just regular tap water.
It freaks me out. It just does. I'm sorry. I don't know. I don't like, I don't know.
I don't like the way tap water smells. You know, when you put like tap water up to your mouth and
you kind of can smell that like chloriney kind of smell. No, it's like that. It's,
it's got a very specific smell to it. What is this? Go find out. Okay. Ooh. Okay. I only hit one of
them. Enjoy the rest of your dinner. Oh, I think I really hurt that guy. Okay. Salmon.
Berry seed. Let's do salmon. How much is this free? Is it free? Stop. Just how do I get him to stop
doing that? This is free. All this is free if I go in here and do this. Oops. I honestly did not
think that was anything alive. I thought that was just like a house. Okay. Cool. What's over here?
Whoa. Um, cool. This way. New follower. The worm it is hungry. It feeds. It partakes of our flesh,
but that is the price for safety for that. We gladly give it all we have. That's why these
guys were freaking me out because they, they do the, they do the fin from multiverses. Swing already.
Do it. Are there iframes? Can I dodge through people? Good. All right. What do you have for
magical powers? Cool. Find commandment stone fragments, which are there on the map somewhere?
Oh, there's meat. What are your current thoughts on multiverses? Give me that mic.
Here's what I think about multiverses. You already know what I think about multiverses. Don't ask.
Steal devotion. Sure. Okay. Break. Is it bad? Oh, champion. Champion. Foolishly persist little
lamb. I hear your lies and I smell your fear. The red frown rises again, but what an unworthy
bearer it has. Crack a quest. Oh, no, I don't want to do that right now. But it stumps too.
That's pretty cool. Oh, I thought I had power. Didn't roll. All right. That was funny.
When attacked 10% chance of negating damage or deals poison damage. Yeah. This one that's for
the fast swing should be cool, right? That power can probably change, I'm assuming, right?
This is a tablet fragment. We've been good. Give us face cam. All right.
Wow. I got more lighting in here and I look at how greasy and gross I look.
My hair looks like it came out of the oven and it's done. This looks like cooked hair.
My hair looked different. Like it's done now. It's ready. Okay. What befell this pantheon?
Alas, this is the nature of beasts to forget and of gods to be forgotten.
We'll get shiny. I should probably wash my face. Yeah, I'm going to wash my face after this.
All right. May have they left, may have they slept, may have they devoured and were devoured
in turn. Those few who remain spread roots, spun webs, molded this world to meet their men, theirs.
Many gods, hundreds. You found enough fragments to form a commandment stone.
These are used to declare new doctrines for your cult to follow.
Use the altar in your temple to declare a new doctrine so that I can change the sermons.
It's kind of cool. Cooked turkey hair. Don't you feel like if you just took a piece of this
off and like it would be delicious? All right. Whoa. One, two. And then he goes,
wow. One, two. And then he goes, oh, you idiot. I'll get greedy. It's four. You get four and that's
it. Oh, whoa. Four times. All right. Use the curse shot. Not enough time, man.
German name one more commitment or I'm going to stop watching. I'm actually going to try.
Thou shalt not steal. Thou shalt not commit adultery. Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not
commit trespasses. Thou shalt forgive trespasses against us. Thou shalt. I actually really don't
know the ten of these. Thou shalt not commit adultery. Thou shalt not. Oh, it's not a bunch
of knots. Thou shalt not steal. Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not commit adultery. Right.
There's other things you can't you should do. Right. Thou shalt thou shalt eat a balanced
breakfast with at least one or two grams of whole grains. Thou shalt always thou shalt love thy
neighbor. Thou shalt drink water. Thou shalt drink eight ounces of water every two hours or something.
Thou shalt always bathe and never be on stream with a fucking cooked turkey hair. Did I get one?
That's too much water. I know that eight ounces of water every. You're supposed to eat eight
glasses of water a day. Right. Thou shalt thou shalt not too much. I don't know. Did I actually get
one? Thou shalt treat each other with respect or something along those lines. I'm just gonna look
them up. Okay. Ten commandments. How do I not know these? Ten commandments. Okay. Thou shalt not worship
false gods. I am the Lord your God. You shall have no other gods. Never take my name in vain. You shall
keep the Sabbath day holy. Honor your mother and father. You shalt not kill. You shalt not commit
adultery. You shall not steal. Okay so the other ones were I just I was thinking of um so honor
your father and mother. Hey I I always do I I say call your mother every day so I knew one. So I knew
it. Does that count? Okay so it's like don't have uh no false gods no other yeah I just I don't know
why I was thinking that they would like instable direct like you do not do this. Do this. Uh follower
form. Yeah I don't need batteries. Let's get a follower. Oh cool. Losing viewers. I'm not no
no I'm not you guys that you it doesn't even update that fast. Every time somebody says oh dude
you you blend like a thousand viewers. Dude it doesn't it updates like every two to three minutes.
You you don't know that. Hey guys let's leave. Let's all leave. Do you have a skincare routine?
I don't. Trust me you don't want to know it today because I didn't do anything. Just didn't take a
shower. I I probably should take a quick shower. Did I? Your faith is a resource spend it as you
would gold where you can always regain their trust with a well-placed gesture of kindness.
I give you power to read their minds. Okay so I can see what they want. You've declared a
doctrine which has granted you a new follower action. Okay take a quick shower but leave the
stream on. I might actually do that. Not right now but in a little bit before we do two point campus.
All right cool. How's everybody doing? It's it's kind of getting overgrown here isn't it?
You got a problem? Great leader the cult is growing by the day. It is time you gave it a name.
Sure my might. It's good to me. It's good to me. Oh water. Yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna take a shower
in between changing game. Is that weird? And on the BRB screen I'm just gonna put. Well I won't
spoil. Is that TOS? Can I do that? All right if I put just on the BRB screen just a running water
shower the kind of just like oh shower sound like and have just like stock audio of a guy going like
can I do that? Uh definitely sleep. So I can make beds now. How much does this cost?
These are expensive. I'll do three. Three is fine. What happened to your BRB art screen? Uh they were
thousands of images and more and more kept pouring in every week and we were never going to be able
to show them. And I only stream like two or three times a week. Not possible. Just was impossible.
It was physically not possible. Bunbob lives here. Rumble lives here. Yeah for those that don't know
I used to have a BRB art screen that would show like 10 to 20 pieces of art and we ran to the
problem where it was just we were months and months behind. So you would see images on that screen
from like a reference from like six months ago. And it got to the point where we had too many
where it was just never ever going to be physically ever possible. And I could have like the only way
I could have really caught up was if for like two or three straight days for like six to ten hours
for three four days just show a drawing on screen for five seconds. But why would I do that?
That just at that point that's just like showing it just to like get it over with.
I don't I don't want to do that. That would that just feels like well I don't want to do that.
So there's a there's a fan art channel in the discord that is tons of people use it. This is
a creative channel in the discord tons of people use it. That's where it is. What do you want? I'm
famished. We don't what do you mean you don't have food? What do you mean? How do you not have food?
Oh let's make some fish. How much is it making? All right yeah. Hey come get the fish and come
get some cool ingredients. Eat up. Go it's in front of you. The base is an eyesore. We need beauty to
celebrate your glory. Let us build decorations. Um okay fine. What do you got? Wow you did it truly
euro without flaw. I'm grateful. Okay oh wait. Should I do it again? I don't think I want to do
body pit yet. Farming bundle. Oh yeah hell yeah. I need another sleeping bag. Yeah that's true.
I have to recruit the new guy. Well hold on. I need to make sure he has a place to sleep.
Okay so you come on in. Convert me. Dimple. You can keep this for him. Okay so I want you to um
chop freeze but go to bed because who the fuck are you? I need another bed. Hold on. Where did
this person come from? Um I have sticks coming out of your head. Those sticks are those antlers.
Cool easy to level up but okay so we don't want this person ever doing uh faith or devotion stuff.
These names are lazy. Half the guys you want you want me to give the cool names to the people
that are going to die in like 40 minutes. Why would I do that? Wait wait wait you have a bed
over here. No no no I got it. I got it over here. This is yours. All right so do I have to sleep too
or do I not sleep? Okay uh decorations. They wanted some decorations. I'll put this one here.
We'll do two right there. There you go. There's your decoration. They want three. Uh is it three?
All right let's get rid of this big rock. It's kind of in the way. Why is he so greasy?
All right everybody. I want everybody to mine. Everybody over here. Get rid of this. Why does
he look so greasy? What's your problem? Okay read mind. Cult is a new building. Our glorious
cult grows. Okay bad chat. Boring. Must avoid them in the future. I agree. Good chat. I had
a great conversation with a fellow cult member. Okay rude. Somebody was rude to them in chat.
All right I need one more decoration. Is twitch integration? Yeah I know I'm not I don't have it
on. Last time somebody was talking about they said it's really slow and kind of bugged out
and they it's not like in a good spot right now apparently. We'll do it later. All right where's
Greml? Okay cool. Um dude I'm loving the Friday game vibes. Thanks. Hey welcome to the stream.
All right it's time. Everyone get in here. Uh we're gonna do crown. Okay I'm declaring. I declare
that um dance around the flame to increase the cult's faith. Oh yeah let's do it. Turn
off. Dude what the fuck dude? Turn off the giga chat filter. Fine. God damn it. So fuck it. I
didn't think people were gonna call me out on this but whatever. I'll turn it off. Nah I'm gonna keep
it on. I think it looked better with the sun don't you think? Why would I turn the filter off? Nah
keep it on. Even even if you know I don't really care. I like that I don't give a shit. All right
what is uh what are we doing? I need more. Were they were they not happy about something? 25 what
is that 25 what? Bones? Do a sermon. Oh I thought I thought there was a sermon. Oops okay.
Destroy their skeleton. Oh all right. Perform rituals in the temple. These usually raise faith
or help you solve problems. Rituals are performed using the bones of your fallen
enemies. Spiders. After slaying a non-believer dis-crate their bodies to gather their bones.
All right let's do a sermon though. Second. Bane weapons. Curse of three new curses will appear on
your yeah I'll see this. Cool. Please put on a different lego headpiece. I don't like this one.
Well now you don't get it at all. Okay looking good looking good. Uh cooking fire.
I need more. All right I gotta go on adventure. These ready? Oh shit they are ready. It destroys
the crop. Please we need cam. I'll put cam back on when I get back from the shower. How's that sound?
Please come back. No I I'm not I'm not gone. Please do Mr. Satan voice. I can do that
for a new follower of course I can. Well new followers. And make sure you say hi.
That person just followed. Every new follower I do that. All right I'm gonna I'm gonna go
adventure. Everybody happy? Uh I'm gonna make some food. Here if you're hungry you go ahead and eat
it. Foods up. Oh take a shower. I'm gonna take a shower. Relax. Who's this? You have so many
mouths to feed you must need some seeds. Okay. Okay I don't think I need it right now.
This game is awesome. This game is genuinely really fun. Whoa traders razor or hounds of
bait. Yeah. Oh I can take both? Wait oh I see. Oh camellia. Uh oh. So it is true the red crown
sits upon the brow of another. Ha we did everything we could. It matters not. We need not bother
Shamura with this. Deal with it brother. See come at. Whoa. All right stop being an idiot.
All right how do I get how do I do the bone thing? No no notice something about the game.
You can't mash. I guess maybe you can. You have to get the timing right to swing because if I go
like I guess it is that way. Okay I think you have to just like mash to keep it in succession
because if I don't mash it gets the combo gets caught. What about the bones? How do I do? Oh
you just break it. Okay and I didn't know if it was special. The game slows down when you connect
the hit. Match some shampoo into your hair. Okay. Oh nice. Hey I thought you I thought that was a
follower. I didn't think that was an enemy. You look like a retired porn star. Whatever you say.
Hi Mr. Raid automated. Thank you automated for the raid. Appreciate it. I don't know when that
was. I think it was a while ago. Welcome. Thank you auto. Poison damage nice. You left the heart.
I was looking at chat. I want to look at more stuff over here. I'll come back once I'm done
from the shower. 10% crit. Yeah although that's really good too. No I want the crit for sure.
More damage. Bones. I know I'm breaking everything. I'm taking so much longer.
Heard you shower every five years. Honestly I know people say like oh yeah I don't you know
I don't like wash my hair like all the time or once a week. If I do not take a shower every day
I am disgusting. Disgusting. I don't know. I must just be a gross person.
I'm so sweaty and greasy every day. If I do not take a shower every day
I am I am absolutely revolting to be around. I don't know maybe some people don't generate
as much filth as I do or something. Poison's great. Maybe it's your mayo and peanut butter diet.
Peanut butter is all right. I'm not going to listen to this slander. Peanut butter is really
good for you. It's so good for you. There's so many health benefits of just really good real
peanut butter. Get that get that slander out of this chat. Not if that's the only thing you eat.
I don't turn the stream off and go get a spoon and sit there and eat
crunchy peanut butter out of a jar and go that's it. Oh all of my nutrients. I'm not like Super
Mario. I don't just eat big mushrooms and then like go to that's not how it works.
It's not I don't have the Super Mario diet guys. It's not mushrooms and cake. The only thing Mario
eats in the entire series of Mario Brothers is the cake at the end and a bunch of mushrooms
and spaghetti. Yeah but that is that cannon though? I don't know if that's cannon.
Is it cannon? And he eats flowers too. You got some spaghetti on your overalls. Oh fuck you Luigi.
Yeah I've seen it. I think everyone's seen that video. Be honest are you actually Mario? Um no.
No. I don't have full health. You like partially hydrogenated or natural peanut butter.
They're I mean they they're natural good peanut butter where when you look at it
it's like watery on top. That's the good stuff. Now just a regular skippy peanut butter is so good
if you want. It's almost like a dessert peanut butter but the one with like the peanut oil on
the top it's oh man it is gold. That's gross. Yeah it's peanut oil. Skippy peanut butter is
is like a dessert peanut butter for me. Natural peanut butter with the oil that settles and you
have to mix it up a little bit or I'm telling you man sometimes I just scoop in there and I get
a bunch of the top layer oil and a little bit of the top layer of the peanut butter
and I eat it. It's delicious. Oh that's good and why is that gross somehow?
Yeah if you have a bag of Doritos on your desk in front of you right now sitting on your desk
you are not allowed to say oh that's gross. If you have if you look down if you're holding a
half empty bag of Doritos in your hand you do not say oh to me eating peanut butter with some peanut
oil on it. Let's get out of here with that. If you look down right now and your hand is covered in
fucking taki dust I don't want to hear shit about how I like peanut butter. It's not the same. What
what are you talking about? What about sushi? That's good. You drinking the oil. I'm not
I don't tip it up in like no I'm talking he's getting a little bit it's like a little test
it's a little tasting like that's it man it's not a big deal it's really not and it's way better
than the taki dust that's all over your fingers that one olive oil or butter they're both good
I mean olive oil is better I think but I don't put butter on that much stuff olive oil is better
yeah y'all just wait just wait when the when the apocalypse comes and and I'm and I'm the guy that
has like the 20 vats of peanut butter in his pantry you can live off that shit I'm gonna live
for a long time I'm gonna be sitting there people I'm gonna be trading peanut butter
for it's gonna be a commodity oh I don't envy you that's if I don't I'm kidding it's an old
routine old bit no it's not um I'll take this right what does recycle oh that's cool you've
already reused two jokes this stream listen guys I've said probably two to three trillion words
over the course of more than 10 to 11 plus years on camera okay I have said every single word in
the dictionary probably 50 times uh times 10 I've said two to three trillion words on camera
people will come to me like hey dude um do you know like what why did you say like seven years
ago um you said this in a video and I'm just kind of wondering like what your stance on that still
is just like I don't do I've said two trillion fucking sentences I don't know how fast you
should have asked me seven or eight years ago should ask me two months ago should ask me five
weeks ago I don't know what is this wait you're gonna eat this person do you run on pure instinct
no oh I can buy I'll take it oh it's a follower cool yeah break everything in this guy's entire
house it actually is worth breaking everything actually bye bye let's do it wait what does it do
oh okay it's just that one I think I only have a couple of those on lock yeah peanut butter is
good I don't eat peanut butter every single day I eat it sometimes it's a great snack you put it on
toast it's really filling you get it'll last a long time you can have it a bunch so you don't
just run out you don't just run guys you don't just run out of peanut butter you don't
I mean you the jar will be empty but it's not something that's like oh shit we're out of
peanut butter no it's it lasts a very very long time no it's not like the bullshit the
bullshit ice creams where they make they have a whole box and there's like two in the box
or like four in the whole box that's how you can look in there and be like somebody ate three of
these and I only had one not the same that one's good by the way I was that person I told you the
story about uh did I tell you guys that the twix ice cream bars or the note was snickers snickers
ice cream bars after I talked about that how um my brother used to get really pissed off at me
not just with snickers ice cream bars but with other very very valuable treats they would only
be like four or six in a box or something I think there was like four and hold on hold that thought
this is like a major fight attack him what are you doing man oh yeah okay so anyways
so I used to I love ice cream I love treats I need a little snack I loved it and in the house
there would always just be one box of like twix ice cream bars or snickers ice cream bars or
drumsticks whatever it was and I would always lie to my brother because I would I would go down
you could I could never eat just one of those I always ate two because they weren't it wasn't
enough those snickers ice cream bars were small so I would just be obsessed with it I would eat
the whole thing and it'd be like I'm I'm they I have to have another one so I'd eat two and then
like an hour later I heard one and my brother would not have one yet he would go to the box
one in the box he'd be like what are you doing Jeremy Jeremy you how many did you have
I'd be like what I had like one it was just lying and then he'd be like I know and he would go look
for wrappers he would go look for wrappers he'd be like oh yeah because I would leave that shit
on the desk and stuff or in my room whatever like and he would go be like oh yeah really
I was smart enough though I kept him in my fucking pocket what do you think I'm dumb
what do you always get so pissed uh let's see if they would I've said I obviously don't do that
anymore since I was like a teenager like I was I was like a young teenager I don't do that anymore
guys I don't really eat ice cream that much anymore I love ice cream but it's not I don't
really have that often it's so good though you do that with peanut butter no one is going to be
this thing but that's what I said it's not a peanut butter is not a high value treat
Quicks ice cream bars are incredibly high value my brother would not go into the pantry and be
like dude the peanut butter's half gone what the heck are you doing man peanut butter's gone
but no way that's not a high value treat that would never happen if peanut butter was half
gone one day or just be like whatever I don't care have jam or Nutella you sicko yeah I'm not
on the Nutella bullshit by the way I know Nutella whoa fuck Nutella no no peanut butter's better
I like me that's fine but I mean I'm not on board with the meme what even is Nutella
riddle me that what's Nutella it's like chocolate and hazelnut right actually that sounds fucking
awesome do you guys know I'm not making this up I swear to god I am promising this to you
I've never ever had Nutella like at the house or like out of the jar
I've never had it I've had it if it was in something else if it was like part of something else I've
never eaten it I know that's insane for a lot of you guys like you can't believe it some of you
but now I've never had it I definitely if you had I've consumed it before with oh yeah this
has Nutella in it it's like part of a dessert recipe or something definitely but never just oh
out of the jar Nutella no I don't think that's ever happened sacrifice a follower oh told you
have you ever had Marmite yes I have and I don't like it I think it's gross wait is Marmite
Vegemite the same thing no wait I've had one but not the other I think what's the difference
isn't it it's kind of it's not the same but it's in the same realm right I think I have had I've
definitely had both what's the one that tastes like solid soy sauce because that's the one that
I don't like they're both like that that's Marmite yeah so there's a it's a solid
soy sauce I'm actually not a big fan of soy sauce it's kind of too overpowering for me
what's wrong oh they're hungry I got it I got it I got it I know this place is gross
yeah uh how about stringy meat gruel cherry bowl and here come and get it what's wrong
what's going on um what's happening um oh who hasn't eaten it's all right whatever
level up pulp level two yeah unlock the rest of this shit I need to save and quit it's a bug okay
halt upgraded oh yeah there we go okay I need to do uh there's some poop everywhere
is there okay there's one more one person that actually like went behind the rocks
how's everybody doing oh all right I need to do a ritual at first let's do this oh strawberries
whatever these are okay how we doing building an outhouse so I can poop in peace okay
um all right I want to do this farmer station allows all of us to water nearby crops
put seeds here oh yeah let's do that first farm is gonna be over here
then somebody can water them one and two right there let's go it's not close enough to the farm
plots how is that not close it was right here isn't it has to be over the plots oh well I can
move it right and I can you guys said I could move it anything right is it yeah you can move
it all right so what's the problem oh all right please give me a break well I'll just I'm gonna
move the the farm will grow this way and I'll replant everything I'll put it right here for now
I'll just replant everything later move the plants yeah this game's really really fun
I like that there's more than just the Binding of Isaac this whole management mode which is
really cool all right let's go to the build menu and you said I can move stuff edit buildings
okay yeah there we go okay will you move with the bag or am I gonna make you angry oh that's not
all right well whatever you'll get up you'll figure it out you'll get up and figure it out
right I want this to be like that yeah no like this I didn't steal this bed we simply moved
okay all right that's good pause it some seeds okay cool cool now wait this is too it's too late
to do a ritual Yarmer how does it level up all right now I have to kill do I just kill this person
you're gonna tend to the farm oh shit I need one two I need two more just fill it out the one that
makes you lose yeah who's the who's the weakest link here I want to build okay so I think it's
gonna be you oh yeah goodbye okay and now welcome to the team it's really nice to meet you
you can um how do I do it how many more people are there shit Marbury oh that farm's fine
okay okay oh good I go um worship what do you want when times are tough we can cook
grass meals followers won't like it but it beats starving make him eat grass okay how's everybody
doing I need another bed no wait somebody has to die um in here we do a ritual right okay
bonfire ritual or okay sacrifice who's dying they're all level one who had all the awful shit
you did hey have a nice life I didn't know it was gonna be that violent what's the difficulty
it's not hard cool thank you there's much more you can take from them give them gifts complete
quests and perform blessings for them and you will increase their loyalty once they are totally
loyal to you it will give you everything they own watch as I show you follower come back in here
increase the followers loyalty to level them up and they will reward you with devotion and a
commandment stone fragment each time a follower levels up they will generate additional devotion
when at a sermon okay increase their loyalty give the follower a blessing once a day when you
interact with them we'll give them gifts complete quests and perform sermons okay
I got it I have much to teach you I'm old and grow weary visit me at my home and I will show you
how to harness the true power of the red crown an overworld map okay you sacrificed
merberry your followers are uneasy about it how are you guys doing what's that above their head
what's that mean oh it's the okay when they actually put one in okay got it how's everybody
on food maybe make a little bit of food basic variable all right there if you want it say a
letter do a sermon after they eat I will all right you're good you're good all right let's do a
sermon so I can just do this once a day nice my mother's will just get it if you level up the
followers you'll get more oh well they liked that all right here's we're gonna do I'm gonna do one
more run and then we're gonna move on to we're gonna play two point campus so let's do one more
run I'm gonna I will play this again though this game is awesome you'll definitely see this game
again or depending how long this takes yeah maybe I'll just save it we'll just move to two point
campus in a minute you've discovered my humble cottage be careful you don't make the same mistakes
I did or you'll end up in a place just like this now perhaps a game of knuckle bones you don't know
you don't know it wait we playing spindle stone really okay is this actually spindle stones
your score is calculated by adding all your dice together when dice the same number are placed in
the same column multiply their value destroy your opponent's dice by matching yours to theirs
um I don't get it just add your dice together but you want to match dice you want to destroy
your opponent's dice by matching yours to theirs I don't I'm just gonna play it I don't understand
so I need to match their dice bro that's fucking I've just beat the guy you lose uh oh shit
oh shit I get it I get it now I actually get it now now I understand what's going on
I understand what's happening now fuck um when is it over when we can't play anymore
oh you piece of shit I lost I won how did I win oh I get it okay cool oh that's fun
cool so these not gonna appear I get it very very fun let's wager sure all right after this
I'm gonna take a quick break and then we'll play two point camps all right let's go
four oh that's fine why would you not get rid of my one oh come on six yeah that's fine keep the
shitty ones I don't care um so I put this in the middle because it's okay can I triple this
yeah let's go all right that row's done you can't do anything else there that's fine
I can increase this left side so I'll win this left side yeah I win you lose thanks to the 10
gold you piece of shit what that's 10 gold I'll take it let's do it again one more one more then
I'm done and then I'm gonna move on to two point campus I like this game this is cool good keep
that shitty number oh yep no five no wow all right he's dumb I'm good nope sorry you're not
gonna get you're not gonna beat me I could have gotten wow not a misplay we're good I want him
to keep that too right or no I want to get rid of my two oh okay I want you to keep that one
I'll be fine on that right side that's all right that's so bad you're gonna be kidding me it's
all right as long as I can complete the don't have anything to as long as I can complete this before
he does anything on the right side I went good no no it's good I still won oh yeah I win
yeah no five yeah see what I win all right cool that's really fun very very awesome all right
let's save the game I'm gonna take a quick break I'll be back when I come back we're gonna make
sure two point campus is ready to go it is a sponsor segment of the stream let's play it it
looks really fun it looks really sweet two point campus incoming I'll be right back oh the shower
routine can I let's see uh shower sound effect shower sounds white noise shower sounds this
doesn't exist hold on I could probably make one of these and have it be like a million view video
how about just like man humming sound effect this why is this one scary
what scary man humming what does it sound like oh it's the
royalty-free humming sound effect no man humming sound effect how do I loop a video
this is like 10 seconds long um how do I play back how do I loop it how do you loop a video
loop okay and then periodic fart reverb
I'll see you in a minute BRB