and you pick you pick yep just like that in Nickelodeon you pick get your toll-free
phone out and dial 1-800 you pick Nickelodeon press 1 for Ren and Stimpy
press 2 for Doug press 3 for our real monsters you pick can you just link the IP to me bonk
boost what's another way to say crit with the B boo uh boss boo no bonk boost boost bonk fan
of war boost bonk BAM are we ready yeah boost bonk BAM boost bonk BAM make sure
you the first B is important which is boost I gotta get the boost yeah and I'm halfway
there next part is bonk I got it in one shot all right you get so get you get get the second B
of the equation fire so then what do I do all right so now we're gonna go bonk and then take
out the melee when you get a chance it's time for the BAM let's get this demo up here no no no this
way this way this is spy over here see the spy where I just went in the end that yeah oh my god
he's right here he's over here somewhere where okay come up top there's a heavy boost bonk BAM
totally kill the heavy with our three damage swings boost bonk BAM you know how easy we would
have won that fight if we were using weapons mm-hmm watch out boost so don't don't fuck with the
formula when we have to both be on the exact same page the formula sucks no we have to be on
the same exact page get the boost I have the boost I don't do not move on to bonk phase stairs
for the boost you get the boost I'll be under these stairs yeah watch out there's a demo coming
over oh make sure the get there's a pyro outside the store excellent you got the boost don't don't
move on to bonk yet I'm going right I'm going right you see where I am right I'm right with you
oh century bonk bonk don't run no no no where you going where you going what I'm not dead I'm
alive okay I have I've got those he was too aggressive with this entry I've got boost
boosting okay where you though I'm going back here I'm behind this sniper the sniper has no
idea he's him he's about to get banned who's bonk bam he's taunting has no idea please tell
me this thank God don't ever taunt you might get boost bonk bam who's bonk man doesn't have
you chasing us just be be aware you get you got your bam ready you get your boost ready
oh he's had my boost ready this is bad this is a terrible place to do this this is a bad place to
do this no this is a great place no I just quit this guy for 11 let's see if I can go right in
front of this guy and have him just shoot himself damn it hey hey drama drama you ever seen this
through this window I don't think you've ever seen this there's these people here and they
they're at they're looking at this map and then they start dancing where what are you talking
about I see exit I see what would you do it didn't did the dancing okay where are you give me a
corner I see I see there is an engineer over there in that building there's also to make make
great teleporter right here we can't talk kill with a stupid fan of war I just we just double team
him yeah whoever comes out of this just just just swarm them just mash him into the corner
yeah make it so get like what what what I wasn't even close was I I already have to turn around
and looked at me he's dead this engineer is following me back here I might have to kill him
what is it here yes it's him again don't oh how much help did he I had five health get over don't
stand on it stand back literally I was right oh my god this takes forever oh shit I gotta run
boost give me the book I'm good I'm good all right I'm still here I'm safe oh shit no I'm not I'm
not safe at all just don't die and I'll be back I get up I gonna kill this guy I got him okay it's
clear up top I have 12 HP house the first house where people go through there's two centuries in
there and I just backstab oh no I'm coming back is it still in there still wanted I still want to
do this teleporter oh it's gone it's gone that's why I said this by second wait come to where the
teleporter was okay okay the engineer should be back in a second when you just chill a second
no let's let's bonk run up the stairs and we'll figure it out I wonder is it is it still here no
figure it in no turn around and hit the century our turn around and hit the century that was
perfect this is all the stupid shit we've done this is the stupidest why is so much interesting
stuff happening