Hello everybody. I don't want to scare you. That's why I'm talking really lightly.
Okay, so we're changing the game here. Let me just change this. So this is the closing shift.
This is requested. A game where you run a coffee shop but it's very scary or something. I don't
know. Haunted coffee shop? Closing shift. All right, is there an audio warning with this game? Is this
gonna- is this a game that's gonna scream and blow everybody's eardrums out? Or what? Gotta be careful
of this. It's not it. Okay. All right, let me put this over here so you guys can see what's going on.
I turn the lights off. This is closing shift. Should I make the lights off? I want me to dim this-
this one? Should I dim the ring light thing? What? Is it good? Turn off the VHS effect. I don't have
settings. Let me just move this. All right, let's go guys. New game. Oh no, I'll be late for work.
I should be on my- I should be on my car by now. DST, Tab, Shift, Run, Crouch, Inventory. Okay.
Well, that's- the sensitivity is so high. All right, graphics. Resolution, yeah. Texture quality,
12 and a half percent. Why would it be 12? That seems really low. Couldn't it be 100?
What is it, milk? Like, milk percent? It's for the effects. Oh. Okay, hard and- SSR, overkill,
VHS filter, off. Yeah, that makes- I'll puke if that's on. Controls, yeah. Our general,
make sure this is good. Even lower? Okay. Refresh, it's changed. Okay, let's do it.
Do you drink skim milk? One percent, two percent raw or whole milk? Two percent.
Anything else is just- it's just- I mean, one percent's fine. One percent and two percent are
both. Like, why would you drink anything else? Whole milk is good if you- okay. No. You know what?
I had whole milk recently and it really tasted like- I don't know, it tasted like fucking meat.
It was weird. It tasted like beef, like meat. I didn't like it. I haven't had it in a long time.
All right, I'm gonna be late for work. I gotta hurry up. Leave apartment. Wait,
do I need to take anything? I think I'm good. Let's go. Well, you know the difference of one
percent and two percent were side by side. Probably not, no. But I could tell you the
difference between skim and one percent. I could tell you the difference between two percent and
skim. One percent at whole. I have to go to work. I think I need the sensitivity drop even more.
Has anyone ever had their mouse sensitivity further than here on every single PC video
game that has ever released? Ever. That has ever released. I don't think- I don't think so.
That's better. Mine is- it's always so, so high. Really? Is my DPI just all fucked up or something?
What the fuck was that? Was that a flashlight or anything? I thought that was a gun. Someone's phone.
What do I do with this? Someone's phone. Use it? How do I use it? Enter? E? I need to go through-
no need to go through here right now. E. It doesn't do anything? All right, how do I get out of here?
What do I just do? This is so dark I can't see anything. I missed it? Go to the car. Wait. Oh.
Oh, okay. Get in the car. How do I get in the car? E? Lights off. The lights are off! That's
the wrong car. Doesn't seem like it. Hold on. Run. Interact. Yeah, I'm clicking. Clicking. Click.
Click. That's the right car. Yeah. Click. Am I supposed to be able to open this? I didn't get the
car key. Oh, come on. I can't see anything. I need the keys to the car. Okay. How far up was
my apartment? Is it all the way up? This one here, right? Dude, I don't know what apartment is mine.
Which apartment is mine? Wasn't it up here? He's going to- I don't know what apartment mine is.
Is it up another thing? Down a floor? I might need to put the phone down. I don't- How do you
put the phone down? Items in hand. All right. Tab. Left, right. Scroll. Space. Go back to the car.
People just f**king with me? All right. I'm- Somebody- What does it say? Look for a person.
I can't go that way. Find the owner. Give the phone to the guy. What guy? This guy- This guy
couldn't see this guy. This guy didn't exist. All right. Is it as dark for you as it is for me?
Excuse me. Excuse me. Hey, um, are you looking for something? Well, I found this. Give me it.
Welcome. I just want to test something. Oh, that's kind of creepy. I kind of hate it, but I like it.
This is my car. Okay. Go to work. My car. I actually don't mind this because it's not
shaky and jittery. This is actually not bad looking. Open and close. Okay. So it's time for
work. Do I get an employee door? No reflection. God damn it. Okay. Put away my stuff and talk to
Senpai02. Back room here. Sorry, I'm late. Be careful next time. I'm going to tell the manager.
Turn up the game volume. I'm very sorry. I'll be careful. Being careful is not enough. Tell me you
won't be late. Do you understand? Yes, sir. I will not be late again. You also messed up some orders,
don't you? If you have any trouble with the order, there are some tutorial videos for you. So look
through it. Okay. I'll take a look. Oh, and one more thing. Never know what's going to happen in
imaginopolis. If you ever need any help, just click me. Make sure to leave your phone in the
locker. You better not be texting anyone during work. Yes, sir. That was so weird. It's like
somebody magnetized him through the door. Okay. Put my stuff away. A phone. Is that it? My car key.
Recipes. Ooh. Okay. Hot. Drip coffee is just coffee. A latte. I know all this. I already know
all this. Latte. Coffee and milk. Green tea latte. Vanilla syrup steamed milk matcha powder.
I'm drinking one of those right now. Well, not a latte, but all right. Easy. Caramel macchiato.
I don't even look. That is drip coffee, water, and whatever flavor the customer asks for. No,
sorry. That's an Americano. Whoops. Who cares? It's my first day. Americano is water and espresso.
I fucking got it completely wrong. Oops. All right. So cool. Chocolate chip chilla
peccino. Blended ice, coffee, milk, chocolate sauce. All right. Well, whatever. I think I know
what I'm doing. Corial video. Oh, we're already starting. Can I help you? Did you say chillas
coffee? I've never been to one of these fancy places before. I feel uneasy. There's something
strange about this place. My daughter seems to be a fan of this place and now I'm here. However,
uh, I'll leave the drinks to you. Oh, and I'd like to get two of them. Would you want a latte
and a coffee? Oh, that'd be just fine. It's really uncomfortable here. However, can you charge such
a price for something like this? Do you want a latte and a coffee? Order sticker. Okay. Coffee.
Coffee. Got that. Here's your coffee, sir. Thank you so much. And, uh, also you wanted a latte,
which is coffee and steamed milk. You got it. Okay. Coffee and steamed milk.
Ah, boulders. Where's the steamed milk? Isn't this right here? How do I turn this on?
Just one moment, sir. How do I turn that on? No, I don't want ice in there. How do I turn the milk
on? I need milk. Oh shit. Okay. That's it, right? There you go.
What happened? Huh?
Okay. There's my steamed milk. There's my coffee. How do I put the coffee? How do I put the steamed
milk in the coffee? Just click it. Does that work? I need the lid, but is that a latte right now?
I'm so confused. That is a latte, so I just need a lid. Where are the lids? Okay.
Will you pick it up? I need to label it? Where's the labeler? Cold cup lids? I don't know. Does it
label? Sticker? It's in your inventory already. What about this thing? Okay, so I'm going to pick
that up if I touch that. Watch the tutorial on the computer. All right, we'll just sit there for a
minute because I don't... Okay. I can't click the computer. Oh, how do I watch the tutorial?
He's getting a zero star review. It's behind the computer. What? There's nothing behind the
computer. Just one minute, sir. I'm still working on this. Is it in here? Don't put a cleaning
product in the guy's fucking drink. Order sticker. Latte. That's not the latte. All right. Can I
throw shit in the trash? That's... I don't even know what that is. Is there a trash? All right,
clicking anything just picks it up. How do I throw this shit in the trash? Like, just throw it all
away. All of it. Besides that. Throw the whole thing in the trash. Okay. Coffee. Coffee cup.
Hot coffee. Milk. There's milk. Steam the milk. Great. Put milk in there. Label.
Cover. Label. Bro. What the fuck is going on here? It's just gone. He left. What the fuck?
Watch the tapes. What tapes? Oh my fucking God. Okay. What is that? Okay. That's how you...
Get this out. Hot drink tutorial. Yeah. Okay. Get the ticket. You have two tickets. Go...
I just was like, I'm out of here. You obviously don't know what you're doing.
Yup. That's what I did. Steam the milk. That's what I did. That's exactly what I just did. Take
the cup. Put it over there. Steam milk inside of it. What did I do wrong? Put the cup. Do it.
Put it down. Put a lid on it. And then put the coffee label on that. Okay. It just disappeared.
I did the whole thing right. Let me make sure I get this right. Yeah. You do cold coffee.
Or do you do hot coffee? Ice. Blend up the ice. Put the board in there. It's the shit
disappearing from your hand or disappearing and going into your inventory that's like freaking
me out. Do the whatever you want for those flavors. Put the bullshit in here like the
cinnamon twigs or whatever the hell it is. All right. I get it. Where's the fucking next customer?
I hope you're in the news. I hear stalker cases are on the rise. It's scary. Women like me,
you see, I have to be careful. All the guys are always staring at me. So careful too.
They don't have to worry as much as I do, but you should watch out either way. Dark mocha chip
please. Dark mocha chip. You got it. Dark blended ice, coffee, milk, chocolate,
blended ice, coffee, milk, chocolate. Okay. There's no ice in there. Ice. Cold cup.
Cold cup. Cold cup. Uh, coffee. Get that down. Put it with ice. Very nice. Okay. And we need
coffee, milk, chocolate sauce, and cocoa powder and milk. Chocolate, dark chocolate, right?
Where's dark chocolate? It's dark chocolate. Where's dark chocolate? I don't see a dark
chocolate syrup. I see chocolate. I'm making the wrong one. Just regular chocolate. Did it go in?
I never said dark. All right. Here you go. There you are. Thank you.
God, do I really need the ticket on there? Oh, come on. Enjoy. The powder makes it dark.
This is too many orders. All right. Four regular coffees. A matcha cake please. Stop pushing me.
Salted caramel mocha. Then I'll have a matcha. Oh my God. You always can't finish your drink.
So let's share, man. Sure. Let's do that. One pumpkin cake. I think I'll have something to
eat too. You can order first. I'll have, um, hot cocoa. Hot cocoa. Are you serious? I don't have
any money right now. You should have said that first. Come on. I'll buy you one. What do you
want to drink? Yes, but just say it. He's got money. No, it's not like that, but really anything
is fine. Uh, really I want a white mocha. Okay. Any food? No, just the drink. Come on. Let's order
some food. But, uh, okay. Uh, American waffles. Waffles. Uh, thanks. Both of you. Hey, where are
you looking at? Did you hear that noise? What noise? I didn't hear it either. Oh, it's probably
nothing. It must be your imagination. Okay. So, um, guys, I got a, a, a, what do you want?
I made up my mind. An apple pie. Apple pie. Um, apple pie. I'm just going to give you an apple
pie and just tell you to leave. Apple pie, waffles, a white mocha, apple pie. Wait,
mocha cake. Pumpkin. No, I think it's this one because I don't remember the pumpkin cake.
Was there a pumpkin cake? I remember the American waffle. I think, no, it is this one. Wow. Can't
believe you remembered all that. We'll be waiting. Oh my God. Okay. Pumpkin cake, pumpkin cake,
American waffle, apple pie. Pumpkin cake, American waffle, pumpkin cake, American waffle,
pumpkin cake. How do I put this down? I need a label for each individual food item.
American waffle, pumpkin cake. Uh, what else was it? A matcha chiffon cake. Hey, got it. Uh,
uh, okay. Now what do you want? A white mocha, salted caramel mocha, coffee,
steamed milk, white chocolate, steamed milk, milk, milk, milk, milk, milk, milk. I'm not soy milk.
White chocolate. Okay. Bingo. White chocolate. Where is it? Move this fucking out of the way,
please. White chocolate sauce. Lid. This is the white mocha. Take it. The next one is
the salted caramel mocha, coffee, steamed milk, caramel syrup, hazelnut syrup, caramel, hazelnut,
chocolate, caramel, hazelnut, chocolate, caramel, hazelnut, chocolate, caramel, hazelnut, chocolate,
caramel, hazelnut, chocolate. Oh, throw it away. Fuck you. Don't move. I'm so mad. Who puts almond
syrup on the right? Where's chocolate? Oh my God. Whatever. Chocolate, hazelnut, caramel.
Here, take it. And then somebody wants an apple pie. Macha chalupa chino. Macha, macha chalupa.
What is it? Macha chalupa chino. Ice milk, macha whipped cream, ice milk, macha whipped cream,
ice milk, macha whipped cream. Ice milk, macha whipped cream, ice milk, macha whipped cream.
Ice. Milk. Macha. Macha. Whipped cream. Whipped cream. This is the, uh, this thing.
You're welcome. And then you wanted, what was it? What was the last one? American apple pie.
All right. Now, now fuck off. What is in my inventory? I have a fucking full Resident Evil
inventory right now. What is going on here? Thank you. I have so much shit in my inventory.
Whew. Here's my order. Latte. You got it. Latte is just milk and, is it right? It's just milk and
coffee. Coffee steam milk. I just might, sometimes it could be wrong. There you go. Fast. Fast as fuck.
Hey, I'm a private investigator. Did you spot anything suspicious around the area?
There have been numerous reports of people getting harassed. I was wondering if you've seen anything
in the store. Probably if something ever happens. Probably closing the store early.
Don't want to get in trouble. I don't want to get in trouble. I mean, we don't want to get in trouble.
Did somebody just press the right most fast forward button on Sims? What was that?
Sweep the floor. It's gonna be like a fucking monster. God damn it. How do I sweep the floor?
Okay. How do I sweep the floor? Okay. There's gonna be like somebody in here. I'm gonna have to like
hide from a murderer or something, right? Right now, I'm gripping this fucking broom like a baseball
bat. Like the actual broom part, I'm like holding that like a lightsaber. What the fuck, dude? What's
going on? How do I get out of here? How do I get out of here? Oh, am I closed? It's just
open. Do I have to lock the door? Oh, my keys. Dude, I can't see anything. Ah, fuck you. What is
that? Put this shit back. Pick up the car key. Hello? Why can't I pick the car key up? Dude, get
the fuck out of here. How do I get rid of this? It's built milk. Why can't I put this down?
Crash item. Built milk. Whole milk weapon. How do I get rid of this? More? Oh, yeah, I fucking hate
this game. Anything else? I can't throw these away. Put it in the fridge? Why would I put fridge?
This was on the ground. Who would put it back in the fridge? Pretty fazbears. Okay. Can I like watch
TV or something? Okay, leave. Do I have my car keys? Okay. Another day. Put my stuff away and talk to
Senpai. Hey. Hey, seriously? You're late again. Did you oversleep? I'm so sorry. No, not I'm so sorry.
I want you to not be late. This is the second time. I'm sorry. A little more enthusiasm would
help, don't you think? Why don't you ask your mama to wake you up? Dick. Dick. Where does this guy
keep going, by the way? Does he just leave? I didn't talk to him twice? Oh, I closed this shit.
I didn't do that. All right, put away my stuff. Start the day. Let's go. All right, I got my
coffee there. All right, let's go. How much shit are you ordering? Coffee, scone, coffee,
apple pie, waffle, apple pie, scone, toffee. Okay. Is somebody like crouching? Okay. What was it?
Apple pie, scone, toffee, waffle. American. Okay. No, I do need that. This is the apple pie.
Go. Here's your waffle. You need a coffee too. That's fine. Here you go. Making it really easy.
Thank you very much. Appreciate that. Thank you. And you wanted a American scone caramel toffee.
Do we even have those? Oh, okay. Scones are good. Ah, hey girl. Thank you very much. Hmm.
Uh-huh. You look impressed. No need to... Nihongo? Go zoom me. I've been living here for more than
15 years. Hey girl, something's not right about this place. I didn't think that because I'm not
around town. Something about this store. Maybe because of that guy over there. Huh? I guess it's
just my imagination. Are you haunted by any chance? Well, maybe I am. Uh-huh. Either way, I'm running
late so I'm gonna have to go. So long. Okay. What do you want? Vanilla. Oopsie no. Plus milk?
Plus milk. You come into a coffee shop and you order a glass of milk. What do you want? How do
I make that? Ice milk. Ice milk. Vanilla. Vanilla. Ice milk. Vanilla. Vanilla. Vanilla. Got it. Okay.
Then you just want like fucking milk? I want just milk. You want just... You just want like a carton
of milk. I don't think... I can't sell these to you. I can't just sell you a carton of milk.
Like, all right, I guess I'm going to. Here, milk. Um, you want two milks? Okay. Here you go. Yeah,
I have to go have two full glasses of milk at the coffee shop. Holy shit. You're cute. Can I have
your number? Would you like to order anything? Hmm. Your heart, please. I think I'll go with
your recommendation. What's your name? Tell me your name. Our recommendation would be the limited
time only double chocolate chilapecino. I see. What's your phone number? I'm that good looking,
aren't I? I lose words myself. I'm quite popular around here. That was your chance. This guy is a
clown. Uh, yeah. You just hit... What do you want? You want a fucking coffee or what? Here. Order a
fucking coffee. What's with the attitude? There's no attitude. I'm fucking... I'm like working.
You'll regret this. I'm going up. I'm literally like... Do you want a drink or not? God. You know,
I'll tell you, I think I mentioned this before, but like working at like food retail like this,
you must have to put up with such horse shit every fucking goddamn day. Here comes the rant.
What the fuck? I thought that was a giant like centipede. I thought that was a monster. I thought
this was a giant centipede monster or something. Take out the trash. All right. Okay. Like, fuck
off. Fucking blanker. Bus tables? Did that work? What was that? I, uh, with a toilet cleaner?
I did. I thought it was just like a bucket of cleaning solution. I don't know. What is this?
How do I bust the tables? Millionaire streamer doesn't know. I don't know where the material...
I don't know where the cleaner is. Oh, okay. All right. It's right there. All right.
I didn't know what it was. Is it more tables to bust? I put the... I want to... Is that where
the milk guy was sitting? That is where the milk guy was sitting. Is that a neighbor? What the
flying fuck are you doing, lady? Jesus, young ones these days. Holy shit. I was like, I'm like,
okay, I'm fucking swinging. I'm like, I'm fucking, I'm ready to start smashing ahead. You know what
I mean? Like, yo, everybody's got a circle, right? That's like five, like six, 10 feet around you.
Nobody enters that circle going a hundred miles per hour. What's up? What's going on here? Hey,
your neck. God, that was a YouTuber reaction. I mean, that was a, that is a, that is a, I'm ready
to punch someone in the face reaction. It is your first closing shift. Oh God, that's the title.
I have a question. Do you get strange customers around at night? Well, sometimes we do. Just
brush it off if they come. Focus on your work. There's plenty to do. Like, you gotta be fucking
kidding me. Actually, I'm afraid I might be, yeah, being stalked. You want me to believe someone is
interested in the likes of you? What the fuck? I guess I'll come flying to help you if anything
ever happens. Dude, you. All right. Picking up the fucking DHS player. Like, rip off the wall.
Sit that shit right fucking here. Can you use the phone? Is there a phone? Is there a telephone? Oh,
I have a phone, don't I? Can I use it? How do I use it? Go to the bathroom. Can you order a macchiato
for me? Okay. I'll have a cinnamon roll, churros, and a cup of coffee, please, and add whipped cream
to it. All right. Cinnamon roll, churro, coffee, whipped cream. Paying separately. Together is fine,
and I'll have a matcha chilla piccino. It'll be fine. What did Mari want again? Macchiato. Oh my
god, I have to remember this. You mean chilla piccino. She's gonna catch a cold. No, she won't.
You know, I would be fine, but Mari won't be. You didn't hear what I said earlier, right?
Hear what? Caramel macchiato hot, please. Hot caramel macchiato. Got it. Okay. Well, I'm just
gonna, whatever you put on here, I'm just gonna do it. All right. Matcha. Do the food first. It's
easy. Oh, strawberry and cream roll, strawberry churro. Wait, what did I just put in there? Did
I put that in? Is that correct? That's wrong. I don't, strawberry, strawberry churro. I forgot
immediately. Okay. Strawberry and cream something something. That's it, right? Strawberry and cream.
Now you want coffee, whipped cream, macchiato. Coffee, whipped cream is easy. Coffee, whipped cream
right here. Hot coffee with a whipped cream. I feel like that just kind of would disappear after
a second window. Matcha, chilapecino. This is cold. Are these both cold? Okay. So this is blended
ice, blended ice, blended ice twice, milk, coffee, milk, milk, coffee. There's nothing.
Wait, wait, one of them's hot. Caramel macchiato matcha chilapecino. Oh, it is hot. Okay. So I'll
do the cold one first. Caramel macchiato. Caramel matcha chilapecino. All right. Milk, matcha,
whipped cream. Matcha, whipped cream. Put a lid on it. Go. There you are. And then you wanted
caramel macchiato is coffee, steamed milk, caramel, caramel sauce, caramel sauce, caramel syrup.
Caramel sauce, caramel syrup. There you go. Now I gotta be scared yet. It's fucking weird. Thanks.
I'll pay you back now. Hey, wasn't that the guy on the bus that was creepy? I think we got off a
different place. Who are you? Latte please. Latte. That'll be 370 yen. Let's see. Four, five, six,
seven, and a hundred. Okay. One, two, two, one hundred for two for boy seventy. Well, I guess
better luck next time. I'll pay the rest. But be a good Samaritan. That's what my father always told
me. It's cold today, so drink something warm. Yeah. For someone like me, don't mention it.
Oh, thank the Lord. Oh, by the way, have you seen any ghosts lately? No? I see. You'll be fine then.
What was that about? I don't know. Must be the stress of poverty. Poor guy. Get it?
I'm sorry. I'll have a vanilla latte. What the fuck are these guys? Vanilla latte and a latte.
Wait, why did I come in here? Okay. Vanilla latte. Oh, no, no, because I don't know. What is the...
Okay. Vanilla latte. Is it iced? Coffee, steamed milk. Okay. Two coffee, two steamed milk. Uh, milk.
Steamed milk. Uh-huh. And then vanilla syrup, right? Right? Did that go in? Did that go in?
Vanilla syrup. Fuck, I figured. Oh, this is vanilla. What the fuck? What just happened?
Oops. Sorry. I'll fix it. Hold on. There you go. Close the fridge. Close this fucking door.
Is the other door locked? Bus. I'm busing. I'm busing. I'm busing. I'm busing. Minus two. Okay.
There are the... Where are the tables to bus? Oh, right here. Does everybody clean up after
themselves? Do we have a trash out here or no? There's no trash. All right. But is there a trash
here somewhere? What's going on? Lights are going to turn off any second. One, two, three.
Get to the breaker quick. Where's the breaker? It's right here. What's going on? What is happening?
What is going on right now? What the fuck is going on? What is making that sound? Ice machine. Shut
up. Blender? I don't know what's making that sound. It's the ice machine. Oh, get the fuck
out of here, man. Where is this? Where is he? Can I call anyone? I don't think I can't use the phone.
The drive-through? Where's the drive-through window? Kill him. I... Lock the front door, please.
I get... Whoa, don't... How do I lock the front door? Do I have to go out there? I have to go out
there? Do I have to go out there? Flip the sign. I can't close this fucking door. Can I go in out
there with a fucking weapon? I wish I could pick up a fucking weapon or something. I think I can.
Can I pick... Give me the broom. I mean, give me a fucking broom. Give me something heavy with a
heavy end. What is that? I'm telling you right now, you're getting a fucking plant in your head.
I'm taking this TV out of the fucking wall and I'm overhead throwing it as hard as I fucking can
into your head. You understand? I picked up my phone. Christ. Oh, Christ. It's the dude... It's
the phone. You gotta be fucking shitting me. I'm telling you. I'm telling you. Fucking guy gets
a TV. I'm talking like Tom and Jerry style cartoon fucking style. You know what I mean?
Like it's going over my head and I'm running and throwing it. I don't want to open this door.
Where's my phone? Don't I have a phone? Don't I have a phone? Where's my phone? I need a...
Where's my phone? Yeah, you gotta be kidding me. If there's another lady with like a baby carriage
down here. Go, go. Get the fuck out of here. The car won't start. I have to take the bus.
Motherfucker, don't jump scare incoming. Probably. I don't know. Bus stop. Wait for the fucking bus.
I don't... I can't turn around. What? What are you looking at? What do you want? Give me one sec.
Can I pause it? Yeah. Uh, I think Otto needs to go out. I can hear him. I'll be right back. This
will be probably the last BRB of the night. I'll be right back. I can hear Otto. He just went...
I won't be long. One sec. All right, I'm back. Yeah, he was just bored. He was just bored. He
did a good look. I need a haircut. Go, Otto. No, he was just bored. He was just running around.
Put my stuff away. Your hair looks good. I could use a trim. All right, so that... The guy was
in front of the apartment. Where's the other worker? Where's the other worker?
You scared the shit out of me. Leave me alone when I'm in the restroom. God damn it. Get to work.
Dude, I... I... Oh my god. What did you just order at the drive-thru, dude? You don't... Order like
one or two... All right, I'll make you an entire like steak dinner and like eight drinks. I'll
be right back. Okay, you want two American... You want two caramel macchiatos, two scones.
What are they? American scone. American scone. American scone. Here's one. One, two, and then you
want two... How do I make caramel macchiatos? Coffee... It's hot. Coffee, steamed milk, caramel
syrup. Coffee, steamed milk, syrup, and sauce. Any milk? Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Caramel syrup,
caramel sauce. There's one. You need a fucking lid. I don't want you to have to carry the... Hey,
what? Did we talk about what was wrong? What is that? How is that wrong? Wait, hold on.
Coffee, steamed milk, syrup, sauce. I don't understand. It's iced. No, it's not. It's hot.
Coffee, steamed milk, caramel syrup, caramel sauce. Coffee, steamed milk, caramel syrup, caramel sauce.
Caramel sauce, caramel syrup. What's wrong? That was actually correct. You want the other one too?
Okay. Yeah, of course you do. You ordered it. The one guy ordering the Thanksgiving dinner at the
drive-thru. Just... Hurry, hurry, hurry. Come on, come on, come on, come on. He's gonna be pissed.
What's happening? It's the milk. It's steamed milk, man. It's steamed milk. Milk. Milk.
Steamed milk? What's happening? How is that wrong? I have so many of these. I have so many of these
in my elbow voice ever since I turned like 33. What do you want? Hi. How are you? Green tea latte
and one of those waffles too. Can I even buy anything? Green tea latte and one of those.
Oh, and one green tea latte and a waffle. Yes. The green tea latte and waffle here are delicious.
I always go for these too. Cool. Well, thank you for serving them. My son likes them too.
Are you alone? I'll give you this if you like. This rosary bracelet is said to ward off evil.
You should keep it. I bought it from an infomercial on TV. They said something amazing about it.
You can believe it for only 9900 yen. That's fine. I own a lot of them anyways. In this day
and age it's so convenient to buy things through the cell phone. There are only a few presses
and buttons away. All right. Green tea latte waffle and a green tea latte is vanilla syrup,
steamed milk, matcha powder. I don't even coffee. Really? Wait. Oh, I had steam blenders
in my fucking inventory and then matcha powder. Okay. There you go. Thanks for the bracelet.
Appreciate it. Thank you. The tip jar. The phone. I haven't been able to use the phone the whole game.
I can't pick it up. The whole time I've been playing I haven't been able to use the phone.
So Mr. Aren't you a cute one? Are you by any chance a model or something? No, nothing in particular.
What a waste. I'm sorry, but you should definitely make use of that style you got.
I mean, do you want me to introduce you to my office? Give me your number.
I'm not sure about that. I see. I don't care if you regret it. I'll have a salted caramel mocha,
please. I'm trying to serve coffee at work. You know what I mean? All right. What do you want?
Salted caramel mocha, coffee, steamed milk, caramel hazelnut chocolate sauce, caramel hazelnut
chocolate, caramel hazelnut chocolate, caramel hazelnut chocolate, caramel hazelnut chocolate,
caramel hazelnut chocolate sauce. There it is. Here you are. Drink. Much see you later. See you
later. I need to serve the customers. I already served everybody. Who's left to serve? Who's left
to serve? I don't like how fast the shit moves. A shirt. Excuse me. Shirt. Okay. Yeah. All right.
Yep. All right. Yeah. I didn't put enough of this. Okay. That's great. Cool. Very good.
It's so hot today. I'll have a caramel chilapecino. Could you please put on some clothes and not make
a scene? Yeah, come on. I won't be here for long. No, it would not. So legally that's out of the
question. Wouldn't it be a disaster if a customer catches a cold? I'm trying to. I won't be here
for long. No, it would not. So legally that's out of the question. Wouldn't it be a disaster
if a customer catches a cold? I guess this one. What? What are you worried about me? Thanks,
but it's hot today. It would be nice if you would consider other customers. It's cold outside. It's
one degree celsius right now. This guy's on drugs. It's freezing out. What? It's in a single
digit? Yeah. Where's this music coming from? Okay. I'm going to say if I will get colder and colder.
Now I only have clothes at home. Look, come back tomorrow when you're dressed. How does that sound?
God damn it. I hate this. I hate this. Like this toilet. All right. All right. Oh, this is going to
where's my stuff? What if this never gets scary and you just have to do this for 300 nights in a
row? Um, why does that happen? I mean, it's already been fucking scary. It's already been
fucking weird. Which trash is there? Is there a second toilet? Is it two toilets? Wait, wait,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, 14414. Whoa. Why is there? What am I making the coffee for? Um, hello. I need
to serve the customers. Give me a knife. Give me a knife. Give me a, give me a knife. Give me a gun.
Give me something. I'm getting out the fucking drive-through. What do I do? What do I do? What
do I do? What do I do? What do I do? I can't leave. I can't open this. Oh shit. You need two lattes,
two latte, latte, latte, latte, latte, latte. Oh, I already started. Why did it do that? Okay.
One, two, hurry, hurry, hurry. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Stop it. Why is it doing that
shit, man? All right. That's it. That's it. That's it. What the fuck is happening right now?
Huh? What's happening? What's going on? I have five seconds. I don't get it. What happened?
Oh, run. Excuse me. What the fuck are you talking about, dude? I can't fucking leave. I'm stuck
here. What's going on? What's actually going on? I can't do anything. Where's my bracelet?
Didn't I have a magic bracelet? I didn't throw it away. Clean up. I think I'm stuck in here.
I think I got, I got soft-locked. I think you threw it away on accident. No way. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
That would have been scarier if I had actually, I had to walk down the middle aisle. Why are
they demons? What were the demons? Dude, why are they demons? Holy shit. No more. This jump
scare is right here. Don't do it. What does that sound? What is it? Okay. I'm, I hear shit going
on right now and I'm just going to go. I don't need to, what do you mean I don't need to go
through here? Pop the trunk. Fuck, entire iron. I don't even have any stuff anymore. My suspicions
were true. Glad you contacted me. Calling the police won't help. All they'll do is brush things
off to lessen, wait, when did I do that? And why are people like me? I'll take a look around and
see if I can find anything. Did they call? Oh, okay. Hey, all the caramel mocha here is so
delicious. I think you'll love it Senpai. Okay, I guess I'll try it then. One salted caramel mocha.
I'll have a dark mocha chip chilapecino. You're not getting that? Yeah, I want to try something
different today. I already had one today. I see, but a chilapecino is on a day like this. You're
so young because it's so delicious. How would you like to pay your bill? Oh, is today the day of the
photo shoot or something? Is the store going to be featured in a newspaper or something?
No, I don't think so. Why? Well, I saw someone outside taking pictures. Taking pictures of the
store. The store and you most likely. I did my makeup. What are you talking about? I'm sorry,
we'll pay together. The drinks are on me. What are you sure? Thank you so much Senpai. I'm in a good
mood lately. My son used to be outed and this is a better, he's in a better mood now that he's
going to school. Son's in middle school, right? Yeah, let's hope he wasn't bullied at school.
I didn't have any good memory when I was his age. What do you guys, what do you want?
Why do I have all these latte tickets? I can't throw these away. Okay, chocolate chip,
chocolate chip chilapecino, ice, coffee, milk, sauce, powder, and whatever. Ice, coffee, milk,
powder, and syrup, right? Chocolate syrup. Okay, there you go. And the other one was a salted
caramel mocha. Coffee, milk, caramel, hazelnut, chocolate, coffee, milk, caramel, hazelnut,
chocolate. Remember, there are seven secret recipes you need to find. I feel like that's a
lie. Where's the protective guy? Oh, it's the jump scare lady. How is this haunted? I mean,
I just was being chased by like demons. I don't know. This is like a fucking weirdo.
Salted caramel mocha. Salted caramel mocha is coffee, milk, caramel, hazelnut, syrup, hazelnut,
caramel, hazelnut, chocolate. Cold or hot? I just made it, whatever. What is that noise?
Not soy. Caramel, hazelnut, chocolate. What is that going on? You okay?
That's strange. Oh, I'm sorry. Give me the usual. I don't know which one of these is. Can I throw
this shit away? I have so much. Okay, salted caramel mocha. Sweet red beans and butter bread.
Sweet red beans and butter bread. What's sweet red bean butter bread? We don't serve that here.
What the hell is a sweet red bean and butter bread? British food? Yeah, that sounds like a
fucking Harry Potter item. Sweet red bean butter bread. What? I don't. Oh, we do own that. You
wanted a salted caramel mocha. I know how to do that. I did that like five times already.
Salted caramel mocha. It's caramel, hazelnut, chocolate. And you also want caramel macchiato,
which I believe that's cold. It is. No, it's not. Coffee, milk, caramel, caramel.
There you go. What happened to my beads? Seriously, where'd they go? Are you repairing
the store's antenna at this hour? No, ma'am. Why? I saw someone on the roof. There shouldn't
be anyone on the roof. Who would be the investigator? Maybe I should check it out.
Could have been my imagination. Anyway, the drink, please. Investigator up on the roof?
The investigator is going to be like dead or something, right? It's going to be, I don't know.
Something horrible. Should I put it or should I put the ladder on? You go up here with a
fucking tire iron, climb the ladder and then pull the ladder up and fucking use it. You know what
I mean? Like I'm like, I don't want to, I don't want to go up there without something. I go over
there. Any reason that can I like jump? Why can I climb this? Yeah. All right. So what? I don't want
to go in there. Okay. It's like, pick this up. These things are like probably fucking 25 pounds
each. Yell down there. Detective, detective, are you down there? Detective? Brought that
fucking thing down. Oh God damn it. I have to close the store fast. Unlock the door. Unlock the door.
What? I gotta close the door fast. Gun. No. What the fuck? What am I, why am I taking all this?
I don't understand. Why am I picking up all the food? Get the money. What do I do? What's going on?
Why did I pick up every item in the fucking thing? Throw it all away? What else? What else? What else?
What else is going on? Sandwich? Count product. One, two, what? I don't get it. Count product.
Count product. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen,
fourteen, fifteen, sixteen. Start over. Start over. Two, four, six, eight, ten. Two, four, six, eight,
ten, eleven. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. I got twenty-one here. Twenty-one.
Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. What do I do now? Twenty-one.
Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. Twenty-one. What
do I do? Twenty-one. Gone? I thought that said police scanner. Okay, now what? What's left? What's
left? What's left? Get money. Did I get it? Count the money? Goodbye. Okay. Fuck you. Fuck you,
motherfucker. Fuck you. Pick up something heavy. Something that can fucking hit somebody in the
face. Like a printer. Or where's my stuff? Room. I don't know. Is this locked? Oh shit, he's gone.
He was at the drive-thru. He was at the drive-thru. He was at the drive-thru. Where do I go? Where
do I go? Are these photographs of me? Screwdriver. I'm stabbing him. Screwdriver. This is fucking
perfect. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
Screwdriver. What do I do with the screwdriver? What do I do with the screwdriver? What would you
open that door for, you idiot? Why would I open the back door? What do I do with screwdriver?
What do I do with screwdriver? Where's the vent? Vent? Where's the vent? Where's the actual- Where's
the vent? Where is it? I can't do that. I can't do that. I can't do it. I can't. I can't. I can't
do that. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. I don't know
what to do. I can't do it. I can't do it. Guys, I can't do it. Should I run to the car? Run to the
car? Ladder. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Where's the fucking ladder? How do I-
Look at all this shit I have. All right, shut this fucking thing. Shut this fucking thing.
How do I close this? Brick? Okay, do it. Drop it on his head. Drop it on his head. He killed
detective. All right, where is he? Drop it on his head. Crush him. Crush him with the brick.
I got him. Yes. I got him. I told you. Fucking TV. Something heavy. Big crush. I ran to the police
until, please, everything happened. Police took me back to the scene and that man was no longer
there. There was no one there. Investigated the scene. Hired after that. Wait a minute. It's not-
This is not over. I want to rest peacefully at home. Dude. Cable's acting weird again. Call the
owner. I even- I bricked the guy. I bricked him. Where's my phone? Dude, I bricked the guy too.
Really? What the fuck? Yeah, I have stereo sound. I know it's out here, but I don't want to do- I
don't want to go out here. Where is it? Give me another brick. I still- I still have the-
All right, motherfucker. You didn't think I still had a fucking broom? Honest to fucking god.
Where is the- What? Where's the phone? Dude, I dropped a cinder block on his head. On his head.
He played a little vampire survivors. Relax. He survived a cinder block, dropped 10 feet. Dude,
your head would cave in. Your head would go- would go like this. You would have a dent. Like,
you would crush your brain from- That was- That was fucking creepy.
Remember, that's cartoon logic. Is it though? I mean, I don't know, man. If somebody dropped a
cinder block from like 10 feet in the air on your head, I don't think you're gonna make it.
I don't think you're gonna make it. How's your review? I was actually talking to Holly about
this. And the PlayStation 1, PlayStation 2 kind of aesthetic makes everything just feel awful.
It just does. This kind of new trend of the last like, what, three, four years or so of kind of
de-making these experiences, everything just feels like a dream. PlayStation 1 graphics is what people
look like in a dream. Like this. That's what a human looks like to me in a dream. I think that's
what makes it that much more unsettling. And I think I would like to see a lot more companies
instead of going with the- looking how awesome the graphics are and how huge the budget is and
look there's all this crazy stuff all these crazy like sun god rays and beams that come through the
window. These experiences are just kind of way more unsettling. It's way more weird and just
kind of off-putting and awful. PS1 brain? You do not have dreams in 1080p. I'm sorry, you just don't.