What's going on? What's up? Who are we? I don't know. Chat? I mean, you're all individuals here.
I don't know who you all are, but I know you all are potential individuals. I don't know. Anyways,
hello. How are you? What drink is this? Uh, it is a water with some hydrating powder in it.
I need some hydration today. Feeling a little dehydrated. Have I seen Breath of the Wild 2
gameplay? Uh, I, no, I haven't. I, I need to beat the first one before I care about the second one
because I will see all the improved gameplay mechanics in the new one and then go, I don't
want to play the old one anymore. The second you show me like the new glider in the new Breath of
the Wild, it's like, well, I gotta wait like two weeks. I can just play that one. Three weeks,
whatever it is. Was it April, May? He's never going to finish Breath of the Wild 1. Well,
it's funny you say that because that's the exact plan after today. I think we are in the last,
I want to say like three or four hours of Resident Evil 4 depending on how long it takes.
Maybe four hours plus an hour of maybe the extra content. I'll try. Because what? Chapter 13,
14, right? No spoilers, please. Go back to sorcery or sorcery. I feel bad for sorcery.
I'm going back to Breath of the Wild, but not sorcery. Sorcery Shans in shambles right now.
That's a, hey, that was pretty cool. Everything started with an S. Sorcery Shans. Everything
has to have like, let's get 50 slugs. Steven is the title today. That's why I said that.
All right. You guys ready? Get through the rest of a Resident Evil 4. You guys good?
Alliteration. Yeah. Alliteration nerd. I have like a soft spot for alliteration.
California Circus of Maryland Magicians. 50 slugs. Steven. No, I'm not ready. Give me a minute. All
right. You get a minute. You get one minute. Hey, you gave me an extra 10 minutes. So I'm going to
give you an extra one minute. I think that's fair. I'll give you an extra one minute. That's fair.
Me too? All right. Everybody go. Go do what you got to do. You got one minute. Somebody just got
really annoyed because I started my stream and the of your washing machine just went off and you're
like, I have to go turn that over, dude. And it's going to take like 10 fucking minutes. Of course,
he started right when the washing machine went off. This guy should play Zomboid. I said I wanted to,
but I don't know. The game feels really involved. Is Project Zomboid a game where you have to really,
really know everything that's going on? I feel like I'm going to die in the first 10 minutes
and then go, wow, that was, I don't get it and leave. Is that possible? Seems like a really cool
game. That's the point. That's exactly what the point is. Huh. Okay. What about another FMV game
stream? There are a couple of FMV games that have come out that I want to play, but I feel like we
played a lot of the really, really important old ones. It is actually tough to find an FMV game
that I've not played on this stream. We've done them all almost. I played almost the entire FMV
catalog of 3DO games. And then before that too, on old PC, Bad Mojo is an FMV game. I did not play
that for like 20 minutes and I thought it was just, I couldn't control it well. Something was wrong.
I didn't, I didn't like it. I don't know why. Something was wrong with that. I tried to play it.
Maybe the port was fucked up and I couldn't capture it. It was something weird with that one.
All right. What about public domain movies? Yeah. Well, where's my headphones? Hold on.
I don't even know. They're not even here. Found them. What do you mean? Hello. I just, I told you
I had to go BRB for a second. What about the Dead Space remake? There's a lot of shit that
I really want to play. Well, we'll see. Let's get through this first. Resident Evil 4 chapter number
14. Oh, it's in the junk draw again. Well, the forest sequel. Oh shit. You guys can't see this one.
Hey, I don't know. Nah, I didn't, I didn't really play the forest one.
Final arc of the game, by the way. Don't even say it. Did your head get bigger?
I don't think so. Did my head get bigger in two days?
I guess I changed too. It just keeps slowly increasing in size.
I think I adjusted the camera. Yeah. This is the chapter that has the scary thing that I don't
like. So I'm preparing myself off cameraman. What do you think? You look like it's smelly today.
Yeah, you're probably right. Don't think too hard, handsome. See you later.
Hardcore run next, Howard. Yeah, I told you I'm going to, I'm going to stream standard.
I have a hardcore gaming mindset though. Very important for you to understand.
And then I'll do hardcore later. Hardcore is going to happen on my own time. I'm going to play if I
do. We've got Breath of the Wild to play. Tag me when Jerma lies. Oh, that's just your name.
Time that person off 30 seconds for having that name. Sniper rifle would be pretty,
let's avoid those pretty good here. No rifle. I, oh, by the way, for those of you that are wondering,
yes, I have a, the reason why the title is 50 slugs, Steven. If you've missed some of these
streams or if you missed the last one, we'll go over it very briefly. I put $300,000 into this
shotgun. It can hold 48 slugs and it shoots a slug every second. It seems to be working pretty
good. Striker Andy. Why is your voice so deep today? Oh, I had like a yogurt. I had like,
I had two yogurts and it made my like voice all yogurt-y. There you are. Nope. Wait. I don't want
to pass up any treasures. This thing's been really useful as well. At first I thought it was
fucking yogurt. I swear to God. Don't get scanned by this. I can take it up by shooting it, right?
I can't. All right. I'm not going that way. Does this kill you? Oh, wait, I go up there.
New items. This thing looks kind of cool and easy to handle. Oh, it's a magnum.
Okay. Do I, is it, which, which one is more powerful? This thing is 24, 27 at full power.
Knife needs care, everyone. That one, the killer seven is way more powerful.
Okay. That's the best magnum. Killer seven by far. Yeah. So I'm going to sell this.
It's not the best, but it's good. So I should sell this, get that one, and then start upgrading
that one. Butterfly does more damage. Does it? Are you sure? Butterfly technically has higher
power. What do you mean by that? The way this, if I get this, then this would be the one I'm going
to use. I'm going to keep this one. The exclusive on the butterfly is way more powerful. All right.
Well, then I'm going to keep this one. You can compare stats. I, but I think I have to own it.
Don't I? I think I have to own the weapon to compare stats. Don't I? Oh, no, I don't. All
right. I mean, but this thing is upgraded though. 24. This one's not even upgraded. I don't know.
I think this one's probably going to be stronger, but what's the exclusive on this?
The exclusive is what puts this over the top. All right. So yeah. All right. So 28, 27 of the
exclusive will put this one over the top. What's the exclusive on this one? Can I see it?
What is the exclusive on it? It's five times crit damage. All right. I'm going to keep the,
I'm keeping the one I have. This thing is done. Ooh. Okay. So let's get rid of these.
I could sell the golden egg. Yeah. I mean, it's, it's 10 grand. I'm just going to sell it.
Keep it. No, no, no. Keep it. Why? Sell the egg. It's 10 grand. It's 10,000. That's $10,000.
Well, I can't do anything else though. Another upgrade ticket.
You could make a golden omelet. That'd be kind of funny if that was real.
Is that real? That's not real, right? You can't make a golden omelet. Yes it is. There's no
golden omelet. You guys are full of shit. There's no golden omelet in this game. The golden omelet.
Really? Who cooks it? How do you make it? Yeah. You guys are full of shit. You guys are full of
shit. There's no golden omelet. I've played this game like fucking 10 times already. There's no
golden omelet. All right. Actually, thanks to the one, one guy that said to, uh, repair the knife
because I would not have. What the hell is that? A nail gun? Oh my God. Oh shit. Run away. Whoa.
Oh my God. Watch out. I want to save ammo. Nice voice. Did I voice crack? I did? When? I got a
better idea. Okay. We just got, every time I start this game again, I have to, I got to get back into
the swing of it. 50 slugs even. Yeah. Well, I had no health. I didn't have any health. I need flash
bangs. Okay. I need some more of this. Here we go. Flash grenade. Thank you. That's going to help
immensely. I'm at max health, so I don't have to worry about yellow herbs anymore. Let's go ahead
and mix two of them. I do not care about yellow herbs. I have a max HP now. Nice yogurt voice.
Why did they harmonize that? That was very strange. All right. I'm going in now. Let's go.
You know what I'm talking about? You guys know what I'm talking about, right?
Right? I hope people know what I mean by that. Where's he going? Is he running? Oh my God. He's
sprinting. Okay. Hold on. Yeah. I don't know why when I shoot this, I do that. If you watch
every time I've shot that shotgun, I've gone, yeah. Every time. Why? Why am I making that sound?
What's the point? Why am I doing that? I don't do that with anything else. Any other gun I have.
The guy holding two. Who did that? What was that? That guy just got lit the fuck up.
Don't do it. Don't do it. All right. We're good. He did the trope. He did the squibs.
The like, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop. You know, I love that. That's like so the squib
attack on like the person's chest. Anytime that they do that in movies where it's like,
it's just like, what the fuck is going on here? What is a squib? The device that is in a vest
in movies and TV shows that has the little like spurt come out. Like as if it was
a, like a, like a getting shot. It's a little device that's made for movies. Can I move this?
It's all CGI now. It is. I think for the most part. They still do use practicals. Yeah. I mean,
depends on what movie, I guess. Right. Or what show. How do I get this milk voice out?
How do I cure milk voice? Anybody know? All right. Am I missing anything in here?
There are no treasures. I need more water. I got, hold on. Is that better? No, it's not.
I should probably lean into it then. Yeah. I think I'll lean into it then. I'm the guy with
a really, really deep voice and really kind of gravelly voice today. Yeah. I think I'll
lean into it. This is just going to shoot me if I walk into it. Okay. That's not an alarm.
That is the machine gun. Okay. So what did I, I need to move this. How do I do that? I want to
pick up the items. I can't climb in this. You live in that house. I'm back. Stop. Don't get me on
that. I, that's not an HD scanner. I thought, well, it technically is a scanner. Where does this move
to? Does that really even help? But hold on. I know I'm, I'm collect every item guy. I'm sorry.
I am. Can I not get that? I need to move this. How do I move this? There's a chest right here.
Wait, I don't even need to move it because I just moved to this, right? Oh, we're good.
There we go. All right. Got it. Go. Okay. We're good. Collect everything. Nice bangle. Yeah. It
is going to be a nice bangle when I sell it for 10, $15,000. You still have that. Got it on your
soundboard from the Wario where stream? Uh, no, that's, that's been cleared out. Unfortunately,
I think even scoring has gone. Sorry. Yeah. It's fucked up. It's actually pretty screwed up.
And I fucked this up again. How did I screw this up? No, I'm all right. Right. So to move this.
Yeah, we're good. Yeah. Scoring has gone too. I know I screwed up items. I actually do have
to conserve handgun ammo, so let's make this happen. Okay. Really? That's annoying. What the
fuck did you spit at me? What happened to conserving ammo? I just used everything.
Get this loaded up. How does that miss? How are these missing? Can you please lie so I can tag
that guy? Shoot him. Stop shooting. Shoot him. Pick what you want to do, Jeremy. Stop shooting.
Shoot him. Don't shoot. Stop shooting him. I didn't even lie. Watch out for it. Watch out.
Watch out. I shot that guy in the shoulder every single time. I got 50. Ooh, what's over there?
Shit. Shit. I missed that. It's all, it's all the way back. I can't get that from here. It's
all the way back. Shoot them in the knee cap. Could go back and get it. Is it actually a treasure
treasure? It's not on the map though. All right. I'm doing this only once. There they are. Okay.
It's a legendary treasure. I don't think it is, but I do want to go get it. How often do I trim
my nails? Um, it's going to be worth like 5k. Let's just see. The thing about Resident Evil
games, especially from four onward, is you really do want to get as many of those treasures as you
can. It just makes your life so much easier later. Upgrading everything you want. Spending all the
money. Here we go. Um, 600 and, uh, no, it was worth it. It was worth it. Ammo I didn't have
before. It was worth it. What was that? What is, what is this? Weird. Okay. Are you liking
this better than Resident Evil 2? No, I think, well, a lot of Resident Evil 2 is being chased,
which as you know, from my experience, the granny likes, I really don't like,
but in Resident Evil 2, it didn't feel, it, I was okay with that. I thought it was fine.
What's a granny like? Um, can we, how do I explain this? Granny like is when you have
to collect a bunch of items and, okay, let me, how do I spell this out? Okay. You open,
the game opens. You're in a house. You're in a, or you're in a grocery store. You're in a
mall or you're in a home. It doesn't matter where you are. And there's a piece of bubble gum
the next to you. It's a bubble gum. You got it. Okay. And then to your left is, uh, a sink
that's missing a pipe. And you don't know, you know, you're going to have to come back with a
fucking pipe to put on that sink, but you don't know where the pipe is. So eventually you end
up running around an hour or so later, 40 minutes later, you get a pipe and then you
have to go back and put the pipe on and then use the gum to plug up the sink. And then you
got to take the thing, the, the key that you get out of the sink and go put it into the floorboard
and then from the floor, but it's, it's just, and then all that time, all while you're doing that,
somebody is chasing you and you die if they get you. I don't like it. I don't like those.
That's a granny like, what does it have to do with grannies? Cause there's a very popular game
called granny where granny chases you around and you have to fucking pick up the floorboards and
put like gum into the sink and find the wrench to then like open the fucking door to the, the,
the, you know, the, the basement. It's granny. I want to kick you off here. Holy shit. That was
cool. Kill this guy. Like hello neighbor. Yes, exactly. That came out of alpha yet.
I have not heard about that game in like six years. Is this, I remember that game was like,
and it was like a, in alpha for a long time. I was like, Oh, what is this game?
Is it, is it actually still not out? No, no, I've seen like ads for like a sequel. It has to be out,
but that's a granny like it already has a sequel. Is it any good? I don't want to kill this guy
because I feel, I feel like he's trying to figure a puzzle out with a crowbar, which is exactly the
kind of person that I want to make sure stays around. This guy's trying to figure this out
with a crowbar and I feel really bad about this. Oh, that's what you were doing. He made pretty
good progress. It was one of the smarter of the zombies. I think you want, can you have a
Roblox stream? My mom really wants you to play Roblox. No, I'm not going to play Roblox. Not
right now. Probably not ever. Probably never. That's never, I'm just going to tell you right
now. That's never going to happen. I'm literally never going to play Roblox. Not that I don't,
I just, I just, I'm not going to, right? Like that's all I have to say. I don't need to explain why
I don't really want to. I don't need to tell you the reasoning. I'm just not going to do it.
And that's all that needs to be said. That's it. There's your answer. Are you going to play Roblox?
No, I'm not going to play Roblox at any point. I hope it's, I hope you have fun in Roblox.
Seems like a pretty interesting world. I'm never playing Roblox ever on this stream,
ever. You understand? It's, it is never happening. All right. Now when, like a year from now when I
do play it, you can tag that guy. All right. Did I get everything? I think I did. There's a,
there's a bunch of like little areas to go explore. Hold on. Is that one? Yeah, I don't,
I'm going to miss something, but who cares? Come on, sneak. This is really good looking though.
Rocket launcher. This isn't good. Night shot. You suck. Harry the rocket. I don't think you can,
man. Suplex. That did not even come close. What's wrong with that? Not bad, right? I have no need
for this, but I guess I'll just stick it in here, right? I'm at full house. It doesn't really matter.
Uh, can I take one more hit? I think I can. I can. I have body armor, so I definitely can take it.
Don't! What is it? Dead? Dead. When are you going to have a skincare product line come out?
What the hell is that sound? Oh, it's you. Skincare product? Going up there first. We're good,
right? Yeah. Treasures? Not listed. Oh, I need the map, don't I? Stop reading random ass messages,
Ella Mayo. Yeah, but isn't that like kind of, what do you mean stuff reading random ass messages?
What do you mean true? I'm streaming. I'm going to read some of the messages that come through.
Okay. I got a lot of gunpowder. I have 18 gunpowder. I need the little blue burrito,
whatever it is. What the hell is this? What is this? Remember April 5th. What's going on April 5th?
April 5th. Remember, remember. When are you going to play Roblox? I'll play Roblox on your birthday.
Okay. Next year. Oh, he's a page. So what? What do you mean? Yeah, next year. When's his birthday?
This doesn't hold off in court though. I could have been talking to anybody. I didn't know when
your birthday was. Could have been anybody's birthday. There's a paper trail on this.
I'm not playing Roblox like next week. I'm telling you that's not happening.
What if I watch a Roblox video or something? Is that sufficient for you? No, I'm not playing
Roblox. I'm not playing it. When I said next year, what I meant to say was I'll play Roblox on
your birthday. No. God damn it. Why does everybody have receipts? Like why do you have receipts on
this stream? Do you know what I'm saying? Like, come on. Why do you have receipts? I'm getting
red receipts right now. I never said I was going to. All right. When I say play Roblox,
if I open up the main menu, go like this. Do my options and then leave the game. It counts. I
opened it. I'm trying to shoot the thing. Oh my God. I'm alive. Go. Okay. Stab. You have to play
Roblox for 30 consecutive minutes. That's not part of the deal. I did. I just said I was going to
play it on your birthday and I don't even know whose birthday I was talking about. It was
misleading info. Misleading the witness. Leading. You're leading. I hear one of those bobbleheads.
Overruled. Objection, your honor. The witness, me, did not know that person's birthday
and I agreed to something that it wasn't in writing and it was no contract. There's no
verbal contract either because I didn't know exactly when the date was. I was never told that,
your honor. So, objection has been sustained. Thank you. Where is this thing? I can hear it.
Where is it? Where is this thing? Where is it? Where is this thing? Above you? I don't care.
Doesn't matter. All right. This is the treasure I gotta get. Somebody said I missed a treasure
with a barrel or something. I told my mother you're going to play Roblox. I don't want to play
Roblox. I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it. It's really far back. Is it really? No, it's not,
is it? This is a shortcut anyway. No, it's not. All right. I'm gone. But yeah. All right. How
about this? We'll take a deal here. On your birthday, I will sing you a Roblox-themed
happy birthday. We'll have a Roblox-themed birthday party for you. Like I'll get Roblox
plates and cups and like a Roblox thing that hangs with balloons, and then I'm not even
going to play the fucking game. That's a Roblox-themed birthday party. That doesn't
mean I'm going to have to play it. Do you accept my plea? My deal here? You know what the best part
about this? I don't even know who this person is. I have no idea who this is, but we're going to
have a birthday party for you. Okay. I fucking heard it too, and I just kept going. It's a binding.
Was that actually April 5th though? I don't want to do this. Actually, it's kind of funny.
Maybe I do. Ooh, nice. Why are you scared of Roblox? I'm not scared of Roblox. I just don't.
It's just like, I can tell you like five things that I really just don't think I want to do
in the next few months. And one of them is play Roblox. I just don't, this just doesn't do
anything for me. And I don't really want to. Like, it's just like, why, why would I, I just
don't want to play the game Roblox. You probably love it, but that's all right. This person is
going to get killed by this. No, you come to me. You come to me. He even was like, no, you come over
here. There was something else down there. This is game progress. I don't want to do that yet.
This is ultimate game progress. So nevermind. Okay. I'm supposed to check in to make sure
that didn't go anywhere. Have you ever been to Five Nights at Freddy's? The movie? You heard it
here. He's afraid of Roblox. That's fine. Just wait till our Roblox-themed birthday party.
You know what? I'm actually probably would rather play the game now that I think about it,
because then there'll be images of me on the internet wearing like a Roblox party hat
and like eating cake off of a Roblox plate at 40. I don't know if I really want those images
to be available to, you know, I don't think I want those images to be available.
Okay. Anything else in here? No. This is the worst part of the game coming up. This is the worst part
of the game. I got through my one out of two of my least favorite scary, I hate being in this zone
areas and now we have to do the other one. I really don't want to, but I love this game.
So I'm going to do it. It's coming up here soon. My mom's grounding me and taking away my phone.
Good. Good. Don't get off that thing. Don't use that fucking thing. Boomer. Good. Put that thing
down. Put that thing down. Why is he so mean tonight? Can I get an instant kill on the big guy?
Maybe I would have if I did it the right time. Okay. I don't want to use it. I'm not going to
use it. I'm going to go on. I'm going to, what are you doing? Got him. All right. Those things,
those guys are not as bad now with all the power I have. You look decrepit tonight.
Somebody wants a birthday party on the fifth. You want a birthday party though, right?
Need a key card. Where's my birthday party? I want a Roblox themed birthday party. You're ugly.
Spoiled, spoiled, spoiled. Hmm. Hmm. I need a card reader. Any trinkets? I'm looking for trinkets.
Why are you being so scary? What are you talking about? You actually blocked it with the axe.
Come on, go down. Down. Pretty good. Suplex. I'm actually really, really glad I got those.
Okay, cool. I asked you if you've visited the movie set of Five Nights at Freddy's. No, I have
not visited the movie set. Why would I be on the movie set of Five Nights at Freddy's? I can't lie
your way out of this one. The great Ace Attorney Chronicles you said on January 4th. Yeah, speaking
of attorneys, look at all these attorneys in chat. On January 4th, 2023, precisely 5 PM,
you stated on your live stream in front of 12,000 witnesses that you were going to play
Ace Attorney at exactly 6 PM. I am going to play that. I'll play Ace Attorney. Well,
I will. I never said I wasn't going to play Ace Attorney. I just said I wasn't going to play it
right now. Play it eventually. That's going to be a good chill stream, I think. Pam, look at those
reflexes. Finger was in nose, left hand was off keyboard, picking nose, looking over here,
talking to you. And I got that guy in the fucking head right when he jumped out. I don't want to
hear it anymore. Look at how slow this guy is in games. I don't want to hear it anymore.
I don't want to hear it. I'm mean today. I'm mean right now. Ooh, that's Full Heel.
Another crown.
She makes no difference. The price. Well, that's our choice to make.
I'm close to doing another 100k. I need, what do I need? I need a red. Yeah, I'm close to
getting another 100k. Thank you. Life needs care every once in a while.
This kind of work is about finesse, stranger. Little B goes a long way. You see. Dazzled,
are you? Go. Oh, you have resources. Good. I need these. I really need those.
Yes. All right. I got eight for that. All right. 40. I got 42 in here now.
The next revolver is coming up. Why do you keep upgrading that one? Because
that one with the exclusive upgrade does the most damage of all the revolvers, doesn't it?
Hmm. I need more of these. Where is the, there it is. Ooh, chicken egg. Not if the killer seven
crits. True, but how many times do I have to shoot to reliably get a crit? I wonder. Like,
what's the percentage chance? I wonder. Change the outfit. Actually, that's a good point. Yeah,
we can go back to the default now. The end of the game. We'll go back to the original. It's been,
it's been like 15 in-game hours or something since I had the original outfit on. I changed
that within like the first two or three hours, didn't I? Yeah, I'll put it back. Vote for the
final outfit. Now that's fair. That's fair. All right. We're going to start with, um,
let's start with Leon. Final outfit. I'm not changing it. Leon. Uh, I am going to veto one
of these because there's only room for four slots. So I am vetoing. I'm vetoing hero.
Nah, this was funny for a minute, but I'm vetoing hero. Your choices are default, villain, casual,
or romantic. Romantic, casual, hero. No, romantic, casual, villain, or default. Default, villain,
casual, romantic. This is it. I'm not changing this for the rest of the game. You guys get to
decide. And I know a lot of people are going to be mad at this because you're probably picking
the, wow. Actually, nevermind. I'm not going to say anything. Damn. Geez. Okay. I'm not going
to say anything. I don't want to influence the vote. There are actually five options for polls.
Yeah, but I don't want to weigh this one anymore. It's all good. It's close, but I don't think it's
close enough. It's close, but not really. You got like five seconds before we were just going to do
what we were going to do. 46% to 41% default versus romantic. You have literally three seconds.
Default wins. Thanks for playing. All right. Next, very important. Sunglasses on or off?
Sunglasses on or off for the final arc of the rest of the game. On or off? Sunglasses on or
off? It's very important. Plus, you know, this gives me a few minutes to take a sip of my drink
and buy some lip balm. Sunglasses on or off? Still close. Very close. Wow. The people want default.
Default. Everything default. Interesting. I guess it makes sense. There's only so much,
I guess, of the comedy outfits if you really want to see kind of how it plays out in the end of the
game. Yeah. Sunglasses off has kind of run away with it here. I don't think it's possible.
Almost 60% of the vote is for off. Sorry, everybody. Well, I apologize. A majority of you,
or at least a larger percentage of you want me to turn it off. All right, we're going default.
Now we have only two more things to care about. Ashley's costume for the rest of the game.
Default, casual, or romantic? Only three options here. Default. Stay with casual. Change back to
romantic. Make your choice. Romantic. Casual. Default. This is very split. Everyone has poor
taste. Well, here's the thing. It's spread out pretty evenly. So you all, you all disagree evenly.
It's like 40%, 20%, 37%. You guys seem to be equally in disagreement. So it's going to be close.
All right. That's it. Default. All right. The final decision you have to make is
Ashley's accessories. Default is sweeping, by the way. I'm just telling you.
No accessories. Just default, classic, nothing. Red hair, the Wellington glasses, or the mask.
Just go full on nothing. Just classic. Red hair, glasses, or mask. This one I'm actually interested
in. Wow. Default sweep. It's not even close. Actually, wait a minute. It is close. It is close.
Hold on. It's close. Red hair is really starting to come up here. This is too close to call now.
Uh-oh. Default has lost the race so far. Default is losing. Default is losing. I would click on
that button if you don't want to look at the thing you didn't want to see. I think red hair is,
no, hold on. You got like 10 seconds. Stop influencing. I saw what was happening,
so I started saying both of them. Default looks pretty cool. Red hair looks pretty cool,
right? Doesn't it? Which one? Either one. I don't know. Only one by about 100 votes.
Red hair it is. And we're not doing the filters. I'm not playing with those on. There you go.
Default everything, but Ashley has a red hair now, I guess. Okay, let's go. Wait, what is this?
Leatherjacket has contributed 550,000 channel points to that. Wait, what? What does that mean?
What does that mean? We enabled channel points to vote more. Oh, you can actually spend channel
money to vote. I wanted default. Hey, come on. All right, we're good. I'm going to eat this egg.
It's rigged. We're, we're not going back. All right, let's go. Wait, she has her trust right
here. There's another one in the other room. What do you mean rigged? We're getting to the
scary part of the game and I need to focus because it's scary. Key card. How's the audio?
We good? I'm gonna go this way first. I need a key card. Okay. Oh my God. I hate these things,
but they do. I don't, I don't hear it yet. They do it. Oh, they do it. They do it. They do it in
the remake too. Oh, I fucking hate it. I hate it. That, that. Oh, shut up. Okay. Dissection,
override card for level two clearance using the machine in the freezer. So I have to go to the
dissection, come to the freezer, scan it, and then some, somebody help me. Now we're going to go up
here. Wait, I'm, I am fucked here. I'm just realizing right now. I'm realizing right now
what's going on. Those of you that played the game before, how am I going to do this? I'm,
I fucked everything up big time. Oh, this is a disaster actually. How am I going to reliably
do this? Honestly, this is going to be my solution. It's going to have to be. I don't have a rifle.
It's going to have to be this. You know what I'm talking about. What do I do here? Is that on?
Right? That's on, right? Oh, I got to power both of them. I fucking hate using A and D. I just want
to use up or like W or use the mouse scroll. That's it, right? I got both of them on. How do I?
Yeah, two to two. That's it, right? Do I have to like activate it? Confirm it. Oh, okay. System
restored. I am so screwed. At last I have created new life. I call it the regenerator.
It's metabolic capacity is incredible. Unless all the parasites residing within the organism
are destroyed, its tissue can regenerate indefinitely. Upon examining the body with a
biosensor scope, I was able to confirm that the parasites behave like vital organs for the host,
almost as though it has multiple hearts. This new creation of mine is essentially immortal.
Surely even Dr. Frankenstein himself would want to shake my hand in admiration.
And then it fucking killed him. So for those of you that don't know, I'm just going to,
I know it's a spoiler, but I know the spoiler. So I'm just going to tell you what it is.
I can't see through their bodies. And you normally can, if you get this scope to do it.
And I'm not going to be able to, because I don't have a rifle. I'm in trouble. Or am I,
or am I actually in trouble? What's wrong with this? Oh my God, dude. That was the worst fucking
scare I think I had in like a year. And that was, I like knew it was going to happen to that fucked
up my whole brain. Oh my God, that was bad. Wow. Why was it that one? Why was it? I knew, I did,
he, I knew he was coming, but I thought it was slower than that. I thought it was much slower
than that. It was the fact, there was a lot of things going on there. First of all, I thought
that I had the key card and I was going to swipe it, but I didn't. I don't have the key card. And
then I looked down the hallway. He wasn't there. Nice fake YouTube jumpscare. It wasn't. It was
real. Um, but a lot of factors there. There really were a lot of factors on that. I looked
down the hallway and there was nothing there. And then I, he turned around. There was immediately
somebody right there. This doesn't have power either. What, what actually does have power right
now? Oh, I'm in trouble. I'm going to have to, you can't come in here, but where is he? I can't go in
the freezer. I can't go in here. So I need to go down here. Okay. So I got to go left, right, right.
Buy a rifle right now. Let me see that scare. I want to see how embarrassing it was. I mean,
it was probably really embarrassing. What's wrong with this? What's wrong with this?
That really does look like a YouTube thumbnail. It's, he's grabbing, he's got his hands locked
around my head and it's screaming. My limiter, my limiter on my microphone was working over time
on that one, by the way. He doesn't sell it, does he? I thought he sold it. Go get the SMG
in the freezer. Oh shit. I know you're right. Okay. Okay. I thought I was screwed for a second.
All right. I'm going to heal full health with the bass and just run. Oh, I need to do this.
It was so loud. I just, whatever. I don't think any of this really matters right now.
I guess I'll put on the, this, get the rifle. I don't have the money for the rifle.
I'll be all right. I just have to, I just have to get to where I need to go and I'm just going to
run. I'm going to save it right here. I knew I was going to hate this part. It's just me remembering
how much I hated this when I was younger. Okay. It's left, right, right. Go. Okay. Left and then
straight across. Oh, there's more than one. Oh, and I have two to deal with this too. I have to deal
with this now. I have to, I have to deal with this. Did I get them all? I got them all. I got
them all. 28 slugs, Steven. It was worth it. I got rid of all the parasites. That's going to have
to be the play if I don't get the scope. There's another one just hanging out here. Okay. I got
three to power. Come on. I got to get that last one. There it is. Oh boy. I got it. Ooh, an LE5.
There it is. And I can put the scope on this. Where do I get that scope though? I don't know
where I get the scope. So you get it later. Okay. So now I got to go. I have level two.
So level two gets me to the down here. So I need to power this back up over here. Go back to this
room, switch it back to here, and then go here. All right. So I don't want to fight this thing.
So I'm going to go straight left straight, which maybe I should just kill it. I'm just going to
kill it. I've got, I've got my, I'm going for it again. Thank God. Okay. All right. All right. I
don't, I'm good. I ran out of bullets, but that's all right. That's exactly why I wanted to have
that weapon. That weapon is precisely what I wanted to do with it. Okay. So now I got to go
back around here. How are this? Another one's probably going to spawn. Now I got to go back
around here and then that is the end of that. Okay. This is it. Can I, can I have an egg? Can
I have an egg, please? Just give me one egg. That's all I want. What the fuck is going on?
Wait, what? Wasn't this powering over here? And I switched it to be powering over here. No,
it was already pop. Oh, I thought I had to put it. I thought the power was this.
And then the second power was over here. Oh shit. I turned it off. I thought it was,
but it was whatever. No eggs. Okay. All right. Yeah. That's, that's what I could look at the
map though. It doesn't look like it's, um, yeah, like this is now powered down. Oh no, it's not
shit. Okay. Okay. Something's going to jump scare me. It's going to be another one and I
have to be ready and I can't use all of my shotgun bullets. It's going to the freezer again.
Just wait. Here comes something, right? You can hear it. Ah, I thought they were talking.
Where are they? All right. Come on up here. Don't the fuck. Why is it making that weird
like banger boys sound? Why is it doing that? Don't play Resident Evil 4 at 3 a.m.
Yep. Fucking thumbnails, man. We like to party. We like, we like to party. We like to party.
That used to just absolutely amp everybody up big time when that song would play. Those of you that
were around and that song was really popular, you would hear that and it would be like,
holy shit, it's about to get real. It's going to be an incredibly fun party right now.
In mere moments, everyone's going to have a great time in moments, moments from now.
Back during like a wedding, grandma and grandpa get up for that one too. You know, that, you know,
grandma and grandpa kind of sitting there, you know, chilling out for most of the wedding. And
then all of a sudden it's like, okay, I'm getting up for this one. And the grandma gets up. Grandpa
gets up. The whole family gets up. Every friend gets up. There's nobody sitting down when that
song was played. They all do the same like, it's just kind of like this up, like, let's go.
I'm looking forward to being, to being that guy. Okay. Let's keep playing. What? Shit. Okay.
They're all going to break out of here. So I am not fighting any more of these. What's this herb?
That's my favorite color. Teal. During a recent power outage, a test subject awoke from cryogenic
status, broke out of his holding tank and escaped. The subject was contained after 20 hours,
leaving seven dead and 19 wounded. We were unable to recover one of the bodies in a tool from inside
of it. Cause of this unfortunate incident is the unstable power supply. The outdated generators
cannot keep up with our demanding schedule. Management must prioritize the needs of the
engineers of those of the researchers to prevent something that's ever happening again. Thank God.
Thank God. Because now I can actually do this correctly. You see what's going on here?
You don't know where they are in the body. That's why I was shooting at the shotgun. If these are
not all destroyed at the same time, within a second or two of each other, they don't die.
All right. Should I kill them? Can I kill them now? When they're inside of this or no? I feel
like I probably should do it. I'm going to do it. This thing sucks. It has no power to die.
This thing sucks. This thing doesn't hurt anything. Yeah. I have to, I have to go like
to do one. I only have 30 bullets. What am I doing? What's your opinion on cheese?
All right. Well, I got another, um, yeah, I am pulling this person right now.
Where? Okay. So all of your, they're all in like this mid section area. Okay. I got it. Ready?
Whoa. I get them all. I didn't get them all. Oh my God. That's it. That's it. That's it. Okay.
You missed both of them. I don't know how I did that. Oh God. I hate this area so much.
I just, I just get so panicky and so high strung. What's going on? Oh, it's blocked.
How do I unblock it? Why is it blocked up? That shit's all blocked up over here. Why can I use
this? It's all blocked off. I need to like power it on. All right. There's the terminal key card
lock down here. Maybe you only need to kill one of them. Read the note. Wait, what? So what? The
tool. So what though? But we're good tool. Wait, what? What's going on? This is the tool. Grab the
tool. What tool? They both died right here. There's nothing on the ground inside the enemy. There's
nothing on the ground. There are more. Oh, there are more. Oh, there are more. Oh, no, there are
more. And there's the tool. There's the wrench that's inside of the person's stomach. I've been
looking at it like this and there are two more and you, I am in a lot of trouble, but you know what?
Let's make this happen correctly. No excuses. Do it. I got scared. I got scared and had to run.
This weapon sucks, dude. Fuck off me. I want to fucking quit the game. I want to restart so bad.
Fuck you. Let me stop pretending. Guys, I can't, I don't know where they are. And I'm, I didn't
buy a, I didn't buy a rifle. So these bullets don't fucking hurt anything.
So I have to see where the parasites are and then switch to a different weapon.
I'm good. I got the tool. I'm good. There's something in here. You have no ammo. I'll be good.
Don't worry. I'll be fine. It could go worse the next time. Where is this thing? It's like hanging
right here. I'll be good. Trust me. I'll be good. Oh, by the way, it turns out that everyone telling
me that the deluxe edition had cheating maps was a liar because that's not real. You guys just made
that up. So that's why I have been, I have not been buying the treasure maps because everyone
told me I was a cheater and I bought the deluxe edition, which gave me access to all the treasures
and everyone was like, Oh, he's a cheater. And I was like, Oh, I don't have to buy those.
Turns out that's not real. That's not accurate. Thank you for that one. All right. I got the tool.
I got the treasure. You only had to kill one of these things. Yeah. But I was scared that they
were going to all break out and it was going to open up and kill me. It was just for the first
area. Yeah. I have to do this right. So bear with me here. This guy will do it for me.
That hit me right in the head. How did you, how did they perfectly do that? That is so annoying
right now. How did they do that? So flawlessly. Okay. That's what I wanted to do. Oh my God. I
broke one out with the grenade. No, that's not good. That's very bad. That is exceptionally bad.
I have to kill this thing right now. Is it dead? Seven, seven, seven, seven, seven, seven, seven.
Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. Wait, I can, I can, I have an idea. Stop it. I'm dead. Throw it at me.
Throw it. Dude, throw that at me already. Thank you. Jesus. This is a fucking disaster, dude. I
really should just die. I should just die. This is a disaster. This is a fucking disaster.
Just kill me. This is a disaster. I have no bullets. I opened up all four of those chambers.
This is an absolute fucking disaster. You could leave. Yeah, but I used all my ammo. I just have
to kill the one. Where am I? All right. Okay. We're good. Everybody relax. Everything is now
situated. I don't have to waste like 200 rounds trying to shoot the stupid fucking parasites in
their bellies. Okay. Here we go. There's ammo somewhere, isn't there? I know I picked it up.
Where is it? Okay. I just have to get this right. I have to, with the 20 shots in this weapon that
has no upgrades in it, I have to get, I have to kill this one person and then I'm going to run out
of this room. Okay. We ready? No more messing around. No more bullshit. I'm doing this now.
Can you play the song? Sure. I just typed in Vengaboy's song. It's probably going to be the
first one. Yeah, it is. All right. I'm going to turn it down just a little bit. I'll activate
the encounter and go, Oh, here comes grandma. I don't, why am I doing this? All right. Here we
go. It's time to go. Watch out. Oh shit. Why is this to the beat of the song? What are you doing?
Who's got me? Call me. The song didn't help. It made everything worse. You know what? Fuck it.
I got an idea. I'm going to just, I'm just going to cause mayhem right now. I'm just going to go,
I'm going full mayhem mode. Now, wait, maybe crazy frog will help. Not a bad idea. Not a bad idea.
Crazy frog could help. It's not a bad option here. What's going on? I still want to shoot this.
This is on the handgun. No, how do I put this down? Why is this even on the bar right now? Why is
this on the bar? I'm fucking pissed now. Eat shit everybody. Where's the key? I don't care anymore.
We're doing fucking relaxing music. Play peanut butter jelly. Oh, that's a good one too. That's
right. I will beat it to one of these songs. I promise. All right. Peanut butter jelly song.
All right. This is, I don't think this is it. This is not the peanut butter jelly song,
but it's going to stay. Let's go.
Peanut butter jelly. Then you take the peanuts and you mash them, you mash them, you mash them,
mash them, mash them. Leon singing. Oh, you're fucking me up so bad.
Leon is singing.
Peanut butter jelly. No. God damn it. Die. Please.
I can't do this. This song goes fucking hard by the way. Shit. No.
Eat it, eat it, eat it. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I'm fucked here.
Don't blow anything up. I have to go for it. All right. Quiet, quiet, quiet. That song was
pretty cool, but all right. Hold on. I need to see where they are. All right. They're on the belly
and then on the neck line. Belly, neck. And then on the neck, on the neck, on the neck.
Just give me the key card and give me the fuck out of here. Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Peanut, peanut butter. The fact that people say that was Leon singing made that a hundred
fucking times funnier. Okay. I need to go back for the items. It was Ashley too. Oh, that's so
fucking funny. That's so stupid. Whatever, whatever, whatever. It doesn't matter. We're gone.
I missed a, an error, but it's fine. It's okay. Peanut butter jelly song. That was not right,
but it's okay. Peanut. You missed a lot more than that. I don't want to go back there.
I really don't. There is handgun ammo down here though, which I will take. I think that's good.
Yeah. Hold on. Yeah. Yes. Yes. All right. We can finally leave my, one of my least favorite zones.
It does get worse though. If I remember it gets a little worse. What is this? What does this want
me to do here? Gap in the wall. Oh, that's for when I think when Ashley's back. Yeah. Okay. Well,
that was an interesting journey. That was fun. Yeah. The red hair is still there. It was voted on.
Did it work? Having a leveled up rifle makes a huge difference here. Yeah. I got through it.
I just shouldn't sell that gun because the regenerators are now enemies going forward.
So I don't want to have to deal with that again. That's surprising considering how
panicky I was with the shotgun. Although I guess the shotgun is hard to miss with.
Getting close. Only a couple more chapters remain. Thank you. Can you stand? Where's Luis?
He's worried about you till the end. Come on. We don't have much time. Let's get rid of these
things for Luis. Let's go get that item. Yeah. Come in. There's a lab where we can remove the
parasites. Had a crazy hunch that you'd know where it is. Their most important facilities are house
and their sanctuary at the top of the mountain. That's where I'd look. Crystal ore? Crystal ore?
What the hell is that? This is such a little book. How do you even write in this?
This thing is tiny. We were imprisoned without warning. One by one we are taken to the next
room. I do not know what happens there. They just took Annabelle. I'm probably next. I've got to
think. Need to get my head straight. All who are infected with the plaga will be at the mercy of
Lord Saddler. If he commands it, they will work. If he commands it, they will work themselves to
death with a smile on their face. Adversely, the host becomes so simple-minded that they're
basically useless for any complex task. However, we succeeded in developing the new superior
species of plaga. It has no special variability. But the host's cognitive functions are not
diminished. Seems like they plan to administer this new species to the girl. Clearly important
that she maintains her intelligence after infection. All tests were successful and
plans for mass production are moving forward. The project is a complete success. But I've been
imprisoned. And preparations to inject me with the superior species are underway in the next room.
Annabelle is not herself anymore. The smile has been wiped completely from her face. Writing is
the only thing that keeps me sane now. Not that anyone will ever read this. Oh, it's another 100%
heal. I kind of just fucked that up. But whatever. Doesn't matter. We're at the end game. Doesn't
matter. Give me more than six. I got to replenish this. I have to use the bolt gun for a while now
because I need to replenish the shotgun shells. Okay. Is grotto be shipping soon? Grotto beasts
is shipping soon. I imagine a lot of people are going to start to in the first pass here,
are going to start to get stuff within the next week or two. I'd be on the lookout if you ordered
very early in the presale. Stuff is going to start shipping here really soon. So I would just be on
the lookout over the next week or two, I'd say. Take a look. It is dropping soon. Okay, there we
go. Blue hair. Blue hair versus red hair. Can we get a vote, please? Are we changing from red to
blue? Yes or no. You're going to need to make this decision very quickly. Blue medallions in here.
They're scattered around. Okay. Oh, there's a shooting range. Nice. Okay, cool.
Some powder. What the hell just happened to my voice? I got a purple gem, didn't I? All right,
how close am I to doing this? Pull everything out. Red. Oh, red's the cheapest. Pull that out.
So yellow, blue, purple, red, green. I need a red and a green one and I can do another crown for
100k. I got this. I have a lot of coins already. I need way more squares. I don't need these
anymore, right? That's the reason why they're here. Wow, blue. Absolutely destroyed. Okay,
I'll do that real quick right now. Real quick. Where's the... All right, blue hair. You can do
it without leaving? I don't think you can. I think we tried before. Blue hair. Let's go.
The accessories. Ah, okay. You can't do the clothing. You ready for the reveal? Okay. Miku.
All right, we... This is upgraded all the way.
Try that on for size. Once we get this thing all the way, we'll be good.
Wait, you got new stuff? What do you got? Resources. I need these.
You get some bet I don't come back. Shit, I need more gunpowder.
Let's do this. New game. Okay, 4A, Punisher and the Riot Gun, Bolt Thrower, and then everything.
Oh, dear. Okay. So, what... I got... Sorry. Do they ever connect all the way?
How do you... I need to... I didn't know... I'm just trying to figure out how to... I don't even know
the fuck that was happening. It's the first time I've ever seen it. It's the first time... Oh, please.
Hey, Jerma, it's the first time you've ever seen this. How come you didn't get it the first time?
It's annoying. Stop reloading when you don't need to. What do I even have the shotgun for?
What's the bonus condition? What the hell was that? What the hell are you talking about?
Why is there so much travel time on them in this mini-game? There's not that much travel time on
this. Dude, there ain't this... I swear to God, there's not this much travel time on these bullets.
Dude, what is going on? This thing doesn't suck this much in real life. Like, in the real game.
Am I wasting these or do I get an infinite amount of these? I have no idea. I'm not wasting... Okay,
I get four. All right, all right, all right. I don't care about getting... No, no, no, no, no,
just do it. I don't care. It's moving. That was pretty good. That's probably a... It's taking us.
All right, we're good. We're good. We're good. This one's going to be horrible. So I'm just going
for like a B on this one. I'm going for a B on this one. Oh, my God. Wait, it's not... I don't like
switching weapons. Just give me one. I hate switching weapons. It's like the worst. I don't
care about any of this. I hate switching weapons. I didn't even know that could be... I just haven't
used the rifle the whole game. I didn't know you could do that. I want to hit two. My fingers are
so huge. They just hit every button when I press three. Use a machine gun. I don't even care.
I just want to get a silver coin. I'm not doing this. I don't care. Just give me a fucking A.
I don't care. B. I don't care. Good. Let's go. That's fine. I am not doing that ever again.
You know what the problem is? So on a mechanical keyboard, the buttons are spaced out. So this is
a mechanical keyboard. There's like a huge gap between every single button on a mechanical keyboard.
I get stuck in the middle. I'll go to press three and I'll go in the middle. I need a mesh keyboard.
I'm not a gamer anymore. Give me my mesh keyboard back. Give me a mesh keyboard. This doesn't happen.
All right. This is the last time we're probably going to be able to do this. That's pretty good.
It would have been nice a lot earlier. Let's conserve them now. Conserve it. Legendary.
Legendary. No. No. Oh, that's actually great. That's really good. That's actually exactly what
I wanted because now I have two shotgun crafting things. All right. I'll take it. I don't want I
got S's on every single one except the last three or the last two. You look flustered. No, I'm just
I'm just I just have a red. I just have blood in my face. All right. Does he sell gunpowder?
I want the case that drops more gunpowder. I think I might already even have it on.
Do I have the money one? Let's see. That's already on for gunpowder. So I have a 35% chance to get
more shotgun ammo, which is a big deal in the melee crit. Do you have anything? You have these.
I need square gems very badly. I have a question. Should I sell the bolt thrower now
and go all into the broken butterfly? It actually might be time to get rid of this
because I'm I don't I haven't upgraded in a while. I haven't spent the
the t-tas on it. So I do like it, but I kind of let it fall off a little bit, didn't I?
Yeah, I let it fall off. I'm going to sell it. It's going. It was fun. It's cool to
new addition, but I want the money now. Oh, yeah. Molding a weapon to suit your specific.
This kind of work is about finesse. Straight. Little bit goes a long way. Better to be over
prepared. Am I right? Don't always have this in stock. Where would it? Pleasant trap. OK,
I just need a bunch of gunpowder. This thing is empty. All right, we're good.
Let me load this up and gun is good. All right. Sell the other charms. Sell your charms.
Oh, these do sell for a lot. OK. Ruby's all rubbish. It makes no difference. So
well, that's our choice to make. You can never hold more than one on anything anyway,
so just sell the copies. OK, this helps. I probably should upgrade this.
All the mines. Yeah, I can sell the mines too. Small key. Can I sell that? Why would I do that?
There are no more locks. Oh, shit. OK. A deal well struck. All right. This is going to make
this thing disgusting, but I really should level. I need to. I need to use this for a little while.
So we're going probably ammo capacity or probably power. I'm going to do power. I think
put it into the revolver. I'm going to make a lot more money soon. This is I need to use this
now. Sell this and just buy the rifle. What can I do? Can I afford the right? How much is the rifle?
Oh, it's only twelve thousand. All right. Wait, there's more than one rifle, isn't there?
In your pocket or your I guess it's fine. Yeah, that's a good idea. All right. I'm going to get
the rifle and I'm going to cancel because I need to sell that first anyway. Let me take the scope
off of it. Get yourself killed. Stingray is better. It is better. I need thirty thousand. All right.
Is what I've got. All right. We are good.
I am not taking the regular scope. I'm going to put on this. How does it look?
OK, very cool. We're good. Good strategy. I've got lots of good stuff. I am ready.
I'm able. Let's go. I'm ready to go. I am tuned up. Where's the tuned? I'm ready.
I am aware. I am a powerhouse. Welcome for a selection of good things on sale.
What's that? Suit yourself, stranger. Let's go. Be careful, Ashley.
Hmm. OK.
You got to see on your awareness report card. I want to kill this guy without
alerting everybody. That would be nice. Oh, there are five. All right. Remind me to do these.
What's going on? Why is he still moving? Shut up. What is it hitting?
Rumor said shut up right after I said sorry. What? I didn't tell you to shut up. OK, so there's one
behind me over here. Up here, I think. Where is it? Like that way. Go up. And what do you think he
smells like at this point? I smell just I just smell like a regular. I don't know. Got everything
down here, I think. No, his handgun bullets. Those are up, though. I don't think I can get those.
I have to get up there first. OK, that's better. Let's go. You look like you would smell like
everything bagel seasoning. That sounds actually kind of good. And I don't have what's the problem
there? Oh, shit. What's going on? I backed myself into such a corner here. Snap that guy right in
the throat. OK, what about her? Ashley. I didn't shoot Ashley. That's why I was swinging the knife
because I didn't want to hit her. I didn't want to shoot her. Really? No, I want square gems.
Those are not square gems. Very frustrating. Does not open. This does not open either. It does.
What the heck? They came from there. You know, BRB. Yeah, when I get to the end of this next
chapter, I will be our be. Come on. Yes. Beautiful. Perfect. Replenishing. Yes. Very good. We're up
28 shots now. That's a good thing. OK. Oh, actually, you do it. OK, that leads us back up here.
Damn it. Where are you? What are you doing? Get over here. Come on.
Oh, my God. It was so funny. Fuck. Fuck. I don't want to. She just got locked. Are you all right?
That was a crowbar in the head. Watch out. Everything is good. Please move out of the way.
All right. Now, this time I'm not going to screw this up. I got everything I did. All right. This
time. So what? I tell her to run. Yes. All right. Still got eight. Very good. Now, I'm going to do
this because that spawns a bunch of people, apparently. Like you do it. My problem was I
jumped out. I should have just walked. Where are they? Fuck. What am I doing wrong? What happened?
Wait. No, don't do this. Not right now. What the fuck did I just do? Damn it. I didn't even turn
around once. I followed that guy up the stairs the whole time. Are you all right? OK. Now do it again.
Is it just out? Wait, what? What was the point of doing all that? You can just go this way.
Oh, because I unlocked it because it was locked before. I get it. We're good. Back up. Back up.
This way. This way. Follow me. No, no, no. Come close. Oh, get off my face.
You just walked into that Ashley and it would not have. She literally just walked into it almost.
That's a lot of handgun ammo. Any reason to go down here? No. Oh, that isn't. Can you recap
every joke? I was asleep. Um, it was the peanut butter jelly. There was a soundtrack to that
crazy room. Then there was, um, that was probably it. You're up to speed now.
I need two more still. Come on. There's going to be like alligators or something in here, isn't
there? I don't remember. Yes. All right. I need one more of these and I got another 100k.
I need a red one, right? Oh, the Roblox birthday party. Yeah, that was a really funny joke. That
was a really good joke. That's right. That was a really good joke I was making. Exactly. I'm glad
that you all we all agree on that because that doesn't really have to happen because it was a
funny joke. Good. Very good. It's not a joke. Well, a lot of people just said it was. Ashley,
how did you mess that up? Wait. Oh, I messed it up at the same time. Yeah. Okay. I pressed spacebar,
not E. Wait here. I can hear it. I can hear it going. What the fuck are you talking about?
What? What the hell is going on here? Oh, nice. I got, um, I got a, I got a hundred thousand dollars
now. That's the upgraded regenerators. Yep. I forgot. Very scary. Get that lever. I pressed it.
Is there a delay? E. There's a delay. There's a delay. There's like a full second delay. I
didn't know that. Give me some space. Got it. I know there's another one. This thing has no power.
Get this for me. Why couldn't I just do it? Why didn't I just do it? You gotta be ready for an,
this is going to be like an attack or something. This is fully loaded, right? Yep.
Ooh, I have so many of these. I really have so many. Okay. Good. Keep going.
Power. Just checking. I don't want to miss anything. All right. Hold on.
Full heal. I need a few more of those. All right. Let's do it. I know, I know it's coming.
That opens. No, no, no. Don't use that. Don't use that. Don't use that. I gotta go. I gotta go. I
gotta go. Oh God. Oh shit. Okay. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I gotta go right now. Hurry up. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no. Oh,
stop doing that. Don't move. Don't move. Don't move. Don't move. Don't move. Don't move. Don't move.
What are you doing? Oh, you're going to turn to the thing. Where is it?
Ow. Jesus. Okay. Nice work. Very good. I missed a treasure, but what can you do?
What can you do? That's okay. What can you do? Nah, what can you do? Sounds like you're at the
grocery store. It kind of does, you know, but people are raging because I'm not taking like
40 minutes on each puzzle now. I had breakfast this morning. Again, I had yogurt. I already
told you I had yogurt. I had a piece of toast. I had a nice big glass of water. I almost lied
instead of orange juice for no reason. I don't know why you would lie about something so stupid.
Oh, rats. Oh, wait a minute. I don't think I got all these. I didn't. Okay.
What can I do? Let's do it. Here we go. We've got red, green, $100,000. Now this one can do this.
$27,000. This one started. Very good. This one cannot be started, but we're making a lot of
money now. $100,000. $27,000. Here it is. This thing now will be doing like 40 per shot.
It's a good idea. You don't even use it. When I press this button, it is now going to be on
my hot bar and it will be used at every major boss encounter going forward. I'm worried.
We're good. All right. In the meantime, I don't think I'm going to be able to get a ticket,
so I'm going for it. Do it. This thing is ridiculous.
Oh, I'm going to buy. You still have those dirt. No, you don't. Okay. Where is the
Magnum is already here. And how many shots do I have with this? I have 19 shots with this Magnum.
There's a better Magnum. That's fine. This can stay the way it is. You're going to miss 19 times.
Now that would be really funny, but I don't think so. I kept upgrading this just because
it's good to have handguns doing just fine. It's all maxed out. Shotgun is maxed out,
getting close 37 in one go. Okay. I think this is a major encounter. If let me just make sure
take a sip. So I got the strategy guide down here. So it says that down here, Leon will be
ambushed by four major enemy types. One chainsaw enemy, one regenerator, one question mark,
question mark, question mark, question mark. Guy doesn't even know. And one boss is what's down
here. So if I jumped down here, let me make sure you can see. Yeah. Right here. I want what the
question mark is. Why would they not say that in the guide? That's weird. My ear is really itchy.
That's a lift. You might be the only person that needs a maxed out broken butterfly on
standard difficulty. What do you, what would it say? I need this. I just think it's fun to do.
Well, wait, why do you think I'm like, I'm doing that? Cause I feel like I need to do that.
I don't need the broken butterfly. It's just a fun thing to upgrade.
Why would driver's ed make you able to drive a wrecking ball? All you did is piss the building
off. You just hit the building on the side and made it scream. What are you swinging at?
Where are you going? What is he talking about? Open the window. Oh my goodness. That's a lot of
shit. What's that? Oh shit. I just like watched him do that. Hey, God damn it. I tried to.
That guy just landed on his neck. There's too many things happening yet. Where is that little
bug? Shit. Actually break the wall. She is actually stop. Stop. We need to think of a different way.
I'm fine. I'm fine. Oh God. Oh God. What do you mean help? Oh my God. What is fucking happening?
Somebody is beating the shit out of me with a club and I don't fuck off. Nice. All right. Collect.
I think I got everything. Most things. There's a lot of money over here. Wait, there's a lot of
money. That was pretty cool. Actually. You ever feel like a plastic bag? Yeah, actually sometimes
I don't think I can get the other two. Get this one. Last one is all the way across here.
I wonder where. Down there. Maybe I can still get it. Okay, let's go. You could go back and get it.
No, I got everything upgraded. I'm good. Pretty much this is what I have for the end game anyways.
Maxed out shotgun. Maxed out handgun. Maxed out magnum. There's a shortcut right here. Wait,
really? You mean like you're here? Oh, yeah, you're right. Okay, so that's the shortcut to
get right here. So then with this map, there's bullets. Where are these bullets? Where are these
bullets? Where are these bullets? In the trash. I thought you meant like in a dumpster. Very cool.
Let's move on. There have been sightings of what appears to be a strange corpse wandering around,
likely the result of some immoral experiment in the incubation lab. Do it or coward. Do it.
Do it. Do it. It's with the regenerators. Do it. Do it. It's going to be an omega regenerator.
It's my least favorite enemy in the game. All right. Fine. We're at the end anyways. Yeah,
that's right. It's true. I really don't want to go back here and do this, but I'm going to.
It is. Emerald can go in here now. Very good. All right. Down in the incubation lab,
straight through here, left, left. I need to save it first. I don't want to. I'm going to
blow through all my ammo. It's going to be a disaster. Have you seen One Piece? I've seen
random episodes of One Piece, but I don't. I haven't really cared to sit down and watch that
much of it. I've just seen random episodes on TV, just like scrolling around. My problem with One
Piece is isn't it still not done? And it's the manga has been going for like 30 years and there's
like 1500 volumes. It's like, where do I even start with that? Only five more years. Hey,
I'll tell you though, that's kind of lifelong media, isn't it? If you were a fan of One Piece,
10 plus years ago, you still get to enjoy it. It's still going. You still get to enjoy. Is
there going to be a thing you can kind of pay attention to sometimes? That's kind of cool.
Yeah, that thing's not dead. It is. Oh my God. This thing. Look at how many things. Stop doing
that. One more, one more, one more in the head. Ooh, that's it. Right. Nice. This is a bad idea,
but I'm gonna do it. I don't care. Ruby. I just wanted the Ruby. You're wasting ammo. I'm all
right. All right. That's all right. I got a Ruby. Kill the others. All this. Okay. I think I can
handle this. Ready? What the fuck? Die. All right. It was worth it. It was worth it. It was worth it.
I got two gems for that. It's fine. I'm good. Dude, the shotgun. I shoot like three times in
that area and it doesn't even kill the parasite. It's a lot of dog shit. All right. Let's get back
here. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. There's the, there's that back over here and then bang a left
up ladder. No, no, no, no. It's just right through.
Nice work. Got a selection of good things on sale. What should I even get at this point?
Velvet blues. Money. This is limitless. I could just get a ton of these.
One each to do. I don't really care about this anymore. All the velvet blues are that's going
to give me like 20, like at least grab the ticket. Nah. Get the funny scope. Nah. Punisher. Nah.
I'm just going to buy a shitload of these. Sell them. I'll get the map and then I'll get a bunch
of these. Hell yeah. Very good. 46k. Am I at the point where I should just start selling the gems
because I didn't find the other items? Not yet. This is good. All right. I do want to buy,
I should probably get this. That's the last upgrade for the case.
Then we're going to do, I don't know, maybe just just do power. Maybe
tuned weapon can make up for a lack of skill. Yeah. Just do power.
All right. Looking good. I need rifle ammo, but I think I can craft it actually.
I can. No, don't do that yet. Now I'll do it. Your body armor. I just upgraded it.
It's already broken already. I am molding. Sorry. All right. Let's go. Whoa.
Oh, it added it to the map, but where is it? Nice. Wait, I could do too. Okay. That's fun.
Let's go. No more stalling. First, we have to make it out of here.
I did not want to press the fucking button again. I wanted to press W,
but I went in the middle of the key. I didn't. I pressed E instead of W because I just have never
learned where they are because if you have a keyboard, it's just spread out and I can't even.
It's just my fingers try to find E and it's, there's a big space here and I just mushed in the
middle. I'm going to get my mesh keyboard back. Nothing in here. Yes, there is.
One of the things they say in the original, they go, and the music goes,
I must stress the use of extreme caution when handling the amber deposits from underneath
the castle. Work with the utmost respect and obedience. It is imperative that you do not
disturb the holy body's slumber. Treasures in here. This must be what Luis was talking about.
You. Damn, that thing's probably worth a lot. Nice. Crystal ore.
Dearest Lord Saddler, I am overjoyed to report wonderful news. Production of the superior species
of Las Plagas is officially underway. If all goes accordingly, rest assured that we will reach our
ultimate goal. The Plaga is a truly magnificent organism that has the capacity to live in any
vertebrae, be it human, dog, or even crow. There is no other parasite like it on earth. The superior
species is particularly impressive as it can assimilate with a host without causing any damage
to the brain. No one can oppose the strength of your dominance, my Lord. On the contrary,
who would resist once they experience the utter joy that accompanies the absence of free will?
I'm living proof how ignorant I once was. In a few days, I will have finished
administrating the Plaga to all the high-ranking researchers, and then they too shall know. And
when your plan is complete, the whole world shall know. The head researcher. Project. Don't touch
that.
Obey. Obey the voice of our Lord. I feel like, uh, uh-oh.
Thank God she's a really bad shot with this. Or she's a really good shot.
I can see this. My faithful disciple shall deliver to you your pennies. Now, child,
you need not be afraid. Submit your body and release yourself from fear.
Hell's Kitchen. Stop ruining cutscenes.
Okay. I got everything in here, didn't I? Yes, I did. Let's go.
All right. I have enough loaded, don't I? Which way does this go?
It can go both ways, but I'll go this way first. Good.
For your request, redevelopment of the island is well underway. Weapons and other defensive
equipment have been set to guard against any outside intruders. By the time we are finished,
the island will be a giant fortress. Very cool. These defenses won't hold up long term,
but they should last until we carry out our plan. Where is this thing?
I wonder how many of those I actually missed. Probably a few at this point, right?
He didn't even see me. Stop. There's one per chapter. Huh. So I, yeah, so I missed a few.
That's good to know for future playthroughs, though. So we'll see. 14k.
I don't really need money for anything else besides a sniper rifle. I'm just gonna make
sure I have enough going forward. When is BRB? Very soon. Want me to read it? Want me to read it?
No. Yes. No. Yeah. No. Yeah. No. All right, we'll do the TLDR.
Few people have heard of the name, even within the highest ranks of the U.S. Government. In
little wonder, too, the operation was not made public. Operation Javier? Started back in 2002.
I don't know if the mission was a failure. It shouldn't have been difficult to extract a single
stranded unit. Why did it take so long? The U.S. Government let those people die,
brave young people who dedicated their lives to protect the country.
And I want to expose this crime. Operation Javier was written by an American journalist.
I don't know if Jeremy doesn't read comments like, you've got a nice sheen today. I just did.
That's me. Oh, no, it's Saw. He made a Saw trap for me. Hello again, Leon. Come on. So annoying.
So annoying. It's so annoying. I haven't sneezed in like nine days. And every time I'm about to,
when I want to do a stupid thing I want to do, it just stops. And I can usually look at the light.
But the light's not on. The lights are off. So I have to look at the big ring light in the corner
and it doesn't work. Usually I can go like this, bang, and hit the overhead light right here,
but it's off. So there's one light over in the corner that doesn't work. All right, we're good.
Let's go. I can read this. Phase one, depart from campus with the target.
Escort the target as usual until the start of phase two. There should be three others inside
the vehicle, including Baker. Able's unit will follow behind you in a separate vehicle.
Continue to drive at your normal route. Stop the vehicle under the pretense of engine trouble.
Transfer the target to Able's vehicle. Able's unit will change course. Subdue and restrain the
target. Place the target in a large container. Baker's unit will create a diversion. Henry's
unit will infiltrate the investigation's database and disable the network. Meet at point K9 and
transfer the cargo. What are they talking about? What does that mean? What are they talking about?
There's a treasure here. A large gold bar. Okay. Nice. Get out of here. This game is so good.
This game is so fun. Look alive. Is there really something in there?
That must be so weird. Imagine you're just hanging out waiting for me at some point.
You don't know when I'm going to show up. And then this is how I appear.
I just would scare the shit out of me. This would be terrifying. That would be so scary.
Welcome. What can I do you for? That's good work if I do say so myself. Reload speed probably. Yeah.
Try that on for size. See how that feels mate. A fellow like yourself should notice the difference
right away. Okay. Will that be all then? Pleasant travel. Are we enjoying the game? Yes. Very much
so. We're almost at the end as well. We only got probably like what? An hour or two? I think this
is the end of the chapter coming up here. Okay. Oh wait. I remember this part. This part was weird.
The ruins. Oh yeah. I forgot about the ruins. It was a little more sandy in the old one.
You always had poor judgment. But if you think I'm going to let you out of here alive,
you're even more naive than I thought. You can't save her. You can't save anyone. Give it up,
Krauser. Had enough. Being a lackey for these maniacs won't bring your men back.
And what the hell for? Revenge on the government? You think they would want that? Revenge.
You think I'm doing all this for revenge? Isn't that what this is all about? See,
in that jungle I had a revelation. The most important thing in this world is pure
unadulterated power. Giving me that. You know you were always an asshole.
But at least you had some kind of code. Some honor. Look at you now. Enough reminiscing.
Move out and draw fire, soldier.
Squibs didn't go off, Krauser. I just turned him into Super Mario.
Drop it. What's that mean? Remember the basics of CQC? Yeah.
Stop talking out loud, Leon. He's laid this place out with traps. I better be careful. I
probably shouldn't walk into the red laser right here in front of me. Can I turn this off if I get
close enough? What is that? What's going on? What's that sound? Oh, I got it. Did I get it?
I got it. Oh, nice. Sentry down. That's a pretty good one.
Sorry. Slowly filling this back up. Slowly filling it back up.
I'd be dead if I kept listening to people like you.
That also means the Reaper is coming for you. Don't talk over me during my big moment.
The Reaper is coming for you too then. Doesn't that mean it's coming for us all?
It's coming for you too? That would have been way cooler.
Chefs, four of you are going to make it through the next round.
Only two of you will do this next challenge. Before you is a sacred ingredient.
All right. I don't want to get killed. Didn't even hurt.
What was that?
Oh, I got them all. He's going to run into this.
We're done here, Krauser. Again. Time for the Las Lagas.
That's the difference between you and me, Loki.
It's like Nightmare from Soul Calibur.
Yeah. Can I get time out for a minute? I'm crafting.
Reload it. Hold on, Krauser. Let me reload every single gun.
I just pissed him off so bad. Hey, guys. We're back.
Get all this ammo now. I'm getting kind of stacked here.
There are slugs. I got all 48 are loaded. I got 50. Look, I have 51.
Here we go.
Time for the teacher to be taught.
Okay, I'm fine. Oh, shit. He's kind of fast.
Look at my head. What the fuck am I doing?
Tab didn't open the inventory. It was stuck. I pressed Tab.
Stop hitting me. It's annoying. What the fuck am I doing?
Get out of here. 50 slugs, Stephen. He loves the cheese shotgun.
Well, I put almost $400,000 into this. I'm going to use it on the bosses.
And then if I run out of ammo, I have 20 shots with the fully upgraded butterfly
at the end of the game and I can kill the boss in like three hits.
Almost lost it there. I think there's some other items to get.
The new knife is sick. I bet it is. And we still have plenty of shotgun shots.
Wait, there's no time to escape, somebody said.
Yeah, doesn't that happen? Did they take that out?
Hmm, interesting. There's a couple of very decent changes in the remake.
Is it on professional? Oh, that's not the last boss.
But I feel like doesn't it? I'm just remembering it wrong.
They removed the underground huge monster. 14 beat Jack Krauser.
Killed two parasites inside a regenerator with a single bullet.
Destroyed five targets at the shooting range with one shot.
Cool. All right, we're going to take a quick break.
I have not gone to the bathroom. I'm going to go pee.
I'm going to get some more water and we will be back in a minute or two.
See you in a sec. Hey, how's it going?
Scared you? Didn't mean to.
All right, let's get to the end game. There's only one.
I think the last chapter is very short. Let's go for it.
We got one more after this, but I think it's a pretty short one.
So this is probably going to be another maybe a couple hours.
I am not going to rush through this because this is a great game.
I love this game and I don't want to just run through.
But we are at the final arc.
You're going to finish this tonight? Yes.
That's got to be their sanctuary.
I will finish the game tonight.
Ashley.
Okay. I feel like I got to move in a little more.
I feel like I'm too far away from everything.
That's better. Okay, good.
Let's go. Wait, I just don't.
When's the boss fight?
Take a look. Something's bound to catch your eye.
I just did one, man.
Well caught a selection of good things on sale, stranger.
A well-tuned weapon can make up for a lack of skin.
You could probably play through most of the game with the knife.
So this is the better knife.
Should I sell the other one?
Should I sell the combat knife?
Ruby's all rubbish. It makes no difference.
The price? Well, that's our choice to make.
Why not? Just upgrade the other one.
You could keep both.
Also when this one's done, I can go to this one.
Oh, so I'm going to have to...
Well, then I guess I will tune it up or not.
I'm going to stick with the plan.
That's cool, though.
40% off. Damn.
I'm not going to use it anyways.
I've already got my setup.
Is it equipped?
It's not equipped, but I'll equip it after.
Buy resources?
Did he fill the shop up with resources?
Oh, he did. Okay.
Don't get yourself killed now.
Okay. Save it again.
I would be so bad with the save shit.
I just... I'm such a compulsive saver.
Whoa. Oh, he almost hit your friend.
Imagine him. Back up.
You got it. Nice shooting.
Shoot him. Shoot these guys.
I got to keep moving. Treasure.
Where's the treasure? Back here.
I mean, I'm farming right now.
This actually is kind of cool.
I can just farm.
All right. I'm done. I'm done.
Thank you. Nice work.
All right. Get them. Nice. Good work.
Stop. You're shooting at me right now.
Treasures. I got you.
Where are you pissing? Where do I go?
What are you talking about?
Oh, my God. You're shooting me.
Wait. Oh, it's... Dude, stop.
Put it down.
Like, what is even happening right now?
Like, dude, I fucking shot the guy like eight times.
He's just so close.
Whatever. And horse shit.
All right. Okay. All right.
You're going to shoot that shit, isn't it?
I can't right now. Man.
You know what? Get the fuck away from me, all of you.
Okay. Where... Are there people on those?
Stop it.
How do I get up there?
I have to go down?
Well, there's a bunch of shit in here.
That's the shortcut.
I don't know, dude. You're the expert.
I haven't played this game in 10 years.
I... Do I go down?
Okay. All right. Now, where can I go?
Up? Can I do it with a grenade?
I don't think so.
I think I gotta go all the way.
I think it's a scripted thing.
Throw grenades at it? No, I'm good.
I'm just gonna go this way.
Okay. You piece of shit.
I'm all right.
All right. We did it. Nice job.
Now what? Jump down? Now what?
You're gonna blow something up for me?
You're gonna blow this up?
There we go.
Did you even tweet?
Oh, probably not.
Out of ammo?
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
The guy hit me.
He got triple tapped me in a melee.
They don't even swing that much.
They literally don't even swing more than three times.
More than two.
I'm... Good thing I saved it.
It pisses me off when they do the little juke.
I'm so angry about that.
They do the...
Just reload. Just kill me.
Reload. Just reload. Reload.
Just hit me.
Just reload it. Reload it. Reload it.
This is stupid.
Holy shit, dude.
Stop overreacting?
I'm not.
This is just fucking mayhem every five seconds.
Oh my god.
This is just fucking mayhem.
They don't even know what they're attacking.
They're just shooting at random people.
Look at this.
I can't even run.
Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Good. Nice job.
Fuck you.
What are you all doing?
You weren't even near me.
Literally nobody was here.
I have a sniper rifle.
Are you dumb?
I just spent 15 hours in game without a sniper rifle.
So now I have one magically and my brain is just like, no, you don't.
All right. Let's go.
Anything else I need to do here?
I don't think so.
I have to put these...
Oh, yeah. Okay. Here we go.
Don't even think about it.
It's the best way to get over there.
Oh, God is one of those things.
What's wrong with me?
What is wrong with my character?
Why is he...
Why am I limping like this?
Why am I limping?
Whoa. All right.
How do I get over there?
Through this building.
Okay. Through here.
This way.
And then...
Wait. How do I get in there?
Can I press the...
Is there an elevator I can press?
I can't go in there.
Hold on. There.
All right. Let's go.
Imagine being in this orchestra.
This is a killing zombie soundtrack.
Really? That'd be kind of cool.
Anybody? No. Let's go.
There's probably treasures and shit here,
but anytime this music plays like this,
I just have to run.
This is just panic music.
Remember when I used to turn off the music
for Dark Souls bosses and win?
Same scenario.
He's all right.
He's okay.
This is new.
I think this actually is new.
Hey, this is new.
In the old one,
he doesn't use his arm and go through the windshield.
Oh, it's a rocket launcher.
Right. Interesting.
Okay. It was a rocket.
Right, right, right, right.
Ooh. Let's check up here first.
Honestly, that makes a bit more sense,
but whatever.
I got a lot of money.
Is there anything else I want to do
before I get to the very end here?
Make sure you shoot this medallion here.
Oh shit. I can't even see it.
Okay. Blue medallions.
Any more here?
Looks like there's another...
I think I have to get them all right now.
Get in the water?
It's below me.
Okay. What about this one?
There's one up here.
What's the best way to go up there?
I don't know.
Below me.
Whatever.
I don't know where it is.
I don't really care about the spinals anymore anyways.
Down in here somewhere?
What is this?
Ooh. Staff of royalty.
Very cool.
Nice.
That's probably worth a lot.
Okay. This is in here somewhere.
No, it's not.
I don't even care. I'm leaving.
You just have to give up and then you'll find it.
This one is...
I wonder if I can...
No, wait, wait.
I think I can...
Can I lean out the edge here and get this one if I go out here?
I think if I go down here and look that way?
Finished.
Is your cosplay is Leon?
We talked about it the other day.
I'll do it on your birthday.
Who's birthday?
Whoever's birthday is...
Never mind.
I'll take it back.
The repairs were completed without issue
since the facility was previously used for confinement.
The work required to reinforce the airtight ceiling was minimal.
As long as we don't run into any issues with the cooling system test,
we plan to bring in all the remaining specimens from Facility 1.
We changed my title.
All specimens were successfully transferred.
However, we experienced a slight hiccup during transport
as one of them became violent.
Luckily, the number of casualties was less than anticipated.
Please be extra careful when dealing with them.
We have received reports that they are beginning to acquire
a tolerance for the low temperatures.
I think I can make some gear now.
Loading back up.
This doesn't open.
I...
Oh, I hear a thingy.
Splendid bangle.
Okay.
These are gonna open, aren't they?
Oh, quick!
So I'm gonna jump out of one of these.
I know what...
What was that?
What the fuck?
Oh!
No, you're on the ground.
That's so annoying.
Homer Simpson?
Maybe a little.
Nice.
Eight.
I think it's just all money at this point.
What's that face?
I think I'm just going full on money.
Yeah, we're just doing money.
Let's go.
25k.
Hell yeah.
25k again.
Ooh, if I can do that.
Let's go.
I have so many...
There might be time just to start selling everything.
It's probably time to start selling.
Sniper rifle all the way?
I can get clothes.
Very cool.
Oh, there's another one of those down there.
Nice.
All right, what can I do here?
There's another one of these?
Holy shit.
Okay, gotta check it out.
Oh no, this is just if you want to do it again.
Yeah, I'm good.
It's a really cool part of the game, but I'm good.
I don't need all S-Ranks.
Very cool.
Let's go.
Sell the old knife.
I'll probably just hang on to it, honestly.
I might need it.
Okay, this is where we're going.
Let's go.
Really?
You finishing the game tonight?
You betcha.
Yes, I am.
What happened up there?
Oh, come on, dude.
I hear a bug.
There's so many critters in this game.
There are a lot of critters.
You're right.
Why is it playing this music?
This is what I'm talking about.
Why is it playing this?
This is the look out, watch out music.
Nice.
We are under fucking attack.
Yeah, that is what that is going on in there.
There's a halloween house over here.
That's a haunted house.
Can you turn lo-fi beats on?
You can just open it.
That is a shitload of people here now.
Throw it, throw it out here.
Is that guy still in there or is he dead?
Oh, he died.
That's a lot of ammo.
Any plans for a Yonkey Splonkey 2?
You had an OG Twitch dance.
Now, everyone's doing their own thing.
I don't know if my...
I think you guys came up with that.
I kind of just did a dance and then you guys named it.
What's that sound?
Do a Yonkey Splonkey remake.
Where is it?
That was pretty good.
That was actually really good.
Oh, thank God.
Oh my God.
Oh, oh my goodness.
Where'd it go?
It's opening the door.
Dude, it's fucking opening doors.
I forgot the last arc of this game goes very, very hard.
Gets crazy.
Okay, nice.
I hate all things that are critters.
Why do you hate critters?
You don't like critters?
Why not?
What's wrong?
Okay, well, I need to turn that off.
It's 11-11.
Make a wish.
What'd you wish for?
You can't tell people what you wish for.
Otherwise, it won't come true.
I know some of you.
Some of you have only wished for this.
The Yonkey Splonkey remake.
Wish granted.
Anything over here?
Hot scene, probably.
I hear red barrel.
All right.
I, Adam.
It didn't go far enough.
But I wish to share this gift with as many as possible.
A humble wish, don't you think?
You see, we are all connected through the Holy Body.
And now your flesh and bones, your very thoughts.
Is that a skull?
It kind of looks like Bowser from the old Mario movie.
Accept the sacred gift.
She did.
Souther!
Yes, the time has come.
We'll be slain to join our covenant.
Oh, blessings on to him and the sweet mercy they bring.
And salt!
And let it be salt!
Ah, shit!
Let's get out of here.
All right.
Time to go.
Any items over here?
Where do we go?
Laboratory B.
Okay, let's go.
Come on.
It's got a lot of strength still.
We gotta get fixed up.
I was waiting for a jump scare.
One of them is not going to grab me.
The Undertaker entrance for WrestleMania.
I loved that song.
It was great.
That was the remix version.
Not the original.
Fuck, I gotta do it now.
Never mind.
He's faking.
What a faker?
What do you mean faker?
He's faking it.
Have we so fucked up?
All right, this is the end.
It was an awesome journey.
It's time to get to the end.
By the way, I didn't do it yet.
I don't know how to do it.
Yeah, I did this.
And by the way, in me trying to figure it out,
I broke two of the lasers.
You're gonna have to hold one of them
against your chest for the next four hours.
Yeah, I found it.
I think it says we can get out if we can.
Hey, we're a team, right?
Keep this up.
I'll be out of a job.
Oh yeah, did you draw on the map with the crayon?
All of this.
Removing the parasites.
This was the week.
Yeah, we're alive.
Thanks to him.
I'm surprised this thing even booted up.
Man, Lewis got this thing going on a raspberry pea?
That's impressive.
Do not be fooled into thinking that
Las Plagas are merely tools for creating powerful bioweapons.
The true value lies in their ability to control.
No matter, I've been doing that a lot today,
that no matter how hostile the subject is,
single injection can turn anyone into a faithful servant
who needs spies and you can turn yesterday's enemy
into today's ally.
Controlling just one insider
can bring an entire organization
or an entire country to its knees.
Mass production of the superior species
has made this possible.
We have empowered Saddler.
It's clear what he intends to do next.
Can you imagine if Saddler had that much control?
Six billion loyal servants at his sole command.
There'd be no opposition, no war.
If for the first time in human history,
the world would know peace.
But I know how Saddler and the others
have oppressed the people of this island for generations.
I know how he treats them.
That's no way to live.
And because of that, I won't let it happen.
Who wrote this?
That was Louis, okay.
Makes sense.
Europe Laboratory Six Dream Team.
Holy shit, guys.
Wait, this is Europe Laboratory Six.
This is Umbrella.
Holy shit.
Damn, what's this?
Someone had a field day looting the Umbrella Labs.
What the hell was that?
Any treasures in here?
First aid spray.
Okay.
Let's complete this game.
Sorry.
Raspberry P.
Thank you.
I think so.
All right.
This inventory is a mess.
Why is it such a mess?
School health.
Why am I angry?
Why does everyone think I'm angry today?
I'm not.
What?
Does my brow look weird?
Does my face look weird?
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
Your face is very mean today.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's a treasure.
Oh, I'm sure she's fine.
Eh, we're good.
She's not the type to roll over that easy.
That's because you said no roadblocks.
True.
Okay.
Wait.
Secret.
No secret?
Was the secret the other way?
There are two ways to go.
Resident Evil more like Resident Sleeper.
We already went this way.
Hmm?
Resident Evil more like Resident Sleeper.
The final chapter of the Illuminatos.
Praise be to the holy insects.
We have been promised paradise on earth.
Man, woman, or child, his love does not discriminate.
Beast, fish, or bird, all creatures shall be equally blessed.
Praise be to the holy insects.
We are the humble servants of God.
His wisdom will overcome any mountain.
His omnipotence will cross any ocean.
The light of heaven dwells in all things.
Let our bodies be the seedbed.
Praise be to the holy insects.
We are the flock and the shepherd guides us.
Our prayers will be sung all over the world.
They will be heard by all.
At last, we shall exceed the stars in the sky.
Osmond, deep beneath the castle grounds, I have found my faith.
Oh, behold, the divine vestiges left upon this world.
It all begins here.
Adam Sandler.
Oh, nice.
Get out of here.
I think I have to go that way.
Lord and Savior, Adam Sandler.
Yes.
Treasures?
Yep.
There are two treasures in here.
What are you doing?
Got it.
There's one more.
It's in this room.
I think this is it.
Wow.
I'm pretty sure this is it.
This is the this is the end here.
I think this is the end.
Is it time to sell everything?
I think about time to sell literally everything.
Because I think this is actually the last place to see him.
That's our choice to make.
I think it's time to do it.
If you can't beat the jet ski escape within three tries,
you have to play Roblox for one hour on your birthday.
Right.
Okay.
Don't sell the key.
I already did.
Sell all your weapons, too.
Everything.
Sell everything and then walk out with nothing.
I think that's good.
Final tune up.
This is all good.
All right.
We can do we can do this.
Let's do ammo capacity.
See how that feels.
And then a fellow like yourself should notice whatever I can do with this.
This kind of work is about finesse.
You've exhausted our normal range of services for this weapon.
All right.
This thing's good to go.
Too bad I couldn't get it.
But it's all good.
You catch my drift.
Buy the RPG.
Now I'm good.
Gotta come back.
Now we're good.
Any time.
All right.
I've got my sniper rifle.
My Omega shotgun.
20 shots with a times almost two damage on the broken butterfly.
This is going to be perfect.
RPG.
What do you mean?
Buy the RPG or you.
I don't want the RPG.
I got what I want.
And that's 20 shots with a quadruple damage magnum.
48 slugs.
I'm ready.
I'm unloading everything.
Anything?
I customize anything here at this point.
I don't think it matters.
Maybe the healing.
Yeah, that's fine.
All right.
Let's go.
Send it.
Can we wager that you will miss the first shot with the magnum?
Sure.
Good.
Make a bet.
Will I miss the first shot I do with the magnum?
Go for it.
Go ahead and vote.
You can bet that.
Now, wait, wait, wait.
What constitutes a miss?
That's important.
Like a complete miss.
Don't hit any body part at all.
Or I have to hit the exact spot that that matters.
Like the weakness part.
We need to make that clear.
We're talking about no damage, a complete miss.
Just a complete miss.
Okay.
Or weak spot.
So if I miss the weak spot with the first shot,
then you can go ahead and pay everybody out.
If I hit the weak spot with the first shot,
then you lose.
And everybody else that's betting on me wins.
The weak spot.
No, I'll hit it.
That's easy.
I'm telling you.
That's simple.
It's I'm telling you.
It's simple.
I'll be fine.
Ada thinks he's going to lure me out.
Well, it worked.
Because here we come.
Stay here.
I won't be long.
A heads up would have been a little more appreciated probably.
Real missed opportunity for him to be like,
you'll never get away with this.
That would have been perfect.
All right.
I got to focus because I don't want to miss it.
I know where the weak parts are.
Got it.
Oh, that stings.
Oh, oh, please.
I have so much shit in my inventory.
Get away from me.
Oh, oh, I had to end it with the shotgun.
Getting sick of your shit.
Oh, my God.
That was a lot of damage, though.
See you later.
Give me that shit.
All 50 shots almost.
Worked out pretty well.
That was pretty cool.
And he take if you don't do the rocket launcher thing,
he takes a lot of hits at the end there.
50 slugs, Steven does it again.
Nothing personal, Leon.
Luis and I had an arrangement.
I'll take good care of it.
What was it?
Three attempts or I have to play Roblox on April 5th or whatever it is?
Fight's here.
We both know this.
It's where we go our separate ways.
I see.
I wonder how hard that is on hardcore and professional.
Professional's probably a joke.
Better get a move on.
Am I a joke as in almost impossible?
Where is she going?
Who knows?
I don't understand.
Why would she just?
I'm gonna move.
Island's gonna blow.
Go.
Time to run.
We got two minutes to get out of here.
Anything else?
Why?
Who cares if you go?
Not yet.
Keep up the pace.
Jesus.
What's going on there?
I love this rat.
Can we take one of the rats with us?
Open it.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Let's do it.
All right.
Don't fuck it up.
I got three tries.
We got to play Roblox.
It's pretty forgiving.
It's kind of, it's forgiving.
I'm all right.
I did it.
I win.
Happy birthday to you.
Baby, what is this title?
What is going on in the title right now?
Mission accomplished, right?
Mission accomplished.
I'm safe.
Ashley B.
Thank you for saving me.
Jet Ski's out of gas.
Don't mention it.
And I only brought one more bologna and cheese sandwich.
I could put an award with my dad.
Where?
Fuck.
Have you assigned to my detail?
If you're interested.
You don't need me.
You proved you could handle yourself.
Even if you could use a lesson in knife safety.
Come on.
Let's go home.
Rooster Condor 1, do you read me?
We are not making it back to America.
Is this thing even on?
Like four gallons of gas.
Whatever it takes in a Jet Ski.
Where are we?
There's like three gallons.
That's great.
If you liked it.
If you liked Resident Evil 4
and you're trying to figure out if you should get the remake.
You should.
Absolutely.
That's phenomenal.
And it's Resident Evil 4.
Of course it is.
Why'd you take the label off your chapstick?
I didn't.
It's like it's in a tube.
It goes like like a little closer.
It's like Trader Joe's.
Trader Joe's cucumber mint.
It's like a...
So the Plaga storyline goes through six.
And then the mold is seven up.
And then the virus, the T-virus is one, two, three.
Or the virus.
Do you think they'll remake five and six?
Judging by how well these do, I think.
And how much people really like these.
I don't know if they're going to do six.
But five is probably up next in a few years.
I would imagine.
I think six is...
I think you just percent...
I think you just pretend six didn't just never existed.
I don't know.
You'd have to remake the whole game.
Six was just not a good game either.
Four and five were good games.
To me, six was not a good game.
Six was a pretty bad game.
So you'd have to do a lot to make a remake of six, I think, better.
I've obtained the amber.
Excellent.
Just one question.
What are you planning to do with this?
Do not pay you to ask questions.
You need to know, as a new dawn is breaking.
A hundred will give their lives so that just one may live.
I, expediting that change.
So, we're talking millions of casualties.
Billions.
How ambitious.
We're changing course.
Now.
I think five was kind of polarizing.
But I really liked five.
I thought five was really fun.
Five was kind of four, but a little more stuff.
A little...
It had the whole co-op, right?
That was a lot of fun.
I think people give five a lot of shit.
I thought five was really good.
I don't think it's as good as four, but I think it's...
It was a worthy sequel, I think.
Six, they just went completely...
It was a mess.
Six, I don't even...
Honestly, I've played six recently.
And I don't even remember it.
I have no idea.
Seven was good.
Yeah, the new arc was fun.
I like seven and eight.
Yeah, me and italics played it.
Yeah, the new ones were good.
I liked them both.
The two remake was hard to beat when it comes to remake.
But I think they came pretty close on this one.
I love this franchise.
It's a great franchise.
Resident Evil is one of the only franchises I can really think of
that has actually continued to do really, really great games.
This far.
This laid into the whole franchise.
They're still making...
I mean, you know, Resident Evil is seven and eight.
Where a lot of people, you know...
I think they were good.
I think that they're from one through eight.
Only one or two of them are really not that great.
I think as a whole, the whole franchise has been doing really well still.
So it's really cool.
I mean, I love Resident Evil.
I always have.
You said eight's ending was shitty.
Yeah, but the game as a whole was fun.
It was worth playing.
It was worthy to play it.
It was good.
Listen to this song.
You should play Mercenaries when it comes out.
Yeah, what's the new...
What's the content release schedule for this?
Because there's a couple of things, right?
There's the little spoilers, but...
Ada's campaign.
April 7th.
That's it, really.
Drops next week.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Are we gonna get the Ada, please?
Play through?
Or is that probably gonna be DLC?
Hasn't been announced.
That's cool, though.
Yeah, Mercenaries was a ton of fun.
I dumped hours and hours and hours into it when it first came out.
Long time ago.
All right, well, we have to spend our currency.
I have like 20,000 of it or something.
Let's go to the bonuses.
Yeah, I'm not even gonna give you a rating.
You know what it is.
It's at least a nine plus.
It just is.
Resident Evil 4 is one of the best games ever made.
This was a great remake.
They did a very, very good job.
How do you tackle a game like this everybody loves?
And it's some people's favorite game ever made.
I think they did a really good job.
I think it's worth buying, for sure.
The old one is still good to go back to,
but I think they did a justice, for sure.
Great.
They redeemed themselves after the Resident Evil 3 remake.
Oh, yeah, 100%.
Absolutely.
The third remake was, it was all right.
Looking back with some time, it was all right.
Could have been a lot better.
But remember, they were coming right off of Resident Evil 2's remake,
which is, I mean, that was game of the year for me, for a lot of people.
So right after that, it's like, oh, Resident Evil 3 remake.
It's gonna be so, it's gonna be just as good as two.
It's not even close to as good as the second remake.
Oh, no.
But if a game is a 7 versus like a 10, that's kind of unfair.
Like that game was like,
Resident Evil 2 was like a 9.8 for me, the remake.
You go right from that to like a solid, but like, hmm.
There's some, eh, it was all right.
Hard to do that.
Especially after Resident Evil 2's remake.
Just kind of rushed, yeah.
It was fine.
It was all right.
All right, I think we're good.
Should I just skip this, I think?
Probably.
Hold on, I want to listen to this song for a second.
What about the Dead Space remake?
Do you guys want to see that?
Should I play that on stream?
Yeah.
Should I play the remake or should I play the original one?
I heard the remake is really good.
So I'm imagining probably the remake.
You'd like it?
Cool.
All right, let's skip.
Get to the end.
Quiet.
Congratulations.
Good work.
Not gonna be.
Is it because I saved 114 times?
Is it because I saved 100 plus times?
If this was less than 100, it would have been A.
I just spam the save because it's like,
I sold this thing.
Save it.
Oh, I broke that thing.
Turn around, save it.
I just saved it.
I saved it one minute ago?
Did I save it one minute ago?
Just to be sure, save it again.
One save every 10 minutes.
It's just for time?
Okay, that's fine.
Complete the main story on standard or higher.
Unlocked a costume.
I got the pinstripe costume,
brown sunglasses and a foam mask
and a flight cap.
Cool.
Okay.
So I mean, I want to do this, right?
New playthrough.
All right, let's do the bonuses then.
Professional mode has been unlocked.
All right, extra content.
I got 21,000.
Buy everything.
Jacket.
All right.
Whoa, what's this?
Cool.
All right, hold on.
I think I have enough to get everything
or at least most.
Whoa, this is concept art.
I want to see this.
I want this.
This.
Weapons.
Get the weapons.
I can't, I don't have any.
At least unlock the cool models first.
What?
These are the cool ones.
All right.
Ooh, scary.
Hate these things.
Cool.
Look at that.
This looks really real somehow.
The shadows.
Okay.
Oh, pinstripe Leon.
Does pinstripe Leon say anything else?
I wish I had the whole playthrough with this.
Why do they have like Woody from Toy Story?
You pull the string.
Got a lot of stuff.
That's the one that goes,
Ah, yes, sir.
Right from the other one.
Oh, yep.
Ah, weird.
I just stepped on my router.
Just felt like, damn.
These guys were cool.
This was a cool.
I don't think these guys were in the old game.
So that's cool.
Bebop and Rocksteady.
Ah, these guys.
These guys.
It's kind of lame.
Oh, the biggest, scariest guy in the whole game.
The ultimate villain.
I am Osman Saddler.
It's just kind of like,
you could have done a different voice.
A different voice line than that.
That was just stating your name.
Not like, you will never escape me.
It has to be just kind of,
hey, this is who I am.
Cute.
Hey, did you have fun playing Resident Evil 4?
Did you like how much ammo you found?
Do you like Osman Saddler?
I didn't think so.
Are you smart?
Yeah, are you good?
Okay, now get out of here.
Oh, I can't do a voice line for this.
These are the incomplete ones.
I'm curious about some of these.
Survive the battle at the villa
without blocking any of the windows with wooden planks.
Okay.
Make it through Ashley's section
without using the lantern.
It's probably kind of hard.
What are some of the high?
Okay, this one's expensive.
Destroy all clockwork.
Oh, you get the super knife
for getting all 16 of them.
Very cool.
I do want to do one quick thing.
I just want to see.
Whoa, wait, hold on.
Face guard?
Oh, I can put this doesn't work with that.
I want to see.
I just want to see.
No auto save pairing is limited to perfect parries
and all weapon modifications
will be available from the start.
I just want to see the outfit.
Yeah, this is the end of the stream, by the way.
Those of you waiting.
I just want to see the costume.
Fucking dickhead.
Agent 47.
That's it.
What was that?
That was it.
Turn the original music on and sound effects.
Oh, I could do that.
No, that's it.
I'll see you guys later.
Let's talk about what the plan is
this upcoming next little bit.
So I will see you all on Friday.
I'll see you Friday.
So it is midnight Thursday.
I will see you guys on Friday.
We're going to just chill out a little bit.
Play some Breath of the Wild.
Just going to be working through it.
That was awesome.
I'm sad that it's kind of over.
It's a kind of post-awesome game depression, right?
Whatever you want to call it.
Like, oh, that was really cool.
That was great.
That was worth waiting for.
What an amazing game.
What an amazing experience.
And now it's over.
But it's not because I can play through it again.
There's a lot I didn't do.
But that was really good.
Also, keep in mind, again,
Grotto Beasts is going to be shipping
for at least the first pass,
the first pass of the pre-sale orders.
So over the next week or two,
I would keep an eye on your mailbox.
So I think we're very imminent on shipping.
So that's really exciting.
Say again when the pre-sale ends.
So you could effectively operate
as if the pre-sale is over.
I would say as of now.
We are extending some stuff.
The posters and all that stuff
has been extended just by a little bit.
But you can operate as if,
I would say as if we're out of pre-sale.
I would say, yeah.
Now there is something that is going to happen
to be the official,
the official launch of the project.
You'll have to see what that is.
I'm not going to tell you anything else.
And it's fucking cool.
That's it.
I'm going to implode, yeah.
What time are you going to stream on Friday?
Probably around the same time.
Probably like 5, 6.
Just put 6 p.m. Pacific.
Easier that way.
It's going to be a really chill stream.
Cam's going off for another little while.
Going to relax, play some Breath of the Wild.
If you want to join us, please do.
Should be fun.
So that was Resident Evil 4.
And when the Mercenaries comes out,
I'm sure I'll play it.
For at least a couple of hours or something.
Very good.
Let me just quit out of this.
See you on Friday.
Are you ever going to play Sorcery ever again?
Let me get through Breath of the Wild
because I feel like the Breath of the Wild berries are...
They are starving.
So let's get through Breath of the Wild first.
What about House Flipper?
I don't know.
Probably not.
This is some new stuff.
Don't forget my birthday, please.
My Roblox birthday.
Would you ever do Stardew Valley again?
There's definitely a place for it
during one of these chiller streams.
Maybe one day.
But good night.
See you Friday.
Technically tomorrow for a lot of you.
Season.
Have a great rest of your night.
I'll see you on the weekend.
Or the start of the weekend.
Take it easy.
Call your mother.
Have a great day.
Goodbye.