I was an hour late. Wait, what? I was an hour late? Where? What? No, it's just one.
I just had like a heart attack. I was like, wait, what are you talking about?
It was 1pm, right? I'm like seven minutes late. You know, Otto did the thing where he
walked around and smelled every smell and spun around three times, spun around three
times. Nope, not here. Found another place to smell. Spin around, spin around this way.
This is it. This is the place. No, it's not. And then finally took a fucking dump. He's
smelling all the smelly smells. Savory dog. I don't need to go over that again. I don't
need to go over that. Yeah, I'm gonna take care of Otto. Right, Otto? Oh, he needs his
bed in here. Okay. Show us Otto. No, I can't because I don't have any clothes on. No, no
cam at all. I don't have any clothing on. Fucking put them on. No, I'm not going to put on
clothes. You can't make me put clothes on. Okay. I am a voice inside of your head right
now. I'm talking to you. Just a voice. I don't have to have a body attached. Just a voice.
Okay. Anyways, we're gonna continue Pikmin 2. I'm having fun with it. I think it's a fun
game. I have a few things to tell you. One specifically, I hope I'm not jumping the gun
on this. Because we've just been essentially confirmed that it's probably going to happen
on this day. So I, I may or may not be jumping the gun. So keep that in mind. The archaeologist
stream is potentially like 80% confirmed to be on. Mark your calendar here. March 6th
of 2021. It's gonna be fun. Not cat boy. No, it is not cat boy. But I could be in a cat
boy outfit. I will not be in a cat boy outfit on that stream. Let me make sure I get the
record straight there. He's gonna find a cat boy fossil skeleton. Well, thanks for the
fucking free joke because there's a there's a bunch of jokes that are going to happen
on that stream. Thanks for another one. I credit that to you the person that just said
that because that would be kind of funny. Okay, I got to see if I can make that work.
But it should be fun. I again, I don't want to jump the gun because we've been working
diligently on trying to get this to happen. And over the next couple of weeks, especially
going to be doing a lot of stuff on it. So just to let you know, it's probably happening
on March 6th. I don't jump with the gun. I don't want to jump the gun. I know. I'm sorry.
I get on a phrase and I stay on it for like 10 minutes and then I never say that phrase
again. Oh, yeah. Pick me up today. Don't forget to tweet. Oh, fuck. Thank you. Thank you for
reminding me to open Twitter. I open Twitter like once every four days or three days or
something. That's a lie. What a liar. I look at it every day. Yeah, I don't even like use
technology. I don't even like use Twitter. That's a liar. I look at it every day, at
least like in the evening when I'm about to go to bed. Okay, what should we title this
Pikmin? Pikmin 2 continues our epic journey. I'm not going to put the last part, but you
get it. Let's tweet this. Why does Twitter do this shit? I don't like when Twitter does
that. It like it gives a link before I'm done writing. That's annoying. How dare it do
that? All right. Yeah, I'm into Pikmin 2. I can't say that what will happen after today,
but maybe I'll still be into it. Make sure I get that right. Okay. Facecam. I cannot
put a facecam on. You can play Yakuza again. That's the plan. Also, I don't have a date for
this, but the Minecraft server, the actual Germacraft Minecraft server is imminent as
well. It's beautiful. It is absolutely beautiful. It's a gorgeous server. So look for
that too soon. We'll be talking about that in detail over the next probably three or four
weeks. Just take a quick sip out of my bottle. Will you visit it from time to time on stream?
That's the plan. The plan is to visit that once a month, maybe. Maybe or so. Once every
couple months and go see what people are doing. Because in the last FTK stream, it was very
clear that the second half was way more interesting to a lot of you than the first. That's the
plan is to kind of do something like that. Again, I just wanted to bring this up because
I brought it up like maybe a month ago is the last time. Two months ago. Isn't it where we
talked about it last? There is no date for this, but just know that like probably within the
next couple of months, it will be a Germacraft server up and running that you can play on.
It's getting close. It's getting closer. We need a Hue cam. No, you don't need any cam. In fact,
I'm going to make sure like the cameras are on. I hate that knowing that that could just be turned
on. We already saw this. In my OBS preview, I can look over here and see that the cam is ready.
And the camera is physically pointing at me and the lights are on. So it's just like this shit is
on. The lights are just lit up, just ready to capture me naked. I'm not even naked though.
You know what? Here's like what I can tell you. Okay. You know how you go to sleep every night?
That's how I'm dressed. I have pajama pants on and no shirt. That's just what I do. That's how
I live every day. Pajama pants and no shirt on. That's how humans sleep. Just unplug the camera.
No, because then if I unplug it, I crash OBS. All right. So we left off. I had just gotten the
blue Pikmin. I'm very excited. Can you hear it in my voice? Yay. Can't wait to fucking play this
game again. I want to go here. He's bored already. I want to go because there's some water things in
here, right? No, wait. No, I don't. How many water Pikmin do I have? Can I see? He hates
it. I'm just going to go here. Whatever. I think I have enough water Pikmin. I should have like 20,
right? Only because they're perplexing. Boom. That you're creepy. Already said chat. You are wicked
creepy. All right. What do we got here? Citadel of spiders. Now there's a water thing to do here.
Let me just, let me take a look around first. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's get some
good look. All 18 of them more like wicked fucked wicked. Oh dude. I'll do that. That would be wicked
funny. And the electricity do 30 electric. And then we have some big boys, right? How many big
boys do I have? Ooh, that's not good. Only five. What happened? What happened to the big guys?
Stewie. Ooh, what happened to the big ones? Brian, didn't we have 20 purple pick?
We did Stewie, but you killed them all. No, I didn't kill them. You did. Okay. Let's go.
All right. Let's go over here. Everybody fucking hates family guy. You all like family guy.
We talked about this like two months ago. Family guy. You all hate it. Oh, shut up. I hate Stewie,
but you'll watch it on TBS every day. I know all of you watch adult swim and family guys on adult
swim. Like family guy is the teen Titans of adult swim. You watch it every time it's on.
No, you don't. You don't. Bridge. Okay, here we go. Uh, let's kill this guy. Only boomers.
Family guy literally sucks. Yeah, but it doesn't that doesn't matter. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Bring everybody over here. No, just purples. Bring everybody. Fuck it. Whatever.
That guy's gonna jump on me. I know it. All right, let's kill all this stuff.
Boomers. Wait, is Adult Swim Boomer? No? I was under the impression that it wasn't. Kill it.
There we go. No! It kind of is. You know, maybe I am getting a little older because I turned on
Adult Swim recently and I thought all the shows were just fucking terrible. Is that- am I getting
old? Because I used to watch it all the time. They are. Okay, well hopefully this guy doesn't
kill me. I need the- we need to build this bridge. I'm gonna leave Louie over here in case they
attack. Louie, come over here. Just in case this guy attacks, I gotta be ready for it.
Yeah, I mean, Erica- I like Eric Andre. I think he's funny. But I don't- I don't really think
anything else is. Don't attack. Don't attack. Don't attack. Don't attack. Don't attack. Don't
attack. Don't! There's treasure here too. Oh shit. I need that because I want these guys to be-
Yes! All right, I'm ready to drink it. Rick and Morty Rea. Okay, all right, fine. When Rick
and Morty airs every three years, I guess sure you could watch it. Is he just gonna fight me?
Is he gonna- he is. He is. He is. He is. All right, you know what? Just kill him. Go for it.
We can do it. Are we gonna come back? No, come back! I'm fine. Don't crush him. I don't know what it
is. You know, you know you could title this video for the second channel? Because by the way, if
you're not subscribed to the second channel, what are you doing? What are you thinking?
Kill. Kill. Kill. Kill. Kill it. Kill it. I'm so afraid of him squashing. He's gonna do it.
Just wait for him to do it. There it is. Kill. Got it. Nice. Perfect. All right, now build a bridge.
You're scared of a frog? Yes. Because if it squashes them then I only have like 15 of these
guys. 20 of these guys. Aha! All right, good. Yeah, bring this back too. Don't go in the water,
go over the bridge. All right, now what's over here? There's treasure over here, right?
Where my white? I'm gonna dig? Wait, what? Wait, was the whole point of that to- huh. What was
the point of coming over here with the bridge? Can I break this? Why would there be a bridge over here?
I could throw yellow over there? Yeah, I could, but wouldn't they- was it just to throw yellow
over the bridge? They're not gonna get stuck over there, are they? I hope not. They're not gonna get
stuck over here, right? Are they gonna get stuck over here? They'll bring that down? Oh my god,
we gotta go. What are they doing? It's all right. I'll get it. It's off locked? Well, not yet. Hold
on. Don't drown. Um, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay, okay, okay. I'm good. I'm good.
I'm gonna sit here for a sec and then I'm gonna call these guys back. All right, now go over there
and- my mouth peaked. My mouth peaked. Did you hear that shit? That was not my microphone,
that was my mouth. I peaked the inside of my microphone, my mouth. That was fucking crazy.
Are they doing it? All right, break up for a second. All right, and then I'm gonna- so then
I'm gonna- how am I gonna get them back over here? I could throw them. I need blue to take- to pick
that up. Wait, what? Can I go over this way? I don't know, can they? I wanna- I kind of want to
hear that. The noise I've made with my mouth and my saliva or something sounded like a peaked
microphone. Throw them over? I can throw- yeah, but I don't want to touch the electric fence.
I wish I could move the camera like Mario 64. Don't I have more of these? Where are the other
blue ones? They all back at the ship? Uh, they are. Louie, go get them. Go get them, Louie.
Why is he- are they fighting him? Uh, where's the pace out there? All right, come back. Oh,
hold on. Is he playing on the Wii? I am playing on the Wii U, to be exact.
Okay, so now, anybody- any stragglers? I don't think so. I just have to go straight this way.
Wait, can I cross the bridge? Uh, no. Wait, can I? No. I won't fight him, just run. Oh, title of the
video. The title- what's the title of the video? The title of the video is gonna be Overreactor.
Pikmin Overreactor, because that's what I'm doing. I'm just like, whoa! It's like a kid's game.
Why am I, like, trying to make it sound so much more dramatic? I'm not even trying to, though. I
promise. All right, here we go. Who's dying? Oh my god! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Okay, Pikmin Overreactor. I'm sorry. I just did the exact thing that I told you. All right,
everybody relax. Come here. I only want the exact fucking thing I was talking about. All right,
can you guys get this? 15. All right, get it. Nice. The rest of you need to be thrown.
Don't pull it into the- what are you, dumb? Oh my god. All right, well, today's almost over anyways.
Pikmin Overreactor. And the thumbnail can be like a nuclear reactor. And it going off,
and it has my face kind of embedded into it going like, whoa! Oh god, perfect timing on his part.
Kill him! Oh my god. He almost just splash damage killed everybody. I'm missing anybody?
Jeremy, when are you gonna come out with a vegan burger? Um, I'm not. I'm sorry to disappoint you.
All right, hold on. These- these idiots just put five- a five blue coin into a red box.
Did they just mess that up? That's basic colors. They took the blue coin and put it in a red box.
Does that matter? Stop! It does matter, doesn't it? Pikmin carry stuff to their own onion, dummy.
That was a blue coin. Why would they do that? Can they not see blue? Can they not see the color
blue? There's a red majority carrying it. But I thought- what, what red majority cannot put the
blue coin into the blue container? Why not? All right, we'll have to remember that next time.
I'm bringing way less reds next time, by the way. They just overpower everything, and I need-
I need, like, a few more purples. Because they just keep- they pick up everything,
and they just take everything. All right, I'm good. At least I got a treasure.
Politics? Okay, well then Team Fortress 2 is politics. That's red versus blue. It's always
like fucking Halo, okay? Every video game ever that had the two contrasting red and blue colors
versus each other. They just got to get rid of the politics in those games. Base? That's not even-
That's not base? That's just- what? You just ruined all video games.
That was a flame ball back? What? I can't even believe it. 140. I keep putting a drink down in
front of my Wii sensor bar, and it keeps screwing everything up. Some say that you should look to
the past, to places you have been already, in order to make new finds. Of course, extraordinary
people like me always press onward. And scroll down, it's got one like on it. And by the way,
that's like the 30th time they've posted today. Here, go back here. In fact, you can use fire
as a Wii sensor bar. Oh yeah, sorry, you can put candles up, right? Like to own post. Boomer Twitter?
No. Yeah, and then there was one comment. It's just, are you coming over for dinner tomorrow?
It's like grandma. No, less red. I want a blue- I want a blue majority. I don't want a red
majority. Look, go ahead. You can't clip it out. He's just a psycho. Someone's going to just take
that and be like, I knew he was a Democrat. Who even cares? I don't even really fucking care.
I'm playing Pikmin 2. Does anybody actually give a shit about where I might lean politically?
Anybody even care? He's finally lost it. Okay, I don't need to bring a hundred people.
This would be good. Who needs to be- who needs to drink? Of course we do. All right,
where should I go in here? What's this place? A cavern? I got the bridge. Now what's over here?
I made that reference probably a hundred times. Oh, these are new. These are new bugs. Get them.
Didn't get a chance to eat them. Good. Okay, you know where to take that. Okay, now that's open.
Is there anything even in there besides that? It might be a secret in there. Just empty. Okay,
but I can go over here. Oh, another electric fence over there. All right, we're going to go this way.
Uh oh, here's the worst thing, the worst part about this. I want to be Louie down there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I hate this fucking thing. Why do I even put the elevator in this?
Like, I know you want to like, oh, you're way down with the big ones. Who cares?
This is stupid. I hate this. No, I don't. Stop coming with me. Stop coming with me.
Hey, kill it. Come on. Way him down. Kill it. Way it down. Oh my God. Kill it. Thank you. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Hold on. First, let me hit C, then one, then C,
then A, then B. Just send the other guy. Who cares? Why is this guy even in the game?
Stop doing that. I told you to stop. Oh my God. Why did you come over here? I don't. Stop picking
that up. Put it down. Go. We lost a bug. I don't care. I put Louie in this game to sell toys.
That's the only reason why he's here. Drink up. He hates Louie. What's over here? Is Louie in
Pikmin 3 as a playable character? I want to just... Yes or no? No. Okay. That's all I needed to know.
That's the only thing I need to know. Watch out. Drink it. What is... Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
There's not enough here. Speaking of Louie, you go back here and go get everybody. There we go.
He's sold? By the way, why does the whistle work on people? Hold on. I'm gonna zoom out. How come
I can use the whistle on Louie? It works on you too. Yeah, I don't want the whistle to work on me.
If I'm gonna have two separate captains, I don't want the B look to be like, hey, you...
Oh my God, Nintendo. Why does every... Oh, I'm already getting mad at the fucking controls.
A is throw and A is also grab. Use the bridge. Does it not go over here? I thought the bridge
didn't go over here. All right. Everybody fucking get over here. We good? All right. Let's go.
I want yellows. Look at that great traction. Go over here. Take that down. You got killed.
You died. I just fell down here. Oh shit. I can't go back up. Okay. Well, I'm gonna go this way.
Avoid the frog. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't go over there. Louie, Louie, Louie, Louie, Louie.
Oh my God. No, no, no. Come on. You're okay. You're okay. Everyone's fine. All right. Go.
Take it down. I want Louie bait him over here. Thank God he's in the game. Thank God I have this.
Thank God I can do this. Everything I said previously, I take back completely.
There's a cave in there. Oh, okay. Cool. All right. Now come over here and weigh this thing
down so I can go up. It's almost done. Then I'm going to grab everybody and we're going to go in
the hole. I'm just distracting this, uh, Pollywog, whatever it is. Don't kill Louie.
You know what? Like, whatever. Don't jump over there. At least do a face cam. I'm not putting
on a face cam. Gooey, gooey, gooey, Louie. Yeah, that's the booger. That's the one with the boogers.
Okay. Everybody come with me. All right. We need somebody to go back and get the rest.
All right, Louie. I'll get them. No, I'll get them. All of them are. Uh, I have to go around.
Don't go up there and kill everybody, please. Okay. I need you guys to come help me knock this.
Not all of you. Oh, God damn it. Oh, God. No. What the fuck? What the fuck, man?
It's just so sad. It's fun when I can collect coins and stuff. I don't want to micromanage
5,000 fucking people. There's a treasure over here, but I don't care. I want to go in the cave.
All right. Where are we at? Where's the other team? Where's the other guy?
Okay. Over here. Can I get over there from here? Okay. Here we go. Holy shit. All right. I'm going
to get in the cave. Everybody drink? Everybody's drank. Okay. Let's go. It also doesn't help that
the whole ground looks just like I have a thousand upload right now. Strong scent. Okay.
You're both drooling. I wish just once. Is there food down here? 88 out of 88. That's good. Um,
let's do it. Let's go with the whole squad. I thought this was supposed to be a family
friendly stream. Is it? All right. What we got? I only have a few. I hope there's not a lot of
fire here. Uh, what's over there? Shit. Okay. Where's purple? Well, everybody back. Come on.
Back, back, back, back, back, back, back. He died? Why are you even over there? Oh my God.
Well, I got to, I got to turn my body and rest my arm on the stupid thing again.
Remember I'm holding out the remote like a remote control permanently. Oh, I'm already getting
annoyed by this, like upset by this. All right. I'm, I'm, my wrist is resting and I'm in a position
where the sensor bar can see it. Oh, let me see if I can do this. All right. All right. I'm good.
Give me purple. Purple, please. No, just everybody in. Everybody in. Just go overwhelm them with
overwhelming numbers. Go. Good. All right. Bring them back. I'm losing the sensor.
Only three purples are alive. That's okay. I'll get them. I'll get more. Let me move the sensor
bar to like here. Will that help? Maybe. Maybe a little. All right. Where's the treasure? Oh,
okay. It's like a glue stick. He's fucking angry. Wait, are they going to get trapped in here?
Damn. Trying to aim with this fucking thing is so hard. I feel like I'm doing surgery
to try to throw a Pikmin over a goddamn bridge and they climb. Oh, I can get out this way, right?
My grandma had an easy time using the Wii because she played for 15 minutes
once and then it sat on her shelf. She played it for like 10 minutes.
Total. She may be maybe one hour of total game time ever. Oh, that was worth a lot.
Wrong. It was a gamer grandma. What would a gamer grandma be? You're weaker than a grandma.
I don't even know what he's talking about. My forearm doesn't start to burn after 25 minutes
of holding it in the same place. I do just fine with my Wiimote. Thank you, grandson.
Lactic acid doesn't exist. It's a made up term that's a scientist made up. What is this?
Go in there? No, no, no. That's cope. I don't care. I don't care what it is.
Easy, easy, easy, easy. Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run. There's so many
weird mutant creatures in here. All right, get them. Those things are not violent. I gotta
kill this thing. It has to die. But okay, easy. He killed an innocent creature.
Now, is anything of a truly innocent? All right, let's start collecting. Where is this? Hey,
that's our fruit. He got it. He actually got it. He stole it. He stole it from us. Get away.
Don't touch that. Isn't he a Pikmin, does he? I don't think so. Okay, let's keep going. They're
just irritating. They're not really that scary. They kind of just get in the way. Is that a purple
flower? Thank God it is. Get that bottle cap. Hold on. I don't have any idea how much that
hurts to aim up there and keep it right there. I'm so glad this shit died. I'm so happy that
everyone thought we were going to go to... Oh man, motion controls are going to take over.
It's going to be what everybody... No, no, it's not. The PS5 controller is a fucking controller.
It's a regular goddamn controller. I'm so glad we didn't go from here.
What about VR? VR is completely different. VR is like your actual hands.
I'm not pointing an ice cream sandwich at a fucking red sensor. That's what this thing is.
It's a heat sensor. Whatever the hell it is. I don't know. I have no idea what this is.
It's a camera. It's a heat camera. Thermal camera. Whatever the hell it is.
Infrared. Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what I meant. Get this. I'm very angry today.
I'm very upset today for some reason. Why am I so angry? I'm so annoyed. I don't know why. Why?
There's no reason for me to be annoyed. Fuck this controller. Fuck this system. Fuck this whole
console. I'm just kidding. Geez. Is he stuck? Somebody said,
Frankie Wanky. I have nothing to be upset about. Shit's going real well. I don't know. Maybe it's
the whistle that's making me mad. Shut up, whistle. Isn't that making you mad? Oh, I want to go to
the flower. Who do I want to turn? I don't have any reds left, do I? Do I have any red? I might
have exactly five reds. Three. I could do a couple of blues or yellow. I'll do with yellow. Stop.
Stop. What? What? What? Laugh out loud. What? Keep the yellows? Do I do it with white then? I know.
White's pretty rare. Oh, is it red? I have red. I wish I could. I want to turn the face cam on
right now so you can see what I'm doing right now. I have both hands on the fucking Wiimote and I'm
leaning my neck down stuffed into my body like perched trying desperately hold it right here.
I don't have clothes on so I can't do that. All right, next level. Next layer. Where you going?
Get over here. You're playing here. Would I lose anybody back here? Where's the exit?
Who shows up naked? I don't have to have any clothes on. If I don't say anything,
you guys wouldn't even know. I'm just a voice in your ear. If I didn't tell you I didn't have
clothes on, some of you could have thought I was in a suit for all you knew. We got electricity.
Ooh, what do I do about that? I feel like, I don't know, is blue going to be in short supply?
How many blues am I going to have over the course of the game? You don't really need blue? Okay,
thanks for the tip. Appreciate it, guys. A is throw. A is grab. I feel like I'm...
Ooh, nectar. All right, break it. Everybody drink? Yes. Okay.
Now, let's go... All right, that's a lightning bug. Stay away. Wait, don't... I'm not risking
this. Everybody come over here. I'm going to go around with yellow. I got a white here. I don't
want that white. There we go. All right. Let's make sure this is safe first before we go any further.
How do I bet on this with draft kings? You can't. Kill him. Kill him. He's upside down.
Break his bones. Get away from me. Bugs don't have bones. Wrong. Their entire body is a bone.
Exoskeletons. Kill it. All right. We're clearing. I feel like I'm playing an MMO.
We're just clearing trash so then we can actually do the thing we want to do.
Okay. Looks good. Bingo. I didn't say wow. I said AMMO.
AMMO. AMMO. Come on. Get him. Flip him over quickly, please. AMMO. I didn't say MMO. I said
Alameo. I thought what you said was very funny. Whatever. He can have it. I don't want it. All
right. That's good. It's safe now. Is it safe? It's safe. There's a big tambourine over here.
Oh, it's not safe yet. This would have killed me later. What the fuck is that?
Oh, my God. Run. No. Come back. I got to run away. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
I got to come back with Purple. Oh, my God. He's flying. He sees everybody.
Okay. We're good. We're good. We're good. I got to throw Purples at him to take him down.
I'm going to wait until he does the blow. All right. Come with me. Don't get caught in that.
Oh, my God. Everybody come back. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. We're fine.
Run, Purple. What are you doing standing there like an idiot?
Kill him. Are those spikes on his back? Am I throwing them into spikes?
Purple. No. What are you doing? He didn't die, right? Oh, thank God. Okay. We're good.
Purple. No. I don't even care if he takes them. All right. Here we go. Now I get my double treasure.
This really is an overreaction stream. I know. I don't know what I'm doing that for.
It's not a tambourine. It's not a treasure. Is your sensor bar set to a button? No,
it's set to below TV. Please take a break. It's distressing to see you. Hold on.
See this is please take a break. It's distressing to see you play when you aren't in a good mindset.
And not only does your gameplay suffer, but we do please take a break. I just started like an
hour ago. I would have to be next level baby. Or if I needed to take a break within like 20 minutes
of playing the game. Okay. At that point, it's like, it's not take a break. It's don't play the
game anymore because you don't like it. Is it necessarily take a break? Starting up a game
in 10 minutes being like, this is stupid. You got to take a break, man. Come back later. Yeah. I
think I'll take a break. It's still treasure. Where? Pick it up. Where is it? Pick it up.
Where is it? It's in the hole. Can we get in there? Can I like knock into it? Hey, wait, it's this guy.
You have something in there? Okay. And what was in his hole? What's wrong with you? I don't know.
Somebody said to kill them so I can get in. There's something in this hole. It's the wrong
one. Can I knock it? Did he actually steal a treasure and I can't get in there? To kill them
all. Um, to kill all the bugs. Holy shit. Run away. They come out for food. Um, so I have to kill a
bug over here and leave the dead body. Build the other one. Just kill the other bug. Okay. I don't
like killing these guys. They're like kind of cute and funny. I didn't like doing that. I wasn't a
fan of that. I don't want to kill them. They were not even hostile. Baste. Baste. Baste. Baste. Hello,
my name is German985 and what you just did there was totally baste. All right, we got it all?
Podcaster voice? No, it's not a podcaster voice. This is a podcaster voice.
I'll show you what a podcaster voice is. I'm going to fuck up all my settings.
So let me just hold on. I actually will mess this up and I won't be able to fix it ever again.
Hold on. Ready? Oh shit. What did I do? Hold on. I want to make sure I don't screw this up.
Okay. Here's your podcaster voice. I think I have to take a screenshot of this
because I'll fuck. All right. Hold on. Here's your podcaster voice. So today we're going to be
checking out, uh, you know, I saw this new movie. I saw infinity war and I was seriously not a fan
of it. I'm not, I'm not sure what they would think of with Thanos. I don't like him as a villain.
I was more inclined to be a happier with, um, you know, Dr. Dreadful, candy cartoon guy from
the eighties, nineties. He would have been so much more fun. Okay. Are we good? I think I'm,
am I back to normal? I hope, I hope I'm back to normal. More compressor. Hold on. I need to print
screen. I fucked it all up. Remember when I had a compressor like that on and everybody freaked out.
Everybody was so pissed off. They were like, Mike sucks. Fix your mic. What the fuck? This
sounds terrible. I'm like, I was so mad now that this is correct. This is the way it was.
Yeah, we're good. It wasn't that bad. I know it wasn't that bad, but if there's even a slight
change in audio, people think that I'm streaming from inside of a bathtub. All right. Is this also
electricity? No, there's a big bunker burger over here. Is that electric? Uh, all right. I gotta get
guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys. No, he ate one. Hurry, hurry. Oh, he's eating everybody.
Shit. He got me into a corner. Uh, has Pikmin die? That's part of the game. Hundreds of Pikmin
are going to die over the course of a playthrough of this game. Like they're just dead. They're
going to die. Hundreds of them. Ooh, ice cream. Squish him. I can't go over there.
All right. This is probably going to be a buried treasure. Anything else that I've,
because I don't want to throw them over there and have all of a sudden like a
bunker burger jump over here and try to kill me. Okay. There's a coffee mug. It looks to be safe.
I think. All right. Just making sure there's nothing else that's going to kill me. All right.
Let's go. Uh, yellow going up there. If I said when I was a kid, I didn't finish the first
level in Pikmin because I didn't want any of them to die. That's so, that's so cute. That's like
absolutely adorable. What you just said. That's so cute. Like my God, you just like made my heart
turn to like, you just melted it. That's so cute. That's the cutest thing I've ever heard.
Where are they going? Why are they running over here? Remember he was 30 when he played.
So he's not, they're not going to try it. Is he going to try to steal it?
Kill him. Don't let him get it. So I have a question about the GameCube controls. How do you
throw Pikmin with the GameCube controller? It's just the C stick. All right. Let's pick up some
stuff. Go up here. Don't get stuck, man. You're going to get stuck. Come on. Is that it for the
treasure? That is. All right. Cool. Isn't great, but better than motion controls when you get used
to it. The motion controls are fine. I mean, I'm, I know I was like talking a bunch of shit and I
was, you know, making a bunch of jokes. Uh, motion controls are fine. It's, um, to be completely
honest with you, it's just like having to hold the thing out, like a remote control for a long
period. You know what they didn't make, which they should have made? They should have made a Wii arm
brace or as a device that you attach to the Wii mode and to your wrist and then anchored it to
something. Like a cushion, like an, well, Wii arm anchor cushion. Where are the other two? Uh,
there's one up here. There's the other guy back there. Bionic boomer. No, look, it doesn't, I,
the strongest man in the world could sit here with a Wiimote holding it up and his forearm would
start to get tired and it wouldn't matter. You guys would still make fun of that guy.
Where's this other one? Didn't I get him? There we go. Arty, the strongest man in the world. Yeah.
Arty, strongest man in the world. That's the best character that was on that show.
That might be the best character from any Nickelodeon show. I remember when Arty, uh,
at, for an entire episode was trying to lift up like Pete and Pete's house and he did it.
He lifted it like a 10th of an inch or something, right? Yeah. The entire episode he's sitting there
like, I will do it. I will lift up your house. And he's sitting there holding like the side of
the vinyl siding in their house. Like the whole episode. Kill. Back up. Follow me. Follow me.
Follow me. Follow me. All right. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Oh, he's going to kill them.
That's close. Take his body. All right. We got these guys to deal with too. I need one good shot.
My arm. I got it. I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. Throw the purples. That's
what I'm doing. Oh man. What I wouldn't give for a C-stick right now. You need to pay attention.
Don't just look at the chat. Excuse me. Don't. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. All right. We're good. Let's do
treasure hunting. Should I get Thai or pizza? I get Thai. Get Thai food. Get Thai pizza. You could
do that. A good pad Thai is, it's, you can't be beat. Pizza's pizza. Yeah. Pizza's pizza. You can
have pizza, but like pizza's pizza. I want some of you guys to get over here. In fact, all of you
get over there because I want whoever has not drank to drink. Oh, I could have just whatever.
All right. What's next? Treasure got. Treasure get. All you eat is heal. I don't. No, I don't.
Oh, fuck. This level is kind of hard. Oh, that's a good thing to do. He's always aiming over here.
I'm going to do that. Stop shooting over here. Oh, I fucking. Okay. I got to split up. I hope
it doesn't aim over here. I need just, just a couple of purples. Come with me. This purple's
very slow. Oh shit. Come on. Back, back, back, back, back, back, back. Come on. Hurry, hurry.
Oh my God. There's so many of these guys. Oh shit. Are we good? Come on. Keep going. Yes. Good job.
You did it. They will shoot only at me. Oh, okay. Now we have to deal with these guys.
I think I'm safe if I just stay right here. Yeah. I'm safe if I stay here.
That motherfucker just rolled it over here. I back up, back up, back up, back up, back up.
Everybody back up. Oh my God. Please. Wait. Dude, I didn't think it was going to roll that far.
I thought it was an explosion. Oh my God. I have to reset the level. I thought it was,
I didn't think it kept rolling that far. It rolled all the way down here. I lined him up.
I was trying to get away. The yellow's away. I thought it was, of course it hits this fucking edge.
Oh God damn it, man. What a pain in the ass. I could have just ran. He just killed another one.
I have to reset. I'm resetting. I'm not. No, that was in half of every Pikmin I own. Wait,
what do you mean? What do you mean? No, no, no, no, no, no. I mean reset the whole console.
That's not reset. Just turn the console off. Wait, what are you talking about? Just turn it off.
Just turn the console, just reset, turn off the console. So you're telling me if I turn off the
console right now, I'll come back and be okay. Consequences. No, not when I lose half of every
Pikmin I own. Okay. I'm turning off the game console. Here we go. I feel like this is bait.
This is bait. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't. It's bait. Okay. Shit. Move out of the way.
He just crushed somebody. This fucking wee man. I have a drink in the way. Oh my god. I hate this
fucking console. It's not bait. It's not bait. Actually not bait. Okay. I'm doing it. I did it.
I just turned it off. I turned the console off. I hope, I bet, I better not be bait. I'd be really
mad if it is. Look at Samara for a sec. You want to know something funny about the Wii U? The Wii U,
I think, has a slower startup time to get from go to game, like go into game, turn on console,
then like an old hard drive from like 1998 to turn on Windows fucking 95 did. Like it's a longer
boot up time. It's a longer time to get into a game. Enter the password for your Nintendo network
ID. Oh my fucking god. Why do they even still have a network ID for Nintendo Wii U? I'm probably one
of eight people that are on the fucking network right now. All right. I'm coming back. TV only,
please. Okay. Here we go. Crying and screaming and farting. Beats to study.
Wii U. Put your strap on. Where's the brace? I want like a foam brace that I can stuck on here.
Like a, what's the thing that you, like a sniper rifle. If you're proning with a sniper rifle
and you put out that thing on the front, what's that thing called?
I want one of those for the Wii. A bipod. That's right. Exactly. That's what I want for the Wii.
Holy shit, it worked. It was, I thought it was bait the whole time too. Holy shit. Nice.
I honestly thought it was bait. Let me get comfortable again. There we go. All right.
I did blue. Does anybody else have this problem too? This might just be a me problem,
but like holding up the Wiimote and pressing A with my thumb like is after a while starts
to become like hard to do and like tiring. Did everybody else have that problem too?
I feel like the A button should have been more to the left or something. I don't know.
Let me just find every way I can complain about like a beloved console that everybody loved.
Except for me, apparently. Watch it. All right. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Move, move, move.
These guys suck. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Did we lose one? Okay. I lost one.
Stop throwing them over there. Why is he throwing them that way? That's so unfair.
Use my power up. Well, I have to fight like three of these guys. Kill that. Kill this guy. Shoot him.
Shoot this guy. Shoot this Bunger Burger guy. Shoot this. He's going to eat somebody.
Thank you. My God. Overwhelm him. Overwhelm him. He won't get to fire another shot.
Holy fuck. That was horrible. This place sucks. Reset. You lost four or three. No. Hold A. Press
B. Aim with remote control. High heat sensor bar. Oh, you motherfucker. This console. Oh, my God.
Let me shake my hand a little. They never intended anyone to play this console for more than fucking
20 minutes. They really didn't. I know they didn't. They even have a thing telling you to stand up and
take breaks every fucking 10 minutes. Like, what the hell? Remember how many times that they showed
you that screen? They were so hell bent on making sure you didn't play for more than 20 minutes in a
row. Remember, get up and stretch and don't knock over the fucking vase that's next to you. That's
right next to your couch for some reason. All right. I split this up. Scratch that. Drink that.
And then VR happened. Yeah, that's true. Watch out. There's a vase next to your dining table or
whatever or next to your couch actually turned into people putting holes in their drywall by
punching with VR. Now, a VR Pikmin that I can get into. I was going to say that killed me. I was
fucking turned off the stream. Shit. Hold on. How am I supposed to do this? All right. Everybody
back up. I'm going in here with like, okay, here's the plan. I'm going in here with just
purples and we'll go. I'm going to split this up small. Is there even treasure over here?
There is. Okay. This is this. Wait, I have an idea. Move. I went over him. Oh my fucking God.
What? This treasure. If I, I have an idea. If I stand in the way, just if I put the captains
in the way and make them get hit by the balls, they can get the treasure, right? I'll just die.
Watch out. Watch out. What's he shooting? Back up. Turn him this way. What are you shooting at? Oh,
fuck. Oh, fuck. He's almost dead. Just relax. What are you shooting? That way? All right. Kill him.
Good. Thank God. All right. There's two more. You don't have to recall them when it
tosses them. They run back towards you and the bullets just roll over them off the ramp.
I'm scared. That's scaring me shitless though. I don't know if I can handle that.
All right. There's nothing there. There's one here though. This guy's going to die over here.
Oh, no. I left one. I left one accidentally. Kill that guy. Yes. Shoot him. Shoot this guy.
You little asshole. Come here. Don't carry him. Run. What are you doing? What are you doing?
Why would you try to pick him up? Run away. All right. Collect. Collect the bounty.
Web, web dev here. What? What is web dev? What a, we you dev here. We, we, we, we you dev here.
Look, I understand my consoles and their motion controls did not revolutionize the gaming industry
the way we intended them to. But to sit here and watch you shamelessly bash my life's work,
who the fuck do you think you are? You know how many years I slaved away Nintendo to bring you
gaming experiences like this only if you stabbed me in the back by calling them garbage. You should
be ashamed. I never said that. I never said that. When did I, when did I say this was garbage? I
didn't say that. I said I want a bipod. And if, if you had a bipod that was for sale, I would have
had much better experience. Yes, I wanted it. I want a tactical Wii mode so I can just plant,
plant it on my arm, the chair of my arm, the arm of my chair and just lock it in there and rest
and have a little bit of, have like a gyro there so I can move the wrist around.
I did not say garbage. I did not. I did not say that. I know I didn't. I did not say garbage.
Let me tell you exactly what I said. I said in very direct quotes, fuck this console.
I think that's what it was. I think it was something like that, right? Now that I didn't
say this console was garbage. I just said, fuck this console and fuck this controller, right?
But that doesn't mean I don't like the game. I'm not having fun with the system.
That's worse. No, it's not. That quote was very, oh, fuck. Somebody said,
in direct quotes, I think. I know. Whatever. No, the Wii U. Alright, I can tell you right now.
I don't give a shit about the Wii U. The Wii U was fantastic. It was very good back in like 2007.
The Wii U is what they wanted the Switch so badly to be, but I guess they weren't ready to make it
yet. They took the Wii U idea and just how truly awful it was, and they made it the system they
actually wanted to make with the Switch, and it's way better. So look, I have to give Nintendo some
credit here. With the Wii U being as messy and as fucked up and weird, and I hate to say the word
bad as it was, if we didn't get the Wii U, we may not have gotten the Switch. And think of how good
the Switch is. Think about awesome. Think about how much you use the Switch. Think about awesome
that console really is. We wouldn't have gotten there without the stepping stone that was the Wii
U. Never bought a Switch. I think it's great. Switch is awesome. It's everything I've ever wanted.
Remember when the PSP came out and it was, oh my God, you're going to get PlayStation quality
graphics on the go. It was like, all right. It's okay. It was cool. I needed to go to the bathroom
console. I used to bring my entire computer in to the bathroom, and I get the Switch now. The Switch
is a full actual 3D graphics of the same caliber. And he's telling me I can die. That's my bathroom.
I can go to the bathroom with it. Best thing I've ever bought in my life. What's this ham
doing over here? Why is it like a piece of pork belly? This guy's freaking me out. What's he doing?
What are you doing? What are you doing? Get away from everybody. What are you doing? What's he
doing over here? This guy, he's freaking me out. I don't like this floor. Somebody died? This is a
very dangerous floor. Don't let him steal that. Whatever. There's a lot going on on this floor.
He's stealing a plate. Give me that. That's not for you. That's not for you. Get that from him.
That's not for you. That's not yours. That's not yours. Give it back. Don't let him take that.
Put that down. Put it down. Put that shit down. Get over here. I want that plate.
Oh, it's a piece of bologna. Meat of champions. It is. That killed him? Oh, he like touched the
beam. It fucking insta-killed him. Were you just going to take your friend? All right, you have to
die. I'm not going to deal with that this whole room. No way. It would be nice if I could fucking
land anybody on you. And the big one is freaking me out though. Oh my god. Damn it, man. I have
bracing every bone in my body to do this right now. Holding it right here, I'm using every bone in
my body. I was just holding it into my chest to make sure it wasn't moving that much. All right,
everybody get over here. Bro, what the fuck? What? Okay. Where's my other dudes? We're missing
somebody. Okay, here we go. All right, there's an egg over here. Let's get that egg. Get that over
here quickly before this guy takes it. I kind of like this level. It's like a breakfast level.
Where you going? Where they going? Down? Not where you going? And down this way. Thank you.
That looks like a pretty good egg. All right, in the chat, I want to know
over easy, over medium, or over hard. If you say anything besides over medium,
you are banned from this channel. Well, looks like we're dropping a lot of people today.
I love over over medium is perfect. Because it gives you the sort of gel,
almost gelatin like substance of the kill this guy. He's gonna steal something event. No,
I've just just get rid of the good I was doing before. Need yellow. They're not hostile. So
it's fine. Kill always over medium other 10 times actually made right. Actually over medium
is the hardest one to do. Because that's why it's the best one. Over medium is the most difficult
egg to cook. People don't get it right. What about boiled eggs? Yep. I love hard boiled eggs. But
here's the thing about hard boiled for me. I don't want soft boiled egg. I want a over medium egg,
but I don't want a soft boiled egg. And you probably be confused saying, Jeremy, isn't a
soft boiled egg exactly what you want? That is exactly an over medium style. And I'll say yes,
it is. But when it's a hard boiled egg, I want it to be solid. I don't want it to be drippy or
gooey. I want it to be solid. Read chat. What? He's stealing the treasure. Who is? I'm trying to
get rid of the electricity. I'll get it back. Somebody die. I can still get that treasure. I
just have to kill him. Yeah, but over medium is my favorite type of like that style cooked on a
skillet. Hard boiled I like it to be fully cooked all the way. I really am not a big fan of that.
So we can go scrambled eggs here. I don't I'm sorry. I don't like the scrambled egg. That's
you put it in the pan for five seconds and you stir it around and then it's done.
No, no, no, no, no. That's like porridge. It's sludge. I like my scrambled eggs to be
solid. I don't like the sludge porridge shit. I don't I really don't.
Okay, let's kill this guy. It's got to be purple. I get it. I don't think he can even
can even hurt anybody can even attack. I don't this is gonna take a while. He's not like the
caterpillar for Mario, right? Like, eventually, he's not going to freak out. So sprinting around
and killing everybody. Or if I get him down to red health and he starts to sprint around,
I'm gonna freak out. All right, split up any purple. Thank you. Where's he going?
He's walking like Squidward. What's that mean? Walking like Squidward. Dead. And he dropped a
can of milk and a donut. Oh shit, he had a lot of stuff. Processing how bizarre an item appears to
have fallen out of the freakish creature. Must have been a greedy beast to swallow something like this.
Probably. We have a lot of yeah, this is why I didn't want to stay.
Yeah, I'm good. Oh, right. Shit. We got warrior where smooth moves on the Wii.
It's like one of the best consoles. Never mind. I'm sorry. I put my drink down in front of the Wii
sense of our fuck this stupid shitty console. The donut. Get a candle. No, I will burn my whole
I'll burn my house of light. I'll burn my entire room down. I don't like candles. I love candles.
But I I'm always afraid of having a candle in multiple rooms.
Maybe some of you can level with me here. Candles great. But I know people that put candles in a
bunch of rooms. You know, there's a candle in the bedroom. There's a candle in the living room.
There's a candle lit in the kitchen. I want to be able to have an eyesight of that candle
from anywhere that I'm going to be standing for the next hour. I don't want to know candle in
a room I'm not going to be using. Absolutely not. If I cannot see that candle, it better be out.
It is far more advanced than the material I was researching. How frustrating.
Space suit made from this wonder ally could insulate the wearer from electric shocks. Oh,
cool. I could walk through electricity. The hard word to say when you're just not prepared for it.
This new material has allowed me to complete my anti-electrifier. It's my own invention with
only the smallest iota of outside inspiration. Do you burn incense with your healing bracelets?
Actually, I don't. I'm a bit I like essential oils, though, not because I think they give me
powers, but I just like the way tea tree oil smells. I just like the way tea tree smells.
I like the way eucalyptus smells. It doesn't give me powers. I just like the way it smells.
Cultist. No, I'm well aware that it doesn't do anything for me. Well, that's not true.
Tea tree is actually really good for your hair. I mean, that's a good thing. It's good for your
hair. It can relax you a little bit. It doesn't do anything. It doesn't give you powers. I mean,
that's how it starts. Okay, well, that's how it starts. Like 15 years ago, I should have gone
down like the rabbit hole. I didn't. I thought tea tree smelled good and was cool when I was like
20. I didn't progress. Sweet dreamer. Did everybody drink? You look like a greasy today.
Probably. That was pretty cool. I like the breakfast place. I didn't like the boulder bugs.
That's $1,300. You're an essential oils pyramid scheme. No, I bought a bottle of tea tree oil.
I want to say maybe seven or eight years ago that I still have it. It's still fine.
I smell it sometimes. Day's almost over. We're good. Nobody's left out. Pretty good. That's
a pretty good day. That's a pretty good day. $1,200. I signed up for this program where I get a bottle
of tea tree. I get 10 essential oil bottles delivered to my door every month. What you guys
don't understand is you could do this too. You could get it delivered to your door every month
and then you could bring 10 people in to deliver them to 10 people's houses and then those 10
people could have 10 other people and 100 people would be underneath you. Years ago
me and Burger Boy would spend a lot of time together. We were going to try to get him to
he and he wanted to do it too. We weren't trying to convince him or anything. We wanted to get him
to do one of those MLM things and see how much money he could make going around trying to sell
people's stuff. We're like, it would be funny if you just tried and he's like,
actually, yeah, maybe that would be funny. Burger Boy shows up and is like, let me ask you a question.
How's your skin care? Burger Boy ends up making $50,000 a month doing it. Wicked funny. No. A wicked
funny pyramid scheme. He didn't do it. We just like joked about it. Omar, you're my hero. You've
erased half of our debt. Still, things have become a bit dangerous. So I'm going into hiding. Focus
on work and don't slack off. What the hell are you doing? What is this? Why is the chat all hacked?
Why is the chat hacked? How are you doing that? Don't do that. Why is it hacked? Oh, what the
fuck is going on here? I don't even know what's going on over there. But no, we were just talking
about Burger Boy. Why don't you join that thing? And if you're like, I'm not fucking doing that
stupid fucking scam. Take the red pill, Jerma. I don't even know what the hell is going on.
Is this some new program? Put it in sub only. Put it in sub only quick. Don't do it. Take the blue
pill and have a nice steak. I'm going back here. Look at all this other stuff I didn't do here.
I have a good steak. He doesn't know what Unicode is. I don't know. I don't know.
Okay, what do we got? We got... Let me take a quick look. What is here? We did this. Okay,
I want more blue. What about over here? Up this way? Will we investigate what's this way?
If there's an electric fence over here, then... Fuck yeah.
Hmm. What's down there? Secret? Secret treasure? All right. There's nothing over here, Louis. I
don't care. You can stay there for the rest of the level. I don't care. There's nothing over there.
Go behind. Ooh, okay. This is nectar. Well, we actually kind of need it. Not yet, though.
So what's the thing I haven't done here? Perfect Jupiter is, yeah, pretty good.
What's up here? Don't fight this guy. Don't even need to. All right. Is it... There's a cave? I
think I've already... Did I complete this cave? I completed this cave. So we gotta go... All right.
I know where to go. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Let's bring
25 blues. Let's pick... Let's spend a day collecting some Pikmin. What do you say?
It's a lot of Jupiters right now. Hey, don't you know now's your op... This is the opportunity.
Now's the opportunity, guys, to put out, like, German TV, an emote that you'll never see.
This is the opportunity to put out as many German TVs as you can put out. Well, hold on. Don't just
start doing that. And we'll do some red. Let's see. 15 red and purple. We got now some white
and then the rest will do blue. No, yellow. 30 yellow. And that leaves us with... Oh, get some
red, too. Why not? First of all, I need blue. Blue, go get this. We need more of you. Put it
in your thing. I need blue. There's a couple more flowers over here. I'm just doing some
Pikmin collection. I'm doing some Pikmin utility here. OK, grab that. That's blue.
Grab this one, too. Blue. Thank you. We're on 10-year slow mode. Go ahead and get it.
Go on. Bring it to blue. Did I take a break yet? No, I haven't. We'll probably take a first break
here in a little bit. After this level, I will. You literally won't. Why do you think I'm not
going to take a break? No break. No, don't bring that over to yellow. What are you dumb?
$25,000 slow mode. OK, now we can take the whole crew. I now have 100.
Somebody get that. Whatever. Just get one more. Just put it in blue. 99 out of 100. Where's the
last 100? Where's the last guy? Wait. Nectar. Where is it? This way, right? Yeah. Stop what?
The stream fucking sucks. Get out of here. Give me a break. Get out of here.
Come on, dude. Like, what the fuck? All right, let's go. Get him out of here.
This is worst stream 2021. Get out of here. Truly get out of here. That's bullshit. No, it's not.
OK. Water. Yes. Catboy will be worst stream 2021? No, it will not. What are you smoking?
You have no idea what I'm going to do for the catboy stream. And I'm sorry for all some of you
might be new here, but if you think I'm just going to put on cat ears and like eye makeup,
you are out of your fucking mind. You think that's what I'm going to do for that stream?
I would just hold on a minute. I was going to put cat ears on, put on like a little bit of
eyeliner. You must not have been here for very long. What we do here, get a competing dog boy.
That's fucking funny. I'll tell you, I'll be very, very honest. That's going to be a very
elaborate stream. It's not just going to be me with cat ears. And speaking of big streams,
maybe we'll see you on March 6th for the archaeology stream. Maybe you learn a few things.
OK, so now I've got to put the bridge out or bridge up. Can I do this with just blue? Good
kill. Good kill. Kill. Do March 5th. It's my birthday. No, I'm sorry. You just pretend like
it's your birthday on the 6th. All right. There's a scary guy over here. Is he fire? He's not. It's
one of these. Oh my. It's targeting me. It's homing missile. Why is it still spinning? What the fuck is
this doing? Get out of here. Get out of here. Come on. Hurry run past it. I'm not trying to fight.
I'm just trying to put the bridge. I don't want to get in a fight. Leave me alone.
Yeah, I might have to fight this guy. All right. Kill him. We might lose one. It's all right. OK,
we're good. Get away from me. Don't even think about coming over here. Come on, guys. Get it.
Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat.
Oh, that almost. I almost lost it at the end. All right. We've got to come kill these guys. I need
fire. Good job. All right. We are now ready to bring everybody here. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat.
OK, fire. What happened to Louie? Kill. You're immune to fire. Kill it. OK, now we need purple.
The rest can come over here, actually. One hundred. Nobody died. Good. This is where it gets a little
intense. And holy shit, I could have been really bad. Why is it curving? Why are they curving? Why
are they curving? Why is it curving? They're homing. That's unbelievable. I'm trying to get
out of the way. What? When does it hit? Just run. I don't even care. What a stupid enemy.
Is it fire? Oh my God. Get him down. What? It's already midnight? Can I get up there? How do I
get up here? Oh, bridge. Stop bringing that back. All right. I got 88. Let's go. Another cave
discovered. Venturing to the farthest reaches has proven rewarding. You may be tired of walking,
but just one last leap remains now to get that treasure. I don't have enough. I don't have any
white. Do I even have any white? All right. We're coming back here and getting that crown tomorrow.
How many white do I have? I'm going to try it. How many white do I have? I only have three
white Pikmin. I think we're safe for non-subs to come back. Bring them back. Let's see if they'll
behave. All right. Where are we? There's purple. Snow. Who do I want to replace for purple?
Everybody line up. What have we got? I have a lot of blue. I think I'm going to do blue.
This might be a mistake. This cave's scary. This cave sucks. This cave's hard. Well,
let's see if I get wiped. Here comes a difficulty chat. Difficulty spike. Damn it. Really? Well,
all right. We're just going in. What is that thing? Kill it. Crush it. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Run, run, run, run, run, run. I didn't know what that was. I didn't know what
that was. I didn't know what that was. I thought it was a snowball. All right. Whatever.
I didn't know what that thing was. I thought it was a snowball.
They got me. They baited me. This game is so bad. I can't believe anyone would even
play this for more than a minute. This is a beloved Nintendo franchise. This is the worst
game I've ever played. This is worse than Big Rigs. I'm sorry. That's going to be taken out
of context like everything I fucking say. Watch out. Don't get caught in the cast.
That's just Attack on Titan again. I think that's funny, but I have to stop doing that.
There's going to be a huge Pikmin fan that's going to see that and be like,
why did he hate it so much? Why is he such a dick? I don't understand. Why would he be like that?
OK, I'm back. You ate one. You fucking ate one. Crush him. Overwhelm him. All right. He lost his.
These corridors are so tight. It's the corridors are so small. All right. This buried treasure
here. I hope I have a white Pikmin to dig this. I do. I'll get it. You know,
I wish if when I pressed C to go to Louie, I didn't. I wasn't still attached to everybody.
It's kind of annoying. I just want to be Louie. I don't want to be Louie and bring the whole crew.
All right. Get that diamond. Nice. The third game fixes that. This boss killed my entire
squad. Good luck. Great. That doesn't sound good. Only 70 for a Ruby. There's a noob in the chat.
Oh, please. Noob. This game's not easy. This game's not easy. Don't let anybody tell you that.
It is. It's pretty easy. Is it? This game was made for children. This game was made for children
like 15 years ago. It's different. They made children's games hard 15, 20 years ago.
So if Pikmin were to be made now, there would be a Pikmin generator that I would just go to
the pause menu and just spawn another red Pikmin as many as I wanted. You think Nintendo would not
put that in nowadays? If you lose the same Mario level three or four times, it will beat the game
for you. You don't think there'll be a Pikmin generator in the menu in 2020, 2021? Further into
the depths. Easy. Our game is so easy. I didn't say that. I still have trouble. I would say,
look, I've been Louie, dude, plenty of times in the new games. You want to know why I've never
played Super Mario 3D World, really, or Super Mario New Mario Brothers Wii, whatever? A lot
of people have said, oh, you should play that. Because I know for a fact that I'm going to get
Luigi'd a bunch of times and it's going to be Omega Lels in the chat. Louie-jied. Bad streamer.
Louie-jied again. I know it's going to happen. So that's why I'm just like, I don't want to play
that. I'm scared to play it. I'm scared to get Louie-jied more than the quota that I'm allowed
of, like three. Okay. This level sucks. Okay. What do I do about this? I'm going to wake this
guy up. Can I get them to shoot each other? I'm going to try this. I'm going to do a tactic here.
Everybody stay back here with me and Louie. Don't come in here. No, he's going to shoot
it right down this lane and kill everybody. Oh, my God. He actually did it. No, he didn't. All
right. Just go, go, go, go, go. Run, run. Why are you still with me? I just, I didn't see. Get out
of here. Shoot him. Good. Do it again. Good. It worked. Now shoot each other. Oh, damn it. All
right. Come on. Get him. Get him. Yes. Yes. Wrap it back around. All right. Now kill him. Good.
Now come this way. Let him shoot. Damn it. I got to spin him around. Punch with A. Yeah,
I do like no damage. I need to move this out of the way. Punch him to death. I guess like.
I'm fine. He's going to. Okay. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I ain't going to have this happen.
Fuck. This is a horrible position to be in. All right. Here we go. I'm going to let him
walk away. There we go. Thank you. Now I'll be able to get him. Turn this way. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Don't let him eat you. Yes. What is that? Is that from something? All right. It's
now safe. It's Captain Falcon. Yeah. Yes. It is. Okay. That's just curious. All right. Get the
spoils of war. Come on. Soundboard. F-Zero GX on stream. I don't understand F-Zero. I just don't.
Everybody talks so highly of F-Zero. F-Zero. Oh my God. F-Zero. Captain Falcon is so cool.
Nobody actually cares about that game. Like why don't they make one? Why does anybody? I feel
like people talk so highly of like Captain Falcon and F-Zero, but I don't think anybody plays it.
And they like won't make a new game or anything. It's not even nostalgia. It's like a new
generation of like kids think he's cool. He is cool. He's really cool. Why don't they just
make another one? Oh, it doesn't need to be a racing game. Make like a Captain Falcon adventure
game where you walk around and punch people and stuff. Like people would eat that up like crazy.
Do I not have enough to get this? Shit. Is it yellow back here? I think there's enough yellow.
Yeah. Oh, there's a ramp here. I literally was blending in with the ground. I couldn't see it.
It's a present too. The football. Oh, the Super Bowl is on. Oh. Oh, I don't know. A Super Bowl.
Welcome to the Super Bowl. It's me, John Madden.
It's like I'm there. Is that all the treasure? Yeah. All right. Who is it going to win? Hey,
no, I won't be. I definitely won't be alive when the Super Bowl is over. I was going to
do a prediction for it, but I'm not going to be live when the Super Bowl is ending.
So it'll be wasted points. Okay. Let's assess what's going on here. There is a white flower.
Good thing there's a white flower. I need to replace. Hmm. I don't know. It seems yellow
probably, right? I don't know. I have an equal amount of pretty much everybody. Don't get it yet.
Do it at the end. Okay. Well, we have fire. Let's get rid of the fire. I'm going to say,
all right, we've got multiple things to deal with here. Louis, Louis, you take fire and you,
you know what? You know what else I don't like about this video game? Walking into
Pikmin collects them. Unbelievable. Unbelievable. Okay. And then I'll let.
What are they doing over here? Oh my God. Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run,
run, run. Don't fight. Run. I hope there's nothing in this. I picked the one hallway.
They didn't have anything. Okay. Turn around and get them. Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Get back here. Quick. They're blocked. Oh my God. You're being blocked.
Fucking land on them. Oh my God. We just saw that. They were dead.
Gee, is there anybody still alive in his ass? Like what the fuck? That was so all right. That
was horrible. Okay. We're good. That was horrible. They just, they were pursuing us. They came for us.
I don't, I hate those ones. They actually actively come get you. 120. That was inside of his
danger chime. Okay. 66 though. Okay. So what was I doing? Right. I was in the middle of trying to
plan my, what I was going to do. So let's blurt it out. I'm going to take electricity with Olimar.
Okay. Electric Olimar. Louie, you, Louie, you need to spread these guys out and get red.
I'm like right next to the microphone. I'm sorry. Okay. Olimar, yellow. All right. It's time.
Fire first. Louie, go. My, my elbow is red. I need one of those bionic arms. Oh shit. Here comes like
another invasion. Get out of here. What happened? A confused Bulborb has fallen in with the Pikmin.
They appear to be, to coexist peacefully. Wait, what? Did I just kill one for no reason?
Strange. This Bulborb has a leaf sprouting from its spine, much like the leaf on a Pikmin's head.
Oh, I would, they wouldn't friendly. Well, oh no, that was a leader. That was a big one.
I love the little Bulborbs. I love them so much. I love them. They're my favorite. They must be
protected at all costs. Okay. Yellow. Let's go up here and just do this. This gas up there.
Tack. Kill everything. Excellent. Excellent. They can't die. Really? All right. And there's the way
to go down lower. Don't want to do that yet. I do appreciate the haunted house exit though. I do.
Just in case you don't want to do it. The guy that's standing at the door and like in the,
in the black jumpsuit that it's like all the screaming, crying kids run out that way before
the really scary stuff. I'm really glad it's there. By the way, just want to let you know,
I have had to use the escape haunted house exit one time in my whole life.
And all I remember was crying buried into my father's chest while he was holding me.
I was like probably six or seven. I was crying and just seeing the guy go right this way,
right this way. And we just went outside into the air. That's all I remember.
I don't remember anything else. Okay. Electricity all gone. It is. All right. We need the gas.
Okay. Everybody stay. I need more white. No. Fuck the Wiimote. Get it.
Put the Bulbman in the white flower. No way. Can I take them out to the surface?
If I can take them to the surface, I'm not going to do that. I can't take them out to the surface.
What? Oh, come on now. Really? That's really unfortunate. That's horrible.
All right. Let's go get everybody. We're ready to move. The fire is up there, but I don't need
unless there's a hidden one somewhere. They're immune to everything. Is there? Let's see.
Just use them while you have them. Okay. Was it a pen? Oh, it's a candle. There actually is.
There is something buried. Okay. We got to get it. Everybody come over here. Okay. So I should
throw the Bulbasaur in there. Use them while I have them. Don't. I'm seeing a lot of conflicting
data here. They're invincible. Don't. Okay. Well, then I'm going to throw blue. Okay. 76. Let's go.
Can they drink the nectar? Oh, wait. We good? Okay. We're good. Take the cupcakes. Those bugs
freak out. Yeah, they do. All right. It's time to go and try to find this one that's buried.
Money, money, money. Butter, butter, butter fills the bowl. We're making us a cake that you've never
seen before. We're making us a cake that you've never seen before. Heat up the oven. Now we're on
a roll. Heat up the oven. Now on a roll. Cheep, cheep, cheep is the name of your soul. Cheep,
cheep, cheep. Where's this last one? And it's buried. Where is it buried? It's buried over here.
Thanks for joining me, everybody. Hope you're having a good day. Hope you're having a Sunday.
Super Bowl Sunday. Hope you got yourself a slice of pizza and a big Subway Sub. The big ones. The
comically large ones. Oh, I don't like Subway. Subway's terrible. Whatever. A chain that you like.
Ooh, this would be worth a lot. Get that treasure. Stop saying dumbass things.
Um, I'm pretty much like 90% sure that at least half the time that I open my mouth on this stream
it's to say a dumbass thing. So if you don't like that kind of content, I suggest you go watch the
Super Bowl. That's on right now. Don't you know it's 50% stuff that you say in the shower when
you know no one's listening to you. 25% interesting true statements. And then like 20% noises. That's
kind of how the stream works. I'm here for the true. Yeah, I got to give myself some credit,
you know. Okay. Yeah. You're here for like 20% like interesting statements.
I got to give myself at least 20%. Wait, whoa, whoa. What did I just do? What happened? I went
out. I went out the Halloween exit. Oh no. Shit. Should I reset it? Oh, come on. I just was ready.
No, I can't. I don't. What the fuck? Oh no. I'll just go back and do it again. I made a lot of
money. Whatever. You can go back. I can go back tomorrow. I'll be fine. I'll be fine. Don't worry,
son. It was just some men in costumes. I am now. I whatever. I fucked up. I'm done with that. I'll
go back tomorrow. He didn't like the way he screamed at me. I had four seconds to hit B.
It's okay. It's okay. We're going to go to McDonald's. We're going to go to McDonald's.
Is that what you want? You want to go to McDonald's? Yes. Of course you do. And I
want a large fry. Okay. You can have a large fry. Okay. And then because it's Halloween,
the McDonald's employees are just kind of having fun. And we pull up to the fucking
drive-thru and this guy in a scary mask that's just like, hello. Here you go. Thanks for coming
to McDonald's. Oh shit. No, no, no, no, no. It's okay. It's okay. That's just a scary guy in a
costume. It's okay. We'll go to Dairy Queen. We'll go to Dairy Queen right now. We will? Yeah.
It's a scary guy in a costume. No, no, no. I meant like a guy that was scary because he was in the
costume. Not a guy that was scary because whatever. Hello. I'm still on the, I am still on
the I am from debt collectors. Well, the time being still on the lamb. What does that mean?
Still on the lamb. On the lamb. L-A-M is it, is it, is it not B? What is L-A-M's? What is that?
I don't know what that is. L-A-M-B is like lamb. Lamb. I've never heard that presented that way.
Lamb. To hit someone hard. To attack someone. Shit. I didn't know that.
I can go back there and the, the, yeah, I'm going back here. Yeah. I wish you were my dad. No,
you do not. It would be, you would not like me as your dad. You would be listening to this from the
other room and be incredibly embarrassed. You would have friends over and you'd be doing whatever
you're doing, hanging out in your room and you would hear like, oh, look at me. Oh, the wee,
yes, a piece of shit. This thing sucks. Fuck you. You'd hear that and you'd be like embarrassing to
have friends over. You would make sure that on stream days you were far away from this house.
I'm not sure you would like that. Okay. So now I'm going to go back to that cave.
My dad's a streamer. You know, I'm actually kind of surprised that like Nickelodeon or the Disney
channel has not done that. Like my dad, the streamer. And they play like the, the handful
of guitar riffs before the intro starts. And the person sits down there like, oh man, it's so crazy
living in this house. And they introduce all the characters. My dad, the streamer is just, you'll
see. It'll happen. They did that with iCarly. Yeah. But I'm, that's not my dad, the streamer.
That's iCarly. Wait, in our, was iCarly's dad a streamer? My dad's a VTuber. My dad, the VTuber.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It would be like my digital family. And they all have their
own little like avatars. That's real. What do you mean that's real? That's, that's, that Disney
channel has that. There's a VTuber family. That's a TV. What? Okay. I have to play the game. I got
to, I gotta go. That's an actual show? There's treasure somewhere over here. Where is it?
Dude, dude, dude, there's treasure here. Dude, it's up there, I think. I'm gonna throw some whites up
there. It spreads. Dude, it's definitely right there. Oh, nice. What is it? We'll dig it out
already. My dad, the VTuber. Oh, onion, onion ring. He made mustard cheese dip. That sounds
actually pretty good. Don't. They're gonna go in the water. You see that? Okay. Well, good thing I
caught that. Come this way. The great reveal. Uh, that was supposed to be very scary, but
I, uh, and now I know it's there. I just, I just think of Donkey Kong. All right. I need, um,
purples. That's not Toad. That's the bird from Donkey Kong. Come on up. Show yourself. He's like
right here. There you are. Oh, he ate a poison one. Good. That's good. Watch out. It's okay. All
right. Get off. Get back up. Where is he? No, no, no, no, no, no. Stop eating them. Why is nobody
attaching to him? Why? I, what the fuck is going on? How am I missing? I can't reach him from here
then. God, this Wiimote. I seriously feel like somebody's strangling me right now with their
hands around my neck, trying to aim this. I can't even, nobody can even reach there.
Nobody can actually, I can't throw anybody over there. Aim for the head. I'm trying to hold on.
Let me, let me aim over there. Hold on.
Dad, dad, shut up. I got a girl over. I have like, I suppose I'm getting ready for prom,
dad. What the fuck? Stop, please. Please don't do this right now. He just hit me through the wall.
Oh my God. Maybe I'm going to lean in. Oh wow. She looked, I'm going to have my first kiss.
What the heck? Oh my God. My heart is going crazy.
What was that? What was that? Do you hear that? I don't know. No, I don't know. I must have dropped
something on his foot. My dad, the streamer. I need to give you a kid to talk, like on stream
for content. That's not, that would be not okay. That would be terrible. I want some more blues.
I don't have like any blues, do I? All the blues died. All right. Put back some yellows. I have
way too many yellows. It's educational. What are you talking about? Oh fuck. I don't have any blue
left. That's not good. That's really bad actually. Oh, okay. Well,
ding, ding, ding, ding.
There you go. That's how every single one of those shows starts. It goes,
and then there's like a chorus. What was the one that was, is it,
did you have to take some time to realize.
That hurts. What was that one? Drake and Josh did that one. That just hurt me. Fuck. My voice
hurts. What the hell? And if you don't know, you know, you should never know where nobody's down.
Yeah, I remember that one. Remember the episode where they like make the tree house and they get
stuck in it because they didn't put a door on it and then like drew a door on it. Remember I said
that was like a funny routine and I accidentally stole it from Drake and Josh. Oh, how many white
shoot that again. I actually shoot it again. Come over here. Fire that at me. Fire.
Okay. I was going to say it attaches to me, right? Come on, kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Oh, you punk.
Oh my God. That was dangerous. This is a horrible idea. This is a horrible idea and he's going to
kill everybody over there. Isn't he? Please don't. Okay. We're fine. I need blue to pick that up
after we get rid of this guy. Shit. Do not please. Do not bring that back yet. What are you doing
over here? Stop doing that. Nobody fucking move. What are you thinking? All of you. What's wrong
with you? They're not going to get this in time. Why are they going? I could fart on them. I don't
think it'll do it though. I'll try. All right. Fart. All right. Go. But he died. That one just
got worked to death. What was that? Oh, it was red. Oh, come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Damn it. I'm trying to get it to hit the wall. Come on. Hit
each other. Hit him. Do it. Oh my God, dude. Watch out. Watch out. Okay. We're good. Now some of you
can bring that back. I want blue to pick up this because we're running out of blue. Blue and purple.
Please. Couple. What? What the hell happened? At least that shit will be dead tomorrow. You wasted
a whole day talking about Drake and Josh. And I could probably waste a few days talking about
Drake and Josh. What a show. Yes. Okay. We'll go back to that tomorrow. You were 20 when that show
aired. Um, yeah. I was like 19 or something. I didn't watch Drake and Josh. So what? I'm like,
if I'm like 18 years old, 19, 20 years old, I can't enjoy an episode of Drake and Josh.
It's not for you. How many of you have Pokemon installed on your Switch right now or your Wii
or something? How many of you guys play Pokemon? How many? How many of you guys are over the age
of 18 that I can't wait for the next Pokemon game to come out? But I can't watch an episode
of Drake and Josh when I'm 20. Okay. Is that, but is that, that's not for you though. It's like a
game for, they make it that game for like a younger audience. You can't, you can't play that. Right?
Right guys? Wait, what am I doing? Continue. What did I just do? Did I not save the game?
All right. We're going back. Hey, I'm playing this. I'm playing Pikmin right now and you're
here watching Pikmin. What does that make both of us? But we're not, you're not allowed to play
something because it was made to have like a general audience in mind. Excuse me. What's wrong
with that? I only have two blues. We've got to change that. Is there any bigger ones out here?
I don't think so. Listen, like Pikmin. Okay. Cute does not mean only for children. Like look,
Pikmin, Olimar. Look, it's like a cute game with like Pikmins and they're so cute. And so look at
them. They're just like, Oh, only children can play this. That's not fair. I want at least like
six or seven. Wait, so you're not a child. No, I just act like one. Doesn't make me a kid. I'm
just one. I'm just a little kid that is wearing the suit. I'm wearing the suit glasses. Like a
nice pair of loafers as a joke in whatever movie or TV show you're watching. We're like, oh no,
the kid's got to be an adult. He's doing taxes. All right. So I got enough blue, I think. I do
need a bunch of red. I need white. 30. Boss baby Andy. 30, 30. And then N9. That's a pretty good
Nickelodeon sound by the way. This one. So let's supplement that with a little bit more yellow.
Okay. I have a ton of yellow. This is a yellow run. All right. Let's go. Who needs a nectar?
Drink it. I want you to be big and strong. Hit the bong on camera. I don't have a bong. I don't
smoke weed. I eat it. If I need to, if I feel like it, or if I want to. I do not really smoke
it. It irritates my throat. Just going to be completely honest with you. I don't like to
smoke weed because I feel like it's an irritant. It's an irritant. I love that snowman. It's so cute.
Okay. We dealt with that bird last time. Now we got this bridge. We went over here.
There was that fence. Where was that fence? Up this way. There we go. Okay. Monka. Oh,
there it is. Monka. Yes. Okay. I found it. White. There's another cave over here.
Anything this way? Let me just look over here. Um, this is the, oh, there's a, there's a couple
of caves. This is that cave, right? Okay. Wait, I'm going to go on this one first.
I think Monka. Whatever. I'm trying to stuff it in there. It's hard. The crown. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Where's that crown? He left three yellows behind. Oh shit, I did. More than that. Did I get them?
They just won't cross the bridge because they're dumb. What's your favorite bug?
Um, one of those big emperor beetles. Whatever they're called. The ones with the gigantic faces.
They have the long noses, the long jaws. They have the big twig face. What are they called?
Hercules beetle. Yep. That's one. I, if a Hercules beetle was on my floor right now, I would not
freak out. The bigger the bug, the less scared I will be of it. If a Hercules beetle walked into
this room right now, I would not get up and go, oh my God, what the fuck is that? No. I'd be like,
holy shit, that's a Hercules beetle. This is cool. Uh, if a, if a spider as big as my thumbnail
showed up in front of me, I would scream like a little kid. I would freak out. I would sprint
around. All the hairs on my body would stand up and I would, I wouldn't be able to come in this
room. I would have to stay out of this room for a few days. I wouldn't be able to go, I would not
be able to come in here. Uh, but a huge bug would just be, okay, that's a big bug. All right. This
guy doesn't want to go over here. Come on. I want to finish this cave. Big spider. Actually, no,
I want this. Yeah. Let's get this. All right. Can I get this without having to deal with this guy?
I don't think I can. I have to kill that thing. How am I going to do this? Just punch him with
Olimar. I can try that. I don't think I can even get up there. I don't have damage.
Wait a minute. I've got an idea. Ah, am I safe right here? I think it'll, I think it's going to
hit the wall. Yep. I'm safe right here. This is perfect. Kill. Oh shit. Everybody died. Perfect.
Nice. All right. Very good. Very good. Very good. Very good. Very good. We need blue to pick these
up. Blue, follow me. I need blue to get everything here. So let's do this right. We need, okay. We've
spread out. I wish I could hold C and make them spread out even further. I'm fucking wee.
Fucking stupid. Fucking wee. Fucking wee. Right. What are you expecting? I need like a, okay. So
we need a purple and a blue. Good. Okay. Now we need a purple and a blue. Good. Purple and a blue.
All right. What happened to, I'll take a break after this level. Oh, and then the rest of you
get that crown. Oh, you motherfuckers. I swear to God. Why are you doing that?
Why are you doing that? Do what? Cause you walked over here. I didn't tell them to do that. So why
are they doing it? I did not tell. I did not say anybody. I did not tell them to do that.
So why are you doing it? Oh God damn it. It's going to kill these guys. Isn't he? I know he is.
This is such a pain in the ass. You better not attack those guys. I will be so, I'll be furious.
All right. Hurry up. Get back to base now. The rest of you get this. Let's go. Raid song. Raid
song. Oh shit. All shame, no wow with the raid. Thanks dude. Welcome everybody. I'll give you a
song. It just takes some time to realize when you show boat, you show me, you show down, you show me
around. Thanks for the raid. Welcome. Am I going to be able to do this in time? Nah. Hope you had a
good stream. Thanks. Welcome everybody. I'm playing Pikmin 2 for the Nintendo Wii U.
The upscaled version from the GameCube to the Wii and then the Wii version ported to the Wii U.
I know. I know. It annoys me too. Name one other character from that show.
Come on. You can get there. Please get there. Don't make this a waste of time.
Are they actually not going to get there? Name one character from that show that's not Drake
and Josh. I don't know. Didn't they work at a movie theater? Josh worked at a movie theater.
There was a movie theater employee that he worked with. Whoever that was. I don't know.
All right. Well, I have 10 seconds left for them to bring these back. Only 120 what? Unspeakable
wonder. 70% of debt has been recovered. 10 seconds. Shit. At least get me one of them in there. Come
on. Come on. Hurry. Four. Three. Two. They're not going to get it. I'm missing somebody. Oh,
just a few reds. Who cares? If it was purple, I would be very upset. It's just like two reds.
At least I got the... The crown was a pain in the ass.
Jeremy, sing the Skyrim theme song, but say Monka S instead. I don't. I really don't know what the
Skyrim theme song is. It's the one that's like... I've never heard it before. What is it? I don't
know. Well, the animals that adopted me are actually rather cute once you get used to them.
Once we get the debt paid off, I might build a refuge for them. What do you think? This is not
a pre-recorded stream. Get out of here. Hey, as they say in England, fuck off. You know what I
mean? As they say in England, fuck off, mate. All right. I want to go back in there and go to the
cave. Let's take a break. I'm going to go pee. I'm going to refill my... Well, I have coffee.
Pretending I'm not drinking coffee. I'm going to drink some water, get a little bit more coffee,
and we will continue. Be right back. Don't go anywhere unless you have to go somewhere.
But definitely don't switch to the Super Bowl. I'll tell you the score right now. It's zero to
zero. Tom Brady has 15 interceptions. It's an absolute disaster for him. At least that would
be like... Whatever. I'll be back. What the hell is that? The ultimate gamer chair? The saw trap.
I got a question for you. Those of you guys that have or have ever experienced any time
with a refrigerator that has an ice maker in it? You have your ice. Water can come out of there
usually. And there's always the thing that says crushed ice. There's regular ice and then you
press the button. It's crushed ice. Has that ever worked in any fridge you've ever used with a
crushed ice? Doesn't it just spit out regular ice cubes but make loud fucking noises? Why is
that even on any fridge? I don't get it. I've never seen that work. It just goes... Ice cubes.
And some of them are broken. I don't even know why they put... Why do they even put that shit on
fridges? That doesn't make any sense. It doesn't do anything. You have a bad fridge. This has been
every fridge I've ever used that's ever had across multiple states and multiple continents
that I've never used the crushed ice fridge feature that has ever worked the way it's supposed
to be intended. I swear to god this is the last time I'll ever draw a German with a cat feature.
I swear. I swear. I promise. Sub. I'm serious. I've never seen it work. I thought that was
supposed to be Cheeto and I was like, holy shit. That's from a spore. All right. Let's keep going.
I want to go back in that cave. I love this game. It's very fun. All right. I want to go back in
that cave. Please read my chat message. Okay. What does it say? I've beaten Pikmin 2 and I've been
trying to give you tips. Well, I mean, there's almost 11,000 people here. Everyone's trying...
Look at the amount of tips that people are screaming at me. Half of them aren't even real.
Now, if I pay attention to your tips, what if they're not real? What if they're fake?
If you're trying to get me to throw a Pikmin off the bridge or something.
Ban if not real. No. I appreciate the tips though. I appreciate any tips you could give me except,
I mean, do I have a no back seating rule on this channel? I really don't.
No. People just write whatever they want. Half of it could be fake bullshit.
I want to go back in that cave, but I'll be okay. I'm going to be totally honest with you.
Back seating for me? Like, I'm not going to listen to you anyways. How many times have you
guys written something in here that was actually helpful? And I just didn't even care. I didn't
look at it. Like, I'm not going to listen anyways. That's happened many times. So it's not like I
have to have a rule. Why do I need a rule if I already don't pay attention? Why do I even try?
Look, it's all right. Everything's just good. I don't need any tips. I appreciate the tips,
but I don't need them because I'm a professional video game player.
And we went over that on the spore stream. Please tell me to go to the secret hole.
That sounds like a pretty good tip, actually. There's a secret hole, a secret tunnel.
Why did everything respawn? Hold on. Itchy inside of my ear. How did I lost somebody? 99 out of 100.
Where's the last one? I don't know where they are, but it's too late.
I'm not going to fight anything. I'm just going to go. I just want to go in the cave.
Why am I not feeding the Pikmin? I am. I'm going to give them the nectar. Let's go.
What's my opinion on roly-polys? The weird bugs that you find under the welcome mat?
Um, they're all right. Do I start on? What floor am I on? Floor one?
Shit. This is the first floor, isn't it? Damn it. It's the first goddamn floor.
Wait, technically I could run, right? Hold on. Technically I could just run and just go in.
I don't have to do any of this. I could just run. Okay, here we go. Where's the exit? Wait,
purple. Don't wake that motherfucker up. Get out of here. Did I just lose a white? Oh, man.
No, I didn't. I did. Shit. Same button. Nintendo. Why? I'm going to back up. In fact,
I don't trust any of you, so stay here. Oh, it's right here. Move. Go invent a console if
you keep complaining. I'm kidding. I don't actually believe any of these things.
I hope you know that. Okay, everyone get out of the way with a big Kappa. Kappa. I was on level
five or six before. This guy still believes in Santa. What a wild concept that we pretend is
real for like five to 10 years of people's lives. That's sort of bizarre if you think about it.
We just kind of like pretend that Santa's just a real thing. Oh, yeah, yeah. Santa's a real guy.
Run away. Run away. Run away. Where's the exit? Wait, little guys. There's only one. Santa is real.
Where's the exit? Thank God he's stuck there. Okay, where's the exit though? Right there. All
right. I mean, Santa was a real guy, but like 500 years ago, 800 years ago or something. Saint Nick,
right? Saint Nicholas. Isn't that based on a real thing? He used to put like toys in people's shoes
and stuff. It's based on something. What is it actually based on? What is it? No, it was a real
person. It was a real like a tale of a guy that did that. Oh, not Krampus. All right, this is the
one that I don't want to leave. There's a treasure on this one. And there's more purples to be had.
Red. Isn't it something in the Bible? Yeah, but there was a guy. Who is the guy?
Santa Claus is based on an actual living person. What was it? Patron saint of... Patron,
whatever. But fun fact, the actual Saint Nick punched a guy in the nose.
No, no, no, no, no. It's somebody else. Saint Nicholas is the patron saint of sailors,
merchants, archers, repentant thieves, prostitutes, children, brewers, palm brokers,
unmarried people, and students in various cities and countries. What? Thank you for subscribing to
Fun Bug Facts. A vroly-poly vulgar has also been introduced to many locations in North America where
maybe each population is absent, whatever. And what does that have anything to do with Santa Claus?
Santa Claus is based on Saint Nick, who is a guy who left gold coins in prostitutes' laundry to
let... I don't even know if any of this stuff is... Thank God there's no timer. Oh, I don't want to
pick up anybody. Jerry, I don't want to pick anybody up. I just want the yellow one. You know
what's really interesting? So Seinfeld is a really, really old show. Nobody really pays that much
attention to it anymore. You guys think it's funny. You guys think that George is hilarious
and shit, and Jerry and stuff. That's really interesting. That's a really timeless show then.
Oh, that's really interesting to think about that. Is that a guy electric too?
It holds up. Oh yeah, I mean... Swarm. Swarm him. Take the swarm. Yeah, the swarm. That sounds like
a new keyboard. The swarm GX500. Loudest mechanical keyboard on the market. Let everybody know.
Just how much you're gaming with the swarm. Sounds like a bunch of bees. All right, electricity.
I have a quiet mechanical keyboard. I like soft. What do I have? A red? Cherry red? That's the one
that's a little softer, right? Didn't get anybody. Tough luck. Cherry red is with the O-rings, right?
I think that's what this is. Oh shit, I just completely... Well, I just absolutely exposed
myself. Yeah, no, it's all right. I just exposed myself 100%. I'm no longer using the Amazon Basics
keyboard. I told you guys that I was using that. I got a new, like a Corsair keyboard or something.
I don't know. All right, can we kill this guy, please? No, give me my friends back. Weigh him
down. Don't let him... Don't kill them. Weigh him down. Oh my God. How is this even missing?
Just rained down on his head. Okay, I don't know what any of this shit is, but take it.
What are they saying?
I can't. My voice is too hot low. I so badly just want to do the I-uh thing.
I just wanted to do it right now and I don't care what the repercussions are.
Oh, it's like a marble. There's so many of these enemies here right now.
You better not. Who's gonna tell you to stop? I'm gonna unsub if you do. How many people will
sub if I do it? That's a better question. Can we offset the sub that that guy I'm gonna lose from
that guy? I will. I'll sub if you do it. How many people will unsubscribe if I do that and how many
people will subscribe if I do that? This is tricky. I will gift a sub. Okay, this one, two,
pull. I don't trust a pull with that. You guys will just pretend I lose somebody. All right,
be careful in here. All right, pick him up. Let's see. I'm curious. I'm just gonna do it.
Whatever. Do it. Do it then. I'm gonna. I'm just thinking about when I want to do it.
I'm trying to get a good time. Don't. Please. I think I'm gonna get like a hundred subs if I do
that. 50 to 60 of you will unsubscribe and like a hundred will subscribe. So that's a net 40,
I guess, gain, right? Exactly, huh? All right, so if I say that word and I get a net 100,
a net 40, then if I say shpee immediately afterwards, will you come back? All those unsubscribed.
That's gonna be really. That's gonna fuck with the whole community, okay?
Because it's one thing that everybody hates and one thing that everybody loves. So I'm gonna.
This is gonna pull you guys apart. You guys are gonna get sucked through like an internet wormhole.
Shpee. What happened? Everybody all right? Is everybody okay? I don't know what happened.
Is everything. Is it going still here? Oh, shit. I'm losing subs. I'm losing subs, but I'm gaining
subs. I'm just kidding. Maybe we should do it again. All right. Watch out for these gliders.
I'm gonna call them gliders. Well, thanks for the community subs. Get away. He took me.
Get away from me. As long as it's not the Bane impression, it's fine. How many subs
to the Bane impression? Oh, my God. I just get everybody over here and spam. Stop it.
I hate these things. Pick me up every fucking time. Just get him. Put us down. Why is he getting us?
What the fuck? Finally. Geez. Kill him. I didn't say it. That could have been Elmo.
Just step on his head. Okay. Apologize. It's kind of fun to say though. You know that I say this
like in my off time. It's fun just to go. It's fun to do it. I don't know. It's nothing about it.
Why are they not attaching to him? Put us down. And now we're gonna die. Fucking dad. Ayayaying
again. The streamer dad. Boy. I wonder if I'm gonna get my first kiss.
Ayayaying. Dad, what the heck?
I hate that so much. What's that? Is that a starburst? Are you okay? Yeah, I think so. Oh,
you didn't say. Oh, I forgot. Shmee. There you go. How do I get health as Olimar? I need some nectar
too. I have a lot of new Pikmin. Get away. The ship will give you health? Oh, okay. You are dumb
dumb. Ha ha ha ha. Is Shmee gonna be on your gravestone? No. I hope not. Why is this not
giving me health? You lied to me. What is that guy? Press C. Why is he doing that? What do I do?
Hold C. What the hell? Hold C. I just did. This doesn't exit me from the level or something,
right? I'm holding C. Hold C. He's not doing anything. Okay, well, there's like a yeti over
here. You're stupid. What? Do it away from the Pikmin. That's not doing anything. Okay,
let's go for it. I want purples. We're gonna overwhelm. Three, two, one, go. Everyone's alive.
Nobody died. Oh, what's that? A butterfly? What is that? Who's in the ground here? Did I just get
more Pikmin? Okay, I'm gonna put some yellow in this. Or maybe some red. What do I have the most
of? Let's get red. Red's the easiest to get. They all missed. And aim. Oh my god. And aim.
Can we start banning? Can we start banning these people? Like, can we start? They're making fun of
me. Can we start banning them and making sure they don't show up again? Wicked funny. Everyone's so
funny. Can we start putting out bans, please? E and them. E and them. Cry baby. One, two, three,
four, five. I wish I wanted to get this to stop talking. Wait, if I switch to... Okay,
Louie's the one that's almost dead. Who cares? Now, oh, more purple. Oh, no, this is blue. Oh,
shit. Okay, I'm gonna get rid of some more. I'm gonna get rid of some more reds. You have so
many yellows. I love electricity. It's my favorite element. Electricity is my favorite element,
so of course I'm gonna want it. All right, what about... Watch out. Be careful here. Blue spider.
There's a lot of shit in here. Oh, dear. Oh, dear. Oh, boy. Well, back it up for a sec.
Let's take blue over here. Don't wake up everybody. Just be easy. Don't do that. Don't do that. Why
can you just... This is infuriating me. Hold on. Let me jam the Wiimote into my chest so I can
fucking aim it right. Why are they not jumping on his head? Oh, that only took like five tries.
They're friendly. What? Don't hurt them. What? Why not? They're gonna kill me. The Yetis are good.
Oh, yeah. A smashing claw animation. They're good, huh? Let them hit them. No. No, I'm not
gonna do that. I'm not gonna do that. Oh, this is not good now. They don't kill them. Frost us,
please. Fine. You better not be fucking with me. Oh, shit. Okay, cool. Oh, shit. We'll do that to
more of them. I got a lot of guys you can do that to. No! All right, there's another one.
I want him to do it to the purples. Get everybody over here. The purples really need to be flowered
up. Nice miss. Again. Oh, you got it. Nice. Just let him walk around and just do it. Stop moving. I
feel like he's gonna hit me with it. Okay, good. Okay. The rest of you, come back over here. Who
else needs it? Oh, look at all these yellows that need it. Come here. Good. All right, one more.
Okay. I'm done. I'm done. I don't care. I'm done. Kill him. Don't get crushed. All right. Well,
somebody attacked. Somebody attacked. Kill. Somebody attacked. Nobody had to do it.
Luis almost dead. Wait, I'm getting bored watching this. So, go watch the Super Bowl. Go watch Tom
Brady throw 50 interceptions. That's what you're missing. I'm telling you. Is the Super Bowl today?
Yes. Wait, the Super Bowl was today? Oh, shit. All right, we're good. There's still treasure
everywhere. Do a Super Bowl watch party. God, no. Okay, I want the nectar. Can I, can, can Olimar
drink this? Can we drink this? Like, can we drink it out of this? To heal? I don't know. How do we
heal? Super Bowl watch party, but it's just staring at a TV. Right, yeah. Uh, I think everybody pretty
much has it, so let's just kill him. Oh, he had a fist. The Super Bowl doesn't need another 10k
viewers. No, it doesn't. Giant metal hand. Perhaps it's an ancient work of art. What? He's going crazy.
Emergency. Pikmin are suffering. If you blow your whistle with B, you may be able to help them.
What's wrong with them? What do you do? Do you take too much DMT? What are you doing? I think we're
okay. I guess they were, they were suffering somehow. Super Bowl watch party with you staring
at the TV for six hours and just putting my fist up and going, yeah, after every time my team scores
points. This object seems to replicate a humanoid fist, a glove much like it once lay in my junk
hold. And here is that very glove. I have just found the missing rocket fist in my junk hold.
Tap A three times to launch it. One, two, punch. Oh, cool. Everyone get out of the way.
Ooh. Boom. Like a little three hit combo. All right. 99. We're good. No more treasure.
Let's get the hell out of here. That's the Luigi's Mansion.
Mm hmm. Level six. Not the final area either. Okay. Hold on. Let me just see what's around me.
What do we got? This is already a horrible place to be standing. Like right off the bat. Oh my god.
Holy shit, dude. What the fuck are you doing to me? What? You've got to be kidding me.
What kind of fucking place is this? I'm okay. I'm all right. Back it up. Purple, purple, purple,
purple, purple, purple, purple. What the fuck? Oh, that was stupid. Two of the homing missile
guys just sit right in front of the guy. What's with the design there? Who designed that? Terrible
design. Awful design. Worst design I've ever seen in a video game and I've played lots of them.
That's RNG. Oh, oh. Never mind. Worst I've ever seen in a video game ever. It's just a dice roll.
What we got in here? Fire, water. Okay. Don't die from this. Stay right here.
Okay. Keep going. Is that, what is that thing? Is that fire related?
I, you're good. You're good. You're good. You're good. You're good. Just get over here.
Oh, statue. All right. What else we got? All right. I think we're okay. This is going to be such a
horrible pain in the ass. I have to throw them across this. Almost all of them. It's a purple
in here. I don't want a purple with me. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
Come here. Now I got a crew. There's like bad guys over here, guys. This is the guy that I'm
worried about. Pen. Fuck. I'm not going to be able to get that. Oh, punch it. Punch it to death.
Look at my health though. No, I need big guys. Shoot the rock. Shoot him. Thank you. Okay. Good.
Good. Good. Good. Good. What else is over here? Fire this way. That's it. Shit. I can't get that.
I can't get any of these things. I don't have enough blue. Come on. Really? What about the
Bulbman? A Bulbman? What do you mean a Bulbman? Did Bulbman die in the water? Oh shit. Okay.
Hold on. Oh, they have Pog. Two. How many do I have? Seven. Eight. Oh, no. There's no more?
Really? Reset the floor. I don't think, I think I only had seven blue to start. Damn it. That's
very disappointing. You had eleven. Did Bulbman are immune to poison, fire, electricity, and water.
I had more blues at the start of this level? I don't think I did. Did I? Did they die? I had eleven
at subspace six. I did. I did? Oh, right. That's right. These two assholes. Right. Okay.
Um, god damn it, Andy. God damn it, Andy. What's that even mean? Oh, wait. I have to turn it back
on. It went into sleep mode. I love his face. Uh, what's wrong with my Wii? Uh-oh. Um, it just made the
I have to put my password in. Hold on. I forget my, I forget my password. I just put it into,
I don't know what it is. Did I get it right? Password is, okay, good. Oh, password is Hewl12345.
All right, we're good. Come on back. Press what? He's pretending. Hey, listen, listen. Did you hear it?
All right, let's come on back. Nintendo. I just love playing the Nintendo. I just love the Nintendo.
Let's see if I get absolutely destroyed this time. The two dumb spawns right next to me that just
start shooting rocks everywhere. What do we got? Wow, that's a way better room. This room doesn't
suck ass. Okay, let's take the purples. I want, I don't know why I want to do Sir Finley Murgleton
so bad right now. It's just grabbing a hold of me. I don't know why. I need fire to get rid of that.
Punch them. I could try the punch. Yeah, I'm not bringing anybody over there. I'm going to punch.
Oh my god, hit him. That would have been horrible. All right, everybody stay back. I'm going for the
punch. I just got stun locked. Olimar is a clown. Olimar is a fucking clown. What happened? Wait,
what happens? Oh, just take rid of this so I can get over here. I don't even know why these guys
are even spawning here. It's like where are you supposed to even go with this? My teeth. I'm just
talking through my teeth. Move. Shoot him. Why did you, one walked all the way over there. What
is wrong with you? Get out of the water. Get out of the water. Get out of the water. I fucking god
fucked this place. Fucked this place. Fuck this level. What the hell? Where are you supposed to
even go? Get out. Make them shoot each other. Yeah, and then one of them is going to fire one.
That was the dumbest thing I've ever seen in my life. I don't even know what happened. How
did that even happen? That was stupid. That was the dumbest fucking thing I've ever seen.
Look, it's a bulbus. All right, I got a bulbus. Can I do this with Louis? Okay, do we have enough
blue to do this? Okay, thank god. Let's go. I need red as well to get rid of the fire and the
bulbuses. Here we go. Well, I had to do that because they have to pull the, they're going
to walk through that. Okay, there's one more of these assholes over here. Oh, perfect.
Good ING. Good ING. Don't get on that with them. You're just going to die if you do that.
That's pretty good ING. Nice. All right, then we just gotta wait for them to be done.
In the meantime, what can I do? I get a meantime. Oh shit, hold on. In the meantime, I'm gonna make
this guy shoot himself. The chest piece. Nice. Pog. Okay, now get shot. How much is that worth?
80. Pretty good. Pretty cool. You can do it. Yeah. Okay, I just keep hearing this in my brain.
All right, blues, get back. I said blue. I don't want any white there. Blue. All right,
we should have enough to get the last piece. It's 10. All right, is there anything else in here?
What about up here? No, that is all that remains. You all right? All right, you're good.
Go in there with them. You guys just really like to put yourselves into danger, don't you?
And then I'll be able to take everybody up. So again, please confirm with me again. If I go
into here just as Louie, everybody comes with me. It doesn't matter if they're part of the crew or
not, right? Correct. Okay. Fantastic. Goldman are immune to everything. That's good because I'll be
sending them wherever they want to go next. Okay, we're good. Hold C. It's not healing.
Treasure's gone. Let's go. But lies deeper. This is level seven or eight. Olimar is dead.
He is. What do we got? What's over here? Nothing. Explore it. There's the way down.
Okay, it doesn't look too bad so far. Unless there's something in the ground. And there's
something wrong there. That's something fell from the ceiling. Come with me. Watch out. Watch out.
I'm very cautious about this. Okay. Yeah. It says stuff. Shit drops from the ceiling. Good to know.
Oh boy. Okay. What do we got over here? That's the way down. Watch it. Where's this treasure?
Down here? Where is this damn thing? Oh man. Oh, there's a white thing. Okay. I need to...
Who should I throw in here? Yellow? Probably yellow. Do not drop a meteor on me right here,
please. Don't drop a meteor here. Thank god. Okay. A couple of, a lot of big guys.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Come back. Oh my God. He runs really fast. He's really fast.
Go back to sleep. Come on back here. Run away
Good. Okay. Now I'm ready. Let's get our
Something to dig up there, but I don't want to get killed by any explosions
I swear to God a meteor is gonna kill everybody aren't they?
I'm so afraid of a meteor just dropping right now. Please don't. What do you think Pikmin tastes like Jerma? Um, probably acidic
Acid they're probably very at like they probably tastes like very acidic
You know the sour
All right, you know what a sour patch kid tastes like?
Okay. Now, do you know what you know? Okay, you know when lightning strikes and you get that smell outside kind of smells like ozone
I feel like it's like a mix of sour patch kids and ozone
It's really funny when people say that what are you talking about smelling ozone?
That's what you smell when it's like a when a thunderstorm is happening
It is like a lightning and that like electricity kind of smell that like rain lightning kind of smell that's ozone
Ozone and like bacteria and stuff. That's correct. I thought I was the stupid one. What are you talking about?
Look it up right now. Don't look it up right now. Look it up right now
You're a bozo and a yo-yo nice, but if he's right, yeah, I know
That's it you're spelling ozone
See all those question marks that was spammed when I first said that and now all of them have been educated
Smells like ozone in here. Um, I would not that that's not good for you
You don't want to be breathing in ozone that a much that's not good. I
Was the uh, how do I go deeper?
Yeah, you really actually like ozone's not good for you like to breathe in just you shouldn't be
All right level eight. I'm still hearing that god-awful noise
little eight
Final floor. Okay, so there's gonna be a boss down here. Oh
Okay, I get slow
Who's eating who's eating
What was that? Oh my god, they're fucking muppet frogs. What happened? I don't even know what I'm able to add
Everybody eating. Oh my god turn the camera
Shit oh god, they're coming. Oh my god, they're coming. Oh my god
Back up back up back up back up
What the fuck were they coming from what the fuck I heard I hear the evil guy music
This way this way this way. I wait where are they?
Where are the other ones? Where are the other ones?
Stop fucking eating my friends. Oh
Shit, okay. Hold on. What the fuck come with me. All right, get him go on his butt. Well, he's got a face
He's gonna roll isn't he? He's gonna roll. He's gonna roll. He's gonna roll this guy rolls
this motherfucker rolls I
Got back up back up back up. Everyone run run run run. He rolls. I knew it
Kill these all right
Shit, okay. I'm good. All right, pull it back. Pull it back. Pull it back. Don't go that way
Alright, I got this in the bag. This is good
Sorry, we had a lot of there were a lot of casualties. That's right. He's dead right here again. Goodbye dad
I got a little shoe. That was terrifying with the little frog people
How would her stink limits?
Stench must be emanating from that object. Don't why are you still here? Did you actually eat one? You fucker?
There's still any alive. I'm so scared that they get I keep eating. I gotta follow these guys back cuz this is gonna be bad
There's definitely a couple that I didn't kill
Maybe not. All right, I think we're good. Hurry up. Well, that could have gone way worse. I think that's a success
That's a six. That's a successful cave
completion
This object is pockets of air under its surface. It is perfect for the boots. I am making
more run speed
rush boots
These nullify wind resistance by circulating air beneath the souls, okay
You'll move faster and you'll no longer be blown away by puffy blow hogs. Oh cool
It's still treasure here. No, that's not damn it
Very cool. That is it. Let's get out of here
Everyone's eating right?
It's free food you the cave at the far side of the perplexing pool
It's a fan favorite a but the far side of the perplexing pool. Well, let's see, huh?
Nothing else here. Let's go. There's the cave. That's yeah. That's a cave. I want to do. Oh, no my little bulb friends
That's unfortunate
4,000 they should be able to come with me. That's not fair. It's time. Do I have left in the day? Oh
All of Mars back. Oh, no, you're not. He's not doing that. Well, okay. Uh, I saw almost a whole day
What do I want to do? I need more blue bad. I guess we'll go get some red and finish it up with yellow
That's I don't we don't need a hundred. It's fine. We already went that way this way
There was another cave over here when they're I swear to God doesn't yeah, that's what the cave over here
I did the one that was further away
Very all of our we're not getting stuck, right? Okay. Have a burial for all of them
Come on, you can do it guys. Come on get over here. You're so slow
Treasure wait wait
Pressure somewhere up here. Hold on. Hold on. Oh
Boy
How many people do I I don't very many anything dangerous in the way or can they bring it back? What is it?
Pineapple artichoke. All right, bring the artichoke back
All right. There was I gotta be careful here. I have somebody slow Pikmin. There's a cave up this way
I haven't gone. Hold on. I completed that one. I completed that one, too. Oh
Sure, I think I did everything here. Did I complete the first actual level?
I think it's done. Wait, what about did I go in this one? No, I didn't do this one
I wonder if I should just go in here. No, no, no with I don't have Olimar
I think it's gonna end the day. I might be a coward but does that make me a coward arm for some Pikmin?
Yeah, that's true. All right, we're gonna kill we're gonna take we're gonna kill everything over here
And they're gonna have blue take everything back. Ooh, look at that. Hey purple come back. Come back. Come back
No, you could have had it. You could have killed it. Just kill it kill kill kill kill kill you had it
Okay, blue bring that back to blue. Watch out for this guy. This guy is gonna she's gonna shoot you
It's homing missile. Fuck. Okay, just
Why they're not my god don't don't ruin this
Hurry run
Hit him. Yes. Okay. We're good. Look at that double. That was completely intentional. I did that on purpose
Don't
Okay, can we please not have the red idiots pick it up purple?
Pick that up bring it back to blue
No, I fucking hate the red Pikmin. They're the worst. It's always them. They're always the one that start picking shit up
It's always them. They're always the ones to do it. Get off
Get I'm about to throw these guys in the ocean. I'm serious. Why they keep doing that. All right, everybody fuck off
That's so mean. No, it's not mean it's called get out of here. We're trying to get blue Pikmin not red Pikmin
Why is this red? I'm very upset with the red Pikmin right now
They're messing this whole thing up
Nobody touched that fucking thing. How many do I need to over there over there?
Okay, purple help. Wait, I need a blue and then I need a blue over there
Okay blue and then I need another blue from here. That's okay. That doesn't matter. You can take yellow from that
I don't care. It's all right when I'm gonna I'm gonna when I get back they I'll make sure I'll change this blue
Don't worry
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, what was that all about? There's too many people
my way
There's too many people
Please don't go this way. Why are you going over?
What happened to the other guys with the coins? They're already good. They went the long way. Did they really?
Of course they did. I'm surprised they didn't get eaten
Back here
Why did they go this way and you're gonna run right into a bunch of red Pikmin and it's gonna fuck everything up
Just everybody stay back and stay here
Why are they bringing go crush his head? Oh, no, just get it. Oh my god
He blew up into blue. I'll touch that. I don't care who gets them. Just bring him in. What about all of our?
Wait, what about all of them are I love how they go? Look at how long that's such a long way
Why'd they go that way you have to leave them?
98 99 98 99
100 you're dead. Okay, that's close
It's really fun this fun game don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't I'm gonna pee one more time
And we will continue. I'll be right back. So we're probably gonna call it here in the next 30 minutes or so
30 40 minutes, maybe something like that. I'll be enough to do another day. I like this game though
I thought I'm gonna beat this game
I think I'm pretty positive about that one or at least the I'll stream this at least one more time
I really like it. They were left to starve
It all you fan art trends in one image minus that weird German dude, you're close
I thought when I get to the end of the dead
I was like just not even like 60% of the way through the game. Well, let's go
when you're down
And I think my whatever at eight thousand
Everything has been done here besides as a cave there
Where if I what am I not done? There's two things I haven't perplexing pool
Yeah, let's go here. There's a lot more game after the debt
Well, maybe I'll just play I'll play it one more time if I don't beat it tonight, then we'll just do it again
All right. What do I want? I want
Yes, there we go. Now. I got lots of blue 30 blue
30 electric I actually need more
20 fire and then
Purple and white to fill out the rest of the party. Okay, here we go. Now. Where do I want to go?
It's pretty open right now. Did I do this cave? I didn't do this cave
What is this cave?
Citadel of spiders zero treasures in this shit. Let's go giant enemy spiders. Maybe maybe they will be all right level one
We got
Spider
Pack him get him nice cool
Leaf what does the leaf get you?
Anything buried? Oh
Pick up the leaf. I want everything I'm gonna die. Oh, there's a tomato over there. Oh, it's cuz they're flying
Okay, I see I want the tomato the tomatoes gonna be worth at least a hundred bucks guaranteed
Together annoying. All right. Did you free up the space? No, get the tomato. I want the tomato and I want everything else
Don't let me down. I won't let you down. Who is that? Who is that? The person I just what was that? Who is that?
Nope, no, no wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong. I won't let you down
No, it's and when when sorry all of you lost good and that's it. We can keep going
Continue through the spider cave level two. Come on Gwyn and I wouldn't win
Anduin come on Gwyn and when come on Gwyn win fire
New offer beat jump King DLC erase the dead. I will never open jump King ever again
Even if this new stuff on it, I promise you that I'm not gonna ever open that game again. All right, let's put out the fire
Oh shit. It's one of these guys
Those guys suck. Um
Yeah, I kind of need him to jump over here
All right, we're good
Fucka don't get burned. Okay a lot of random shit in here. Why is there a yellow guy here? Oh
Come on. Come on Gwyn
How many guys were actually here for that? Why'd I get so loud?
Run throwing him over his head kill him. Oh, he got a bottle cap. Oh
Cool and his lipstick. Go get it. You're gonna eat a whopper again. No, I'm not gonna eat a whopper
I want to eat a whopper. It wasn't that good
That's a hundred. Holy shit RC Cola. It's a good one
I think I can this little guy tonight. Is that a guy I kill that thing
RC Cola is nasty. I mean, it's just it's colo. Is that an enemy or is that a treasure? Okay, that's a treasure
Is it red? Oh, what's a little duck?
Think a little rubber ducky. Oh cool. Look at that kill
Well, that was a purple in there. I think it's pretty good haul
paradoxical enigma
Emergency emergency
Hickman are suffering if you blow your whistle. He's good. Oh my god. There's a fire over here. I
Didn't even see him. Holy shit. That was terrifying. Okay, we're good. Uh
That's it. There's nothing else here. I can just leave I don't need to kill everything. Why would I need to kill everything?
Let's go. Yeah, hun. Yeah, hun. Yeah, hun. Yeah, hun. Yeah, hun. Yeah, hun
Yeah, hun. Yeah, hun. Yeah, hun.
Level three. I missed a purple flower. Oh fuck. Oh well. I'm practicing cat boy. That's supposed to be a Pikmin
That's a bad place to start
I need uh, that's electric, right? Well didn't do very good job separating. Get over here. I'm gonna here we go
How did red even get over here?
Alright, here we go
Put him down put him down
Start killing this guy's the biggest pain in the ass. He's gotta go first kill them all. Yep. That's the plan. Yep. That's we mode
I'm so like bitter and awful like what the hell
What the why?
There's the um, there's a nectar. Oh, there it is. Okay again. Nice. We mode. Why is it doing that?
I never played Pikmin. I don't really understand what's going on. Can you explain it? Sure
So I am a guy
That landed on a planet and there's these little creatures little alien bug things called Pikmin
They're different colors and the different colors are different things. So yellow is electric red is fire blue is water
white is gas purple is super strength and
That's it and
You have to pick them you have to you have to take them and have them do various tasks
They have to pick up stuff. You have to get treasure
You have to go deep into caves and find stuff
It's pretty cool
Now, hopefully they don't okay. This is bad. And then at its timed at the end of every day
You have to run away because the monsters will come and eat you and it's fun to collect stuff you run around you just collect things
What am I doing that for? Oh, there's an egg in there. Okay. Yeah
Everybody get that bring it back to the base and then crack that away. I gotta kill everything in here first
There's a lot of treasure in this one. There's like five six hundred bucks worth of stuff in here. I'll let him slam
And what's that work a hundred?
Welcome to the jam
Everybody come up. It's time to slam now. We got the whole world watching now. Welcome to the space jam
This bit I'm worth it gonna make another one
They are I feel like they've been talking about that for the last five plus years
Are they actually gonna make it?
Why is that movie vaporware? I feel like a space jam to coming out in like 2013
And get this oh
Put him down run away run away. Come on. I need my other friends
Whatever. Yep. I'm sorry. I don't care. I do care, but I just not enough
Everybody stomping but I thought electric was your favorite. They are my favorite
Hit this thing. All right, bring it back. Nice cool. I like this any other treasures
I mean, I guess people could you guys could just get these just get them while we have a minute. It's free money
That's it right and I break that egg nice water chestnuts
Something really funny about water chestnuts. I was gonna make a tweet two days ago talking about how much I loved water chestnuts
And I only eat them like once a year. I
Was gonna tweet about my absolute love for water chestnuts. How come they're not in more stuff. I
Love the texture. I love the way they feel. I love the sound they make too
When you bite into a water chestnut, it makes this incredible noise
It's just like
It's amazing water chestnuts are gross
They are not I'm sorry. You're you've lost your mind
They're wonderful. They have that amazing texture to them. Oh, I can feel it right now like that
That's it. Let's go Luigi's Mansion
They don't have any taste well they they soak up whatever the sauce you have is
All right, this is still not the last floor. Oh, I thought that was my phone ringing
Is my phone on vibrate
Yeah, I cracked that egg we need some more food there not be spiders in here
Delish break this down. This is free treats, man. This is awesome
I've made like almost a thousand dollars in here and this is not a hard dungeon. Oh
What do I need to replace?
Blue I think I'm running out of reds. All right, let's do fire again
Wait, break this down
leg
There's so many reds in this ship
Yeah
Yeah, that's true. Okay now
Fire but kill but was nothing. What does it shoot fire?
Weird octopus thing. What does it do?
Get on his head to get on his head
Okay, I need purple purple purple day. I can't do that any purple. I don't even think about it
You get in line so I can throw purples, please
What happened to him? Oh, he ate a white Pikmin. Okay
Hey get rid of this
86 who's all right. Okay. Hey
We'll just eat a white one then kill it before I can go back in. We had something too. All right
Let's get a let's get the whole good stuff wait this fire take it out electricity. What are you doing?
What is behind here another treasure? Oh nice. Yeah, it is
15 or oh, it's a chocolate little chocolate. That's cool
One match come on
Bowser's on there. I was her matches
This was the Flintstones did cigarette commercials. I know get that is that the end of the treasure?
Let's find out I think it is
See is it gonna be a six-hour stream? Probably not after I clean this up. I'm gonna get to the final floor here
I'm probably gonna call it. Is there more treasure? Oh
Shit. Oh, it's a little dog. That's cute
time capsule a
Real picture of a dog treasure done. All right, cool. Let's move so I will be live next
I'm
Break Andy coming up
So there there's a couple of streams that need a lot of work done on them and they're currently being worked on the
Archaeologist stream is gonna be the 6th of March gonna be a lots of crazy shit. Hope to see you there
But I'm not going away. I'm not gonna go for that one
You'll see me in probably three days
So what's today Sunday Monday Tuesday Wednesday? See the Wednesday or Thursday or Thursday?
I'll see you guys on Thursday. Let's make it easy
Final floor here we go. Is there a boss on every final floor of a cave or no?
Something's over here. Hmm. Where is it? I wanted the nectar. I just wanted the nectar. Do we have everybody?
Alright, what does he do? I'm assuming gonna grab him right in the belly. I missed run
There yeah, you gotta grab him the stock that's kind of hard to grab back up
Shit
Grab on no go get her his leg. You guys are stupid
Why can't they grab him? I'm just gonna throw yellow
Got it, and he dropped a key a key to what door
Sweet victory that giant insects body has crumbled to dust. I'm quite relieved to know I won't have to store such an enormous bug
Analyzing soil samples anomaly detected. What's that glittering widget?
That's a little Mario key. We're gonna get it. There's another treasure over here somewhere. I could dig it out
Take up here. Maybe
treasure no treasure a
$100 my wrists are my elbows are so red familiar. I'll combine it with the president's parallel dimension controller. What does it do?
massive dimensional shift at a distant location
Receiving a message from a far-flung dimension
Challenge mode can now be accessed from the title screen. It appears to be total gibberish. Oh
New game mode. I will name this worthless device the key. We're ready to get up there and help dig
Be useful for god's sakes. Oh, it's a diamond nice now. There's is that in it's probably it
Let's just make sure that's pretty good regal diamond. Is there more? That's it
Let's escape. That's fun. I
Made up with almost a thousand bucks
Cool
Think I still have a little bit of a day left here. I do I have a whole day
So I've got a whole day left. Is there anything I can let me just look around for hidden stuff
Do I need blue go to the castle or the submerged castle? Oh, let's see if I can find it
submerged castle they don't this way
I'm gonna say I just gonna take blue everybody hang out here. Well, you know, just kill these guys first
We already died. All right blue. What's over here any treasures?
Electricity, how do I get over that? I do have to throw them from here. How would I do that?
Stop doing that. How do I get electric? I've got to drain this. Oh, what is that? Is that a treasure?
It's what is that a stingray or a treasure? I don't know what that is
Guys, you didn't walk up here with us
Really? I get over here
Help out. This is why I didn't bring anybody but blue. This was been a disaster. Oh
Electric can take that down
Perfect. Cool. All right, let's go get yellow. This is gonna be really hard to bring everybody over here
Missing a lot of people
Well, let's hope I don't get every yellow killed. Stay away from us. No, come back. Come on. Come on. Come on, please
You can make it you can make it you can make it you can make it you can make it
Are you supposed to fucking do that? How are you supposed to actually do that? They're so stupid
They just run randomly in random directions
It's so dumb. It's not even possible
Get over there. Oh my fucking god. You are so stupid. I hate you. The yellow ones are the worst
They're stupider than the red ones and they're slow. Get over here. I'm fucking actually pissed. Yes
I killed like 30
Yellow Pikmin I killed 30 of them. It was horrible and I'm pissed off about it. What is over here?
Um, I can only go in there with blue. This is a blue only level. Oh shit. Well, we'll be doing that next time
He's gonna kill so many on the way back
Shoot oh crap as long as they do it
Is there any just treasure chest in the hair down here or anything on the ledge? What about it?
Well this thing I think it has killed somebody you kidding me. You did it. All right good for you
Now ready to get back here. Okay now follow me down here this way. What are you doing down here?
Get out here. Stop following me down here. You're gone. Keep going. You did it. How do I get them?
They're one way ramp. What did I do that for? That's to get them on the other side. Okay
Well, the sun's going down. So let's just go ahead and pick everybody up
Missing somebody who the bridge behind me a large rock sits in a reservoir of water. Oh, I thought that was a cave
You've been caught. I thought that was a cave to face the dangers ahead
You must be free of the shackles of a boss worker relationship
Learn to you see to separate and yeah, whatever. Oh, well, let's I need blue get over there. He's fighting
Somebody's just been fighting this whole time. I
Think that just go get this where are they there it goes? All right, and that drains the water. Oh, all right
I thought it was just a cave. Okay
Now can I how do I get out of here? Okay, can I that weird frog?
Shellfish thing in the middle. Yeah this thing. Let's kill this now. I
Have enough time to get this whatever that is. Oh fuck right. I forgot about these guys. All right, let's uh, let's kill this thing
What's going on? Oh shit 10. Oh, he got something. All right. All right, get it. I don't have time
Just pick it up pick up everything. I don't care where it goes. We gotta hurry up. Oh go go go go go go. Hurry
Hurry, save them save them. I will I will don't worry the yellows deals are fine. I'm good. I'm good. Don't worry
I got it. I got it. I got it
Come come come come come come come come come come
Nobody's left doesn't hurt. Okay, go go go go go 95
We're the last five. We're the last five Oh in the drain stop fighting and get over here guys
Yep, you're too stupid to follow me. Okay, I don't care 100 cut
Don't move one of the blue ones is it who just couldn't figure out how to walk up the goddamn stairs
That doesn't matter, whatever. We're good. I tried
I went back twice, and he just like I'm walking to wall. I don't know not my fault. I went back for him
All right, I'm gonna call over tonight. I will be back on Thursday
I'll probably have some more updates for you guys
Thursday's plan is we're gonna beat Pikmin and then depending that probably is only gonna take like another hour or two
Maybe
We'll move on to something else after Pikmin. That's the plan
I am have to assume that to get to 10,000 and to do some of the late game stuff
Probably another couple hours two three hours, and who knows maybe it just we finish Pikmin and do a whole stream on it
We'll see it's really fun. I'm really into it
All the more you'll soon be promoted to manager only a small bit of debt remains. You've done great, so we'll see you on Thursday
Thursday around
Two o'clock Pacific 2 p.m. Pacific time. We'll see you then. Thanks for joining me as always see you soon
I love Pikmin big fan really big fan
Thanks to the subs everybody there were a lot of community subs for a joke, but even still that's a lot
Thank you guys. Hope you had fun. Oh, yeah, I said ayaya. Yeah, that's right
I did a few times more than once. It was at least a few times. He was so drunk
Now we'll see you on Wednesday. I mean don't say that on Thursday. Don't get it wrong
No Thursday not Wednesday was streaming on Thursday at 2 p.m. Pacific. I'm gonna dump you guys on italics today
I say hello to italics to see what he's doing. What is he doing Valheim? What is Valheim? It's a survival game
Okay, well his Alex hates us. Well, I don't know. Maybe it's like bullying people into singing
Hey, you gotta get you we have a better reputation for you guys
One of these days somebody's gonna shut you guys down and be like I ain't singing like fuck off
And then you're gonna feel real bad. You're gonna be like, oh shit. He was pissed. I'll see you guys on Thursday
Good night. Take care of yourselves
It's already happened. I've probably I don't know that I doubt if I was a streamer
I'd be like, I don't know. I'm not singing for this random dude. Good night guys. Take care of yourselves. Go say hello to italics