Hey, I was checking on you. How are you? How are you? Good to see you.
I'm dry. My hair's a little wet. In the shower. I had to take a shower and I just didn't.
Oh, I'm clean now. Clean Andy. Prove it. You got to prove it.
Okay. I'll prove it. In a minute. Did you get stuck in the drain?
Obviously not because I'm here. I did actually. My toe got stuck.
He's lying. I'm not lying. You'll see my wet hair in a second. I'm not doing face cam today.
Maybe I will. I got a coffee too. We can go over a few things today. Let me tweet this. I'll be
right back. All right. I didn't tweet yet. I have to send a message. Let me send a message. Okay.
A rank today. That's exactly what we're doing. I'm going to try to get to A rank with Cosmic
Calamity. If you don't know who Cosmic Calamity is. I've been living under a rock.
Biggest superstar in the monster fighting leagues. Okay. Let me just put my Twitch here.
Yeah. I had to take a shower. I was feeling very icky. Okay. All right. I'm ready. No more stalling.
How are you? Let's move over here. Maybe I'll stall for a little bit. Just a minute here because
I have to explain a few things. So this week, we got some interesting things to do.
If you missed the stream from a couple days ago, I would suggest you go watch it. It was a fun time.
I was on Ms. Kiff's stream doing parasocial. It was a good time. That was Monday. Today we're
going to do Monster Rancher 2. And then from Monster Rancher 2, we're going to go to Monster
Rancher 2 and hopefully beat this game real soon. Hoping to. Like I told you, I'm not going to stop
streaming this game until we at least get to S rank with somebody. After this stream, we're going
to get the You Laugh, You Lose stuff ready and the Baby Sensory stuff because that's where we're
going to take an entire stream. So that will be Tuesday the 21st. I have to come up with some
incentives. I don't want it to be like, oh, if I laugh, I lost. I think this should be some
interesting incentive. Yeah. What do we get if you laugh? Exactly what I'm saying. Well, you just
lose. Well, yeah, you just lose. But I want it to be something to do. You give subs. Yeah, that's
I could do that. I think there's other ones too that could be fun. Okay. I saw you said ice that
motherfucker. You're talking about this. Talking about this character. What I thought you were
saying is pour ice down your pants. If I laugh, that's a good do that possible. You laugh,
you pour ice down your pants. I fucking spilled already in even 10 minutes. God damn it.
This is why I have an AI. This is why I just have to only use Amazon Basics keyboards
only. They're never I can never have anything remotely valuable underneath me in this room.
Ever. You know, you see those streamer setups that they look amazing. There's all those cool
swirling lights and there's awesome pristine keyboards and they've got so much cool shit.
They have so much wire control. No, I will break that stuff. I will ruin it.
Coffee is underneath the space bar now and I can't get it. I need a paper towel. Hold on.
Give me one second. All right. Hello. You do that thing where you bunch up a piece of toilet paper
or paper towel and you slide it under. I'm picking a lock. You have to slide it long ways
underneath the keys and like tilt it around. I'll break it if I pop it off.
Will I break it? Let me see. Have you voted in the awards? I mean, the voting is not open yet.
Hopefully that's not a problem. I just pulled the space bar off. Is that a problem?
Oh no. All right. I can get under here though. Oh, what the what else is under here?
I feel like I just lifted up the couch. Oh, oh, that's what it looks like under there.
Cover it back up. All right. Let's go. Shit. I didn't put it on right. I put it on upside down.
I don't care. I don't care. I'll fix it later. All right. Let's do it. Welcome back, everybody.
We're doing vigorous training. You want to just prove that? Okay, I'll prove it.
Okay. There you go. See? Prove that I was just in the shower. There it is.
No more face cam. Not today. You're looking, you're looking nice and slick. Hey, nice.
Oh, yeah. The you laugh, you lose stuff. I've never done it before. I can't believe I've gone
10 plus years across YouTube and Twitch and I've never done it. I have no idea what's going to
happen. Why have I not? I don't know. I just haven't. There's never was, there's never reason
for me to do it. It's because it's lazy content. I think it's fun. Look, something can be lazy
content and be really fun to do. It's all right. All right. So what does the schedule look like?
First of all, hey, welcome again. Thanks for coming by the stream. Let's go. Put the cam back on.
All right. I'll put the cam back on for, there is something else I want to address that I thought
was hilarious, but I want to wait till a lot of people are here because it's one of the funniest
fucking things I've seen in like at least a month. So we need to wait. I want to wait till everyone
gets here. All right. Last thing I did is I beat C rank. So we're going to take this guy, do some
training. Wait, what is the actual, let me see the data. 621 intelligence. 8K is not enough.
8K isn't enough. Well, I'm not saying it's not enough. I'm just saying it has to wait. Give me
like 30 or 40 minutes so everyone that wants to be here is here. So I want to get to like probably
700 intelligence and like three or 400 skill. The only way this thing is ever going to be worth
using is just by being a glass cannon. That's it. So we're doing the same thing we did before.
Get them in there. Start with the, not power. Intelligence and skill. Meditate. Go for it.
This is the worst monster in the game, Jeremy. You need to let it go. I think I can get this guy to A
rank. I really do. Needs more life. All right. You see him well. How am I still soft? B. All right.
When's the actual official B tournament? Right here. All right. I got a little while. I got some time.
Okay. You guys ready? Are you guys ready to hear like one of the funniest things I've fucking seen
all week? So somebody in the discord had a little bit of a problem. Just a small problem. And they
brought it to the discord's attention. And I, my stomach hurt from laughing at this picture. So
why don't we take a look and see what happened? So this is what they posted.
I'm actually going to turn the game capture off for a second. So, uh,
jazzy ball has a little story for us and it goes something like this. So I'm home for the holidays
from college and I decided to watch some germ of vids on my parents' big TV because I was bored.
Okay. We've established what's going on. So I microwave some pizza and turn it onto this
compilation of edits of Jerma's faces. When it gets to this face, however, the TV froze.
So I tried turning it on and off to restart it, but the TV just won't turn off. And it's stuck
on this fucked up image of Jerma's face. Okay. I don't know how that happened. A couple hours
pass and I don't know why it took me a while, but I finally decided to unplug the TV. And then I
realized that the face is permanently burned onto the screen. Like it's just stuck there.
My parents aren't back until later in the night. So now I'm freaking out trying to cover the screen
so that they don't see the stupid face burned onto their thousand dollar TV. What do I do?
I don't even understand. Green burn-in? How long does screen burn-in last? People are saying fake,
but I mean, it looks kind of real. The screen burn-ins for OLEDs can be permanent.
No, it's not. Okay. That's insane if it is. It's fucked up forever. So what do you do?
OLED, it can be permanent. Okay. Well, here's what we need. This is very important. 24 hours from now,
I need an update or even now, like even like a like six to 12, you know, hours from now.
I want to see the improvement. Imagine coming home and this is what you see on the TV.
But you were asking, how do you, what do you do about this? I don't know. You can't just
throw a blanket on this. I mean, why is there a blanket on the TV? What are you going to have
to just come clean and say, I don't know what happened. I left this face on here, pay them back,
replace the TV. It's your fault. You need to replace the TV. I didn't do anything. It's my
fault. You have to replace it. I didn't sell the TV to this person. You, you psycho. You destroyed
somebody's TV. So that's what, okay. According to what they said, this is what it looks like when
the TV is unplugged. Buy the TV from them. All right. I'll tell you if it's permanent. Thanks a
lot, dude. Now this is burned into my monitor. Just have a screensaver. How is it emitting
blue light if it's unplugged? Oh, it's not unplugged. That's okay. I see. I see. But that's
just what it looks like when it's turned on. Okay. We need an update. Replace it. Replace the TV.
Can you imagine? Like just, I get him in touch with community Jake. It's just like, let's get,
let's get, let's get this person a new TV. It's your fault. I love that though. That's so funny.
We need an update. Buy this TV and put it in your house. They're very active on discord right now.
It's too funny. Put it up on the Reddit shelf. Yeah. Maybe if that's actually real, that's too
funny. Maybe we'll have to get you in touch with community Jake. Let's see. Uh, see what we can do
for you. Cause that's absolutely hysterical that you like are going to get like in trouble. Put it
up as a third monitor. There's no way the burning happens like that permanently. I don't know. It's
really funny. Regardless. It looks real to me. Use your head German. It's not real. It's funny
though. You're going to get scammed. I didn't say this was going to happen. I just said we need,
we need some extra evidence and some extra proof that it was real. I need to write this down. Note
funny equals real. I didn't say funny. I said we need a little more evidence. Okay. We need to do
some more training as he didn't do it last time. Don't fail it again, please. All right. Good.
Even if it's fake, the idea is really funny. Yeah. All right. The image view naked on stream
is burned into my monitor. What should I do? Now let me be very clear about this. Very clear.
This is a, this is funny. There's a funny little thing that happened. I, I ain't replacing all your
TVs. Okay. If you go buy an OLED TV today and deliberately burn an image of my face on it,
I ain't fucking replacing it. I just, let's be very clear about this. You're doing it on your
own free will. I have nothing to do with that. I'm going to make that very clear in before the
wave of OLED TV burning images that like, dude, I fucking left the TV on and it burned an image
of you and oh my God, what do I do about it? Help me. I'm sorry. Not happening. Oh, it's,
it's calamity's birthday. Yeah. So if you want to do that, that's up to you. I got nothing to do
with it. I got a lot of money. How old is Cosmic Andy? Cosmic Andy is two years old at this point
now. My dad saw a video of yours. He had a heart attack. You owe, no, no, we're not going down
this road. Not going down this road today. Now let's get three mint leaves and let's get three
nuts oil. Oh, I can only hold two. Okay. Fine. Okay. Uh, I actually am going to, no, I won't do
nuts oil and we're going to do normal skill training. How does it feel to be a permanent
screen saver skill? Let's go. I'm doing this in the wrong order. Okay. I got to, I'll fix it next
week. Remember there's a lack of, there's a lack of worst hair nominees. I don't think that just
means my hair looks better this year. I need to do 50 beam usages. All right. Keep counting. And
we have to do the mint leaf. I wonder when we're going to get, when is he going to get too old?
Hey Yorn, thanks for the five. Give me it to yourselves. He's on death store now. No, he's not.
He's got like at least not a year or two. This monster has one of the longest lifespans. Exactly.
Don't tell me that it, that he's going to die. Won't be able to handle it. It's literally just
a wall dude. It's going to live a long time. It might. Tablets training. It's got a normal
lifespan of 410 game weeks. Oh nice. Aaron tree. Okay. So if this is Aaron tree,
all right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Good, good, good. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Stressed out. I know. I know. I know. I know. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got a bunch of dumb items. What is all this shit? Ooh, just eat this. Is this the new release? It
is. This game is currently on steam right now. It's a bundle of the first and second game. You
get them both. Uh, they are, and there it's also on iOS too right now, I think, which is amazing.
And it's on the switch. God, I hope they make another one. Like just make another monster
rancher. I know it sucks because they need like, they need like 10 million people to buy this game
to make it worth doing another one. I don't know if it's going to happen. Whatever number they need
to hit. I hope they hit because I would really love a new generation monster rancher video game.
All right. I need to buy much more of this stuff. Actually, hold on. I can sell this crap too. Can
I? Stimulate a monster's abilities. Can you get banned for doing these drugs? This will temporarily
stimulate a monster's abilities. What does it do? Yeah. All right. Well, I'm going to sell some of
this stuff. The magic banana. I'm just going to sell it. I don't want to use it unless maybe I
should just use it. We have at least two or three monster rancher lore masters. It's going to reduce
your lifespan. Don't use it. Okay. All right. All right. Okay. All right. I'll just sell it.
I need to make room for leaves and, you know, sell the mango. I don't want it. Sell the banana.
I don't want it. I don't even know what it does. I think it reduces lifespan. 500 for this. Holy
shit. All right. That's pretty good. I'm going to keep the disc chips because you can combine them,
right? And when you actually combine monsters. All right. Now we need at least two more mint
leaves and four more nuts oils while the sale is here. Okay. Five, four. I'm about to use one of
these anyways. So, all right. Okay. I had a dream that you were streaming yourself cutting
stirs breaks. Why? Okay. I'm going to rest because I need to kind of reset this. Wow. What kind of
dream is that? Cutting his breaks? All right. Well, let's do nuts oil. Let's do this right.
Mint leaf. Regular training. Nuts oil. Heavy training. I'm going to go take a nap. Dermot,
can you wake me up in a couple of hours? In two hours, I'll make sure to scream really,
really loud and just make sure you have your headphones on. Wait. Yes. Right. What a scream
timer. I'm not, that doesn't seem to be a screen timer. All right. Give us a big value here. Is
it cheating? That's cheating. Whatever. 700 intelligence should be enough to be able to
at least beat a rank. How long is the stream going to be? I don't know. So don't have fun.
Do defense. I think it's too late to do defense. It's too late. I think we need to be able to
one hit anti people. Defense is worthless. I think they've changed a bunch of stuff in the game
or not change, but patched old broken shit that doesn't work anymore. Right. There was a bunch
of bugs in the original game that they just fixed. And I think it made some of the things
more valuable. At what point is the magic slab smarter than you? Probably now. I don't,
it's out of a thousand. So I wonder what my monster sheet would look like.
Okay. So if it's out of a thousand, my monster sheet definitely looks like this.
Life is probably one 20 power, like one 41, like 50, like here intelligence, probably like 240.
So like down here skill, I'm putting up to like seven or 800, like here speed is probably like
one 40 and defense is zero. What do you mean? What fame is zero. That's not accurate.
Fame would be 30. All right. Who would, okay. At our peaks right now,
German nine, eight, five, or this slab in this game's universe, who is more popular
with the 18 to 35 demographic? I gotta make that very, very, very clear. No, I don't think so.
I think it's me. I think, I think I would be more popular. All right. Well, I, yeah, all those would
be pretty bad. So the last thing we did was, what did I eat? I, I such a stupid attention span.
It was, what was the last thing that I just did or the last thing I clicked on? Cause I need to
give a, you didn't do anything yet, but what was the last thing I did? I gave tablets. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. All right. Big success. Do it. Good. 656 intelligence
in there. When is the tournament? I think it's coming up soon in like a week or two.
I wonder if I can handle it. So I can do skill rest and then we'll, we'll go in for B cup.
I could get skill over 300, which would be big. Good. Excellent. I don't have that image anymore.
There we go. You want to peep the horror here. It's an old ass clock too. I like that clock.
I didn't even see that clock. That clock's awesome. All right. Rest up for the battle.
See if I can handle B rank. If, if, if this, this is a rank, if I beat this, I'll get to a rank.
What time is it on that clock? It is six, six, like six, like 17, six 18. I win.
You're in pretty good shape. It's very well. All right, let's do it. I hope I can handle this.
B rank. This is the big one. This is a huge deal. Official B rank cup. Let's go. I'm actually kind
of scared because we've not seen any of these people here. All right. Go. What is with it?
What's this defense? Oh, you're dead though, because that doesn't matter for intelligence.
It's over. Let's go. You know what to do. Stay back. Bye. Let's get this B rank, A rank today.
Get all the defense in the wrong places. People were not feeling this strategy before,
but here's where this all falls apart. If there's another really high intelligence,
high speed monster, that's the hard, complete hard opposite. That's like paper versus rock.
I absolutely lose that. So we just hope that's not anybody here. Whoa, look at that thing. I
think it was like a weird dinosaur wall versus wall. That wall does maybe that wall is power.
All right. I was actually really scared before. Now I think I'm all right.
Look like, like, like, like, like the bunny. I'll be high speed. This is still fine.
I just have to hit you once. I don't have to care about anything else. We can throw coins in the
air. All right. I do have to worry about that power though. That's a lot. I have no defense.
We just stay back. 46% throw the coin in the air. We went if I miss it's over because I can't take
more than one hit. I don't think or two hits total. I don't like Cosmic Andy. Well, Cosmic
Andy is probably going to be dead. If I've been within the next, like one stream hour. So the
whole point is to get Cosmic Andy. I just keep forgetting their name up to a rank. So we unlock
the other monster types that we can unlock from the CD stuff. It looks like they're going to do
what they're supposed to do. As long as we beat B rank, we get access to like, I think five or
six more breeds. That's good. All right. Wall versus wall. What do you got? All right. That's
speed. How do you even have speed that low? You built your character like a moron to spread out.
It's over. I went way too spread out. See you later. Hey, it's worked every time so far.
People, I don't know if I would vote against this right now. That's a bad idea. Remember,
there are some unlockable monsters that you can get by beating a D rank battle at a specific time.
Really? I actually might be able to beat a rank with this monster and that just opens up the flood
gates. What if you miss? Then I lose. But it looks like statistics are on our side today.
The official a rank match is way harder. I'm going to assume that this is not going to be the
character that I beat a rank with. I just wanted to get to a rank with this character because then
we can unlock some more stuff, do some combinations, have maybe some higher base stat monsters and go
from there. All right. Epsilon. It's like a robot. This looks like a rare monster. Very spread out.
I think I still, I just have to, I don't know if I'll one hit kill. That's a lot of speed.
All right. I'm kind of scared. A lot of speed. Oh, it's over. It's actually over. If you missed
the first shot, it's over. Oh, no, it's not. No, it's not. No, it's not. No, it's not. I
can do it again. Hold on. Hold on. Yes. Different move. Okay. It's almost mathematically impossible
for me to lose the Hirate who needs to lose one more time. And I actually know I have to
win my next two. Okay. I destroyed Pirate though. That's the competition right now.
That wall has 25 speed. It means you're going to get hit by every single attack.
Nothing will miss you. All right. Sanjuras. This is the weird like sun one, right? I kind of want
one of these. That's so cool. Oh, oh shit. Okay. Hold on. I still think I'm okay.
The speed and the life I'm concerned about, but all we have to do is flip a coin
and percentages here. I knew it. I knew that just dumping every training regimen into
intelligence was the right call. I'm getting great coin flips though. I've only lost one coin flip
out of probably seven or eight times. Somebody said I'm missing a doctor's appointment for this.
No, go to your doctor's appointment. Trust me. You'll be pissed in a few days because whatever's
wrong, you're going to look back and be like, I fucking had an opportunity to go.
Trust me. Too late. I already missed it. Oh, I'll watch the stream in the waiting room. All right.
Robe Neil. Robe Neil has not been doing very well. I don't know why. Stats are pretty good.
Really high health. What's the problem here? Just too spread out. Oh, it ain't my fucking problem.
It's taking fucking cemetery. Oh, oh, I can't go backwards. I just had to hit you once. Come
here. Back it up. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. What? Shit. Okay. Holy shit. That's the four
in a row that I've missed. All right. It doesn't matter. I just hit one. Back it up. Back it up.
Oh, you piece of shit. I'll be able to do one more. I need 24 guts. Come on. 22, 23, 24.
I lost. I lost. I actually lost. Well, here comes all the coin flips I'm going to lose in a row.
60% lost it seven or six or seven times in a row. I still win. Who has one loss?
Okay. Pyriteu is the only one that has two losses. If they lose the next match, I clenched it.
Yeah. Pyriteu just has to lose. All right. Who's Pyriteu going against?
Uh-huh. All right. I just can't lose this. I either can't lose this or Pyriteu has to lose
the next match. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Yikes. Okay. I just have to get a hit
off first. Oh shit. It's Jerma. Right? Because that's exactly what I said my stats would look
like. I don't have wings. Coin flip. Not yet though. I just pissed him off.
Clenched it. All right. We got it. I just unlocked like a bunch of breeds. I love this game. This
game is so much fun. It really is. Rank alone doesn't unlock breeds. They have very cryptic
unlocks. Yeah. I know that there's probably like a more than a dozen breeds that you
have to do specific things for. But once you get to rank four, doesn't that unlock?
Four or five different breeds? Getting to that trainer rank four. No? Are you sure? I thought
it did. I guess it doesn't unlock shit. It doesn't? I thought it did. It unlocks a tournament that you
have to attend. Oh. It's something very specific for everyone. All right. Is there a good unlock
guide? I know there's a good website. What's it called? The Legend Cup, right? Isn't that a
good place to do it? Monster Rush to unlocking guide for all 38 breeds. Holy shit. There are
38 other breeds to unlock. Wow. All right. Let's go through this. I'm at 100 fame.
Okay. Some of them are locked behind errand trees. I'm a cryptic as hell.
Ooh, look at that increase. That's good. Okay. Achieve breeder rank of four, beat B rank,
and you need to purchase the first house upgrade. What the fuck? Okay. Hold on a minute. This is
ridiculous. If you have 17,000 gold or more on May 4th, Vinto will arrive and upgrade your
stable for 15,000 gold. This will unlock these two. Wait, I have to have a certain amount of
money on one day? Oh, okay. Okay. One of these is I have to achieve a rank four breeder and then
have to finish the expedition at Correa. So you have to send somebody that's at least B rank to
do the heavy errand tree, which is the Mandy desert between the months of March and August.
If the monster is uninjured, it will return with a spear. Your monster and the centaur will fight.
This will take an entire week. So you'll lose lifespan afterwards. You may use the
spear and combining to unlock the centaur. There's no particular penalty. What the fuck is all this?
All right. So, um, cool. Very cool. You did a great job. Oh, this is kind of spoilery.
Maybe I shouldn't be reading this. I want a silk cloth. Yeah, sure. Whatever.
Some of these are spoilery and some of these are literally impossible unless I did it step by step.
What are some of the easier ones? You must be on the ranch one week, four of May to trigger events.
Okay. The Fimba versus IMA is every four years. Centaur is really easy to get.
Hello. It's an express mail from IMA. Oh, here we go. This is us being ranked four. Nice.
The expedition ones are pretty straightforward. I'll do those ones first. These other ones seem
kind of confusing. All right. We're ranked four. Cool. Why are you playing with a Minecraft block?
That Minecraft block is one hit killing every single monster. So I need to get, I need to
purchase a house upgrade. Remember for expeditions, you'll need to have your monster to have high
life and high fame. He's at a hundred fame right now. Okay. So I need to, how do I get the first
house upgrade? It's January, January, February. When, when do I get to do this? His life stats
really low. You need high strength life and intelligence. I'm supposed to do that. I have
lots of money and just wait. Okay. So let's keep the training going then. I might be able to do
a rank next time. When's the next day? Wednesday. This one's four grand. All right. Here we go.
The official A cup is in a couple of months. You should have a separate expedition monster.
All right. I love this. This is so much fun. Okay. Did I just start banking money? I mean,
do I just rest and then just do this and just bank money to make sure I can afford the house
upgrade? All right. Let's do that. Let's go wipe the floor with everybody in B rank.
They're a bunch of, they're a bunch of shitties. They never, what? They're never going to make it.
Just go there and fucking wipe the floor with them. Here we go. This is for just four grand.
This is quick too. This is a lower grade tourney. What? Your monster's fame will drop. Will it?
Maybe I shouldn't do this. Nevermind. Who cares? Make the money. Just do it. All right. Let's do
it. I don't care. I need money. Oh, the serious cup smurfing. I got to try to get to at least 10
to 20,000. Then that makes the next monster so much easier to train. I don't have to worry
about anything. I would kill about these guys in one hit. We're fine. Give me that money.
You're going back to middle school to beat up children. That's not accurate. Going back to
middle school to beat up children would be doing E rank or D rank. This is B rank. These are grownups.
Not as good as me. This is kind of unfair. You basically just made a gun.
What is that move that they have? What's that? What's that like Verizon tower signal?
What does that move do? It's a 5G move. And what's the T-Mobile data thing do?
This one was quick. Called Soundwave. It has an S rank hit rate, but it's weak.
I actually might want that. Because if you miss, then it sucks. Being able to guarantee
a hit at least to have some damage. Oh, confused. It would have been scary if I didn't have
high intelligence. All right. This is easy money. This is easy money for you guys, too. I imagine
some of you guys, I don't know. Yeah. Five and a half million versus 150K.
I mean, 150K, I'm looking for the huge payout, but I don't think that's going to happen.
4,500 bucks. Don't drop by that much, right? Okay. I'm going to keep doing B ranks. Especially the
four monster ones. And I keep getting bonuses and shit. This is awesome. I want polish. Finally
got over 10 grand. Yeah, fine. I need 15 grand, you said, right? What? 20 grand? What's the next
one? Free for all elimination. Can I hang here? Do you think I could do it? Or is it going to be
way too hard? Probably not. Okay. Is this one here? Ooh, five grand and only four entries in its B.
Perfect. All right. Let's rest. Heavy train. Oh no. Fuck it. Why? Heavy train. Who needs to sleep
when you do this? Remember my wife is divorcing me because I lost all my channel points because
of Cosmic Andy. What the fuck? Very, very weird thing to be divorced for. I feel like there's
more going on. I don't think it's, I don't think it's just the fact that Cosmic Andy lost your
channel point. Okay. Let's go. He was joking. How am I supposed to know that? No, it's all right.
You're well. That's fine. Let's go ahead and do the mint leaf for your stretch. Please throw the next
fight so we can get a huge payout on people that are doubters. Eh, I want the money. Sorry. All right,
I got this week and the next week. So we'll do another big training and then we'll rest and not
no. Yeah. Don't fail it again. Really? Well, now it's a rest week. Tablets. Just do the A tournament.
Somebody said that the A tournament might be way too difficult right now. You're ignoring chat.
Why do you think I read chat? I don't even look. I have not looked at the chat in probably like
two or three years streaming. I don't even look. I just kind of guess what you guys might be talking
about. And then I just kind of blend in. All right, we need to rest. We're just going for A.
Let's go. I don't even care. Train a shitload and we're going right to A. Rest up. Let's go.
All right, come on. Let's see it. Train. Get over 700 intelligence. Nice. The A tournament will be
too late for the house upgrade as I've understood it. You have to have the money by the first week
of March. Level down defense shit. Don't I have the money though? Everywhere. First week of March.
I have 10 grand. Isn't it like, isn't this two upgrades? I don't have the first one.
It's 15. I don't have the first upgrade. It's May for the first one. Is this this two upgrades?
There's a house upgrade and a stable upgrade. It's May 4th. First one is 15k. May not March.
Oh, okay. Well, I think I'm all right. Yeah, I'm good. I need a press release. It's guilt.
You need 7k for the first one. Okay, I have that. Press release? No, I said stress relief.
Ah, shit. We got to do a press release. I got to do a press release. Cosmic Calamity. I got to be
Cosmic Calamity's PR person. Comes a bit. No, not really. Great. Yes. Come on. Well, that's good
enough. I need a face cam. I don't need a face cam. You know exactly what I look like. No, you don't
have to count my nose hairs. You know how what my face looks like right now. I want the stress
reduction. Official tournaments at the end of the month. Okay, keep going. I need items. All right.
Make sure I have over $7,000 though. I might actually be getting to the end of the training
regimen. My understanding here, this is accurate. Eventually they stop getting like really even
worth training stat increases. They're like less than two or three of them like per stat increase.
It's no longer. Oh, plus 10 plus 20 stats. It's like plus three. So probably getting close. Maybe
this one or two more weeks. Yeah, definitely falling out of prime at this point. Heard about
you from Reddit. Everybody hears about me from every place that I don't participate in. Let's
do a big one. I close my eyes every time you do a face cam. It's probably a post-it note on your
screen where the face cam is. 700 intelligence finally got it. Yes. Now I can beat a rank. I can
just laser beam just lightning melt everybody. You don't participate in Reddit. I read it sometimes.
I'm not an active participator in Reddit though. 20 weeks we got. We got this one.
This is a skill. Skill. Rest. A. Nice. 350 or so. All right. Good. Rest. A rank. That's what this,
I made this title. The title says A rank. So I better beat it. Let me save the game in case
I get instantly killed and died. You know what I mean? Whoa. What happened? Oh, oops. This is
the big one. I've never done this before. I've, I've, I used to play this game when I was like 16.
I never got this far. Played this game again a few years ago. Did not get this far. See if I can do
this. You could do an air entry and get the sound wave. It's a hundred percent chance at this point.
Oh, I'm kind of nervous. Kaplan. Kaplan. What is that? Okay. Whoa. 585 speed. Oh god. Only
200. Okay. I'm never going to hit this thing. Can I even hit this? Oh, I hit you. Oh, I got an onion.
Oh, an onion ring. I blew his head off. I blew his head off. What the fuck? Oh my god. The force
buying that one. 30% chance. I had to hit that arrow. It was over. By the way, uh, I'm probably
going to lose this tournament because we're not going to get lucky again like that. That was a
pog moment, but minus two. I know. I just, it's, I heard the exact same sound. It was that like,
I have to fight a dragon. Oh boy. These are all pretty rare monsters. It seems. Dragon. I'm scared.
Oh my god. 600 power, 600 intelligence. How do you even do that? How do you have that much
training time to get it there? I think this is a loss. Let's have faith though. Have faith,
have faith, have faith. Don't let him get up. Do it again. Have faith, have faith. I just beat
this motherfucker. I just killed him. That was the guy to beat right there and I just won.
Nothing can stop the laser beam. Those were low percentage chances too. Although I don't know.
Some of these other things could be high, high intelligence, high power. That was the worst
possible thing. That dragon just had to do one move and I lose. I'm surprised he's not playing
the monster rancher DX. This is, this is monster rancher DX. This is the one that just came up.
Team wall. Yeah. All right. Arculon. This is also 2-0. Arculon. You got a cool name too.
Wait, this is a robot scorpion hybrid? That thing is awesome. All right. But it's just no match
for the flip a coin and you die. Oh, I can do the same thing. You know, you know, I can do the same
thing. It's over. It's over. Shit. Oh, okay. It's still winnable. It is as long as Arculon loses
once. Okay. More. The dragon won. I'm not the only person that beat the dragon. Just by sheer luck.
Okay. Lamb sweet. This is a must win scenario here. That speed. This is a must win. Come on.
Let's go flip the coin. Boy. Oh no. No. We just got lucky on the first two.
Most people have lost twice. This is not over yet. All right. Arculon needs to lose. All right.
Okay. It's still doable. All right. Sharkin has not won a single match. So I'm not that concerned.
How? 60% chance. Let's go. You got that off first. Are you shitting me? You fucking piece of crap.
Are you kidding me? You saw I was spamming it. Give me a break. I'm sitting here spamming the
button. Yeah, it's over. I'm just going to reload the save. Through that. I'm reloading the save.
Okay. If I don't get any prize money, I'm reloading the save. That's not even the move I wanted to do.
Oh shit. Fuck. I'm reloading. I'm done. I just wanted to see if I could do A rank. This doesn't
even count. Like I was just checking. It doesn't count. I was checking. We're going back into
training. You just need to level speed a little bit. Stream title is clickbait. No, it's not.
I got to A rank. I didn't say I was going to beat A rank. Oh, that's not enough. That's just a waste
of time. We could have been training. We could have been training. When was the last time I
saved the game? Oh my God. Wait, I just fed him a potato. When was the last time I've saved?
Did I save right before that? Oh no. Never feed a potato. Ever. Yeah. Fuck this. Let's go.
Okay. We're not doing that. Instead. Yes, rank. No, thanks. Back to the training.
Try just doing air entry. Do B for the money. B for the money. That's eight. That's only three
thousand for eight. Eight entries. I need the money. That's going to take a long time. All right.
Fine. Let's just go farm this. Speed run. We don't care about what everybody's stats are. All we
care about is mashing A and hopefully the beam hits them. These are, these are new monsters.
All right. This is easy. Whoa. Look at this. I think it's cool. All right. Come on. I've spammed it.
I've been spamming it. What the fuck? No more swearing. He said, realistically your attack is
A plus right now in power, but you need either high dodge or defense to counter that RNG.
Yeah. I think it's probably going to have to be speed. We'll just work on speed for a little bit.
I'm just going to hammer speed, speed, speed, speed, speed and just make them drink nuts oil.
I don't think we need. Okay. I don't need any more intelligence. I should solely be focusing on
trying to get speed over two or three hundred, right? That's it. That's cool looking too. Shit.
Oh, that's not good. All right. I need to hold back. Try to stay back. Didn't even do anything.
That was a dinosaur, by the way. That was not even a dog. The T-Rex people are saying,
what are you talking about? That was a, that was not a lion. It was a stegosaurus. All right.
This is one hit kill guaranteed. You realize that they didn't sample actual dinosaur sounds, right?
How do we even know what dinosaurs sounded like? We've given them these crazy big roars,
the T-Rex roar and big growls. What are they saying? Like birds. I met T-Rex probably was like,
they were probably birds. Aren't they like descendants from birds? Birds or dinosaurs?
I'm not, I'm serious. There are a lot of experts that think we have dinosaurs all wrong.
They may have had just feathers all over them. They weren't like these lizard skinned animals.
They may have had feathers all over them. Oh, let me just kill this guy real quick.
Wow. That was pretty, that was a cool move. Come on. I don't suppose we're feathered. Yeah.
Okay. Wait, let me pay attention because I somehow just got hurt bad. Don't let this guy win. Come on.
Don't let him win. I just hit him once. 24 guts. Do it. Yeah. T-Rex didn't roar kind of rummed.
What is rum? The rum? Like that? I didn't mean to do that, but I just got to the end of the coffee.
Wait, let me take a guess. Is the rumming like this? Like, is that what it might be?
Kind of like use your throat and your vocal cords with your mouth closed a little bit.
Like the velociraptors do in Jurassic Park. It's like the rumbling alligators make. Oh, okay.
I got five health. All right. Let's just insult this person. Oh no. Okay. Good. Did my BM work?
So you're talking about the sound that it sounds like an alligator when they open their mouth and
they make a noise. It sounds like they're releasing steam from their body or that they have a gas
leak inside of their throat. No, that's a hiss. It's a low croak. I mean like this. All of you
just prepared, just wincing, waiting for that noise. And I even see somebody said minus two
because you wanted to be the first one to write it, but I didn't do anything. So you look a little
silly now, don't you? I want one of these big dogs. There's the money. I imagined it and it
made me cringe. So minus two. Yeah. These take too long just to get three or 4,000 bucks.
This is too long. I'd rather just train them. I like those little snail guys. How do I get
one of those? Did you do the fast forward mode? There is a fast forward mode, but I don't want
to do fast forward mode. I feel like I would accidentally screw something up and I would just
die. The snail guy sucks. Looks cool. Fast forward is good when you train. The Papa's B cup in July,
it's worth 9,000 bucks and it gives you pure gold. All right. This has to be the money farm
character to get ready for the real character. I'm fine with that. Okay. We got the nine speed.
That's exactly what I wanted to have happen and the health. That's good. I want polish. Yeah,
you deserve it. This stream is very cozy. That's nice. Sometimes it's fun just to play a game and
hang out. All right. I need some help from the lore masters. Is tablets still worth doing at this
point or should I just feed a cup of jelly for the stress? I need some lore master help. Please
don't try to level speed. Cosmic speed is literally one of the worst in the entire game.
It's defense is pretty good though. Really tablets is also stress minus. Okay. So wait,
they have the worst speed in the game. Does that also mean they train the worst for speed? Yes.
Okay. So then what do I, what do I do? Well, I just have to really rely on just keeping intelligence
and skill high enough so I can be the first person to attack and kill somebody in one hit.
Defense is worthless. Defense. People saying defense, but I've heard that defense is not good
or just farm money. That's why galaxy is bad. So this is why this is the worst character in the
game because okay, I'm beginning to understand because you can't really level these up because
he sucks and you get really shit increases when you do. I get it. That's why nobody plays with
this guy. I need to get a new skill. All right. I'm just going to do air entry. What's there? What
is it? Let's go for it. Let's do an air entry. It's good. I mean, it's $2,000 though. This one's
through. Okay. I'll do this one. Just make him the moneymaker. That's a good idea. Yeah. But the
double beam, as long as I keep using beam raise life is the most important defensive step in the
game. Okay. So I got a few options here. One of the ways to make this character really, really
okay is if I keep doing the beam move after I do it 50 times, I can then do an air entry and get
double beam, but I already kill things in one hit anyway. So two hits. Do I really need the double
beam? Oh, okay. Look at his gain. His life is D. His defense gain is B. The same as your intelligence
gain. Life gain is D. Defense is B. You're literally at 49 out of 50 beam usages. Okay. Yes, do it.
It's content. Okay. That's all I needed here. So I need to do this at the end of the month to just
to do the 50. He's leaving. He's not leaving. His ranch is huge. He promised a face cam in a minute.
All right. I'm going to let's do training. I have any more oil. I do just do heavy life training
then. Or should I just just spam life increase, which is just run, just do run over and over again.
Do defense, do defense, do defense, defense and life. So just do swim, defense, adult life will
make him expedition capable. Maybe I'll just swim. I should get it. I'm going to don't swim.
This is late game. Shit. I don't know what to do. I've never gotten this far. You don't. I'm going
to do swim. Swim is minus intelligence. Oh shit. You're right. All right. I'm just going to run.
Just run. Just go run. Meditate only. Oh, yucky. Ugly. Three. Huh? Three. That's it. He's getting
old. Upgrade intelligence and skill to become an actual one shot sniper. Please train defense.
Hold on. I need to sneeze. See if I can, can I catch it? Did I get it? Did I not get it? Yeah,
I did. Didn't I? All right. I don't know what to do. Speed and intelligence. Just keep running.
Defense is better than you think. It's against intelligence and power. Int and pow just also
scale damage resistance against themselves slightly. All right. I'm going to go for it.
Let me see. I'm going to do endure. Endure. Let's check it. Success, right? Four defense. That's not
good, man. Double beam has worse accuracy and you don't need the damage. Sound wave has the best
accuracy in the game. Get sound wave instead. All right. Where do I go for sound wave? Just choose
one with your eyes closed. Sound wave sucks. You guys have a lot of different opinions.
Should I just send him on an errant tree and who cares? We haven't had a discount in the whole
time we've been playing. Go to the beach and get sound wave. I'm going to the beach and I'm getting
sound wave. Rest. Don't miss the house upgrade. Yes. Who is it? You have mail. Look at this.
Oh, it's errant tree, isn't it? That's not bad though. All right. April. So help me out here.
When does this happen? The first week of May. So I need to just stay here the fourth week of May.
So I need to be on the ranch here. So we're going to continue to train or I'll just do this and just
get money. The video for this stream is going to be five minutes long. That's not like 30 minutes.
All right. This will be easy money. I need 17k to activate it. Will I have it after this match?
I was at 12, 13, 14, 15. I'll be at 15. All right. That's not good. How do you 93% chance
that they missed? Will you fuck off with this bullshit already? Really? Am I actually going to
lose? No, I'm not. I'm going to get to scream in five minutes to wake that person up for you.
Oh, it was a single elimination. All right. This one was really easy. What about the toxic monster?
Yeah, I just have to be able to unlock it. That was a 500 damage crit. I feel bad.
We need to put a poll in the chat. Very important. Because I can now get the strongest beam move in
the game, right? I can go get double beam. Do I get double beam, which is more damage than single
beam, but less accurate? And we actually just go for 30%, 40% kill everybody in one hit. Or do we
go get scream, which is almost a guaranteed hit, but doesn't do as much damage. I think we need a
poll for this. I don't know either one I would be fine with. You lose single beam. You do not.
Whoa, this is getting me more increases than if I were to heavily train the character. Holy shit.
Do double beam for extra brain dead build. Uh, have some tablets. All right. I got 15 grand.
What do we got? Looks like pretty unanimously. People do not want double beam. They want scream.
Just get double beam and then saves come until it works. I forgot to buy this shit. Wait, what is
this? What kind of seed is this? I don't know. A wholesaler often brings in new items. He said he
got this at parry parry region. I wonder what seed it is. I've never seen this before. It's not even
in the textbook. I will give it to you because Jax and cult are my loyal customers. Thank you,
auntie. What does that do? It grows into a monster. Holy smokes. Do I have to grow it?
How do I do that? In like three years. Okay. Nevermind. Cause this is going to take a long
time. It's 10 years actually. Oh, all right. We got, I can't do, wait, there's only four entries.
Okay. Air entry, air entry. Then we're going for, we're going for air rank again. Air entry. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't do that because the, right. Okay. All right. Speed
intelligence. What do you think? Let's do leap. Power down. Who gives a shit? I need speed. I'm
not training anymore. There's no reason to. It does so much fatigue and so much stress for
barely any gain at all. Just have to do the tournaments now. Wait, let's bury the seed in
the corner of the ranch. I wonder what kind of plant it is. Let's wait patiently and see. Let's
wait for 10 years. Yeah. Fuck it. I think I'm going for it. I'm going to save here. I'm going
to rest. We're going to see if I can win. It's only four people. Save the game. I can get lucky
four times. Hold on. Should I do? Okay. Rest, rest of it. A rank has insanely fast monsters.
That's all going to be about coming flips. I think I'm in, it's only four monsters though. I did,
I beat two in a row. I beat two in a row. Dragon was insane. It was horrifying. I beat it in one
hit at Ray. I beg of you. It's your best move. One thing at a time. I don't remember beating
any of these people, but we have improved since the last time. All right. It's just, it's flip
a coin. Let's go. I just have to get it right now. Again. Do it. Yes. Oh, what do I do? Stay back.
Stay back. Stay back. Stay back. Stay back. Dodge it. Oh, yeah. Oh, dodge it please.
I have health. 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24. Fuck you. Whatever. You literally only have one chance a
year to get Ray. It's June 1st. Please do whatever you can to get it. It's the Korea
expedition. June 1st? I don't even have expeditions. How do I get those? How do I do that?
They mean Erentria. Okay. All right. Let's get lucky here. Not happening. We need Ray. Bad.
Holy shit. Okay. Well, whatever. I'm just going to be able to save. Fuck it. Remember the game.
Okay. So we're not doing that. I still can't do it. I do need to wait till the end of this month.
So let's just rest or training. How about straight up speed or speed? Just do it. Whatever.
Oh, that person needs to wake up. Right. Hold on. We help. Plus one. Why even do any of these
anymore? All right. We got to wake that person up. I got it. All right. Give me one sec. It's
been two hours, right? It's too early. No, it's not too early. Okay. Let's do. It's four o'clock
p.m. It's four o'clock p.m. You're up. Turn it off. Turn it off. I hate that alarm. Everybody does.
I was sleeping. That was not a scream. I'm not going to actually scream and like hurt your ears.
All right. Just, just go to sleep. Just wake up tomorrow. Here we go. It's about our house.
You know, people say the might of the house is the might of the trainer. Our house is getting
too small for us. We have money. Total cost 5,000 gold to renovate the house. Go for it.
I will ask the carpenter. Jax, this is Binto, the carpenter. He's the number one carpenter around
here. Stop it, Colt. Although our motto is fast, cheap, and detailed, you will not be disappointed.
I'll be looking forward to seeing your job, Binto. Oh, but we cannot concentrate when someone
comes into our site. I have to ask you to visit somewhere while we are working. When we finish
our job, I'll come and get you. Wait, what do you mean leave? Got it. I asked to stay at the
Pabbs house, so don't worry. Of course, leave it to me. What does this actually do? How about that?
Pretty neat, huh? What, you're done already? I told you our motto was fast, cheap, and detailed.
I'll take the money. Ask us anytime. I don't know what to say. It's a good house, I guess.
That takes care of all of it, huh? More inventory space. Oh, it is a little house. That's cute.
Are we sure that it didn't just go in there and move the furniture? Okay, somebody said
first of June is the most important thing in the world, so I need to sleep here. Wait,
that's sleeping two days in a row. Wait, getting Cosmic's life to 140 or higher will let you go on
the first expedition, which can potentially unlock a new monster. I have 140 health. Dude, I got 187.
Let's go back to sleep. Double rest. I don't care. 187. You meet the requirements. You just need to be
ready to go next week. All right, I'm ready to go next week. He's nice and rested. I'm going to do
tablets. Check your house for asbestos and radon. Yes, who is it? Is this Jax's residence? Yes,
it is. Who are you? Oh, this is my calling card. Oh, here we go. Dr. Talico, Corbel University.
And what is the purpose of your visit? This is a serious question, dude. Do you have a
carbon monoxide detector and does it work? Yes, I do. Don't worry. What? Yes, I do. I check my
smoke detectors, my carbon monoxide detectors. Yes, so don't worry. Okay, once upon a time when
the world was one big continent, God sealed the monsters into disk stones and hid all the disk
stones in a shrine. This is when we say put us on the do not call list and close the door. I have
ascertained that the legendary shrine is located on this continent. Aha. No, aha. It is a great
discovery. Isn't that what aha means? I must go there. Well, what does it have to do with us?
It looks like that there are various obstacles on the way to the shrine. I want you guys to go on
this adventure with me. Pay you and give you some of the items we find during the adventure.
Huh? In order to get rid of those obstacles and proceed with this adventure, we have to use a
monster. Strong monster, that is. I came here because Pabs told me. Oh, you know Pabs. You
should have said that in the beginning. Now I understand. Jax, your monster might get injured.
Do you make it go with him? You can now get the big dog. Really? Save the game? I don't think I
can. I can't. You can get a phoenix from this. Um, does it autosave? Okay. Let's go. You don't
know what's going to happen. Something might injure your monster. Are you sure? Yes. Dr. Talco,
we can let it go. It's just what I expected. Jax the Wonderful. And can either Caldor or Jax
come with me on the adventure? I can't handle your monster by myself. You even know my name.
Okay, I'll go with you. Well done. Let's go. Are we all ready? Yeah. We better take off before you
change your mind. I'm leaving, Jax. Phoenix Volcano Adventure. Prologue to the adventure.
We finally arrived at the Phoenix Volcano. First, let's set up a base camp. Let's get started.
But before we start, let me explain a little about the adventure. At the beginning of an adventure,
energy points will be given depending on your monster's life status. What? Energy? Yes, energy.
This energy will be the life gauge for this adventure. The energy will be consumed with each
step your monster makes. It'll also be reduced if the monster checks the inside of a building.
Or moves of rock that might be sitting in a way. This girl's confused about everything.
So always pay attention to your monster's energy level as you proceed with your adventure. Come
back to base camp while your monster still has some energy points. Wait, let me read this again.
Come back to base camp while your monster still has some energy points hits minus 10. What's that
telling me? What's that telling me? If you don't, the monster's lifespan will be shortened. Just
don't let it hit minus 10. Okay, let's take off. Where do we go? Do I have to do this? Which way
should I go? This seems very important. Go north? How do I move? Whoa. Whoa. All right.
Keep going? Where the fuck am I? The path is blocked and we can't go any further.
Do you want Cosmic Calamity to move the obstacle? Yes. Nice. Okay, you're great. Change the camera.
Where should I go? Up to the volcano? We're down. Up to the volcano. We can't go any further.
Move that. All right. Into the volcano? There's nowhere else I can go. Oh, there is an entrance
here. I smell something in the cave. What do you smell? I don't mean that kind of smell.
I feel something related to disk stones. Or how can I say? I have a feeling that
monster's legend may be buried in here. Really? They usually say women's intuition,
but I guess we should call it doctor's intuition this time. Well, shall we investigate it? Yes.
Now what? What's that sound? Does it destroy the volcano? What is that thing and how do I get it?
I want it right now and I want to use it. It's the next monster we're going to use. I want it right
now. Oh, isn't that the legendary monster Phoenix, the guardian deity of the mountain?
It's not just a legend. It's real and it's alive. I better let him know about it as soon as possible.
Oh, who are you going to tell about it? Huh? Oh, never mind. Anyway, it seems like this is
not the place I'm looking for. I wonder where that shrine of gods is. By the way, I wonder if
Cosmic Calamity is all right. So shall we investigate inside again? Yeah. What is this?
That seems pretty far away to me. I just got something. I picked up something. I got
something. A fucking bunch of bananas. No, come go back in. Go back in right now. Go back in.
Get it at the top. Nice. Okay, that's definitely it. Get something else too. Fire feather left by
the legendary monster. If we investigate, we might be able to unravel the unknown secrets of the
Phoenix. Should I keep going? Do I just pull them out? Leave or are you going to hit minus 10? Okay.
All right. I don't need anything else from in here. I'm actually really excited. I've never seen
this before. All right. Let's pull it out. All right. Let's go. I just leave. Pull them out and
check the HP. I have 65. Should I do it again? Remember, go mix something random with that and
you'll get the Phoenix. Are you serious? One more? One more. Come on. No, you idiot. All right. Get
up. You're supposed to have 700 intelligence. I can do it again. One more. There it is. What do you
got? Oh, what did you get? I got a... No, get out. Now I just leave? If I go straight down,
will that take me back? I have to go back to the entrance. I can't go down. Yeah, I can't go down.
I have to go all the way around. I can't go down. I'm okay. 17, 16, 15, 14, 13, 12, 11, 10,
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. Oh, I made it. I made it. He's fine. All right. What did we get? We got
a magic banana, a fire feather, and disc chips. It was quite meaningful. Go back home. Hell yeah.
Did you tell me I'm going to get to be able to make a Phoenix and then combine it with a weird
plant monster and make a plant Phoenix? That was a good adventure. All right. We're going to go with
tablets again. What do we do now? Should I just make a Phoenix? After you create a Phoenix by
combining, you get infinite more from music tracks. Can Phoenix be combined with stuff?
Can I make like a cosmic Phoenix? Phoenix can't be combined, but I can pull a Phoenix.
So I can pull a different kind of Phoenix. Phoenix is only Phoenix or Phoenix plus Phoenix.
Save the game? I will. There's only three Phoenix types. Okay. Let's go make one.
So let's freeze you. But now what do I do here? Can I do this wrong? I can do this wrong?
Oh God. I hope I get it right. Whatever it is. Saved. I did. Get two monsters from the market.
Combine two monsters and just use the feather. This is impossible to fuck it up.
Just combine two. All right. Who are we going to sacrifice here? All right. Who are we sacrificing?
Xbox Series X and Noodle? Batman. Does it matter? Well, the stats are still transferred,
so a high int monster will give good. Oh, okay. Should I do calamity? Should we just say,
fuck it and let's go? Bug Batman has high stats. All right. I need, I need a lore master to tell
me this. If it, if any combination with the feather gets a Phoenix, does it act? If I combine Bug
Batman and cosmic calamity and the feather, is the Phoenix going to have really like crazy base
stats? I need a lore master to help me here. Dude. Combination is such a fucked up math problem.
I can't explain it in chat, dude. Stats will not be transferred for Phoenix. It's a unique summon.
Okay. Combining is extraordinarily complicated. All right. All right.
So it just doesn't matter. So we're just going to do two people that we don't really care about.
I care about Wellington. I don't care about the Xbox Series X. Who cares?
And Noodle, I don't really care either. Wellington and Bonnie, I think it'd be used pretty well.
Secret item. Where is it? There it is. Let's go. Let's do it. This one's all up to you.
Phoenix. Yeah. Phoenix sucks at power, has insane int and the rest is average.
You'll need to errantry for the int move again, but it only has one non-int move it can learn.
Ready to face game for this one? All right. Whoa. 170 base health, 190 int. Oh my God.
Phoenix is the one we saw at the volcano. Well, take good care of it. You have to give it a name.
A phoenix familiar. Red wizard has got phoenix familiar. Blue wizard is about to die. Red wizard
needs food battery. Oh, it's definitely familiar. It'll be called familiar. Let's go familiar.
That's lame. Familiar. Name it phoenix right. No. Long chicken. That is a boring one. All right.
Yeah, it's boring. Familiar. That's fucking boring. BKLC? BKLC. Burger King Long Chicken.
Now it's name is BKLC. Shit. It should have been spicy. BKLC. All right. Cool. Wow. I have a
phoenix. This is cool. All right. So I need to make... Excuse me. Hello. Loremaster of Monster
Rancher 2 in the chat please. Phoenix. All the monsters have different times where they peak.
What does the phoenixes look like? Is it early? Is it late? Should I? Because I want to train this
one correct. At the Britney Spears toxic monster. I can look it up. Oh yeah. I can just look it up
myself. Right. All right. Game stuff. Game guides. Okay. Monster Rancher 2. Looking for
monster battle specials. Monster data. Here we go. Monster breed. Phoenix. Phoenix.
Base stats. Stat gains. So it looks like it gains crazy intelligence. But everything else
is pretty bad. Okay. You can eat like an iceberg? What? All right. There's an iceberg and there's
like a dark bird. How do I get these? Spoilers. What do you mean spoilers? The lifespan is only
350 weeks. If you want to train him well, you're going to need like $15,000 a year. Okay.
So we're doing heavy intelligence. And what's a heavy intelligence skill? Like build it like the
wall? Look up. Look. Okay. Well, let, let, let, yeah. Let's take a look. I'm very curious. Let's
freeze you for a second. Can I unlock a different phoenix now? One build Andy. Can we freeze him?
It's painful. Okay. Shrine. Fiskstone. All right. What am I looking for? Toxic by Britney Spears.
Can I actually do this yet? No, it's a rare monster. Okay. Look up. Well, white snake.
This one was rare. Oh, it's the band. Okay. All right. What am I looking for? Do highway to hell.
I will snake bite. Where's snake bite? Oh, okay. Let's go. I want, I, what if I want another one?
Dude, this, okay. All right. All right. All right. Look at this. Look at this thing. So this is a
unique monster. Oh, no way. 229. What's the difference? But wait, there's probably a
difference though. So there's a phoenix and then cinderbird. Okay. Let me check. Stat gains are
CEACCC. I think it's the same as the phoenix. What's the difference though? Besides the base
stats. Yeah. Same exact stat gains. That's right. 14 movement speed. Same exact thing. Base nature
90. Base nature 90. Cinderbird is enemy only and it's only available in this version.
It has 20 more weeks of lifespan. Is that it? It's just a better phoenix. That's the only
difference. It's just a better one. Okay. It gets extra tech. All right. Very cool. All right. We're
definitely using this one. Burnt BKLC. I had to use a space. I don't think I can. I don't think
there is a space. If the phoenix is on fire, this one's like cinder. This one's kind of like burnt
out. Smolder. Smolder. Smolder? No, I'm not going to name this character burnt fucker. Okay. You
did that in your game. Smoke? No. Charcoal. Brickette. Brickette. All right. Smolderloin?
I like Brickette. How do you spell this? Brickette BK. How about BK Brickette? Somebody just called
me a knob. I'm going to keep Brickette. That's not iconic like Beanbag Sonic. I like BK Brickette.
Smolder. No, the name doesn't matter. I make garbage names anyways. Brickette is with an E.
How about Brickette? Brickette. All right. I got to pick one. Briskette. Oh, now I got it. Briskette.
Briskette. Like that. Get rid of the E. Get rid of the U. Briskette. There you go. Briskette. Done.
It's with a Q. I'm seriously, I got to fucking move on. There it is. Briskette. Briskette. Got it.
All right. Now let's just look for some more. Why not? What if I combine? You can't combine
phoenixes, right? Let me look up a few more. Because there's other monsters to get. You can
combine two phoenixes. All right. Let me look up a couple songs that I want to look up. We lit
SpongeBob. I can't get SpongeBob. Give me Neutron. Metal Gear. Oh, Beanbag Sonic. That's right. We
could get Beanbag Sonic. Although, come on. Okay. Hip to be square. I like it. Wait, what? Where is
it? What? I won't picture this. How about just Huey Lewis in the news? Huey Lewis in the news.
Four? Wait. What do you mean four? Do a random one? Random. Nova the album. Okay. Well, Nova the
album. Ooh. Suizo. Hey, look at this little guy. That's not bad. But I don't want you. How about
like DuckTales? DuckTales theme. Metal version. Maybe it's a duck. I'm not doing another wall.
Sorry. And those stats are dog shit. So no, not happening. Meatloaf. Oh shit. All right. How about
Meatloaf? How about Bad Out of Hell 2? Back into Hell. Uh, we already have one of these.
I wasn't too big of a fan. Stats are actually kind of good. 157, 157. I might actually hold on to
this one. Who's purple in the Batman universe? Joker? Nah. But I'm only going to use this for
a combination, I think. Whatever. Who cares? Lowercase doesn't matter. It's Joker. Goodbye.
I don't want to run out of space either, though. All right. What else do you want?
You know the monsters before you take the, uh, Cinderbird? Okay. What do we got?
You have 20 freezing slots. Okay. Uh, Gangnam Style. I don't think that would be on here.
Find out, though. It is on here. Which version? Which version? No, not that one. This one. Rare.
Got the other one? Am I spelling it wrong? Wait, what's happening? Wait, what am I doing? Okay.
Here we go. This one works. Ooh, one of the dogs. Cool looking. I like the speed. I don't like
anything else. Sandstorm? Imagine Dragons. Not here. The Rude? No, that, okay. I'm an idiot.
The Rude is the artist. Sandstorm the remixes. Or, let's just do regular Sandstorm. Rare.
Try the remix. Um, okay. Definitely this one. Yeah, this one. Really? Come on.
Tenacious D. All right, what's the one that's...
It was the... What's that one called? Seinfeld. Seinfeld. Yeah, it's called Tribute. All right,
where is it? Tenacious D. Ozzy Osborn? How about the Funk Hunters? I like that. Tenacious D,
Tenacious D, Tenacious D. Where is it? It's not even here. Whatever, what's going on with
the Funk Hunters? Ooh, a water monster? Strong looking, really. Looks dependable. So it's a
dinosaur jelly? Water Raptor? This is not bad. It's kind of all around not bad. It's a chaos.
Um, that's cool, but I don't know if I want it. No thanks. Uh, BBS is Death of a Bachelor by
Panic at the Disco. Here we go. Time to bring him back from beyond the grave. Beanbag Sonic.
I love Beanbag Sonic. Speed is so... Beanbag Sonic is unironically very, very good.
Base health and the base speed are very, very good. We're going to keep... Beanbag Sonic is back.
Freeze. You know what I really want to find? I want to find one of those apes. 64 intelligence.
All right, all right. It's time to move on. I want to try to get one or two more decent ones.
Do Baby Metal's album? Baby Metal? It's Baby Metal. Baby Metal? Baby Metal. Jelly. The jelly
monster? Is it just jelly jelly? I think it is. How would you ever use this? What? One, two, three,
four, five, six. These stats are awful. It's just a meme? Oh, okay. What about hamster dance? Hamster
dance. Did I spell it wrong? Hamster dance? Is it two words? Hamster dance. The hamsters.
Rare. Jim Carrey? What do you mean Jim Carrey? Jim Carrey pecan pie? What is this? I've never
heard of this. Oh, it's an ape. It's an ape. It's actually an ape. All right. Awesome.
What kind of ape is this? Oh, that's not bad. Yes, I want it. Okay. Now, what if we combine the ape
and somebody else? Ape Ventura. Ape Ventura. I like Ape Ventura. That's a good one.
Combine the ape with the monolith. Okay. Let's freeze. Let's do a little bit of work here.
Wait. I want to see what kind of monster this is. Wait. I got to look at techniques and shit. Hold
on. Ato. Let's see. Okay. Likes jelly. Doesn't like milk. Nature is bad natured. What's the...
What kind of monster is this? I see the sub monster. This is an ape and something else. Or
is it just ape? It's just ape. It's ape ape. Oh, okay. So if I combine this, I should look
for something to do with it. It's just pure ape. Okay. Let's do some combining. I have disc chips
too. The ape does not have very many subspecies. Okay. Wait, let me save it. I've been doing a lot
of stuff. Let's make sure I don't lose it. There we go. Very cool. Okay. What can we get? Ape. Okay.
We've got Burger King, Long Chicken. We can't combine this though. This is Phoenix.
Brisket. Wellington. Ooh. What about ape Wellington? That might be kind of good. Or
ape, um, ape Bonnie. No, stop. Stop it. Why not? I think I want to try it. Let's try it. Ape and
Wellington. Yes. And we'll use some seasoning. Uh, hair? Hono mochi. Ape disc. Should I put an ape disc?
What would that do? Oh, not with Wellington. Stop it. I don't, why? Crossbacteria is unsure.
Oh, we're just going to get it. Wait, what? We're going to combine these two and it's just going to
pop out one of the two? Ape, ape and dog Batman? Bonnie, we'll use, uh, ape disc. This one's up to
you. Okay. No, no, not anything interesting. Not going to get anything weird. Try it again. Ape
and beanbag Sonic. We're going to call this Robotnik by the way. Ape disc. This one's all up to you.
What's a Gaboo? Oh, it's already what this is. No shit. Sonic is a Gaboo. Okay.
No, I want a different ape. The ape disc is messing it up. Just don't use the ape disc.
All right. What about ape and, uh, don't use the disc. Ape and beanbag Sonic, no disc.
Let's see what happens with this shit. I'm curious. We'll do a secret seasoning of,
uh, hair's disc. Let's go. This combination sucks. And then we'll do,
this is the only one we haven't really tried. And no seasoning. What the fuck? All right. Fuck it.
Let's go. This is just for stats. Oh, okay. All right. I'm ready. What are we pulling out?
I think I have to pull the wall out. Yeah. We're doing cosmic calamity. We're so close.
Brisket. Cosmic. Should we do brisket? I need money though. No, not yet. I need money. I,
I need to make another like 10 to 20,000 dollars. Take out bug Batman and let him die.
Oh, that's right. Okay. Good idea. We're just gonna, we're gonna make money with bug Batman
until he dies. It's going to be very sad. Everybody say goodbye. We're going to get some money
out of bug Batman. Kind of a cool monster, but a really, really awful name. Not funny. Just sucked.
But rest up. The next battle is, uh, we need to do C, right? 3,000 bucks.
Get some rest. Uh, how come I'm so cruel? Because when a monster dies, you unlock another breed.
So somebody has to die. Uh, C I would say just to make sure I can make the money.
There's a lot of fusions with this guy. Somebody has to die though. I got the cinder phoenix.
That's going to be the S tier monster. Bug Batman style is doting. Yeah. Cause I spoiled this shit
out of him. It's the first monster we used. I forgot. It's not just one hit Andy. Are we trying
to kill bug Batman? We're not trying to kill bug Batman. Bug Batman is about to farm money
and hopefully get to somewhere around 30 to $40,000. We will put bug Batman to rest.
He will have done his job. Well, Batman seems to not be able to hit anything.
Oh, I'm in trouble here. I have to swing. I'm dead. I forgot how much this guy sucks.
The other high level cup today gives 10 K. It does. It's too late. I could just say,
yeah, I load the same. Yeah. I know. Fuck this. I give up. Yeah. I forget that it's 10 grand.
There's no way I'm not doing it. The game kind of glitches out a little bit sometimes. All right.
Let's go use the monster rancher. One disc. The thing dies in one day. Is the one that's 10 grand.
It's a 10 grand. What are you talking about? 10 grand. Where do you see 10 grand?
There's no 10 grand. None of these are 10 grand. Pure gold. Oh, this is pure silver.
Oh, oh, oh. You sell the gold. I got you. Let's feed you some soil. Clean this up.
I need to do that air entry and get this stupid move. All right. Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry,
hurry. Farm, farm, farm, farm, farm. Instant kill. One, two, three. One, two, three. Dead.
Very nice. Okay. Okay. Okay. Money. Get some money. Let's go. Watch out. He has psychic scream.
Just use the speed function. Yeah, that's probably a good idea. How do I do it?
I think I can enable it from here. It's FF. What does FF stand for?
Fast fighting. Fast forward. Oh, shit. You're right. Okay. Okay. This is like too fast.
It's actually just times two speed. I thought this hurts my head. Gold bar.
Can the gold be used for anything else? Nice. Sure. You're going to have polish.
It makes gold suazo 1% less stressed. That's so stupid. It feels like it's in slow motion now.
I'm not doing that again. It's fucking my brain up. All right. I got almost seven.
So I need 17,000 by what date? How did you get this much money? I'm struggling to get money in
the game. It actually takes a little while because your first couple of monsters are going to be
kind of dumpy and you're going to be spending a lot of money just keeping them alive and trying
to win shitty tournaments. But once you get the one person that can reliably do C and B tournaments
and you can just kind of make money with that character. So it takes a little while. The first
six to 10 hours of the game, actual in-game gameplay. I'm not sure if you're like a
veteran of the game and you know exactly what to do, but if you're just starting, it could be
a little bit of a curve, especially the training regimens. They're kind of confusing.
All right. When's the next battle? One here. I'll do that one too. So let's do, I want to do an
errand tree. Uh, lore masters. When do, when do I need $15,000 by, when do I have to have at least
15 by July 4th? So literally tomorrow. I need 17,000. It's August 8th. Sell something.
All right. Is it actually, do I really need to have $17,000? It's May 4th next year, not July.
Okay. So I have to wait a year. That's fine. So in the meantime, I'm just, I'm going to do an
errand tree. I have to, I can't just wait for the dumb sale. This guy needs shit. So if I do an
errand tree now, I will be able to rest. Okay. Let's go do an errand tree. What do I get the,
uh, the move I want monster is higher than B rank and you can use any location you want.
Oh, okay. You need to do Korea. This is the place I unlocked Mandy. What's the one to get the,
the a Korea seems that there is some chance to acquire a new technique here. I want Ray. Okay.
Let's go for it. Yeah. Let's fight a monster too. One of these,
you can definitely do at least a C. Oh, unicorn bean bag, Sonic, Harry, Harry. Who could I? Whoa.
Magma heart. We go for Terry. How about one-eyed? Let's go. Good. Nice. I got it. All right. So I
think I got Ray crash bandicoot music. It kind of is. Or an actor. Please turn an OST on and
turn the in-game music off. We're dying. I, that's not unanimous. I think I'm not failing this. This
is defense training. All right. All right. That's good. So bean bag, Sonic's organs. Holy s**t.
That looks all right. Please no more clown music. I would like 200 health. I ran a sword. I get one
of those s**t. Come on, get up. Oh, I got saved by the, nevermind. Get him, get him and then fight
Terry, whatever his name was. Yeah, that's it. I win. Now we get to fight that weird monster at the
end. How was that? Like 20 defense? That was pretty significant. Goldy. I should win as long as he
does an intelligence move and isn't an idiot and just bumps him a thousand times. Let's see. Oh,
that was okay. Got him. I should have went for one of the B monsters or even one of the A ones
probably. Great job. Easy battle to win against those guys. Let's go back. Good job. What do you
actually get for beating the monster at the end? Prize money? Oh, it just lets you get it. Okay.
Yeah. I remember you get half back. Nice job. Pretty tired. All right. What's that technique?
Ray. Okay. This is force. So it's hit B. These are all hit C. Okay. At least I'll be able to
actually do s**t. Withering is B on this as well, which is guts removal, but that's really good.
Whoa. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. That's a huge amount of guts to use.
35 guts? The monster has 700 intelligence. He probably is smarter than any human that has
ever existed. Yet you force it to fight instead of letting it learn a language and contribute to
humanity. Yeah. Oh yeah. That's fine. We need some anti-stress and rest. It also greatly reduces
the enemy's guts. That's true. Maybe I should start with that or maybe that's like an oh s**t
button. If I miss the first one, just get in close and try to take their guts away so I can stall.
Need to buy. Oh, overweight. Keep game OST or play something else.
Sorry guys. That's democracy. The next battle is coming up here and it's three grand and then I
could try A again. All right. We're going for this one. This one here. So we'll rest up. No,
we need to do some training, right? Let's do another air entry. F**k it. Let's do another one
after this tournament, right? No, just double rest, triple rest. I want to see the Phoenix.
I know everybody wants to see the Phoenix. I do too, but I need to make enough money
first because the Phoenix is E rank. I got to get to like 20 plus thousand dollars. Once that
happens, I can comfortably bring out the Phoenix and train the absolute hell out of it with buying
all these products, doing the air entries. Air entry. All right. Nice. Okay. All right. All
right. All right. I can learn. Where's the other move? Cosmic limit doesn't look very good these
days. What? I'm going for A. I'm going for it. Save the game. I guess I f**k up. He's got one last
fight. He's got more than that. Probably another year. Let's go for it. Four grand. All right.
Something else to keep in mind. Your no rest schedule you're doing does not work in the new
game. It reduces lifespan quite a bit now. The new one is harder and RNG based because of magic
bananas. Really? Really? Oh, okay. Well, magic bananas in this economy. I got confidence we can
land at least one hit here. 60% get it. I f**king am spamming. Spam it. All right. Now get in close
and make the guaranteed hit. Get in close. Get in close. It's big. It's bigger hit. Get in close.
Thank you. 200 and what? Excuse me? Did that much damage? That was insane.
Did I just do that? No rest method still does work. That's definitely the play is you go for
the coin flip. If you miss you just get in close and you'll do some withering. That's a lot of
power. This thing is awesome. What is this whale? It's a bipedal whale. All right. Get in close
and go. Hell yeah. Okay. Just actually stay in close and do it again. Should I go back? Stay in
close. Get the guaranteed hit. No. 66%. Give me a break. What the f**k? Heck. 66%. You know,
you can't even land that and you die. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Back. Back. Back. Back.
Holy s**t. I actually pulled it off. No, I didn't. God damn it. He has got grit too. Just push him.
Just bump into him. Bump into him. How much does he hate? Bump him. Bump him. Bump him. Bump him.
Get in close. Close. Close. Close. Close. Bump him. Who wins? I won? Wait. What? Oh, because I had a
high... Wait. I don't understand. Doesn't he have higher... Because my health is lower. So my max
health... Okay. I'll take it. How come I censored myself? Because I promised my mother I would say
less swear words. That was crazy. Am I going to win my first A Cup? Find out. It's going to be
tricky. I have to get a big crit here. Oh, that's it. I'm still in it. What? Injured? 2,500? Reload the
save? Uh, yes. I think Cosmic Calamity is injured. It's not serious, but I'll put it in the hospital
for fast recovery. It's still in the hospital. Hope it will come back soon. He's fine. All right. Check
his hate. Hate? Loyalty went down. It's okay. It takes a ton of its life away. Um, wait. I should
have done the V... I'm reloading the save. Uh, we need a little bit of light training. Why not?
How about a little bit of dodging? Whatever. Cheating? All right. I promise I will not save
scum the bird. Save scumming is pretty much required for this game. Yeah, there's a lot of
heavy RNG. Heavy RNG. Let's make some money. He dislikes tablets, Jeremiah. Yeah. Well,
here's the thing, though. Uh, according to the experts, it doesn't matter if they don't like
tablets. It's still the best food to feed anyone, even if they don't like it. What I've been told.
Hey, pill boys, thanks for the 10. You know what I mean? Community stuff. What's your opinion on the...
Hold on. What's your opinion on the... What's your opinion on the socio-economic climate
of Sugandhi's nuts? Um, I've already said the joke for you. I get to make it. You don't. Wait,
you backed out? He forfeited. That's how you know I'm not supposed to be here.
You couldn't have put less effort into that. After this, we're going to try... We're going to do
another air entry. We'll get double beam because that's like the culmination of this whole thing.
Double beam, try to just RNG ourselves through A rank, and then either let him die or put him on
ice. All right. It's the biggest crit we've done so far. 517. All I'm doing now is I'm trying to go
for, you know, long distance home run records. I want to hit like a 600 foot home run. Slow down
so we can gamble. I don't think gambling right now is a good idea considering I'm almost guaranteed
to win every single B rank match. What's this item? Manselton? What is that? Nice. Wow. Okay.
All right. You're almost ready to actually get us to S.
Get that double beam. Paul is sure you deserve it. Life go up, fame go down. Yeah, that's all good.
All right. We're looking... This is the one right here. This is the official cup.
Can I get through this? Heavy. Okay. If you go to the heavy air entry before August
and you succeed with no injury, you'll be able to unlock Centaur. If you'd rather that than double
beam. Hmm. Well, August is already over. I don't know. Let's go for double beam. Cosmic's going to
die soon anyways. Yeah, but I kind of want to see a huge number through Chad's go straight for S
rank. I'm going to try. Rest up before the... Let's try it again. I have to at least get to S.
Look at your view count. 13,703. What about it? Big number. He didn't get the joke. Oh, I don't
get the joke. I don't understand. Who cares? I don't care. I thought I was supposed to get
something. What am I missing? All right. Come on. We can just luck Andy these people. Save the game.
Official A rank. Get in there. Feed some items and shit so you're happier. Stress banana. Whatever
this is. You wanted to see a big number. Oh, oh, that's not, that was not like a joke. That was
like nice. I can't believe there are this many people here. Hope you're having a good time. I
love this game. I think it's fun. I think it's worth buying. Thanks for watching. Hi, everybody.
All right. It's time to save. Sounds good. Battle time. If I got lucky once, I can get lucky twice.
And if I can get lucky twice, I can get lucky five times. If I can get lucky five times,
then I just have to hope I place. I have that new move, so I didn't have that last time I tried to
the official cup. The only one I'm actually afraid of is the one that is that go trick.
Let's go. This is it. I land the first hit. You're dead. You got to hit. Go before me. Not here.
And go. Just have to do that a few more times. Finally get to S rank. Although this did happen
last time. The best part about this, though, is that Dragon is not here anymore. I think the
Dragon got promoted to S rank. They're not here. We're here the last two times. This is a big
tournament. All the major tournaments are eight. All right. Lamb sweet. This person beat the shit
out of us last time. All about it's the speed. It's just the fact that I have a plan and I think
it was going to go forward. Was it 30%? I have to go for it. It's going to be a shit percentage,
but I have to do it. I'm fucked. Dodged it. I got grit though. I got grit. I got grit.
I have to just land one. Just crit for 500 right now. Crit. Dodge. Dodge. Dodge. Dodge. Dodge it.
I need 24. 24. Kill. Back. Back. Back. Back. Dodge. Whatever. All right. Don't be fucking hurt again.
That was a crit and it's probably going to be hurt again. Oh, come on. Why? What? What? Yeah.
He's elderly, dude. Kind of bring out Phoenix. Wait, this is pure silver. Wait, what happened?
Oh yeah. Okay. Let's get it. 4,000 gold and pure silver. Let him rest. I just gave him nuts oil.
Nuts oil is essentially sleep in a bottle. That's what it does. That's why during that training
regimen, I'm able to give nuts oil and they don't have to sleep. What was that? Like weird glitch.
It's weird. Is this guy going to get his revenge on me? I've one hit killed this guy
a thousand times. Okay. Very nice. Duelist. Oh no. That's a good name. I like that name.
Duelist. See, I've been doing, they're all getting hurt probably. Also, you laugh,
you lose is going to be on Tuesday of this coming week. I think that might be the next stream. I've
got a lot of stuff I have to do this next few, like three or four days. I wonder if I can sneak
a stream in on Friday, but we're going to probably, it's not there right now, but we're
probably going to set up a thing where you guys can recommend you laugh, you lose videos. Are you
guys seeing that? Why is that happening? You guys saw that, right? The screen like is flickering.
Is that happening to you guys or is it just on my end? That's weird. It's not happening. Okay.
So in the discord, just keep an eye over the next couple of days. There'll be probably either
channel or something, or we'll set up a thing to make it so you can recommend
some videos to watch. That's also the baby sensory stream. If you have no idea what I'm talking
about, I'm going to open up a notepad. I'm going to watch baby sensory videos and I'm going to,
in real time, describe to you how I feel. I'm going to lose. This guy did the same thing last time.
Come here. God, call it back. Just do it. Go forward. I don't know which way this guy's
trying to go. Oh my God, dude. Really? What? No, he's three and oh, I didn't even win the tournament.
What? This guy's getting old. It's over. He's, he's old. I'll take the two grand. That's fine.
He's old. Okay. That's fine. You did a good job. You made us like 50 grand over the course of the
last year and a half, three year old birthday yet strong and even much stronger. It sounds like a
math problem written out as a sentence. Here's your cake. All right. It's time to put him on ice.
We got to A rank. It doesn't look well these days. I guess we have to consider his retirement.
Who is it? Look at this. Ooh, let's load up. This is perfect. I'm going to load up a shitload because
we're going to do the no, uh, no rest regimen. This is perfect. I'm going to buy like 10 of each.
What can I sell? What is this? Medicine from the Far East life and skill will increase. However,
speed will decrease. I have too many of these chips. I'm getting rid of one. That's stupid.
Hey, let's get rid of this stuff. Just sell them. I need at least 80 K for the no rest regimen.
Well, you can feed these to the monster, sell the chips. That is not that useful.
Should I really just sell them all? Are they not that useful? No rest is $15,000 a year.
It influenced the breeding. That's it. Chips are just money. I sell them. They could be used.
We'll just get rid of them. I'm not going to use them. I'd rather buy the useful stuff to
do the training regimen because they're all on sale. Did I get rid of the banana too?
They just favor the breeding outcome. Disrelating to the species. Okay.
You still has a decent bit of life left. Go get sound wave. It'll carry you to S rank since you're
into so high. I'll keep the banana. I have six of each. That's I'm at my max unless I get rid of
these 15 K per year. And you can sub the monster out during the months with the gold and silver to
get 20,000 ish per year. Okay. You can see a beard on his face. You can. Let me see.
No, you can't. He has a beard. Let me see. Oh, whatever. Put them on ice. It's time. It's time.
You did a great job. You made us a lot of money. Bring it out. Phoenix. Phoenix is insane. Where
are you? Skept. Look at these base stats. They're ridiculous. Let's go. I don't even know what the
moves are, but I'm really excited. So everything is the same except for intelligence. Intelligence is
monster gains on this guy. What's, what stat is the least for the Phoenix? Let's find out.
So there's literally no reason to ever do power. Power is worthless. Stat gains are E, which is
awful. So intelligence and everything else and don't ever do power. So just everything on
intelligence and I'm assuming probably speed. What should I do? Let me see. Int and speed,
probably. Int, speed and life. Int, speed, life and skill, I think is the order. Int, speed,
life skill. Probably in that order. All right. Let's begin the regimen. Regimen is as follows.
Regimen is, I need to look up what Phoenix's peak performance is. Okay. So they spend. They're a
late bloomer, apparently. They hit their prime very, pretty late at their fifth and sixth stage
of life. So they spend actually a pretty significant amount of time young, but we're not going to see
very many stat gains. Go for it. All right. Training. You know what we're doing here.
Real. Editate. Do errantries during the early stages too. Hooray for errantry farming.
We should go fucking do one right now. Literally. Just let's go right now.
Errantry immediately. All right. Where's the, I need to get a good skill. What should I look for
here? Pappas? This dude was just born yesterday. Why are you making him do this? Skill or int?
Save it. That's so cute. Get a cute name. All right. Let's hurry up. Location. Let's go to.
I'm going to say probably paripari or torbal for the skill. Or should I do Pappas for the speed?
I don't know. I'm so indecisive. Cosmic Andy literally lived three years out of eight. Well,
he's not dead. He's still alive. I'm going paripari. I skipped that text. Sorry. Sorry.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
I'm just getting very distracted. I just want to fuck. You get one chance to do this. I don't
want to fuck it up. He's so cute. Don't ever go to Torbal. It's useless. Got it. Oh, I got it. Nice.
First try. Hell yeah. Didn't wait. Don't do it. These two wings. Fucking idiot. I guess you're a
baby, but you can definitely do it. That's it. Nice. Good job. You know,
errant trees might just be what I need to do because you get really, really small, less than
four, less than three plus when they're babies. I'm going to end up with like plus 20 intelligence
from this. If I got the money, might as well just do it. They take three weeks of life off of you.
Oh, okay. These increases are huge though. I'm already almost at 250 intelligence.
You didn't fight the thing at the end. Nice job. All right. Time for rest. What'd you get?
Like cedar logs. Best nature. Oh, flame shot. Hell yeah. Force D hit percent A. Force D hit
percent C. It costs a lot. All right. We need to do stress relief and sleep. Let's rest. I am fairly
certain that this character will be able just to blow immediately through D rank. 250 intelligence
already. Okay. What do we got? I think I'm just going to put them into the official cup and just
skip a couple of grades at school. I don't want to fuck this up though. So we probably should do
speed. Speed and intelligence probably number one, number two. Or should I just dump into
intelligence? If you get over 500 intelligence, go to Korea. You'll get the fire stream. Okay.
Nice job. Tablet time. Take your pills. Take your medicine. All right. It's a new month.
I'm going to do, let's do oil and then do heavy training. Mint leaf. Is there an intelligence
and speed? There is. What's more important right now though? Focusing on intelligence or focusing
on speed? I wonder. Just wait for the loyalty. Hour is going to be irrelevant. So leap is probably
pretty good for this. Just swap between them. We'll do speed. I'll just jump between them.
Nice. Very nice. Okay. Now let's do intelligence. When's the battle? Okay. I can do intelligence
this time and then. All right. Should I even, should I just fuck it and just train the absolute
hell out of this guy? Try to say guy and bird. And I ended up saying like pie. Okay. Not soil.
Heavy speed and intelligence. He'll die in a year. Oh shit. I'm going to go for it. Whatever.
Let's go for it. I'm going to beat the whole game in less than a year.
Doesn't he just come back? If he's a phoenix. I don't know. I want health too. All right. What
the fuck did I just do? Okay. We're just doing the intelligence study. But once we get into the prime,
has it been a BRB yet? No, not yet. I'm too addicted. I can't leave. Okay. Now we do. Oh,
wait, I need to do oil, right? Yeah. What? I think so. Is this a BR? No, it is a fighting
one versus one game. Get 300 skill and go to med bay. You can get a strong intelligence mood
called that's not in this game. I just read your message for no reason. Speed again. Excellent.
Come on now. That was only plus three. Okay. I'm going to do intelligence just straight up.
Put on a face cam. All right. You get your face cam after I go to PRB. We'll do this one. I'll
play. Just to make sure I can do it, right? I'm going to go with meditate. Freddy dread coming
in with 50 community subs. Holy shit. Freddy. What's up Freddy? How's it going? Thanks for the
million dollars or whatever that is. Plus one. What is that? Oh, thanks dude. Good to see you.
So much. Okay. All right. We got this week. We're going to train and I'll rest and we'll do the
tournament. That sounds good to me. Uh, life too. Maybe sprinkle it in. Not yet. Maybe later. Speed
brisket has not failed a single training. Not one best nature. I think this is the, I honestly
really believe that before the stream turns off, we're going to do an insane training regimen
and this bird will be able to just wipe the floor with everybody. And I'll be able to skip like
eight. I'll be able to skip to a rank in like 45 minutes. All right. Let's rest. What's CD made
this? Uh, I had to unlock it by finding the feather in the volcano. And then I forget what song
actually was to get the cinder. Let's give it a go. All right. After this tournament, I'll go PA.
Promise. Thanks for reminding me to drink water. It's been like four hours. We can't lose. How do
you compare? Cause we did skip a whole rank pretty good. Even though we skipped E I'm very curious.
What are your moves like? Oh hell yeah. That was sick. Hang back. I got, I have high speed. All
right. Roger. Exactly what you want to see. Roger. All right. Okay. I'm not going to be super
powerful yet. I know Millium has low HP. There's also a skipping a rank too. Yeah. I mean, if I do
well here, that means the official tournament, I'll just do D and just skip right to see. Perfect.
Ooh. Uh, I think I'm just going to do power moves in there and just use beak. Nice. And then again,
stop doing that. Stop. I'm not doing any moves. There it is. All right. We are capable of doing
D rank. That's huge. That means the first tournament I do, I should be able to skip right
to see. And then we can focus on training. I don't have to win tournaments. Take a few bucks.
Should get a little more than that. I skipped a whole rank. Ooh. I probably should do tournaments
then. Maybe not the official ones. We'll do the non-official D tournaments. This one's not official.
2000. I'm going to do that one again. All right. Let's uh, go P. Right, right. Okay. Okay. Perfect.
See you guys in like two, three minutes. I have returned. Guess what I'm eating. What am I eating?
Nope. Cliff bar with what kind? Come on. We need to know. Blueberry crisp. Thank you. This is so good.
It really is. I used to hate these things. I used to think I was chewing on tar. I hated these things.
I thought they were terrible. I don't know if this is a new formula or if this is blueberry crisp.
The crisp versions of these are new, but these are a million times better than I remember.
This is fantastic. You promise to facecam? I will. Have you had a builder bar? No, I haven't.
Is this sponsored? No, it's not. Have you had a builder bear? No. I don't like that you put a
heart in it. It makes it like real and weird for me. Nope. It's, I don't know, it's weird.
When you build a bear, don't at the very end, you put a heart inside and you like seal it up.
I don't know. That's weird to me. I don't want to, I don't like it. I want this shit full of
stuffing. That's it. I don't want to put like a, I don't want to do like a freaking
seance. You whisper into the heart and you can have it have a secret message.
It's not German. It's a plushie. I know what it is. They're like every mall in America.
This is so good. Oh, I mean they look like they're high quality. I just don't want to like
breathe a wish into a heart and seal it inside of the thing's body. All right, let's go. It's
not a voodoo doll. Facecam? You guys seriously are, come on. Want to see what it looks like?
What do you think about that? But we need a worst hair candidate, right? It's not enough.
It's like, okay, you know what's really funny about hair? I look like a mad scientist right now.
I just made myself handsome. Do you see how fucking weird that is? Mad scientist, scary person,
handsome young man. Like why? Because I got something on my mouth. It was on my mouth.
Everyone was just freaked out. I thought I was going to do it in one bite. No, I would joke.
I'm still young. You're young until you're 50. That I believe. You look like your name would be
Maurice. I look tall today. Thanks. All right, I'm sick of holding this. Okay, I forgot to talk.
All right, let's go. Bye smart. I rest yet. Are you chewing a tire? It's a fucking cliff bar.
It takes ages to eat these. I didn't just bite into like a piece of deli turkey. I'm not kidding.
I'm still going. Almost done. Yeah, I have plenty of teeth. I guarantee you can't eat a cliff bar
in like 30 seconds. You'll fucking choke. Yeah, I have more than six teeth. I promise. I like
drinking on camera. This is a beer. All right, let's go. Show me your teeth. Give me the controller
while you're eating. I like wood. Training begins now. It's going to be air entry, isn't it? Come on.
Come on, Gwen. Come on, Gwen. Air entry. Which one do I want to do? Which air entry do I want to do?
I'm just going to address this person because I think they've written this like 50 to 60 times
in the last two hours. This game copied among us. I'm just going to say it because I know that
it'll probably make you stop saying it. I've said it. There you go. Why is my face came so dark?
Because I... Okay, I was thinking about buying one of those ring lights. Then you'd see what I'd
really look like. I don't want that. Why did you acknowledge it? What air entry do I want to do?
Scale one? Okay, it's cheap. Let's go. No, you guys said Torbo was awful. Speed or intelligence?
Mandy. Go to Mandy. Power in life, though. Pappas. I'll do Pappas. No, let's go.
Intelligence. You get something called Fire Twister. All right, we can skip this somehow,
right? I know I'm going to start becoming Skipping Andy. Didn't get it there. Sorry,
I got another chance. Nice. Give me that skill. Skulled it? Why? All right, didn't get one.
Your remaining skills are Fire Twister from Pappas and Fire Stream from Korea.
You need 500 intelligence. Okay. Pappas in Korea. All right, we need to rest. Sleep.
Just lost an S-ranked tourney by missing a 93% chance. Is this another air entry? Am I going
to do back-to-back air entries? Oh, all right, this is good. I'm going to use the mint leaf
right now, though. I'm going to do Heavy Technique. Oh no, I did that wrong. Oops. Oh well. I'll buy
nut oil instead. Move out of the junk. Disc chips. Burn them. Okay, I'll get another mint leaf. It's
not what I want. This one right here. Okay, good. We're not peeping any horrors. No. Speed. Speed.
Ooh, great. Come on. I can't get more than that. I wonder when become... When am I getting to Prime?
Probably not for a little while, right? I think I'm going to do Meditate. You're an Amazon Prime
streamer? What are you talking about? Intelligence, just normally. Nuts oil. Do Meditate again. This
time get it right. Oh, you're going to piss me off. You pissed me off. You pissed me off. Who do you
want? You have to have 17k for May. Oh shit. We have to unfreeze the wall to make some money?
What day is it? Okay, we have to bring the wall out to do this C rank because I need to have
$17,000 to get to this. So I can train here. Can I do this already? I'm supposed to forget what I
fed them. Please get it right. Good. Good. Good. Looks like the seed we saw has already germinated.
Ooh, very cool. Well, okay, we're gonna go make some money. Only nine more years. Yeah, that's good.
Okay, so we have to make this money. Oh, I guess I could. Yeah, I get the 3000. I want some wiggle
room. I don't want to be broke. Phoenix Prime can take four years. Holy shit. What? Go make some
money. I actually might just have the wall do this one and this one, right? Like who cares? If he dies,
then I guess he's gonna die. Do you want to poll for this? This is C rank. Why you put a face cam
on if we can't even see you? There. You see me? Why would you ever vote against this? He's too old.
He's too old. Really? I actually lost. 20, 21, 22. Saved. Right at the buzzer. He's just too old.
He's just sloppy. Scammed. This actually, I'll probably do it in one hit. Maybe another hit.
How close is he to dying? I don't know. Probably pretty close. Well, to be fair, I am just farming
money with this guy. This is not... If you're voting at your own risk here, you're betting
at your own risk. I just want to make sure I have enough money where I'm not going to go broke so I
can still train the bird. It is free money. You have 750k. 750k what? Subscribers? That'd be weird.
Oh, it's followers? That's cool. Do you think I'll ever get to a million? That's the one thing. So on
YouTube, I've moved around too much. So I remember I was approaching like 700 or 800,000 subs on
German985 on YouTube, and I didn't get there. So I moved on to Twitch, started this channel,
getting to 750,000. The second channel has 700,000. I wonder if any of these platforms
will ever have a million. I might get close. It depends on how much longer I do this.
Third account. Yeah, but I get to say, right? I can say, well, you know, I have over 2.4 million
followers across his platforms. No, more than that. If you include Twitter and shit.
I've got over 2.5 million followers across all of my platforms. I can say that. Even though it's
fucking horse shit. What happened to Cosmic Andy? Cosmic Andy is going to be all right. How about,
how about it Cosmic Andy? One last A win. You can do it. Only four people. All right, let's go.
Time for Cosmic Andy to pull it out. This is five more grand. One last one Cosmic Andy. It's not
even his name. Let's go. So before five or 6,000 and I can solidify Cosmic Andy as an A rank,
technically S ranked monster. All I gotta do is flip a few coins and win. Let's go. 740 intelligence.
I'm going to pick my battle here. I'm not going to do anything right away.
Build up the guts. 34%. It's a big problem. And you drained me of my guts too. He's dead.
This little shit has won so many times. It's so unfair. I always have to fight this stupid
guy first. I can still make a few thousand dollars though. I just have to win. This character is
ridiculous. I just have to get a crit. Pray for a crit. Bounce away. Bounce back. Eat shit. I'm
going to get money. I actually get money. I think I'll get at least a thousand bucks.
Got to win one more. All right. Lampsweet wins. I have to beat Kitty. Oh no. Arkealan.
All right. This is a must win scenario right here. Fuck. 2,000. 200 for third place. What?
Okay. Put them on ice. Get them out of here. Dude, you're fucking up my schedule. I have to pay for
the stadium. Whatever it is. What happened? Oh, come on. I have to buy the... It skipped the week
that I need to build the stable. You know what? Go back to town. Just stay here. You tried. You're
just too old. I got the money that I wanted from the last one. So we're good. Let's go brisket.
Okay. We can do a little bit of a rest. How are you? Are you okay?
Intelligence. Is Brickette tired? I thought birds are supposed to be smart. Birds are supposed to
be intelligent. Here we go. Better provide the stable first than bread. If the stable is clean,
brisket can live comfortably. Besides, we cannot train a big monster with a small stable.
$15,000 to rebuild the stable. Brisket will be very happy. All right. Got it. Now I can get
huge monsters. Very cool. We got 4,300 bucks. All right. So now we do nut oil. Heavy train.
I can now get the big dog. Nice. All right. Meditate. Let's go.
Your receive award submissions close in two hours. That's right. Let's actually talk about that.
If there's something that you want to nominate, now is the time to do it. And then in a couple
of days, probably like two or three days over this weekend, I'd say by Sunday, I will put the poll
in the discord. I'll put it here and I'll tweet about it. So if you have something you want to
nominate, this is the last opportunity to do it. Have I caught a shiny yet? Not the right game.
Tablets. There are way too many submissions. Well, like all awards ceremonies, the nominations,
every single nominee is going to get in. It passes through a filter and some stuff is going to be
removed. It'll be narrowed down. So don't worry. There's going to be, it's not going to be,
you're not going to have to vote between one in 40 submissions for the same category.
Stress reduction. I'm going to do speed. 1984. Not getting increases. Come on. Get into the
prime of your life already. How old are you? Seven months. How long do they live? When can I expect
to see a prime here? Five years is prime. Three years. I want more speed. Tell people that when
they check the spreadsheet to control F and make sure they're not submitting the same thing. Yeah,
make sure you take, get a, give it a good look. Make sure you're not quadruple submitting the
same thing. Intelligence. I'm not going to do life until I can actually get good points for it.
I hope the toucan is getting paid. Should I do the official tournament? Yeah, we'll do this one.
Remember I skipped the rank, so I'm good to go. 330 intelligence already. Not even in my prime yet.
I might get this guy to 800 intelligence or more. All right. We'll do the tournament this week because
I need to make a little bit of money and he'll get stats. You're going to do Mario paint tonight.
Intelligence again. You probably get 802 stats. That'd be insane. Phoenix has the highest stat
growth in intelligence. So it will grow super fast like that. Nice job. All right. Let's kick
some ass. I need to buy more shit. I don't want to blow all my money. All right. That'll be a full
week battle. You missed somebody who was majoring in bird law. I watch always sunny too. I was going
to wink at you, but nah, thought about it though. How do we square up here? Really, really good.
I even have pretty good power compared to this guy. All right. Hold off here. I'm going to farm
some guts because I don't want to, well, actually stay back. You can't do anything. You used to be
in the phone. No. Oh, all right. You got to land something, dude. Like land and move 20 seconds.
There it is. Good dodges. All right. We're, we're good. Clean. Is him defense? Well, that's what I'm
doing. Speed, speed and defense. Uh, don't work that well together. You should focus on one.
You can only realistically get maybe three or four stats even remotely increased.
I could do defense, but defense, I want some of the Lord masters to help me here. Defense, I think
is the worst stat in the whole game. They fixed that in the remake because defense is supposed to
be the worst stat in the game. The way that it's calculated is awful. Apparently you're much better
off just not getting hit and building a little defense. So I'm going to go speed. It fits
thematically. I'm a bird. I want to go speedy and dodge and fly and come on. It's thematics.
It doesn't hurt at all. It's a crit. Just let's go for the kill here. Any point you can take in
defense is better spent on life. Well, especially because life works on the expeditions. So speed
in life, it'll help the expeditions. Speed is technically defense. I feel like back,
back in the game here, I'm not just one button Andy. I actually have to move around and worry
about placement. It hasn't felt like this in a while. I could probably one hit kill this person.
Actually might be able to do it. Let's see. Don't get cocky. Oh yeah. All right,
I'm going to go for a talent face. 2000 bucks. What happened to Cosmic? He ate too much shoe
polish and died. Back to the training. I forgot that was 2000. Yeah. Oh, should I take those drugs?
Will that fuck me up too much? Will I like get sick? Not bad. Oh, I think I sold it. No, I didn't.
Where are they? Yeah, this life and skill will increase. Speed will decrease. What is this worth
it? Does this lose lifespan or should I just sell it? No, it's bad for lifespan. So we're just going
to sell these. Okay. It seems like all the items are not really worth using because they just bring
your total maximum lifespan down. 1500. That's a lot of money. All right. It reduces your lifespan
by five weeks. Your skill and life go up by 10. It reduces your speed by 10. Okay. All right. Let's
do it. I need to do a little training first, which will do intelligence. What about skill?
I'll do it. Hit the prime of your life already. I'm going to do an errand tree too.
Intelligence and skill. Bitchy nose. Meditate. So what am I looking for in an errand tree?
It was Papa's and Korea. Well, like the heat. Shit defense. You have a Wikipedia page now.
Only do an errand tree if you have intelligence at 500. Okay. So let's just get it to, let's just
burn it up to 500. Fire twister. Fire. That sounds awesome. What do you think about Spy Kids 2?
Um, is that the, is that the shark, uh, boy and lava girl? It's a different movie. Wait,
that's a different movie. Are you, are you sure though? Are you sure? The same director.
Spy Kids 3D was the best one. That was an Omega. Oh hell yeah. 17. We're not even in prime yet.
All right. We have to stop praising cause he's getting a little fond. He's getting a little
soft. Spoiled. Uh, speed. Pick it. It's a better game. Monster rancher or a wrestling empire.
That's not fair. They're both completely different things. Focus on skill now. I think we can. Oh,
I don't have enough intelligence to do this. Do I? Oh, okay. Well, come on. All right. I'm
going to do the skill one because it's a thousand bucks for like probably 10 to 20 guaranteed skill.
Do Mandy for the int move. Okay. It's power and life. Oh, should I do, should I just go
to Torbulent just for the skill or Papas for the speed? Mandy for the move. How much better is the
move and what I have now? Save. Mandy gives a move guaranteed. Oh, all right. Is it intelligence?
Is it actually intelligence? Mandy. And let's fight the plate. Yeah. I don't care about the
tournament cause I'm just going to skip it anyways. Cause this guy's going to be unbeatable.
Twisters. Let's just drop that. I'm not going to skip it if we haven't seen it yet.
I love the beam bag Sonic like Pepe dancing. Got it. Are you a monster rancher streamer now?
I told you this is going to happen until I at least got to S rank. I don't know if I'm going to
beat the whole game, but I definitely want to get to at least S. I want to, I want it to level up
at least two or three monsters to like full completion. I'm having fun. I think it's fun.
Did you make it? Oh no. Did it work? Kind of. Play Digimon world one. I'm not really into the
Digimon Pokemon. I only like this because it's big numbers. It's a really large scale between zero
and a thousand. I like the idea of pulling monsters randomly. That can be kind of combined
randomly. I like the RNG of this game. I don't like the RNG of Pokemon. These are not big numbers.
Zero to a thousand is not a big number. Digimon one is pretty much at this game.
Well, all other games don't exist to me. Other games are just not monster rancher.
Just remake this. Just remake Monster Rancher. Have it be not a remake, but a reboot.
I don't want a one-to-one just graphical update of the first game. Just reboot the whole franchise
and instead of there being like a hundred monsters have to be like 500. And instead of
two types, you'd have like the main type and the subtype. Have main type and like three subtypes
of something crazy. Don't make it pay to win bullshit either. Don't make it like paid
bullshit. I don't want to open up like gotcha containers for monsters. Don't do that. Please
God. I got the new technique. I can't praise. I want to, but I can't. I'm sorry. It's a hundred
percent would be gotcha if it was made today. Oh no. A to rest. Remember the TV burn person
updated in the discord. Please look. Are you serious? Wait, hold on. Really? It can't be.
It can't be. I need to see. I can't tell. Is it still there?
Okay. Hold on. Hold on. I have to show this. This is unbelievable. No fucking way. No way. I don't
believe you. This is one of the funniest images. This image is actually really funny because hold
on. The fact that there's people, we have to dissect this. We need to dissect this right now.
Okay. Hold on. You got to be kidding me, man. The fact that you're taking this photo, by the way,
like you're taking this photo, like hidden somewhere, like look, there's no fucking way, dude.
No, that would be so horrible.
The best part is the fact that you're taking this from like hidden in the staircase up. I don't know
where you are, but like, look at these people watching the TV. This image is unbelievable.
Like the sleeping dog. Like you guys have to deal with this now. You guys have to put up with this
now. This is unbelievable. What do you mean this is not real? What?
I mean, can we see the angle here? It looks like the angle is a little bit,
we need to cross reference the photos. Oh shit. You're right. That's perfect. Let's do some
detective work. We actually have to cross reference the photos. What are you doing?
What are you doing? Where's the clock? Is the clock here? It's real. But you can't see the
clock from this angle, but wait a minute. Look at that. I see the sound bar, same sound bar.
The console's in the same spot. Dude, let me just tell you, if this is real, this is one of the
funniest things I've ever fucking heard of. I can't believe that you've ruined your TV. It's so stupid.
You know, I think we need, we need a little bit, we need one, we need one more piece of proof.
I need, I need this, this is proof, like real proof. What about the fake reflection?
We needed, we need another picture, but we need one or we need a video.
All right, if you can get me a video, if you can get me a video, I swear to God, I'm not
fucking around right now. I am not kidding around. If you can get me a video where this is real,
I swear to God, I am not kidding. I will put you in touch with Community Jake
and I will get you a new TV. I swear to God, this is too funny, but make sure, make sure in your video,
well, I will have one of the mods take a look at it because I want to make sure you don't,
you know, no personal information or anything, right? All I need is that TV. God. Okay,
let's get back to this. I just imagine everybody else that has to watch the TV in this house is
probably just, how irritated must you be? Was this a new TV? I don't know. They probably hate me.
Remember, why are all your fans insane? Look, this was an easy mistake. If you get us a video,
I might, it might be, I might not be able to stop laughing. I might have to leave,
but definitely make sure if you're going to make, if you actually, if this is not a joke
and you're actually going to take a video, please, you know, protect your privacy. I don't want like
your, I don't want to like blow up your spot or anything. You know what I mean? Just we'll,
we'll have one of the mods look at it to make sure that's absolutely hysterical. Let's keep playing.
God, look at this air entry again. If this is real, I'll have to probably leave too,
cause I'll start sobbing. I don't, that might be the most, I don't think we can even nominate it.
It's literally in four hours, one guy, the year nominations close. I think that we just have to
give that a pass that like it's, it could be one of the greatest ever. I can't focus on anything
right now. Having that in my brain. That's so ridiculous. Okay. What was I, what's going on
item shop? Oh, they are cheaper. Nice. Okay. What was the last thing I did? What about the camera?
Right. Sorry about that. I'm breathing. I'm fine. What was the last thing I did before that bird
rested after being stressed. Okay. So now we can just go back to starting over. I want intelligence
and skill. Go for it. Oh, check that. I got to move. Right. What? Yes. Gold. Hired. What?
Kind of hate you to be honest. Why? What? I'm sorry. I hate me. I don't want anyone to hate me.
All right. Skill. Simulate the burning. Oh, I just got like an electrocuted. You even get like a
chill that just like electrocutes your whole body. Oh, one year birthday. You know, a week from now
during the you laugh, you lose challenge, the video's not even going to make me laugh. I'm
going to like see that family sitting watching the TV. It's going to pop into my head and
I'm going to start laughing for the good work for scat. Seems well. Let's do the stress relief.
Intelligence. I wanted really hammer intelligence because I got to get it over 500 so I can get
flame tornado. Nice. Oh, 12 tablets. Always tablets. Nothing but tablets only. All right.
Dragon quest. I would probably like dragon quest. It's just never committed to it.
400 int and speed from Papa's. Oh, okay. I'll keep that in mind. I should probably do a. Yeah,
I'll do a tournament. We'll do this one. Why you always broke every other streamer I've seen. This
has a lot of money. Well, I had like 20 grand. I just used it. I upgraded the house. I had like
23,000 24,000. Oh, I'm strict. I got to change that. I really like dragon quest 11 the most
because you get to see enemies on the map. That's huge for me. Yeah, I got to be less strict.
Go for it. Oh, I didn't even look at the I didn't even look at the move. You're right.
Lot of intelligence. I need to get that speed and life up. Oh, shit. It's heat beam. I got to take
a look at that. Whoa. This character is awesome. That's a lot of guts, though. It's not very good
percentage. Probably does a lot of damage on dude. Really angry means you're going to miss.
That's why we build speed. Precisely why I need speed at least at 300 before I even
attempt C or B. Can you do Homer Simpson impression? I like that show. And I thought
it might be funny. Yeah, but you can't use that. The submissions are over. You can't use it.
First, it wins by default. They're afraid of me. Could have said no. Then I wouldn't have offended
them to leave. I like gatekeep my own new viewers. It's weird. Oh, guys, I'm going to do this thing
where like a new viewer is going to come and hate me. I do that all the time. I don't want
anybody to hate me. I just said I didn't want hate. I don't want people to hate me. I really like
really don't. Look, if you like actually hate me, that makes me like feel like shitty. I like hope
you really don't. I don't know. People probably do. I don't know. I like hate that feeling.
Nice. As long as you like yourself. Yeah, I'm very happy and comfortable with me. I am. I'm
just pretty comfortable. I don't be too much of a dick though. All right. All right. Good job.
You learn some stuff. Do I have enough items? All right. Rest. When's the new week? All right.
We'll do a rest. Sleep. Yes. Drill intelligence. I want an air entry. Let's go. I'm sorry for
calling you broke earlier. I don't matter. All right. Tablets. I'm starting to see
increases in the amount of stats I'm getting the first time here. What's up? We are well.
We're going to take a nut oil and then we're going to do heavy intelligence training or do it. No.
Yes. Make it great. 400. Hell yeah. Now I'm going to focus on skill and speed for a little while.
Let's go with skill. I'm going to alternate between skill and speed. You can't just dump
everything in one stat and you're just going to lose. You'll get killed. These increases are so
small. What are your thoughts on beans? I love beans. Speed. We'll go with this one. I want to
int and skill from Papa's. Should be good. Ready to go. No tournament. No official tournament
because I don't want to lose fame for going up or going back down. When's the next battle?
Not for a while. Not yet. Do I do life? Yeah. I got to sprinkle some life in here. Come on.
Otherwise I'm going to be a little like weenie. Here we go. Play Hearthstone Battle Royale.
I have 150 wins in first place in Hearthstone Battle Royale. Wait I made that up. I don't think
that's a lie. No I have 150 fourth place or higher ranks and like 50 first place wins. I had like
five or six thousand rating when I cared. 5200 or something? 5100? Win one right now. I can't.
The only way you could. No I couldn't. You have to play that shit every day and every time they
make a new update you have to play it because as of now there's been 10 new characters and like
40 new cards. I'm just getting my ass kicked for like a week. All right more training.
What was the last thing I did? Oh fuck it whatever. All right speed and intelligence. No
intelligence and skill. I will never stream Hearthstone ever again. I'll never stream it
again. Are you going to play Peggle? Nah. What about Yu-Gi-Oh? Nah. Good job. Oh really good job.
Hell yeah. 11 points. All right when I get I do a lot of spinning like this. I was just spinning
around in my chair. It's probably distracting I'm sorry. Speed and intelligence again. Not getting
hit sometimes is almost more important than getting hit. Than getting hits. Do not eat a magic banana.
Oh it's a glitch. Do list of the roses. It's chess combined with Yu-Gi-Oh. Sounds pretty good. Speed
again. What's a game that you could confidently speed run? Uh I actually tried to do Mario 64
recently just in my own time. Uh I was able to do the bomb glitch through the wall where you go
like yeah what and you grab the bomb and boom through the gate. I did it a few times but then
I realized it took me like two or three hundred attempts to do that like while I was just sitting
on the couch. I said I'm not I don't want to do this ever again. I don't have the patience for it.
I just don't. That's not a fake story. I could probably do it right now if I really sat there
for like 10 to 20 minutes. I'm not kidding I could probably do it right now. Do it right now?
You want me to do it right now? Thinking about it. I'm thinking about going and getting the switch.
And yes I'm I did it on the switch and I have everyone says don't play it on the switch. Switch
has input lag. That means I did it on the switch with the input lag. With the Joy-Cons. Okay uh so
look what I already have a save point right here. I already have a save point right here. Why would
I have a suspend point there if I wasn't doing this? Huh? What do you think? You want to see
something fucking happen on this stream? I'll show you the practice that I've had. Move this out of
the way. Can you see? Can you see it? All right you can't see it. Hold on let me. I let me move this
shit out of the way. I how am I gonna be able to do this shit? I'm gonna I need the dock. I need the
dock. I actually think I need the dock for this because I'm gonna be like uncomfortable. Let's
punch again. Okay uh let me see. Let's punch. I need the I actually need the dock. You ready?
Here we go. Fuck. I fucked it up. Fuck. I'm getting the dock. I'll be right back. I'm not
ready yet. Why can't I see it? Plugged in. Put the music on. All right here you go. I'm doing this on
stream right now. It's gonna be so like scuffed. It's gonna be terrible looking. Okay I need a
the video capture device. What the hell is it? We're gonna add video capture device. What the fuck?
Hello? What just happened? Can you see me? Can anybody hear me? What the fuck is go-
What the fuck is happening? Dude I swear to god. I swear to god. Can you guys hear me? I just I went
live to try to go to come back and this shit was like somebody's already live on your channel. It
was like oh yeah there's a connection error trying to stream to this. My screen was like black. That
was weird. What the hell? The VOD's probably so fucked up now. All right let's go. I'm going for
this right now. I'm gonna get this. I swear to god. That was that was really really weird. All
right hold on. Sorry about that. I'm back. Give me give me a second. Ask me what the fuck that was.
Okay let's do this. It's not going to be perfect but I have to desync myself.
It's not going to be perfect. Just relax.
Okay there we go. So now I have to put this on this tv. All the- I'm swear I'm gonna get it. I
swear to god. What a viewer drop. Well I mean the whole stream fucking exploded.
He'll be back. Don't worry. He'll be back. Okay let me just plug this in here. Watch this shit.
You ready for this? You ready?
Fuck. It's just end point.
God damn it. I get it. I fucking hate these little things.
Yes. My knees. I swear to god I've done this like three or four times.
I'm gonna smash these into a million fucking pieces.
I'm getting the controller. I'm getting the real controller. I'll be back.
Oh my fuck. I forgot. I just leaked the dashboard. Now you all know I bought this.
And I wrote like a tweet saying this thing but I would never buy it.
Hello? I have to re- oh change grip and order. Stupid fucking thing.
I'm gonna get this or I won't turn the stream off. Let's go. Can you guys hear it? Is it loud?
Fuck you game. Oh it says I'm playing Monster Rancher. This is wrong.
It's gonna- I'll get it in a second. We'll go right back. Oh what?
What? No!
Hug the wall? Oh fuck you. That was it. Oh that was gonna be it. Damn it.
Gamer card deactivated. Not yet. I had it so close. God damn it. I hate this game.
Did we break a thousand? Wait there's not even a thousand viewers here? What happened? What?
I don't even have a thousand viewers? God. It's ten thousand? Okay. I've gotten it before. I
swear to god. Dude this dude's past his prime. 30. Past his prime. I'm 36. Oh my god. Believe in me.
Mario goes like this to turn around. Oh it's the fucking dumbest thing. I hate this game.
Oh wait a minute. I think I'm supposed to do that. Fuck you. It's chat. What's going on in chat right
now? What are you guys doing? You suck. I don't. Stop. I'm gonna say losing viewers. Say gaining
viewers so I get confidence. What happened? That was it. Oh my god. I could never do this.
How many viewers are here? Losing viewers.
I give up. I give up. I give up. I give up. I give up. I give up. I can't do it. I give up.
I actually can't do it. I give up. Just ground pound the pole. No. No. You don't. That's not
what I'm trying to do. Oh fuck. You explode already. That was the one. You fucking idiot.
Yeah. All right. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Did you tell that I've been practicing?
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. That's it. I'm done. Fucking practice makes perfect, baby.
What else we got? What else have I been practicing? How about this one?
All right. So we're gonna play Monster Rancher again. Never playing fucking Super Mario ever
again. What the fuck happened there, by the way? My stream crashed three times. I told you I was
gonna do it before the stream ended. Fix this. Fix that. You earned it. Well, now I have to do
that in like 17 and a half minutes. We're back. We're ready. I don't remember anything that just
happened. Sorry for the crashing. Should not be a delay anymore. What do I wanna do now? Why are
you angry? I wasn't angry. I mean, I was angry at Mario 64. You just blacked out for the whole
thing? Okay. What was the last thing that I did? Which has been breaking a lot today. Actually,
that hurt. Yeah. I heard that too. I think I rested. Let's just go. Oh, here we go. Right.
All right. Let's do, um, we'll rest and then we'll take, uh, brisket into the fight.
I'm glad I actually got to prove myself. I want the skill points. This should be pretty easy.
I need to turn the switch off. I love Jerma, but I just can't enjoy his non-Super Mario 64 streams.
He should just stick with what he was good at. That's so stupid. You know, I was thinking,
you, okay, there's a deeper reason as to why I was practicing that. I wanted so badly just to
go live one day with splits and actually really desperately try to get like sub 25 minutes.
Just to just not tell you guys at all. But then I saw how much actual work skill and dedication
it takes to do that. And I threw that idea out the window. All right, let's farm here.
That takes so much guts and I don't even know if it's worth joining. I'm going to kill. Oh,
not quite like I got a headache from that Super Mario thing. Did I really think I was going to
be able to hold it this way and do that? You got to be kidding me. I was just too lazy to get the
dock. Can I have a turn or am I just going to keep doing this? Any more question? Are you all
right? Yeah, I'm good. What are you talking about? I feel great. How long have I even been streaming
for? Six hours. We'll keep going for a little bit. Six hour Andy. Yeah, I am a six hour Andy.
He's actually really funny because I'm, when I was bringing the switch here, it was open on YouTube
and I was, I must've been, I don't, I don't even remember. I was really tired. It was, it was like
an XQC playthrough. Like he was playing something like a horror game. And I was probably like, oh
yeah, get scared. I was literally, that's what was open. I must've been watching it last time. I had
the switch open. Juicer. I can't say I'm a juicer. I'm a juicer. What's wrong with that?
You know, the best part about being like a new juicer is this like 600 years of XQC streams.
I got a long way to go. It's like, oh wow. Look at all this. Look at all this. It's here. Stop
calling yourself that you weirdo. I got a lot of fame for that. Very good. Very good. Already have
more health than the entirety of our training for Calamity. Still on the grind? Not really. I just
like having fun. Remember, you're not allowed to like other streamers. He's cheating on us.
Remember, you doing that Mario 64 bit gave me anxiety and a stomach ache.
All right. Good fight. Good battle. Yeah. You guys kept talking about peep the horror. All of a
sudden you see a Mario 64 horror and you leave. I lost like, well, that doesn't, that's not fair.
I lost 2000 people because of the crash. That's what I'm going to tell myself when I'm taking
a bath later crying. All right. Let's go for it. Training. Grill. I want speed and intelligence.
I want speed. When are you going to do a snowman stream? I don't know what you're talking about.
Tablets. Always. Tablets when you're doing the training regimen.
It doesn't really snow in Vegas. Not really. I need to move this camera though. It's wrong.
It does not really snow here. Maybe, maybe once a year or once every couple of years
there'll be enough to see. But not really. I love it here though. It's really, really cold
and really, really hot. During December, January, February, it gets to be 30, 40 degrees here
Fahrenheit. I like it. It's kind of like a chilly dry. I like it a lot. We're going to be able to
get the new move. And then in the summertime it gets like 110, 115, 118 degrees Fahrenheit. I love
it. I'm just, I'm a weirdo. All right. Okay. Let's do mint leaf and then we're going to do
the errand tree. And I want to do Papa's errand tree, right? You miss Boston? Um, sometimes. I
miss the people in Boston. Not necessarily the place. It's kind of how it is though.
Papa's is where I can get the tornado move. It seems that there is some chance to acquire
a new technique. I can definitely handle. Yeah, this one. I don't care about the tournament.
We're going to skip it anyways. You're going to bed now. Good night. Well, have a good night.
Yeah. I'll probably won't stream for that much longer. Once we hit six plus hours or so,
which means you're going to have to see monster rancher too again, which I'm fine with.
Got it. Got the skill chapstick. Is this a burst piece? I'm only 30 minutes in. Oh, that's right.
The screen crashed. Start raising skill. Yeah. Once I get to speed, cause I'm going to hammer
skill. Once, uh, I get into prime, but I really do want like 300 speed and like four or 500
intelligence before I hammer skill. Cause I'm going to just pump, pump, pump, pump, pump, pump
into skill. Once I get, um, out of the kind of adolescent stage. What's the flavor? Uh,
the flavor of this bird's bees is coconut and pear. It's pretty good. All right. Let me take a look
at the moves that this guy has. I actually do need to do a tournament though. Why you do
chapstick so much? Well, uh, because my lips get really dry and I have this sort of tendency
constantly be like all the time air entry again. Oh no, that's good. I'll take it and honest. Oh,
very tired. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'll get some rest. I'm going to ask you about your dry
lips every stream. Yeah. I'm pretty much a lizard. I do need to buy some items. Don't lose all my
money. I will be pissed if I do. Can I sell something? Why is the plant one 1500? Is there
an update on the TV yet? I don't think so. I don't think we have a TV update. Is a good reason why
I saw Connor choke you the other day. You all right? Yeah. I was, it was uncalled for.
He's reached over and start choking my neck as hard as he could. I was like, what the heck, man?
I need the money. I need the money. How many I'll buy a couple more. I can only buy one more.
All right. That's fine. Have you eaten today? Yeah. I've eaten twice. Okay. You need to rest.
What did I have to eat? Well, you watched me eat a cliff bar and then earlier I had a coffee
and some air. So I actually didn't eat at all. I was lying. Battle today. No, I need to train.
Be life. Should I start? Not yet. What is wrong with streamers? Um, I'll tell you what's wrong
with streamers. A lot of us don't really want to eat on camera and the prospect of eating
like a dinner on camera or on stream, uh, it's kind of hard to talk and it's kind of hard to,
but okay, if I were to eat, it takes me probably like at least 15 to 30 minutes to eat dinner.
So I would have to like go BRB for 30 minutes, maybe 20 to 30 minutes. And I mean, if you're
talking about people watching the stream, I think you just saw the stream crashed for about
two minutes and two or 3000 people left. So if I disappeared for 25 minutes,
how many people would still be here? I wonder. Have dinner with us. Well, that's another thing
too. Like I don't stream long enough to hit that problem, right? Like, okay, if I have,
I usually have something before the stream. I usually be like a salad or like a light
breakfast or something, or like a lunch or something before the stream, which will,
my streams are only five to six hours, five to seven hours, which that's a decent enough time
where I don't really need to eat. I have plenty of water and sometimes I'll snack on something,
but, um, I guess if you're streaming like eight to 12 hours a day, you can't, you have to eat on
stream. Um, but if you stream less than six hours or seven hours a day, the prospect of kind of
taking 20, 15 to 20 minutes to eat, um, is like, you're kind of live and I'd rather scream because
I only stream for five hours or so and I wouldn't want to waste like 30 minutes of that eating food.
Get it? Don't yell at me, please. I have 90 loyalty, very, very loyal. This time I'm going
to do, I'm doing it again. We're going heavy, double heavy. I'm messing up the regimen here,
but I want to do it. I want that 500 intelligence. Bingo. All right. Now we focus on skill and speed.
Seem like you're the kind of guy that chews ice. Sometimes kind of fun. Depends on how big it is.
I like chewing a little bit of ice. I need to do a tournament. I'm not constantly doing it.
If I have a little drink that's, let's say I drink a soda, there's ice in the cup and I get to the
bottom of the soda and there's three or four little ice crunchies that are as big as little,
um, like chiclets. I'll just go, I'm not eating ice cubes, almost a hundred loyalty. This is a big
deal. I'm going to do skill and we'll go back to skill. So what would you guys say is a good
speed number to be able to hang at a rank? 300, 400, like 350, 450, 400. Oh, the tree's growing.
Oh, the lore master's left. Is the entire game pretty much just RNG? Um, kind of. It's pretty
much RNG, but it's fun. I'm going to run out of money. I need to do, all right, I'll do the
Gemini Cup. We'll rest. Oh yeah. I need to do the monster rancher one thing. Yeah. I'll do that
before I turn three months, so I don't forget. Does fame do anything? Fame increases your crit
strike chance. It's the bizarre back of the, in the data of the game code. I don't know why. It's
just, if your fame is higher, it's tied to your crit chance. Let's get some money. Is this baste
or fringe? Rotisserie chicken is the best chicken. I would say that's fringe. Bastetake would be
a, like fried chicken breast for a chicken sandwich. That's pretty fringe. Uh, it's looking
pretty good. I really need to work on skill. Skill and life. Yeah. I need skill bad. God,
keep picking this one. That move was not hit once. 74% chance. Am I actually going to lose
to Millium? I'm going to lose to Millium. Finally. Jesus. There's an update? Is there,
is this video proof? No, this is not. Don't fucking tell me. Are you serious? I don't see it. I don't
see it yet. Hold on. I need to show. This is funny. It's not, no, no, no. It's something else. It's
something else. Something else. It's funny too. Wait, they said so in the discord. I don't see it.
I need a mod to like vet that video and make sure like it's good if it's real. There's something
else I want to show. This is so funny. This is like actually me. It's my face. What's wrong with me?
Yeah, there he is. I just like want to go watch his stream. All right. Do we actually have a video
update? If we do, then I'm ending the stream because it has to end after that. I'll keep an
eye on the, on the mods. It's not, it's in the works. I can't, I can't believe it. It's real.
It's currently in transit. They have to finish rendering it? What do you mean,
what do you mean rendering it? Cell phone, film, and then send. What do you mean rendering?
I don't know about this one. I don't know. I'm not so sure about this one. There we go. Double tap.
You got to be patient. Okay. I'm patient. I'm going to be very patient. I mean, I'll tell you
what I'm looking for in that video. I'm looking for like a turn the TV off, turn the TV on and
like from at least three different angles. You know what I mean? Like, like it can't be doctored.
Unplug the TV. I'm mentally preparing for whatever this is. I want to hit him with this move.
I don't even know what it looks like. Oh, they might be uploading it to YouTube. What they said,
rendering. You got to have somebody walking in front of the TV. Oh shit. Like a body crossing
the plane of the television, right? Oh, it was a joke. Okay. I'm telling you, if I get undeniable
proof that that's real. Oh my goodness gracious. It's crazy. Part of me thinks that that's just not
possible. What TV is he talking about? He's talking about this. I never mind. I'm talking.
I, I, whatever. I thought it was this. I forgot to replace the image with the XQC image. 47 fame.
Ooh, nice. Very, very good. Very good. XQC is burned into my Nintendo Switch. Somebody said,
dude, I don't think it's real. They said, I don't think it took years for the Cartoon Network
logo to get burned into my TV. What? Yeah. What kind of TV do you have? Do you have like a liquid
crystal plasma TV from like 2002? I'm getting more and more skeptical by the minute. Oh,
LEDs have burning. I'm freaking out. I got to calm down. Okay. We're good. I'm going to lose my mind
if it's real. There's a piece of my brain that's like Jeremy. It's not going to be real. So don't
worry. It's just a joke. Speed. No, skill. I got a message from, uh, I got a message from, from,
from VR Josh. VR Josh says, Hey, check your DMs. So, uh, it's not real, dude. Uh, it was a Rick roll.
I'll leave it up to you how you decide to tell everybody. I was about to buy a motherfucker,
a new plasma TV. All right. I knew it wasn't real. No way. Your TV from like,
your TV has to be from like 2003. No way. No fucking way. So what the hell? What, where,
what, where were you? What is the picture? Is that actually your living room and you just doctored
it? I'm so confused. That's so funny. I want to look at it again. Oh, I thought you wish it was
real though. Like that's so perfect. The original image. You guys are such fucking jokers. I swear
to God. The original image is this for those of you that weren't here a few hours ago,
there's a message in the discord and it said this. Where is it? I'm home for the holidays
from college. I decided to watch some German. You just, you can read it. I can't read it. It's
gonna make me laugh. That was a good fake up. That was great. Yeah. Now thinking about it. This is
way too detailed rendering. Oh yeah. That was pretty good bait though. You had us all rolling.
You had, you had, you had the whole group fooled for like four hours. That was great. I nominate,
I nominate that for best one guy of the year. So I'm going to give it a stamp of it's already
one of them that wins. So it can't get nominated because it's going to win. I was really hoping
we were going to get a fucking video though. Even if it was fake as shit. Time frame. It probably
would take a little while. All right. What the hell am I doing here? Official D. I'm going for
official D. Let's do a little bit more training. Skill. Now I want a big skill. Is there a big
skill? Power, speed, defense, and intelligence. No, there's not a big skill. We're just going to
do it this way. What if somebody actually burns your face into their TV on purpose? Well, I talked
about that earlier. I ain't replacing any TVs. If you go and buy like an old LED TV and you burn
my face into it and you go, dude, you owe me a thousand bucks for a new TV. I ain't going to
give it to you. I already talked about it already. That was legitimate. I was going to, I was about
to have that person contact community Jake to like get that TV and replace it. If you break
any of your shit and you play, I didn't do it. And I'm telling you right now, I'm not replacing
it. If you do, let's just make that dead serious clear. Imagine if, imagine if they faked it so
well that they got like a fucking $1,500 TV out of that. I would think you would have deserved it.
Yeah. You would deserve it by that point. Absolutely. If a TV has a prize, that effort
should warrant a new team would have to be warranted a new TV. You got to respect the grift.
All right. When's the battle after this battle? I'm going to probably, I'm going to take off.
I'm going to get some food. No, don't intentionally burn a TV. Don't intentionally burn in a TV.
Don't do that. No, it's this, the bit was funny. The bit was cool, but I don't, I don't want to
wake up like on Friday afternoon or something. And there's like 30 images in the discord of like
people burning their TVs. And don't do it. I'm not even going to click them. I'm not, I mean,
I'm not going to click them. Nope. The joke's over. Joke is over. I need to do mint leaf.
That's so goddamn funny. Wait, what the fuck are you talking about? You look like you smell salty,
not dirty, salty, but just straight up like sulfur. I smell like, like the end of a creamed corn can
when you dump it out and you just go like this and you smell it, which actually smells kind of good.
Ooh, excellent job. That's going to be at least 10 to 15.
Oh, all right. Okay. Okay. Let's do it. Official D over to C. I never do that voice again.
People beg me to do that voice on a monthly basis. I feel great if it drinks from this, really.
Grandma, can we get one more before the nominations close? That wasn't even nominated. Oh my God.
That wasn't even a category. What am I thinking? It was, it was. Okay. It was. I don't think it is.
All right. Adding another category. We're adding it Ooh, category. Last minute category. You have
two hours to figure it out. It might not even show up. I bet you can't do Toy Boat for one minute.
One, two, Toy Boat, Toy Boat. One, two, Toy Boat, Toy Boat. Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat,
Toy Boat. Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat, Toy Boat,
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat
Lost my mojo. How do you spell? I was gonna do a really love
I
Could probably do it. No don't need to be nominated. I'll do it. Perfect. I'm never doing it ever again
I'm gonna get it. Perfect. Just wait
I'll get it. Perfect
don't even nominate it for anything i already did the best one because i'm leaving um don't
make it a category i'm not gonna don't make a category for it oh he's so wacky oh he's like
the wackiest guy in the world it already was a category no it wasn't i thought it
all right i gotta go i need to get food in my body i want to see what this move looks like it just
sucks heat beam damage mosquitoes after that oh you're gonna hit me okay fine he's delirious
i think uh the mario 64 part of the stream took like 10 years off my life i smoked like 400 packs
of cigarettes right there like an hour ago that was an errantry can you talk while inhaling at
the same time hi no can you please spell the sound it's just oh oh oh just spell it oh oh
i have to spell this word for you the category cat the category is best oh oh oh i this is not
i didn't put that for a category i put it in oh my god my eye did you see that oh what's happening
look at this what the fuck my eyelid just like went inside out for a second that was crazy
i put it in this character is awesome we're not even in prime yet can you believe it i'm
getting off camera right now i'm fucking out of here i can't have that pointing at me because
i just act like a fucking weirdo i'm sorry everybody put it back on nobody said are you
breathing in mold did you even say that or what why did you say that all right i'm out of here
all right i'll come back on i'll behave this is great though almost 470 intelligence 220 health
the speed is really really good get that to 300 get the skill to 300 and get intelligence to
five or 600 that should take me all the way to s we're never gonna get to see that move
actually really good i really want one of these dogs can i make a phoenix dog is that possible
that'd be pretty cool no don't get too close dude don't do that don't get hit don't get hit
oh my god who has a higher percentage okay good what's on my forehead uh it's my eyebrow bone
dude we'll be officially rank c we're not even in prime yet this is the one this is definitely
the character i was auto auto is great auto is very very good let's do i gotta just just punch
low defense i'm just gonna hurt how old is auto auto is 10 i believe turns 11 in march
we don't really know so i don't really know it's hard to tell because i rescued auto
did not uh i did not have auto when he was a baby auto was already about two to three years old they
didn't really know uh but thinking about 11 maybe maybe 11 years old and do a birthday party okay
i'm gonna lose this let me do a move i won yeah i won skill is now the most important stat
definitely what was the last time you ate beef wellington i've never had beef wellington before
my life big fancy corn dog i don't want it it's like red in the middle no thank you it looks
nasty it does you're not qualified to impersonate gordon ramsay i won't make that mistake again
prime rib is superior i'm not a big meat guy though i just not i'm not i don't like a big roast
i like cheeseburgers i like steak like shaved steak i like corn beef or if it's really good
but like a big pot roast i don't know something about it it's like too wet i don't like a pot
roast it's wet does that make sense to you something about it feels wet to me what about
meatloaf meatloaf is okay it's got to be really good meatloaf though some people make meatloaf
they just throw a bunch of shit in the pan they just dump like just beef in there and just put
ketchup all over it and they don't even like some people just make a shitty meatloaf meatloaf is
bad i like it it just has to be made right almost 100 loyalty all right all right i'm out of here
it was fun you'll see monster ranch 2 again we have the brisket saga to complete which is not
complete yet yeah i want to get some food did you ever get to a rank i got to a rank i didn't
beat a rank uh what's the next stream going to be that's a really good question i have a lot of
stuff to do very exciting stuff but a lot of stuff over the next like three or four days
it's i'm not sure i'll get back to you on that it's at least on tuesday because that's when the
you laugh you lose stuff is going to be i don't know if i'm gonna have time to go live this
weekend i'll figure it out expect to stream in the next four or five days uh and if you'll see me
on tuesday guaranteed i also want everybody to understand that there is no more nominations
after today they will be this weekend the categories the poll that you will be able to vote
on these categories this weekend this is closing in like an hour or two so make sure you get
something in if you want to see it baby sensory and the you laugh lose is tuesday it's going to
be fun i've never done it before i feel like it's gonna be a lot of good time we'll find out have
a great weekend everybody if there's a surprise random stream in the next two days just it might
happen i can't tell you i figure a place to put it what is baby sensory uh i'm you'll see thanks
watching everybody let's end this let me save this before i do that though we're good to go
brisket saga can continue i might change it up a little bit though might do something else and
then we'll go back to monster rancher but i have to do this i have to beat it figure it out thank
you for watching as always the credits are broken oh shit all right well thanks for watching everybody
appreciate it oh because the stream crashed the stream crashed that's right i forgot sorry about
that everybody regardless thanks for the subs this usually shows everybody that's subbed today
really appreciate it i'll see you guys within the next four or five days keep an eye on the sus
take care of yourselves don't burn any images into your screen we i am not going to tolerate
it i won't look at them but thanks for watching see you soon have a great night