For more sound effects, please like and subscribe.
I hope you enjoyed this video, and I'll see you in the next one.
Hey guys, welcome to my stream. I'm friends with Ster. For more sound effects, please like and subscribe.
That's all the plus twos I got. That's not fair.
It really isn't. Hold on, let me make sure I get this right.
You've farmed plus twos for the last two and a half hours and now they're gone.
No, just everyone wants to give me shit.
That's fine.
You want to give me shit? That's not a shower.
That's the menu.
Hi, Professor Jerma. Hey, thanks.
Oh, right.
Let me make sure I turn this on.
It should be on now. Cool.
Make sure I turn this on.
Okay.
Summa cum laude, here we come. Is that a good one?
I think it's pretty good. I think that's fun.
That's fun. Alright, but yeah.
In all seriousness, no fucking around.
We are going to be playing Two Point Campus on stream today.
It is going to be an ad stream.
The game actually looks really fun.
I actually want to play it, so it seems like it's pretty fun.
Let's go for it.
You guys ready? I'm opening it now.
I've heard good things.
Was the Black Ops 2 stream sponsored?
Why would Black Ops 2 stream be
a 10-year-old game?
Alright, let me make sure this is still here.
So by the same people that made Two Point
Hospital, we played that, if you remember.
I remember having a good time with that.
I'll put the camera on, I promise.
Alright, let's go. Alright, let's go.
I will put the camera on. See?
A man of my word. And I'm freshly
showered. And by freshly showered, I mean I threw a little
bit of water in my face. And that's it.
I definitely look a little less greasy, though, don't you think?
I look clean, don't I?
I'm ready to go. Are you ready to go?
Okay, Two Point Campus. New game?
What is going on in the school?
Wait, you can be a clown?
What is happening here?
If I can make a clown college, that is what I'm doing.
Without a doubt, that's what I'm doing.
Two Point Hospital was fun.
I guess you can build the whole campus, too.
You can do the whole outdoor area, everything.
So, it's gonna be fun.
What? Why did that building just shake?
Alright, select a member of staff.
I'm Albert Crank.
Your own per- wait.
Unplug this.
Your own personal advisor, and I'm here to help.
You may or may not have
an experience as a campus administrator,
but the people at Fresh Lay County
College are eager to give you a chance.
I didn't scam anybody.
I'm not sure what that
says about them, but hey, let's head to
Fresh Lay Meadows and get started
on your academic empire.
Hashtag advertising.
This actually is probably gonna be fun.
Alright, this country-side college has low expectations
and a nice canal. It's the perfect place for you to start your career.
Alright, let's go.
Campus Management 101.
Is that the school mascot?
Long ago, by dignified
people who wore bowler hats
and spoke via subtitle,
the world is a creation
of the past, and it is
our job to keep it all going
and try not to touch anything.
Stewie Griffin. Alright.
It looks really nice. The graphics are
beautiful. I thought that said
Scientology.
Alright, first day of school.
Welcome to Fresh Lay Meadows,
where life moves slowly and expectations
are lowly. The two-point
countryside is the perfect place to start your career.
Learn the ropes, make mistakes, and hit the
ground smiling.
Scientography.
Ten students, alright.
Alright, there's no school.
It's just an auditorium.
Okay, learn the basics of
campus management. Try moving the camera
and have a look around. You got it? Okay.
Okay. Zoom the camera.
Pan the camera. Sure.
Spin the camera. Pitch the camera.
R and F. Oh, okay.
He's desync.
Shouldn't be. Okay.
So our campus is going to be running a Scientography
course. Let's start by building a science
lab. Okay. 18,000?
That sounds fine. Alright, so
it should probably be in the corner. How big
should it be?
Should it be huge?
I don't think it needs to be that big.
Five by five? Okay, so
it's a science lab. Let's put a door here.
This is actually way too small.
Okay. I got it.
Do you want to sell one invalid item?
Wait, no. What? What's invalid?
Make the entire school a
cafeteria.
Yeah? Okay, cool. There we go.
Let's hire a teacher.
The dabbing. Okay.
Toby Eastgate is going to be our Scientography
streamer.
Streamer.
I can't speech jam myself with this audio.
Okay. 70%
teaching skill. Excellent personal
hygiene. Toilet comfort
decreases slower than most.
Dives head first. Alright.
Did you say he can't work
in the science lab?
Wait, we only have one course?
Where's he going?
Where are you going?
Where are you going? We have to start the
school year.
Where's this guy going?
The students are about to arrive and this guy is walking
around on acid in the front lawn.
Here come the students.
Oh, hold on.
There we go. Okay.
Why are we all going the long way?
That's easier to go in there. Oh, I guess
it's closer. He's the teacher. It's closer.
Okay. Wait.
Do we do the class in here?
What's this for?
There are no seats.
Oh, okay. Here they go. They're in their first class.
First day.
There's no place to sit down. Hey,
put those down. This is dangerous.
We just make cubes?
There are no seats and there's no desks.
Okay. The students
learn experience points.
Increase their academic level.
Okay. Where's the teacher?
What are they making? They're making
gas. That's not
normal. Oh, by the way,
Two Point Campus is across all major platforms.
You can get it on
PC. You can get it on PlayStation.
You can get it on Xbox. You can get it on
everything. All right. So it's almost done.
Almost more than any gloves.
Feels fine. Squeaky clean. Iron
blood.
Did you get chin extensions?
Yeah.
This camera sucks,
okay?
Okay. Class is over.
They passed the
first class. Sadly,
they didn't do all that well. It seems a number of them
were distracted by one
need or another. What?
What are they doing?
Okay. Take a look at our campus.
Take a look at our students
and see what we can do to improve the campus.
Stop making me feel
jealous by telling me how many consoles this game is on.
I only own two, and you're making me feel
jealous of other people's possessions.
Bro, you own two of the
current gen consoles?
What?
Okay. Okay. We need
bathroom.
Tired?
The key to campus hospitality is remember that
three Rs. Students need somewhere
to relax, rest themselves,
and relieve themselves. Sure, two of those
might be the same thing, but it does sound convincing.
Let's build a dormitory
and a bathroom to keep people comfortable.
This poor kid.
Okay, I need to build a dorm.
Build a dorm.
Dormitory. How big?
It's got to be big, right?
Can I make the campus bigger? It's got to be
a lot. Shit.
How do I fix that? I need to fix that.
Okay.
Okay, place an item.
You can rotate it. Okay.
This is like a fucking hospital.
Turning into a barracks.
How many beds do I have to have?
What?
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Oh, shit. I thought it was
tutorialing me.
I thought I was getting tutorialed.
Because remember I put the door down.
I put the wardrobe down.
It selected it for me.
Okay.
I need an ATM.
Everybody gets a hand sanitizer
next to their bed.
Where's the bathroom?
Alright, where's the bathroom?
Do not cancel this room.
Okay, we good?
Wormitory is a great place for students to relax
when they're low on energy. One bed between
five students is considered normal on
campus. What?
Okay. Students may dream
of having their own bed, but they'll happily
share with a few friends. What are you talking
about? They don't get it at the same
time. Who gets into
a bed like that?
That's a weird
person. That's a weird
person. Who gets into a bed
long ways? Nobody.
Oh, there's only one wardrobe.
Why are there bones in there?
Why is there a dead body in there?
Alright, hold on. I'm confused.
I need a bathroom.
Okay. Sink.
Okay.
Hand dryer.
Plant. Hand sanitizations.
Okay.
And a window. No!
A window?
Put in some slot machines.
Okay.
Bathroom done. New room
unlocked. Shower room. Did you
hear that? I think our students might be hungry.
Originally, campuses offer a range of
food and drink to, you know, sustain life.
Let's add some vending machines.
I think I didn't make it.
Wait, you just went to the bathroom. Why are you still
holding your stomach?
This person...
Why are they doing this?
Why does everybody have diarrhea?
What happened?
Everyone's holding their stomachs?
Oh, they're hungry. Okay. Right, right, right, right.
That's my bed. Okay.
How do I get food?
Oh, okay. Here we go.
Cheesy gubbins machine.
I don't have to go far.
Alright. If we were up to the students,
I'm sure we'd be all living in our own filth.
We have very little say in the matter.
Let's hire a janitor and place a bin.
Okay. Jackie
Clear. Wait, these are teachers.
Jeff Vacuum.
That's a great, great janitor name.
I think is the one that we
hire. Okay.
There's a drink stand right here. You're good.
You're fine. Okay, so.
Place one bin. Alright, you got it.
No one authorized
talking? Okay.
Let's see how the students do in the next class.
Oh, shit. Alright, we're doing a lecture.
Pass a Scientography
class with a C+.
What do you got for grades?
Bursting. Feeling
freshly. Peckish, thirsty, tired,
bursting, and bored.
Oh. Where are the rest of the students?
Absolutely
bursting.
Tired, peckish, and thirsty. So
go to the bathroom.
That's funny that there's bursting and absolutely
bursting. That's different.
It's in the books.
Everyone's sleeping in the same
two beds.
They're just sharing these two beds. I don't need
these many. Okay.
Who are you?
This is the class clown. Makes things
nice and cheery with a steady stream of jokes
and slapstick delights.
The class is just an audience that keeps coming back.
Keeps people entertained and has
poor hygiene. I love
this guy. Let's see. Tell me a joke.
Oh, there we go.
The better they do, the more money you'll have
to fund the campus who's smart now.
Yes, you get tuition
fees from all students enrolled in courses at the campus
as well as a bonus for how much XP they're earning.
Sick.
All right.
What? Studying.
Okay.
I need a place to study. Completing
assignments is a great way for students to earn XP
away from the classroom, but it looks like they
need...
Are they throwing just trash down
on the ground here?
You're a faculty, man. Pick that up.
You're setting a really bad example for all these fucking
kids. What are you doing?
Why would you do that? Okay.
Check your inbox
to see what they need.
All right. This is the check on
requests. Library requested.
Okay. Henrietta Belcher
has requested a library.
And nine people have agreed on Facebook.
Or whatever social media.
I'm running out of room.
How do I make the room bigger? How do I make this room bigger?
Try it again.
Library. That looks good.
All right. Let's put this here.
There. See?
See how it's doing it? Okay.
I got everything I need. I'll do one more bookshelf over here.
And...
Hand sanitizer. And a trash can.
That's good. All right. Completing
assignment in the library. You got it.
What's that icon? Can I just sell all this stuff?
I don't... I mean...
Oh, this dormitory sucks.
I can't believe they're removing the beds.
Oh, what's that?
We're all sleeping in the same two beds.
And we have... These have been like
fresh, cleaned
beds that no one's touched.
And I'm getting points removed for that.
Move this. That's fine.
I'm gonna pull the room over a little.
It doesn't have to be this big.
What? Oh, it's
a copy. I thought it was move.
Okay.
Okay, now I'm gonna... Let's edit this building.
I wanna pull this in.
I wanna pull it in.
Like that, right?
Subtract, right?
All right. Subtract it.
Much better. All right. That's fine.
That's more realistic now.
Those don't very much room for whatever.
Maybe like a food place or something?
Get the banner?
Okay, I need to hire an assistant.
Open the hire staff menu to view
applicants.
Full of staff for different jobs. New applicants will apply.
Okay, so I need an assistant.
Assistant.
Oh, that's for the library. Shit, okay.
Okay, makes...
Happiness brings happiness. What does this bring?
Comedic timing? Yeah.
Moves fast and is really clean.
Yeah, for sure.
All right, okay. You're good.
Open the library.
Oh, there he is.
All right, we gotta make sure this... We gotta make sure this student
gets an A+.
Some of our students are completing an assignment in the library.
Great way to earn XP outside the classroom.
Cool. What's your schedule?
You got science here?
In January? Hold on.
You have one class in January.
And...
You're just gonna stay here from like
August through July?
A full year? You got one class?
I need more than one class.
No wonder everyone's walking around aimlessly.
There's only one piece of curriculum and one teacher.
Oh, shit. All right.
There's only one class.
Stay on campus for a year.
You know, and go to class for one week.
All right, let's go. It's a tutorial.
So, where do we get to build our own shit?
Apparently, there's a relationship system.
Which, I wonder how that works.
I'm very curious.
The bathroom's bigger than the library.
Yeah. Everybody needs to go to the bathroom.
Everybody doesn't study.
Do you need me to explain that further?
Maybe you should... All right. Pass a sign...
I keep...
Intography class.
They're gonna get a B. Look, they're doing pretty good.
Oh, wait. There's the Joker.
What's wrong? What'd he do?
What did he do?
What did he do? Why did he say free?
I don't get it. What happened?
Oh, they're bored.
Bored.
Just get a B and we'll be fine.
Hired.
How do I make a... Is there a...
Do the teachers go home?
Statement, okay.
Tuition fees, rent, XP bonus,
and then staff wages. All right, cool.
Seven grand.
All right, we're good.
So, can this be used for more than just
the science class?
The science class?
Nice.
Okay, if you had a B+, you'd get an A-.
If I'm the teacher and I look out the window
and you got like
an 88, or like an 89
on this exam here,
and I see you doing those funny movements out the window
just kind of dancing around, I'm turning it into
a 91. I'm making it a 91.
Your students have gone from C grade
chumps to B grade brain heads.
Let's recap how you did.
All right, tutorial over.
Provide better staff and facilities to improve
your students' grades. Make students happy
and comfortable to increase their learning rate.
Earn more cash by growing your campus and
enrolling more students. All right.
Spend Kudosh to unlock
new items as well as staff outfits and interior
design options. Okay, I got half a
million. Unlock an item with
Kudosh. Okay.
Oh, hell yeah.
Arcade machine.
What if there's no actual
learning? I just make a bunch of food places
and arcade games.
Just make a big arcade with no actual
learning. And just give everybody A's.
Make a casino
college. Test your strength.
Yeah, definitely. All right, where am I going to put this?
In the bathroom?
You go take a piss and then you come out and just
I got 200 points.
Okay. What is this?
You didn't even try.
You stink.
You are offensively
smelly.
Oh, I need showers. Oops.
You're right. You're right. I need showers.
Where do I do that?
Shower room. Okay.
Right here.
Security breach. Please change
your passwords. What?
Oh, I thought you meant. Okay. Was it? What the hell?
All right. Let's have
How many of these should I have in here?
And now for the segment we call
Agony Answers.
Should be individual rooms, right?
Agony Answers. This week's
problem is
Get out and lie down under
these.
Just lay down flat and push all the buttons.
I'd start by
contacting someone under less
anonymous circumstances.
Perhaps a friend of the local authorities.
Best of luck and so on.
Okay.
Door? Is that all right?
Is that okay? Is this okay?
Do I have to have
Separation?
This is fine, right?
Why is there no shower
curtain?
Just like a
Mario collect the star animation
and got naked
without a curtain or anything.
I probably should put
doors, right?
All right. What's wrong
with you? You have a staff
on break with nowhere to relax.
Where? Where are they?
I have one teacher.
This one overworked teacher.
Where are they? Where's my
staff? Is he sleeping in his
car?
No. Wait, wait. There you are.
I need a staff room.
I need a staff room. Staff room.
I need another teacher.
This person wants a dorm?
What happens when this gets all the way filled?
Students are reminded
that I'm not your mom.
Jeff vacuum is really carrying this place.
Okay, I need a staff room.
Staff room. I have no room. I need a
bigger building.
We got to make this really comfortable.
There are literally two people
that work here. I don't need more than one
couch. I was like,
why are they running? Let's do
a nice lamp
and a TV.
Oh, a dart board. That's nice.
Sky painting.
Purple rug.
Okay. A
snack table with
cookies and shit. Yeah.
I think that's good.
Here we go. I need some more staff.
How about another teacher?
Okay, Mack Pike.
Weed infestation?
Isn't that just college? What are you talking about?
Alright, how about Randy Bird?
What do you teach? Wait, what do you
teach? Okay.
Scientography. Where are these weeds?
Where are these weeds?
This one? That's not a problem.
Alright, I'll get another
assistant. Oh, no. Another janitor.
Maintenance. Yeah.
Definitely.
Actually, you know, take care of the weeds.
Okay, B+. That's good.
Student lounge wanted.
I've tried kicking back in every
room on campus, but nothing is quite hitting the spot.
I think we need a dedicated room for students to hang out
to relax in the lounge in.
Alright, fine. Can't fit there.
That's good enough.
Microwave.
What are you going to microwave?
The, like, old mac and cheese
machine stuff you get out of that?
Why would the people...
Okay, it's microwaved out of
here, and then you re-microwave
it over here.
Okay, here we go. How about some, like, video
games? Okay, move this
into here. That's better.
You're listening to campus radio.
I love TP.
Okay.
What is that?
This is a clown
trunk. Yep.
And funny costumes.
Fancy hats. That's a pretty good
student relax room.
This is not even a couch. I need,
like, a chair. There.
Good enough. Alright, go have fun.
Alright, we need... Students will
send a request. Level
3 science lab. There we go.
Okay, how do I level up the science lab?
Why is the environment so bad?
Cheese and fire crackers.
There are a lot of jobs for janitors around
campus. I already have
two janitors.
How do I upgrade the room?
That music's a little loud.
There you go. That's better. Maybe make the room
bigger and add furniture. Oh!
Where'd you get a hot dog?
Do I sell hot dogs here? You're not going to eat it?
Wait, you're just going to microwave a
hot dog in the bun and then
put it in your pocket?
Okay, wait, wait, wait. They have a bee.
Oh, okay, hold on. Let me add some stuff.
Okay, we need... Here we go.
More, like, science equipment.
A whiteboard.
And, dude,
that's $8,000. No.
That's good enough.
Is that enough? I need a roof?
There's already a roof on here. Campus management.
No, we're good. Alright,
level 3 science lab.
Room prestige. This place still sucks.
Hold on.
Oh, I got it. End of the year rewards.
Oh, my God.
I just punched you in the face. I'm sorry.
So what happened? Expelled?
Alright.
My pass rate is 100%.
Average exam is 81%.
Oh, okay, so now end of the year. No one's here
so I can do management.
Okay, let's expand our range of courses by starting
a virtual normality course.
Alright, new course. Next year's fee
is $180,000
for the year?
Okay, so this is the virtual reality
class.
Can I do something else, too? That sounds good.
Alright, cool. Buy a new plot
for your second year.
This is not quite business as usual here at
Duckworth Campus Food Court.
Where one of the servers has lost
a contact lens.
Unfortunately, they do believe the lens was
lost during the preparation of a
particularly big lasagna.
They're asking every student
to check their portion before
they chew. But as of yet,
no sight of the missing
lens. I have to redo some of this.
This looks pretty terrible.
This looks terrible.
I should have one be
dormitory, right?
Dorm. Student
facilities.
Food. Lunch. Yeah.
One of them's going to be the
actual work building.
So, we're going to change this.
This is going to be the actual student dormitory
student facility. Okay, so let's move this.
Why are the students still here? It's summer break.
What's the problem?
Course points?
What are the course points?
Alright, get rid of this.
Can I move this whole building? The whole thing?
Just sell it?
Move your webcam?
Oh, sorry. Oops.
Just remake it? Yeah, I'll sell it.
Alright, everybody take a shower
but then get out of here.
Alright, close the room. Everybody out.
Sell this whole thing.
Fourteen thousand dollars. You got it.
Okay, cool. Someone was
in there. Alright, we're good.
Okay, pause the game
because the people are going to freak out.
Oh, yeah. Actually,
probably over here is better. It's better over here.
Alright, it's paused.
Alright, so now, it's time to
expand. You can build.
A lot of areas in this game.
Like never before?
Mirror world?
Oh, you think I look weird because
I flipped it, right?
Yeah, this is weird.
This is when you take a picture of yourself
with an iPhone
and your face looks like
you hit it with a hammer like five times
because you're seeing yourself flipped.
It's like, what's wrong with my face?
Why does my face look like that?
No, I know what you mean. Watch.
I'll show you. Ready? So, check this out.
This is what I actually look like.
Isn't that weird?
This is what my face looks like, for real.
But if you flip it, it turns you into like a
nightmare person. See?
You definitely, you caught me.
It does look weird, though. I agree.
Okay, two point campus!
Which, by the way, in case you didn't know,
by the same people that made Two Point Hospital
and in case you didn't know, it's on every
it's on, it's PlayStation, it's on
PC, it's on Xbox.
There's a new and improved relationship system. Have I told you
that one yet? Have we talked about that yet?
Nurture and grow your students with a deeper and more meaningful
sense of connection. In case you didn't know.
Keep the students happy with clubs, societies,
gigs. Surround them with friends.
Help them develop relationships and furnish them with
care. You understand?
That's in this game. Nurture!
Nurture!
Why are you in a fisheye lens?
Can I do a fisheye lens?
Hold on. Can I do a slight fisheye
lens? Is that possible in just like
OBS? Not enough, just enough to
look a little weird. What's action movie?
Holy shit, I look so much
cooler. What?
Oh, yes.
That looks so much better. Wow.
Actually, I'm keeping this filter on. I'm not even getting around.
These look so much better than just being
a regular. No, I'm putting
this one. Look at how good this looks.
This actually looks better. That's ridiculous.
Okay. Well, that's cool.
I'm gonna keep this on. I thought I just
I thought I just closed my fucking OBS
and end of the stream. Alright.
Hey, I gotta play. I gotta play. I gotta play.
If I go to the school and some psycho keeps
stealing the shower.
That's very weird considering
that you're supposed to be paused
and frozen. So you're not actually
here. Because if you were, you
wouldn't be talking right now, would you?
Okay. Don't just drag it
like an idiot. Where do I want
all the beds? Right here, right?
I'm thinking just like right here
and then we'll do bathrooms, shower
and then student facilities. So
this is gonna be dorm rooms, beds and shit.
That doesn't need to be huge. It doesn't
need to be gigantic. We want good
beds. So let's go like one,
two, up to
five people can have a bed together.
It's weird to say that out loud. I know. I'm sorry.
Okay. It's five, ten, fifteen,
twenty, twenty-five, thirty.
That's I can add them later if I need to.
There's that. We should have a couple
wardrobes so people aren't fighting over it.
Add some desks. Okay.
Okay. What is this?
Oh, a dorm notice board.
Where should this go? How about like right here?
See? People like that.
Trash can.
Trash cans. What is this?
Oh, I thought I had four hundred and sixty-nine
thousand Kudosh
coins. I was gonna say this is not
tuned correctly. I was like this is
really inexpensive. You can definitely buy everything.
That's why I was just buying everything.
I thought I had five hundred grand in this currency.
So I bought some of this
dumb shit. How much was the clown
trunk? This feels like my channel point
rewards. That's what I was thinking. I was like, ah,
they're very low. It's like
two hundred channel points
to do anything here.
This is the relationship bed?
I bought this painting.
Well, I have to use it then.
Everybody gets one.
Okay, I'm
turning the clown sounds off. Everybody
gets one of these. And I got the rug too.
So we're gonna put a rug down under
a couple of the beds. Okay.
Sanitizer. Plant.
Yeah, I'm gonna delete all channel points. All channel
points are getting deleted. And we're gonna bring
it back even stronger. You know
what I mean? Okay, so that's fine. This is a nice little
dorm area. This bed needs to be
actually on the wall. Everything looks good, right?
Okay. So that's good.
What am I missing? What's wrong? Oh, there's
no door. There's dormitory
too, apparently. All right.
So now I'm gonna make a bathroom right here.
Bathroom and shower room will be right
here and here. And then
the hangout room will be here. And there you
go. What do you
guys do in channel points? I gotta turn off channel points.
Delete. Make channel points not redeemable.
Sink. Hand dryer.
And a
trash, just in case.
Wait, one more sink on the other side. Yeah, right here.
Now I need a door. I actually want
the door to be here. I screwed it up on them.
That's better. Okay. Shower's gonna
go here. I'm smart. I have
to turn off channel points right now. It's out of
control. How do I turn channel points
off? I need to turn it off right now. How do I turn it off?
How do you turn off channel points? How do you turn
them off? I have to turn them off now. Yeah, no, no, no.
Fine. I'm not gonna turn it off. Would you
shut up? We'll put it in emote only
mode and you shut your
shut up. I'm very angry right
now. This is a sponsor stream and you're making
us look bad. How am I supposed to show up
to the board meeting? Huh? How am I supposed
to show up to the next board meeting and explain
to everybody at that part of the
organization what's going on here? By the way,
the board is me and Otto.
And by the way, he's the accountant. I don't handle
that. Don't delete the room. Room's done.
Yeah, keep it in emote only.
They're abusing the channel points and I don't like
it. It's making me very, very upset.
Don't you just imagine Otto with like a pair of glasses
on and a suit. He's like a
board room table with like a pencil and
a paper and he just doesn't know what he's
doing and it's just so cute. Okay, showers.
Okay. Maybe one sink.
One more towel rack. That's better.
Okay, good. Complete it. There we go.
Much cleaner. Much
cleaner. And then there's enough room in the hallway,
right? Okay. Because then this will be
an activity kind of area for the students,
right? Campus building. Student
lounge. Yep. Okay. Student lounge.
Shit. No, it's okay. It's alright.
There's enough room. There's enough room. Yeah, we're fine.
Alright, that's good. Maybe two couches.
A little game table.
Microwavable snacks. Like a sink to
wash your hands. Arcade machines.
I almost did it.
There are TVs.
There's no TVs.
That was good. Alright, on the count of three, I want you to
let them out of emote only. On the count of three.
Let them out of emote only on the count of three.
And I'm going to sit here silently.
And if I'm not happy, it's going back. One, two, three, go.
I'm happy.
Is that too much? The one clown
trunk? Costume area?
Yeah. Alright, this is fun.
Maybe another chair in the middle or something.
Dartboard over here, too? Yeah, dartboard.
Maybe
somebody's to watch
people just sit here.
Do you want to have a little hangout
in this couch area?
Yeah, like a place to lounge and have
a snack together. Yeah, that's fine.
Alright, we're done. This one's perfect.
Alright, so this is the student hangout zone.
Student hangout zone looks good.
Now let me remove it from over here.
They're all here. Well, they'll figure it out.
I should probably keep the bathroom.
So you don't have to go all the way back to the student
lounge to go to the bathroom?
What? That's fine. Okay.
This has got to move, too. This is
annoying in the way. Can I pick it up?
Let's make a new one. I'll make a new one of these, too.
Wait, if I delete this, I'll lose
the prestige, right?
That's actually a bad idea. That's a really bad idea,
isn't it? Yeah.
One person just goes, yeah.
Y-E. And to see
if people are getting just banned and timed
out. Yeah. Yeah.
Thanks for the help. I
appreciate it, man. Alright, so
I'm gonna just expand it.
It can stay here. Yeah.
Ooh. Okay, wait. I need to
edit the room. Pick up room, edit
room. Alright, here we go. Let's add
some wall like that.
Okay.
This can stay over here. I need the other science
equipment, right?
Wait, edit it again.
What is this guy talking
about? Okay, now I need
another piece of equipment in here. Something better.
I need some science equipment. What the
fuck is that? Um, how do I find
it? Where's the science room stuff?
Oh, here we go. Okay. I don't have enough to do
that, but I can make the room better, right?
So I got a couple of those. It's almost a level
of prestige up. So let's do two of these.
There we go. Science lab level three.
Yes! A couple more whiteboards.
A place to sit down, right?
Is there any desks or anything? Oh,
why would I not? I spent it on
a piata or whatever the hell it was.
What did I even spend that money on? Okay, that's fine.
What's wrong with your camera? It's bent.
Is that a window or did I just take the wall
away? How are those windows?
Oh, people really like that. This is
level five now. Okay.
Alright, so this place is better. I need like
chairs or something. I need chairs.
There we go. It's five, um,
what are they called? Isn't it suma
not sume? It is?
Wait, is it sumo? What did I say?
Sumekomlade.
Yeah. Alright, that's good enough.
I got it leveled up. So that'll be giving
people better grades now.
I'm strictly an anti-camera
kind of guy. I need a lecture hall.
My philosophy is I can't
see you, you can't see me.
Lecture hall will go right in the middle. So I like to
keep things as low tech as possible.
I'd recommend strategically
placed strings
attached to some bells.
You hear a ring and you got yourself
a visitor. Of course,
sometimes it's the doorbell
and you really do have a visitor. Alright, what else can I put in here?
Is it a camera?
This guy.
These guys are freaking me out.
Okay, people like that. Wipe board
behind you over here.
Just in case you need like a ton to show a lot of work.
Trash cans and
sanitizations. Okay.
And plants. Looks good.
Do I have two of these? No.
Should I? Shit.
Does that matter? I don't think that
I don't think this matters. It gave me points.
What's that? What poll? That's fine. It gave me points.
I don't care. Alright, that's a lecture hall.
Now we have to build the other
room which is the
VR lab.
35 grand. Alright, I hope this is worth it.
I'm thinking over here, right? Like yeah,
over here. Alright, this is the VR lab.
Should I make it bigger? Bigger?
Should I fill this whole thing? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah.
Is that too big on this side though? Maybe
whatever. I don't care. It's fine.
I hate the way it looks. I hate
the way it looks. I hate the way this looks.
Why do I hate this so much? Should I just fill
the space and just say fuck it? Who cares? I'm just gonna
whatever. Fill it. It doesn't matter.
Should I have more than one of these? Okay,
so this is a VR
area here. I should probably have more
than a few of these. This is a VR
chair. These are
really expensive.
Five?
Okay, I'm gonna do
five of those and then the VR desk.
Wait, they need to be in front of them?
I'll just do this. And then
VR headsets.
Where do these go? Against the wall here?
Okay. Hand sanitizer.
Is that okay? Do I have
two? I'm gonna do two. And then
windows. Okay.
Trash can. Okay. Windows
in a VR room. Why what?
What platform is the best to buy Two Point
Campus on? I'm really glad you brought that
up, Mons. Let me tell you. You got
quite a few options here. You've got PlayStation.
You've got Xbox. You've got
PC. You've even got
the, um, you've got it on the Nintendo
Switch. So you've got a lot of options.
Pretty much every major platform this is
available on. It's got
really cool new abilities. You can
build in the, for the first time, you can build
in the great outdoors. You can build outside,
which is the, uh, you couldn't do that before. Uh,
if I were to take a pic right now, I would say it's,
you know, I'm gonna give you a little wild
card here. I'm gonna say this is probably great
on the Switch, because you can bring it into the bathroom.
This place, this is a perfect go to
the bathroom game, I think, if I'm gonna be really
honest with you. I can see myself playing this in the bathroom.
The Switch lets you do that. What
is he looking out the window for? Alright, that
looks good. Maybe some,
maybe this is too big. Here's a question
from Gyro. What is some
of your favorite panic room past
times? This guy with the panic rooms.
What is this, this guy,
this guy. I find that you can have a lot of
fun with a little bouncing wall. This guy has
one piece of content. In fact,
one time I was bouncing,
lost track of time, and it turned
out that I've been doing it for 16 hours. I think we're ready to start the next year.
I went cold turkey
after that, meaning I was hungry. So we've got
the library still. Should I put the library in the
student hall? That might make more sense
over here. What do you think? Library
in the academic building or library
in the student area?
Yeah? Yeah? What?
Nah. I don't know what just happened but it's gone.
Okay, thank goodness.
Stop. I'm going to put the library here
where the students are. Wait, oh
no, this is the staff room. I don't want this over here.
Okay, keep it there. This is the library.
I need two lecture theaters?
Oh, that's not good. Okay, I
need another one of these. I need another
receptionist here. This room is way
freaking small. Salad.
Computer desk? Yep, we need
computers. Maybe two of these?
Make a meth lab.
That's not happening.
Alright, some more books? Okay.
This is now a true, this is a library now.
The room has the same painting. Alright.
That's much better. I do
need two people working here now.
Yeah? Okay, I need two people working
there. That's good. That
meeeeeeeeeeeeeee
I just froze. My brain just
turned off. The lecture hall, they have to be
back to back over here.
One step ahead, sneaky getaway.
Couldn't install your panic room
in a hall of mirrors.
Or, get signed on the door that
says, out for lunch.
This place is way too big.
It's massive. It doesn't need to be
this big at all. Let's
close it up a little. Salad.
Salad. Salad. Salad.
How do I do it? How do I sell this?
Is your camera on 120 FOV? I don't
think so. How do I sell it? Subtract,
right? Yes. How do I do it? Which
pizza is the best? What's going on?
This is so wrong. Meat pizza sucks.
If you say that meat,
like meat pizza, I'm imagining
meat time is meat lover's pizza. Wait,
it costs money to vote on this poll. I was
wait, what? No, I'm not wrong. I'm not wrong.
Let me tell you something. Listen to me.
Pepperoni is amazing on pizza. Sausage
is amazing on pizza. Hamburger is amazing
on pizza.
Turkey or whatever. I don't know. Whatever
weird shit. Chicken is amazing on pizza.
But when you put them all on it at the same
time, it ruins everything.
It just becomes a fucking lasagna. You can't
you pick it up. You try to pick a piece of
meat lover's pizza up. It falls apart.
It goes everywhere. It's not even a piece
of pizza anymore. It's just annoying. I'm of
the opinion, and you guys can tell me if I'm wrong here, but that's fine.
It doesn't bother me. I don't think
there should ever be more than two toppings on a pizza
ever. Ever. For any reason.
When you put more than two toppings on a
pizza, it weighs down to a point
where it cannot be eaten anymore the way that pizza
is. At that point, it's not a pizza. It's a casserole.
Three maybe. Depends on what it is.
If you...
This fucking
panic room guy.
I need to quiet him while
I'm talking for a second.
Where is...
I feel like this is TTS
donations and you guys are on this
panic room meme. Okay.
So anyways, what the hell is just
coming out of my mouth? What were we talking about?
No, we're not talking about panic rooms.
We're talking about pizza.
Okay. That guy's wicked funny.
But not at the
exact moment when I'm talking about pizza.
Pepperoni. Like, okay, if you have like
mushrooms, onions, and peppers,
that's three items.
That's fine. Pepperoni, like
garlic and onion, that's fine.
Anything more than two or three and you just
come on. Just, you might as
well just make a lasagna. Seriously.
Items, small items are fine.
But more than three or four, it starts to become
too much for me. Garlic on pizza? Have you never
had garlic on pizza? Garlic and onion pizza.
Wait, you've never had garlic and onion pizza? What are you talking about?
That's kind of crazy. It's amazing.
You're going to ewe garlic.
I don't even listen
to that. Okay. So let me
try this again. Alright. Subtract.
How do I actually subtract it though?
Do I need to have this in here?
Invalid wall. Oh, okay.
You have to actually complete the room. I get it.
Oh yeah, it did not need to be that big.
So that's fine. Okay. So now I need a second one
of these. Sorry students,
you're going to have to move immediately.
I was going to say, what the hell have I done? That's fine.
Okay. Wait. That's
probably not a great idea.
Okay. I'm going to extend the bathroom a little bit.
Okay, that's fine. Now
I've got, I need a second
lecture hall, which is going to have to go down here.
Or maybe it could go here. Yeah, it could go here.
Under the door. No!
Okay, that's fine. And I'm going to take this
edge here. And the other lecture hall will go right here.
That's perfect. Much better.
Let's even this out. There's some shit in the way.
Look at this stupid hand sanitizer out here.
What are you doing? Alright, that's good.
I need a second one here. Oh, it's because of this door.
That's good. Okay, cool.
This is fun. Okay.
I'm going to get a ton of, they're going to get good grades.
Alright, here's another lecture theater.
This is lecture theater two. There it is.
Done. There we go. Alright.
Yeah!
I think I'm ready to start the year. Un-mirror the
thing. You look like an uncanny troll face.
You have to get over it.
Okay, let's hire some extra staff.
So we need a VR...
What's the difference between you two?
Moves faster than normal. Excellent personal hygiene.
Gets hungry easily. Gets thirsty
easily. You're fine. So we need
a VR technician.
We need... Should I get another
science teacher? Do we only have...
We already have one. Aerodynamics?
I definitely need another... Okay, I need a
library assistant. Yeah,
okay, you're good. Okay, so that's two
and then maybe one more janitor. I don't want to lose
I don't want to blow my money. Your head looks
like a slice of pizza. Alright, now what I need
to make this look a little nicer.
This is so barren out here.
What are the needs? Table, football,
wanted. I need a hundred coins.
Tree bench. I need a hundred coins.
Can't do it right now. I'm sorry.
Table, football, tree bench. I don't
have it. Alright, well, I gotta put like
some cool decorations.
How about this one? And then... What's this?
Oh, a fountain. I don't want to overdo
it. Seating like right outside. This is like
a good place to have it. That looks good.
That looks great. This is shitload of items.
There's actually a lot. Okay. What's this?
Paths and terrain.
Oh, okay. Alright.
Manage courses. I think we're ready.
Ready to go? Should I have some seating in here?
Alright, I can't even put... Wait, what about sofa?
Couch. Let's go.
It's time to start the academic year.
What am I doing wrong here?
Here we go. Are you sure you want to start
the year with the following courses?
Yes. Oh!
What is... Okay, it's literally... Alright.
That... What the fuck is that?
And why is it floating around the light?
I just got scared by like a hair.
There was this big dust bunny that was
floating around and it like got attracted to the ring light.
At least I think that's what that was.
Can you see this?
That floated up into the light and
casted a shadow. And it was
horrifying. I thought I was
getting attacked by an insect. It's just
dust. Yeah, I know, but it floated by the ring light
and casted this massive
shadow. You made a Lord Voldemort
sound.
Alright, new year, let's do it.
Welcome students. We've got more
classes here. We've got a nice
place to hang out. We've also got...
That's cheating.
Let's go to the toilet.
Alright.
We have a relationship forming between
The academic year is starting.
Wolfric Halfmoon
and
Randy Fenderson.
Students, virtual normality.
I think I can only have 20
students. Alright, come check out the
dorm room, man. It's pretty sick.
Yeah, I remember Benny Bungle from year
one. Yeah, trying the hats, man.
Check out the clown trunk too
when you have a chance. There are way
too many students. We only have two classes.
Two students have a
personal goal of wanting to sit on a park
bench. I mean,
really? That's a
goal of yours is to sit on a park bench.
I mean, I'm not going to deny you that. That's
fine.
Here, go
fulfill your greatest
desire. Where are the teachers?
What's wrong?
Learning rate, 118%
textbook cubicle required.
Get to class, hurry up.
Wait, Benny, the teacher.
Oh, the students are in here unsupervised.
How many teachers do I have?
Jerma, the VR students are making
porn. You have to stop them.
Students are asked not to ask questions.
Oh, you got an intelligence
boost. They're definitely going to end up
with a C, right? Uh oh.
There's only 10 room capacity.
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten. Yo,
how do I add more people?
You're doing a
broom on the sofa?
I thought that, did you see that fly by the
screen? Did you see it? You saw that,
right? Make the room bigger.
Nobody's going to the library. They're all just
goofing off in the hangout room.
You could hear a pin drop.
Look at this.
Look at this. Come on.
No one wants to study.
Oh my goodness.
Hot dog kiosk?
This might be frightfully exciting for you. The people of
Freshly now have a second thing to be proud of.
Congratulations and so on.
Don't be too complacent. This is your first campus
and it shows.
Alright, I have a new, I can do a new college.
I unlocked a hot dog machine.
So we're the,
we got that from a different campus.
Alright, no more like just potato chips
and sodas.
Could this be outside?
Maybe this shouldn't be inside here.
That would actually be amazing though.
Do you know? Okay, somebody confirm this to me.
I've heard
just randomly through
various people and stuff.
Has any of you guys ever heard of this?
Of like a restaurant being in your school?
Like a McDonald's?
Or like a fast food place?
Being like in the school?
Or like a Starbucks or something?
Yes, that happens. A subway. We had a subway.
We had a subway.
If there was like a
McDonald's in between the science room
and the math room, I would have been there all the time.
There's a Dunkin' Donuts here.
Really?
That sounds amazing.
We had a deli but not a brand name.
We had a Taco Bell, Wendy's, Arby's, Dunkin' and a Panera.
That sounds incredible.
So you tell me, you could like go out of
your logic class
and they would just be a Starbucks
in the fucking building
right there.
In College Univer- yeah.
That sounds amazing. It's a separate building?
How far though?
Corporate takeover.
Bro, just walk to the fast food.
But how convenient is that?
If I can walk out of the lecture hall
and there's just a Burger King here.
It's just like-
Alright, I'm getting a number two.
Let's go. I'm ready.
That would be so awesome.
I would have become such a fat- fuck.
I really would have been.
We had a Papa John's in the cafeteria.
That's so unfair.
We had a food court.
Yeah, that would be amazing.
If there was like three or four different restaurants
in the campus hall, what happened to you?
You just did something cool. What did you do?
Good grades?
Friends with Charlie Leotard.
Alright, they're friends.
Maybe it was a bad idea to have
the fucking hot dog kiosk.
Nobody's doing well.
He's holding his ass.
Oh, no, no, no.
He's walking like this.
He's holding his ass.
They all have stomachaches and they're gonna shit their pants.
Now everybody wants to go into the library.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, no.
What do I do?
There's too many people.
You're either gonna study or you're gonna get up.
Don't sleep.
Sleep in your bed.
No, don't sleep. Get up.
You've been expelled.
No.
What, a dictator? No, dude.
It's not enough room.
They're crying.
Wait, do I have coins? No?
I do. Okay, I got 200 coins.
Tree bench.
Why do you guys want benches so bad?
The most boring shit.
Ask for like a pinball machine.
I really would love a bench.
What do you mean a bench?
Ask for like a dozen pinball machines.
Ask for a McDonald's across from the campus.
Look, we have plenty of benches.
I count one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Why do you want another bench?
Please put a bench, please.
It's $4,000.
Oh, wait, this is like a romantic bench.
All right, let's put it like here.
Who's gonna use it?
Develop romances, dating, sweethearts.
All right, there we go.
Somebody's like, wait, we want this
because, well, do you want to tell the story?
No, I can't.
I guess you have to be there.
This is getting ripped up and put into the fucking recycling.
Like, I'm sorry.
If you have like a formal request and you're gonna send me to like the dean of students,
this is not how you write it.
Hey, we want table football.
I think a lot of the students would like it.
Actually, a lot of the people on the football team
said that they thought it was fun to maybe
just shoot the shit and hang out.
There's not a lot of stuff in the
recreation room so far.
This is not how you write to the dean.
I request this article of the night with no
with which to strengthen the moon's power.
Oh, please, I think it would be lovely.
This person's expelled.
Where are they?
I'm gonna put the poster right in front of them.
There you are. Look!
I gave you the
haunted Halloween poster.
Oh, nobody works here.
Where are you going?
I was gonna expel you if you threw that on the ground.
I was gonna hover over the expel button.
There you go.
Here comes the needs meter filling up.
Nice. Look at how happy you are.
Now go get an A. Dark aura.
That was a violent
door close.
How are we doing? Somebody has to work here.
I need an assistant. Somebody's gonna open this
kiosk. Wait. Oh, shit.
Isn't that person working at the library?
Where's my staff menu?
Yeah, I need another staff member.
I need more assistance. No, no, no.
I'm going for it. I got it.
Somebody can do food.
Can you do food?
Do they have to have food as a trait? Can anybody do it?
Or do you have to have food as a trait?
I think anybody can do it, right?
You're hired.
Get in there.
Where'd they go? Where'd that person go?
Did they just hire someone?
Oh, they're just in the staff room.
Alright, that's fine.
48, 46, 45.
What's why these people...
What's that mean? Why? What's gonna happen?
What happens if this goes to zero?
You're expelled. Hurry.
How do I pause?
Alright, alright, alright. They want textbook cubicle?
Oh, there's only one
in the whole college. Oh, there's not
one in the entire university.
Okay, I get it. There! Your demands
have been met. Is that okay?
You're gonna get rid of your little
countdown thing here?
There, see? Where is this person?
This person's been sitting in the break room.
Why are you just sitting here?
Who works where?
Weeds. There's only like one weed
on the whole thing. Alright, that's fine.
This is looking good. Looks good,
looks good, looks good, looks good.
Is there a face swap filter on?
Oh, it's kinda laggy.
Hold on.
That's not better.
Look at my eyes!
Why do they look so weird?
That's better. Not really, but whatever. I don't care.
Take off the troll chin.
That's just my face, man. You're very
blue. I think it's the action movie
filter. Okay, so you guys have gotten
used to this filter. Let's turn it off.
People are gonna be very surprised. You ready?
Yuck.
By the way, Two Point Campus is
on. Nintendo Switch.
It's on. Xbox.
It's on.
PlayStation 5.
It's also on.
P P P P P P P P P P P
P C D P P P C.
This hurts my head. Wait, can you like see
like the heat profile of my face?
Look at my eyes.
Holy shit, that looks weird.
You can see like the heat in my eyes.
That's terrifying.
I'm back. Nice heat detector.
That's not thermal. Wait, whatever.
Alright, let's keep going. And yes, this is by the
same people that did Two Point Hospital.
I sss...stop asking it!
Stop asking it! I see it every five seconds.
This college is bumping!
Please change your passwords. Sorry.
I have showers, right?
Yep. I actually might need
I need more classrooms.
Yeah, I need like another two or three
I need more classes. I need more professors.
Should I hire another professor?
Okay, we need a VR teacher.
No, I don't want to replace this person. That person was doing fine.
Wait, you just threw trash on the ground?
You're not going to leave, are you?
It's okay. I don't know what to do with you.
Where are the students?
Oh god, there's so many requests.
Please give us a coffee kiosk.
Please give us a crescent bench.
Please give us two-player game tables.
Give us a love bench. Okay, fine.
Okay, what else?
I feel like Bruce Almighty.
What else do you want?
Family tree wanted.
Okay, fine. I'll put this in the dorm.
Okay, there you go.
Oh, Statement of the Year.
12,000 profit.
That's good.
It would ruin my reputation if anyone knew I was talking to the Big Cheese.
But listen, I really want one of these.
Alright.
Oh, cool. Yeah, I'll put it here.
You want a bench?
Alright, here's your bench.
Can I put this anywhere?
Tuition fees are expensive.
And education is priceless.
Somebody even walks over here.
He's going to sit on this random bench in the corner.
Okay.
Two-player game table.
This is a big one.
These two want to hang out.
Alright, this is going. Pause it.
There we go. That's fine. That fits.
I should move this in the corner.
Nobody wants to play darts.
I haven't seen anybody play it once.
I think the two-player game table will be more popular than darts right now.
Yeah, it will.
Darts is cool, but people are requesting this.
Look, happy.
Very happy.
Oh, man. I love a nice coffee.
I love a nice coffee from a kiosk.
I'll put this right here.
You know how amazing this would be?
Right in front of the door.
Perfect.
That's much better.
Wait, I need another person to work here.
Someone will take care of it.
Alright, so far so good. What about my goals?
Career goals.
Level up 100 Scientography students.
Alright, I'll take it.
Anybody using the benches?
You look italicized.
Dude, don't run to the bathroom in class.
Do not piss into the chemical generator.
You look askew.
I don't know why.
I need another worker.
I'm in profit right now, so that's fine.
Where are you going?
Looking for work?
Can you not fit here?
Finally, somebody's here.
Alright, who wants a hot dog?
I could go for a hot dog right now.
Three. Just three hot dogs.
Mustard.
Ketchup, Tabasco on the third one.
Mustard, mustard on the first two.
Ketchup and Tabasco on the third one.
That's it. Don't put anything else on it.
That sounds amazing.
That sounds so good.
Are you doing the class in a VR helmet?
That's awesome.
What's your performance like?
Are you happy?
Low energy.
How's everybody doing?
Alright, I need campus level nine.
Average dorm rating. Almost there.
Quick, add some more
Nintendo consoles and shit.
Hold on.
Rose Garden.
Hold on. Wait.
Dorm rating. We need some more stuff in here.
I need some...
Electric guitar.
We need 70%.
There it is. Rug.
Another sanitizer.
Come on! God damn it.
I didn't get it. Alright, how'd we do?
Did we do good?
I think we did okay.
I think we did alright.
Oh, that's right. I did that.
Everyone's got a C+.
That's passing grade. That's fine.
Everyone has a 77%.
97%.
97% pass rate. I expelled somebody.
Alright, so now what?
I can't believe I didn't get that.
Thanks a lot.
We sold one hot dog.
Are there new courses?
Wait, I can upgrade.
I want to check out the other campus.
Okay, here we go.
That's cool.
How do I get to see the campus?
Build more beds for the rating?
Hold on, I want to check out the other...
I unlocked another campus. Exit to map?
Oh, here it is. Save.
Okay.
Piazza Lanatra is now available.
Let's check it out.
Countryside college is low expectations and a nice
canal. It's the perfect place to start your career.
Let's check it out.
Bring back the... Oh, forgot I deleted the panic room guy.
I should definitely bring him back.
I'm not sure exactly where I can get
this awesome looking game.
Well, I'm really glad you asked.
Two Point Campus is available on Steam.
It's on the Xbox, PlayStation.
It's on Switch. It's pretty much every
major platform you could possibly imagine.
Also,
there's a link in the chat that's
being shown.
Obviously, there's a panel down there you can click the link to if you want.
Just go to Steam.
It's on Steam.
I mean,
you can
get it. I think it's good.
You can get it on Switch.
My only talking points that I've said all...
It's just like you can get it on Switch.
You can get it on Xbox.
You can get it on the Switch. Hey, by the way,
you can get it on the Switch.
I want to see the
relationship system.
It's important. Where's the people that
requested this?
Oh, panic room guy, right.
Two Point Hospital was fun, too.
If you liked Two Point Hospital,
and you were like, damn, I kind of wish Two Point Hospital
was like a college simulator game,
this is the game for you. It's clean.
It's fun. It's cute.
Seems like there's a lot to do.
And why am I here? Did I pick the same
place? Oh, I was like,
what? Didn't I pick it? It should be a
weed dealer. This is more of a
city.
Wait, there are clubs in this game?
There's like clubs.
There's no way that that's a real picture.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What picture? You mean the up here?
Wait, what do you mean?
I mean, you're very obviously like
fucked with this. I mean, if you do it
subtly enough, I get it.
You can make me believe something, but
you're not going to make me believe this is a real picture.
I mean, you're very obviously like
fucked with this. I mean, if you do it
subtly enough, I get it. You can make me believe something, but
you're not going to make me believe this is a real picture
in the state this currently is in right now.
You just not.
Oh, dude.
Real picture, this is what you look like.
That's not serious. You have to make it at least believable.
That's not very believable at all.
You bulged my
eyes out.
Look! You can even see the Photoshop fucking
smudge tool. Excuse me.
Yeah, I can see
the smudge tool that you dragged my face
Look and see the darkness you use the Photoshop tool.
You got to cover your tracks better than that.
Yeah.
Students are reminded such thing as free time.
Okay.
Hello there.
I'm DJ.
Wait.
Oh, okay.
DJ Sue Chef.
You'll find my restaurant and nightclub beat root right here in Piazza Lanotrara.
I'm here to help turn your student body into a bodacious stew of learning.
Welcome to the culinary world.
It's going to be delicious.
Where's the college?
It's a pretty cool campus.
Oh.
I guess it's all right.
Oh a savoury kitchen.
Here it comes.
Ugh citizens a potty pool.
I'm Richard E. Hawthorne.
Today was election day special will be talking all things mayo as 2 Point County approaches
another important day in its history and indeed its future.
get in touch to tell us what you're thinking and how you're feeling who
will be the next mayor of two-point county you decide you can only be a chef
at this college sorry people have the fucking bowling ball ingredients to
each other maybe it's already placed on a second one that all right if there's
like 30 40 students guys then we need a lot of room this is gonna be the chef
college why is this room so weird oh it doesn't go all the way down how did I
mess that up how did I screw that up the easiest thing to do we're back today's
election sees incumbent mayor to win sock take on all challenges one such
fool is gumbo McNally yes the cousin of jumbo CEO jumbo McNally ms. Winsok has
held a steady some seed tedious lead in the polls over mr. McNally but what
effect if any will his last no I wanted to do what was over here 12 minute
display with a story of how he once took a modest pile of change from his father
what was the item that was over there
lunchtime spring sandwiches crisps and sausage rolls thanks or something was it
now that is impressive recipe station thank you okay now we need just like
hand sanitizer oh my god hopefully you didn't hear that you can see that it's
just buried hey they like this kind of stuff all right
oh utensils utensil station okay what else can I do in here okay now lecture
hall right gastronomy teacher lecture theater we'll put that here okay I'm
good that's fine I'll fix it later put a whiteboard or two why would you put it
over there two plants and the scary poster and an electric guitar okay and
some windows okay now I need a teacher do I need a dorm room that's good enough
okay that looks good okay bathroom now I just need a teacher I also need a little
place to sleep or something right shower do I have to have a place to shower
though what does everything have to have a dorm really from Michelle and
smoggy I spoke to me a windsock after a cue okay um this is enough that's enough
she said that she's enough reading it but I'd never sent it to her so what did
she break into my house what is she like telepathic but just with post lovely
Michelle you got a sink over here you're fine that's willing to go above as well
as beyond that's fine this thing is over there do you have a gigantic sink or
need it there are two towels there to tell racks okay that's good and then the
dorm will be right next to it this doesn't have to be big either just big
enough and we'll do what like one two three four five six different color seven
eight all right that's good that's good desks one two three desks I'm gonna say
and then a couple of wardrobes you really only need one or two of these it's
fine and this no man just like some fun stuff okay that's fine all right that's
fine look at that nice okay I need a staff room and then some food and then
we can get rolling a library too this place is so small how much we put a
library here okay computers I think this is one of each for now it's fine okay
all right that's fine okay I'm almost ready I need a staff room staff room
foundation we'll go shit we're gonna put the way over the staff room it has to go
here I got no more room to do anything else I got no more room for anything
there's no room for anything else oh I wonder if this image is fake I don't
get it what does this mean your head looks like the in-and-out sign what I
don't get it that's that's reaching it very far I don't like is my face is like
tilted okay sure whatever you say in and out sign head I'm trying to fix it I
gotta look I'm not I gotta look directly in the camera this is the problem one
why do I look like that what yeah I'm like this why am I that way I'm so
confused but hold on but does it fit but actually I'm serious does it fix it if I
do this well what's happening what's happening to my face what's happening to
my face what's happening I just switched back to normal what's happening to my
face I'm serious but out of my face you saw that right that was fucking weird
you saw that why is I like up here that was weird
it's election day here in two-point county yo I got a crooked face sideways
it's amazing to think that that was jarring when I did when it went the
other way if no one voted that year that's the mysterious one today
technology looks pretty good anyway here's hoping that this year we'll get
some votes in that's not what it looks like though I mean this is funny but
this is not what it looks like look like a hearthstone card that doesn't look
like me okay um that was actually jarring when I swapped it the other way
okay let me finish this please okay this looks like image one of my tinder
profile well I don't think anyone's gonna notice that this is a this is a
tinder picture not looking in the camera making sure the edit looks good and I
look perfect I'm not looking at I'm looking at I'm looking right now at the
active real-time editing of my face like yeah that looks good I'm gonna
screen cap that and I'm gonna put that on tinder yeah and then my bio all my
bio is gonna say is looking for tens only that's it no I bet you'll get
plenty of dates all right all right I gotta play this video game why is it so
high up oh it's a shelf I thought it was a bookcase wait I unlocked food didn't I
oh not for this place all right food but it's a culinary school all right if we
don't make food here and eat it if we use the vending machine that's kind of
messed up I think you're catching the lens distortion from being on the wide
you know what you're probably right so the camera word from Jeffrey and the
camera is not right in front of me it's all the way over here because I don't
want to get this in the frame so I'm sitting on the very edge of the webcam
maybe so I'm catching the very end if I were to drag this over you'd see it why
it's the camera's like over there
it's the camera it's not it's not my like twisted face all right we're good
let the culinary school begin what's wrong unresolved campus
requirements oh there's no teacher that's a pretty big requirement all right we're going with
earnest let's get a couple of janitors I just want it's very fine maybe that's
extreme you got to send people home private tuition room I don't want to
private tuition room a gastronomy teacher to teach the culinary class what
is gastronomy that sounds like it sounds like a like a digestive doctor from like
outer space it's like you double majored in like the stars and also in the gut
bacteria gastronomy that is it it's just food gastronomy food science oh okay
that's cool that's a cool name oh oh they're all chefs okay I need somebody
for the library they're all getting this chef clothes all right it's time do I
have to build the private room private tuition room no I'm not I'm not building
a private tuition room unless it's one of these other rooms that goes away
holy shit that's a huge cake um can I fit it here I can it's fine it's like a room
closet it's all right though good all right students get in private tuition
one-on-one help from a teacher what requires a teacher to be qualified in
the same course you with this okay we ready for a first lesson giving that
fateful cross to which I should have another teacher then just goes to show
Gilbert pillow private tuition all right cool cool cool cool cool cool are they
sleeping in their chef costumes wait the person is different are they different
when are they gonna get in here and cook get in there and start making food oh
they have to learn how to make food oh shit there's nobody here they're just
playing with the desk of the librarian you got this in the bathroom all right
come on in it's time to start cooking anybody need a private lesson oh friendship
nice these two are friends spends their nights dreaming of runny eggs and
pretty law gross runny eggs disgusting and perfect when Nellis in their days
making food for their studies themselves and for others wards off hunger by
eating their homework all right here we go let's see what they do this reminds
those old play dough of food makers that's cute that's an L egg opinion I
don't like over easy or runny eggs I think they just ruin everything else now
don't get me wrong do not twist my words around I love eggs over medium eggs over
kind of from easy to medium is perfect how many times I have to have this
conversation with everybody here I don't know how many times I have to tell you
to be pleased while others must be when you have a plate of food entirely what
we do know is that hold on he has triumphed meaning that yet again the
people of two point come on I want to hear what he says what they asked for
we've made our bed and now it's time to sleep in it all he knows he can hear us
all right stop eating toilet water okay so of eggs are not usually the only
thing you eat if you have a meal whether it's breakfast whether it's you know
brunch or lunch whatever you put your eggs on eggs is not the only thing that
you have on the plate so there's usually eggs bacon sausage tomato toast you know
what doesn't matter whatever's there if you have a runny egg you when you touch
the yolk it just explodes and gets on every single other piece of food it just
kind of gets everywhere and then it starts congealing and gets hard and
weird over medium is perfect and over easy to over medium somewhere in the
middle because the egg is still kind of runny and jammy and soft but it doesn't
just explode everywhere and then turn to this mess on your plate that's the point
but I don't want just egg yolk all over everything else that I'm eating I want
to choose to dip my sausage in the egg yolk I don't want to be forced to have my
sausage in the egg yolk right I want to be able to choose to do that sometimes
you just want to bite a sausage that has no egg yolk on it but sorry if you have
a runny egg every bite has egg yolk on it everyone a student union what's the
student oh I do that do I need that okay egg Karen yeah anytime that I have a
runny egg and it I open it I go what what the heck what the hell I it gets I
open the egg and it runs all over the sausage and I lift up my phone and I
filming the whole plate and just like I'm not I'm not happy about this not
happy about what you've done here at all stupid and I posted to Facebook and it
gets two likes me and one person that is just like I'm gonna do this just because
I like don't care but I don't care but I like I have to like be in the fucking
next room hard-boiled Andy that's right you mean Giga Chad hard-boiled eggs
fresh out of the out of the water no you're right you're right way too much
inventory look at all this food is not being used we have 10 students I have
40 areas soft-boiled egg mmm now that's good because it's it's it can't be
runny though it has to be a jammy yolk it has to be not a runny yolk somewhere
in the middle hard-boiled eggs are sent from hell well that's kind of
unfortunate because I'm about to eat a shitload of them after the stream is
over and I'm not making it up you have a baby palette it's the same food this
I'm the Antichrist it's the same food ah dude you you your palette is sort of
fucking ten-year-old we're both eating egg yolks they're both the same exact
food I just like mine a little jammer than you like yours it's the same food
huh it's the same food is the same ingredients it comes from the say comes
out of a chicken's ass it's the same food it's the same exact food
plagiarism is not a belief system stop oh my god my face is really long every
time I look over here stop saying jammy why cuz that's the way to describe the
egg that's the way to describe the egg I know that's like this dumb fucking like
food tick-tock video way to say it it's a jammy yolk okay that's what it is a
runny eggs good yeah and the other 40 60 70 80 90 100 and the other 43% of the
people in this chat understand yeah I don't know what it is man I could put a
huge annoying pie actually that sounds pretty good it's 33 60 70 80 90 whatever
I just same idea and look if you gave me a runny I we I am having fucking
Groundhog Day flashbacks I can't we do this every few months we do this every
few months guys somebody says oh runny eggs are delicious and then they put
like a fish so I read it and then I just do the same fucking routine that we've
done and times now somebody just like highlights the message and I read it and
then I just I just start talking about it again this is what I just it happens
we're on this repeat cycle they want benches because they can't stand this
don't go to bed needing to go to that's the worst nobody doesn't know even if I
have to pee a tiny bit if I have to pee even slightly I can't sleep it has to
all come up oh I need to build this student union entertainment it's
parties how we're supposed to pull this this is Harrison wolf I need a more area
wolf power I've been seeing a lot of stuff about colleges lately lots of
study here learn so-and-so qualification are these just too big and
qualification dad but let me tell you something they don't want you to know
it's a scam all of it students are right this is huge
it's huge I know there's funny for five seconds um okay hold on let me fix this
pretty sweet oh what happened there
required and standard diagnosis doctor attending psychiatry please nice door
it's not done you can't just criticize a work in progress and you know what you
want to do better you go get it by the way I'm sure people know what is that
what I mean I got away where's it what is it available long I get rid of the
door get rid of the door get rid of the door get rid of the door get rid of the
door get rid of this door all right I actually wanted to get rid of this okay
there we go what question you write that sir and then some bozo tells you
that you wrong oh so I need to pause the game if we've all got the same bad at
doors I just want to because I can't delete this unless I move the door but I
can't get rid of the door I didn't want to make a second door how do I um oh wait
there we go put two circles on it um hold on I'm busy shouldn't I be able to
delete the door I should be able to delete it right well that fix it I mean
that actually did work all right now we need a student union whatever it is bar
oh shit okay wait this is just a bar student Union that was called cool yep
okay I need an assistant let's move point assistant many of us huh did they make
kids take their tests let's see you like somebody going to be dancing events are a
great way to promote healthy work-life balance all right to make it schedule
one party let's do a party a schedule it's like to Roman then use the event
setup button all right let's do an SU party it's eight grand okay well let's
book it all right eight thousand dollars okay is it happening they love the dance
floor they're having a blast eight grand for a party there's only there's only a
few people there there's only like two people here pause the stream I need to
pee yeah you'll be all right just go to go right now you just go right now
holy shit that tired me out watching that that's a great move pause it so
they can go pee somebody not happy no you're fine okay what are my objectives
parties party was a success there's a wide range of events that you can run on
campus so don't forget to spice up the academic year okay cool let's hope they
do okay make a funny film funny film during the filming of good cop sad cop
Roderick Cushion was forced to pass out blindfolds and earplugs to tell you but
if Jumbo McNally's getting involved in something let's make that let's make a
funny movie what a racket you can teach mr. McNally a lesson by signing my
petition is it but wait is it here goes or thousand-dollar indie film pause the
game that guy's feet just hold on when's that part when and what are they
filming the thing pause it okay go go pee you're gonna get 60 seconds wait more
all right all of you are going well don't all of you go just that one guy
that needed a minute or two just go pee you wait we'll wait fucking waiting for
anybody you can tell me what to do on my stream really you can say like oh stop
your stream I'm really glad by the way that I spent four thousand dollars on
screening this indie movie for a guy to show up 20 minutes into the film and
there's one person I'm paused look my hands are up in the air see see we're
good are they back pause the face cam too okay I can do that they back I want a
French bread pizza fuck yeah they're back all right let's go quick come on
she's a movie starting one two three four it's four thousand dollars a ticket
bro you met you're halfway through the movie already those are the among us
sound where's the teacher where's the stuff oh it's just he's just getting a
drink he's just getting a drink why does he drink the cheesy gubbins oh come on
man don't do that just throwing it on the ground I can't think of I I would
never that's just so rude that's so unbelievably rude can't I can't even
imagine there are no garbage cans yes there is this one right here this this
dickhead has one in his office what do you mean this he has one in his eyes he
is one of one of two trash cans are in his office this person is really smart
level seven there we go we got a B student we want people want club
sandwiches powered nap what is this this is a strange-looking machine what is
this thing it's a power nap stand oh I thought you sleep on here I was like oh
okay see whatever what it does check it out it's a sleep club you ever thought
about why they're so keen to teach us to read think about it so we can read what
they write since we think about it it's just another way for them to control us
that's fucking funny only trust the daily disorder for my news they take the
regular news and turn every word hi the end of the year how do we do with B
minus that's not bad everyone seems to be happy I got a couple of rewards
everyone seems seems fine breaking dick can't understand oh this is pastry chef
it's perfect we changed the channel on that guy sweet
kitchen oh I can build somewhere else right that's a construction right only
three people join did I unlock a new room I thought I had a new room to
play with no where would you put it that's I think I did I unlock a new
space like oh yeah right here okay with buildings empty up just I don't want to
do it make it 10 grand I don't care this is way bigger now okay so what am I
gonna put in here a dessert thing up the quality on your webcam yeah I don't
webcams I don't care about see the problem is this thing has this stupid
auto exposure that even if I turn it I can't is such dog shit they really are
it's so bad so I can't really mess with the settings on this what do I do this
well let me try something yeah so I get it does this auto exposure that if I
turn off auto exposure it goes just dark so this is it without auto exposure on
I keep in mind I have a I have a ring light glaring into my face right now it
doesn't make any sense it's doesn't make any sense here's I have a light right
here I'm gonna turn as bright as that's as bright as this goes and it is it is
filling this room and burning into my face and if I turn the exposure up just
a little bit now look at this we're at like 10 FPS right put it down again with
the ISO changes yeah it's annoying and then when I hit auto exposure here it
blows me out I don't get it it's annoying that's for sure in the room
light on it is on you have no idea how I actually bright that really is it hurts
what is gonna have to be 20 FPS Andy oh also keep in mind I know I'm looking at
you here was that also keep in mind change the gain yeah if I turn the gain
down or turn it up it does the same thing it's weird wait let me try that
and see if I look like an idiot Sunday is green screen movie night part 2
because it's some fancy but nothing tomorrow but we'll be back on Sunday or
green screen radio is pure jazz man and that's gonna be a fun one I'm
predictable and just learn sure you could pay some let me try this tell you
which buttons to press and so let's turn this on that radio that's that we
scheduled so then if I turn the gain up here we'll try it that better my semi in
60 FPS said is that way better contrast is a little too high though isn't it
how's that I think that's actually better I think we're good now you can see all
the gross individual hairs on my beard because it's darkening them whatever
that's what the exposure down to the gain up
your chicken should not be pink hey we really loved the sponsored content when
you were fixing your camera and we're having a fucking blast in two-point
campus I actually this game is really fun I actually like I like to point um
hospital as well so that's not surprising to me sorry it's not
surprising to me all right let's upgrade this I can have 15 students now upgrade
we are not you yep this is a sponsored stream and this stream will be over very
soon very omegle camera you put that you keep the chef out on hey yo hey Jermo
what platforms of this game on well I'll tell you in just a second so first of
all this is the platforms you can get this on it's on it's on it's on and who
could forget and of course it is check it out on those places here's a question
if you missed it it's on it's on the flight and and get it on those
platforms just because education is a scam doesn't mean all those teachers are
bad people I forgot where I put them but whatever I used to like making the
little volcano it's pretty trippy to learn that volcanoes what's wrong this
but oh I thought this person was sad like it safely that's what they all be
teaching us man the dance floor is like Club Penguin oh that's so sweet that's
so sweet that's so cute that reminds me of this one time when I when I opened up
mine and I looked to see what was on sale what was available and lo and behold
a two-point campus was on and it was just such as I could take it into the
bathroom and I called my friend Dave I was like Dave I know you've got and I
know that you're looking for there's something for fun to play with is he
trying to make a joke yeah that hurt it's in there somewhere this is Joe why
is it's bad stink what's wrong with it why is this bed stink that's not gonna
do anything you're gonna change the sheets why would a bed smell that bad
that's something wrong all right do you have to get up you're gonna fucking
smoke us out here you get what don't do it every single bed did somebody die oh
no he's filling room with gas this is really popular people love this why
won't anybody join this club only three people how do I make how do I promote it
I never went please you hit all the flies the day Sun goes bye-bye and the
spooky white beach ball cast down its dark favor on us all oh no nevermind
this I thought that was a swarm of flies it's just like chatter I thought it was
like near and then a million flies okay things that I was supposed to make a um
oh right a cake place a sweet kitchen was the entrance right there do right
there that good enough no it is not I don't blocked blocking it I had him
blocked item blocked why why is item blocked can't use it here why can I use
it here I need more space around the machine I don't think so maybe I do I
want to see this thing in action what the hell is this speed walking club will
somebody come this way oh there's no door how do they get over there how do
they actually get over here they can't come out this way oh they they just walk
from here all the way across oh I only have 900 bucks you're right can they not
leave no they can leave hmm can they they're not trapped in here right drink
some water all right I will is it there they can't leave the dance floor I
actually think I have to connect it somehow there's even a single one of
your students know the spell lines access to Northgate I don't think so bad
teacher Andy I want let me go to the map I'm curious about something I want to see
how many zones there are this one's like medieval themed this is the original one
this is like the one we're on now this one looks like it unlocks maybe this is
baseball kind of stadium this one over here is there a sandbox mode I'm curious
did you take a shower there is a sandbox mode oh you have to like beat the game
okay okay that's cool well you have to get at least through the game this is a
German stand-in I could see how you feel that way all right let's go back what
else yeah we'll be like another five minutes you need to do the first four
levels you're a genuine question how do you manage your pain levels when your
chronic pain flares up um if I'm really honest distractions help and this is
kind of one of them whenever I'm just kind of sitting there hanging out and I
like don't care about that kind of the shitty way that I feel a lot of time
it's I kind of just put it back here and it's not accessed you probably see from
time to time I'm you probably pick up on it when I go like this that's me going
like anytime that you can see the letters down here when I go like that
it is there it always is and but I just do it and I just try to put it back here
and just not put it in the front of my head and it's crazy that if you do that
if you actually try to just distract yourself with stuff you don't focus on
it and I know that sounds really like yeah man that like it sucks it does but
I'm right now having fun I'm having fun playing this game hanging out being a
dickhead on stream so like I don't I don't have time to care about that I
don't have the capacity to give a shit about that right now right and also go
to your doctor to pain management's a huge pain in the ass it really is there's
so many weird dumb things that our body does for no reason that you really
should have a program with it out with your doctor yeah it's a lot of
distractions and the more that I have like fun that the more that it does it's
not a thing that I care about and it sucks it when the stream turns off and
I'm just kind of lying in bed it's like oh what that's a no excuse me yeah oh
yeah but that's just that that's just the fact thanks for the cool streams hey
thanks for being here I'm glad you're here let's have some fun and with that
I'll see you guys later if streaming helps manage pain why
well let me make this really clear it's not like the act of streaming that's
managing my pain symptoms it's just one of a few one of many things that can
distract me from the current problem make no mistake about it the reason why
I only stream two three days a week is because it actually does become a
problem after I sit here for a long time then I'm not hey guys I'm managing my
pain with twitch streams that's not that's not what I mean yeah that's two
point campus I give it a stamp of recommendation I know the stream is
sponsored but I mean it's it it's a fun tongue-in-cheek light-hearted management
to point kind of tycoon type games it's fun it just is these games are fun there's
no other way I can spin that for you it's available on you know devs obviously
I appreciate the sponsor so thank you to two-point campus devs it's a great
game I think it's really fun I actually think it's a fun game hope you guys
enjoyed it if you want it if you wanted to you know do your own get on steam
right now seems like there's a lot of content seems promising is it on switch
oh yes it is and then a call to the lamb you will see that I will bring call to
the lamb back after baseball I got a lot of things lined up after baseball yeah
then that game was really good too two two solid video games back to back today
yeah that's gonna end the stream that'll end this off with obviously the sponsor
segment as well go support these devs because you know if they supported the
channel so that's good special thanks to two-point campus I'll see you guys on
Sunday it's green screen tomorrow green screen is Sunday Sunday at 4 p.m. Pacific
Sunday at 4 p.m. Pacific not tomorrow yeah take care everybody see you soon I
think there are there are more than a hundred green screen videos we're gonna
be watching I know for a fact that there's at least three to four hours I
think of content that we have not seen yet so should be exciting stuff I agree
yeah you should it's I mean in about six hours here you've been potentially
watching for a long time I would hydrate if you haven't yeah see you on Sunday
green screen movie night part two have a great night and of course call your
mother see you guys Sunday