Hey, oh, I almost just fell down through my ground. How you doing? Welcome back to the stream, everybody.
MakaS, what? Uh, hold on, is there something wrong? What's wrong? No, not again. Hold on, what's
wrong? Hello? Why is this doing this? This is- there's no- there's no sound effects on. There's no-
Okay, this- I- I don't know what just happened. I don't know why there was- I don't know- I
don't know what happened. What I do know is now it's gone, and...
On the GoXLR, there's an effects button. You can press it, and I didn't press it. It shouldn't
be doing that at all. That button was not pressed. We sound- we're good now? We sound fine? We're good,
right? This is a good audible level. I think we sound fine. Let me turn this off. Okay. Where's
the shoe? Yeah, I know. I know. Let me- I can address the shoe situation in just a moment. Just
wait for people- people have to trickle in for it. Uh, whatever. I'm just gonna talk about it right
now. You can link to this if you want. The shoe eating stream had to be postponed because there-
There's been, obviously, a lot of, um, panic in the grocery stores. There's been a lot of,
like, the national emergency being called, countries being locked down. It- it was actually
kind of not on the priority list at the last, like, three or four days. It actually was probably
gonna be pretty hard to get somebody to make a comedy shoe. So, because, like, the bakery that
I was gonna use was not really, uh- it's kind of hard to do that the last two or three days.
I was gonna have a fucking comedy shoecake made, all right? That's the joke. And now it's- I-
what am I supposed to do? I have to tell you the joke. What it is. Now you have to eat a real shoe.
I'm not eating a real shoe. You could make 15 accounts if you want. Dermal lied about eating
a real shoe. And plus, it was a me costume, by the way. I don't have to eat a real shoe. I- I
could eat, like, a fucking Ring Pop if I want. Eat shoe. Eat shoe. I'm not gonna eat a real shoe.
Why would I ever eat a real shoe? Think about this. I- you guys have to process this information.
Imagine eating a shoe. You can't eat a fucking shoe. You said. Yeah, I- how many fucked up things
have I said on this stream? You can't eat a shoe. I'll- I will have to go to- I'll have to go to,
like, the hospital if I eat a shoe. I'll die if I eat a shoe. If you eat a shoe, you die. Right?
Like, you can't just eat a shoe. Leather is edible. You want me to go buy, like,
leather shoe? I'm not- no, leather- no, no, no, no. I'm not- why do I- I'm getting a little
worked up now. I'm- yeah, I gotta calm down. I'm not eating a fucking real shoe. I'm not eating a
fucking shoe. I had, like, a comedy routine planned out and it kind of fell through.
Doesn't mean I'm not gonna do it. I'll- okay, I will eat a comedy shoe within the next two weeks.
I'm not gonna eat a real one. I'm not spending any more time on, on, like, eat the fucking shoe.
I'm not gonna spend any more time on this. Don't- don't talk about- why are people talking about
that? That's pre-stream chat spoilers. Come on. Just have them make- you can eat leather shoes
if you boil them. No, you can't. No, you can't. No, you can't. You can't eat shoes. No, you can't.
I'm not eating a fucking shoe. Okay, here you go, guys. I will eat a shoe if there- if- no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm not fucking going over this. I'm not gonna boil a pair of
leather shoes. I love the- I love- the best response to this is, in all capitals, look it up.
Yeah, um, I could eat the t-shirt that's on me right now, probably, if I boil it and, like,
remove the ink. Do I- am I gonna do that? No, it's very bad for you. It's probably not- it's
not- it's probably so bad for you. Eat a shoe, you poser. Um, you can't call somebody a poser
for something that literally no one has done on stream. I- I wouldn't be the poser. I'd be
the first guy that's fucking ever done it. That's not a poser. I'd be the first guy.
Okay, TLDR. He read it. He's a Reddit user. TLDR. Um, some of the purchases I would have wanted to
make and the coronavirus has caused a lot of widespread kind of panic and people buying a
bunch of shit. Grocery stores locked down. Places are, like, you know, it's not- it wasn't on the
priority list the last two or three days. It's been difficult. We're trying to get through this shit.
That's an excuse. It's not, though. Preparing for, like, a- all right, let me give you a list of
things. Uh, preparing to eat a comedy shoe versus prepare for a global pandemic. Which one of those
two things is more important, do you think? I mean, we gotta get some priorities somewhere.
It's just- all right. We're gonna play Binding Advising. This doesn't mean that I'm not gonna
eat the comedy shoe, okay? Just pretend that we just gotta- you gotta give me some time.
All right, I'm gonna go over something real quick. Uh, real quick. Uh, so there are lines out the door.
All the grocery stores and all the bakeries and stuff. But I say I- I lump bakeries into the
grocery store because I'm a fucking liar. Uh, but there are literally lines out the door for the
grocery store. People are freaking out, buying, like, water, buying, like, thousands of dollars
in groceries. And I was gonna have this bakery in the grocery store. Make- make this. Imagine the guy
walking in there. It's like, oh my god, we gotta get toilet paper. We gotta get water. We gotta get
fucking, um, we could just buy a bunch of frozen foods. There's hundreds of- hundreds of people,
thousands of people in these grocery stores. And I'm the guy that walks up to the- to the
bakery counter and is like, hey, can you make me a fake funny comedy shoe?
Excuse me, sir. Uh, this, like, I gotta- I gotta deal with something over here. Uh,
can you make me a funny shoe cake? Uh, sir? Can you look around? Yeah. Sir, this is a fucking
global emergency. I need you to make me a funny cake today. Anyways, welcome to the stream.
Take care of yourselves. Be careful. Uh, actually- actually be careful, right? Do your own due
diligence. Take care of your friends and family members, especially the older ones. Because,
you know, but this is- this is- this is the real deal. You know, you can't fuck around.
Just be careful. If you have shoes in your house, eat them. All right, we're over the she- we're over
the eating shoes thing now. I'm excited for this because I haven't played Binding Visage in a long
time. Uh, this is Anti-Birth. Uh, we talked about this last week. A lot. And, uh, I- you know,
when- when you get something in my brain, shit becomes- I can't get it out. My mic is going
in and out? What is wrong with this fucking thing? What? Hello? Hello? All right, here we go.
Shouldn't be doing that. That was a one-guy moment? All right, fine. Anyways, um, we're gonna play
Binding Visage. But this is gonna be a gamer stream. I haven't- haven't been in one of these in a long
time. But what was the last- Jeremy plays a video game and, like, does- doesn't, like, fucking walk
into walls and stuff? How- when- how long ago was that? It hasn't happened. Mario? Two streams ago?
Was it? Sekiro? Oh, it was all right. I mean, Mario was okay. But it was probably Sekiro. This is the
first time. All right. When does the official- now, here you go. You- people- I know, go ahead and
laugh. Like, make fun of me. This is- this is an old save file. Yes, okay. Hadn't even beaten the
game on Hard with Eve yet. I know. You can laugh. But I- this is, like, an old rebirth file. I just
want to make sure that I didn't have to beat Mom's heart, like, ten times. This is- I had to- this is
an old rebirth save file that got pulled. I don't even know who these two are. Minus five. Yeah, but
when you play Binding Visage, you just- if you don't- by, like, the third floor, if you're like,
nah, nah, this ain't working. You just quit. Ah, why did I say that? People are gonna make fun of me.
What? You- you gotta go all in. Fine, y'all. We'll go all in. All right, who do I want to play with?
Kane? I got nothing on Hard of beating on with Kane. I could literally do anything with Kane.
Let us pick. We'll do in Kane. This is the anti-birth mod, by the way, and soon it's going to be
official. I don't know when, though. I really actually don't know. And why are we- why is the
start button getting pressed over and over again? All right, it's been a while. Uh, dude, this is
anti-birth, not afterbirth, just so you know. Yeah, this is anti-birth. Anti-birth. This is not afterbirth
reset randy second or third quarter this year really so i actually i don't have like really
any experience with anti-birth so you guys gonna have to help me let me actually i know people
gonna no people no one's gonna make fun of me for this i have that platinum god uh cheat sheet up
to know what items do i this is just how it works all right let me get this uh let me get this split
up actually the cheat sheet eat the cheat sheet print it out and eat it print out the cheat sheet
and wear it on your feet like wrap it up around your feet take it off your feet and eat the shoes
wait a minute okay what if i like get like two pieces of ham and like wear them as shoes
do those count as shoes and then eat the shoes does that count oh that's disgusting no i'm not
doing that it technically would count but i'm not doing it all right let's uh let's go no not yet
okay now we can go eat them i'm not even gonna say what you just wrote all right let's go mario
look at how much time is left i'm only all a minute 40 has gone by i gotta like beat the clock
cane starts with the luck foot right actually you know it's actually weird it hasn't it's been a
long time since i played on a big screen i played this on the switch a shit load i'm actually kind
of it's weird to not have this play in a tiny window let's go yeah why can i not um is there no
extra hud on anti-birth i like having that hud on the left oh if anyone wants to see there it is
play along with me fucking go oh my god uh unc eternal life you can die once right fucking go
i'm gonna step on this once oh it's a mistake i don't have any bombs go god damn it holy shit
relax this is new enemies what's what is this guy oh my fucking god go i'm gonna die i've never seen
these enemies before these new oh and why did i use that in here i can use this the sacrifice
room now saved by the hematomasis all right wait can i do i have to be in the room the whole time
i don't think so right can i just do it can i just go up and just hit oh come on all right give me
another heart yeah i can go back and forth right i'm gonna get a chest here right shouldn't i have
gotten something by now it resets i'm kind of scared to do it again because i'm gonna i'm gonna
have one heart you have to die guys i i know what this room does okay but it didn't i think you have
to be in the room the whole time it's risky but i did it i like to see the stats on the left you
don't leaving is fine it's just random well that kind of sucks i just got i just got completely
that was bogus i just hurt myself like six times just time to fucking reset you know what i mean
this baby plum i can fuck away from me i don't know what you do i know what you do get away get
away get away holy shit this is an exclusive anti-birth enemy this fucking mod has been out
for like two or three years all right i'm gonna die don't talk it's not a comedy stream i almost
died this is hp and regen up oh sick nice sick cool i just got hit yeah but that's the first time
i've seen that it's pretty good for the fucking first time ever seeing that enemy i want to see
people clapping in this fucking chat let's go go back to the sacrifice room no fucking go play
jesus man it's been five minutes i hate the darkness you know the things i hate the most
this game i hate the curse of the blind i hate curse of darkness just makes this oh i hate these
guys too i hate these enemies they're so fast and erratic i hate and then some of them explode
you really let's just do don't hoof speed up is that all it does look it up on my cheat sheet
goat hoof it's just oh that's it that's actually what it does all right that's not what is how is
that cheating what do you mean cheater oh i am speed i'm going faster cool whoa i hate the
spiders they are the worst oh there's tnt right there all right careful not a big deal fine fucking
die oh shit god damn it i'm trying to explode this thing i can't see where it is all right i'm
fine whoa all right i'm good this is bob's brain common cold poison damage wow that's lucky right
there oh that's super lucky wow common cold blow these up i know i'll fucking do it accidentally
this build sucks like this is a shit build so far come on i'm dead if you say i'm dead then like
everyone knows that's watching the stream they go oh he's dead like yeah it's a heart he's he's
gonna die and then when i don't die it's like oh nice he didn't die i use that same tactic when
i'm by myself too instantly take all pills i know and i just what's the point of even hold it and
what's the point of holding um the trinket now the trinket's just i want to see my stats should
i blow this up and yes why would i why i asked that question god damn it what is it i thought
i was gonna get keys i want keys well i can get two i can get two i gotta save this for now oh i
should have had you blow up over there fuck curse of darkness i didn't even know it was over there
ah whatever okay keep going he's not even good at this game shut up i'm doing fine what has
happened i'm just like playing finding of isaac he's not even good what how do you can't even make
that judgment yet this is shit build here we go f10 f10 f10 f10 f10 what why is it we're saying
f10 f10 why why what am i doing f10 for press f10 i'm not gonna press f10 because i don't know
what it does uh clubs are keys or clubs are bombs which one i know you get two i'm not ready for
that yet it's for stats no it's not i didn't that doesn't do anything did i just take like a
screenshot what is f10 supposed to do f10 f10 f10 i just pressed it like four times we got him
he's already playing hard mode you geniuses wait is that supposed to change it to hard mode i'm
already in hard mode oh they added the stats in afterbirth right and you can't do them both at
the same time all right do i what is the club is clubs bombs clubs is bombs right there's hearts
clubs spades is keys right i want this look at that i know i got infinite bomb all right did i uh
where's the secret room over here secret room probably right here let's check it we got our
free bomb as we'll try and use it fuck i'm gonna i'm gonna go down i want another key oh no no i
need two keys to get in there no no reset it no don't reset it it's fine shit i'm actually really
this is usually really really good third rock you make you mark rock yeah i i knew what i i
should have known what i was getting into and i was like i'm gonna play isaac today if you say
you're gonna play the binding of isaac what you actually are trying to tell your chat is scream in
all capitals missed rock every time you see one i can't get in here no i'm not oh don't get mad
where's this missed rock nice nice eyes how did you see that and not me i don't doesn't make i
don't it's because you i'm i'm playing the game you're not playing the game no damage up items
it's like really actually is bad there's another one i can't promise to blow it up i don't have
anything missing rocks i can't blow them up all right so i brought this up like a few streams
ago and i didn't really give it much thought until very recently and maybe even today is this one of
my most favorite games ever made is this like on the on the list somewhere i think it is i think
it has to be i i keep coming back to him playing this game like hundreds of times i don't do it
with anything else i used to do that with like team fortress and like that's it how could this
not be on that list maybe oh we've got a devil don't go in there oh this build is really bad
range up you hate to see that wait what you really hate to see that uh and these are all awful
we got a familiar that shoots with me spectral tears or die it that item is i'm not why would i
get that that item is just guaranteeing you're gonna die eight times i'm not taking that take
guppy why would i take that you get one heart and it's just i'm gonna die nine times and then
going to have to reset not if you're a gamer guppy transformation yeah but that's not guaranteed
wrong order idiot what are you talking about i mean wrong order why would i get it i don't know
because this this all right this build sucks so this is like a who gives a shit build you could
have taken all three i don't know why i'm gonna hold what do you mean take all three press f6 or
f7 for stats somebody confirmed that before i press it i'm gonna just kill me i don't know
what that does oh shit okay that just freaked me out i googled it that's our in options no they're
not old r i know what that does it doesn't work like the original flash isaac wait what we're
going for guppy because that's the only way that this works out what are these um well these like
little like white things on the ground are these like collectibles not supposed to be making any
jokes that was a mistake this is no joke stream that was not even funny what are these i was
trying to think of what looks like this i was gonna say marshmallows and then i just said
collectibles holy shit that was very bad oh you know these collectibles that was bad that was
desperate oh what are these things through the ground i think if something looks that small and
white something small and white uh collectibles i don't have seen these guys before either these
things are crazy what was that laugh i don't use pictures of fucked up is it where i die
don't when you see like three or four champions in a room you just you just accept that you're
gonna die but i guess i didn't all right remind me to blow this up when i get uh bob's brain back
f7 all right on sub i'm not gonna press f7 it's gonna kill me that's probably like the
suicide button or something right like items that you have you can like die and then maybe
is there a die button in isaac i think there is f7 i'm not gonna press f7
there's no stats in this one because it's tied to rebirth but this i'm on a mod right now guys
what the fuck really yeah they're going yeah just press it they added it to anti-birth f7
no that's not what i want i don't care about that i care about the stats f6 all right let's go
whoop that rock okay i'm gonna get two bombs and one key oh well shit and it's the worst thing is
it this the poison tears aren't they tied it's tied to luck how often it procs right yeah that's
fantastic oh there's a a demon heart watch out for these these ah well this runs egg fucking stupid
this run sucks hey well at least i can die 10 fucking times wait a second i have the ankh too
so i have the ankh and i can die 10 times
that's so dumb oh boy i don't know what these guys do when they die some of them explode oh
they just do the oil okay no you also shoot what the fuck one of them was a bomb
what oh that was a heal it scares the shit out of me sometimes how come how come greed modes
not in this because it has an anti-birth thing i talked about this in the pre-stream chat and
i'm the only person in the world that likes greed mode apparently i thought it was like fun
i was like oh man maybe she should maybe uh pog greed mode and everyone's like no fuck you greed
mode sucks greed mode fuck greed mode i'm like oh my god i thought i was gonna get like oh pog
greed mode no lay not fucking up but i'm about dumb mode sucks delete it oh fuck okay sorry
open look at my damage 420 that's it i'm gonna get this up is it chat hates greed mode yeah why
what's wrong with it laughing my ass off it's so funny it's so funny oh so that means
the statistics this that's statistically impossible that's not to blow up where i wanted to do
that's statistically not even possible it was like 5000 pixels of space but where that could blow up
your luck is down that doesn't mean that doesn't mean anything what is this oh okay yeah i know
people are going to be telling me not to do that and shit but it doesn't matter i take every pill
instantly no matter what it is i don't care what it is if i see question marks it's being taken
immediately there's no strategy here oh what's that glasses is this double shot oh yes it is
yes okay run save run actually saved i need some hp up though hold r to save run answers vision
does this open up the secret room so i i don't remember what these do oh i hate these guys
i'm thinking of a different enemy actually this is not bad at all i'm thinking of the ones that
get up and they spit like forward if i hate those guys still this damage really actually suck all
right uh what does answers do it was the entire map yeah let's go no wait i should probably save
this i should say this is like when i go in the next round yeah next floor all right so where's
the secret room let's see uh secret room is either up here down there no it's definitely over here
it's definitely that that that middle section right has to be like right here right this is
correct not damn okay so what so then it's over uh up up here bottom left by the boss room no no
what a fucking idiot i'm gonna say here god damn it secret room has to be surrounded by at least
two these are these are these guesses are perfectly fine these these are perfectly normal
this is how you decide grab the hearts i can't pick up hearts i have no heart containers that
was perfectly reasonable for me to think it was in the middle or up here it's very reasonable
give this double shot dude look at this fucking double shot oh and there's poison on it too give
me my luck back give me give me my luck back give me damage up and we got and we're talking this no
no i mean i can hurt people with this i've gotten such shitty boss room item
it's all right do the challenge room i don't do those the bandage is is insane
oh hold on does this can i use this and will it give me the site will it remove the curse no
will it not come on i hate this i hate this because i lose track especially when you get
later on in the game so we're going down first remember we went down what's the question mark
under the question mark on the top right what's that little red question mark in the box like the
melted box what is that is that the curse are we going right watch out for that oh oh oh oh
what am i watching like a fucking sports game oh oh oh oh oh just take this whole entire like
however long this bot is just put it up next to like the red sock no no no no no oh come on
come on ref that this has got to be like a referee in this game at some point like a referee enemy
uh this thing's dumb come on ump there is okay i've seen a lot of minus twos on this i think
that's actually kind of a funny one i think that's actually i think that's kind of funny
i think that's funny all right i can walk i'm just no i'll lose i'll forget where this is whatever
i'm gonna i might i'm gonna need to cross um uh oh here we go all right do i go in here with the
two keys or do i use the two keys on the item room we're going we're going all in and it was
a fucking the right call two hearts stupid worthless see in my mind they can't all be
fucking bad in a row they can't but apparently they can uh two hearts don't need it hang man's
fine this tier is down getting real close to resetting what was what i just beat the game
on hard with pain right that's the thing i had that's not a long there's not over here he's
gonna be reset randy no i'm not not today i know what you guys do i've played this game sometimes
all right is it weird for me to actually say that when you get tears down from the pills that is
almost an immediate restart no matter where you are in the game right that's like that's like an
instant fucking just restart immediately instantly but i'm not going to i'm not going to um i think
i am gonna do this though because i need no i'm not a child maneuver is that me being a child
or is it me being realistic all right we gotta go we went down right i gotta go up wait did we go
left now we gotta go up i might come on i might use the uh hangman over there get the fires or
something i forgot how much i liked this game i mean i don't get me wrong i played this a ton
on my switch like in bed but you know i just forget just how much you fucking like something
didn't get hit one time by the way you know a lot of you thought that room was going to be
impossible to not get hit shit i tried to sneak by i got stuck on the rock in tears down and the
guy would have been dead already what's that mean what's that little what was that little like
insurance commercial jangle mean that does that does i see something to find something why is
it i don't i don't play i've never played anybody he doesn't know i actually don't know tears down
let me take it i got extra i know what the blast damage is but that's just that's pretty good
that's wait does that count for my active right now that counts for the active right
that's a that's blast damage technically right or is it only bomb well we're gonna get some free
bombs i forgot it's okay i forgot how huge okay we're good oh what is that thing all right i have
enough money for this what is it what is this thing all right i gotta i gotta look this up on
my fucking platinum god cheat sheet what's it called where is it uh the cheater you do the same
thing you can't keep track of everything in this game what does it look like it's a it's like a
face it's a face with like a bunch of needles in it where is this is this an anti-birth item
i don't see it anywhere what does it look like yeah that's i don't see that on my platinum god
list anti-birth like uh rebirth items i don't see this on the platinum god list it's called voodoo
head there it is this item has a chance to spawn additional curse rooms on each future floor that
kind of sucks oh wait a minute no it doesn't because guppy first rooms are yeah that that's
not bad because that's doesn't guppy spawn in the curse rooms more often yeah i'm going for it let's
go and give me some more money i want more money um i'll just take it out of here hold on okay i'm
fine oh he's not dead what oh he's not dead i thought he was dead and tears down all right
i gotta be careful that's not good that's not good did i even get to the item room yet i didn't did i
what did i get in the item room the bombs all right okay all right here we go i can't believe
i missed all right get out of here there we go milk now we're cooking although there are hearts
somewhere weren't there that's mega built yeah i'll let you have that one i'll let you have that
one temporarily oh i don't even need hearts regeneration oh the reveal item right right
right right right don't lose that one where's that down down right wait if i had any luck at all this
would be this would be great this way ah here we go why did i do that i mean waste i can only hold
one item i can't hold more than one item in my lower right look see i can't hold that i've used
it in the boss room why would i need to do that to blow these up to get a maybe a spirit heart
maybe but my luck is zero i don't i gotta save these bombs to bosses that's my damage man
my damage sucks ass right now don't click the link i have no plan on it here we go bang oh this is a
double shit this is a big one double all right i love when he's a good look at this you don't
mean all right we do the item rooms we went down we'll do okay i love this oh how much damage did
that not do what didn't know you could do that i was gonna make a joke say like oh here's a tip
on isaac you can these guys can eat the bombs but i feel like if anyone's played this game for more
than an hour they'd know that already oh we use that hangman right here huh it has to be greed
of course it does oh shit minions somebody get the alts that's actually really that's really good
i got a steam sale from that everything 50 off what's this who cares take it instantly speed up
hey what those fire i thought only the red ones did what the fuck do those things do
they're gonna keep doing it i'm gonna forget oh fuck oh no okay i gotta watch this reminds me of
mario sunshine what's the timing here down here okay i got the timing ready you have to go
holy shit that's bad you use one of the bombs nice use the key i don't want to use the key
that's not cheating guys i can die nine more times i'll be all right the way this is going
to be a problem is if i don't have more than like two or three hearts going into like womb two
oh jeez i don't know i don't know the tech i don't know the tech on these guys
i don't have the patterns down on them i don't know the tech hey what
best item in the game this runs well run you should do uh-huh uh-huh here you guys are you
guys ha haing binding of isaac poop pac-man enemies these guys suck let the poison kill them
don't you just let the poison kill them don't think stupid just let the poison kill them
i don't have any keys great this is fantastic they're inspired by the legend of zelda um i
would say this game reminds me more of star tropics than it does of zelda in fact it's
almost the exact same video game those who don't know what that is i'm seeing a lot of question
marks but some of you guys don't know the the the beauty of one of the great star tropics is
is it one of the you you don't know it and it's sad that you don't one of those games are like
nobody gave a shit about when it came out the regular nintendo it is this exact video game
it's a boomer game i don't know what it is but it must be boomer right right
okay okay i'm sorry take a room and this is a super secret room so that means you're gonna get
oh yeah don't pick that up those who don't know about binding of isaac that is an eternal heart
if i pick that up it's gonna give me half of an eternal white heart and as long as i do not take
damage that will remove that white heart and i go to the next floor i will gain one full heart
container don't touch that until you but wait a minute um aren't i about to fight i'm gonna
fight mom you can't leave after you fight mom right so i'm gonna just don't get hit by mom
get it i'm not gonna get it right now get it before going in like i can do the first boss
and then leave i can at least do the first boss and if i take damage you know whatever
fucking go god some of you guys so you guys are so impatient he's gotta go no i'm strategizing
easy
i was gonna get a couple of spiders don't just wait oh my god i'm freaking out why
i can't it's hard to see it's like too dark what's gamma at right now
should be 120 right ah excuse me excuse me oh okay that's much better that's not no that's not
cheating it's 120 go to binding about open up binding of isaac right now i want you all to do
this open up binding of isaac right now open up binding of isaac anti-birth plus go to options
and see what the game is if i by default it's 120 yes it is i win yes it is i win yes it is i win
watch out these shoot you just play the game shoe eater don't make me laugh it's an important
video game being played all right i i'm an idiot i'll okay i'm good we're good i'm gonna forget
that exists hate these guys hate these guys ah ah tuber oh man i can't even get
once a tuber always a tuber right hey good like i can die eight more times the rock rock rock rock
rock rock rock get the rock where are this this one right here which one is that no where's it
which rock are you talking about on the right side oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah the mega bomb is gonna hurt me all right second item room
give me like something big what the fuck ten bombs and i'm just mr bomb guy well let's don't move
what the fuck i'm trying to just guy yeah all right let's i just have a blue pile what the
fuck is this thing i'm trying to bait him oh my god this is gonna be hard to do this the bombs
oh my fuck just keep oh my holy shit okay we can try it again is there a way that he
telegraph haven't even been looking not really i don't just jesus whoa you put the fuck he does
that shit how did i not die he's gonna do that oh oh my god this guy sucks all right no more bombs
just try to dodge i guess fuck is that how many more moves does this guy have oh
ah all right first time ever fighting boss let's see if i can learn how to fight him
oh my goodness this is so bad this guy sucks this is the end of the run okay omega lol easy
it's not easy what are you what crack are you smoking i'm going right now i think i got that
done oh what the fuck this motherfucker can just tele-frag you is he like pointing a direction
oh fuck where does i don't understand how you avoid that is it just ran is it random
maybe i should just keep make sure just run in a circle i'm just gonna run in a circle
oh that didn't work i'm just gonna literally never stop moving is it knowing i'm doing that
it knows i'm doing that he's trying to catch me he's like i know what you're doing i'm gonna
trip you i'm gonna trip you you motherfucker oh i'm dead well i'm gonna go to the shop for the
last ditch effort here i have to go to the shop this guy killed me like nine times which oh my
god this guy sucks imagine if he died right there that would be so bad you have one heart
this build isn't that good anyways just keep him oh this is all 50% off good thing it's
more options in the store a super key and a pill oh that's full health though uh give me this
whatever i'm dead this is i can take i can uh no no i'm gonna get hit i need more hearts there was
a mistake to take the fucking guppies tail i shouldn't even touched it go to the library
holy shit there is a library what i i is it two keys to get in there don't do that to me right
now come on larry's larry's jr here we go well uh okay this may this this may have saved the run
if i can just play well all right we got we got uh soul protection just get the free heart uh now
we this is just uh evil go ahead and use it get the free heart okay uh and then psychic shot like
i just got two soul parts so this one psychic shot should i do maybe i keep this one this doesn't
add any damage though keep the satanic one all right well i'm gonna get hit like i'm gonna get
rocked back and forth like five times guys don't you understand i'm gonna get hit by a spike room
accidentally on the way back up to the bus by the battery i already didn't already do it i already
bought the battery the extra half heart i told you it was gonna fucking happen i knew it i'm like
looking at chat and i knew i was gonna walk into a spike i told you it was gonna happen
blow up the skulls oh oh yeah okay now we do this one too run save run saved what is it
ah okay this is possible now just don't fuck it up don't mess it up i just have to be careful
i forgot imagine if i explored before yeah i know but i was so upset that i couldn't kill this guy
his fucking teleport move it's just it's just stupid you know what i mean like i don't understand
why that's even in the game i don't know why that's in the game it's just it's stupid like why is it
even in the game right just like say just quote that hey hold on i got an idea well i'll do it
for you it's just stupid it shouldn't even be in the fucking game that's good right can you hear it
i don't know you can't hear it right sometimes the go xlr just doesn't work i don't know why i just
tried to record it on the go xlr so i could play it like five times but for some reason it doesn't
doesn't work and sometimes it like makes me sound like a fucking robot randomly for no reason okay
well whatever bring back the wink command what happened wait what why is this different person
what's going on why is it war wait why do i have a new boss did the game feel bad for me
because i use book of revelations oh that's right oh shit hope we don't see that bone guy again
no damage no damage no damage no damage okay so do i that's that's i could get bandage that's a
band-aid girl right or tears up get the screw tears and shots beat up yeah ah okay okay let's
go what's the blue mom i've agreed nice okay so i haven't unlocked the negative yet so well runs
actually saved what does he need to i need to do in an hour so i don't have the negative right
now yeah this is an this is a rebirth save file i there's an old save file to make sure i didn't
play the game like a thousand times go do satan then should i just what what's the protocol here
to go to actually just go to satan just go in don't pick up you don't don't take the polaroid
to go to satan right because isn't the polaroid to take you to heaven take it take the polaroid
what take it doesn't the polaroid mean you go to all right let's go you can still choose to go
down oh okay yeah that's right all right well here's this is where we actually like lose the
game is it to be like i look at my damage i still have like 400 420 divided by 10 damage that's not
good this guy should okay if you're not killing enemies down here in the womb in less than three
seconds it's over this guy this guy doesn't die in three seconds the runs over how am i supposed
to beat mecha satan uh how am i supposed to beat mecha satan like this all right almost time for
another heart man i'm getting kind of lucky with these hearts why is there a grainy filter on the
game because it's supposed to be scary and weird i didn't give me a full heart oh is i never played
this game why do you sneeze on people this is good all right i'm gonna take it right now i'm
gonna just don't just don't take five hits easy it's not easy anymore god die dance dance dance
bad aim fire pots keys i can't get over there never seen these guys before give her the hershey's
kisses and deal with the rest imagine taking damage from one of these little poop things
holy shit i should have just ended my career oh they just die no do they okay they just explode
all right well this is let's go yeah i don't have any bombs just realize this i have half my items
and bombs yet i don't have any it's a bomb damage great die die die die die die die die die die die
die die die die die uh-oh get him with poison forget about them they're not even scary we're
good toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat hmm all right left or right left or right left or right
left or right which one which one which one just right left left right right left left is always
right well it's all right stay in the sides this guy's not even a problem all right we're gonna
get the coal give me like the rock give me no what is it a lump of coal all right we need range
lump of coal this is you get more damage the further the balls travel right all right give
me the thing that gives me really slow shot speed tons of range and bring my shot speed down a ton
so this just these turn into gigantic snowballs all right let's use this too might as well free
heart that's not how it works so i've been wrong for three and a half years i think four years
so what does that actually do i've been i've been wrong for probably five plus years what does that
do it's just distance not travel time no casino i only brought five dollars into the casino
what is this what the hell is this thing do it's a battery machine wait okay what's the what if i
just keep getting coins and keep getting uh black hearts holy shit all right hold on is my is my
idea all right come on i can overcharge it no give me more than one coin bullshit oh thank you
well i made out uh let's play this don't worry i'm gonna i'm gonna i'll blow this guy up in just a
minute you got a refund ah lemon party all right let's go i still have no damage up this is gonna
this is gonna fail catastrophically at some point i need like i need more tears one more damage or
anything this is easy i won't say that out loud though because if you say that out loud you're
gonna take like three hits what difficulty you're playing on this is on normal i'm just casually
playing them well i've only played this game for like a few hours so i'm just trying to
this is on normal still learning the game i don't step on the spikes what are those things uh
collectibles oh like i'll never get over how bad that was you couldn't think if i could like
marsh bellows that would be on what would be worse going here what does this do i don't know that is
uh what does the two room do all right room two the room of two that's not how my cheat sheet there
it is okay rerolls all pickups in the room okay this rerolls is the pickups in the room so to
reroll the four coins so just whatever what are we gonna get oh that's actually pretty good
wait can i do it again how many times i'm gonna holy shit that's a jackpot tears down of course
tears down tears down why can't there be tears up twice well okay cool let's go uh there's a
chance that like the rock could have been in there away from me ah we gotta have those youtube
reactions whoa i know i know i know and don't be the spine hand thing have the regular hand
regular hand good watch this ready tells you that have never played this game before i got
a secret technique for you what's this challenge up i don't want that what does that do does that
do anything else okay higher chance for champion enemies that's it that's all it does no i'm not
playing on hardest mode all right let's go it lives oh look at this look at how slow this is
taking to kill it lives i might as well just fucking uninstall the game good song though
like if it lives doesn't die and like i'm just telling you real facts here it lives is still
i thought if i didn't move you unlocked glass baby wow oh this hold on goat head and all right
guppy fuck out of here all right what's the cloak do what's that cloak what is it called get them
both you're taking away all my health man gives isaac a guaranteed devil or angel room on every
floor they can appear even if they've already beaten the boss and it didn't show up originally
who who cares the goat head i i have like one opportunity to do the goat head or a heart was
a cloak you was it called was a cloak called coat the black coat cape not called eight robe
ceremonial robe three black hearts one damage up when depleted black hearts deal day yeah oh
all right yeah i'll do it i need the damage i need the damage bad let's fucking go both i'm i only
i'm telling you one more floor why would i take them both that'll kill me i'll die i'll actually
keel over and die and then you can all laugh all right you want me to go up i have the polaroid
polaroid invincibility what does that mean take it i'm not taking it i'm going go down i'm going
down up down i'm going down let's be safe this is progress runs you guys shale i can already feel
that new damage imagine not taking that and thinking it was you know going to be worth it
oops oh it doesn't matter that's stupid fuck is this thing what does it do what does it do what
does that do okay all right good money that's gonna be 100 useless in a minute oh who's singing
bigger room god damn it a dime i can't i need like a casino room where am i getting all this money
where was this 20 minutes ago these guys just just kill them they don't do anything weird hey
what's going on guys jerma here with a whining of isaac let's play and what i mean by let's play
what i say by this is remember back in 2012 when somebody would make a let's play of a game
and it would be 12 minutes and you'd make a new video every 12 fucking minutes that's why i never
played these games i never did let's plays could you imagine if i only streamed for 12 minutes a
day anyways i'm playing with uh this is cain and i see you guys in uh 12 or 15 separate youtube
videos to see if i get to mom see you next time what's this are these guys melee i think so where's
the dubstep music watch out for the watch out for their melee this guy has clothes on he must be like
i think that's the leader by the way for those who're watching satan is the easiest boss in the
whole game until his phase three he becomes the second easiest boss in the game but for some
reason i have so much trouble with the third phase because my brain um is made out of eggs
this actually this guy actually sucked actually the worst boss in the game i hate this guy
i hate this guy i hate it no actually not this one the other one the green one what's the green
one there's a green version of this guy that's way worse than this okay god he did that oh my god
forgotten his moot the bloat sucks yeah he's stuck perma sucks oh don't worry everything's gonna be
fine okay things are starting to get a little a little more uh scary but it's okay i tried to
fucking move oh boy this is bad all right stop super nintendo kid right nintendo kid what's this
called oh my god i don't know the patterns this is the first time i've seen these motherfuckers
emperor let's let's go let's go i gotta go now let's go what's no just let's go let's go tears
down no i'm going three two one take oh what the fuck what was the intro ah all right here we go
oh my god i'm fucking panicking for no reason oh my god i'm fucking panicking i'm hitting every
single wrong button oh my god fucking here comes the choke i just choked so fucking hard
oh my god damn it it's been a long it's been a while i haven't played it in a while
fuck all right it's good it's okay why do they get a shield what all right i get focused come on
it's not that fucking hard polaroid what me where was the sip what all right i'm fucking yeah all
right it's a warm-up round it was a warm-up round plus this build sucks ass okay this feels
terrible this is built suck it was like it's eight bomb items it was like seven bomb items
sorry it's all bad i'm here we go looks to go sometimes you gotta fucking just get a warm-up
rounded it's so easy too i just like haven't played in too long it's all right you take one
warm-up round yeah you can't beat fucking satan are you first try coming back after like nine
months all right like a baby could have been bored in the time that i've played this game left
we're fine everything's fine and now we oh that's not quad shot game suck shit it's just that like
oh i've got here it's been a while and i lose i talk i get hit 12 times i'm so angry right now
but i can't like if you get if you let three grand slams the bottom of the ninth inning
you're still a pitcher right you have to you're still a pitcher of the game what am i gonna like
stop rolling on my back and be like yeah like smashing my hands on the ground
no i let off a grand slam you gotta keep pitching i feel warmed up i feel warmed up i feel good i
feel just terrible and remember when i told you it was like we had like the third floor and i was
like no this build sucks i don't like this it's gonna suck we're gonna roll on roll on the back
of the pinterest mountain and put my hands on the ground and go smash okay stop good look at that
first item right off the bat that's what we're looking for all right now be be calm be collected
explore god damn die to satan with like it that's not even like a stupid ass bullshit
all right good i got another key i missed a rock apparently i'll get it this infestation is pretty
good it helps oh whipworm i know what this does drop speed why is chat mean tonight may i welcome
you to germa985's twitch channel must be new here i think he must be new he hates us
no stop i can't look at chat anymore you're gonna kill me don't look at chat play i come on
don't be an idiot this is a good start okay where's that brock oh god damn it okay i missed a tinted
brock right here why is it lagging every time i go to new room is it happening on your screen why
is it happening you get a shitty pc i don't have a shitty pc how dare you all right let's go did you
get the real hulk game uh like why is it lagging what is this running on like open gl right now
well uh i don't want this i don't want this again secret room damn it open gl is really smooth
why is this lagging have you seen that too i don't understand why this is happening
like when i open a new door it's just like holy shit he almost got me a good shot close platinum
god wait that could be accurate that actually might be accurate i think it was let's see don't
you wish i had a sorry like it's like a hair in my mouth i'm relied about hulk no i'm gonna
play the game cube hulk very very soon thank god for this infestation it's fucking perfect oh man
how could i let that happen i just let that happen that's unbelievable
tonight no not tonight some other day i'll miss that rock i have a bomb yeah oh wait what's that
what does this do your rage grows this is the samson thing this is every time i take a hit it
i get a higher damage right that's probably it's better not every time it's good for bad players
no it's not every time no keep the worm that's not good then that was what am i supposed to do
about that what the fuck come on an rng i should i should have an emote that's like rng or something
oh let's just kill it now go to the other room i need to um i need a key why did i use my only key
on the chest because i always think the chest is gonna have like three keys in it
i always completely overthink what could be in that come on no give me a key
quick jingle keys don't need money last chance is right here can't even go in the fucking item
room there's one more chance here uh he there's no keys in here all right that's guppy's tail
secret room is either i could be anywhere it could be up here it could be in that little
spot in the middle it could be down left and no bombs i have the explosive head right here
no i already tried this one or down here right here could be right there i'm gonna try it
there we go thanks for the key imagine being on the second floor and not being able to go in the
item room fuck that's so bad no all right let's go it's my fault i know and i'm taking i'm gonna
take the blame for it but it still hurts let's get it pulls his mouth back right and he goes
i'm waiting for him do it if you get up close you try to cheese it he rips to the left all right
this is a pretty good start this is toothpicks tears up shot speed up this is what this is what
we needed in the very beginning let's go in here i don't know what that is but it looks new and
cool but i can't get it i can't afford it what does that do i need to see i just want to know
what it does what does this look like oh what's it called oculus rift fire tears now have a chance
to summon a rift when they land on the ground the spawned rift sucks in enemies projectiles
and pickups and deals damage to enemies caught inside that sounds so much fun but i can't touch
it it sucks it's not good item suck suck suck oh does it oh okay well just it's stuck what's the
left one that's the contract right contract from below doubles your pickup drops including chests
soul hearts and other consumables which spawn at the end of a room but i'll only have one heart
but i'll get soul hearts i know i'm an idiot whatever run over as long as i can not get a hit
well this is excel we got two item rooms here i need keys you got a lot of health man how much
else do you have let me let me get the last hits on these guys stop stop oh nice okay worth it so
far no key though oh that's impossible now i'm afraid to do anything because i have one heart
when i play the i need i this is why i used to play with uh with magdalene there we go thank you
it's because she has four fucking heart that's a noob character yeah that's whatever that's fine
this is really great though look at all this money all right i need the item room watch it excuse me
items see those gold chests you either get screwed or you don't keep generating bugs yeah those are
the two options yeah i know a little hunt this kind of follows me around what does he do a little
friend i usually don't like getting the familiars because i feel like they just kind of randomly
will do interesting the rock huh is there a rock the familiars just kind of randomly will do
something good randomly down all right here all right use bob's brain damn it really ah
yeah this is going pretty well just don't die i need health and i need another item step on the
spikes not me you not me stop saying me okay i got lots of money so i'm just gonna take the
soul heart this active sucks though doesn't it i mean it's better than what i have he was a fool
great give me another one high priestess come on he's a boss so bad he's very generous all of my
money take it all take all of it all right stop making this is not supposed to be comedy stream
jesus all right i have more money that uh all right we're good okay there's another item room
go get the pill it goes five dollars at least you got you you got your five dollar fart okay
this little guy is kind of good he just turns away an enemy that's kind of good it's not bad
it works out pretty well what's replacing wink um uh sink i there's a cam that's going to be
connected to my sink and i turn the camera on and like turn the water on why would i do that
that'd be horrible what a waste of water black bean toot on touch black bean upon taking damage
isaac will fart causing all enemies in close proximity to be poisoned bad that doesn't help
me at all close this lagging game thing okay art and scream well there's the two item rooms
just go fight the boss i have plenty of bombs and yeah let's just fight it the dragon another um
don't answer that that's not too bad are we got yes since all damage and range up now we got
seven fucking damage yes this is where we needed to be last time and another familiar right little
steven psychic friend there's the stars that's the item room right i'm gonna explore a little
bit more because why not i just i'm gonna be able to kill things pretty quickly this is an
opportunity for keys all i want hell's good wonder what they are we'll find out when i instantly take
break no keys lots of bombs lots of bombs is my opportunity to get two free
i need these okay we're fine but don't explode them wait fine oh god what do you seem to
forward that's it okay we're fine we're fine okay we're fine we're fine everything okay yep
wait are we gonna have a moment where everything oh everything everything everything all right in
there uh wait the tower another great one uh this just puts bombs in the room when you like get
really mad at a game or something and you're like fuck and you hear like through the door
everything okay in there and you're like shit somebody heard that uh i'm just like watching tv
and laughing at it and somebody's on the phone with me what the fuck this finally bob's brain
this item is i hate this item why do they even pick it up this item sucks this is the
run ending item it's gonna blow me up i don't why i just i saw it i picked it up then i was
this so it's so bad the run is now over i know what have i done uh what am i whatever it's still
possible it's fine you can win with anything i just need hearts what is this one priestess yeah
i can't believe this dying to bob's brain wheel if you don't know what bob's brain does that
i have no control over it it could just blow up in front of me and it's not good use the card use
the card use the card it just takes me to the item room well there's dad's key opens all doors
now does this open all doors on the whole floor or only in the room you're in this is the whole
floor just the room just the room you're in okay although i want to get i want to get another
card from here let's speed down but keep dad's keep a mega satan i don't think i have that
unlocked yet god damn it i knew it was gonna fucking happen there's nothing i could do i had
to do it got a secret though this is gonna kill me and this is it why did i pick up bob's brain
you have to be so hyper aware of every shot when it's active uh don't open that i can open it free
poison two it's actually kind of bad is the stars again all right well just take the two hearts
what am i gonna use it for i have the stars now let's go get dad's key let's go open the door
take dad's car not very good selection but whatever now i'm keeping the money
just quick jingle the keys wait what is that how do i get that i have an idea i can get it if i go
really quick ready bob's brain's gonna kill me fucking boss brain i can't do it i can't fire
reap creep what does reap creep it's a new boss i don't know what this thing is
does it shoot fire in his mouth jesus dude that paceman you don't know what the fucking enemy does
where do i go i'm dead hey what happened did i the he spit spiders and the puffs brain
fuck it's okay it's okay that wasn't even a grand slam that wasn't a grand slam that was i i threw
pitch and the the ball was hitting the line drive and it came back it hit me in the chest
all right what that was not a grand slam he can't even reach mom yeah i just i just got to satan
which i know that's like wow oh you got to satan oh come on i just got there with a shit build by
the way what can you hear i'm almost crying what is this book of despair temporary tears up
i need my cheat sheet for this book of despair this is anti-birth upon use gives you a large
tears up for the rest of the room oh that's actually pretty good so that's it that's it
this is really good all right don't fuck it up don't pick up bob's brain come here you little
shit all right oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fine
when you that sucks when you get in a serious scenario like this oh come on no let's do this
spider web right here okay okay jeremy you don't have to die from the fire i can't move these over
you can't push these just run across i know but i wanted the coins that could have been in them
i'm a greedy fuck now let's kill this guy gurgling that's a shitload of tears up but one of you die
i almost baited me into that one oh man this is too this is hp up tears up and shot speed down
this is the thing i was taught technically i'm already at what out oh let's see so it was set
and then i know what will happen is this will bring me down to four okay i get it all right
well let's do the other room down down right i need a bomber key or something i need just a rock
well i can't blow it up until i get a bomb that's what i'm trying to do i'm trying to get a bomb
trying to get open the doors got a key oh i need like another coffee or something
somebody else i get tired i want like a coffee or something i'm gonna have to get some of my
cold brew downstairs right damn it that's the crutch item but i kind of want it i'm just gonna
use it once this thing's so much better it's so much better i know i need it but this is much
better this is so much more damage no i got three hearts i'm fine cat puke that was a cat you use
key on door use key on door no we missed a bomb first room no i need the health do i do the curse
room what do you think i never go in the curse room and this is why i don't go in the curse room
all i did here was just delete a full heart for no reason because i just don't it's too much it's
too it's too unlucky guys i already take every pill every single time you want to go in every
curse room this is bad news i think i got that one coin hog it's worth it one doge coin that's
it's not even funny but it is why is that funny it is all right let's go to the keynote i mean if
i had like a million dollars right now i would just keep having like halving halving halving
halving my tier delay until it was like 0.2 he's malding where do you get that idea there's a hard
cap of five tiers well although technically true you can go under the cap if you have things that
half your tier delay even if you have a tier delay item it'll work that is that is actually
she's called me a nerd for knowing that all right okay well how you want to respond to that one
i should what should i say no i'm not go in curse room if i have extra health to work with i will
i don't uh i'm not gonna do this either if i had like four or five full hearts i'd probably do this
and you need like a i'm not doing it use door on key what are you talking about get rid of the
carters everyone's got a wedgie i actually kind of do that i i do actually it's been bothering
me for like the last 15 straight minutes so the person's not wrong what's this brain worm
ding brain worm let's look it up brain worm mist tears will redirect themselves and travel
sideways towards enemies holy shit this is unbelievably good that's very very good the
amount of times that you miss by one or two pixels in this game is that corrected completely this is
awesome well maybe not quite that kind of wow this is great okay now all i need is a shit load
of tears up and like plus 10 damage and 10 more hearts and i should i'll beat the game seeing the
beam is like i'm about to hold r it's just but it's just such a waste of an item oh she's gonna
be looking to do sad face the bean he doesn't like to be no nobody does nobody thinks that item is
any good gemini look at that tier corrector working flawlessly the strategy with this guys
don't spam like i know what the fuck i'm even talking about don't listen to a word i say
this is a fun game though this is another tears up item tears up and shot speed up so this item
does this book become useless pretty good for a devil room i'll be honest all right uh uh triple
x jossi i go just gave seven community subs thanks a lot triple x why are pills so bad they
kind of just are you can get extra luck doesn't kane bike if i have the luck foot doesn't that
make pills better doesn't kane doesn't know doesn't mean that no i'm not in this one only in the
flashed one now coffee what do i get coffee from so i gotta get rid of this book because the book is
not gonna do anything anymore it does not actually change the delay it just tears up keep the book
it's not gonna do anything though is it what a coffee maker in your study
but you got the quotes right but you got the word wrong it's office my office
coffee in quotes why oh this is a tricky little room all right we need to be an experiment here
comes an experiment doesn't do anything anymore that's kind of sucks what you it's not having
the delay oh that's kind of annoying well now i know i need to do active it should add delay
shoelaces what why'd you write that why'd you highlight that you just you mean you're making
fun of me that's supposed to be like a joke making fun of me or something what's that mean why is
he writing right that thinks he's fucking wicked funny no shoelaces you like fucking don't tie him
and you trip on him and shit because you're an idiot you don't know how to tie your shoes
fuck that guy you know what i mean like what the fuck and that person fucking shit for me and shit
velcro shoes don't knock velcro shoes because who cares what so sorry it'd be cool to wear
shoes that you don't have to worry about tying you just put them on and go why is that a problem
that's not even a problem that's a good thing i'm so fucking mad right now like what the fuck
shoelaces fucking idiot the fuck why'd you say that to me like whoa whoa experimental pill luck
up well my luck is zero no luck down well i gained the shot speed that i took from the other
pill what is this credit card what does the credit card do credit card removes the price tag from
all items in the current shop or devil deal making everything free so okay holy shit don't
accidentally press r1 but i want to go to the item room did i go in the item room yet credit card
that's awesome zero first yeah did you have to do this wait did i do the i don't remember
did i do i fucking hate the dumb question mark rooms hey jump you call yourself a germa 95 fan
well i'm that's me this worm is so good the worm this worm is so good this should be a pretty
clear victory into that bomb germa can we get some tips in this game well i knew that bomb was going
to kill all the enemies in the middle so i went to the guy in the top left bob's brain sick it
wants me to take it so bad okay everything in here is free what's that thing on the left
is it like a ring save it for the devil room hold on wait wait wait what's this ring what is that
thing the cheat sheet see if i can find it here it is mom's bracelet upon use so it's an active
mom's bracelet allows you to grab objects in the room and throw them damaging any enemies which
are hit pots rocks etc that's i mean cool but what's the charge on it i mean i have seven i
mean just just get it didn't buy it yeah like you do what you can do it every room use the credit
card i'm gonna use credit card on the devil deals could you forget about bob this bob kills me
every time i play yeah then my dude there might be an opportunity where there's three items in the
devil room i'm not getting bob's brain no that's an instant run ruiner there's a shit room imagine
i had bob's brain right there i know what would happen there's a tint of rock did rock re it did
rock re where right here nice thank you guys so much thank you thank you close that cheat
sheet so i don't get uh in-game video lag and now i gotta fight the boss i throw can i throw a
rocket how much damage does it do wait i'll try it here does this explode wait i can do more than
once in the same room this is actually pretty good this is really fun wait i can just pick up i can
pick the rocks up i can pick the tinted rocks up no bombs that's really good i didn't know that i
thought it was gonna be cool wait let's do this see nice all right let's let's go take the rock
you can't you can't take it with you all right where's this dumb boss room wait oh i don't want
that wait i can just do this forever i can break everything they could be like a am i ever gonna
catch a fucking break with the pill i've not got one good one never take pills no i take them i take
every single one you're not gonna stop me yeah you're not gonna stop me i'm gonna take every
single one all right let's go is this the third run uh yeah technically this is the third attempt
well i should have yeah oh come on something good please well at least i know what it does
all right where's the boss room down left i don't fucking remember can i break secret room doors
with this can i pick up tnt holy shit you can i pick up oh you can't pick up the metal block okay
he's gonna take 20 minutes every floor doing this i mean if i have an opportunity to get
pills then i'm gonna do it there's items in these things addicted that's full health
oh but the credit card alpha why is he doing this why is he doing this why is he doing this
why is he doing this blog blog blog blog let's do it the wretched easy man watch out the spiders
fighters first priority you didn't do the priority this worm is so awesome just correct
all right uh come on but anything besides the speed belt no devil room either well looks like
i'm gonna be holding this credit card forever go faster another why does it have to be like
imagine if i have fucking bob's brain oh that's good no okay i'm not gonna let that that guy just
got in my head he was like go faster i'm like okay fuck i've got better go i gotta go faster
all doors are now open for free need rocks he's playing mind games germa
bro just we're good all the way to the right my range is terrible wait i missed this game
yeah we were just we were talking about it the other day a week or two ago and it was just like
yeah i'm so i want to play it like it's been a while i like this game i can't get that
wait i've hit no you can't pick up spikes jesus i'm like opening all their doors from here yeah
this item is so much fun all right now give me all objects thrown plus 100 more damage anything
like that in the game oh no i need to use it can i put it down sorry uh-huh funny poopoo game
i don't know why i said that i'm just you it's so easy to manipulate me to do anything
still missing an item room which influencer influencer influencer you guys influence me more
than i influence you you know that right you guys have way more influence on things than i do and
say than i do to you it's free to open all right give me the steam sale no the steams
doesn't matter these coins don't even matter well they said i'm playing the casino wait does
go into the casino with my credit card make all the machines free no well i can sneak in
uh i can't even get that no i'm really excuse me what's this the shiny one now he don't push it
i know i'm doing i'm doing all right i don't want to push it oh come on what was that jump
bullshit no item room what you should say no i don't feel like having that be one of the
three times i say that word all year that full health uh is there a sacrifice room anywhere
no the words come moist hey wingman thanks for the five community subs wingman appreciate that
five subs thank you wingman uh where's the haven ribs it's so big i can't even it's too big i can't
even like see it i can't i where's the item room did i already go in it i don't remember
i wish i could see i was rushed in bed it was like the weird what's the sock do stay away from it
nothing wire i don't think you can do that ah damn it i hate those that panic when i see them
blow blow blow blow blow no no don't blow it up pick it up great all these doors open for free
uh this is full health clown poop is full health and i need it i'm not gonna blow it up though i'm
just gonna save it because i need it i'm gonna do everything else around it like i'm gonna
fucking remember where this from is the mulligan they grow inside mulligan is an amazing item
mulligan as a isaac has a one sixth chance to spawn a blue fly when one of his tears hits an enemy
picking up this item as well as two other fly type items will allow you to transform into the
load of the flies wait this is a one at a sixth chance on any hitting any enemy i need a ton of
tears up then that's awesome that's really good okay so just don't fuck it up now i need the boss
room rock get soy milk that would be amazing i've been on this floor for an hour i know it's because
i'm picking up every rock and throwing it into the wall i'm sorry just wait till you don't watch me
play luigi's mansion is that boss room yes the secret room i'm not gonna be able to do that
all right here we go it's also full health right here too chad well guaranteed to get chad right
you see chad that means you get chad those things are just fun like crazy huh need a ton more tears
up though give me something crazy some tears up item devil rum uh i can't really take anything
eleven germa just says things and expects us to understand that room very bad very bad room
very bad room very very bad zero percent i have to i gotta like kill somebody oh fuck
please do well this does so much damage just throw rocks at him throw skulls at him we're
gonna be here for a little while we're gonna be here for like at least 20 minutes oh okay we're
good keep going whoa what's that card against humanity wait this i know what this does i know
what this does it fills the whole room with shit okay well we're gonna do that in the big room
all right hold on to that we're gonna do it in the huge room okay that's fine stars uh there's so
many all right hold on we're gonna be take this slow i'm gonna put my item stash over here come
on nothing really here we go what is it strength fuck so many good things to hold speed run opposite
but look at all these items wheel of fortune okay cool now throw a rock at the machine
i don't have all day well i do so i'm gonna do it what do you want me to tell you okay that's it
no okay okay okay okay come on all right whatever credit card is gonna be over here
and then uh all right i gotta think of a good strategy so this is to go we're gonna use this
right now we're gonna go to the item room for free all right robo baby robo baby is pretty good
you're fucking using tears i'm better with the rock throwing than i am with actually shooting
tears in the game so why would i use them okay uh we're gonna make our way up there where we
had long room just tend to drop yep um yep that's damage up oh yeah yep oh oh yeah i didn't even see
it not a great room to be in but it's okay not a great room very very very tricky very difficult
hard video game stop fuck you right what am i thinking wait don't do that i need it what was
it a tinted that tinted rock okay hold on we're good oh boy just stay back here don't let anybody
get near you robo baby can handle the rest of this what whoa got a card the world i can see all the
everything it's a double i'm amped the fuck up right now like i gotta calm down i'm amped the
fuck up he's popping off any other skulls or anything in here no i'm gonna go to the right
to get the their item room uh-huh joe joe uh-huh wait what's going on in chat here what are you guys
doing why is everybody freaking out in the chat room ooh vision oh i can't hold this till the
next room though i gotta bring the credit card although i might be able to use the credit card
at the devil room if we get one whatever we have constant conflict where's he oh fuck where's he i
don't know where he is where is he where is he where is he spawn already come on where is he
oh shit scary stuff a big room are you making a joe joe reference no i missed the rock unbelievable
no i'm not making a joe joe reference oh fuck you jeremy what have i done i can still get it
i think i can with the bomb i might be able to get it with the bomb all right can i blow that
across i can't what i might be able to pixel touch it hold on i blow it oops wrong button
it would tell joker what's joker do does it just take just takes you to the devil room
should i not use this though if i use this i don't have the credit card
oh boy i don't have the credit card just use and leave no if i use and leave won't the door close
i don't think this is even worth using the credit card on the goat head maybe so i can get more
options i'm not getting both i'm not getting both i don't know i'm gonna i know i'm not getting both
i'm not getting both that's too many hearts two fucking hearts you think i'm capable of beating
like mega satan with the shit uh i think it's another familiar all right sticky friend little
gish boom power just use it just that skips the thing that i was gonna do okay i guess somebody
random items all over the place damn it this is just too much to think about okay let's
should i go uh use the poop card in a in the big room i know i know i know i know i know
yeah i'll do that right now while i'm thinking about it i want to do i want to do it in a huge
room one that's very very like this is a lot of space in here any rocks to throw come on spawn
spawn but get him robo baby i don't even want to walk over there card against humanity
we're gonna be here for a while a long time robo baby can clear whole lanes holy shit wait a minute
all right we're looking for the golden poop thing whatever it is you can just clear an entire lane
that's a weird hitbox nice this is ridiculous i'm gonna have a lot of money this one right here
up a little higher good look at this one good this one good this one okay good this is really
worth doing grandma i'm trying to eat pudding oh there it is shit okay we're good come on yes
oh it's glorious it's absolutely glorious yes oh it's so good why did this not spawn earlier
okay i'm gonna have 100 coins what am i what do i spend these every poop gone okay 76 77 78
max out coins oh i missed a couple it's all right no it doesn't matter at this point look at me
okay now that's done i feel like i'm doing chores okay now what's next on the list
this is what i'm going to use to kill the boss and then all right cool next keys he still hasn't
left chibi robo what i mean left chibi robo let's go to the store that's next on the list
idiot there's a left poop oh i thought i moved out of the way the trinket the trinket the trinket
the trinket please you left the poop please please please left big poop please the trinket
please what do you want me to get get the poop why big poop poop on table what are you talking
about there's no i don't have any more poops to clear blind fuck what are you what are you guys
talking about you dropped the poop i don't want the petrified poo how what are you talking about
i don't want it i didn't pick it up because i don't want the damn thing oh shit this is going to get
ugly what the fuck we stopped doing that i'm gonna go fast huh what was that um how the
fuck do i get by this i guess okay don't be greedy all right oh that's uh this is this is
pay to win right don't you just press it and you just fucking kill every enemy it's it's bad it's
useless is it it does no damage trash i have so many coins though yeah it's good but not throw
rock good i don't want to buy any of this stuff yeah i'm not getting rid of this this thing is so
fun it's it's so good okay so now we go down right down right down right down down oh now we go down
down down right down down down down down down right there's a super secret room down right
ah bad place to start in this room bad placement no secret tinted i know what to do here oh my god
that's okay i almost blew that nice this is shot speed down i found pills take the fucking thing
okay and then two strengths double strength all right well i can use them each boss that'll work
out i got baited the last time doing this how would i throw it over there come on baby get them
why is it not firing okay double boss time we do strength go get strength strength don't worry i'm
gonna get the credit card i will oh no oh no no no not this guy not this guy right i'm okay it's
not even a problem it's not even job speed up strength again all right i gotta go get the
credit card get credit card now get credit card now get credit card now die that was so whiny
robo baby get him all right where's the credit card down over here okay there's a credit card
here but hold on a second will this show the super secret room it will and we're getting
past the rock monster all right fucking delete that person increase the game audio a little bit
was it is it is it too low but i increase it wait what's with this what's with the spam
no more spamming no more spamming are you gonna get me angry no more spamming or i'm gonna get
angry don't i'm not gonna read that i'm not gonna read it you're making me angry die already super
secret room nice here we go one two three one two three go open ah oh yeah this is the same
nipple deal it's the same one we can get the polaroid here we go
stand in front of him so he doesn't throw it into the spikes there it is portable slot gamble 24
7 i never have to leave oh they got me locked in with the spikes what was that oh okay slow down
slow down let me collect this stuff and look at it health up oh fuck yeah range down i almost just
said fuck yeah hit that holy shit are you kidding me come on okay that's fine oh my god another one
this is great i have so much money what is it what is this one range down fuck i don't want that i
want you guys to throw items he's a high roller well i gotta use the money somewhere that sounded
really bad i mean like in the game shit all right you get one bad roll it's okay no no no no no no
yeah all right too much stuff this is full health drop speed down i have 19 more coins holy shit
oh i thought that was i thought that was a help up there's help up all right this is if i don't be
like if i don't beat satan after this you're gonna be shitting me you know what i mean like i
why would i not pyramid the pill shots beat up tears down sorry another one no okay that's
energy choke guaranteed not possible all right all my money's gone that was fun okay now i have to um
well i gotta get all this shit out of the way so was this one full health idiot no i won't even
give me the credit card no i don't i'm there's so many things on the ground i swear to god i
didn't mean to fucking do that whatever i got like four health from this who cares i'm going
i'm just leave the fucking room with shit on the ground just hold on i can't can i know why why do
i not know what that is why do i not know what that is you're taking full damage remember oh
that's right that's true forgot about that actually forgot about that damn it can't get over there
whoa they blow up the joker but he's it but i can't use the credit card though
wait don't do it yet wait you already you already have it guaranteed that's true okay let's go use
it on the next floor don't get me out of there yeah i have the goat head i didn't need to do that
get all these babies wait actually i'm gonna i'm gonna do this sacrifice room i have like
five full heals i have like i have like a full heal i can just go walk on it like 10 times
what do you mean it's not worth it why wouldn't that be worth it i didn't even know that was behind
me i'm gonna go do it i'm going to do it what's the point what what what what's the worst that
could happen i have i have two full heals okay go heal okay give me the full heal where is it
full health there we go actually i don't think i've ever done this before what happens if you do this
like 50 times wrong fucking door idiot i'm not sure i've ever had an opportunity in all the
hours i played this game to actually do this you have to get something good for doing this right
get lots of items psycho you don't know don't do it more than 12 times how many times have i
done it so far what the fuck what what bullshit you're throwing i don't even know what that
fucking thing does after that much okay we're good we have health i need the credit card back
keep going ha ha ha ha ha ha ha keep going ha ha ha ha keep going ha ha ha ha well if you tell me
to keep going and then you write ha ha ha in all capitals i'm probably not going to do it anymore
riot snid look at all good this is going this is the daddy's long legs oh really nothing to
throw in this room that sucks just hit me all right what is it lunch hp up good and come on
well this sucks oh and it's crampus's head i mean the item is good but it takes too long to charge
and it's really is it really that i mean it's all right use the joker card now it's not rock
throw good if we're at the end of the game right now so i is rock throw even we've been capable of
using rock throw anymore all right now use the joker card right no that just brings me here
what if i can't even next but what about the credit card why would i i need the credit card
sacrifice one more and then use the joker card immediately why no shops the credit card but
what about the devil run tat is fucking crazy if i bring this down there and i get a devil deal
after killing uh mom and i mean i get a guaranteed devil room but i can use it there
i'm keeping the credit card there's no items there credit card is useless what you have seven hearts
yeah i need them all you'll never know what happens take credit card dude you can't be
this stupid what are you talking about i have the goats head on i have one more floor to do after
this two more actually right there how are they no more devil deals i have to kill them it lives
and then i have to go to hell that i can't get a devil deal room with it lives what are you talking
about i'm just gonna i know that's what i'm i know what to do you can you can you can i know
why is everybody freaking out about this oh i know why everyone's doing this because there is there
are no items in that room it's a devil room but it just is it's just a trap door to hell
right so i'm effectively i'm going to skip it live but don't i want the item no i'm gone i'm
not doing the sacrifice i don't know what it does i don't know if i step on that one more time it
might instantly kill me all right so i'm gonna use the joker and cool whatever happened to this
no item i'm not taking this holy shit okay now it sucks him in that's cool okay just kill this
guy immediately oh luck down that's not an oh that's a no i saw a dollar i saw a dollar minus
two luck okay this item was not worth two hearts at all it's just like this i guess mediocre as
you could possibly get i gave up getting hit two times to get the the fun rift item that doesn't
even do anything by the way no rocks on this whole level what is that chewed pen what is it
chewed pen do look at it up tears have a chance to slow enemies that's it um is that oh that's it
that's actually but look at my hell no that's not worth it because look at the my luck is terrible
oh i can throw this nice i think i kept that rock not rock you know what i'm saying the throwing
ability oh fuck oh it's not good i think there's hearts everywhere i think i have little chad with
me can't throw that poop it hurts if you touch it can't believe i traded two fucking heart
containers with this this is gonna end up killing me i know it fucking bob's brain again he got it
i have plenty of hearts 28 keys i need a key guy what the fuck was that hold on is that gonna skip
the floor or is that some of those trap doors is that gonna so aren't some of the yeah some
of you can get items for some of them right top left it's a fog moment the hell is in here
isn't usually an item right here where's the credit card where's the fucking credit card
why do i don't have the credit card no what oh are you kidding me no where's my card no i swear
to god i have a credit card out but i can pay for this these items are all bad yeah they actually
kind of yeah they are makes me upset that i can't have them for free right i can just skip this
whole thing i want to fight it lives to get the item get the bible and just kill satan immediately
that's true i could do that let's do it wait that doesn't kill satan immediately does it
oh shit no oh i thought i thought it does it oh no
now you're throwing no but i'm i'm not throwing you're throwing me does this do anything else
does it give you like a heart or something i fucking can't believe i just wasted that
i'm gonna stop listening to you guys you guys are always out to get me how i you're out to get me
no one can throw you without the bracelet pretty good all right whatever let's go
bad damage still whoa that's oh that's this thing sucks this is making it a way harder game
oh no get the fuck away from me oh i'm wondering what's in the devil dude because there is no
there's no what's what what about permanent health loss let's go bible instantly kills it lives
all right i gotta kill who am i going for it doesn't really matter does it doesn't matter
i'm going up down down down down i'm going up okay get away from me the box within a box and then
electric penny wealth of power i think i know the worms better tell me if you find a tinted rock
that just makes it i can charge right i'm just i'm making this game so much harder with that's
gonna kill me to take the cool item when i fight satan it's gonna scramble all of his projectiles
and i'm gonna die and i'm gonna die satan again the second time this is gonna be a disaster oh
isaac even worse isaac has more projectiles isaac has like three times as many projectiles
this is gonna be a fucking disaster oops oh you're killing me here with this forget about the
fucking rocks man you gotta i gotta kill the boss where is he flying around where is he
let's talk him in that hurt me does it hurt all this money seriously come on rock rock you missed
a rock i missed a rock where actually i gotta break i gotta break all these sorry i have to
all right where's this where's this tinted rock you guys are talking about it's up oh we lied okay
cool good to know thanks we lied smiley face i hate the little weasel things this little fucking
weasel eyes the moon that's the secret room might as well just do it and that's odd mushroom
this is what does this one do this one's damage up oh yeah good good okay and i got another heart
container so that's good this this is probably going to be fine use bracelet on isaac and throw
him i can't do that man i can't do that you can you don't know that i'll take contact damage if
i touch him you can and you will oh sorry wait was that was that a oh you can and you will
is that what you're doing don't touch that that's what they were doing i think
oh fuck never seen these enemies i've seen these guys about those ones this mod is weird it adds
a bunch of weird enemies into the rock this looks in a rock here so oh come on man what's this do
you pick up items that you pick up coins it makes you fart right swallowed penny what does it do
getting hit makes you drop though money i need to spend this somewhere i need a donation machine
or something drops coins when you take damage oh okay chocolate bar mysterious candy oh i think
this thing sucks yeah i think sucks right oh i got saved all right anybody any tinder rocks
not that i can see i don't think so they have like a little x on it right take out the ads please
i hate the fucking weasels all right there we go full health uh tons of money let's kill isaac
i'm not picking him up don't even say it don't please don't do the thing it's gonna do it
don't move we're good i hate that the rip makes it easy no the rip is written off for me
i'd rather just dodge them than have to worry about them spinning around in random circles
because after the rift is over it fucking throws like that see i thought that was a portal for a
second pick him up for the good ending all right did we go we go further down or is that i haven't
beat the game enough times right now we go further right we're in the chest look at all this stuff
okay we have magnetic tears um poison tears fortune cookie reusable fortunes may your troubles be
many and then we have the original game from the first game back in 2011 and i'm surprised they
haven't deleted it yet because it is so bad that it's not even worth picking this up i can't pick
up chests there's the mega satan door but obviously we're not doing that we're gonna go kill
question mark question mark question mark right if i can even get to it there's really bad items in
those chest rooms this is terrible what's that epic hack explosive what have i done
wait no this is good isn't it this is good it's gonna kill me it's this is just bob's brain but
i can do it every one second this is bob's brain you do it every one second i think i might ruin
the whole run oh my god wait they say it's they suck they suck to enemies that's insane
i still have the worm magnetic tears epic hack and the worm holy shit that was insane
who's this guy actually not that bad oh and there's another buddy little chubby look we've got the
whole wizard of oz here there's five people in wizard of oz yeah there's four people and a dog
shit dude that's so weird it just goes in a random direction
i don't know where it's gonna go
you're the dog oh yeah i kind of am i have like the head right all right any health homing homing
crit rocket yes watch out it's gonna get it's gonna suck on one of those things i just got
freaked out because i thought come on hearts oh god great i have extra health that's actually why
why am i upset about that that's good god damn it what why did that just suck to me
what this thing man no what jim and i can join the stars are calling what freaking me out ways
holy shit man seriously i need health come on chad drop some more of these
what just hit me what what just fucking hit me all right i need this i'm taking this from now on
it's too many people on the screen okay i need this because it could drop um
forget about the rocks there are no rocks to throw in this one yeah i'm getting so
range on these bad two all right give me some hearts i gotta go in every single room without
finding the fucking boss blind blind what do you mean blind what's what's going on the icon is
there what do you what you missed a rock wait what's going on oh shit that was bad thank you
finally another one yes good you missed a wink oh sorry how many motherfuckers are in here
oh it's the it's the whole wizard of oz i use that joke already it's the every deadly sin
i just used that double minus two don't touch anything just let them let him kill him okay
let's go in every single fucking room before finding the boss that would be really really swell
all right i'm gonna take this i'll take it i'll use it oh i can't even use it
let's kill both of your friends you man why can i fire something good i priest this worst i'm going
up save it for the boss no i can't wait just i'm gonna i'll kill it with the feather it's so stupid
all right we got full health i can find the secret room too triple low keys uh secret room just maybe
up here no i have a headache uh maybe take a Tylenol tears up plus knockback i'm getting
every single one of those all right we gotta check the secret room here no no what's up i
want to find the secret room that's good that's okay i got i get how's that okay uh there we go
uh nope nope nope do we really care about the secret room is it really i really even give a shit
right now what could be possibly in here that i would want i don't think i can find very much
that i would care about where is it hey guys um can i overcharge this like a hundred times what
just hurt me i can't i can only do this twice it needs blood that doesn't deal damage well okay
so i have two go get the book bye oh i don't need the book do i need the book i don't need
guys i keep teleporting shit around stop stop what the fuck oh my god dude this thing will be
double charged though right book is gone no it's not spreader oh i see what you mean just keep
this again i'm gonna pour the fuck out of a lot of you open this is gonna be very very boring here
we go i do i really need this much of a crutch i don't think i do don't pick these up unless i
get hit this is absolutely thrilling this boss is really easy yeah but i also want to prevent
me just absolutely embarrassing the shit out of myself and not completing even one like hard mode
oh like just typical run or the binding of isaac on my stream that would just be that would be a
catastrophe you know i'm saying i know i'm capable of doing it i play this game a lot but
i got you got i gotta have like a security here because i know that all it takes is one like oh
my god oh my god oh no no no you've heard it 100 times before it's happened 100 times
all right that's good enough that's literally i can't i cannot die i can't die here so i cannot
lose one more time okay that's that's it let's go i cannot lose it's impossible to lose this
one more okay i'm done i want the uh i want to beat the guy with the feather thing he's gonna
start throwing now it would be so dumb if i would have like throw for to make somebody laugh once
wait i want to fill this up double it's like maybe 10 of you in chat that would think that was funny
and the rest you would be like dude you just like wasted so much fucking time like what are you
doing man all right i'm ready i'm ready to i'm ready to beat this guy in probably less than
10 seconds i'm gonna win in probably five to 10 seconds spam it hey look at that what was it 12
seconds hey i completed one run of binding of isaac on the stream let's do it again right at the
anti-birth path what's the specific um shit you have to do you go to do the anti-birth stuff
where do i go to do anti-birth the anti-birth floor do you samson i love sam look it up on your
cheater app why is it an app uh unlock by having 12 soul hearts and then just lock
do eden powered the eden's just like a eden's just free it's free you get you get like two
like items for free so i have what do i have i don't know what these are what's that look it up
the weird like mouth dripping uh where is it the anti-birth there it is rotten tomato tears have a
chance to mark enemies marked enemies will be attacked by other enemies i'll try it working
penis map yeah sure funny like no not even nothing close not even remotely close what is wrong with
you he hates us more more more take it i don't care what it is eat it don't even open wait this
two locked doors though one of these is like a book room or something right well that's not
correct what's out the soap what's this what's the pink soap what's pink soap do rock throw
i don't have enough to get rock throw again we've already done rock throw i don't want to do rock
for another one all right what's this no that sucks mass room damage i mean this is the only
one to take is it better than having a slot machine though they both pretty terrible look up how to do
the anti-birth path okay fine okay cheating well i kind of want to know chapters uh any
birth introduces four new chapters after unlocking a secret exit locked doors to the new chapters will
appeal appear upon defeating bosses in the first three chapters i don't think i've unlocked it yet
how do you unlock a secret exit it's cheating yeah of course i defeat the three new bosses on
the new floors i have to just beat all the bosses yeah i have to be the new people need to beat
reprieve okay cool did we unlock the negative first yeah i had to pull like my rebirth file
i just haven't played a long time i've uninstalled this game like a thousand times over the years
and i just don't have the files for any of it crystal ball is pretty good too all right i'm
gonna kill the boss with the what's it the necronomicon then i'll take first of all this
ball's good i'm gonna remember i'm gonna show you the whole world and give you like a card
pretty good all right let's go come on stro and then i take the first of all and don't use it
i'm gonna use it immediately on the next floor yeah yeah yeah yeah taking forever to kill anything
did my voice change terrible item uh what do you mean my voice what's what's going on
why people keep saying that my voice is like high and robotic i mean it will be right now
right now if i do this like this is like this is okay okay okay but it shouldn't be now filters
off look at that shit um let's do the other room he's immersive and i'm getting pretty immersed
in the game right now the game is just fun it's just fun to throw a hundred dice in the air and
look at them all that's really what this game is just throw a hundred dice in the air and count
how many sixes you have and then do it again just do that irl that would be so bad that would be so
bad this thing is so so so key dice throwing stream what if i did that one day i just got like
30 dice and i just was making random bets with you guys rose repeat what's this okay if i'm
gonna throw dice in the air and if it's anywhere between 20 and 50 then i win and if it's anything
else you win shit i don't have any keys deal that would be such a pain in the ass
i would have to throw a bunch of dice in the air and then suck them all up in a vacuum it
would be impossible eight that's not blowing you up why how is that possible are you gonna count
them i don't just they need to be like in a pub all right yes right oh my god i don't know i'm
trying to find ways to make that not painful who secret thank god all right i'm going for it i'm
going for it i'm going i know people are gonna be like don't do it i'm going for it i'm gonna i'm
gonna get this first yep thank you yeah such as you make a wish keep away platinum bar what's that
iron bar concussive tier okay i'm gonna do a lot of behavior or whatever you turn the stream on
emotionless without you know what this time turn whatever i don't even know what the fuck you're
even saying uh here comes the r9k let's trigger the r9k turn it on hey germa hey germa just want
to paste paste paste paste that's all i see you guys do realize that right anytime there's a huge
copy pasta that gets thrown here i just see hey germa hey germa hey germa hey germa hey germa
germa i don't actually i can't read what you're writing i see the first four words i hate these
are mistakes forever all right get the other guy in their little holes tend to rock in here somewhere
it might be help me please help me please no hey gamers yeah this is a gaming stream it's been a
while since i've played a video game and just tried to win figured you you would do you would
deserve it a little bit like i figured it like you you deserved a little bit of like just
gameplay streaming i got hit by that which is embarrassing good all right i'm not opening that
door because i might not find another key the whole fucking game anything else worth doing here
maybe to find another key probably yeah did he choke yeah i died too um i died to satan again
my game fucked up i think it's i don't know maybe the mod fucked up i got stuck in the
wall his shoe came down he crushed my head next to the wall and i couldn't fucking move that felt
good there we go oh then i turned the webcam on and i just swallowed a shoe hole take a room
secret super secret no what am i doing i already had that i don't open that door i want to save
keys let's go baby plum damn it it's not the one we wanted well i fucked that up it's the
reap creep is the one i have to kill right we'll see him next floor something good oh fuck i've
missed out sorry double room what's in it i've brimstone baby is very good but i can't take it
now i am gonna go open the this is something i can't no i don't want brother i don't want that
one i don't that's brother bobby right take them no i can't i can't i can't go in with three hearts
you're a coward take them both i'm not gonna have one two-spirit heart that's so bad you have the
crystal ball so if i don't have any health does this make any sense am i invincible
i can't can i do i just take i don't get it why is this working is this an anti-birth thing
all right okay what is that that there's no spirit hearts in here um all right i'm gonna what is
that thing that like i with my chi chi what is it it's like a weird like battery battery pack when
picked up this item fully charges your currently held active item and drops between two and four
battery pickups hold on so i can just i'm gonna go for it holy shit okay hold on what is this
it was it was what is it was it skips to the next floor well shit okay and i got brimstone baby
which is great it's a skip okay go use that in the in the trap room with the last battery
more batteries i only have four coins what use the ball no no i don't use the ball right now
because if i i want to use uh because this is when i go to the next area it'll show me everything
let's use the donate what are you talking about donation box you want to blow up the
donation box everyone was talking shit to me when i did that before look at how many shit
talkers now are telling me to blow up the donation box fool great let's get out of here it's good for
curse rooms yeah it's all right it's not great but it's not terrible see this is why i held it
because of that well take a run but this place is kind of small don't you have bullshit in here now
give me some good damage items and i'll be good to go look at that fucking look at demon baby
doing work over here brimstone baby doing fucking work give me a shit load of damage up and i'll be
happy the interrupt okay this just got real interesting this that's a fog moment right there
yes it is all right now give me tears up and damage up and then the game is completely actually
over here's up damage up and this thing is just in the bag completely don't you love when you
just get like a solid build in the first two floors and you just like nice feels pretty good
let's put down and let's go let's get piercing shots that'd be awesome come on shoot it shoot
it i please don't let me go up there fire rate up doesn't do anything with spread shot i mean i've
21 tears right now which that's really slow tears up items won't affect us yeah they will
why wouldn't it shitty although i could buy a battery okay here's the plan i'm gonna buy a
spirit heart and the battery after i do one more room give me a full stack of spirit hearts
ah shit i thought he was one of the uh i don't know what i'm saying i thought he's one of these
guys on the right here use it the joker the joker just use it let's go rock all right Krampus come
on really the head is good but it's just i wish it didn't have some i guess if it had a small
charge it'd be way overpowered you can kill some enemies instantly can you well couldn't you use
to do they patch it or something oh fuck oh ain't no getting away from this one very bad room very
bad room hp up luck down fuck yeah i'm not happy about luck but uh bad but no but now i don't have
to just have spirit hearts we have more than that now say bad rum five times fast bad brum bad brum
bad brum i don't understand take it again luck up shot speed down watch out for these stupid
fires they mess me up every time that's pretty much it did i miss anything battery but
hmm i need two more rooms calendarman boss will give you a you know what ronnie you are
fucking really smart this is true more free shit well it's not for free i earned it another one of
these what if i use this one and then use this one again you might get the seller is it wait
well is it gonna make something under the ground wait open both hold on all right how can i tell
how can you tell which one it is right ladder oh if there's a ladder all right what happens if i use
this in here i use it again what the fuck is this a walnut a walnut deo reroll enemies one charge is
reroll enemies i don't want that i guess you could bring that into the womb and chest and
calyrium land and use it and this bad i can reroll high tier enemies though what happens if i use
it was right now what happened this game break find out okay uh i don't want to go on that one
right if it spawns to the left you fuck do it do it do it don't that just goes to the do it
no i don't want to do that it'll be epic get boss item yeah i need to get the boss item i'm not just
gonna skip that you guys trying to ruin my run why are you trying to ruin my run we only spend
like 12 minutes per floor while i talk to you guys and don't play the game you want me to have to
restart all this again oops i forgot about uh hold on wait wait wait um we're good that thing's over
here what the fuck i'm playing the game with the demon baby i'm not even like playing with me
i'm trying to aim with the demon oh hp up here we go this run has just got so saved saved saved
saved all right now i'm gonna go in the secret tunnel waste of the joker no i'm not gonna go
this i'm gonna buy the battery see if you guys weren't here what would i do what would i do huh
wait i gotta go up i can't skip okay i'm not gonna use this yet until i get to the next floor
don't tell me to do things that are not smart here's a wacky challenge say i lied about eating
a shoe five times fast pretty wacky and judgment uh this spawns a little guy don't really want that
yet until i have some coins but we'll just hold on over let's go can you get like soy milk with
triple tears does that work i'm still alive you can oh that's so awesome uh this is worth doing
there might be a key in there might be two keys in here please come on yo this streamer's on
fucking frack shit i'm gonna start blowing these guys up they might drop coins or spiders either
one up a little up a little ah you panicky fuck great what a waste what are you guys doing you
can bomb into the rooms from the secret room oh yeah yes you can that's not a cool room
this room's stupid not stupid anymore okay save the keys somebody mentioned this and now we have
it spectral tears and well not piercing technically but you know here we go very good luigi what about
luigi what the fuck oh what the fuck man cheap that was fucking cheap almost haven't just killed
the boss excuse me out of the way please luigi what oh okay let's uh go to the item room first
will the job oh it's because the weegee board right okay i see where you guys are going to use
the ball i'm thinking about it if i can get a battery yeah fucking dude you're right never
mind you just charge it i just want to use judgment too okay open open open because i'll stop
shooting the weegee board game yeah what about it here comes the airplane what are you talking
about here comes the airplane why are you feeding a baby i don't get it open why jerma stop come on
hate fighting greed it's so i it's dumb i don't even have that many coins why is he spawning
greed is just it just takes a run shitty all right it's not let's oh really what am i gonna
have i don't i want to spend this money whatever is it money over here yeah he takes the red hearts
first yeah i don't even want to do it it's not even worth it use the crystal ball no no no i'm
saving until i go to the next realm you guys could probably hear the head tilt right there
the dog tilt thing the hell is this mom's pearl it eliminates purity what's this do mom's pearl
grants a secondary chance of any non-specific heart drop during turning into a soul heart
holy shit that's really good uh that this is unbelievable for what i have right now literally
cheating it's a bit please jerma it's awful no that means they can turn hearts into soul hearts
why wouldn't i want that that's all i need right now this dream would be funny if you didn't cheat
what how why would this dream be funny yeah true what what the fuck does that mean
oh true that makes no sense this this is not a comedy stream this is a gaming stream
oh you see the title this is not a comedy stream this is a gamer stream
fuck i i buy my testing for secret rooms i already had it all right let's let's kill the boss please
keep quickly come on spam it up good he's so good something something something something what's this
evil range and shot speed up yeah pretty bad i'm just a true no comedy gamer streamer who
played africa photo game for playstation 3 will you jera abundance what does jera do
a magician right what a waste jera is op well what does it do it doubles any items that are
in a room that's actually really good i should just use it right now use it right now i mean
that's like just free money no you're looking for cards it doubles chest items doesn't really
that's pretty cool all the way to the right okay out of here die please bomb items they suck
burning blast yeah well how do i get okay this is fine are you saying you can double
check so i can double it should i double a chest where were you when i wanted you before
okay hold on i double that fanny pack filled with goodies okay filled with goodies only pickups
and chests he actually took any back so what it's a free item why would you not pick up a free
passive item come on why twice in a row whatever yes what's wrong with cursed eye is the proc rate
just so stupidly low or something i don't get it magician again worthless i let them die on the
spikes why am i so afraid of this stand over here hey cursed eye and mark that work out pretty well
there's a tinted rock i'll get it where i see very good what a keen eye you have
heard keen the hell was all these little yeah that was kind of wild all right there's another
rock no webcam resident sleeper no there is no webcam sorry why there's no other rock here no
webcam resident sleeper i need to be able to smell his face i want to zoom in up his nose
reap creep here we go and this this will open up the next area geez these new bosses are
fucking hard a lot of health too what he just fire what the fuck was that what the how long
does he do this for oh die okay good more range up fucking useless take the no that one was
what's the pause gonna do do i have another guppy item i mean that the one in the middle yes
the one in the middle yes absolutely because that's just i have permanent damage up right
take them both pick up the item is free anyways yeah wait hold on hold on what you fucking idiot
you just did this everyone told me to do this this is a smart idea did i just i just got pogged
what if i use this is it no there's nothing to use it on oh this is really great i need to buy
some i need i need a spirit heart but right now it pogged you moron sorry kid um okay you
fucked this one up fuck it ain't over yet it ain't over yet it ain't over yet come on spirit
heart in one of these yes all right now we use jara right now it ain't even over they all thought
it was over and please have this be balls of steel i hate this game is it should be no no one
should play it no one should buy this you should you should not play this look at the cards right
now i'm looking for balls of steel i'm looking for the uh what's the one that gives you i'm playing
it right now well if you want my seed there it is tears down so awful i need tears up otherwise
this is donezo okay not this is all right i do have permanent uh babalon whatever it is
i have what is a horror babalon right i have 6.34 damage permanently there's a rock i can't get to
it though i can't get that rock i'm sorry nice all right have it be the uh uh the the the
herophant don't worry he's a gamer god no it's a magician but that card responds like four times
this run come on please baby no i thought you got two spirit hearts for this card what the fuck
i replaced it with tears down probably not a great idea come on uh no thank god again just
used this dialogue for me watching a baseball game yeah you could just have it be just like
two balls three strikes nothing exciting even happening i expect to see it soon that's minus
two snow so i said sports sorry i said the word sport i said baseball okay this is a cart i'm
using now okay now we just need a shitload of we need spirit hearts what are the chances of
getting something like this twice in a row and like i don't think i've seen don't you dare pick
it up it's too much money i can't even spend it i need hearts i need hearts don't i need the mom's
oh so far okay this is good oh yeah yes what's that why's everyone blinking why's everyone
blinking it's a special heart uh what on earth is this okay don't pick up any more money
99 okay don't touch any more coins did i miss any you're you dumb ass what i don't know what
this fucking thing does okay i need a shop and it better not be agreed in there money money money
that's all you need all right but i also need to go in the secret room which is right here hopefully
i get it so i don't get laughed at i didn't i'm gonna get laughed at i need this is a maze okay
you picked up a coin i know i didn't mean to what do you want from me this is like a million dollars
on the ground i missed a poop whatever let me just do this first i have a lot of money
this is plug thank you okay what's the plug do or i'm just getting it charged with blood doesn't
matter just get them all okay forget about the bible just use the bible right now does it give
you anything charge every time you get hurt oh that's pretty good just donate money yeah okay
donate donate and then go collect all the money again hopefully doesn't uh thing 500 what do you
give 500 gives you flight yeah but i'd rather whatever use the bible to get through the rock
rock wait what rock i have too much money all right where was that rock what the hell is it
okay there it is can you believe that i've gone to zero hearts twice from having eight to ten
i've done this twice all right now that i was like i can buy so let's just go yeah i just gotta go i
have to leave i feel bad having all that money on the ground not being able to use it just use baby
but so i have i have to beat satan to get the negative right how that works shit why don't i
get this talk the chat if you want negativity not unlock well we're gonna have to keep going
this it was funny fight the hush you know i would love to but i don't think this game has enough
unlocks yet i want the secret room what is that it was not worth it die die die die die
key you're not doing good all right this is the i just burnt those coins i didn't i didn't even use
them and skip to a room why are you looking the other way oh it's gonna just stand still
stand it still is that a word could have just stood still stood still stood that's right good
still we just want to play tomorrow monster lab for the week sounds like a plan oh now hulk is
saved for a special occasion that's almost hurt my body doing that okay mama gurdy shit
whatever okay that was not very good got speed up the stars
you're gonna watch out for the collectibles yes oh thank god two of clubs who cares finally i can
go into the casino and spend all my money let's go it doesn't even matter to spam every machine
where's my heart where's my heart where are my hearts where's the fucking hearts
whatever the hearts where all my hearts what's going on it's oh i definitely have okay what the
fuck is going on how does it almost my pants no give me oh nice all right give me pretty fly
there it is i'll take it yep i'll have 79 points this sucked this sucked
just get it right because i'm wait what does it cover the bottom one first well they're all
bottom ones all of them are bottom ones first okay i have to get this where i fight mom i'm
not gonna take this and yeah not yet don't get it you'll you'll ruin uh babylon oh that's right
that is a very good point you couldn't hit it dude why did you get rid of the poop thing
i know you don't remind me so what we think a monster lab for the wee tomorrow
i think so no no i'm up look i can't play hope tomorrow why why why because i didn't buy it yet
okay i'm gonna be honest with you i'm not gonna lie to you guys i start lying to you guys you see
you guys just make fucking screen names that say that i lied about shit this is not actually too
bad this is pretty good actually all right uh i think everyone really doesn't matter what if
you don't if there's no more no doesn't this just do whore babylon where's this rock rock
where the hell did you even see that all right here we go i'm really i don't have i'm not seeing
enough damage i'm not seeing enough damage wait can i do this again no wait what is that no no no
no no no no all right what should i do what do i have what do i have to do i try to just kill
satan down satan down down you fool you've gotten it i gotta get my revenge that's not a whole lot
of hearts what the fuck hide back here jesus never scream if you see a tinted rock i really
i need to know this is a really bad place to fight this guy oh get the fuck away from me
rock hello hello wait you talking to me where right here bomb the fires oh that's right the
purple ones can give a uh spirit heart holy shit i almost got hit okay where is it if i want on
with that secret room no i don't yeah i do it would be something cool this is way too many rooms so
why would i do this what's happening um okay please don't do that again i only have one more
bomb 91 coins good thing i have all these coins somebody said really fun ed hold r to double
charge the item does that really work i should try it i can't believe i got fucking hit by that
i was too busy looking at chat to look at the guy that said that to laugh oh one bomb this sucks
and i can't even get it if i want it why i can't even bomb them okay at least i got one more
jesus let's go all right fucking kill this guy come on i've walked into it slow down all right
i'm good you beat the easiest boss i know it's really not that hard stupid i like how the cut
scene was drawn by an actual baby there it is okay here we go who do i want to do this with
samson okay so it's just it just appears randomly or what nice good start do i have to beat the in
a certain amount of time or is it just going to show up now just go i'm just too much to do
i'm gonna take the hit here yep good idea good call fast all right those of you that don't know
every time samson takes a hit you gain more damage and it lasts until the next floor he's so good
good start come on item what's the chili pepper bird's eye it burns wait what
was it randomly doing that whoa does this hurt me that's actually okay that's really cool i need
luck give me a shit load of luck with this that's really cool all right all right i'll take the hit
that's so much fucking damage i want i want the damage speedrun guys kill the boss let's go light
open what the hell is that is that it how do i go in there let's just open anything do i need a key
shit i need a key stay all right give me a key i got two more rooms to look in no nothing in here
great one more one more chance for a key i can't blow that rock up i know it's there
sorry reset no no these fire tiers are cool will it wait does it disappear forever or does will
it show up in the next all that wait is it only going to show up once it will be on the next floor
oh yeah that's fine now let's go it'll show up again yeah all right let's go first of the unknown
it didn't do anything i want to get smaller is it based on how much damage you have that's kind of
cool actually that's what it is that's really no it's not look at this broken code what the
hell happened here save the key i don't want to use it miss the rock well i well all right
it's not worth blowing this up to get in there all right yes it is
yeah not necessarily for a second i thought the fire attacked me i was like why is this an
anti-birth why is it coming out of the flame i was coming out of the camp fire thing this game really
is just so much fun you guys want to see isaac again i want to play isaac like i don't know like
once like once every week or two or something i'd play it like once in a while for a little while
this is like nothing going on but there's like nothing to do and i'm just like you know let's
just move to let's give it to isaac that's probably what's gonna happen all right i'll take that uh
this is technology yep technology is so good wait there's a there's a good one and there's a bad one
it's like technology this technology too which one's the bad one tech two is the bad one okay
i would love to go on one of these but i don't i can't yeah this one goes through people does
the other one go through people too like it just sucks on somebody yeah i have to keep this key
so let's go go to the monster oh he's easy oh i have an update for you guys about something
so the boston marathon got cancelled and those who that know the i was gonna do a charity stream
to uh sponsor one of my friends to run in the marathon so so everything everything's getting
um so that's not they're pushing that i think to later in the summer i think i have no idea
they're still not 100 clear on exactly what's happening but that rumble stream might not be
in the next like couple weeks we're all we were also thinking of maybe we would raise money first
and then hold on to it until it was ready to be you we're trying to figure out what to do
because we started planning a bunch of stuff around it all stats up nice perfect just hold
on to it that's kind of the idea we're just trying to figure out exactly what we want to do
uh one heart for a quarter no i'll take both these i fucking it's i'm so mad
all right okay bye all right we're fine take the cloak the robe no but i don't have enough
no no no no no i don't i don't want it jesus the robes no the robes there's too many hearts
too many hearts to do right now these buckets all right cool here we go anti-birth down poor
two he gives three black hearts but you know i'm gonna lose those all right we got all new
enemies i think is it a mirror or is that sorry hit me hit me hit me i want the damage
holy shit what are these whoa they flashy or something this is pretty cool um which one i
don't know what these what are these ones do what do they do is that lemonade in there what's the
peepee one the wasn't one that you go like you peepee all over the ground right in front of you
it's is it this one here hold on i i what i want to see what they do just take it take left take
left just take left all right that's a lot of this is getting pretty good this is going to be very
good look at his face look he's so happy look at that dps it's gonna spike in the ground
collectibles oh i don't have enough money to do anything here let's just move okay good what the
fuck hey speed up tinted rock hold on to your bombs oh oh why would i blow these up what would
that what what how would i release these just aim down here don't even move let them walk into it
um okay a lot of shit in there i think what's raining is it raining oh when you when you kill
them they exploded okay i see it was passage all right i'm looking for a ladder right rock rock
tint where i don't see one all right this technology combo is fucking crazy all right i think i'm good
i need two bombs i got two bombs save two bombs what is in here what's that indicator on the
mini map what does that mean well what's in here this it's a secret oh oh if i bomb that i get to
all right well i don't want to it's an invisible chest when the lightning flashes you'll see it
pretty cool oh shit all right how do i get it all right if i find another bomb let's go find one
this actually is really cool this is a cool addition how many new areas are actually in
any birth i don't even remember playing this maybe like once all right no it's not worth opening that
four oh that's cool no bombs oh well keep the hoof yeah isn't the cartridge doesn't
randomly make you um run around with the glowing face and you can not get hurt like hackman style
thing pain brain maker you don't stand a fucking chance you just got instantly killed that was a
cool boss is too bad we didn't even see it all right two bombs we go deeper this is a mod this
is the anti-birth mod and you will be pleased to know that the anti-birth mod is going to become
an official dlc to the game very soon in the next few months didn't know am i shooting more
i'm shooting faster why am i crazy or is this faster no am i losing my mind whoa what's that
why is this why are we not opening the door why is this a spider watching me i didn't see that oh
shit okay be careful that's a cool enemy all right i know that thing sucks but i don't even know
what this is knockout drops they pack a punch what is this doesn't work with technology no
that's sad yes it does it sure does oh look they're in donkey kong carts all right i'm gonna stop
paying attention to the cool stuff and play punch lasers yeah this is awesome little gold nuggets
oh shit i'm assuming they become hazards yeah that's so dumb actually very useful though
give me another hit i'll take another one okay 11.16 damage every quarter second this is insane
oh yeah the little minecarts are great and it does concussion damage too that's fantastic
that's crazy yep use the did i use the coin pick up the penny pick up that penny yeah i guess that
is pretty good with samson but i know them i was looking how slow i am yeah i actually it's
completely negligible what am i talking about please hams i don't want to go in the boss yet
i want to keep looking well whatever i need soul hearts uh i don't have any tinted rock two soul
hearts oh hey i thought that was the shit i only have one i need two it worked yeah it did work i
thought that was the damage rock thing should i open up should i buy one i think i'm gonna try
to buy i'm gonna buy one if it's available not available oh well that's kind of sad just don't
get hit do it after the boss you need it on the next floor not on this one oh okay just don't get
hit i see bomb the donation uh thing okay yeah it's not a bad idea i don't have any bomb donate
four coins please okay fine 500 all right let's see what it is i'm not gonna get hit by a boss
i've never seen great gideon look at this health bar oh i got hit i got hit i can't damage him
just kill the enemies i guess that's what you do watch these fires i'll step on one
what the fuck why is that frozen hamster hey that is okay um here's up i can't go any further than
that i'm at the top of the i don't think i can get any more spirit hearts unless there's uh
let's get huge bits 5 000 bits from volemy 50 dollars i need to hear delay yeah thanks for the
50 dollars volemy thank you for donating 500 bits to the shop jeremy we appreciate your support
well thanks for giving me 5 000 bits thanks for the 50 dollars that's a lot of fucking money
all right spirit hearts up at this floor okay i'll keep that in mind all right
hierophant let's get lucky right here hierophant i would just saved envy i kind of hurt my eyes
this is not what i need i can even see tinted rocks please explain everything uh was there a
rock oh all right i'm good i need bombs yeah i need a lot more than that come on spirit hearts
bombs there you go put a bomb oh what you turned us uh i just lost all the gains i just got that's
a all right no don't get the hearts till you beat the boss yeah i know i know i know i know still
need to get spirit hearts i do still need to get them skip leg day what the fuck all right i'm
gonna die down here i'm not careful i need health not just spirit hearts i need i need health
does this work with technology this is shielded tears isn't it this should block everything
okay so there's a rock where is it oh okay well let's shit those things are cool all right we're
looking for we want to just make it so we can buttons how might what did that do that do you
failed you failed the puzzle i just saw i saw buttons so i stepped on them look at the pebbles
i what i did what oh well damn it it's okay all right there's a spirit heart here
i'm glad there's not an actual heart all right there's one here and there's a rock where's that
tinted rock is there a rock in here too i've been feeding like five and a half hours all right where's
it in here there it is okay spirit heart let's get one there's one don't touch it ah it's okay
this two now available i have two spirit hearts available i need to not die all right i gotta
play well there's another one where more in the other room go down okay this one here you go okay
so um i can take this i just need two so i have two available i'm ready to go just don't accidentally
touch it one of the other ones i still want to get help i still i need help so i'm gonna just
keep playing very cool thanks for your participation oh what's wrong with me all
right hearts and rock for free i don't see any in here i can't even blow it up and i can't blow it
i don't i don't have i don't have any bombs is there bombs in the uh store i don't think there
was fuck i i don't have a three and a half hearts bomb in the shop okay bomb in the shop and then i
need the tinted rock where was it over here somewhere right i hear a beep here here back
oh it's in there it's not gonna hit it it's not gonna hit it from here oh is it i don't think it
is will it oh no come on that sucks it's the only one that didn't get hit oh well let's hope i can
kill this boss without being terrible okay here we go puff twins i feel like activate the bomb
i have to touch a bomb activate the bomb they have to run into the bomb i touch bomb okay i got a
bomb i get it for some reason it was red i thought it was going to kill me all right this is okay
cool oh what the fuck just happened what just happened what what just happened wait is he is
he free he's free all right he's free get the fuck away from me all right i gotta break the rest of
his head come get down here didn't time it right everything's fine that sounds yes okay i can't
even get the fucking item yes i can well good thing it's little steven i need two spirit hearts
wait why can i go down what's down good thing i saw the door on the right because i was going
to get the spirit hearts and go down the fucking well all right let's go that's normal route oh
okay i don't have any bombs to blow these up but let's let's go in mausoleum one all right i
gotta stay alive do i need any any special items for this or is it just oh holy fuck oh my god
it's nuts don't do that again turn the music up what the moons mean symbols or step on them
what do they mean this is the doctor house music all right got it you just ruined it for me sorry
i'm sorry what's wrong that's a good song that's a good that's a quality song i need hearts now
or who's the last don't but don't even spoil it who's the last boss of the energy bird rock go
back i don't know how you guys see this shit you guys are so like good at everything how like where
i can you pay that much attention on the right side how would you even see this shit i don't even
know how you do that not only that you're at a lower bit rate than me you're seeing this at
6000 up i'm seeing this at like 500 000 perfect score um let me check something okay for a second
i thought my microphone was delayed by like two seconds the whole stream hasn't played the uh we
shit before come on stevie your mic is muted fuck is it that's my first day screaming pretty good
combo two diamonds money well i know it's here i need money i'll come back huh well uh that's
the one of the worms does that do anything to my laser beam rock rock rock rock rock rock rock
i see this one hell fucking yeah up to 8.4 damage per tick that's per tick that's not per second
that's per tick eight before eight before eight before eight before eight before eight before eight
before eight so good protect uh how do i turn this on your mic compression is so bad i don't
have compression on it's not even turn i don't have it turned on i don't have compression on
it literally is not even activated you want to prove it i'll prove it right now hey hey how are
you how are you doing how you doing ah see what would have happened there if there was compression
on the whispering would have been really loud and the screaming would have been dropped way way
lower so here you go why is there poo on the floor this is a dirty game this is literally what
happened no it's not i'll let me show this to you it will now so as you see here this is with
compression on notice what's happening what's happening whoa and then now we're turning on the
see this is what happens when compression is on now it's off here we go it's off it's literally
the same it's not the same you just don't have fucking audio engineer ears like i do
i'm an audio engineer are you this is really cool the whispering was as loud as the yelling was
welcome to welcome to compression 102 because you should have learned that in the fucking first
year of classes dude shit your fly is down oh shit hold on whoa i was gonna go for it but
now it wasn't it wasn't even worth it why aren't you using 20 to one hold on i got no fucking idea
with this room just got annihilated from here come here what the fuck don't get hit by this guy that
would be so embarrassing an audio engineer would never get hit by that judgment give me something
good yes yes that's the best thing i could have possibly picked up please continue to make this
keep having please make this happen and lunch give me your lunch thank you now i have a full
hill i'm good to go move diamonds pay hands off shit you're right it's okay i had plenty of money
uh the relic right soul generator yeah nice anything in here that i want i got 15 coins
it's the exact amount that i'm looking for i get the treasure map it's fun why would i do that
no this is not the treasure map this is the full map what's going on over on the other side
what is over there what do i get over there teleporting thing up there
the big teleporter room how do i turn it on it was off and i tried to go for it
nice nightbot telling me that the scream is not on well i want to explore a little more i don't want
to just end it is this the last zone well the last boss check the map yeah but what is this spring
oh shit okay r.i.p scream you're late what are you talking about well this this room was a disaster
but i only took one hit okay so hold on wait i just fight the boss i kind of want to see what
this teleporter thing does i don't have i can't get up there i don't think so do i have to blow
my way up there i don't think i have enough to do it definitely not riot bomb rock oh my goodness
is there a bomb in the shop because if there is how much is it and it's i got the diamonds
i got the two of diamonds let's go i'm gonna get it let's get up there it's got to be like
something right it's got to be something yeah like i guess i gotta get like a straight point
or something just hurt i'll get hurt it hurts it hurts it hurts it hurts okay hurt yourself
where do i get hurt how do i hurt myself is there a spike i don't think there's any spikes
anywhere stand in the fire in the shop all right this is gonna work out we're gonna do the secret
entrance there's no oh i sprayed them i sprayed them out i sprayed them are there any more fires
i just instinctively spray every fire all of them you've seen me do it i do all of them
i sprayed them is there any more fire child's proof floor purple ah fuck i can't do that
get hit by the boss get hit by the boss yeah but i mean does that can i come back out here
oh so this is not the end then i can come back out here all right give me strength let's go
my two diamonds of the sun no where's strength there we go the fallen fallen holy shit why is
the what's the fallen doing down here i didn't get hit fuck it was so fast
shit it was so quick i was so taken aback that i instantly killed him i was so taken aback that
i died and i was like why is the fallen down a fucking god damn it thank god there's fire in
here yes okay what do these do what do they do eternal life question mark all right now we go
back did we is that is f f f what's going on what are you talking about what what what what what's
going on why is everybody freaking i'm going to get the diamonds right now two diamonds bomb is
five coins i'm doing i got i'm i got diamonds what are you guys talking about why are we freaking
out i'm going to get the bomb right now what why uh people this is a chat scenario what chat is
this is chat dot dot dot scenario hey we're good okay now we go back and we get the sun card again
because i want the full heal i'm sorry strength i want the sun thank you that's the bomb let me
make sure it works oh i really want that oh no all right so i know that was a i know that's minus
two i did it on purpose let's go i wish i had a bomb oh they're connected connected by this guy
so this is the real final floor then because that one was going to take me back to the normal game
right do i have that correct nice i'm at max damage though now 21 30 a tick this is crazy
the fires don't put the fires out yeah now i bombed this fire well that's what we call perfect
damn that's easy all right another shop i get up should i buy some bombs or something
what should i do matter donate never even got an active item that yeah that's true i didn't get
anything buy a bomb buy a bomb so this is it just donate the rest of the money no donation is sad
there that's all that's over here huh okay well that's not cool there's another floor
that's fun so correct me if i'm i just go down this floor down into the thing right it's not
like oh no don't go don't go down the worm that's right i do have i do have bombs now you're right
worm is not going to work or it doesn't do anything okay rock fuck i'm overwhelmed okay
i'm just gonna go what just happened what happened hello what happened to the game
whatever the game continue right it's crashed continue continue please what the fuck is this
mausoleum one is it what's gonna be the exact same thing i'm so confused wait i have to do
everything again why did i just get like banned oh i don't know what just happened but i gotta do
it again that wasn't that bad maybe i had to fall in i was like oh kill them in one hit okay whatever
let's go quickly is there anything else i need to
remember here there was the sun card i should do it all again at least the run isn't over yeah
that would have been really disappointing it's gonna be really annoying all right don't get like
cocky here and die very easily that goes on my health too i thought it crashed again for that
that was me okay let's go rock top right i don't remember where any of them are right okay yeah
over here we get a better outcome this time i think we just got a better outcome weird okay
keep track of those rocks this time use the diamond card again rocks the rng manipulation
that's actually going to be kind of a big deal though is that possible that we'll get something
different items no it's the same seed right oh what just hit me what just happened what did
i get sniped a fucking bone hit me i'm activated by that one all right here is two diamonds don't
use it yet okay remember this part is of rock there it is i freaked out about this i was like
holy shit nice can't do that okay remember i was like oh i'm gonna get that i'll come back and get
the diamond thing redo the jokes what jokes didn't tell him oh yeah this is uh wait we have prior
knowledge what is this okay i got hit by the same enemy in that one okay so hold on make sure i get
enough money right we have 14 it's a rock in here but hold on i can't do this out of order
you gotta realign the timeline that's what i'm trying to do i fucked up the timeline how
don't buy the map this time yeah why would i i'm not buying the map it's a greed fight oh right
where is it down here this timeline's fucked up i had more than three hearts by this point
telepills right is judgment oh yeah right right i spawned judgment i got hp up we're not doing
this yet we're gonna change the timeline okay okay i remember this soul generator we went in here
do not buy the map right now so that's we're fucking with the timeline a little bit
it's not donation is 504 hold on the donation is it 504 oh it doesn't make any sense
wait is this different urging okay i gotta do give me the two of diamonds use it i'll have like
50 or 60 coins where's the greed fight it didn't even happen wait i'm gonna i'm gonna
telepills into the green fight right okay let's grab that uh oh well all right i just started
world war three so uh okay um well i don't even need to go to the secret area either
but i need hearts fuck why does it have to happen okay well let's just slow down use this 44
get judgment get my my lunch do a hearts in the secret area that's true this is new there's the
sun okay this still is intact and then he gives you lunch but so far so good now i need to go buy
a bomb while we continue to correct this timeline we're gonna shit lotus queer at heart fight the
boss first buy a bomb forget about the map i don't need it at this point i had to do that just to
get well that that's to prevent the crash i need rocks that i missed importance remember i was
like oh fuck i can't get in there yeah just go probably took the same amount of damage here
there's telepills again let's see if we can get greed no wait i could buy this yeah i'm gonna get
that by the big fly thing but it doesn't really do anything for me i don't even have the flies
i don't have any flies by the bomb too oh i know i'm fucking with the timeline here but
there's been a little shit in there you i just fucked up the whole thing for no reason oh my
god i've ruined everything for no reason oh i don't like it grabbed it's impossible
when you make me do it again i have apparently trouble what mod is this is anti-birth i don't
know why i just almost hit star wars anti-birth anti-birth all right we're good back to where
we were before get the sun car to get the hell out of here but that bounce is fucked up it's weird
okay am i missing anything okay get these there's a couple other um there's a couple other things i
can do with some tinted rocks i know there is all right where's the where's another tinted rock
no i'm not gonna get the worm sun on the boss room all right break these two okay what is it
not bad not bad falling it's so unbelievable and then here we go this is my damage resistance now
which makes it this is impossible for me to lose okay let's get the fuck out of here blow it up you
who did that which one you guys knocked into it wait no crash no crash good mausoleum two curse
of darkness my favorite one great good good good looking good um the hair is it a brain
all right timelines fine because his greed oh steam sail wow puberty two
uh double puberty this build is fucking just diarrheaing all over everything it's great i
love it so powerful and i haven't even taken a hit with sam where am i what how can i fire
stop doing that they teleport around that's cool it's different it's different i have infinite
health here actually i'm gonna take some hits because i want to build up samson's uh damage
i'm gonna take some hits just hit me don't hit me back kill me boom perfect one two three four
five one more six there we go fuck the damn it what what what do they do what but there's a puzzle
you have to shoot specific fires sorry there's just a row with fires in it i don't know i'll
remember that for next time we'll get him next boss room already i don't want to do that yet i'm
so powerful you know when you play isaac and you you have a build that's so good and you're so
destructive that you don't you just want to like go kill every room and you just want to kill
everything it's just so powerful because it's so easy in this game just to have like a shitty
build and run into a wall and die and be mad so when you get to actually kill things very quickly
it's a lot of fun it's great and i'm and i want full bar there we go don't give him the infinity
stunt oh shit secret hey look it's the goat head i found him that's too much help i might max for
a samson i could just test it in that triple puberty am i max already with samson yeah he's
died i didn't do anything easy i'm unstoppable i have a never-ending supply of of hearts
god hurt me i don't even care it doesn't even hurt for real because then i just replace it
all right we're gonna oh give me these all right what is this one i can see forever oh
more puberty puberty five puberty six am i gonna wrap around eventually or no
this is good no it doesn't i did don't touch anything don't okay okay okay yeah don't touch
anything what do we do fire it's the solution to the fire yeah okay all right we're out
out of the final area tinted rocks don't even matter i have full health well everything
and this is time time to fight the boss i think so i haven't found the item room yet wait i just
got the is it is an item room is it weird that i don't even want it i'm not doing that
free chest oh right speed up and health down not taking that
all right puzzle or something what the fuck is going on finally bob's brain i got an
what's happening what am i stepping on what the fuck stop doing that okay there's a puzzle here
where is it all right so what do i press okay we got this one was already pressed
one of them was already one was already pressed this one this one was already stepped on i didn't
step on this one it's not a puzzle with bait yeah so tell the people in chat stop it and he's
dead oh finally item room um should i get poop hat just for fun like the lap this is a serious
screen now let's have the whole group yeah it's fun to have a big group but this on the other hand
this is probably a tinted rock doesn't matter here's shit on sale all right what's that what's
this what's that thing handle first immunity plus evil up oh no that's neat it gets rid of all these
the things they can do half of the rooms that's cool finally we can see all right boss time
full health full everything why am i so huge uh i think a bunch of random stuff let's go mom
what the fuck is this it's just like a triple jump i want a coin dead now what does this keep
going at is this a just go down dude you fucking show up every time thankfully it's the hole
it doesn't really matter you had to do the puzzle right oh so laser's huge at the end that is
is so did i do it is it is it is it meant does it not matter now just take the bullet
right and go down over now it's the normal game oh well you should be able to beat everything i
just did again this is the best build i've had all night without a doubt well yes yeah i don't
want that because remember i was talking about this it's a roman isaac by the time you get here
takes you more than 10 seconds that's what you're looking for that's what you want
so you know it's going well okay i want to take a few hits give me a few hits again keep replenishing
this uh this evil heart uh we're going oh wait wait i want another key i want to do mega save
all right let's meet another angel hi there i'll play your game you could get it possible i have
62 just i'm just do not do any evil shit like i don't i always blow this guy up every time
we're not doing that right now i want the i want to be able to do megastate if i want to
i'm already bored with this i don't i don't want to play this anymore
is that the video game i'm talking about this i just give me i don't want to do this anymore
i don't even do it i don't want to do this what pretty fly right all right that's it
i'm pretty fine that's it i don't i hate this i don't even want to do this anymore
the philosophies stop doing the one on the right it doesn't even matter
there it is just let it all go left side thank you very much finally got my poop hat everyone
now can rejoice i'm getting really ballsy right now what was the point of that just to show you
that i could that i don't care was that just to show you that i can what a psycho well i just i
just want i'm gonna refill that see we're fine it's rocking here it was not so i need to get hit
a couple times anyways look at that health just disintegrated so i'm not that's just like a 40s
comedian i know what i said i can't believe it all right stop getting fucking hit all right
glyph that i i nominate that i nominate that for worst choice of the year i nominate it
that is that's that's going on the list for me i nominate that fucking hell that was very very
very bad veto in favor of the tasmanian devil what do you mean bad if i blow this up is it bad
somebody tell me quick all right let's go yeah oh yeah yeah all right yeah all right yeah do i want
any of this stuff probably not it's not an angel by the way bad they both good yeah but i'm not
going to have that one activate i'm not taking them both four hearts no i'm not taking any of
this all right down or up up or down up or down up or down up or down up or down i'm unstoppable
there i got it down what do you think down up up i'm gonna go up i don't want the other one
that other item is something i don't want i don't like it i don't want that i think it was the pride
before the fall what there's no way i lose this i'm gonna just absolutely taste meld everything
there's no way i lose i can't lose no that actually is a way that i lose if the game
crashes or if i like i don't know get like sick okay if i get like sick right now
and like puke sick like i have to leave and yeah i'll turn it up
holy shit what was that why did that just happen first item reusable fly hive
oh that's i got the big flies that's right move it very cool very cool very cool
i must get hit by that that would have been embarrassing what on earth is this
jawbreaker don't chew it tears have a chance to become a tooth feeling more than triple damage
that's not possible though all right this is not possible only a quarter sometimes you gotta just
stand still look at all these flies too am i missing something i could use the sun right now
but why would i almost a full stack yeah pretty good diaper on your head or it's pre-recorded
it's a new one somebody earlier said oh wow what a hard game it's getting to this point is how
it gets hard oh wow hard game huh well there's two of those and i didn't even try i didn't even try
to kill that guy and he died i looked in that guy's direction and he died here we go isaac
i can like punch him around now goodbye the journey continues oh don't leave that i
no angel room or anything that sucks gonna have to kill right wait could i get another angel room
piggy bank boom spectral i mean spectral tier is that's cool looking with a joker maybe piggy
bank i like savings uh reasonable soul protection i i mean it's just it's not even worth it i have
already have that oh pretty useless i hope for a joker card this guy died so fast
the spectral tears fucking up the damage they maybe i don't think so i just shot him in the
fucking head with a shotgun like holy fuck that was ridiculous it's a hard game jeremy
it is a hard game we just got very lucky three or four times i actually should take some damage
just a little to get the extra damage all right you're on journalist difficulty this is on the
hardest difficulty this is on hard there is no other is this normal and hard it's on hard
37 difficulty what another kid's game jeremy come on you're better than this
am i though you sure are you certain of that nobody can even contest me i'm uncontestable
just take it who cares nice try i don't even chance this is great
and when i was up here last time it was just like dodging and freaking out and
watch out oh fuck i had like four hearts or something five hearts i i want to get hit
just to like you know i feel like i'm playing it feels so good though starting at zero again
after you do something like this at all if you okay you ever jump on a trampoline
for a long time and then you get off the trampoline and you jump and your whole world
is upside down you it feels like you you miss the superpower the superpower is gone
and fucked with you i'm good give me the money i'll take money pain hit me again 82
i'm not done i'm not done i want to keep killing people i'm not done give me that money oh that's
it there's no more people for me to attack and no joker card okay good i'm not even gonna move
99 going yeah too bad i couldn't do well delirium is not in this one because this is this replaces
after birth right bloody penny really you're playing easy mode now now they nerfed him i
remember when they nerfed him he used to be so much better but when he was better than this
i'm not gonna i'm not gonna play for you much longer i'm just addicted to the game
let's be honest with you i was waiting for it ah sorry i need to go to the at least the item room
i'm trying to go fast not even playing as the lost no i'm not uh i like to have fun
when i play a video game and you pick that character if you don't like to have any
rock blast what is stone bombs oh shit okay it's kind of cool goat again i think the goat's been
in every single seed it has been how many games have i actually played seven six the goat's been
in all six or seven of these there's a seed if you want it all right let's get the hell out of
here i'm going down back into the uh into the river zone whatever it is i just want to see this
place again this is cool i like this am i gonna stream this again yeah probably this would be a
filler this would be filler content or something that i you know if we get to the end of something
i'm like you know what can i do for three hours gonna be this full health doesn't matter all the
steel that does matter bombs i need to keep two bombs but that counts as two bombs what's going
on here what does this mean bomb or something with the bomb in the middle bomb the bed that's
just the whole level on the bed whoa oh it just refills your health right all right i blow the
bed up oh nice i get three hearts i don't want to skip i mean i want to go fast but i don't want to
skip i have the spirit hearts when i need to deposit them i mean it's absolutely uh hp up
i'm not gonna i know it's cheap but i'm not taking it i mean what i'm as i'm as a cell no
this dude drunk uh i don't think so i got the bombs let's go i'm ready wormwood
oh back i get too close to this shit
whoa that was fast okay this is ridiculous uh you want dark dark bomb yeah dark bomb is good
that's it tell us the shit stain story because there's nothing there's no shit stain story
where's the next uh part am i out of my mind where is it oh there's a part tell the shit stain
story you guys are fucking crazy what are you even talking about i can't tell us this oh tell us the
shit stain story oh sure okay one time i shit my pants and didn't get rid of the underwear or
something uh and then oh haha that's it okay that's that was it did you need any more than that
i'm wicked all right what's this trickled charge battery no
is it hard in here all right take this give me a skirt heart thank you oh just have him hit that
yeah nice that sucks i need keys oh man man man man man man man man man i just these a lot of random
things on screen what is that guy guy with the track i just threw a trash can at me thank you
so much you're so helpful there's so many enemies in here no keys i just shit myself so i just shit
myself i can't even say it i just shit myself right from the underwear yes you should yes um
just get new underwear there's something i don't know yes you should
shit
hey this one i need the bombs get him fly get him good boy these rocks not like it matters i can't
use them gotta get too close to these guys i don't like it i don't like having to get too close to
these people you got something for me just you just picked up a full heart come on man
what are you talking about you don't have anything for me diesel bub
bye here's up not much more you can get than this geez okay hard game what do you got for me
i can't i i can't that's too many that's too many go back to the empty room i wouldn't even
look in there it is knife piece one what is the knife piece where do you get knife piece too
this is new dlc this is a mod it will be new dlc soon enough this will be official dlc in a few
months like that from my understanding i can't i don't know from my understanding uh admin
mcmillan is working on this in his sort of his random off time it's not like a priority is it
i don't think it's been actually a couple years hasn't it since it was announced at least a year
or two and it's gonna use the anti-birth mod and there's gonna be other additions too apparently
it's not just gonna be anti-birth well i got plenty of spirit hearts if i don't lose them
it hates the mod it hates it nice fill it up easy okay there's just a poop in there
the stars may find what you yeah let's go left or right left or right left or right left or right
left or right then whatever i say more in chat i'm doing i'm seeing a lot of rights
damage reduction good choice good choice left probably was the bean all right so now i'm looking
for that secret thing right eventually here when i go down to the next floor damage should i just
buy it i mean like i buy it i think it's gonna buy it who cares i'm buying it fanny pack great
did i get the item room already i did all right cool i have spirit hearts move horn fell oh
shit oh this is pretty cool whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa all right my fly is my
fly going after him fly is going after him stop going so fast now kill him all if you fuck off
hp up stop showing up in my games coal and weird mushroom i'll take it weird mushroom is pretty
good you get a random mushroom effect every floor right okay the this is let's just let's go
emphasis the worst mines too all right that way i'm not gonna touch any buttons right
isn't this important just try to kill my friend versus the fires that's important and not this
everybody hates that item i'm not touching it look at how many people are down here
oh cancer was can't wait cancer was over there i don't think cancer's gonna do anything
isn't cancer is just more tears right that's not gonna help me i mean i'm already pretty high
i mean that's it's fast but i'll keep it i need hearts what's the one on the right do it's
that speed i don't want the i don't want the baby i don't want a rotten baby what i do right
randomizes your stats oh that's the shuffle one yeah never mind i'll take the infested baby
let's go what does that do
great gideon you shouldn't be that bad with that kill it oh something's wrong with me
something's wrong with me what is this what are you talking about game what's going on why
i'm flying around i'm flying i can fly what are you talking about i can fly i can literally fly
why am i why can i i'm getting touched by the fire in there
about speed up i could have put that yeah whoopsie puzzle puzzle room puzzle room puzzle room go to
the puzzle room first puzzle first puzzle room and where is the puzzle where please
i'm not telling i'm not picking that up the button room how do i get the fuck out of here
there's no door i can't that's wasted that but okay so go to the room with the buttons
you guys are gonna help me right i can't do this on my own oh my god where the fuck did you come
from i just got like a pre-fired getting dangerously low on health i want this please god take the devil
deal devil item is the best item free hearts constantly what don't do it yet don't no no no
no no no no no no no no oh my fucking god god damn it what the fuck is this is this even possible
for me to do anymore no i can't do i can't do the actual end of the game why would i do that i
know i just like i don't know if it's my brides i don't know two people told me to go get the
fucking nail and i'm like all right go get nail i'll listen to two people in the fucking chat
but yeah but more importantly why can't i fucking leave it's the bad place for this door to be
oh it's already ruined so who cares explain what happened okay uh so in the an anti-birth um you
don't just fight enemies and then go down and and find no you have to do like a dark souls dlc
fucking convoluted bunch of shit to get to the actual end of the game i don't know if the nail
does what does the nail even do use the bet i can i fly over that what the fuck would they
do this for go get the nail fuck go get the fucking nail and i was like yeah there's no
reason why i won't be able to get the fucking nail right now all right i'm soft locked in this room
god damn it why it was like on pace to do it too i wanted to see it get that lost world record
pace what close i'm like no i don't know i don't know why you don't just like finish this with
azazel they're just like blow through the rest of the game i'm gonna like look this up i'm gonna
just look up exactly what i have to do on something i hold r not worth wasting your time it's not
why is it like that actual boss of the game delirium is well this is not anti-birth
delirium is not even in this game uh bottom one right
delirium sucked anyways delirium really is like a mess i remember fighting delirium a few times
and being like why am i doing this this is dumb what just happened okay suicide king what does
suicide king do uh i think i wait this is this just kills you right this is just good this kills you
use it yeah but you motherfuckers go get the nail god damn it i can't get over that why did i just
i'm such a i'm such a good dog i was on my way to do something and all of a sudden it's just like hey
hey i'll go to that what's the goal okay come here come here yes okay okay do i get a treat
hey hey hey jerma if you had to eat cat food would you eat wet or dry wet every time
would you ever eat dry cat food are you serious please enjoy it are you sure i think i'm pretty
sure sun card or um there's no reason for me to have that suicide thing i'll accidentally
press that button it'll be a disaster jerma enjoys wet i can't believe i'm still
why am i taking that teleporter great teleporter by the way i know you obsessively compulsively
just making your buildings as an engineer but like nice work no reason for those to be here
dude get the nail for some reason i don't know why but i thought that maybe like i was gonna
miss out on my opportunity to get the nail like someone's like dude go get nail are you stupid
like you gotta get that nail now like fuck why is there's gotta be a reason why you're telling
me to do this now i'm not an isaac expert i'm i what do i know i got a cheat sheet over here
for god's sakes you just trust chat so blindly yeah what you guys do with my trust just do with
it i trusted you take care of me right now you are my cheat sheet well there we go well i'll
at least i'll finish this fairly quickly selfish of me to want more damage like is it selfish
me to say i want damage i want a bunch more all right let's go wait i'm gonna do one more room so
i can get another nail there's nothing in here you're lying just come back to haunt you
the visage break the chain whoa oh they're connected again somehow all right watch out
why is this thing still good speed and damage up perfect no fuck that it's not going to do
anything doesn't do anything right that's not doesn't do anything it's too late get it before
it's too late get it before it's too late whatever we got some resident experts in here
no it does work it does work that was kind of cool boss oh a puzzle room can i still do it hey
is that is this stuff possible do i do anything here no nail hey easy with that tongue is it
lucky rock there's something inside of it um no i'm used to the cancer i'm used to the speed
something good um one plus one equals i don't know one plus one is free forever 520 not as funny
holy shit oh it's double everything holy fuck okay that's incredible puzzle wait where big bits
puzzle what are you talking about puzzle where's the puzzle not here get it before you leave puzzle
where is it is this a puzzle is this what you're talking about fire room puzzle get the nail for
yourself please let me get rid of this oh sick sick it's pretty sick i did it i did the puzzle
and there's not uh two nickels this game's a liar game's broken bugged game i'm going way too fast
okay wait wait the puzzle game all right so here's the puzzle pop left all right so pop left pop
right and then this will make us just a big smiley face and then we got all the ones in the middle on
the other side so just make the smiley face for those ones i have to blow out okay and then all
the ones in the middle on the right side so top left top right and just smile the ones that are
littered the ones that need to stay lit oh okay damn so many items it's ridiculous stay lit i
sure will donate uh compass all right time for the puzzle wherever it is not here keep finding it on
the other side please stop stop what what do you stop what what do you okay what are you talking
about please stop what lucky rock i don't want the lucky rock all right puzzle room where is it
let's go i want to see it i'm gonna get to this game okay don't nobody move so the ones that were
lit are the ones that have to stay turned on right is that accurate for the ones that were lit so
all right the ones that were lit are the ones that were turned on so get rid of this one these two
up here okay there's the smiley face we these are with that with that on i know it's not these
all four corners here we're off okay and then these two bottom ones are off too got it knife
piece three shit you need i have knife piece one i need knife piece two no is there any way is there
no way i can get through nail use the nail as knife piece two there's no way i don't need to
get all that stuff come on console command cheated in you this that doesn't exist oh well
put in the konami code i don't i don't even i don't even know the konami code
was it up up down down left right left light up up down down up up up down down left right left
right b a star there it is sad i know get the nail well did i just get guppy wait do i have
anything from guppy already i'm not no why would i take that take it it won't override souls lie
it's a lie if i take this i'm gonna go down to one so there's a lie oh it's not a lie all right
i'm going down this time i know i just got the polaroid but we i gotta kill satan like three times
all right please i'll take these things literally you cannot lose i know
all right now get out of here how many of these you have all right no more no more no stop stop
stop stop reusable tear burst holy shit that's better than the nail guppy i'm guppy right you
unlocked bethany you unlocked challenge four and you why am i not um is there a reason why i'm not
guppy you are i don't need to go how that's an afterbirth though well this is i'm gonna one
hit kill every enemy in the whole game just tammy's head check this out watch this
holy shit okay fantastic i can do it in every room oh i am guppy oh woman i'm unstoppable how
do i do the hardest thing in the game what's the hardest thing in the game i can do right now
it's mega saiyan but i can't even do mega saiyan it's four rerolls all pedestal items on the floor
does not roll your devil item to it no balls hit it you're saying
what is that what is that thing enemies get feared if they come enemies get feared
anyway and enemies can fear if they come near you wasted broken combo again i didn't really
didn't mean to still this is not my second time being down in the anti-birth cellar i
you gotta do it a few times before you get it i want to pick up the shovel uh hopper down
i mean the paw room oh the nail in the paw will be different it rerolls all okay i see what you
mean well this is just a ton of damage what a broken fucking combo it's so broken and i didn't
get to do the i'm so upset by this this is seriously like it's just probably the best thing i'll have
in a long time and i told i didn't get the third fucking second piece why did i have to listen to
that person one person just was like go get it dude what are you doing oh it's a tinted rock it
doesn't matter ah upper down they're done i'll beat satan like check this out this is insane
i don't even know what i just got hp up look at how many minions i have this is the kind of
build that this this is what beats like delirium you're going you fight delirium with this and it's
like it's too bad i don't have that this is the wrong game this is the most broken
fucking thing i can't believe i'm not fighting the last boss i'm so sad look at this shit it's
unbelievable nobody can touch me for real just go oh well that was insane
oh imagine that actually you know i'm kind of glad i'm kind of glad that i didn't see the last
boss in anti-birth you know why because i want to fight the last boss i don't want to delete the
last boss i would have deleted the last boss let's just do the new character definitely book of
virtues three hearts terrible damage and really slow it's terrible what's this do you familiar
how often can i use it it stays with you the whole time wait what is it it's gone ten bombs
well what's with the new currency down there for for what there's a new currency down there
four hearts of some kind hold r just to reset faster all right i'm trying to hold r in my
controller you don't add spirit hearts actually this time yeah yeah yeah that was probably the
end that was yeah i'm addicted again i can't stop what do i do so hearts are charges for your active
item that's actually pretty cool you guys said this character stuck so what's the point should
i not be using it should i just try not to get the thing hit don't listen to us keep pressing it
holy shit what oh man okay this is actually pretty cool but they can be destroyed and you
don't get soul hearts anymore they just i get it try not to let them die i see
hmm shit i have i have to i have to stay i have to stay i just got like the all right don't i got
okay wait wait wait i'm probably gonna lose but you know i've extra luck too i need the item room
damn that's kind of hard to do that you know die on floor one well you can't say past tense
died on floor one when it hasn't happened yet that's not fair you reset yeah that's it
you know how many people play this game and they go to the first room they go to the item room and
they it's not the exact fucking one thing that they want and they've reset 200 times until they
get the one thing they want sorry i reset once in seven and a half hours sue me this is actually my
pure reset because it's not this item is not very good all right what is it oh too bad powerfully
those are two awful items but i did get that really good damage up item i'm willing to give
it one one solid attempt use the book oh okay that's like burp really loud you can get in here use
those soul hearts no i'm storing them how many can you have as many as you want can i have how
many can you have around you come on they stay with you with five floor to four floor to floor
that's good what am i missing here uh one try to keep them alive just stay the hell away from
everybody keep getting more and more bust them bust them this is the worst thing that could have
happened to me this is the worst enemy that could have attacked me actually died to fly well no i
died to the thing that was i'm thinking okay that's it can i see it wait what is one of these
pervo with the whole game times two i'll never attempt this ever again this hurts this hurts
my head actually it really does kills heal okay cool go go go go i'm going i'm going i'm going
as fast i can what do i have to kill this mom's heart these guys are so much harder when they're
faster fuck i'll try it again try again try again try again try again this is fun good start
jesus i was holding back and so it's vision no we don't want this yet fuck one more invasive
friend holy shit what the hell is this thing five like super squad all right can i like slow this
down and bring to the regular game fuck no i like this item what's fuck no fuck this is stupid
slow down i'm done see you tomorrow i'll get stuck here for like another four hours all right the
plan tomorrow was gonna i think we're gonna do monster lab for a week it looks like fun it looks
just stupid enough for us to enjoy it i love binding of isaac it's a great game and you will
see me beat the boss in anti-birth this time i won't mess it up i won't mess it up i swear
but i'll see you guys tomorrow gonna do some more uh we tomorrow have a great night have a good time
take care and i can change the music now to the regular one there we are okay all right let's do
the bits it's time earlier we had 250 from a drummager a drummage door thanks to the 250 yo
funny man i got laid out from my job my laptop that was really important for my music production
died and i got rejected from university i really wanted to get into all within a single week it's
kind of funny how fast things can go into shit anyways thanks for cheering me up even in my
darkest days love from finland sorry to hear about this shitty week that's just what it is right
i'm really sorry to hear that that's a lot to take in that's a lot to do it's a lot for you to have
to deal with i seriously wish you the best of luck in trying to figure out all this stuff i'm sure
you will it might take a little time but i'm sure you will thanks for hanging out here and
cheers from america the one thing i will tell you is if this is one of those really really awful
weeks that's just a terrible week you may have just rolled the dice and they may have landed
very very badly and something like this probably won't happen to you again at least in that
succession you got like that the dice roll of just a bunch of bad shit in a row i wish this something
that could be done about it but sometimes life throws us these weighted dice unfortunately
remember you have a gambling problem but i just dice bad what but i really do wish you the best
of luck take care of yourself sorry to hear about that vegas is not good for your well-being i don't
i i don't go to the casino i don't go to the casino i go to the casino like once every like five months
i don't know how you guys don't understand this old chipster move those out of the way
hey kabu thanks for the 500 bits durham have you ever heard of the game under hero it's an
RPG on steam that i really think you'd enjoy check it out um under hero i'll give it a look
is it good what is it a streamable game or is it something that just to play in my off time
durham i'm sorry to say this but i'm afraid i have to leave i found a more fog champ streamer
i wish you'd do the best i wish i hope that they're the most fog champ person you could
possibly include in your daily video life just not fog unsubbed have fun hey seven layer wario
thanks for the thousand bits ten bucks hey durham i'm trying to make my voice sound deeper because
i'm a trans guy as a voice actor do you have any good tips for deepening your voice when you talk
something more masculine um not not necessarily because your vocal cords are your vocal cords
there's not much you can do about changing your vocal cords or the way that like sound comes
through them you can manipulate right like i i can go as this is as deep as i can go
i can't go much deeper than this right but there are people on this earth that for some reason
their vocal cords and their and their trachea have been able to go even deeper than to the point
where they are people there's some people that have insanely booming deep voices i don't know
is that the physiologically how that all really works just smoke a lot that's not gonna worry
don't make it sound like this it's bugleberry with other markiplier yeah markiplier has one
of those just like hello everybody body room more it's so it's so incredible people wish they had
markiplier's voice they really do his the way he speaks is so clear and so it's so radio like
for me to for me to do markiplier i actually have to do this i have to do this to do this to do this
and it doesn't even sound doesn't even sound completely wrong completely wrong
hello everybody everybody my name is that sound better that sound better why is it this
shouldn't be echo on it uh long story short it's an incredibly talented man pretty much all there
is to it it's an echo i don't know why the echo is on here the echo is not even turned on there's
a button to turn it on but somebody mentioned speak from the chest which it's hard to describe
but speaking from the chest and using your entire diaphragm that's what singers do
but thanks for the 10 buck almonder high five almonder hey dark soul thanks for the 250 it's
entirely possible you're just a coward i don't know what i did just grabbed eats squeaky boots
as a cartoon character a real person but it's not a real person eating actual shoes
uh great great wikipedia edit when it comes to like a source for real life
anyways uh thanks 250 hey actually spazz out thanks for the five dollars do the funny thing
i don't know what the funny thing is i don't know what the funny thing is hopefully i did it for you
peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 germa have you ever seen the clip when taison day streamed tf2
and his audio fucked up i have it's very funny that's another talking about voices that's another
big booming i can't even do them like markiplier hey hey taison day hey hey it's and you can't
mimic that another person that has an insanely booming just deep radio voice it's incredible
i have seen it though it's when his audio just keeps looping over and over again
and he doesn't know and he's just playing and it's just his he has his own stream open or
something right important but yes this is very important it's very important i think it needs to
be even worse than this to be honest with you like i think it needs to be like this is good like it's
supposed to be very bad like worse way worse this is this like looks good but don't spoil that for
anybody no i don't want to show the image that no no no we're not spoiling anything this is
talking about pre-stream chat spoilers don't do that that's very funny though hey elf elfkin thank
you elfkin for the four dollars i don't know if you still have those photos from that fire watch
video you did ages ago but if you do how much do i have to cheer for you to send them to me those
photos actually went i believe they actually did go into the trash the real trash maybe i shredded
them i think i may have shredded all those i don't think those exist anymore i'm just gonna dig
through the trash and find them um i don't think so but unfortunately i do not have them anymore
uh yarn i'm tourist shop thanks for five dollars jerma i once i am once again asking for your
support to beat some blood-borne bosses jokes aside please accept this meager donation what
you do is invaluable to your watchers especially in times like these thank you and may everyone
be well uh the tourist shop ps why didn't you record or stream your first blood-borne playthrough
you've robbed us you absolute biscuit well that's a very easy answer because i wasn't a streamer
back when blood-borne came out and i played it three or four times in a row
it was i had a twitch account i streamed maybe once every four or five months maybe twice a year
or something it wasn't really until like 2015 2016 that i really started actually streaming
and spending more than three four plus kind of days a week doing it uh it's before twitch
before i started using it time for another one maybe maybe uh thank you hall of one zombie for
the 250 did you ever play out of this world i'd imagine you'd enjoyed it old school platformer
but really memorable i have played i have played it but another world that is what they made for
some reason uh they changed the title i don't know why another world out of this world the
same game dude what he did scream it but what wasn't i shit faced or something wait i did
stream it for like an hour right i was like drunk i was like shit faced right shit was i drunk when
i did this there was a i remember what the going the transition from boston to vegas i got trashed
one night and played like 10 games in a row like minecraft and was that part of that the fake
stream no no i think this actually happened that was the best worst stream ever this was in 2016
this was a 2016 stream i don't wow i guess maybe i did it once but i have played out of this world
and it is very interesting uh fun story about out of this world or another world uh the person that
did that that is responsible for making that game i'm gonna make sure i get this correct because
it's pretty cool it's pretty cool piece of information i believe it's the same person that
did the heart of darkness game is that a complete lie i don't think it is remember the heart of
darkness game that's not a lie right that's true that's that's that's correct right yeah i just
want to make something sometimes you you have this knowledge but you don't remember if it's real or
not is that ever happened to you guys uh that game is also fun i streamed that game i never
beat it though because it's very hard and very frustrating but i have streamed heart of darkness
it's very fun wait did i beat it i might have hey spoons for self-defense thanks for 15
dollars 1500 bits thanks a lot for that hey germa i don't mean to alarm you or anything
but i hacked your web camera and i've been recording you for the past four months
i want to talk about your abnormal behavior behavior off stream but if you turn the stream
off you just sit there motionless unblinking without emotion until it's time to turn the
stream back on what's the deal with that um this is what all streamers do i thought that was common
knowledge by now thanks a lot for the 15 dollars bow and jackal thanks to three bucks the toilet
paper shortage has hit us really hard so it looks like i'll be switching over to diapers soon
what brand would you recommend for someone who has long gaming streaming sessions well i would
recommend the uh toilet because a diaper is not going to help you because even if you like shit
you still have to clean yourself up so that's not going to do very much for you if you piss in a
diaper you're just making yourself dirty you just pee into the bowl in the toilet so that's not
really solving the problem thanks for three bucks uh magic muffin thanks for three bucks i had a shit
day at work because my co-worker is an asshole stream cheered me up though thanks for that king
i thought it was only one person doing the king thing is it wait that is that the one person
it is it is that person oh is that one person okay sorry to hear that sorry you're having
troubles at work thanks to three bucks and happy to cheer you up happy to let you hang out here
well let let you hang out here sounds like i'm allowing you to like oh i i know well it's good
to have you let you be here i like this like a the point of like entry from monetary anything
like that you're permitting us to hang out here i mean technically you could ban everyone
yeah but that is no that's right here about you day at work uh five thousand bits from
valemi which is insane thanks a lot of let me for the 50 dollars just go off king i am
thanks to 50 bucks a shitload of money uh let's get the let's go to the new scene here
we're gonna go back to the wee tomorrow i like playing binding of isaac though it's fun just
to play a game that i know at least some stuff about i am the greatest player in the world but
it's just fun to play it because that guy i'm not like lost yes i am but not like usual
i'm gonna bump you here is isaac go to two to three hour filler game i think it is i think if
we need to burn a couple hours let's say subway it's like oh it's only been like three or four
hours i'll play isaac for a runner too easy to do that but here come the credits here comes all the
subs from today thank you guys for your continued support and you may be brand new support maybe
just sub today thank you and maybe you got community sub you got to be part of the community
you got to be somewhere around you had to have shown up at some point so thank you appreciate
it let us continue with the bit swindle swine swindle swine thanks to the 1600 but 16 dollars
hey germa i love you well you didn't say i i added that hey germa love you i added that i love you
so thanks for the 16 dollars and you gave a community sub right after that so thank you
wow rl thanks for the 500 bits no message just 500 bits thank you cell juniors thanks for 500
bits i don't understand this game with a smiley face uh if you've made it you've never really
played it it can be very confusing random items and shit that's what i mean i have hundreds of
hours in this game over the course of 10 years and i still need a cheat sheet i still don't know
what half this stuff even does when i see it thank you though wembley ttv thanks the 250 germa this
is a mod oh hey germa the germa this is a wait germa the is a mod there is a mod okay see hey
germa there is a mod on the steam workshop for afterbirth called the binding of undertale it's
a really solid mod as everyone from the game with music and newer bosses and items are you serious
reading comprehension no it's not reading comprehension they they missed they missed
a couple of where they missed a couple of letters i have to add them in is that true i'd have to go
look that up it's kind of fun thank you wembley appreciate it under birth eat to burger thanks
to the three bucks what was the last thing you ate and the last thing you drank uh the last thing
that i ate was half of an italian sub like an italian sandwich the last thing i drank was uh
coffee i didn't even go holy shit i didn't even go to the bathroom i didn't go to the bathroom one
time in eight hours wow dude i gotta i have to like go pee i didn't do it i didn't we didn't
there was a break i didn't take a break did i really just sit here for eight hours and didn't
holy shit all right i gotta like get up and fucking move around well this was a gamer stream
that is truly that's accurate uh that's the last two things i ate and drank thanks for the three
bucks shadows one disciple thanks for the 250 gerba uh hey gerba won't be any more donations
for a while since i'm saving up for a shamrock shake but anyway don't you think it's kind of
irresponsible to hold a 5 000 person gathering like this uh with the virus going around what
oh you oh you all right okay i see what you're doing i see what you're doing
anyway had some ideas for big channel points replace you with bugleberry or grandpa for one
minute no i'm gonna just knock that down right now uh tuber germa or boston gerba for one minute
say shpee none of these are gonna happen i'm going to be really honest say shpee instant drew
which i'm assuming is having nancy drew game ready to play and tell the shit stain story so
you want me to have channel points to tell the same story over and over again so like a hundred
thousand channel points is to tell the shit stain story but if it's only one story so somebody has
to do that one time and then nobody has to buy it again if none of the no none of those are going
to happen no no no no that's so funny oh i'll put something there there's no shit i didn't
there is no story you guys made that up and made me think i had a story where i talked about how i
shit my pants or something thanks to the 250 though hey patty thank you patty too for the
three bucks germa i want to thank you for streaming and making me laugh my mom passed away recently
we were working together and i was very close to her again thank you so much for just being
you but may she rest in peace i'm really sorry to hear that take care of yourself take as much
time that you need to grieve over something like that because that's that's a that's a major that's
a major thing to happen i'm really sorry people and look at the people in the chat i've got it
got it correct stay strong can't even imagine what you're going through but thanks for sticking
around thanks for hanging out and thanks for three dollars we also had 1500 bits from dr noob
stein thanks for the 15 dollars germa i'm so sorry i was the one guy who told you to get the nail i
didn't mean before the puzzle fuck i can't believe i didn't get it oh i just scatter brain adhd brain
just doesn't didn't process it and didn't keep it in permanent memory
oh that's my own fault there's nobody else's don't worry thanks for 15 dollars hey mitchell thanks
with a thousand bits thank you for 10 bucks mitchell hey jingo i'm so happy to hear you're
finally gonna play hulk ultimate destruction easily in my desert island games selection
if you ever try the freedom force games on stream i'm gonna lose it thanks for every amazing content
thanks a lot thanks for the 10 bucks multi trip thanks 250 germa are you gonna play neo 2 omega
lull no no and i see that all capitals omega lull that's yeah i i know no i'm not gonna no
i'll play the surge too before i play new it's just fuck that's harsh damn that's that was harsh
hey goober juice thanks for the 250 i just want to tell you hey liar 985 want to tell you i found
scientific evidence that it is in fact safe to eat a shoe watch it and weep fella you owe
us a shoe chomping what are you gonna say pal if this is the spongebob video again i'm gonna be
really upset this is okay this is what happens when you eat a shoe i'm this is a this is like
a just a weird creepy 3d video okay i don't want to watch this this is like hurting my i don't like
this video like this video oh no i'm not gonna eat a shoe okay i'm gonna eat a comedy shoe and with
that same time same place saturday see you soon we had one more bit from the mojo poe
three bucks binge watched your best of videos when i was in japan in my hotel room
totally get your sense of humor please come to a west coast convention after corona blows over
i want to shake your hand uh twitchcon is probably the next thing that i would go to
because obviously e3 is has been canceled so that's not really on the table anymore
uh and if twitchcon is if this all is um under control by then if they don't have to cancel
twitchcon that'll be where i go next where i go but thank you um you get it you totally get it
good i'm glad you do i'm happy that you get it all right so we
are going to what we're gonna do we're gonna raid somebody raid raid he'll be right
raid raid rump pump he's making frog really okay what do you mean frogs and paint and frogs
what what is this what you got this is a clay holy shit this is pretty this is pretty good
wait neo 2 is out great wait neo 2 is already out i thought it was coming out in like 2025
i'm not playing it my hands are getting sweaty all right go say hi to grump pump
are you serious you did why would i know when neo 2 is coming out when i didn't like when i didn't
give a shit about neo 1 i said it i got it off my chest okay and when you take the bandaid off it
feels so much better uh i respect it but i don't care fuck how do i make this better how do i
make this how do i backtrack bury this there is no backtracking bury this there's no backtracking
bury on this one okay he's got to own it all right yeah i i wasn't a big fan of neo uh is it
it looks fun like no don't even forget the backtracking go say hi to grump pump she's
making frog uh grump pump is uh one of our one of our mods here uh she's also uh queen of the
discord go say hello see you guys later see you tomorrow have a great night
you