Hello. Hold on. And I had to tweet too. I had to tweet that out. That we're playing Patapon.
Hello, good afternoon. How's your day going? Is it going good? Good. He's a social media mogul.
Can't wait for social media tycoon. Started zero likes. Can you get up to 500,000 followers?
Does that exist? Does that game exist? It probably does. But yeah, I'm gonna play Patapon 2,
actually. Not just Patapon. Patapon 2. In the pre-stream chat, we had a little bit of a
vote. And I've been told that Patapon 2 is just a better version of Patapon 1
in almost every way. It's just one but better. That's what I've been told. And that's what
we're gonna do. Because look, we can always go back into the prequel. But I'm gonna give it a
shot. We'll see how it goes. We'll play for a while. See if I like it. New game? Yeah, we did.
Gotcha Force. Gotcha Force is dumb. I loved every second of it. Patapon 3 waiting room.
I heard Patapon 3 is not very good. Doesn't people say Patapon 3 is the not good one?
It's too grindy. Who made this? I saw a Japan studio pop up. What company actually made this?
Bungie. I don't know. Bungie didn't make this. Pyramid did. Pyramid Studios.
Bungie. They need to make a new Patapon. Am I gonna love this game? We're about to find out.
But right now? Am I gonna love this game? Place your bets. It's kind of already doing it for me.
Not much time has gone by and I already like it. All right, so let's do a new game. How can
I continue nothing? I'm ready. Let's go. As the ship neared completion, Patapon suddenly remembered
an old story. Almighty leader, let's sail off into the dark unknown as our search for earthen.
I didn't get to read it. Patapons bravely set off on their voyage, leaving behind their loved ones,
friends, and the safety of their home island. They braved many violent storms and sweated through
many scorching days. It was indeed a long and arduous voyage, but the brave Patapons refused
to give up. This is Patapon 1. However, all their suffering was insignificant compared to the trouble
they had. Only after 49 days and 49 nights, the Patapons truly learned of the evils that lurked
below the depths of the sea. Their fate unknown. What will become of the Patapons now? All right,
we just watched the whole, we got the whole story from Patapon 1. Patapon oath. I gotta take this.
I, hold on. I hereby pledge to honor and keep my promise to be the great leader of the Patapons
and help them reach earthen. I will not stray from my goal, even in the face of death or great
peril. Even at moments of weakness, I will keep the beat and feel the rhythm of the earth.
From this point forward, I promise to keep my pledge and take this drum of courage and be the
mighty leader I was meant to be. This is my oath. Won't you tell us your name, almighty one?
Transfer Patapon save data. Tell us your name.
Okay, well, okay, you can only do four letters. Welcome to the world of Patapon. Oh, great one.
If this is your first time playing, might we recommend you start off in the easy mode? Oh,
no. What do I do? Do I say no? Okay, how hard is Patapon? Is this a hard game?
No, say yes. Yes. If they laugh, it's extremely hard. Hardest game. Yes, it's hard. Can I,
okay, can I change the difficulty whenever I want? No. Can I, I can't change the difficulty.
Hey! Patapon. It's a kid's game. Every game is a kid's game, apparently. Oh, it's a rhythm game.
Name me a game that's not a kid's game. That you guys would, all right, I just got freaked out
because I was like, why doesn't it know my name? I just put it in. Earthen turned out to be
unreachable. The Patapon's long voyage ended as this ship sank to the bottom of the ocean. I told you.
Washed up on an unknown shore alone, Hatapon exhausts its last ounce of strength to hold
onto the sacred drum. Almighty leader, I pray to you. I'm the leader? I beg of you, please have
mercy on us, Patapons. Pon pon pon, strike the drum four times. Listen to the drum's rhythm. Pon
pon pon pon. Okay. That was cute. You got it. There are four drum beats in one measure. If you
keep to the beat for four counts, one measure, you'll perform a command. Give it a try. Hit
pon four times in a row to save the princess. This is like a turn-based RPG. Listen to that drum. I
feel it returning our power. What could it be, our mighty leader? Oh benevolent one, I always knew
you would come for us. That's why I protected the drum at all costs. Please take the drum.
I'll take it. How many drums do I get? We're going to learn about the next one.
Okay, that's pon, pata. Cool. What battery do I have in this controller? We'll find out. Almighty
leader, I pray to you. Almighty Jerry, lend your strength to the Patapon so that they may continue
their quest. Let's practice. Next, pata, pata, pata pon. Pata pon. Easy there, mighty leader.
Chillax and feel the rhythm. If you match the four beats properly. I didn't do it.
Please don't beat. Wait, what? Patapons will march for four beats. When they stop,
you got to start drumming. Oh, I haven't done it. Okay. It's four beats in one measure. Okay.
Okay. I'm going to fuck this all up, aren't I? They're going to get so hard. You're ready.
I feel like I have Pringles can. Anybody want to invite me to their band? I'm pretty good at the
Pringles. I can't read. You can read it. Too much fever. Wait, we have to fight? Do I just sit back
here and just make noise? Attack. I did it. Do you just have to keep the beat? That's going to end
up being like square, circle, triangle, triangle, triangle, triangle, square, square, square, X.
Now I'm going to fuck the whole thing up and have to quit the game. Third time, four minutes,
touching, zero, coils, none. This seems kind of cool. Patapon's march. It's easy to look at
the Patapon's location. He's always dead center. I thought it was the same place. He's always dead.
Okay. During the Pata Pata march, Hatapon will march along with the rest of the army.
During the Pon Pon attack, chant, he'll bravely maintain his position.
Uh, all right. A mysterious race that hide their face behind masks.
Medan came upon them when she went wandering on an unknown. She took Hatapon and the others
to the place she had stumbled upon. They arrived at the end of the night in the ruins of Patapon's
village, Patopolis. I gotta turn this up on my end. Almighty Jeremy, thank you for helping me out
of that disaster. You're welcome. I need to be able to hear the beat. All right. Yeah, you're
welcome. Great to see you again. I'm the priestess of the great Patapon. My name is Medan. Your
return celebration is about to start, but first please follow me. This stone obelisk is the pride
of the Patapon tribe. It shows that our ancestors once thrived in this area. If we want to reach
Earthen, do we have to retake the former Patopolis? We'll talk more later. Right now,
please head through the obelisk to go hunting for some meat to fill our stomachs.
What? I can like move around. Look, I should save. Okay, cool. Let's go hunting on Torchira
beach. Those Patophons are always hungry. Hunt some game so they can prepare some meat.
All right, let's do it. Headquarters. These are the troops. HP 120 crit ratio 15%.
Damage 4 to 12. Attack speed 2. Resist. Ignite. All right. Equip. Wooden helm. Wooden sphere.
Do they have it on? Wooden helm. Standard issue helmet. Okay, a normal Patapon. You can select
who. All right, should I give somebody hair? What's the hair do? Hairpiece worn by the lord
of a certain island country grants the user a body of steel. All right, let's do it. I love this.
There's an optimize button. Look at that stat difference. Is there a bad stat difference?
Wait, how do I equip? Lordly hairpiece. There's no stat difference. I see like a bunch of
ups or something. What's on the bottom? Just hit optimize. Optimize the squad.
Takes it off. That's resistant. I want you to wear this. Somebody can wear it. Whatever.
All right, let's go. Let's rest up. We've got a big day. Lordly hairpiece gives immunity to
all statuses. That's cool. All right, are we ready? The Patophons have the courage to fight.
It's amazing. That's the way. Guide the Yerepons to find their prey. What was it? What was it?
What was it? Wait, hold on. Tell me the forward march. I just got struck by lightning.
Okay. No, shit. What's attack? Okay, attack. What's attack? I don't remember. What was it?
What is it? What's attack? What's attack? Attack. Forward. No, not backwards. All right, attack.
Again, it hit its dead body. There's too much going on. What do we need? Shit.
We're good. I pick up two. What? Ruined. Go, go, go, go, go. Go, go, go, go, go, go.
I got three teeth. Earth end to earth end. I'm going to be really bad at this game. I just want to
make that really clear to everybody. There's going to be like five combinations eventually,
and it's going to be too much for me. It's going to get locked up and confused in my brain,
and I'm going to rage put the game in above 45. I'm glad we're seeing the credits right now.
There are only four combo. I'm just kidding.
Oh, great, Jerry. Thank you for this food that you've blessed us with. Yum. Look how our people
have come home. We're all excited over the great Jerry's return. Hooray for Jerry. Hooray for the
great Patapon. Everyone, give you thanks to Jerry. This grace has made all these blessings possible.
Great Jerry, please allow me to show the way to our altar.
Phrase. Phrase. All the collected bounty is placed on this altar as a humble offering to you,
oh great Jerry. I have to see what kind of offerings have been made. Upgrades? Are they
going to do upgrades? This is from me. Pon Pon. The bravery drum obtained by agreeing to become
the Patapon God. It's oh. The strokes drum. Okay. The song. Pat-a-pat-a-pat-a-pon. Attack.
Pon Pon Patapon, right? Legendary memory. This great warrior once fought a thousand foes.
Meat. Cafeteria meat. Okay. And then wait, there's a crafting system? A magnificent
warped fang. Shaved down to use as a weapon. Huh. Oh, all right. Do I eat this? Oh. Use it later for
materials. Oh, okay. It's used for upgrades. Oh, all right. That's cool. Can I do anything else?
Our wish is to look upon it at earth end. A's upon it for eternal bliss.
How come only two people have a piece of meat? All right. Let's go. What's next?
What did they find blocking their way? It's demons. No, it's the Karmic.
All right. So wait, can I use the like anything new? Can't use the fangs. Let's just go.
Let's rest up. We got a big day tomorrow. Okay. Here we go. One, two, three, and then
will we start? Here we go. Wait, we just start. Now. Attack. Get it. Take it down.
Time it. Kill it. Get up there. Wait, it won't crumble. Well, why? Do we have to go home
because we're not strong enough? Oh, okay. Can I pause this? You guys are getting a
delay because people think I'm missing the beat. I think there's a delay because I'm doing it
right. Um, how do I, I gotta, I gotta change this. There's a delay on here. See if this fixes it.
For a rhythm game, you guys shouldn't have a delay. Is it better? Better? Okay. Don't kill him.
My kind of known as Tetipon. We will join you. Okay. Victory. Let's go. Do I have a new beat now?
Attack. Holy shit. Oh God. Oh God. Go forward. Go, go, go. Can I lose the fever? Get in there.
Kill him. All right. Forward, forward, forward, forward. Oh shit. Get this tower.
Get him. All right. Forward. Kill. Shit. I thought I was going to be alive.
Is that a spell? I don't think you have any trouble. What? Wait, come with us. What?
Can we stop singing? Dude, I'm telling you, reading this shit. Okay. Reading and like pressing these
buttons is impossible for me. See you later. Mighty Jarrah. Okay. Just go get it. It's a,
it's scratching your head and rumbly belly at the same time. Kill it. You're good. It's literally
two buttons. All right. Well, I just looked at chat to read what you said. Uh, just rub head
and circle belly. If you land perfect beats, you can get fever twice as fast. Okay. All right.
You'll be constantly acquiring new weapons and helmets. Don't forget to equip them. They'll
raise stats like HP and attack power and can become the key to victory. Always use triangle
and optimize your Patapon's shoes. Sure. A great warrior, Pan Patapon is a legendary hero.
He'll be the one that restores a master sprout to full glory. Great, Jerry. If you could please
follow me, I must show you something. We need Mater Sprout to return Mater to the Tree of Life
back to life. This must be done. There are rumors of Dodongo is here. The Dodongo ruins
just past Nanjaro Hill. Defeat Dodongo and return the Mater Sprout. These are all made up words.
Okay. Oh yeah. I can't believe you can't pronounce a Mater. These are all made up fucking words.
It's the guy. What's the guy from Cards? What are you talking about? Cards2fan can't pronounce
Mater. Wait, somebody said, so there's one person that was nice to me. What does it say? Don't feel
bad about missing the pattern up. You'll get used to it. Wow. A C and a C of, of just, of thank you.
Wow. I mean, I'm so happy to hear that. Holy shit. I thank you. You, I thank you. Wow. I feel great.
All right. What do we get? Common stone full of impurities, but vital nevertheless.
Oh, there's a shield. What is this? Key item. And that guy is feeding his ego.
All right. I want to make some items. All right. In search of the Mater Sprout and the rumor
Dodongo that is said to be roaming around these parts. Unbeknownst to all, a destined meeting is
about to take place. Here we go. Let's equip and should we just do optimize? Oh, iron spear. You
have an iron spear. Damage six to 16. All right. Well, yeah, that's good. And switch. I want you in
the front then. Oh, somebody in the back. I don't have, I don't have a bow. All right. Well, I'm,
I mean, he has an iron now, but I got one. How do I, how do I put it on? Can't make new units yet.
Oh, well, whatever. All right. Let's, let's go. Groups ready. All right. I'm going to get it.
That one person. I don't worry about messing up the patterns. You're like going to get rid of,
you'll get it. See? Oh, let's go. That person was just, did it. There we go. Oh, you're missing.
Get it. What are they doing? What's wrong? Attack it. Why are you jumping? Why are they jumping
higher? What happened? It's a drum solo. Get over it, Patipont. I'm fucking God. I could do what I
want. Oh, we got a triangle now. Oh, mighty leader. Can you hear me? Time for you to learn a third
song. The chaka chaka song. This is the lament of defense. Used to get out of tough spots.
How is it? What does it do? How do I do it? How do I do it? Oh, fuck. What does it do? Defense?
Move. I forget it. I forget it. I don't know what it is. Kill. This? Attack it?
Split it. All right. Now defense. Go forward. What? Oh, hit him. Did I block it?
What is this? No, back up, back up, back up. All right. Attack. Kill him. Wait, defense.
What? Why did they put the hat on that guy? Kill it. No, no, no, no, no. Don't go forward.
I forget the controls. Defense. I fucked it up. Okay. Bro. Oh, I did it. Sounds like the minions.
Somebody just lost a shitload of money. Heading on the fact that I wasn't going to figure out
how to do that. I gave a certain. I gave a C with certain. You put like 500 fucking thousand
dollars on that. It's like, what a certain play that is. And you just lost a ton of money.
And in a way, I feel bad for you. Here, you bet against me though. All right. If you perfectly
time all four beats, you'll hear Crystal's ding. Okay, cool. Rack up enough perfect beats and
combo points during fever mode to set off the hero mode. He'll perform unnatural acts of bravery
and might depending on his class. All right, that's cool. Jeremy, we finally found the chosen
one. Chosen one, huh? Don't make me laugh. I heard it's an old legend. Funny looking mask dude
will save the world after meeting Jera the great pattern. Funny looking. Great Jera, what should
we call this strange masked fellow? Call me? You're going to name me? Oh, you must be insane. In the
membrane.
Hera is a very nice name. I love it. Hera. I guess Hera it is. I like I have a choice.
It's Jera, right? Here's the deal. I must obey the one that names me, which means you.
Oh, great Jera and brave Hera, please come this way. This is the Parajet Prime. Only Jera and
Hera can enter. You have a mysterious egg. You can interact with heroes from other worlds.
You can't run a mysterious egg, so don't worry as they pat upon. Do you really care about naming
them? Let's check it out. I was going to just press enter. I was going to just press enter
when you're on hero. All right, let's go in here. Please don't forget the Mater Sprout. We needed to
succeed, but you are the chosen one. You can teleport to another world. Okay, that's cool.
Should we do that here? Wait, who are these people? Formation. Dodongo Egg One.
Mysterious egg that leads you to battle with Dodongo grants Demerian's power. He Lord of
Halon and Fire Tardens. Okay, what do I do with it? Iron Spear. Ooh, what's this thing? Friendship
Spear. Raises HP. Friendship Helm. Wow, and a Shuba. Okay, what's this normal? All right,
Friendship Spear and Friendship Helm. I can't touch these people, right? Boy,
are you sure you want to engage? Yeah. Wait, what is going on? Going to another world with four heroes?
Wait, what? Wait, what? Oh, shit, hold on. All right, now block. He's gonna do it. He's gonna do it.
Kill. Forward. No, go again. Defend. Forward. Forward. Here we go.
Attack. Attack again. Attack again. Get it. Oh, wait, what? The boss fight?
All right, now. No, don't do that. Now attack. Spears. Throw. Forward.
Karla? Karla. Subs? Holy shit. Come on. A lot of subs came in. That's a lot. That's a lot of subs. A
hundred subs. From Zyxia. Thanks for the fucking hundred community subs. That's so many. Wait,
we're not getting out. Kill them. A hundred community subs. Holy shit. Thank you for that.
I think there's gonna be an insane amount of subs. Look at those coins. Where'd you get those coins?
Oh, shit. Kevon's dead. We got him. I revived him. Attack. Shit. Too much. Too much.
All right, now go forward. He's running. Shit, he's not running. Oops, I forgot. Oh, fuck. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Kill him. He's looking kind of fucking grim. Okay, he's running away.
Pick it up. What does this do with this? Is this like a slot? Timing's way off. It's not.
I mean, it was right there. Look, there's a delay. There's a desync that I can't.
Just hold on a second. Oh, there's a time limit on this. This guy's not strong enough.
Are they strong enough for this?
Kill. Kill him. Oh, fuck. That guy got like yeeted the fuck out of here. Is he gone? He's dead.
All right, run. Get to the end quick. Yes. The drum in time with the rhythm. What? Oh, what?
This is like wrong. Now everyone come together. It's time for the big finish.
I did it. One last time. I got him. Oh, it's copyright. No, no, this is not fucking copyright.
God damn it. I'll see you guys later. Fuck. I'm out. How was I supposed to know this fucking
whole game was copyrighted? What the fuck? That's how they do it to me. Oh, there's a treasure
chest. Wait, how much does it cost? 60? Shit. I got adamantium. Okay, hold on. Do you want to
change Parachari into Kaching and return to Patopolis? Like I just opened up like my
teenager's phone and looking at text messages and I don't know what these things mean.
What is he saying when he's talking to his friend? Do I want to change Parachari into Kaching?
Yes, I think. Quite 130 Kaching. I don't know what that does. What is it? All right.
There's a delay on the fucking stupid ass thing. Try to fix it. It's ruined. The Pata Gate is a
portal that connects fragments from other Patapon worlds. There's a distinct beat that permeates
throughout this realm. Listen closely to its rhythm. Don Shin Kenhai. Success will only be
achieved if all hero Patapons follow this special rhythm. I thought I turned off my Discord
notifications. Don't call me. A hundred community subs from Zyxia. I want to make sure I address
it because that's a fucking ton of money. That's $500 that they just dropped. Be able to buy those.
Thanks. That's fucking insane. Thank you.
We cut the dinosaur's head off?
That's a hundred Little Caesar's pizzas. I mean, yeah, I guess it is. All right. So that was like
a little encounter. Oh, this is this game's pretty cute. This is a cool game. All right.
We got all this other stuff. Life Seed is hidden somewhere in the Ancient Ruins. Defeat the Dodonga
at the Dodonga. Defeat the Dodonga at the Dongara Ruins. Oh, this is the sprout. Okay. Here we go.
Let's do some equipment. Let's do some optimization. Iron Spear is wooden helm. Iron
helm. Oh, I got an iron helm. It's a lordly hair piece. No, I don't have any more iron helms.
Yeah. Put on that funny hair. But you. Friendship Spear. Yeah. Friendship helm. That's all I got.
The funny hair. Oh, no, no, no. All right. I think I'm ready. A bunch of iron helms.
They're all not wearing them. Oh, oh, oh, oh. You can change the Masked Dude's class.
Hero Mask of Phantom Strike. I don't think I can do a. Oh, just go. Let's rest up. We got a big day.
Oh, it can't be offbeat. I wouldn't have a fever right now. I just defended. Are we all right? Oh,
shit. Blocked it. Broke. Blocked. Good. What? We're dead. Wait, what? Does defend not happen
until after they sing it? Because I defended it and then he hit me. But it wasn't ready. Do
they have to sing it first? I was like when I when I do defend don't don't don't don't
they have to does it take one was too low? Why they all leave? Nobody think I'm cool anymore.
Oh, this guy's not we're just guy didn't die. I didn't like that. We're gone. New God. They
defend right when the beat finishes. OK, try again. How long does it defend last?
One of those things that's like, oh, it's like two seconds or three seconds. There's the next bar.
Unturned. OK. Now we go. Did it.
We just got struck by fucking lightning. How do you get back? Is it like a go back command?
What's like the go back command? What is it? I don't have that yet. Oh, wait, what?
Oh, wait, am I supposed to be here? I think I did it. What's with the lightning?
Oh, sorry. I defend. We're going to start for fucking lightning again.
Don't don't come on. Get the fuck out of here. Back up, June.
Back up. I need the guy. I need that fucking funny hat on. What the fuck? This is the armor.
I have iron armor on. Is that the problem? Well, we're dead again.
But the lightning is just destroying me. All right. Well, I got to get like lightning
resistant. I have to go back and grind. Wait, I can do that. I have to play other. Wait, hold on.
What? Oh, it's not just play the game. I have to go back and like and like grind for items.
I got to grind. Hold on. Let me go look at my stuff. You're offbeat. I'm.
I can't get fevers consistent. You're not. And I have a shitty Elgato. You are offbeat.
How do I get fevers then? That doesn't make sense. All right. So why does fever appear on screen?
What are we talking about? Pity fevers. Can we go over this right now?
Is there a delay when I'm selecting these? You guys have seen a delay. You have to be.
We're not. What? The drums sound different. What? Just just emulated. I'm going to try this. No,
let's see what they have for equipment. What about with my resistance? This guy has a hat on.
Iron helm. Wait, was that person lying to me or does this actually conduct electricity with
lightning? We need gas lighting and we almost got him. Oh, you do. It happened like 20 minutes ago.
He almost got him. Let me try this again. I can't have any other gear. If I don't do
this now, I'm going to go back and get better stuff. Here we go. Here we go. Fuck. Fuck. Attack.
Call it. Where is he? But you guys talk about perfect. Perfect every time. What?
You got to get perfect. If you don't hear the cymbal, then don't play the video game.
I forgot. Didn't break combo all the entire game, but didn't get it perfect every time. Why even
why even load the video game in the first place? I mean, what the hell? Load up a fucking robot to
make every press perfect. You fucking stupid. I did it. Am I on easy? No. Keep to the rhythm
for a few counts and score multiple combo points. Soon you'll be in fever mode. When the Patapons
are in fever mode, their attack and defense skills increase dramatically. Cool. Yeah. What's the next
paragraph say? Oh, if you don't get perfect every time uninstall this game. Oh, is that what it's
trying? I can't see. Can I zoom in? Does it say that anywhere? Where does it say that? I'm just
trying to find where that says that. It's you have to scroll. Oh shit. I'm sorry. I didn't scroll.
Roll down. You guys are fucked. All right, let's go. Awakening from the sleep that has
overtaken your roots. Oh, we had huge money. Hold on. Throw away 985. Thanks for 50 dollars.
Thanks for the huge money. Throw away 985. Thank you so much. They say, hey,
Jerma have bits. I'm not letting the government have this money. Chat are paid actors. Top
Donators are your gambling addiction fencing money. I know the truth. Stay safe and marry the McChicken
Queen already. Are you guys like paid actors? Is somebody you guys just get getting paid from
somebody to come and like tell me that I can't get perfect every time. Somebody's gonna be paying you.
It seems like too much work. Are they right? Wait, you guys aren't getting paid.
Wait, are you getting paid? Who's getting paid? I'm not a livered shea.
Oh, let's see. Legendary memory. 286 Ka-ching. This is where I get another person. Wait,
confirm. So these are my slots. Hey, Kazzy. Thanks for the five subs, Kazzy. Five community subs.
Just dropped him right now. Thank you. So should I get a tate pond? Normal. Pollution map.
Pateria meat. Okay, I can only do this. Create normal, a normal pat-a-pon. It's one meat,
one stone, and 12 dollars. Pio Pio. Pio Pio. Hard iron. Okay, tender meat. These extra large
size pat-a-pons are great against knockback. Resistance gets cold but weak against fire.
Should I get another one? Should I just get two? Or should I get another yary pond?
Should I just fill it up? Whoa. Is that your TV to game mode? I'm not on a TV.
It's always so funny going to somebody's house that had that shit where there was like a full
half second input delay and they didn't even know it existed. And you sit there and you grab
the controller or you try to do something, you're like, holy shit. And then you change it and they're
like, what did you do? This doesn't feel right anymore. What the fuck? It's like, dude, you have...
Okay, let's get another one. Here we go. We're going to plant another person. Here they come.
Okay, let's do another one. I got money, right? Wait, what's this? Oh, it's it.
So I have three yary ponds and three pat-a-pons. Should I just fill it up?
No stones. Oh, I don't have any more stones. Shit. Yeah, well, I have three guys now.
Master will surely be of use to you. Mater, whatever it is.
I got like, can I... Look at all this stuff. New shields. All right, I got some new stuff.
I got to look. All right, well, here we are. Carmen fortress. Did you use the tree of life
to befriend some tatypons? Time has come to rally the pat-a-pons and head out for earthen.
All right, so where's my... Where's my tatypons? Oh, right. There they are. What do they got?
Optimize. Whoa. Friendship sword, wooden helm, and friendship shield. Steel shield.
Pin axe. What's a friendship sword do? Oh, raise HP. Is HP at now 300 versus 200? That's pretty good.
Okay. What about you guys? Optimize. It always takes the hat off. What about you? Optimize. Glass.
Evolve to yary pond. Evolve to tatypon. Special move. Energy... Hold on. The iron fist causes
damage over a wide area. Effective against enemy structures and any enemy nearby. Energy field.
Surround all pat-a-pons in an impermeable protective shield. A major drawback is that
the shield will limit the troops' attack abilities. Dammit. Iron fist. Let's do this one. Does it work?
Evolve to yary pond. He already is a yary pond. Oh. All right. Let's move out. Shuba duba doo.
Here we go. The pat-a-pons are here. One, two, three, four. How do you do his move?
Oops. Get off. All right. Now attack. I forgot it. The coins. Bow. Bow and arrow guy. Go forward.
Here we go. You're not a gamer. Forward. Forward. And... I think Carmen? Forward. I don't understand.
Oh, this is not correct. None of your commands are on beat. That doesn't make any sense.
Somebody said it's getting old, chat. Well, just leave him. Oh. Two consecutive beats takes it. Oh,
okay. All right. Sorry, sweetie. The PS4 remaster has a slight audio delay. That's why it's not
on beat. You notice that sometimes the pat-a-pons sound different. That means it's on beat.
Wait, the PS4 remaster has an audio delay? Am I being lied to? It's real. It's true? As a germ...
I'm seeing a lot of one guy say it's real. Oh, who cares? It is real. Google it. What? What?
Pat-a-pon 2 remaster audio delay? Why did I put... I put an ex... I put like a... I asked a question.
Ironically, the first pat-a-pon remaster also had this delay issue and it hasn't been fixed
despite pat-a-pon 2 remaster launching nearly three years later. You'll need to play with
headphones to eliminate the sound lag that's introduced between the controller and the TV.
What? This shit is real. Wait, what? Oh, no. This is bad. It's pulling through a capture card,
so it's always going to be bad. It's always going to be fucked up. I don't think I'm ever going to
get it right. It didn't fix the input delay for pat-a-pon 2. Hold on. It was unplayable in the
first pat-a-pon on PS4. And to be honest, it's a little better on this one. We still have to
really be sharp when playing the songs. I was expecting some kind of calibration system like
in Guitar Hero. The real problem is the controller has a big input delay because of the wireless that
happens to almost any Bluetooth device. Try watching a movie on a Bluetooth speaker.
Wait, what? I tried playing with a metronome at 120 beats per minute, which is the beat of pat-a-pon.
Metronome. 120 beats per minute? Is this going to work? Let me see if I can... I
can't hear both of them at the same time though. Why are you playing on the capture card? Do you
have any idea how streaming works? Do I have to actually answer this? Wait, how do you think you're
seeing the video game? I'm using telepathy to give you this on the screen? I'm delayed by 650
milliseconds because I'm going through the capture card. Yeah, this is not going to work because I
have to delay this by 650 milliseconds for you to even hear it. All right, so just do it earlier
is what the goal is. This proves I apparently have to hit it like a quarter of a second earlier than I
am. Later? Let me try that theory. Do it earlier. Let's just try this out. Let's just go to like
fucking level one. See, I'm just going to level one. Let me get this right. Okay, let's deploy.
Set it to easy? Hold on. Let's just see. Just do easy mode. So earlier. Later?
So it's slower? Okay, hold on. No. Okay, here's how I'm doing it. No, it's not working. Nevermind.
It's slower. What the hell are you saying? It makes no sense. It would be delayed for us a .u.
Uh, will you hear what we just talked about? Oh, this is like a game issue.
You, we all welcome. Hi. Let me, I wish I could hear this. It's playable. It's just you stressing
over nothing. Yeah, I kind of don't give a shit. I'm just gonna play the game. I'm just gonna play
like whatever. Who cares? I'm not gonna, it's not gonna be perfect. It's not gonna be perfect.
Game was remastered like shit. What do you want me to say? Okay, wait, wait, wait. I can make other
characters. There, yes. How much do they cost? Okay, I can make another one. Here they come.
Here it comes. Do you not split? I'm not. I play on a monitor. I capture it through OBS and I'm
playing the game captured on my monitor. I'm not playing on the OBS window. Turn the volume up and
then down. I'm going to play the game. What are you talking about? Oh, shit. That's cool.
One, two, three.
What? Where is he?
Is that like a boss? I got this little tower. Get that gore. All right, go for it. All right, now go in.
Okay. Walk. The fire is killing us. Walk. I'm a gamer. What? Get in. Oh, shit. I'm destroyed.
Oh, shit. I'm fucking dead.
Keep going. I'm trying. They got a lot more people than I do. I don't get it, man. I got to like,
I don't know.
You guys are not even very good. I'm losing too many people. All right, now go forward.
This game, I'm tired of dancing. Oh, I'm trying to do it later. Oh, I got pulled the line.
What happens when Jerma smokes DMT? What? I only got like two guys left. I'm dead. Maybe not. Oh,
he's dead. All right, go in. No, fuck. Protect that guy. Do something. Go. Do it. Yeah.
Many casualties. Hey, I still won. The Zigotan hero, Gong the Hawkeye, appeared as the Patapon's
rival in the first game. Spoilers. Thanks a lot. He fought for the Zigotan queen,
Karma, to stop the Patapon's invasion of his land. He went two to two against the Patapons,
but they fucking killed him. What if it burns one's eyes? Our scouts have looked at a giant
monchichi on the Sutton Plains. Gong might be a problem, but Medan will be way whatever.
I want to make a new guy. I need a bone. Shit. Plumps of grass. Okay. This guy drops bones.
Wait, should I go in here? Can I make other units? How many people can you have in one squad?
Oh, I can make these. Wait, hold on. I can make a Pio Pio. Should I make a Pio Pio?
This is against cold chills. There's a lot of fire units. I feel like it's probably better to make
another one. Maybe another Patapon. I'm gonna make another Patapon. Go look at the crew. Build
the squads out first. Yeah. What is this? Oh, we almost got a full squad. Steel helm, steel helm.
Still have wooden spears. What the fuck is this bullshit? Friendship bow, iron bow. Does the iron
bow do more damage? No, it does not. Am I not upgrading? I don't know. Should I save the
resources or should I just start upgrading people? Let's go like Yarra Pond. I can do this, but I
can't do this one. What about the other guys? Like what are these dudes? Yeah, I'm on a full squad
first. Can I afford another one of these here? No. So now I got six six. I wonder if this will be
good. Let's see if this works. Game lags after I open a menu. This game's just full of problems
tonight, huh? What about you? Do you still have stuff? What can you do? Friendship spear, friendship
helm. What's this? Oh, the hairpiece. No. This is so much. I have so many more units. Let's do it.
Let's go. This is going to be the only Patapon stream. You don't know that yet.
Bad guys. Oh, shit. I've killed you. Holy shit. All right. Defend. No, never mind.
Phone. Get in there. Even go in. What? Just beat him. Is this the only Patapon 2 streamer?
I don't know. I like this game. This game's fucking really, really fun. I really like it.
It's very fun. If I have to deal with a bad port, I'll deal with a bad port. It's still fun.
I still like it. It isn't a bad port. Imagine playing this on a cartridge. He won't emulate
I don't know. I don't know a DS emulator. I don't know where the fuck we can get one of those.
PSP emulator. Look, when I bought the remaster, how was I supposed to know there was like audio
input problems? How am I supposed to know that? Can I even kill this thing? It's running.
Easy. I will. I will after this. Do I have to negate some of the grinding? Is that what it does?
Jesus. Kill. Block. I got like a rare bone. Monster hunter.
Block. I thought he was going to wait a turn. He's going back. He's backing up.
All right. Block. Block. I got him. He's playing on hard. Isn't this on normal?
I got it.
Possible lose their stance and easily stagger once their HP is low.
If an item has dizzy staggered bosses have a tendency to drop items.
Is that where I got the red one from? I got a red item. All right. Let's see. I want to see what I
got. Dodeca bone. A large bone from the carcass of a large beast. These huge bones are often
used in the central pillars in homes. How do I put this on easy? Will that actually help with the
input stuff? Back to the title screen. Let's go back to the title screen. Levels like normal.
All right. Wait, speak. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. It's a documented issue.
You can't look at that and make fun of me. It's not fair. It's a documented issue.
Should I try the headphones thing? Headphones. Let me see if that helps.
Let's test it because maybe it was on speakers and maybe that's fucked up. I don't know.
It didn't save. Yeah, it did. Here we go. Ready? Same exact problem.
I have both headphones in. Let me try it. Let's put it on easy and see what happens.
He failed. Yeah. Sometimes you fail. What the fuck do I care?
All right. Here we go. I did get some new stuff, though. Hold on.
Friendship sword. I didn't get anything else. Wooden helm.
What do you got? Do one of you guys in the middle put the hair on?
I've got a bunch of materials. Can I not? Do I have to craft them or something?
No bullies, please. Let's see. What can I do? Level two. Two more stones and two more fangs.
Hey, Ben, thanks for the five community subs. Ben Elnor. Appreciate it. Thanks a lot.
Thank you, Ben. Upgrade the hero. How do you upgrade the hero?
Oh, we can do this now, right? Heroes inherit upgrades from anyone in the class. Oh, okay.
Questions eight. Should I go for this? Do I? I hope I don't lose out on this.
Don't waste your time with this. Change the egg. Change the egg. All right. Level two.
Mysterious egg that leads you to battle with Chichi. Grants gas hanger his power.
That's right. This is how you get better masks. All right. What's going on? Okay, I get it.
I'm like, I don't think it matters. No, it doesn't matter. This mode is always in normal.
Oh, okay. I thought he was going to attack. Yep. No.
Let's see what happens on easy if it fixes the issue.
It's emulated. Go ahead and get it on PSP. Failed. Wait, what? How? I was walking forward.
Read. I was too busy getting angry at the fact that the input works now.
How do you fail a cut scene? I'm not even looking at the screen. All right. Listen up.
Oh, it was failing for views. All right. Let's get perfect literally every fucking single time
I do this now. This window is a little bigger. This fixes the goddamn... I'm not going to get
angry about this. Let's go. Get in there. Get that thing. Kill it. Kill. Whoa. What was that?
It just gave me a new thing to do. Wait, what? Can I do it now?
I have to do it while it happens. Wait, I have to do it when that pops up.
I thought it was like teaching me a new move. Yeah, I want to get the resource.
This is way... The window is way better now. Let's do it again. You know they have X or
circle or whatever. So the idea is you grind out levels to get materials to make you guys better
to do the later level. Okay, I get it. All right. This time I got to do the beat that pops up on
that scroll. Forward. Where's that crab? Here we go. Okay. Here it comes. How do I do that?
Be closer? Square, triangle, square. It's not working. Square, triangle, square. What?
When I hit triangle, it says no. Press it. I did. Fail the rhythm. That's normal. Wait,
did I do it? I don't need to do it with the rhythm. I thought I had to do it with the rhythm.
I got too close to the totem. Cancel's combos would just do it.
I guess I'm gonna do it again. I need the materials anyway. Okay, so...
Okay, so when I see that pole to the beat, just do it. It doesn't matter. Even if it doesn't do
anything, just have to press it to the rhythm. I feel like I was trying to do that, but even if
they go, uh-oh, like, yo, that was wrong, just do it. It's not a real command. It's a pad upon.
Just push through and keep on beat. Oh, okay. I'll try it again. Do it as soon as you see the totem.
Do it four times in a row. Okay. Forward, forward, forward, forward. Where's that pole?
Forward, forward, forward. Where's that pole? I can't see what it said.
Square, triangle, what is it? Square, triangle, square, triangle.
What? I have to be closer? I thought it didn't matter. Okay. Oh, fucking god damn it.
Thanks for the key. Bye. This game's confusing my cat. What is your cat watching?
Why is he kept watching? He should be sleeping and eating like cat food.
They're too close to the screen. Tell him to back up. A ching are golden coins that shine
like newborn stars. Their glimmer of energy come from the life force they possess. Wow.
Each coin is a pad upon's life energy, so it's a soul.
Life coins. Uh, Ben coming in with five more community subs. Thanks, Ben. Another five from
Ben. Thank you fucking Ben Elnor. Thanks a lot, dude. Let's get more. More critters. More creatures.
Yeah. Wait, can I do more? He's demanding more money. More. I demand more. In the game,
of course. Okay, so now I have the thing. Let's go. Everybody's nice and locked and loaded.
How about you guys? Optimize. Yes. Okay. Go beat the shit out of this guy.
Whip it, you fool. What? Wait, that's not just like a key item? Okay. Who holds it? You?
Oh. Goes into the slot over here. Okay. $100 in bits from Vilemi. Thanks for the 10,000 bits,
Vilemi. That's fucking crazy. Thank you for the- it's a lot of money. It's a lot of money to give
somebody. Thank you. Jeremiah, I only have so much money to give you. Don't give any more.
Keep it for you. It's your money and you need it now. Don't worry about giving me money. You've
given me an insane amount of money. Don't worry about that. Thank you for the huge, huge drop.
$877 cash now. $877 cash now. You have an annuity and you need cash now. $877 cash now. $877 cash
now. It's- it helps. It's 120 beats per minute. Wait, here's the- don don do don.
Oh, great Patapon, can you hear me? Your eyeball army will melt if they continue to
trap these barren lands without some juju. They'll first turn to black puddles and then
evaporate. Use your juju powers. I'll give you a quick lesson on how to use the secrets of the
rain juju. In order to get your juju going, we first need to reach fever mode. Okay. Yes.
Once you enter in fever, hit x, x, x, x, x, don, do don, do don. When the juju dance begins,
listen carefully to the Patapon song and hit the drum to the rhythm. Okay. We need to do-
I have to be in preview.
You did it. Rain will help you cool off and it also has other secret property. Use it to
flush out Centura, a beast only visible when it rains. Okay, this is the beast.
Good job, Patathons. Play the game in mute mode.
Sorry, a fucking ghost just came out of me. I had to put it in a bottle.
I just had to spit it into a bottle. Ice shield. Wind currents will always affect your defense,
attack, and hunting strategies. It should always factor in the direction when planning your
adventures. This is- wait, this is- was it golf? All it takes is a careful eye and you'll notice
the change in wind direction. Sometimes it will blow left, stop, and then blow right. Do you
notice the pattern? Is that- oh, there's a wind? Nice golf reference.
Patathons report an invisible monster in the bouyayan basin.
Great, Jerry. Could this be the Centura creature? It's time to put the rain juju to good use.
Should I level- no. Fill it up. Where can I get fangs?
Be shaved down to use as a weapon. I guess I gotta go hunting.
One more level two. Sorry, I'm gonna go hunting for level two. I'm gonna go get fangs.
That sounds like a good idea. Centura drops fangs. Oh, okay. Wicked axe.
Okay, we need to use the gong. All right, here we go. Everybody's optimized. Ice.
Ooh, what'd you get? What's that? Ice shield. Oh, wait, wait, somebody has an ice shield.
Well, I want to see what it does. Counter- counteracts flame attacks.
Nice. Should I give friendship spear and the shuba? Let's go. Is there any reason why you're
starting at midnight EU? Because I live in the United States of America on the west coast all
the way at the end. You live in Alaska? That's not the end. That's a different- that's up in Canada.
We just like- we just like stole it one day. Okay, ready? It's time to do it.
Wind. Heed my call. All right, now is it gonna rain? All right, now we
go in there, right? Attack. All right, let's go. Block. Get in there. Defend. Yeah. Say it.
That's not a giant. That's a- that's like a slug coming up. I can't- that's hard. I have to
pay attention. Sorry, I can't. Get in there. Yes. Okay, guys, I got one core. Okay, this core
is like 12 gigahertz, but it can only do one task. You guys got like dual and quad cores.
Not me. I got one fucking core that just has a lot of computational power. And that's it.
I can't- I can't. Streamer has a pre-built brain. Don't.
Pre-built. That's fucking hilarious. Oops, I screwed it up. Okay, if you had one-
oh, the computer hung up for a second. I opened up Firefox. Okay. Oh, it's- hold on, hold on.
Come on. Get over here. Attack. And this is where we go. Defend, defend. Do it. Defend.
Defend. Do it. Defend. Attack. Attack. Attack. Attack.
Put forward. March it forward. Let me see that. Defend. Defend. Put it on. Defend.
Do it. Defend. Defend. Put it on. Defend. Attack. Force it. Attack. Force. Attack. Motherfucker.
Motherfucker. I did it wrong. One core. Fringe. Ban that person for life. Give me that. Give me
that. Get it. Okay, here comes the- defense. Put it on. Defense. Shut up. Pre-built brain.
And I'm way too expensive. I like like caviar and shit. I'm a pre-built PC.
Like you could go to the- you could go to like McDonald's and get a dinner for-
oh, I'm pre-built fucking single PCPU core brain. Yeah, there's a joke. I can't even do it.
A single fucking PCPU brain. After the boss, I'll tell it. The wind is strong. Get in closer.
Wait. He's dead. And I got an egg. I can't believe I got an egg. All right. So what was I saying?
Oh, yeah. Okay. You can get like- you can go buy like a- you could go get like a bologna
and cheese sandwich from the fucking grocery store. But I go and get a fucking bologna and
cheese sandwich from like this expensive restaurant. It's the same exact thing,
but I pay $400 for it. And by the way, I'm from outer space. I fly around in a spaceship in outer
space. That makes me some kind of a creature and an outer space being. And I like to wear clothes.
I like to put on clothes. I like to put on clothes. I like to put them on. I like to put them on.
XL size Patapods. The face cam has been on the whole time. Good. I hope you saw my fucking-
Okay. I'm going to turn it back. Maybe I should get a
Bioko. Can I get an extra large Bioko? I'm going to get one. I'm going to evolve into a Bioko.
Not for an archer. Oh yeah. One of these guys. A shield Bioko. Do I do a level two Bioko?
Dude, let's just make a level two Bioko. Nice. Holy shit. This game. Good. Whoa. Do another level one.
Do another level one Bioko. Holy shit. All right. Let's do another level one Bioko.
An archer. Cool. All right. Cool. And then I can make stuff.
Battle at Mount Gonroth. I worry your spirit is more important than orders. My ancestors
would be ashamed if I never crossed swords with you. What does that even mean? This game is
fucking terrible. What the fuck, dude? I'm just fucking kidding this guy. You think I would still
play this if I didn't think it was fun? Didn't I get another one of these guys?
Evolve to Yummy Pond. Blazing fast volley of arrows. Yeah. Wooden bow. Excuse me. We need to take a bow
from one of you guys. Give me this good one. Fire bow. Excuse me. You can take a fucking
goddamn wooden bow. Give that to the leader. Played gotcha for us. I was just kidding.
I did that because I was just making you have a reaction. Hey, you guys do it to me all the time.
I can't do it back. Here we go. Long is not our enemy. Our real opponents are those masked fools.
No, damn it, Pond. Urk. Oh, I've been waiting for you, Supreme Patapon.
You can't even beat me. You won't have a chance of beating them.
Prove your might. Give me all you got. Eye of the tiger. Okay, fine. Fine. Let's eat this shit.
Rain song. It's already raining. So now we'll get on their eyes and shit. Two rain. Double rain.
Get in there. Only offense. No defense. No. Volley. Volley. It worked. I got rid of the lightning.
Did it work? Get him. We're good. I guess I get six. That guy just got... Okay, I was gonna say.
Forward. Forward. Forward. Get in there. Now... Oops, I was... Why did I look at chat? I don't know why.
Peace out. Get in. Defend. Defend. Get in there. Defend. Again. Good. Come on. Get the guys in the back.
Attack. Kill them. Forward. Forward. Forward again. Attack. Yes.
Yes. Oh, hero sucks. It's all right. He's doing okay. What's that? A surprise attack?
Who's doing this? What? What? Who's winning? Won't cause you any more trouble.
If you wish to learn the truth, just look at the skies.
Oh, I thought you said... You can't do a timeout. What? I can't believe you guys used a timeout.
I got a lot of stuff. All right. Get in there. World ruler. That's me. Defend.
Iron helm. Get the lightning off. Oh, you mean...
Man, that person for a year. Stop. Oh, no. What's going on?
Hold on. I need a break. I need a break. Mommy, I need a break. You know, the problem is
it's really dark in my room right now. It's getting dark out. The light's not on. Hammers.
Like, look. I can't think because it's dark. Well, it's really dark.
Just look at how dark it is. It's fucking dark in here. All right. I'm going to go take a piss.
I'll be right back. I have returned. I'm ready to play more Patapon.
Yeah, I know. It's a scary image. Okay. What do you want me to tell you? It's a scary face. Yeah,
I know. I got it. Mom, they're making me look bad. Mom, they're making me look bad.
Call their parents. You have to call their parents now. All right. Let's go.
Turn of resigns. Okay. Let's keep going. I didn't even turn the fucking light on.
Shit. Have I ever eaten two pounds of yogurt in one sitting? I don't think that this is an
odd thing to admit. I didn't think so. All right. Let's go. The real threat of the Carmen. It's not
just a dirty way of doing things. It's hard to forgive. Ace opponent for eternity. I'm going to
play these guys. Should I make this? The guys with the spears, should they make them bigger?
Pick up, make up. Yo, yo, get up. Yo, yo. I need things for that. That was just,
it was incredibly satisfying. Had to watch the whole thing.
Build the, kill Centura again. Ooh, that's not a bad idea. Yeah. Let's go kill that character again.
I love that sword. Yes. All some more level two. I was going to scream. I guess
let's go. Let's just go kill Centura. What's my millionaire streamer up to today? Oh, you know,
withdrawing a thousand dollars from the bank in ones and counting it. I knew it.
Why would you ever do something like that? I don't know. Why would you? You wouldn't.
Yeah.
Germa sucks. Thanks for the five community subs. Thanks for the sub. And get in.
It is actually very fun. A blocker. It really is Monster Hunter, isn't it?
Oh, just with a bunch of little guys.
Oh, is that a golden fang? Yeah.
Hooray. Second highest tier fang. Nice. Demon fang, huh? Cool. All right. So. Oh, what?
Oh, I just shook the chills a little bit. I'm going to upgrade some of the bows.
Still need a fang for you. Because big spear guy. Oh, I can. I can level it up too. Whoa,
wait, I can make a Wanda. A rare pawn whose attack power increases gradually as he levels up. His
stagger rate is 20 percent. He's easy to put to sleep. And then do Wanda level two. I think I'm
going to do it. Wanda level two. What's down here? Whoa. Chig Yobi. This rare pawn's attack abilities
like critical. Stagger and damage will increase as he levels up. It's critical. He's got 30% crit
resistance. Wanda two or rare pug? Three. Rare pawn. Is this a rare pawn? Oh, I'm doing it.
Cool. Let's see. Top one unlocks a new unit. Well, we got a rare pawn. Go up. I'm going to go. Okay,
two. I'm going to take. I'm going to make a Tata pawn. That's a Pio Pio.
On Tama, rare pawn whose critical rate rises gradually as they level up. At level five,
their attacks become very fast. I can do this like three times. Oh, ho ho. Level two. Yeah,
I'm doing it. Level three. I did it. Cool. Okay, what about the archers? Maybe I should also do a
go up and over there as well. The Pio Pio. Yeah, because that's good too. Critical strike on an
archer. All right, that was cool. Squish. Squish what? Fortress. Edgey cliff.
Tata pawns head into the skies above where another Carmen fortress stands before them. It's time for
battle. All right, we got to move some people around, right? That you go over there. Level of
you. You, not you. Over here. Optimize. Friendship sword, friendship shield.
Optimize first. You're in the front. That's good. Optimize. You're in the front too. Okay, cool.
Give it a try. Army looks beefy. Yeah. Oh, they're cold.
So are they. I turn it into rain? All right, I'm going to make it rain instead. That'll work,
right? Will it turn to rain? Yeah, it's um, then, then, then. Fucking God. Where's the beat?
Where's the song? And forward. All right, forward. This song's good. I think it's so big.
Fire made for a small screen. That makes sense. Here we go. Unbelievable. Forward.
I'm not hitting myself with my own air hose, right? All right, knock the shit out.
Now bend. What's the wind look like? Wake up! Jeremy, catapongs are attacking my apartment right
now. I'm sorry, man. Like you're in that building. Man, that's, that's so funny. It is. That's funny.
If you don't think so, then you need to go to comedy school. Like that person did.
Okay, I went, but I, I, you know, whatever. I fucked out.
Loud strange noises. It's not comedy. It's like, oh, really? You think so?
He's so fucking smart, though. Aren't I funny?
He flunked out. Rain again? Oh, more rain. How do you flunk out a clown college? You can't make
balloon animals. That's like the SATs of clowns. You got to be able to know how to do that. All
right. I do need to do rain. I said the item's fine. It's going to be there. Currently in a
clown one-on-one zoom call. Do you have to be in makeup for that? Or is it just like, you know
what? We, no, we don't have to be in. We're just, we're just here. No more rain. No more fire.
Not makeup. It's not makeup. What does that mean? Ink? Big walnut. Pick up the walnut.
Yes. Okay. Don't. It's not analog. It doesn't do anything.
People are born clowns or not. That's a lot of items. This game looks great. But was it really
worth $250? It was actually like seven bucks. Did you know that you can change here class
at the headquarters? Oh, no, that's the guy's name. Do you know that you can change
a class at the headquarters before you buy
Oh, wait, we have to watch this when he buries it all.
Oh, should I, uh, I'm getting some more, uh, yary pond upgrades. I can't. Oh, God, I'm died.
All right. What am I supposed to say? I could go. I could do a little too. Cool. What about you?
Yeah. Oh, I want this one. That's this one. A chiku. Nice. Okay. He's not my stuff.
It's fun. Why does it get so crusty? I don't know. It just kind of does. It just does. Doesn't it?
Crust is real. Can you change menus? Don't ask me why. Defender of the sky past the impregnable
mountains. See if the clouds spreads before them. White clouds, black clouds, thunder clouds.
But this isn't heaven. It's a battleground class. Uh, I'm going to make you a yary pond.
Steel saber. Optimize. Optimize. Got them all hats. Optimize. Nice. Give hero the good one.
Oh yeah. You, yeah. Give me this thing. Friendship spear. Get off. Friendship spear. Give it to me.
Friendship sword. Okay. Let's go. Nothing like a good old friendship sword.
Look out for that cloud monster. Okay. Pick him up. Lousy patapons.
The hell is that? Is that it over there? Kill it. Fuck. Oh, can we back up? Holy shit.
Right. Or a good hit. All right. Now block.
Got it. Again. Okay. Again. For hours now. Yeah, me too. Is there a way to mute their voices?
I don't think so. What? That's like a secret. Before it disappears. Get in there. No.
No. Let's go. Just pick it up. I'm muted. I'm not muted. I'm not. I can see the indicator.
The streamer can't even unmute. All right. Now five minute break from reading chat. I think
that sounds good. No. Get that thing. I think it's like a staff. Get a staff. He's in the way.
Get it. I can't walk by him. I can't walk by him. I can't move by him. I got an egg. My DPS is too
low. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Security number.
Why the hell would you put that in here? What's wrong with you? Patapons like to stay clean. So
they'll run from the smelly game. They pass under an enemy bird. The bird might drop a poopoo on
them, which would make any patapon upset. Make sure to keep them clean. Lady of the Den. You again,
let me guess. The scouts have found something terrible. Right. Lady of the Den. How did you
know? It's a castle up in the clouds. Oh, fuck. What the fuck are you talking about?
Should I do one of the egg thing again? Sentura egg one. Maybe let's just do a,
I'll do Sentura one. So who are these little guys that I just get them? This is my hero.
You have to go over here. Oh, what the fuck is this? Formation.
He appears on horseback riding with none. His form must be that of a true warrior.
Oh, that's cool. Does he always have to be in the front? He's doing solo. Oh, this must be okay.
Let's just go kill this thing. This is for multiplayer. How would multiplayer work in this
game? You have to do it at the same time. Let's do it. Forgot. Not on the easy mode anymore.
The four inputs don't work. Forgot. What the fuck? What is going on?
Get the coins. What are you doing? That's what he does.
Kill. Come on. Get those coins. Get in there. Get the coins. Is this on PSP? It is. It's being
played on PlayStation 4 with the remake. Technically the remaster. That's true.
Get it. Those coins. The remaster. Play everything on a CRTV. Oh, shit.
Oh, great. I have no fucking idea. Yay. Who did I get? Who is that? Who is that?
Pura Battle Egg. Spit off to Alita Battle Angel. Didn't do very well at the box-off.
Disney lost 200 million dollars. Okay, so wait. Did I get the big one or get a bunch of the little
ones? Take them all away. It's the funniest movie of the year. Let's move. Do you want to change
Harachari into Pacheng and return? Yeah. Don't be honest. Did you get bogged? Is that why you
don't go on biz anymore? Hey, dude. Hey, be honest. Did you get bogged? It didn't everybody
did. What are you talking about? Did I get bogged? Every single person did. All of everyone. He
admits it. It becomes a crypto rent. I mean, what do you have any more to say? Yes, I was
responsible. And when BTC reached that $20,000, I was like, yep, it's time to sell it here. And
this is a good idea. And I'm going to sell it. It went down. Just keep it. It's going to be the new
paradigm. It's 14,000. Just hold on to it. We're going to get a big rally here. 8,000. I'm telling
it's going to be the new technology everybody's going to use. What do you want me to say? You
want to say? Oh, I'm responsible. And I took profits when I should have. Sky Castle of the
gods. Oh, no, he's angry. He finally admits to getting bogged. Oh, level. Yep. He fell for a get
rich quick scheme. No, I didn't. Because this is it's still like cryptographic technology. It's
like a good technology. It's a good it's going to do some good things eventually here. All right.
Everybody knows that. Come on. Cryptographic techno stuff. Keep telling yourself that.
I don't have to keep telling myself that. It's even if it's not money. You know, there'll be a
use for it. It'll be the thing that communicates in your car. The tell it to like turn its engine on.
And like to be careful. Get all that self driving AI blockchain car. I don't know.
Oh, let me have to get I have this. Can I have like a little bit of hope, please?
I think I'm self driving blockchain car would take you'd be like, Okay, time to take a turn
signal. All right, hold on. About to take a left. First, let me download every single left that's
ever been taken by every single other car. Okay, almost got it. Okay, now it's time to put my left
on the next one. Okay, I'm playing the game. I've made 1000s of dollars in crypto in the last month
alone. I'm so I'm really happy for you. That's great. I that's fucking awesome. I'm really happy
to hear that. It's gonna do something. It's it look it's like a new technology. Fucking pets.com
came out and nobody gives a shit anymore. There'll be like an there'll be an Amazon of this of the
crypto world be a few of them. Probably I don't know. I'm just optimistic. Okay, and I'm glad
you're making some money. It's cold. Whatever. It's sure it is. Of course it is. What do you want me
to pretend? He got absolutely bogged. He's delirious. How much money did you lose?
Um, not enough to be sad, but enough to be annoyed. Let's put it that way.
100k. If you think a slight annoyance would be from $100,000 in losses.
Um, I how much money do you think I have?
Bragging about being a millionaire again with like, what was that face?
Dude, you're a millionaire. I'm gonna hiss into the mic. I'm gonna hiss into the mic.
Oh, by the way, I got all the easy bake oven stuff. That's gonna be disgusting. I saw the
packet for the pizza. I don't want to eat this pizza. It's gonna be fucking revolting.
I've been making a pizza out of a powdered packet. That's what it is. Guys, even the
Lunchables. Lunchables pizzas are cold and they're weird. They don't come out of like a powdered
pouch. It's not, no, I don't even think it's flour. It's some alien liquid. I don't know.
Wait, get that sword. Get that sword. Somebody touch it. Nice. Thunder sword.
Huge fog moment. Pressing for those things.
Shooting? We just came in and said veto. Um, you're about four hours too late. Annihilate.
Can you move? What's about some other scams you can help with? Um, wait, that's applying that,
that like, no, that's not a scam. Air restoration. That shit actually works.
That stuff, it works if you do the right, if you do like surgery or whatever it is.
Nobody can tell it's not my real hair. Nobody can tell it's not my real hair.
Because I had a video of me in a pool coming up from under the water and my hair like goes
back and just look at it. And I look into the camera and I go, it's my real hair.
And I pretend to yank it and you can clearly tell that I'm not putting any pressure at all on it.
I'm just like, I'm doing like a pantomime that I'm pulling.
Why the fuck would I want to like compromise that this hair on TV commercial that I probably got
paid like $300. Procedure was like 16 grand. Why would I compromise this? What are they saying?
Oh, but this shit works. It works. That shit actually works.
Okay, get in. Move closer. Show no mercy. Now the hint. Brain cells.
Of the sounds and the colors. Pressing the same sequence of buttons over and over again.
I don't like gamer fatigue. I know what that is.
You're going to rock you. We dropped something. Go get this items.
Can I get the items? How do I get the items? It's like a yellow item. I can't get it.
How do I care about lore when there's items on the ground?
3D Grinner. Okay, I want to see the new thunder bow. Cool.
Somewhere in this world hides a dark place known as the underworld. The underworld has
its own leader with demons and trolls as residents. They can't come to our world on their own,
but all they need is a special summon to make the trip. Generic ass fucking story.
I'm like this game a lot. Don't you know I say that? I said the same thing. I got to be careful
because I did that with Mario Sunshine and I think I got to stop doing that. I got to stop
shitposting on my own stream. I've done that a couple of times today. I'm going to stop
shitposting on my own account. I don't like this. Why? Whoa, look at that hair.
Go all the way to the left? I can't. There's nothing here. There's nothing here. Go left.
There's nothing here. Wait, what do I mean? Call the guy with the hair?
There's no more left. Call the guy with the hair. What is going on?
There'll be something to the left soon. That was fun.
Those pursuing earth end won't be stopped by a mere blizzard.
No, we will not. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait a minute. What's happening? Thunder sword. Magical sword that harnesses the power of thunder
to deal critical staggers and knockbacks as well as set fires. I'm going to have to give that
a gun from. Thunder bow, right? Yeah, there is. Stagger. There's frog. What's frog?
To the hero. The hero is... I have to make the hero a different class, right? So then you take
the full shield. I just killed everybody. Take this off. Put on this tin axe. Give me that ice shield
too. An axe. Thunder sword. Friendship helm. Steel shield. Ice shield. Ice is better. I can
make you a... Wait a minute. Five to thirty. Yeah, let's go. Let's go. Putting your teeth together
and that's better. Pairs of peaches. Neither of them. Throw them both in the trash and buy
nectareans instead. They think they can really cross the snow field. I mean like theoretically
throw them away. Actually throw them. That big sword. Anime darn these pataphons. Aiming.
I got a chance to leave. Inhuman, those pataphons are monsters.
Yeah, defend. You're killing them. Get that flame. Nice throw.
Rain, dude. All right, I got it. It's a migraine scream. We're probably going to be getting those
to the end soon. This is kind of turning into a migraine scream, isn't it? Is the rain ritual?
I actually hate this game. Oh, I don't. The games are on the agenda. Well, No More Heroes 2 is on
single core brain. Yeah, No More Heroes 2 is going to be on Monday? What day is it? I don't know.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday. The idea would be No More Heroes 2 and that takes us
from two screams and then we do Resident Evil 3. Can you hear me? Oh, sorry. No More Heroes 2,
Monday, Tuesday, and then the idea is then to get that sword and then do Resident Evil 3
on Wednesday, Thursday, if it takes that long. Resident Evil 3 takes one day,
like, for instance, on Wednesday and it might take one day. Shit. When's Easy Bake?
Easy Bake Oven Stream and the Green Screen DLC for Free Stream. It'll be back to back
on May 15th and 16th. Back to back. Easy Bake Oven Stream will be probably Friday
and the Green Screen DLC on Saturday. Am I permanently frozen here?
Just move. Come on, guys. Game's so fun. All right. I got it. When are you going to do a
cringe stream? Somebody could probably argue that that's every single one. I mean, I'm sure
there's somebody that would be watching this. I don't like that. I mean, oh, I can't argue with
that. Just kill them. I'm just going to do it defending only. The wind's too strong. Your hero
makes you unkillable. Why would I ever? That's awesome. You should do a cringe only stream.
You mean just like desperately try to be as horrible as possible. Headache stream. I and
I are, I just, hold on. I'm trying to get after this. You already do that. Hold on. This is a
torture stream? What? This game's fun. It's just, I mean, just turn, I know you're hearing
la la la la. Put the mission and goal left. I'm about to beat the mission. Remember who's better,
Ace of Base or the 90s Beach Boys? Ace of Base. Ace of Base is the ones that I saw the sign
and it opened up my eyes. I saw the sign. That's, is that Ace of Base? That pot. Get that pot.
I'm out of pots, dude. I got, I'm out of pots. I'm potting. I'm potting. That's the, that's the,
that's the cringe content I'm looking for. That's the real cringe content. Don't say that. There it
is. I'm losing my mind. Hero makes you take no damage. This is great actually. Viewers are
plummeting. I think that already happened back when I was arguing with you guys about the input
delay and thousands of people were just like, ah, fucking out of here. This is, I'm done with this
for one. We're the true fans. We, I feel like I'm fighting the same three people here for
15 straight minutes. We stayed for the input delay stream. Oh, mega lol. I still had fun. I mean,
this game is fun. There's the ice foresters finally. I like the RPG elements. This is not
the final boss. No way. I need more rain. Can I get these guys closer? Get in closer. Closer.
All right. Now, the pen. Game's 25 hours long. Plenty of content. Maybe I'm not strong enough.
Maybe I was supposed to grind. They definitely use this kind of stuff in Guantanamo.
You consider and play this? It's not, you guys are overreacting. Come on. It's like
my alarm clock won't turn off. It's, don't worry. Don't make me laugh right now.
I did it. Kill, kill, kill, kill. Yeah. Hey, do a game mute sound joke. Come on, relax, relax.
I don't want to have to start banning people. Remember, a wave of my finger and you're gone.
I did it. I say the word, you're out of here. Don't ever forget that. Okay. Now follow the guy that
go to the left, right? The streamer gave me a headache and then banned me. Well, I never told
you to turn the volume up all the way and put your eyes, so the wet part of your eyes is touching
your monitor. I didn't tell you to do that. Left one, two, three, one, two, three. Oh, the
mighty Jerry. I'm delighted. I am to meet you. I'm fabulous. I'm the fabulous dance instructor.
Sharaba Yapon, master of the disco, foxtrot, polka, and waltz. The mission is in life. It's
great. The most fabulous dancers. I love people who are practicing right here. I'll be able to
versus training. My name is master of disco. It'll be my honor to teach you a good movie.
Okay. Right here. Behold the amazing things to my build pupils. All right, let's do it.
Yes, I guess. Cafeteria meals. Okay. Meat. Here, take a walnut. I don't take one of these. What
should I give? What do I give? What do I give? A map? Stick? Give a wooden branch?
The as a rich person's doorbell. I may not be too smart, but I'll do the best I can. Please teach
me to dance. Great, Jerry. Have you danced to this song before? No. What button is that?
The important notes scroll across the screen. When a note gets there, press O. As long as we keep on
dancing, the notes will keep on passing. When you see a whole bunch of notes coming through, press
the circle button as many times as you can. Go nuts. The more times you press, the more kaching
that'll pay. Now instructor, I'm ready to begin. If you press O in time for notes, Sharaba Yapon
will wave his batons to help you dance along. Dance. More fun than the actual game. The blob
two waiting room. Understood. Okay. How about level two, level one? Is this level correct?
That was fun. Into the stream voice. He sounds like you. He does not sound like you.
Into the stream. How can you hate this game and then play gotcha force for 15
hours with its one song? I didn't, I never told you I hated this game.
You are implanting that as I'm being asked. I'm being, that's not, I never said that. I didn't say
that. Oh, left again. What's a better Olympic sport term, a trampoline or the ribbon dancing?
The ribbon dancing is the, is the best sport in the Olympics completely. It's just the coolest
thing that, I mean, trampolines is cool, but the ribbon dancing is way cooler. What are the tree?
What do you want? You missed it. Like this, nothing here. I'm gonna call it here. We're
gonna hang out for the bits. We'll chill for like probably like an hour. He hates it. No, he doesn't.
Just trying to adhere to his schedule. What would you give for a grade? Seven out of 10.
He just decided to torture his chat today. I can't, I don't, I don't, I think it's, I think
it's cool. I think it's cute. I think it's fun. I think there's a lot of depth. He will never beat
Groyo Groyo. A strong seven. Um, it's very, very strong. I'm so glad that Jerma hates chat. Why
would you be glad about something that's not even true? No, I, I, I can't wait. I can't give
something a grade that I played for like four hours. It's like a 25 hour game and I played it
for like four or five hours to check it out and see if I liked it. I liked it. I can't be like,
ah, it was an A plus. I don't know. It could be. What would you rate us? Um, that changes between
Monday and Friday. On like Tuesday, maybe sometimes maybe you guys could be a six. On like Thursdays,
you might be a nine. Saturday? Oh, that's where the fives come out. Sunday? That's where the
fives come out. Monday? Fives come out. Tuesday, usually sixes come out. Wednesday, usually the
eights or the nines. Thursday, probably like sixes. Wait, what's today? I didn't give a day. I know.
Oh, I didn't give a grade for Thursday. Ah, Thursday. Oh, you guys are great. I'm fucking
kidding. Relax. You guys are always a fucking, at least 8.5, at least a nine. First of all,
I don't get a 10 because somebody says I have big zits on my forehead. If I turn my face cam on,
that brings you all down. It brings you all down to a fucking nine. If everybody in the room got
an A on their test and two people get an F, um, sorry, but the collective class was like a B plus.
That's just how it works. Oh no, I got an F out of 4,000 students. No, I'm saying if you got like a,
that wouldn't even like move the needle. If you had like 4,000 A's and like two F's,
they wouldn't even affect the grade. You can hear the bogged in his voice.
Nah, I'll see you guys on Monday. We're going to do No More Heroes. We're going to do Monday,
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday. And then we're going to do another community content night
because I want to catch it up. We'll do another community content night probably on somewhere.
Let's see. You know, no, you know what? This makes perfect sense. You ready? We're going to do,
it'll end up being Thursday the 14th because that's, that's like perfect timing because then
it's Thursday the 14th will be community content night. Friday would be Easy Bay Govan and then
Saturday will be DLC for free green screen. So in like, like two weeks from now. Exactly.
But I'll see you Monday. We're going to start and complete No More Heroes 2 and then we're going to
start and complete Resident Evil 3. And then if we still have time on Thursday, if I don't beat it
on Thursday or on Wednesday, we will do something else. That sounds like a good plan to me, but
we'll see you soon. Thanks for watching. Thanks for spending your last week. Thanks for spending
your middle of your week with me or the beginning of your week until now. Yeah. Thanks for spending
it with me. We have fun. You're definitely going to beat it in one stream. Even these weak ass
short streams. The game, weak ass short stream. I'm trying to get healthy. God damn it. This was
good to hear you. You better do another 12 hour stream someday. That's never going to happen.
Stop smoking. I don't smoke. He got soft. Whatever it is, he got something. Whatever,
whatever weird bone disease I have, I've, I got it. I don't know. It just happened. Shit happens.
Oh, we'll see on Monday. He's got boneitis, pretzel bones.
It must be from all the donkey donuts. You're going to do no more streaming on weekends.
Um, no, that's just kind of how it, this is, I mean, Friday and Saturday, we have a plan for
Thursday, Friday, Saturday for the, what? It's just how it plays out, you know, four days in a row,
like three days, four days, three days, five days is kind of how it just plays out with the new
schedule. I want to try. Tweet about it so you don't forget it. Do a face cam. You're too
self-conscious. I already did. He's got a germ. I'm sorry. The game sucks. Why is everybody saying
that? It's no, it's because I did the stupid comedy thing where I was like, it's fucking
game. Stupid fucking goddamn fucking game sucks. It's fucking terrible. Like I, I tell I gotta
stop doing that. I have to stop shit posting it on my own stream. I got to stop doing that.
I'm not doing that anymore. No more jokes, but let's, uh, let's do the bits. See you Monday.
Stop denying the fact that you wanted to stab your thumbs through those juicy pat upon eyes
and watch them squirm omega low. That's not, that's not an omega low scenario. That's a, uh,
that's a monk S scenario. That's an actual omega psycho. All right. I'll see you Monday. Let's do
the bits. We have two 50 from pigeon. Jeremy, you cannot title your stream. The marching band.
I thought I meant you finally hired the high school marching band. You said you would on the
official podcast. And I got so hyped just for this. Just kidding. That's it. I, uh, that's,
I promise you one day that'll happen before I stop streaming forever. Whenever that date is,
there will be a full 20 plus person in full costume marching band on this stream. I promise
without even no, no good audio either. Do like just the regular mic. I promise. I fucking promise
it's going to happen. It has to AC 4G. Thanks for the two 50. What's the status on the resident evil
three stream. But I, there you go. I hope you're here. Talked about it. Well, it's going to be
happening next week on Wednesday, Wednesday, Wednesday, Wednesday. Should be fun. Hey, Lando
Bando. Thanks for the two 50. Hey there, big J. You've inspired so many of my creative endeavors.
So now I'm working on a German mockumentary where I tour around Boston to important places
such as the donkey doughnuts, where you were born as you chase me. Also, you should play
blood bowl too. It's kind of like the league, but all this kind of like blitz, the league,
but all the stupidity has been brought up to 11 helicopters, crash, fantasy races,
and straight up killing the other team. Is that really what I'm going to look into that. It seems
fun. Thanks for the two 50. And here comes a mockumentary sticks renegade. Thanks for two 50.
Hey there. Hey Jerry. Remember if you cannot play Jackie Chan stunt master within 10 years,
you automatically admit that Willy Wonka 2005 is better Wonka movie.
Jerma Grin. That's fine. Not going to happen. X in X. Thanks for the two 50. When's toon town?
It'll probably happen at the end of May. I would guess a drum major. Thanks for the two 50. Happy
May day, Jerma. Today all over Europe, we celebrate spring and the workers day here in Finland. It's
one of the four major holidays there are. The tradition of those graduated from
Lucio, probably closest to senior high school in the US school system. They go out to parks and get
wasted while wearing their graduation capes, which sadly isn't possible this year due to Corona.
Do you celebrate it all in the States? Here's a few picks to give you an idea.
Um, not, I mean, people have like grad, people had graduation parties where yeah, it would be like,
oh, like we graduated, let's hang out. But also you have to remember, um, he's talking about
going out and like having drinks. Uh, the drinking age in the United States is 21. So you can't,
we, you can't like go out and get drinks and have, get drinks when you're 17, 18, 19,
drinking age is 21. So it was more of a grill food outside and have people have your friends
and family come over and give you cards with like $20 bills and more so how that happened.
So not necessarily the same thing. What is, um, I'm just, just out of curiosity.
What is the drinking age in Finland? What's like the, the, the legal drinking age in Finland,
the 18, 16, 18, probably 18. A lot of the European countries are somewhere, what 18 and some of them
even lower than that, right? 18, 20 for alcohol over 21%. Huh. You're in Denmark. It's 15.
Germany is 16, 16 in Germany. Yeah. So it's weird. It's as an American,
it's so weird to think about that at like 16, you could like legally drink alcohol. That's like such
a foreign concept to me. Wow. What? No, you can't, you can't do that. You're not 21. Are you? How do
you? It's interesting. People drink anyway. Don't be ridiculous. Oh, I'm talking about
in a legal sense. Like you, you can't go into the, into the grocery store guys at 16 and buy
like beer. You can in Germany. Like that's, it's just so different. You can't go and do it. Period.
Oh, it depends on where you are. Yeah. But, um, we don't know. That's, that's not something that we
really do. At least I didn't do it just because it was, it was more like a family get together
and it was like, have like a big party with your friends crazy that we can draft someone,
but not let them drink. Yeah. Where did the, well, okay. I know it's like the age of being
knighted, right? Isn't 21. Is that even real? Or is that just like a fake article I read one day?
Wasn't it like, Oh, the nights got night at a 21 or something.
Mike, because that's fake. That's a, why is it 21? That's an anime plot. Anime laws.
But like you, you're considered an illegal adult. You're an adult at 18 and you're an adult. You can
but know that now like cigarettes are now moving to 21 all over the place too.
A lot of like to buy cigarettes, 21, which it was, it's been, it was 18 for decades and decades.
No, no, I meant you celebrate May day, not graduation day from high school.
No, that's not really a thing here. Most of the, I mean, most of the holidays that are in the
summer, like this late spring and in the summer, and you're talking about, I mean, this it's May
day, May day, but like Memorial day, right? Memorial day with the July, there's a bunch of
things that we do. July 4th. Yeah. But not in particular May day. No, I wanted to say Zyxia
again gave a hundred community subs, which is fucking crazy. It's just so many subs to give it
in one second. I really hope you can afford it. That's a lot of money to give somebody ever.
Thank you, Zyxia. Do a drunk stream, please. I just did. I just did like four or five days ago.
Hey, nope. Thanks for the 500 bits. Yo jumbo. I just wanted to say thanks for streaming. Gotcha
farts the last few days. It helped me fall asleep and fix my sleeping schedule. Smiley face, no space.
Thank you. Hey fishies. Thanks for $5. I've been a long time watcher since 2012 and I've been subbed
ever since I found your Twitch channel, but this is my first time donating. Well, fishies,
thanks for the $5. Thanks for donating. I feel like you deserve more than just a sub. I want
to make sure how you know how much all of us in the community appreciate what you do for us.
No matter what game you play or how long you're online, your streams always make me smile. I just
want to say thank you for being you and never change. I appreciate that, but a sub is you're
kind of paying for it already. You know what I mean? Like if you are subbed to the channel,
you know, you talk about that, you get, that's like $5 a month. You're already contributing.
Like that's, that's already more than I could ever ask anybody to do. So if you've subbed to
the channel, you don't, you don't feel, don't feel like you have to, oh no, I want to get,
I have to give more. You don't have to. If you, you don't have to give anything.
Being subbed to the channel and thinking I have to give more money,
something I really hope people don't really think they have to do. You're worth donating to. If you
think that, then that's, that's for you to decide. But I've, I've, I've toyed with the idea.
And I mean, this, this is, this is just all hypotheticals and all, um, just thought project
in quotes. Those of you that remember from a while ago, it, I, I never had a donation link.
I never had one. It was always something that I was like, I don't really want to do that
because people sub your sub, you already paid for it, whatever. And then when bits came along,
it was like, oh, I guess it took me a while to kind of be okay with it and like, want to do it.
And I think about stuff sometimes if, what if there was no bits? What if you could just sub
to this channel? Sometimes I think about that. Community subs would be insane and you'd have to
bring back sub sounds. Imagine there's no bits. It isn't hard to do. Oh, I see what you're doing.
I think about this kind of stuff all the time where it's like, well, what, what if you just like,
okay, you've, it's fine. You pay, you, you just optionally pay $5 a month if you feel like it.
Like it's not, oh, I, I, I want to give you more money. I want to give you like
5,000 more dollars. Like essentially like an optional Netflix subscription,
Patreon, but, and then, well, what happens to stuff like this?
Is it, it's worth it if you're going to keep streaming? Yeah, I've, I've no, nothing would
change. It would just be like monetarily speaking, subscriptions would be like the only
form of this channel bringing in like money. And this is not something I'm saying I'm going to do,
but I don't know. It's something to think about. I don't do Patreon.
Thought project for the day. He's thinking of ways to make less money.
I mean, that's no less money equals less carnivals. That, but that's not even necessarily true.
Set chat to true fans only mode, less clowns. No, no, no. Five million. He already has too much
money, but to move on from that, I just something to think about not happening. No worry. I'm going
to keep those bits on released a little while longer. Just a few more. That's it. Just a couple
more of those bits. Let us pay you. I look, but you do. You, you do. Like you don't pay Netflix
extra money a month. I'm sure they'd take it. Who cares about them? Yeah. Netflix each shit.
You are at Netflix. You're yeah. But that's what I mean. Like optional.
Like it is now Netflix doesn't have easy bake oven. Yeah. It's just a thought. I'm just,
I'm just giving hypotheticals and kind of seeing what you guys think about it. We can move on.
It's not happening. This is not like, by the way, next week, there's bits of deleted.
Just want to see what you guys had to say about, Hey, Nope. Thanks for the $5. Yo jumbo. Just want
to say thanks for streaming. Gotcha. Far. It's already read this one. Hey, hey, sick. Ik sick.
Ikka sick. Ikka sick six. It's pronounced six. Ikka. All right. I got it right. Thank you. Six
Ikka for the six Ikka. Yeah, I got it. Thank you. Six Ikka for the thousand it's and your
hundred community subs. I say Zyxia. It's hard for me to forget and hard for me to learn new words.
Thanks for the huge amount of money. Hopefully I got your name right.
The chef's corner. Thanks for the thousand bits. Jeremiah Elberton is not real. Please
refrain from attacking thus weak point from massive damage. Jerma hates Fortnite. I don't
hate Fortnite. I just hate playing Fortnite. There's a difference there. Stains. Thanks for
the 250. Your hair is great. No matter what they say. King. Thank you. Hey, Locky man. Thanks for
$5. I always enjoy watching you play rhythm games. Keep up the good work. Hey, the funky man. Thanks
for the 300 bits. Hey, my mom got me these bits because she wanted me to tell you she thinks you
are hot. I'm not kidding. She actually did. So here's her Instagram. Please message her or
she'll keep bothering me about it. I appreciate the compliment. I'm currently in a relationship
and I am everything is going great and everything's cool. I don't I'm sorry, but I am me.
I have words coming out of my mouth. I really appreciate the comment. I appreciate. I'm happy
to hear it. Okay, I don't even want to let's go. Hey, thanks for the $5. Jeremy, do you call Otto
your furry boy that make you and Kim his skin parents? No, actually his name we call Otto. We
call them Mr. Horace Zonto for a couple of particular reasons. Because he went in bed.
He always sleeps. He never sleeps vertical. He always sleeps horizontally. And he's kind of just
gets in the way. Oh, he's in the way. Oh, he's horizontal. Oh, come on. What are you doing,
Mr. Horace Zonto? Horace Zonto. That's weird. When I'm even vertical, like he sleeps like
a horizontally on the bed, not like vertical like a human. So he's kind of gets in the way.
We call him Horace Zonto. You're gonna minus two, like a little fun name I give my dog.
I didn't preface that by going, Okay, I got some funny to tell you. My dog, right? He's a dog.
That's not even a joke. That's not that I shouldn't even told you. It's like a me and Kim thing.
Can't believe I just like told you guys that I just like let you I just like got the looking glass
and got to see into my private life. And it just throws back in my face. See if I share anything
else with you guys again. I can't wait to a blue screen of death to a symbiotic entity. Thanks for
the five community subs local IRS agent. Thanks for the $5 local IRS agent. Thanks for five more
dollars. Hey, Jeremy, you haven't returned our calls about our findings. It's come to our attention
from a very reliable source that you were in fact, a million dollar streamer will be taking
our cut of the dough next tax season. Hey, thanks for the $10. Do I get to deduct that?
I can can I deduct this? Or what would this count as? Now I owe 10 more dollars. 1 million and 10.
Fucking millionaire streamer thing. Check his account he has in the Bahamas. Talking about how
bad I'm getting bogged. And we think we think I got a million dollars. Hey, goiki. Thanks for the
500 bits. Beyond bogs. Beyond boggers. Beyond meat, man. But thank you, goiki. Thanks for the $5,
goiki. My sister borrowed my PayPal and asked me why I spent nearly $150 on Twitch this week.
And I hadn't the heart to tell her they were important expenses to appease an e-clown. In
all seriousness though, I don't know what else I'd spend it on rather than someone who brings me so
much happiness. So here's five more dollars to the bank. Please. The bank will be pleased.
Maybe maybe your girlfriend. Wait, you didn't you know, why are you guys saying girlfriend?
It's a sister. Take your sister out to a nice steak dinner. Thanks for the $5 though.
Hey, S Halukko. Thanks for the 250. What is the best pasta shape and why is it Casa Ricis?
Also, thanks for all the laughs. The best pasta is angel hair pasta. Angel hair like spaghetti.
Either that or big sloppy fettuccine noodles. Just absolutely just soaking, slathered in sauce.
Just slathered in fettuccine Alfredo sauce with crispy sliced up chicken. All right, I'm hungry.
Bye. See you guys on Monday. Olive oil. Good olive oil. Good one. Yeah, yeah, that's gonna be
good. Welcome to barbecue pit boys.com. Today we're going to be making some barbecue
stuffed hamburgers on the grill. Man gonna be good. Oh, you're getting hungry or what?
I watch every single one of their videos. For real though, thanks for the 250. Enough of these
baby games. Play mercenaries playground of destruction. Holy shit. I bought that game
like eight months ago and I was going to play it eight months ago and just be like, hey, that's
what we're doing today and I just forgot. All right, I gotta get that done. I can do that soon.
The game looks insane. Yeah, we'll do that very soon. Don't let me forget about that because I
will after about 10 minutes after the stream ends. Mercenaries too. Yeah, that's the one. Hey,
Wembley TTV. Thanks for the 250. Do you know what day it is today? It's Thursday. Thursday for me.
Gurus say thanks for the 300 bits. Hey bro, I just finished high school tonight. Graduating
early because of online school. Thanks again for all you do. Congratulations. Close that book and
open a new one. Open a new one. Close that book and open a new one. Remember when you're on that
highway. Forward. There ain't no brakes on the highway. No slowing down. No going back. You
don't turn around on the highway. Forward. Miss the exit. Gosh, it's okay. Get off of the next one.
Nah, seriously though, congrats. Thanks for the motivation, Jeremy. You're welcome. Do you guys
think I could make a career out of being that voice on the radio that comes on and sounds like
this? I guess I could. Are you serious? You want to talk about like a millionaire? Just absolutely
throw myself out there and just do 500 of those a day. If I do like 500 of these voice radio
commercials, that's a million dollars right there. That's easy. Each one is worth how much? Okay,
let's do some math. Let's say each one's worth what? Like 300 bucks? 400 bucks? 300 bucks?
Let's just say 300 bucks times a thousand. That's 300,000 dollars and then take that to the casino
and put it all on on black. That's 600,000. Write a children's book. If you make a million dollars,
you would only gain one fifth of your net worth, Jeremy. What do you mean a fifth? I would only
gain one fifth. What are you talking about? Because of like taxes? They're claiming you're
worth five million already. No, guys, I'm like an idle game. If I ever got close to a million dollars,
it would just be removed because I would do like a fucking ultra carnival. Every time I get close,
it would just be constant idle game. Like I would never, it would never cross a million. It would
never happen. It admits he's been close. No, not even close. Not even remotely close. Not,
not even halfway there. Not even, not even a quarter of the way there. Not even, not even
like a tenth of the way there. You guys got to remove some zeros. He's a hundred K
heir. 90K after the whole beyond meat thing.
Are you still in debt from the live rumble? Did I ever talk? You know what? It's been long enough.
Have I ever talked about where I got the money for the live rumble? Do we talk about this yet?
No, we haven't. We have not. Have we not talked about it? Um, I, uh, I drew from my retirement
account and liquidated it. It's true, but it's okay. I take it back. He's broke.
Did you invest in a new one? I did. I don't know. Everything's fine. Don't worry. I was like,
all right, how do I, uh, uh, I'm doing this. How much does it cost to do this? Oh,
$10,000 to make this video. Oh, let's go. Well, how much more do I need?
And he liquidated the new one for the carnival. No, somebody said something.
This doesn't count as a retirement. Uh, I don't want to even, I don't even want to even go there,
but what you said is fucking funny. Uh, no, how much was the carnival? Um, I, it hasn't been long
enough. It hasn't been long enough. It hasn't been long enough. It has to be like three years
for me to say it. It's been three years. It's been three dog years. It was $40,000. He's broke.
Who are those estimates at again for how much money I have? Uh, no, I'll be real with you.
Let's be real. Ready? Let's get real for a second. Um, if I want to do something and I think it will
be fun, I'm going to do it. I'm just going to fucking do it. And if I have like the capital
to do it, I'm going to do it. Did you get any profit from the carnival? Um, well, that depends
on how you look at that, right? Because no, no jokes, no fucking around. Like let's get serious.
There's been a huge amount of attention on this channel since then, but just there has been,
and a lot of new people have showed up. A lot of people are here and the channel has grown a lot
since then. So I don't know over the, over the year of, of, I'm not looking for a return though.
Like that's a, I'm not, I don't look at it that way. It's like, did it, was that fun? Did people
like it? And did a bunch of people have a good time and was it worth doing? I think, I think it was
and mean some things, things cost money and I'm going to pay for them if I can. And that doesn't
mean I've used every cent I own, right? Like I would, I would never put myself in any real,
like financial danger. I hope you guys understand that. There was an opportunity,
then I took it. Do I have a safe savings? I do. I don't worry. I have a retirement account and it's
doing fine. I have, don't worry. But I've been holding on to that one for a while. And I,
but that's the point though. Well, who cares? Like I don't, hey, it was, that's how much money it was.
What do you guys think about that? I don't, who cares? Like I don't want to make it about,
this is how much it costs guys. So, you know, that was money that I had to spend and excuse me,
what's going on? Hello. That's why I don't want to talk. I don't like to talk about like what,
what things cost because I don't want, I don't want to put a burden back to you guys because
then it's like, Holy shit. Well, that was a lot of money. Should we give him more? No,
no. The answer is no. Like a full stop. No, absolute no. But if I can put money back into
the stream because the stream makes money, anybody with a calculator and a computer,
can, you could take some wild guesses as to how much money this, the stream takes in a month. You
could. So if I'm capable, I want to put money back into the stream and do fun shit. Why the hell
wouldn't I? There's no reason in my, for me. It's just, Oh, okay. This I have some, like I've
revenue from this channel. Do I do a carnival or do I not do a carnival? The answer will always be,
I will do a carnival, you know, always. So that's just the way it is. And that's the, that's,
there you go. I talk, I'm, I'm naked in front of you. Hey, Yoda985, thanks to 281,
you're a persona five villain. And that's also where we get into, not to go any further on this,
but that's also where it comes down to maybe involve some company or a sponsorship that
thinks some of that, those ideas are funny and like, lets me kind of do what I want to do
and like helps out financially. Like maybe I can not have to do that much more money. You know what
I mean? Maybe like, all right, meet me halfway or something like that to do streams like those.
That's, we brought up this up a month ago or so, and I don't know, is that possible? Maybe.
But if I can make a better stream, then I'm going to take the avenue that allows me to do that.
Or if I try to make a better stream, like try to, because that's all I can do is just try.
And like, that's it. Was it good? Was it bad? Maybe it wasn't so good, but maybe some of the
projects you've seen, you're like, that guy, that wasn't that great. Did I learn something from it?
Can I try again the next time? Maybe, but I don't want to get long winded more than I already am
about this. Off bugleberry pottery cough. No, no, that was worth it. That's like one of my favorite
things. I like, I love that segment. It's like, I can't wait to see him back on camera. We're
going to move on. Do not take anything I said for any reason. I think you need to be concerned
about my financial life. Yes. Yes. I, I, I pulled from a retirement account to make the German rumble
video and I would do it a thousand more times because that was some of the most fun I've ever
had in my entire life. And I will never have that experience again. That's an experience that I will
never have again. And it was an experience I will never forget. It was absolutely worth doing,
but that was also, uh, like almost five years ago now. So don't worry, don't worry. I'm doing fine
until live action rumble two, which will be live and streamed on Twitch. That's the plan.
I want to do one on Twitch and I want to do one live on Twitch. I have, I've told the whole,
the whole thing's already written. The whole thing's done. This needs to be set up and
videotaped. Who has any idea of when that's going to happen? I have no idea. Probably not for a long
time. Here goes another 40k. No, no, but I don't want to, I just, all right. I, I, that's why I
don't like talking about like money and shit. I don't want it to be like, eh, whatever. Let's keep
going. We're almost done. Uh, we have the man with the baby hands. Thanks for 500 bits. Chat has been
more psychotic than usual tonight. I mean, early in the stream, people were fucking going nuts.
We're very mean today to me. They were very mean to me. They said he's stupid. He can't even do
just no rhythm. He's dumb. Then I like turned the webcam on and one of my teeth fell out.
I was like, what the fuck you guys fucking did? I don't know what, is that, is that possible? Can
you guys like radio frequency? One of my teeth fall off? It's weird. And then I played the same
song in their ears, uh, a hundred times. And then people, uh, were like, I'm going to bed,
which is completely understandable. Thanks to the 500 bits. Hey M. Weldo, thanks for the 250. They
say it can be done. Uh, what can be done? Oh, what is this? F it up by Lewis Cole and be done.
Yeah, you can fit them. You can fit people here. But, but here's the only difference is they're not
in full marching band costume and they don't have, and they're not all playing trumpets and
tubas. I remember I want a tuba. It can be done though. Yeah. I want to link. Here's a link.
This is ridiculous though. Anywho, Hey Dell kit. Thanks for the 300 bits.
Jeremy, first time ever donating. Do you plan on playing Morrowind or even perhaps Daggerfall?
Um, probably at some point, I feel like you kind of have to. Star and I were talking recently about,
um, getting SWAT four together, something that we've been trying to do for a long time.
And it's, it came onto GOG and seemed like a fun idea. And, uh, I was also talking to,
talking to Italics about it. Maybe get a few people at three, four people maybe and do some SWAT
recently for the past six years. Well, no, no, recently it came, it came out on GOG like last
year. Six years ago, we were like, let's play SWAT four, but it's like, oh, you can't, it's kind
of weird. You can only do it through LAN or you had to buy a server or something. But now on GOG,
I think you can do a direct connection to each other. I think it was years ago. Well, we'll see.
But it turned, that was something we were talking about. Cause I know people said Morrowind
multiplayer do it. That's another thing that'd be fun to do for somebody. I think a lot of people
say when Joel was playing it or something. And I don't know, it'd be fun. That it should be fun to
do. Peaceful Haley. Thanks for 250. So I moved in with my grandparents and what do you, what do
you know? The internet is shit. Download speed is not even one megabit per second and upload is
like two megabits. Rip my stream. Damn. That's like, it's like next level low. That's like in
the earth low. That's like, that's in the earth's mantle low. That's insane. Well, hopefully
we need to get it upgraded or, uh, get to a new spot. Maybe whatever you do. And you can,
you could maybe, you could squeeze though. You could squeeze some work out of two
megabits up. It's going to be a little crusty, but it, you, you might be able to make it work.
It's possible. Ray Joel. Yeah, sure. And I don't know, tell them like, tell them like I shit my
pants on streaming. It was like insane. Like, dude, it had really, it was fucking crazy.
Like freaked out and like ran out of the room and like the stream was just on BRB for like fucking
30 minutes. They came back and he was wicked embarrassed and his face was bright, fucking
ready at face came on at the time. What the fuck? He left the game on. You're a pathological liar.
I'm a pathological comedy liar. Come on. No, excuse me. Uh, the proper word is storyteller.
Thank you. I'm putting that in my Twitter bio. German nine eight five visionary storyteller
streamer liquidator of retirement accounts. So you're a Virgo. Oh yeah. Well, Ray,
Joel, you don't have to do that. Say hello when we're done here. Hey Yoda nine eight five. Thanks
to the two dollars and 81 cents. The year is 2,107. I checked my cybernetic implants and
see that German is streaming. He's on his death bed and sadly announces that this is his last
stream ever. He tells us not to be sad as he's lived a full happy life. His heartbeat monitor
goes flat and chat is filled with F's and germa Pluto's full high school marching band kicks in
the door and begins filling the room blasting the pirate spy song. President Elbertson dies
like a true clown beloved. That's sad. Thanks to the two dollars and 81 cents. Hey reant deliriation.
Thanks for the thousand bits. Germa said, give more money. I'll take it. But I never said that.
Thanks for the 10 bucks. King sherbert nine 87. Thanks for the three bucks. Shut up and take my
bits. I'll take them. I'll take them. Thank you. Chunky baloney. Thanks for the 500 bits. Everyone
hurry and give him bits while we still can. Thanks for the five dollars. Chunky baloney. Unnecessary.
Don't worry. You don't have to give me money ever. And I know that that's like oh he says that. He's
saying that and then people are going to do it. Don't feel obligated to give me money. You don't
have to. Look at how good look at how good I am. I know. I know. Look. Trust me. But you don't have
to. You really don't. If you do then I'll take it. Thank you. Okay. I won't give you money. Now what?
Hey evil fish. Thanks to 250. If you had access to a movie production crew, a well-connected
casting director and a few. I just broke my headphones because I'm sitting there playing
with them. Same exact thing happened to the last ones. Ah damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. I
broke the thing in half. It's okay. It's the other. It's the left headphone. I played with
it too much and I broke the jelly thing. Whoops. If you had access to a movie production crew,
well-connected casting director and a few million dollars, what sort of movie would you make?
I would make a Jerma Rumble live action too. Here's a joke that will never make it into a
Jerma Rumble but um this is the this is this is a two million dollar joke. I want to do it really
bad but here's a here's a this is this is written down. I wanted one of the contestants to be a
school bus that just drives into the ring. Oh here comes a school bus and it just drives up and like
fucking runs the whole ring over and the ring is ruined but they people are still getting
eliminated and stuff like the ring is collapsed but people are still like having to somehow find
a way to like throw people over the top rope even though it's on the ground. Two people like two
people hold up the top rope you know like we're gonna eliminate this guy he's too good one person
holds one side one person holds the other taut and like just to be able to eliminate him yeah that's
like a that would be that would be a ton of money that was written down that's one of the things
it's not gonna happen ever though. You have to throw the bus off the top rope and there'd be
there'd be somebody driving the bus that's like silhouetted out and they never come out like the
camera will pan around there's like a guy in there just sitting there like just without like an
emotionless face he's just sitting there driving the bus. Is he the contestant or is it the bus?
It's the bus but that guy never comes out. NPC bus driver why are you linking me a monster ebay link?
But you have to understand a free local pickup look just hurry up and liquidate your retirement
account I want to do it so bad so you'll know you'll know if I got what I wanted like in quotes
creatively speaking if a school bus runs the fucking ring over at some point in live rumble
2 keep an eye out and it would just go on as if it was normal for a while there's like another
thought of like oh the it's fucking ruined it's destroyed oh I can't I want to tell you this part
oh but it's it's so fucking funny it's the funniest thing that I've I've I've ever thought of
and I don't care if wow he thinks he's funny yes this one's funny no this one will happen
is somebody gonna suplex the bus can you imagine fucking like getting cranes
it happened like it'd be able to have the bus get suplexed somebody could get brushed I don't
that's not gonna happen someone could be in serious danger no the bus runs over the ring
and then in real time while they're still wrestling in the in the ring
immediately a construction crew is called to build a second ring next to the ring that was
destroyed and then they move to the next one and somebody accidentally eliminates themselves
because they've walked over the top rope because they was doing we could all right
everybody get over to the next one hurry the fuck up get like the referees and like the guy that
was doing really good at the time like steps over the top rope okay he's out stop spoiling
this is like 3 000 of these in german rumble life too don't worry giving you I'm giving you
teasers of hypothetical jokes are these written down the whole thing's written down it's all done
it's done that was one thing where it was like holy shit that's like not possible but it's kind
of funny and if I ever had like the the right crew and the lots of fucking money whether it's
from a sponsorship right or something somebody stuff like that these are all like fun hypotheticals
to tell you like oh he's spoiling no I mean that's you're talking about that's that's
probably hundreds of thousands of dollars like let's be real to get something like that to be
a reality it's just it's a lot and I don't know I did that's why in case it doesn't happen yeah
I need to tell you you know because it probably won't I have to tell you I've been I've been
having I've wanted to tell you about the school bus entrance for like two and a half years and
I did because it's fun who wins why would I tell you who wins anyways let's keep going
uh but that's what I would do and evil fish that's what I would do if I had
a well-connected casting director of a million dollars and I could do whatever I wanted the
school bus joke there you go I have to be honest Wembley TTV thanks for the 250 sad to say you
fail that that Metal Gear Solid 2 reference after you get asked that a hundred times during the game
I find it funny during your rants about paying your taxes you remind me of an old WWF wrestler
Erwin R. Scheister IRS cutting a promo about people not paying them IRS what an interesting
character okay so this is uh rip Alex Trebek thanks for the five dollars Jeremy I love this
video what do you think let's find out what I think about it yes baby you think you're so
fucking cool huh you think you're so fucking tough you talk a lot of what the hell is this
I don't like it there you go that's my thing hey Yoda 985 thanks for the 250 what happens on the
day Jerma thinks Jerma fear Jerma Mars killing people is fun Manka S was this a reference to
the school bus thing the school bus driving into the ring no the school bus school bus getting
suplexed and you just imagine the school bus getting suplexed and it's on its back upside down
and it's just still trying to drive the wheels are like spinning and then everybody has to like
get over and like lift it and lift it out of the ring and roll it out of the ring yeah the driver
is still emotionless there would be a at least two or three close-ups of this dude driving the bus
while even like in the air being suplexed and he's just like kind of putting his like fingers on
his nose and like kind of like like blinking and he's not it's not him it's the bus he's just there
he's just like a crew member he just like has to be in there it has to explode when it gets thrown
out of the ring you just added another 500 000 to this project hey behemoth thanks for 250 oh god
I'm sorry I made you reveal your carnival secret please eat you starving artist that's not even
true I was gonna tell you guys one day I didn't want to it was long enough it's what was October
last year yeah it's it's been long enough you can know that's okay that's fine I got plenty
of baby food right so everything's good uh we're gonna do the credits they come thanks for subbing
this channel everybody how long has he been talking uh five hours and 29 minutes give or take the
strings of about 30 to 40 seconds where I was silent trying to play the
concentration video game thanks everybody for the subs all of you continuing to support this guy
all right none of you have to do it it's a lot of you do so thank you appreciate it they're all
gifted subs and I can't even fucking believe that thanks a lot guys we're gonna finish the bits
demon hunter 790 thanks for the 250 germa confirmed to never retire from streaming
will one day I can't lie to you guys I will one day I don't think I could ever just like not do
it though I could probably I would probably I would probably just tone it down maybe eventually
over the years instead of streaming like three four days a week or four days a week or so but
I would probably just just to kind of be a presence I'd still be around you gotta make the last stream
a wild one yeah I mean it's not gonna happen anytime soon but it is gonna happen I would
tone it down first before I really was like all right bye I would stream like I don't know
once I got to the point where I was like all right this has been really fun but it's time for me to
step down I don't know I probably stream like once or twice a week I wouldn't just disappear
I would slowly be like all right guys I'm gonna take some time and I can't believe no this guy
this is not happening like tomorrow this is like in the distant future how could this happen
and tell us yesterday's spoiler I will tell you yesterday's spoiler when I play
next month's game as you'll see it on camera hey 25 dr peppa thanks for the 250 I'm very excited
you're going to play resident evil 3 but to be honest I doubt it will take longer than one stream
also I like the older games in the series like the resident evil 1 remake I think have a lot of
stream potential thanks for being entertaining as always now I don't think it'll take us that long
either I'm looking forward to it I've been putting it off for a long time get your kin to
stream on the channel the twitch channel must persist through the ages I'm done I'm kind of
afraid to have kids I feel like my kid I feel like my kid would like bite me in my sleep and
drain all my blood and take all my powers is that all I have to do he would become he or she would
become the next streamer could you imagine like a little like like germa or like germette
and there's they're they kind of look like me in a way and they're like oh look at me look at me
it's me you guys you guys would fucking hate this kid are you serious no way you guys would hate this
kid you'd be like it's not the same fuck this kid this kid sucks what a cheap imitation of the real
thing where's your get your dad where's dad I don't know what you guys are what wait what do you mean
uh look at me shut up kid where's dad hold on let me just come in here and say hey guys
how's everybody doing how the fuck are you germa bites and they would be like fucking bog bog bog
bog bog bog i'll see you germa bites later and they would be like oh my there he was and then
like fucking five thousand people would leave and like maybe like maybe like 60 of you would
stick around to watch like germa jr. nine eight five dink and doink the clown what an egomaniac
he's berating his fictional son thought project hey chud studley thanks to three bucks germa just
want to say i wish you had more merch an official fireman rat plush would be wonderful also do you
know that bella lagasse is dead i filled the rest part in i think that i think i know
yeah i'll get more stuff i gotta get more stuff for you guys to collect and display on your
reddit shelves see you guys monday we have uh four more bits to do it's me you see thanks to the five
dolls you really inspire me to keep working towards my goals the passion you put into some
of your contents amazing also stop playing the game through an obs screen i uh i don't i didn't
i didn't play the game through an obs screen i played the game out of my fucking monitor
uh
it's so easy i've come to realize it's so easy it's like you guys could just it's you guys have
it's so you you could just so easy for you guys just to get me going i i it's easy he's easily
entertained it'll never not be funny i know i just i can't like i just like what the fuck
it's all right uh yeah you get you guys get i'm the easiest person i think to get like going
well it takes us like one sentence for me to be like excuse me the fuck hold on i'm replacing
coffee with like hot milk i'm gonna like start to like slow down hey digitron surfers
remember i saw this picture in my first thought was that you would find it funny
you think it is i think it is because i read it in your voice it's a picture of please of a
lady talking to a baby is this please eat your vegetables they're good for you and provide the
nutrients you need to grow big and strong baby says yucky yucky pills and milk you're a beefhouse
watcher aren't you those guys are so funny oh it's the spoiler you'll see the spoiler when you see
the game in like i don't know in like june thanks for the free dolls thank you trans scout for the
five dollars dude get some fidgets i have adhd too and i'm always wrecking my shit because i
fidget a ton i recommend koosh balls or tangle toys look them up i lose them i lose them i buy
them and then i they disappear in like three hours oh cool like oh what cool man like what
the next day i don't know where it is it's gone forever i stopped getting them thanks to the uh
five dolls though they do they are fun they're they do work pens uh rubik's cubes are fun too
also what's like another one of my favorite things i like um i like utensils if that's weird
i like um you know the hard drive just locked up you can see the light blinking what's happening
the light's just fucking solid the hard drive light is solid but the shit man what the fuck
maybe i shouldn't have torrented every single fucking band 10 episode i knew one of those had
a fucking virus on it hey scott seven one three tf2 thanks to the five dolls germa a couple years
ago when you played tf2 on stream you said that you had an idea for a germa rumble as an onstage
play that you do in one take keeping the fuck ups in is that still a possibility thank you again
for all the laughs yes there's gonna be like choreograph choreography and dance numbers and
singing and getting eliminated would be like a big extravagant like song yes i of course it's
still up there entrances in the ring there'd be a big elaborate dance numbers but yeah that's
no longer in the front it's somewhere in the back thanks to the five dolls though demon hunter
790 thanks to the 250 i knew the stir truck punch line would find its way back it would be the bus
punch line this time future gamer thanks to the 250 i feel like if you stopped streaming you would
enter month two of retirement and come back full force probably yeah i i would probably be like
okay i'd be one of the i'd be one of those professional athletes that retires like four
times it's my last game i'm done and then a year goes by and they're on the free agent list again
anyone want me to play for them i come kind of bored do the yeah if i do the funeral stream then
like i can't come back when are we raiding joel right now i'll see you guys on monday thanks for
watching as always and we got some fun stuff coming up so stay tuned what is joel doing
go say hello i'll see you monday take care of yourselves as always have a great night have a
good weekend see you guys soon see you guys soon did i get cut off okay it went through good night