Hey, what is going on everybody? Little Gems here. Wait a minute, that's not my name. My name is Germa. Germa here with Little Gems.
Alright, we got that little awkward intro out of the way. This is going to be a different standard format for the Little Gems series.
You're probably by now used to me spending five or six minutes on one particular game, talking about why I like it so much, the reasons behind why you should buy it or download it.
But I kind of want to take it in a different direction, only because I only plan on doing two Little Gems a month for this channel.
So instead of doing one game, I'm probably going to cover at least two or three per episode.
And the reasons behind this, you can probably imagine, if you look at the App Store every day, something comes out every day.
Something comes out every couple hours on the App Store, whether it's Android or iPhone, iOS, iPad, whatever.
We are just bombarded by releases. So I'm going to throw together a few of my favorites the past couple weeks and spend maybe two or three minutes on each one.
Little Gem lightning round, baby. Here we go.
First up on the list is something called 1001 Attempts. This is arguably the simplest game I have ever come across, but it is quite an addiction.
So hear me out here. The game breaks down to doing one thing only. You pick up hearts. That's it.
There's no story. There's no levels. There's no upgrade system. You just have to frantically collect these hearts.
And you do this by moving left and right on the screen. You see in the lower left and the lower right, there is a jump button.
So when you jump, it doesn't really jump. You just change your gravity, so to speak.
And when you're in the air, you can strafe left or right. It's really very simple controls. Once you pick it up for the first time, you'll know exactly what you're doing.
Also gotta mention that random stuff just spawns around the screen at all times. And the more points you get, the more insane it starts coming out.
And if anything touches you, you're dead. And you need to start over at zero points again.
So it's very nerve-racking. It has, I guess, a combination of Super Krait Box and Super Meat Boy, like jumping around, dodging things, trying to get all this stuff.
It's got a really crazy mashup of a million different things going on. And it's only 99 cents.
That's only four quarters if this was an arcade machine. So for one dollar, I definitely recommend you pick this up.
If you are into the frantic jump around, collect a bunch of shit, and don't die game.
So I'm gonna rate this four Burger Boys out of five Burger Boys. That's the scaling system we're gonna be using.
Alright, let's move on to the next one. The Silent Age is going to be very hard to explain in two minutes.
So I'll try to say as many cool things about this game as I possibly can. And we're gonna start with this.
Time travel adventure game where you control time and stuff.
Alright, let's actually explain what that means here. So the Silent Age is a adventure game. It's a great one.
One of the best on the App Store right now. And it's free. You saw on the corner. Look at the corner right now. It says the game's free.
Anyways, you play as a janitor for some big corporation and your name is Joe.
Right off the bat, you are given a promotion to get higher clearance to clean the trash cans in the off-limits area.
Oh, sick, dude. And then the game gets kind of weird. I don't want to spoil anything for this game because there is a storyline.
There are things that happen. But the atmosphere and storyline is so good in this game.
And I think it's gonna be episodic. I don't know how you actually say that goddamn word.
So this is chapter one of potentially a very long series.
And the reason why this game is on here in this Little Gems lightning round is because of its amazing time travel mechanic.
You go through the game solving puzzles, figuring out the story, et cetera, just like every other adventure game.
But you do it in this one by traveling in real time back and forth from the late 60s to the destroyed post-apocalyptic present or future, whatever you want to call it.
It's such a great mechanic because just exploring and using the time device to see how things have changed is fun in itself.
And there are no loading screens. You just click this button and bam, you're in the exact spot in the past or future.
And you have to do this to solve a bunch of different puzzles.
You got to go back in the past and pick something up and bring it back to the future in real time.
So really, let's hope this guy who made the game continues with episode two because I want it right now.
Go play it's free out of five Burger Boys out of five.
Last up on this list is something I'm going to call the speed run game.
And for pretty good measure, it's called Mikey Shorts.
It's a platform jumping coin collecting game that keeps track of your every single move.
Think of it like the ghost feature in Mario Kart.
We all know that where you raced against yourself your best times trying to beat them over and over again.
The gameplay is incredibly simple.
You have a jump button and you have a dash button or a slide button.
And that's how you go about each level.
You want to go as fast as you can, collecting all the coins, touching all the statues to open up each checkpoint.
When you get to each checkpoint, it shows you on the screen how fast or how slow you were in comparison to your best time.
So having it pop up on the screen like that, let's say you're minus, you know, five seconds.
You're like, oh, damn it. I'm five seconds ahead. Sick.
And then you get to the next checkpoint and it pops up saying that you're plus point six seconds.
So it's having it pop up on the screen really can make you want to drive ahead and do way better.
And this is actually how professional speed runners do their times.
They have a little thing. I watch a lot of speed runners.
I'm a speed run freak. Even though I suck at it, I like to watch these people do these things.
So they have something on the left side of the screen during a stream.
And when they complete a level or get to a certain point, they go and it shows on the screen exactly how far behind or how far ahead they are in milliseconds.
So that's kind of why I called it the speed running game.
Oh, by the way, this game has hats. You can get a bunch of hats.
You can get a bunch of miscellaneous new haircuts and stuff with the gold you pick up in each level.
So it's an instant download for a lot of your TF2 fans and the price wise, this is free to download to try it for the first few levels.
And if you like it, you can buy it for ninety nine cents.
And I'm going to rate this last one a four out of five cheese burger boys.
Wait, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, that was five for four burger boys out of five.
And that's going to wrap up the little gem lightning round starring German at eight five and burger boys face.
So thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
Hopefully this has helped you decide on a couple of games maybe you didn't want to pay for them.
Maybe you want to see some of these games in action on the app store.
And of course, links in the description for all these things, their prices, where you can get them and the devices that they are compatible with.
So again, thank you so much for watching.
Really do appreciate it.
I would rate this video a five out of five burger boys.
Burger Boy, baby, loved this.
I'm just going nowhere right now.
Bye. Take care, everybody.