Your mission is to find L. Ushin's hideout and eliminate him and his entire drug cartel.
You do this as this guy.
This guy doesn't see me?
As long as you stay hidden in the bushes, enemies will not be able to see you.
Oh look. What the fuck dude? Are you kidding me right now?
There's gonna be some guy that's gonna walk over here.
Yeah, oh look, oh I wonder why I can't believe that.
Where's, oh there's somebody in that bush I think.
Oh no, I'll just take my 2D gun and go yeah.
Whoa whoa whoa, press enter at the right place to, oh I have to blow the bridge up.
Okay, this looks like, hmm.
I wonder where the right place is.
It's not a giant blue arrow.
Make sure you find the right place, indicated by the gi-
What? Did that seriously blow me up?
It was a cutscene! That was just a cutscene!
Three, two, one, boom!
What was that?
What was just on the side of the screen?
What was that giant clay brick that just came over?
What the fuck was that?
Why would they have an explosion animation if you were just gonna take it out with a slab of clay?
Why is this a lumberyard? Why are we at a lumberyard?
Dude, dude.
No dude, like, you've got to be kidding me right now.
You've shot down dozens of gang members, but you still aren't a single step closer to their leader.
To make him come after you in person, try to make things more personal.
That's a pretty nice car, dude.
This is his recently imported from France super sports car.
Trash it with your baseball bat before he returns.
Excuse me, but are you making this up right now, or am I hearing you correctly?
No, this is, I'm not making this up.
Attack it.
Yeah, you show him.
You show him what it's like to be a gang member.
Mission failed? I fucking trashed the thing.
Dude, I trashed the car.
Oh, you better hurry up and do it.
How much more damage do you want me to do to this car?
The car was like in a fucking junkyard by the time I was done with it.
If I fail the mission right now...
What is this?
What happened to the enemies?
What's going on?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, easy, easy.
Oh, it's an armored car.
Well, you didn't really take the right correct route to come get me.
You actually just drove into a tree.
Jesus, dude!
So what happens when these all get actually exploded?
What happens?
Oh, there's another one. Look out. Beep, beep, beep, beep.
I'm an animal.
The cars in this game are animals and they just drive into walls.
All right, I did it.
What's next?
What's next, huh?
What do you got for me?
I hear you.
Where are you?
First car. Where's the first car?
First car. Where are you at?
There you are, driving into walls.
You ain't even going to make it over here.
Your pathing is so...
Bye.
Goodbye.
Sometimes you find a bug in a game.
And sometimes you just interdimensional time warp through every single map that they made.
I have no idea why this is happening.
We've landed.
We're on Jupiter now. Welcome to Jupiter.
Enjoy your stay.
Please pick up your bags at the carousel.
What the fuck is actually going on right now?
This just turned into a completely different game.
I feel like I'm soul searching right now.
Look at this.
What happens if I go into like the great void?
The great void awaits you.
What's this?
A new land.