You might need to crouch.
Okay, nope. Yeah, I just barely did. Uh-oh. Be careful. Oh, he like pointed at me.
He's trying to punch you. He's trying to punch you. Oh, is he?
He's got the seal mask on.
You just punched that dude.
Come here.
You have crits.
I have crits? It's also crits. Yeah. Is there anybody around I can even shoot at?
Make sure you get this ammo. You run out of ammo real quick.
Oh god, he blew up.
Five seconds. We gotta get on the car. Come on.
Come on.
Where is it?
Stand on it.
That was heavy. That was awesome. That guy had the seal mask on.
You have like your your beard and everything on. It looks so goofy. Oh, I do? Yeah.
The sniper's just shooting at me.
Okay, you're not gonna kill the scout. Kill the scout.
Behind you.
I'm trying.
Yeah, one of the snipers got me.
Oh my god.
No, I'm healing you. I'm healing you.
Are you? Oh dude, this is actually like
No, there's gonna be a spy behind you. Watch out. Yeah, I see him. How much damage does he do?
Uh, his back stab will destroy your minigun before it can kill you. Really? But his revolver adds many crits to destroy that scout.
Oh
God, the spy is destroying me. It's a good thing we like respawn right here.
I'm just pushing this cart by myself. I need help. Oh
The fun is over. Spy.
Oh, that was awesome.
Why is that hat so big?
It is so big for your head.
Oh, I'm stuck in that wall. What?
Uh, if it spawns you on the right side of this spawn room, you get like stuck in the wall. Oh, okay. All right, let's go.
Come on, move it. Don't you like the punch animation? Yeah, I thought the guy was like pointing at me.
I thought he was going like, yeah, you and you I thought he was doing like the point to the crowd like everyone like
Oh, yeah, I see you up there
Okay, you've got third person. So you gotta watch out for like I felt like I was at a rock concert
He was like pointing at me. He was gonna dedicate a song to me
All right. So this is gonna give you crits and
Uber. Yes. Uber.
All right. Well, I'll be aware of all the sneaky spies felt like you just did that to him
Oh, oh, oh if I had a shotgun ready, I almost punched the dude
He uh, he flew by so fast
That was
Shows up behind us too fast. I remember if you take out your bone saw and right teleport, okay
Oh shit, they got a heavy. Oh
Just like stabbed you accidentally and it scared the fucking dump out of me you're heavy
I have like this
Get out here. I'm trying i'm going
I look like
I look like jerry gasea
They cannot mesh with robot heavy behind you behind you behind you
This thing is spread is so huge watch out for that sticky on the ground. They do a ton of damage
How do I get rid of it?
Shoot it. It's just sticky. The sniper's gonna kill me. No, he's not then we'll behind us behind you behind you behind you now
Ah
What they didn't hit him?
No, he's dead
Can I get through this door?
You crouch
Let's go down the tunnel. No one will contest us in the tunnels. All right fine
I feel like i'm just too big. I feel like i'm like the fucking cool aid man
Let's let's get up these stairs over here the stairs
No, no, no, no, no the other stairs. Oh, you mean like up here? Yeah
If you can get underneath this i'm trying
Anyway, don't worry
Come on you need to like you need to like give me some
Ah go go go go go. I can't i'm can't fit through the door
What just killed that got destroyed? I don't know. I didn't do it
where
Get out of here that guy
Hey, fuck you
Can I punch this guy? It's too far. It's not too far
Get over here
Oh my god, he just teleported
He just teleported
There we go. There we go
No, it's not
No, oh, it's got uber into okay. I guess we win. I'm not upset anymore
This is so fun
You just make a giant fucking robot heavy mode
Killed the spy. Are you sure he's dead? Yeah, he might be dead. You can't get him. Oh, it is not. Okay
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do why is it lag lag?
Uh, uh, oh shit, they're heavy. They're heavy use uber use uber. You got it
That was awesome immediately he was like, oh shit he couldn't get through