Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary,
and tonight I'm going to be playing as the Huntsman Sniper with the Huntsman, the Crush
the Spy in the Face Baby, the Huntsman, the Darwin's Danger Shield, and the Bushwhacka.
Now I take the Bushwhacka off because honestly it's there for no reason. Pretty sure I swap
it out with the default Kukri in a minute here after my second or third death. And speaking
of deaths, this gameplay is crazy. Take a look at the number right now on the top of
the screen. After, of course, you take a look at me shooting that scout right in his teeth
with an arrow, but there's a minute and 25 seconds left. I was in a Skype call. Me, Boo,
and Stealth were all in a Skype call. We were just raging at each other this whole time.
You don't even understand. They had us spawn camped the entire time. And the round before
this, they were absolutely rolling us and dominating us. So we were just in the Skype
call going, like, this is bullshit. I'm so, oh, this is ridiculous. Oh, Spy, look out
for the, and it was just crazy. And then watch what happens here. The mood in the Skype call
went from, oh my God, we're going to hang ourselves depressed to the most joyous, amazing
occasion. Like, really? Because we've all been in this situation before. I know I don't
speak for myself. When you get on Team Fortress 2, you want to play, you want to have fun
with your friends, and every single round you get into, you happen to get on the team
that is the unbalanced team, and you lose every single match. That is exactly what was
happening to us in this string of games we played. I think we did maybe three or four
in a row where we were on the unbalanced team and we got rolled within two minutes of the
game starting. Also, right there, does that happen to anybody else? My mouse, my optical
mouse will sometimes just freak out and just move around in random directions. I want to
know if anybody else has that problem. But take a look at what just happened over time
right now. Getting on the cart as the Huntsman sniper, I got a heavy with me now. We actually
capped this point. And from here on out, it is a total roll. We absolutely destroy them
in a way that I can't even really comprehend. And I think I die only one more time after
this right here. And it really was just crazy. Nobody really expected this to happen. We
were in the Skype call, like I said, just in shock. I kept on landing these shots, you'll
see I get some really, really amazing Huntsman shots coming up here. And we were just stunned.
It's like, wait, wait, wait, this team was just totally dominating us. They were destroying
us the whole time. What just happened? Why are we winning now? I guess it's just the
nature of the Team Fortress 2 beast in parentheses quotations right there or whatever you want
to call them. I think because this game is just so ridiculous, there's so many variables,
anything can happen. So as you saw with one second to go being spawn camp the whole time,
we managed to still cap the point and we're still going. I believe this is the only time
the cart stands still for more than one second without moving. After we get it through the
middle of this tunnel here, the next time it stops is at the last point. And while I
have a minute or so here while we roll the cart, I want to talk about an update for you
guys on the model search, the search for a CGI model maker or something, however you
want to phrase it. But before I get into any of that, I want to say thank you so much to
all of you guys. Everybody that sent me a PM or that sent me a comment telling me a
certain modeler or even if you offered up to do the service yourself, I really appreciate it
guys. I got a great response. Thank you all so, so, so much. But I think I've narrowed it down
now. I think I've got the guy I'm going to try and contact. Hopefully I can make some kind of
arrangement with this person because I don't want it to be like, oh, hey you, yeah, hey, go do a
bunch of work for me. Like I wanted to benefit them as much as it would benefit me as well.
So just wanted to make the update that I no longer need any modeler names or any community names
or anything like that because I think I got the guy. But thank you everybody regardless, like I
said, if I ever need anybody in the future, I will definitely make another video asking for it.
So let's talk about the gameplay again here. Look at this pyro. This pyro was so laggy I couldn't
even hit him point blank. The amount of lag that was being generated from that guy's bloodstream
was off the charts. And look at that guy. You see that guy fall off the edge?
I always love when that happens. And let's talk about upward now. Speaking of like falling off
the edges and upward being a crazy map, this is a pretty difficult map to get a gameplay on.
As you've probably noticed by now, there's only maybe two or three upward gameplays, including
this one on my channel. And that's really just because it's so long. If you do not roll on upward
or even bad water, to be honest, if you don't absolutely can lootly roll the other team,
or when you're on defense, if you don't defend the point really well, you're going to end up
with like a 45 minute round. And this happens quite frequently. I spend at least 20 minutes,
25 minutes at least in most of my bad water or upward rounds. So it can be quite tricky
sometimes to get an actual gameplay that is watchable. Because like you guys know,
I don't like uploading like 27 minute long videos only because it kills my internet and my computer
will just explode if I try and render out like a 30 minute video. I did that one time before,
and it was for a Q&A video and my computer like exploded. So I don't want to do that again.
So coming up to the end of the gameplay here, a demo man takes out the sentry that's at the top
left. I get critscrigged for I think one second and I end up getting a critscrigged kill with
the huntsman. And it was just pure luck. One second he had it on me and I got the kill with it.
And I still can't believe we came back from such a huge deficit. Because I mean, we were down to
one second at the first point and less than five or six minutes later we win the game.
That is just unbelievable to me. And I give a huge standing ovation to my teammates.
We were in Skype saying, Oh my God, this is great. What an awesome comeback. And it really was. So
thank you guys so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And I will see you guys all
next time. So take care, everybody.