Hey, what is going on everybody?
Jerma here with some Slender.
By popular demand, a lot of people wanted me to play this.
I got a lot of comments telling me to do this.
And I looked up some stuff on it, and my god, I'm not ready to play this game.
But you know what? It's Scarce Saturdays, so we gotta go.
The whole point of this game is you're supposed to collect eight pages
and avoid this thing that's in the woods, the Slenderman.
Here we go. This is just a giant wall in the middle of nowhere.
Oh my god, a page. Okay, there's one.
How do I pick it up? Okay.
How do I zoom back out? How do I zoom out?
Okay, Q. What is that noise? What's going on here?
I'm just gonna run. I don't even want to know. I'm not gonna turn around.
Oh, where is this guy? I don't want to go in the same direction that he is.
Oh my god. He's right behind me. He's back behind me.
Oh my god, please tell me there's like a place I can go over here.
Get me out of here. If I'm holding down shift and I can't run that fast.
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Team! Go, go, run, run, you mother.
He is right behind me. Just go.
I found a little archway. A little archway. That's what I want. That's what I want.
I don't see him. Don't see him. Don't see him. Don't see him.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Go, go, go, go.
Let's grab this note. The drumbeats are gonna drive me crazy.
Can't run? What the hell does that mean? Can't run. Can't run. Great.
What is it, like a bathroom in the middle of nowhere? What the hell is this?
Alright, I gotta take like a dump. Hold on, I gotta go in like the bathroom.
This is a bad idea, man. This is a terrible idea. There better be a note in here.
Oh man. Oh my god. Oh my god.
What's with this bathroom? This is the weirdest bathroom I've ever seen in my life.
What is going on up there? Oh, there's one. There's a note.
Help me.
Wonderful. Absolutely wonderful.
Where else have I not been? I'm lost in the forest.
With a madman.
Oh my. That was him. That was him. He's right behind me.
You have to run faster, you son of a bitch. Go, go, go, go, go, go.
What's going on? Sticky keys? No, screw you. Oh my god, he must be right behind me now.
Dude, like Windows just had like an error because I hit shift way too many times.
That's a tree. Oh my god. Oh my god, oh my god.
Just don't look at him. Just don't look at him. Just go this way. Go this way. Go this way. Go this way. Go this way.
Oh, man. Oh, you...
Where's the other notes?
Alright, this is different. This is different. This could be a note.
Could be a note here on one of these big trees.
Come on, give me a note. Give me a note. Give me something.
I have no more run. I have no more run. I have no more run. I have no more run.
This guy is just a relentless prick.
Dude, playing Ring Around the Rosie with this guy right now is not a good idea.
I just walked into a wall. I just walked into a wall.
Well, I'll see you guys all next time. And the link is in the description if you want to play that game.
Slender.
I'll see y'all soon. Take care, everybody.