Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here and boo and MLC stealth and Cadbury
Introduce yourselves guys say hello. Hey, baby
So on the screen you're probably wondering what in God's green gravy is going on
We're doing an all-heavy man versus machine match. So this could either be very very bad or very very good
Oh my gosh, I've already lost some pull out of hell. Yeah
No, oh hey
This is over like we're not gonna we're not gonna best get past the first wave
We're gonna get like a d-minus
All right, so somebody's gonna have to be on money just go like fist of steel and just
There's no way oh
There's no way
All right
Hey, what's going on everybody? Yeah, Jerma here with face cam for two
Playing on man versus machine with a bunch of buddies and we're doing all medic say hello guys
Okay, I have an embarrassing question can someone please trade me a blue
So we actually just tried to do all heavy that didn't work so well, oh
Get him get him Taz Oh
Cadbury
Why this guy have crits why does that guy have a hundred percent crits
Why is that bug?
Do that guy has a legit 100% crits right now
Okay. Yeah, we're not even hurting them
No way dude
He just got smoked
Yeah, hold on that doesn't count that doesn't count
We forgot to buy things oh
Man, this is such a failure. I just spit all over my desk. Hey, what is going on everybody?
Jerma here boo stealth and Cadbury here. This is the third time we've done this intro
This time
We're gonna do awesome. Oh
We're not gonna get past wave one. I don't even know what I want to use
There are times a charm we will get this I at least we have to beat one
Goddamn round as all one class like I refuse to give up until this happens
That is the goal completing wave one is the goal
We did we did heavy slightly we just about yeah true I wasted all my height
See the problem here is one person is gonna collect all the money and the rest of us
Don't let him get it. Oh god. Don't let these bastards get it
There we got it. We actually gonna do it except. There's a ton of them coming around this right side right now. Oh
My god Wow
No
We're gonna do it
We're gonna complete this wave
Get your face we beat it we beat it
We got a really we got an egg. How did we do? How did we get an a on that?
Thank you so much for watching really do appreciate it wave one. We could finally completed wave one. Oh
My goodness. Yeah, but take care of buddy. See y'all soon
That's legit the end of the video