Hey, what's happening guys? Jerma here with the binding of Isaac. Now I'm gonna do a sort of let's play of this game. I don't really want to call it a let's play because this game is friggin hard. So I'm gonna do as much of it as I can, probably at least three or four videos, try and get through the at least first three or four levels. So we'll see how it goes. If you don't know what this game is, this game is made by the
same guy that did Super Meat Boy. And I love Super Meat Boy. So I gave this game a try. I got a lot of PMs, a lot of comments saying, hey, you should play the binding of Isaac. So I said, apse-freakin-lutely, dude, let's do it. All live commentary, by the way. So we'll see if I can freak out or not. I've already played this game a little bit at Burger Boy's house. So I sort of know what to expect, I guess. But it's, it's a very twisted game, as you can see. You're a baby that shoots crying eyes of death. So we'll,
we'll see how good this goes. Get out of here, Beetle. Also, this game can be very, very much attributed to games like Star Tropics for the NES. If you've never played Star Tropics, it's a game where you went room to room dungeon crawler style. And hold on, I gotta go through. Actually, I'm not gonna waste my key. But it's a game where you went through dungeon style just like this. You can also say this is just like The Legend of Zelda too. Takes a lot from those types of games. All right, let's see here. And like I said, the game is very twisted. I'm
gonna get stuck. The worst part about this game is if you die, you have to start all the way at the beginning and you lose everything you've done. So that really is a downer, for sure. But you clear all the rooms. Once the monsters are all dead, you can keep going. And it's pretty difficult later on. God, I keep, I'm gonna get stuck here. Man, this is not a good start. This is not a good start at all. Come here. Come here, you walking corpse. Oh, a chest. I will take you. And it's bombs and a
heart. Okay, there we go. That's what I like to see. All right, let's go. No, I want to go down. Let's go to the right. So I'm gonna try and complete as much as I can in one video. We'll go with the, if I die, I'll probably stop the video. So let's see how far I can get without dying. Or how far I can get. Oh, that's the boss room. Don't want to go in there. Oh, there's an item room right here. 10 bombs. Oh my God. Couldn't I blow something up over here? I'm pretty sure I could. Wait, wait, wait, what? Why do I have a, oh, there's a fuse
coming out of my head. That's kind of twisted. Can I, yeah, there's nothing I can blow up. What can I blow up? Wasn't there something? Maybe I'm just crazy. I am crazy. I absolutely am just crazy. Let's just get out of here. The binding of Isaac. And everything's random, I think. Correct me if I'm wrong, but I believe everything is random. Let's go to the first boss. Isaac versus Gemini. The twins. Oh my God. Okay, yep, yep.
All right, why is he green? What's with the green thing? Let's drop some bombs. Bomberman style. I'm going to get myself killed. I get it, I get it. So when he takes a breath, I'm going to drop a bomb right down his throat. Here we go. Blow up. Hell yeah. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. That's creepy. Walk into that. This is pretty easy. But I'm not going to say that so soon because obviously, run into that. Obviously the game is going to get harder. And there's a lot of dumb ways you can just die in this game. Give me those hearts.
What is this? Pentagram. Damage up. Oh God. All right, more damage. I got a bunch of bombs. Things are looking up. Let's go. Let's go to the basement two. Isaac just wanted to play with his mommy, but his mommy hates him. The story is, I guess, pretty morbid. Not sure I want to go into the details because this game is very, very messed up. But it's, it's, you know, the story is okay. It's very twisted. Ooh, I got plenty of bombs. Let's go get these chests. I got plenty
of bombs. I'm not worried about losing them. What's in this chest? Ooh, coins, life and another bomb. What about over here? Oh yeah. I only need one to begin with. I'm an idiot. Let's go left. Why not? Oh, and we got to get rid of the chocolate sundae. That's a chocolate sundae. Don't be like fooled. That's chocolate sundae. Oh, I don't have a key. Oh, damn it. Oh, you used. Okay, I get it. Shit. You have to use the keys to open the chests. That was a mistake. Probably could have saved that.
For the golden chest. Speaking of bombs, let's drop one right there and right there. This damage up thing is awesome. You kill these things in two shots. That's awesome. All right. Watch out for the stakes. Watch out for the steak and cheese subs. Oh boy. A coin. Oh, the cauliflower of death. He's going to blow up by his own. There we go. Okay. Nothing over there. Nothing. Now, if I'm missing like secrets in this game, just make sure to scream in the comment section because damn it. No.
Because I want to make sure I'm getting my money's worth. Speaking of money, this game is only five dollars. So if you like what you see and you want to try it out yourself, it's only five bucks on Steam. So yeah, I'm blowing it up. I'm going to go get the chest. What is that? What's down there? What is this? Can I get in there? Can I blow it up? I don't want to go in that door because I want to use the key on the chest that's over here. Let's just go.
Two hearts. Thank you very much. Full health. Oh, okay. Here's a conundrum. Do I open the chest or do I open the door? I'm opening the door. It's guaranteed to be an item. What is this? Faith up. Whoa. Whoa. I just got three extra hearts. Holy crap. Can I fill my? Oh, it's just, they're just there. I think they're temporarily there. Yeah, they're temporarily there. Let's go to the boss. And I'm all beefed up. Isaac versus Mastro. Monstro.
Oh, he jumps around. Okay, this seems pretty simple. Okay, that's fine with me. Go ahead. Keep puking. Oh, boy. Walk into that bomb. Boom. Nice. This game is disgusting. Like, look at all like the gross stuff all over the place. If you're not for the faint of heart, I apologize that this game is pretty insane. Let's just say, okay, this is grapefruit juice. And the stuff on the sides is
chocolate. And this guy is just a big jelly bean. No, no, what is he? He's a certain snack that a certain candy he is jujube. He's a jujube. So don't be alarmed kids. It's okay. It's just ketchup, grapefruit juice, jujubes and chocolate syrup. So don't worry. It's most of the third level. Die. Will you just die? A radioactive spider has appeared in the basement. What the hell does that mean?