Hey, what's happening everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Soldier with the Liberty Launcher, or the Liberty
Launcher, the Strange Shotgun, and of course the Equalizer. And this is probably my first
Liberty Launcher gameplay, since the thing came out back in June of last year. So it's
been about four or five months, so I figured I'd give this thing a go. I also plan on
doing a calm angler video as well soon, so be on the lookout for that video. At some
point in the future, I just don't know when it's gonna come. Probably in the next few
weeks. So what I want to talk about, specifically in this video, I want to bring up a couple
of things. The first thing I want to bring up is the rocket speed on this thing, and
how after playing with it for a long time, you can really screw up your Soldier gameplay.
Now let me just brief, before I tell any of this, before I get into the story at all,
I want to say that no, this is not like the worst rocket launcher, this is a great rocket
launcher, I love this thing. But what I would say to anyone that wants to use this rocket
launcher, and use it well, and continue to use it, I would say get your hands on this
thing as early as possible, and stick with it. Because if you transition from the normal
rocket launcher to the Liberty launcher, or if you go back, oh I've played for a couple
weeks, I'm really into this weapon, and you go back to the normal rocket launcher, you're
gonna see a pretty weird problem where you can't really hit people with your rockets,
because you're so used to the different speeds. Now I would say the same thing about the direct
hit, but the direct hit has a totally different mechanic, they're not really in the same ballpark,
because obviously the Liberty launcher and the default are the exact same thing, the
only difference is the rocket speed and the lower clip size. There's no other difference.
So I'd say going back and forth between the direct hit and the default is fine, because
the direct hit has that other mechanic, that straight on fast hit them in the stomach,
get them right in the gut mechanic, that you can get used to and go back to the default.
Now this is not a boycott the Liberty launcher video, that's not what this is, I'm just giving
you guys my experience with this thing, and fair warning that if you're new or if you're
thinking about trying to play with the Liberty launcher a lot, then be weary of your default
rocket launcher going back to it, because it happens all the time to me, I get so screwed
up. So the second thing I want to talk about in this video is specifically the new update
that is looming over all of our heads. I'm sure a lot of you guys know that the Dr.GroardBot's
people, they have a Scout pack and they have a Medic pack that's kind of just sitting in
the wings, and I think we're going to get it soon. I hope we get it soon, I hope we
get a ton of stuff soon, but one of the things I was thinking about, and I was talking to
somebody about this the other day, is the Scout. So the Scout is supposed to get one
of these Dr.GroardBot packs, and I was really really trying to figure out, I was really
trying to piece together in my brain, how a Scout GroardBot pack, that's a hard word
to say, GroardBot, how that pack would work. Because the Scout with a laser beam, because
all the GroardBot stuff is laser beams and alien stuff, how would they put that in the
game? I can't imagine a Scout running around with the Phlogistinator or something. If any
of you guys have any ideas, if you think you know what they're going to do, definitely
shoot me a comment or shoot me a PM or something, because I like hearing your ideas, you guys
know that, but it's just blowing my mind. I cannot imagine a Scout with some kind of
crazy laser beam, because that, it scares me. And also the Medic, the Medic has a new
Medigun apparently you could use, a laser beam Medigun, I just, I'm so, I love this,
I love this time period. Once we get into this period before a huge update, there's
so much speculation, there's so much stuff, everyone's making up these crazy item ideas,
everyone's throwing stats around, everyone's throwing ideas around, I love it. I love going
on the Steam forums, let me know if you guys do this as well, I go on the Steam forums,
the Team Fortress 2 sub-Steam forums, and I just read all the crazy ideas people have,
and I read all the interesting things people have to say. It really does get you hyped
up and it puts you in the update mindset, where you're just waiting, is it going to
happen this week? No. Is it going to happen next week? No. When is this goddamn update
going to happen? And you really start to get so hyped and when it launches, I log on to
Team Fortress, I see the blog post, I see the new update, and then of course you have
to deal with the downloading, where you don't download the whole, it takes like 12 hours
to download the update, but once you get that update, it is the most fun ever and it's like
Christmas Day. I also, I want to bring up something about the gameplay, if you noticed
in the background here in the gameplay, I, they had a teleporter up on the second floor
over there, and I could, I went up there twice, I went up there the first time as you saw
with the shotgun, I put five shotgun shots into that thing, and the engineer was repairing
it, and I came back and I put three rockets into it and it was still up. Now I don't know
if that engineer, it was just a coincidence, and he was just back there that whole time
just whacking at it, or if that's some kind of glitch or something, I have no idea, but
I was really mad about that. I couldn't believe it, because I sacrificed my life pretty much
two times to try and get rid of that thing, and it didn't work. So I have no idea what
was happening there, that's either a good engineer or I'm just crazy. So this is going
to be the end of the video guys, thank you all so, so much for watching, I really do
appreciate it, and I'll see you guys all soon, and let's get this update rolling out here
Valve, huh? Take care everybody, I'll see you all soon.