Alright, what's going on everybody? It's Germa here with Boo Man 61 and MLC Stealth.
Gonna be doing... Hey, I'm trying to do the intro here.
Gonna be doing a live commentary on Payload Race Hoodoo.
And what am I doing? I'm just like standing here.
I'm playing an engineer. I'm just like standing still going like, okay, so I play this game like this.
That's just like you're a Germacraft where you're telling stories and building the same tower of blocks and taking them down.
I gotta move this thing. I can't stand her anymore.
Did you say Payload Race? Did I say Payload Race?
I think you said Payload Race. Maybe I did.
We're here on Payload Race Hoodoo.
Is Payload Race where there's two of them? That's not what this is.
That's not what this is. If that's what I said, then I'm totally incorrect and that's not what this is.
This is on regular Payload.
Oh man, they're gonna... No, I got it. I got it. I'm good to go.
They seem to have a lot of soldiers.
Unless they get an Uber, I don't think they're gonna be able to get over here.
Oh, come at me. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god.
Ah, I knew that was gonna happen.
Is that sentry still alive? Yep.
I was trying to back away from it. I was just getting hit too hard.
Boo, the floggy pyro bastard.
Wait, what the... Oh, I went in his hell border. Whoops.
I need to change my name.
Oh, I just shot through that. Oh, lucky crit.
There, they got it.
Alright, time to go like real floggy pyro.
Trying to get another sentry up. Come on. Come on.
Alright, there's another sentry sitting here.
Go, go, go, go, go.
That was close. Spy, spy pyro, spy pyro.
Spyro. Oh, save Martin Van Buren's...
We got it, we got it. Teleporter.
Or, what's that called? Oh god, I don't have any ammo.
I don't have any ammo.
God, get this spy out of here.
No, keep him off the cat. No, they got it.
Oh my god, it just teleported right into the middle of the wall.
Shit.
Yeah, this teleport is still up.
Oh, not anymore, not anymore. It's gone.
That's spy. I knew it.
I can smell ya.
I can smell ya from a mile away.
I can smell ya getting off the elevator.
Oh, wait, that's from Home Alone.
Oh, come on.
I can smell ya getting off the elevator.
What was it? Home Alone?
Phony bop.
You were smooching all over everybody.
That is such a fantastic movie.
And happy new year.
What did you call him?
That's a spy.
Wow, we have like four snipers sitting in the back here.
I just got clubbed.
I got the spy. Oh, save my century, thank you.
Marcus Van Machinery, you are...
Machinery.
Am I even saying that word right?
For the longest time, I didn't know how to pronounce the machinist with Christian Bale.
I thought it was called the Machinist.
The Machinist.
That was a sniper up there.
The Machinist. Oh my god, that guy.
How is that guy still up there?
Yeah, he had nowhere to go.
The gates closed behind him.
Kind of trapped himself.
Poor bugger.
They're coming through the tunnels up ahead.
Oh, get through there.
Let's get this thing built.
Oh, beautiful.
The devil man up on the top left.
He's being a real prick.
Yeah, there's a heavy up there and a medic.
He's trying to take this stuff out.
Oh god.
The heavy's dead.
Oh, they're trying so hard.
I'm moving it.
I'm reflecting everything away.
This thing is going to go down. You good?
See? Look at that.
It's all right there.
What's up, pirate spy?
I think he clubbed.
I'm reflecting every single thing.
I didn't realize you were doing that.
Thank you.
You were just sitting next to this man.
Wow, that is crazy.
You've been babysat by a pyro.
I'm just going to shoot down this hall.
All right, I think I can leave now.
Oh no, I can't.
No, they're going to get my dispenser.
Oh, the devil man's back for more.
Here's a real test of might right here.
Follow me up here.
I'm going to put the sentry up in front of that god damn door.
No, I'm going to die.
I just had two quick runs in a row.
Go up those stairs.
Go up around the left of this corner over here.
I'm going to try and put the sentry right in front of the door.
Go up there and protect me.
Is that a spy?
All right, lock it.
Good.
Did they open this door?
They are in big trouble.
I almost just made that devil man kill himself.
I'm going to save my dispenser.
Sniper in the tunnel.
I just saw that.
I was trying to reflect it back at him
the second it opened and it would kill him.
Which I almost did that.
Oh, great.
Not happening.
You're not taking this out.
Oh, he got it anyways.
I tried.
I tried to run.
I'm doing my own cold demo right now.
Did you just kill him or did he kill himself?
He killed himself.
Okay.
I scouted him.
He has 5,000 kills.
It's fun being a troll pyro.
Demoman in the caves ahead.
I need a medic.
Oh my god, there's two demoman up on the left.
The left walkway.
If you have sentries, they're going down.
Trying to shoot up there.
Trying to punch him through.
Open up that door.
Get slotted.
Oh, three health.
Okay, that's really cool.
They got anything going on?
They got a dispenser. Get out of town.
That's a spy pyro.
Where'd he go?
I have no idea.
There's the teleporter.
Did they get another one?
I think there's another teleporter somewhere.
Oh, that's so unlucky.
Oh, it's a battle of wits.
He got me.
How does he have full health?
There's not health right there.
I hit him twice with that frying pan.
That's what we call grade A bull snip.
Two demoman on the car and a mini sentry
behind it.
This is bad news.
Okay, I'm going heavy.
They might get this.
No attack. I'm on the point.
Oh, damn.
No, get him up.
Dude, I have no...
Oh, damn.
I got a lot of points.
I had a critscreek. I was going to give it to you
right away, but I just got murdered.
Oh, well.