Alright, now I'm gonna change the title. What's it? What should I change the title to? This is a From Software game, by the way.
Everyone that's gonna go, what? What? Wait, this is From Software? Yeah, From Software.
Here's how From Software was a part of this game. I think like two people walked into the office of the
people making this game, from From Software, and like drank out of the water cooler and looked at
what they were making and said, yeah, that looks alright. I don't think they had very much to do
with this. Maybe they did. Alright, Metal Wolf Chaos. I need a title though. Title, Metal Wolf Chaos.
From Software made this. Please click. Metal Wolf Boppin'. I like that. Metal Wolf Boppin' brackets.
From Software made this. Did you know that? Click my stream. Please watch the whole thing.
I like Metal Wolf Boppin'. Now this one, people said I was gonna really like this.
What do you think? Am I gonna like this? This is like a mech kind of jump around and
shooter game. This is gonna be loud. I gotta protect you guys ears for a second. Hold on.
I'm late to play this game. I'm late to play every game. The only games that I've ever played on
release have been the From Software games. Fuck, you're right. I should have played this like two
weeks ago. From Software presents. Hold on. Yeah, I play every From Software game at launch
and I didn't play this. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I can't see it. We can't see it. There
we go. What? Let's party. Let's party. Good sneaking job. Do I just pick it up right now?
Play now? I guess not. Yeah, I'm gonna turn this up a little.
I don't have any idea what's going on. I know that this is just constant conflict. That's it.
Do you really need to know anything else? Or just constant conflict. That's it. And just hold down
left mouse button.
All right. I'm the president?
Believe in your own justice. Metal Wolf Chaos by From Software.
Welcome. We got to work on this for a second though. Hold on. Graphics. Quality. Get that out
of here. Get that off. Quality high. Use those settings. Um, display. This is important because
this is full screen. It's not full screen. I'm already tough. We already got, I think this is
a 30 FPS game. Should I do controller? I think I'm gonna just, no, I'll do mouse. It's probably
easier to aim. Keybinding sound. Music volume. Nobody wants to listen to this. Voice volume.
Keep that up. You do. I didn't think you did. It was designed with the original Xbox in mind.
Bust that out. Yeah. I'm, I'm, I'm, yeah. I'm into it. Hold on. Dude. Hold on. Dude. No, I know.
I'm gonna stick with the mouse for now. If I hate it, I'll switch and you'll tell. You'll be able
to tell because I'll be like, this is stupid. That's not even fun. It's not even fun to control
this stupid game. That's like, it's just not even fun. Like when I do that, you know that's real.
Put voice on max. Sure. I want to take the volume of the music down. I don't like when music is
playing in my ears. I know some of you Sonic the Hedgehog fans are gonna be really mad about this.
All right. Let's take a look at the keybindings. I'm not, there's probably not gonna be much of
a tutorial. Jump boost. Yeah. Left shift. Change weapons. Middle mouse. Left mouse. Right mouse.
WSAD. Taunt is T. Burst attack. Um hmm. Burst attack. Stomp. We'll do, well I'll change that.
Burst attack with this. Stomp will be this mouse. All right. This seems easy enough.
Yeah. Let's go. I do have a gamer mouse. I have a Razor Deathadder because it's the only mouse
that is big enough to my big fucking wide palms. All right. Here we go. New game. Sellout. No,
no, no. I don't, I don't think anything else from Razor is worth buying. I think I've already
talked about this already. All right. Here we go. By the end of the first quarter of the 21st century.
I do that all the time. Of course the speedy boy says it. Freedom was dead in America beginning
with a large scale military coup d'etat that erupted in various cities throughout the nation.
The rebels seized power in all the central institutions of government. The entire nation
appeared to have fallen completely into the hands of the coup d'etat forces. However, one final hope
in opposing the coup d'etat forces remain. This final hope being the U.S. president himself.
Michael Wilson, the 47th president of the United States, equipped with a special mobile armored
op suit developed in secret by the military, boldly waged his own personal war alone
to take back America's freedom. I do appreciate the like 12k audio bit, right?
Get out my special op suit, Jody. That's back in the day when it used to be looks like CD
quality from the drop down in your windows menu. This kind of party is a first for me.
Mr. President, you're going to burst through the door.
All right. The people outside are really scary. Mr. President, Mr. President,
escape via the Eagle Star in the underground base. Now I'll open the entryway to the underground
base. Please give your guests some face time with her and she. How much damn, what's my health bar?
Oh, shit. All right. Where am I going? Do I have any other weapons or just that shotgun?
Oh, I know my right click. So is it auto aimed during the square? I think it is. It seems like
it. That square is huge. It is sorry to keep you waiting, Mr. President. Enter the underground
base using this oversized back door here. You got it. I'm on my way. I wish I could voice
this. You've got it, Judy. I'm making my way down through it.
The enemy are just lowly foot soldiers. Even at you in fire, they're no longer a special heavy
mobile armor. Anything you say, Judy. That'd be good. I'll be back. I'll be back. Better.
How long does that boost go? The Eagle Star is beyond here. Get going before the enemy chases
after you. Whoa, what the hell was that? While destroying anything that stands in your way.
Switching over your weapons, depending on the situation, is the main key to fighting.
Try out the weapons in your backpack as you like. How do I select them?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Is there like a way to move up and down on them?
Current, current, current. Do I change them?
Scroll. Yeah, scroll on. I'm trying to scroll. It doesn't do anything.
You click. Middle mouse opens it and then scrolling doesn't do anything. I don't have
access to anything. Oh, there we go. There we go. You actually just have to... Okay, I get it.
You have to click left and right mouse.
All right, nice. I'm ready. I kind of want to speed up the turn.
There's an aircraft hangar beyond this passageway. Now, let's hurry. The aircraft
hangar is behind the barrier. I'll open the barrier now. Please wait a moment.
Let's just target the tiger. Just waiting for an air break.
Whoa, something quite dangerous awaits, but with missiles of that caliber,
if you aim and fire, you should be able to easily shoot them down.
Yeah, if you aim and fire. Oh, there's that FromSoftware dodge that I like.
That's it? Oh, I'm hitting the grail in front. Nice.
Enemy's behind. Where? Watch out! Rocket launcher kind of sucks.
If it hits the guardrail, it doesn't hurt.
Okay.
Guard, grail.
Air Force One, protected. I like it. What else we got? Up in the top?
Can I remove the HUD? You're not going to touch here. I'm going to get an S-ray for this one.
Anybody else? No. I'm good.
Oh, what? Oh, no, he got it off. That one guy saved whatever they're fighting.
I don't even know who's fighting. Who am I fighting?
Welcome to Air Force One.
What is this? Is this like, what invasion? I don't even know who I'm fighting.
Oh, that's right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
What? Oh.
Like they were ever invited, they're definitely Michael.
Mr. President, it looks like this party is just getting started.
D. All right. E. C. Rush combo points. What's that mean?
Display KO point details. That's what I'm going to see.
Who believed in his own justice even when it seemed the whole country had turned against him.
DNN correspondent Peter McDonald.
I feel like this is part of that dream game.
I can't make it. I have to save America. We'll have to do dinner on Tuesday instead.
Mr. President, to my beloved fellow Americans. Good evening. This is an announcement from the
government policy promotion department, your American justice and freedom supporter.
First of all, what I would like to tell each and every one of you is this.
Recent events were not a mere coup d'etat, but rather a revolution to correct the wrongs
in the United States of America. To our regret, our nation is in a crisis situation.
Since 2010, domestic terrorism problems have increased rapidly.
Economic disputes originating from the exhaustion of fossil fuels
and the sudden rise in unemployment due to the influx of large scale immigration.
Neither the current president nor the American government took actions to address these various
problems. On the contrary, they have filled their own pockets adhering to terrorist cells.
To correct this situation, Richard Hawk, Arizona insurrection hero and vice president of the
old government and the U.S. military rose to the task at hand. Much like our ancestors did
based in a belief of winning freedom and based in the belief of an independent war
and based in the belief in this great nation. However, to our regret, an evil to disobey this
belief exists in the United States of America too. And here is that evil.
Currently donning this XB88 battlesuit. Who first appeared in Washington and began his
unjust rampage goes by the alias Metal Wolf. His current whereabouts are unknown.
While all of America will be under martial law until Metal Wolf is caught, please
do not confuse the issues at hand. Without fail, the U.S. military elite forces with a combined
strength of 1.5 million promise to smash this unforgivable evil to pieces. This has been an
announcement from the government policy promotion department. Your special remedy for all kinds of
evil. Evil. All right. White House. Reach Air Force One. We did it. Now we have San Francisco.
So we're getting getting attacked in San Francisco. All right. Economy. Technology.
Energy pod. What does this mean? All right. We go here. Should object to targets. Is this all
I can do now? Anything else? I guess we're going here. The Cudito Army that occupies
Francisco still runs rampages as the base of their military activities are built around the town.
Okay. Target areas where enemy forces are concentrated are dangerous, but you can weaken
their moration of San Francisco shine as a beacon of hope. I think they literally got this voice
to speak over the phone. What's the call name?
Okay. Got to have a drum roll.
Here we go. All right. Ooh, you actually get to make your own
loadout. That's cool. All right. Equipment. How much money do I have? Total money. 15,210.
All right. Develop. Fund and research. Fund research and develop new weaponry.
Investment. Fund weapon research. Manufacture. What is this? Single bazooka? Oh yeah, I think so.
Development level zero. Development costs 11,000. I have this. Oh, but what do I want the next one?
Okay. Missile launchers. Tracking capabilities. Grenade launchers, sniper cannons, rail guns,
multi-missile launchers, flamethrowers. I want a flamethrower. Yes. So this is now available
for development. Okay. So I can have an FLT 350. Nice. Okay. So now manufacturer. Flamethrower is
is shit. Rare metal required. How much do I have? Insufficient money. Damn it. Okay. It's all right.
I'll be able to do that next. All right. Equip. Shotgun. No, this is fine. This is like level two.
It's all right. Oh no. Mr. President, you left the office with a briefcase full of hundreds and
that's it. You only had 15 grand. What are you going to do now? Enemy list now. All right. Let's
go. Start. Meanwhile, in the skies above San Francisco. Mr. President, how's the sky?
Okay. Talk like you're in the wind. The correct direction there is there's a loud vacuum cleaner
and you're trying to have a conversation. The gentleman in me goes off the clock
at five p.m. Take America back. Here we go. Place the enemy army by destroying the target areas
where the troops have amassed. Destroy all the target areas. Give me. No. Give me. I want the
rocket launcher on this. I'm a sniper. All right. And then I want the rocket launcher here. Got it.
Or how about bazookas? All right. Give me. I want something better on here. Yeah. I want this.
And then give me this rocket. All right. We're going to stay with this thing. All right. Here we go.
What's this? Oh. Ammo. You need to string the chain to get it, right?
Hello? Oh. You have buildings. Okay. Anybody else? I think that's it. No? Dead.
Destroy the cage with light firearms and rescue the people inside. This is light, right?
Scientists. All right. So save the people in the cases and give it to the bad guys.
Let me get. Oh, I mean, they're on it. I want a copter.
Okay. I got to get a bazooka here. Hit. Hit. I'm definitely doing missiles. Missiles only.
I want to double. I want missiles on either hand. Heavy arms ammo. What's that? Shield unit.
Cool. Should I do double flamethrower? Just glide around to flamethrower? I think that sounds
like fun. No, don't. Okay. I blew it up. I didn't mean to. But it happened. No. Shit.
What's that? MP7. No, that's fine. Let's go this way. She told. I thought I told you.
Don't do that. All right. Let me try to get like a 20 or 30 chain here.
There's got to be more people on the screen if you get a better chain.
I missed Lou. I'll get it. I'll get it. Come on. Bonus rare metal. I should be blowing up all
this shit, right? What did I do? I missed something here. There. Shield unit.
You can break stuff by dashing through it. That's good to know. Thank you so much for telling me
that. Whoa. Are there bosses in this game? Yeah, there are. No, I know. I'll take care of it.
Can you shoot two things at the same time? Yes. Oh shit. I'm out of ammo. Uh oh. I'm at 49. That's
enough, right? I just hit the damn sign here. Don't ask chat. 99% have never seen the game before.
Yeah, but some people have. There's like one person here that's played this whole game
and has S ranking on every level. Oh shit. Where's my health bar? Is it the top right?
That like teal bar on the top right? No item? We failed. Left. Oh shit. You're right.
What does it say? Nice. M939. Nice. What does it say? Nice. What's the bopping for in the title?
Uh, I can't really explain it. The first hour of the stream will explain why the title is
metal. Metal gear bopping. Whatever this is. It's, you know, like roll my hand and
spin it around a few times and slap my wrist back and forth. Put my finger and my palm up
to my mouth. Lean forward and say you got to be there. You know that thing that I do?
What? How would I successfully explain what bopping is? I can't. How would I do that? It's
not possible. I want to use those. Bad. Look at all that. Look at all those yellow circles.
Come on. I got to keep it going. Chain. Chain. Chain. I'm going to get it.
Oh, but by the way, I didn't really talk about what's happening tomorrow.
Tomorrow? Wait. Target? What? Destroy all this stuff? Oh, that gets the building.
I'm getting like a real bad, like, lady is drunk vibe. Ooh, look at this. Take out the support beam.
I need more than just this rocket launcher if I'm going to do this.
Oh, anyways. Tomorrow. Tomorrow. Tomorrow. So tomorrow, I have bought an Xbox 360 for one
reason. I bought the old, not the Kinect, the thing that came before the Kinect. It only was
available for like two games. It's the Xbox Live Vision Camera. And it's called You're in the Movies.
Not the U-Star one. This is before U-Star. This is the first one.
So it's going to be a fucked up screen tomorrow, I can guarantee you that.
Press F for you. Super. That's not, I pressed, you got me to press F. Is there a better way I can do
this? I feel like this is, oh no, I'm out of ammo. Missile alert. Oh, you weren't lying. Missile
alert. Missile alert. Where did it go? Oh, okay. Right, right, right, right. Okay, I get you.
Yeah, that's tomorrow. Tomorrow's, tomorrow's Terraria. No, Terraria is going to move to Sunday.
We're destroying the area. Tomorrow is Xbox 360. Green screen, fuck face stream.
All right, here we go. I don't, what about ammo? Drunk. I can't hurt this. I need something better
than that. What's going on? Am I sniping? Why am I standing still? Stop, stop. I don't want to stand
still. How do I get out? I don't want to be sniping. Mr. President. Mr. President. Mr. President.
Snake, yeah. Oh no, I don't want to do this again. Fuck. Oh my God. What the hell. All right, I,
no, I don't know. I don't know, I had the sniper out before and it didn't zoom in. I couldn't get it
off. I tried to take off the sniper and it wouldn't do anything. He didn't light the bonfire. No,
it didn't. All right, let's just go. I don't, I don't need to destroy these.
I know where I'm going. This is a bootleg armored core. Here's the funny thing about that. Made,
this is the same com- Prime software actually made this. Don't walk into the front of me.
I want to get a better weapon though. This is, the shotgun's fine on here, but I need the, yeah,
the ammo. No, and I didn't. I know what they are. I don't want to use that much of this though,
because I need it later for that tank. Mr. President. Mr. President. Mr. President.
Mr. President. Happy, sad, excited. Say it all different ways.
Give me your best. I'm sad, Mr. President. Now give me your best. I'm happy, Mr. President.
I'm on it. Michigan report from hell. That game was insane.
Michigan report from hell was, because I had to play that on like a weird emulator because it
wasn't localized. That was a Japanese game, right? I don't think that even released in the United
States. We're going quicker this time. EU. Yeah, but that's a PAL console. I didn't have a PAL
console. Make sure to use your rush from the circle was flashing. I'll give it a try.
Why? Wait, let me save these people. No items dropped. Got it. That is actually really,
really effective. Somebody said I can't tell the scale of anything in this game.
It's just a lot of running, shooting, sprinting, dashing. How big am I? Am I just a guy in kind
of fallout armor? I'm not supposed to be like a hundred feet tall, right?
What? Which one is it? You're supposed to be five, seven. Nice. That's pretty big.
Shut up. Shut up. I think you're a five, seven in this game.
I don't know. Let's look at the official documentation of the game manual.
Imagine being short and actually being a dick. I got you. No bullets. All right. No, no, no,
I don't want to waste these. Here we go. Nope. After this, it comes a tank and then I'll take
care of it. I got the... No, this is an epic building. The boomer is fuming. It's bad after
all those boomer comics because I know what it's like to fucking roll out of bed with my back hurt
because I slept on it wrong for like an hour. You'll know. You'll see. You'll see.
Ah, that's it, right? Is there more down here? Defensive argument? No, augment. Defensive
streamer. Something like that. Something like that. Light-armed ammo. Okay, is there anymore?
Did I miss ammo back here? Whatever. There was something back here. No, there wasn't. I'm
getting jibbed. Don't ban us. Why would I ban you? What have I happened to scare Saturdays? Scare
Saturday. Let's go. Let's get in close. Go! Come on. Bring it down. This is fucking weird.
What do you mean it's weird? What's wrong? What's the difference? This is a mech game.
What do you mean it's weird? This game is weird. Bring it down. Come on. I mean, I guess it is weird.
You're right. All right, now this is where I gotta be careful because I'm not gonna screw this up
again. Get rid of the tank. Here it comes. Here we go. Gotta watch that explosion. I feel like
she's talking to me like I'm sick. Make junk food out of him. Turn him into, turn him into,
turn him into a chicken nugget. Is he gonna? Bam. No, I'm not.
What? Is he vulnerable somewhere? This game's really weird. This game's not that weird.
What is so weird about this game? Stop it. Oh, it's a weird game, huh?
Why? It's like a mech shooter. Why is it so weird? This game's weird. What a fucking weird game.
Okay, I don't want to lose again. So, okay, I'm good. Are they even reaching? Shoot it in the gun.
Right in the gun. Yeah, I gotta hit it right in the gun. Ah! I'm like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not dead. Am I? Oh my god. Why? What happened? What? Why did I just lose instantly? What
happened? What happened? I don't understand. Is it missiles? I have to do this whole thing again.
What a weird game. Play the Shire thing. I gotta pee. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I need to upgrade.
Fuck. I shouldn't have bought the flamethrower. This is a mistake. I gotta upgrade. You're not
supposed to win there. You're supposed to listen to the From Software game. I just walked up to
like the third boss. I had to get souls and upgrade my guy. I have to upgrade my, go to
my garage and upgrade my character. That's just what it is. All right, I'm gonna pee. I'll be right
back. Dude, did I seriously pick the flamethrower, which is expensive and I screwed everything up?
I played a From Software game and I put like six points into faith
in the very beginning of the game. What the hell did I do that for?
All right. Let's get this fresh beer open. Ooh. All right. Develop. Can I do anything else?
Manufacture. Like a new shield. I should have, I should have manufactured one of these.
Missile launchers, grenade launchers, sniper guns, rail guns. I need to just do explosives.
Like grenade launcher or something. Damn it. Why did I pick flamethrower? Why'd you guys let me do
this? Just redo the first level? I can do that. Oh, I can do that. I can do that. You're right.
I can do that. Oh my God. You're right. I can do this. Yeah. All right. From Software. Let's go.
Get out my special ops suit, Jody. All right. Yeah, I'm ready. Give me like a 30 chain.
100 chain. Get some money and then I'm going to upgrade my missile launchers.
Already grinding on the first level. Kind of, but not really. I would call this a mini grind.
This is not a real grind. Oh, by the way, I didn't talk about this too. At some point after the
carnival stream. I'm not going to do it yet, but it's going to happen at some point in September.
Uh, I'm going to be pulling the streams back. Start time by about an hour.
I'm going to be starting my screens somewhere around this time.
Like between like, well, not now. I mean like, you know, a couple hours ago.
And the reason for that is because my streams have been going much more than like four hours
like they ever used to. Before I moved to Vegas, my streams were like four to five hours long.
They're starting to become six, seven, eight hours long, more than half the time, I'd say.
And what ends up happening is if I start my stream at three or four o'clock in the afternoon,
after that, like six, seven, eight hour period, it starts to become like two, three, four, five
o'clock in the morning Eastern. And who God knows how long. So I've decided that I don't
want to have my streams because they've been going late. They have them. That's kind of the theory
because it used to be, you know, I'd started like seven o'clock Eastern and my streams would end at
like 11 or 12 Eastern. They didn't go for that long. I have, holy shit. I'm going to get like
a good lot of points for this. I forgot to move. I need 250. All right. I'm good. Let's go.
That was one of the things I want to talk about though. Keep the train going at 265.
This mission is so short, so it'll be fine.
I also have this thing. I'm going to use it, but I think it's better for everybody.
Beyond this passageway. Now let's hurry being on Pacific time is as far back as I could possibly
be. Come on. Come on. Did I go too fast? I guess I could be in Hawaii and I can notice when, you
know, when people started to get tired and it's to be one, two, three, every stream in the last
few months for pretty much, I think like 80% of every stream has gone to like at least two or
three a.m. Eastern. I never used to do that before I moved here. I would much rather have
the streams end around 11, 12 Eastern than be still chugging along. I'm going to get money for
this. Put it into my missile launches from September. Yeah. I want enough time for people
to know that that's going to happen. I don't want to just start like today is kind of just
I'm just seeing how I like it. I would have started at like three or four, but I'm just
trying to see how much I like doing this. I'm going to do it a few times, but officially I'm
not going to say that yet. Probably after the carnival stream is when it'll be officially my
stream will be pulled back like two hours because it's easy for me to be like, yeah, as of today,
I streams are not going to start at 12, but that's not a reality. All right. How much money do I get?
Two air force one. So stream length will be the same. Just where it will be there,
what period will be an S rank. That's an A rush. What is this rush combo? That's really bringing
me down. That's fucking up my whole GPA. Well, that's how you get that's $69,000. That's so
I'm I did it correct this time. You have to be dashing. All right, let's go to the garage.
The coup d'etat. I'm ready. Develop. Here we go. Manufacture. Let's get that flame throw.
All right, let's get it. Develop this weapon. Yeah, I have one of them now. All right. Investment
handguns. Where are we going? We want multi-missile launchers, rail guns, sniper cannons,
grenade missile launchers. Develop. The ML-60ST is now available for development. Do it again.
How much is that? Do it again. Oh, the gold VE is now available. All right, I got 30 grand.
Let's try. Let's get some of these. ML. The ML-6ST ham. Let's go to the manufacturer.
Let's see. Firepower 1160. No, no, no, no, no. I want to look at it. Basic missile launcher
offers a balanced set of capabilities. Fires missiles vertically. Specialized tracking capability.
Lock-on speed F. Guidance system S. Range S. 1060. This one's just better. I'll get it. I'll try it.
I want this one too, though. Grenade launchers that don't have any. I definitely want more of
these. Where are they? I want two of these. What? I need active research in here to be able to do
this. Machine guns. How much is it? Let me go investment. 10,000. Let's just see. Let's get
something. MP7 is now available. I can't make it, though. All right. That should be all right,
though. Let's go to equip. The handgun is all right, but flamethrower. No, I can, I can,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I can have another weapon here. Okay. That's cool. Where's my
flamethrower? Get that on there. Oh, it has to be both hands. That's annoying. Well, the sniper
rifle is stupid. It's not good. I don't want it. Let's do, uh, this one and then the ham.
Okay. Shotgun pistol. That's easy. These two are fine. And then I definitely want to be able to
have at least, yeah, these two. That's good. All right. Let's see if I can do any better this time
and not lose at the last boss instantly. Save it. Go. No, I'm messing around. I want to test
them out, though. Here's this. Here's this. Let's set the flamethrower first. Am I, where, am I
reloading it? Is it using the boost, too? That's not good. It uses the boost, so I can't speed
down the road and do it. Use the boost to get through it. I'll try. Move out of the way.
Let's do, let's do shotgun for this. Right in the beginning here, it's really not a big deal. I
can just get through this. Once the towers become a thing. That's when I move on to the rocket
monsters. I also want to talk about the highlights activity book stream. I had the, I brought the
mods together and we talked about it for a while. And it should be interesting. Don't, I'm not ready
to give any dates or anything right this second. I want to, but by the end of this weekend, you'll
have a real kind of plan and date on how that's going to play out. All right, let's give me the
hand and test the hand. This is so much better. Having two missile launchers is a thousand times
easier to take these things out. Weird, this is a weird stream.
I think this changes everything. How many bullets do I have? I have 50. That's all right.
There's also a stomp. That's right. There is a stomp. Oh shit, I totally forgot about that.
This stream is quirky. Would you get, you wouldn't classify me as a quirky streamer, right?
What did you guys say? A musician? What does that mean? You get what you think I'm a quirky
streamer? I don't think so. I think I'm more of an intelligent streamer. Like when you, when you
turn the stream on, you know that you're going to get some really, really just smart things.
Intelligent, smart, like discussion.
As I don't know now where to go. I was too good. I cleared it too quickly. It's down here right
here. He says that as he plays the video game equipment, smashing toys together and making
explosions sound. That's the metal gear solid. Travel through time cigar lady sound. Slow that
down. Stretch out the tempo a little. You got it. You got it. It's there. You know, I didn't, I
wasn't sure about this game at first, but now that we've played it for about an hour or so,
half hour, I'm, I could see how I'm, I could play this for a little bit. I could see this.
Let's try to get through the second level. That'd be great. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This will explode, right? I, I, I was standing right there and I did it. I mean it failed. You
just saw me do it too slow. I was not too slow. That was perfect. No, I'm not going to do it.
I was going to just say something just to say it, just to say words, but I'm not going to do it
because it's like, it's like one of those video meme things that have just been like a thousand
of them. I will tell you the thing that I was going to say, just, just to like say is on the
screen right now. Like the word is on the screen and it's a meme that's been just done a million
I'll give you another hint. The thing that this originates from, uh, the original source material
will probably be around in two to three hundred years. It'll be on season like 300.
Judy, stop. I need ammo. Otherwise this is not happening. How much ammo is in the other ham?
Or it almost sounds like her lines have been pitch shifted a little bit and slowed the tempo
has been changed, not pitch shifted. You know, when you listen to a audio recording that just
sounds off, even if it's pitched a tempo change by about 10%, a normal speaking voice just sounds
normal because you hear me talking and you, you, your brain connects all the dots in between.
Yeah, I have an accent, whatever. Right. But the second that you slowed down speech, it sounds
really strange. You can hear every single mistake. Why is this not falling?
So me going like this, hey, what's going on, everybody? Slow down tempo speed is like,
hey, what's going on, everybody? And it's just like, oh, you sound like shit. Is that actually
how ugly your voice is? It's like, yeah, it is. He's drunk. Oh, fuck. I have to pay attention.
Nobody talk. You see, can I not shoot? What is going on? What the fuck is happening? Oh,
I didn't close it. Get this off too. What am I doing with this? Well, I only have three shots in
this. Dude, something's fucking hitting me and it's bad, really fucking bad. And it's almost
killing me every time. Is it the missiles? Is he pretending? I'm not pretending.
What would I be pretending? I've done this. This is the third time I've done this. I think I'm
going to fucking pretend to like get hurt by this. This would be such a dog shit stream if I had to
do this a third fucking time. Do you understand? Why would I want to do this a third time?
Do I want to make your viewing experience horrible? I've got like a fun idea. Let me do
the fucking like second tutorial mission six times. Maybe everyone will leave.
Dude, okay. Did you see what happened? What the fuck, man? What? You gotta be kidding me.
This thing does so much damage. I'm getting hit by these like stray rockets that come in and just
kill you. They do almost the entire life bar. This is the Tails mission. What is that? I don't
know what that even means. Oh my god. Oh my god. This is unbelievable. Like what the fuck is this
game? What? What? That was like stupid. Why is this game like this? I'm just, I'm just,
I don't even care about points. I'm getting... Oh, shut up, Judy. What the hell was that? That
didn't make any sense. I'm like actually upset with this game. I'm going. Just go. Just go. Go.
Each area. Destroy each target and blow the air that's come from the adjacent areas.
When there are too many reinforcements... Shoot the missiles? I was shooting the missiles. I was
targeting with my, that's why I had the assault rifle out the whole time. If one of them touches
you, it takes like 60% of your health. ...facility. When communications are made, largest, so destroy it.
The dying joke. Yeah, why would I ever do this three times? Shoot the missiles. I'm shooting the
missiles. I was dodging them and shooting them. You just rewind and watch. I was shooting the
missiles. I just watched the last encounter. I wasn't just letting them hit me going. What is
that? What is that thing flying at me from across the screen? What are those? Those aren't missiles,
are they? No, no, they're, what are they? I think they're bugs. I'm getting hit in the face. What's
hitting me here? Should I shoot those fucking things? Nah, nah, I'm just gonna let them hit me.
Now, I'm saving my missiles. I want, I'm saving my hand missiles.
If I don't do this right now, I'm gonna refund the game. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes.
Do I get extra health? Why am I taking so long? Tank. I hate that fucking tank. I hate it.
I'm just going. I don't even care. How many times does he stop, how many times does it take for him
to stop pretending and play at the normal? Well, usually what happens is, I don't know, after about
the fourth or fifth time of like LOL, he's patting his screen and he can't beat it.
Like we'd laugh about it and I'm like, what? I can't do it. What happened? I can't beat the
level. And then everyone like laughs. I've had like six or seven times. I turn the face,
came on and I go like, what? I died to the tank. And everyone like laughs like LOL,
you died to the tank. He's like, he can't beat it. And I get like a fucking clown whistle and I go
like. I looked right into the fucking lens. I go like this. I just go. Nevermind. I can't even
turn the camera on. Yeah, I die. I die. And then I go like this. You know what I mean? Like,
what is that? It's my ceiling. Where is this camera? Why is it over here? You get it. You
get the idea. I go like this. Oh, that's why. That's why it's fucked up. There's a big explosion
and it fucking takes, like takes me out. Like, oh no, I can't believe. I'll show you. I'll give
a couple of examples. We'll keep the face cam on for just a minute or two. Just so you understand.
Right. So I am going to keep the face cam on for this. Because that means I have to like, I can't,
I can't like do any dumb like facial features or anything. What on the bug cam? If I lose this
fucking thing again, I swear to God. I'm gonna be spreading like lips on chat. Am I out of ammo for
this? Oh, just. I'm not doing this again. I swear to God. I promise. This game's fun. I'm gonna get
my acting on my flies down. Oh shit. Let me fix that. What are you doing? Oh, I almost died.
Okay. I'm going to do it. People are going to come into the stream. They can fucking hate this
stream, but I'm going to do a stream. Here comes the video. Yeah. People are going to hate this,
but I'm flustered right now. So we're going to do it. Here you go. You ready for this?
I can't do this. I'm going to try. No, I'm not even like, I'm not happy enough to do this.
Let me get rid of this for I'm going to make this quick. And then here comes the tank and I'm going
to get it right. Turning the face cam on means I have to like behave. All right. Here we go.
I am ready. I've got my two launchers. I shouldn't even use this here. I should use it on the actual
tank. That's the problem. Okay. So I don't, I know I can't double it up because they have to shoot
the missiles, right? Like I shouldn't do this because then I have to shoot the missiles out
of the air. I don't have anything to shoot the missiles out of the air. I just have to get,
I had to just do good. I just have to dodge the missiles. I can't even do this. It's impossible.
It's not possible to do this right now. Use your shotgun.
Oh, where are they? Here it comes.
I just shut my nose. My nose just closed shut.
You can't tell me that I'm doing, you can't tell me that that's okay. Don't even tell me that's
okay. I died. I died. It killed it. It killed me so fast that it gave me 50% of my health back.
I don't have anything else to shoot them out of the air with.
It's killing me and bringing me back to health. This is, it's toned up too high. The game is
broken. It's a broken game. It's killing me so fast with these missiles that it's actually
fucking resetting my health. There's a wrong number here. Toned incorrectly. It has to be.
I need ammo for my assault rifle. Offensive argument. Come on, give me something
that's not, I need ammo in this gun. Ammo, light arms ammo. Got it. All right. Good.
Good. Good. Good. Shield unit. Got it. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Fuck off.
No, not you guys. Where's my, there it is. And then I need this missile alert, missile alert,
alert missiles, missiles alert coming in. Where? Missile alert coming in. Missile alert. No bullets.
Dude, you can't beat the game. You just don't, the game doesn't, you can't win. I'm convinced.
Nice haircut. See how fucking big my hands are. This is a full size.
In San Francisco have, Mr. President. Sure. All in a day's work. All in a day's work.
It just begun. Fight will continue. Oh, Eagle. The America inside my heart is still alive.
Okay. Camera, I can turn this off now. I don't need it anymore. That's a hundred. I don't care.
I don't care. That tank was dumb. New weapon. MP7N. Saving the citizens increases your economy
rating in San Francisco. Survive saying the scientists increase your technology rating
in San Francisco. Seven. Okay. I've got some money. What is this? What is this?
That doesn't even look like me. I mean, it does, I guess. Look at that huge chin.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I gotta get this on here.
Uh, it looks like, it looks like something dragged this chin. Did you drag this down?
Did you smudge this in Photoshop? I don't know. Did you smudge this in Photoshop?
Are you sure? No, you definitely did. I don't actually look like that, right? Do I?
No, you did the smudge tool in Photoshop and you're just making me look like a fucking idiot.
Yeah, it's a smudge tool. No, it's not. Look at the clip. Oh no. Hold on. This is really,
hold on. What the fuck was that? Wait, what? No, what? Did I get linked to wrong browser?
Where did it come from? That was the noise. What is going on? It's the wrong video,
but the fucking Twitch clip is still here. Did you hear that? Right? Where is it coming from?
No bullets. No. Stop. Stop the browser. It's not even playing anymore. There's nothing on,
there's no browser playing right now. Therefore, it's impossible for there to be anything else.
Right? Oh my God. Where's it playing? No bullets. I don't have it open. I don't have it open
anywhere. I swear to God. Where is it open? This fucked up. Give me the steam overlay. No,
this is on the steam overlay browser. This is on the steam. I don't know how I did this.
I'm going to close every window. This music. I'm going to close. Every window is closed.
There are no windows open. This fucking clip does not exist anywhere. Oh my God. This is going to
drive me fucking crazy. Okay. Hold on. I fixed it. No, no, no, no, no. I don't look like that.
That's a Photoshop tool. Right? That's fucking horrible. I, I, no, I can't fucking believe it.
Thanos chin. Oh my God. I'm done. What? No, I thought that was the face I was making right now.
A sharp rubric of cannon fire echoes across San Francisco. President Wilson
commends his counteroffensive against the prize president's regime.
The liberation of the city struck a chord in the hearts of a small band of patriots
whose alabaster souls still believed in the freedom that Richard Hawke had stripped away.
MOA movement had been born and it wanted to talk to get the hell out of dog.
The wings of justice were spreading like an eagle. Here comes the president.
The information management department received an email that might interest you.
It's Thanos's really, really happy, like reverse, reverse brother. You know,
Thanos wants half the people gone. Uh, fairness was 50% more people.
An email. Actually, it's a sound file. Play it for me. Hey, here comes the sound. Yes, boss.
Didn't get very much of that. Uh, we are seeking volunteers to oppose the coup d'etat forces.
Two response from fellow sympathizers. The sound quality is terrible.
Could you try and contact the person who sent the email? Sure. Of course, boss. I ain't ever
going to beat this game. Maybe America's faith and freedom hasn't faded just yet. And Jody,
I'm taking back our country going from west to east. I mean, east, young man. What?
Huh? Mr. President, we got a message from the information management department.
The coup d'etat forces are making an announcement on national television.
Connect me. Here we go. Dear fellow Americans, good evening.
This is an announcement from the government policy promotion department where the password is
overflowing love and daily benevolence. Today, we bring you a most unfortunate bulletin.
Last evening, the city of San Francisco suffered extensive damage at the hand of metal wolf
who suddenly appeared. In addition to slaughtering unresisting citizens, this
heinous terrorist took citizens hostage and made an unjust demand for the release of violent
criminals and the sum of 500 million dollars. This vicious act could easily be the worst in
U.S. history. That like fake cry. Metal wolf's pilot is meaner than Satan himself.
And we will not permit him to get away with acts like this. We Americans will never
yield to such evil. We Americans will obtain our own justice.
All right, that's my line. Although martial law continues,
my fellow Americans, please bear with our situation to defend this lovable nation.
Let's lead the brave fight together. This has been an announcement from the government policy
promotion department where our motto justice over theory is your motto.
We've been made public enemy number one seeking exile. No, I'm the president. I can't be the one
to start a war in this country. I'll be the one to wage the war. Isn't that what is that you just
said? Mr. President. Hey Jody, update me on the situation in the west. Where we going? All right,
we got more. We got Grand Canyon, Alcatraz, Grand Canyon. Which one of these is the easiest?
This is, I mean, this is like, you know, this is Grand Canyon. Destroy the Alcatraz cannon.
Okay. On the prison island Alcatraz, only three kilometers offshore from San Francisco,
the enemy force is setting up a huge electromagnetic Alcatraz cannon to combat terrorism.
All the shelling in the desert region has implanted fear into the hearts of the people
on the west coast. The shelling is directed at keeping the dissidents in check. By destroying
the energy tanks around the Alcatraz cannon, you can stop its operation. The current is so strong
that no one has ever escaped from Alcatraz. Please be careful not to fall in the ocean.
Got a little closer to the mic. This mission goes by the call name. Call name.
Good one. Okay, I have a lot of money. We're gonna go and do some development.
Manufacturing investment. Okay. Let's see, shotguns, machine guns.
Let's get some development. No, assault rifles. Yeah, let's get some development.
Now I can make two of those. Let's do it again. That's it. I got it all. I can do more.
Should I do it again? I'm gonna do it again. Development level two. Yeah. SG-552. Yeah. All
right. Where is it? There's a new link. Of course there is. Okay. This is honestly, this is just
here. Hold on. Just color me green and make me a Hearthstone card. It's like, oh, there's
the greedy Grinner. It's a 1-1. Each time your hero takes damage, a coin is deposited into your
hand. Divine Shield 1-1. No, this. You guys are just bombarding me with links right now. Somebody
make it a Hearthstone card. It's not there. There's a template to make a Hearthstone card.
I want the greedy Grinner. Dr. Boomer. That was quick. Holy shit, that was quick. He didn't do it
that quick. What? This is so funny. It's just stupid because imagine this is a Hearthstone card.
Face. Face is green. And in the background, this is like foam. There's like a wall back there.
You can tell when Blizzard's gonna get real fucking lazy when they decide to do some shit like this.
Why would this have Divine Shield? Oh, I can have like a, yeah, a car, a car drop sound. Yeah.
Hold on. Give me a second. I'll get this. I gotta turn this off for a second though. This is
important. Okay. It's gonna be a little bigger than that. I'm gonna, I gotta like play the
card. You know what I mean? I gotta turn this off. This is fucking so stupid. Can you guys,
okay, tell me if you guys can still hear the, the in-game audio. You can't? Good. All right.
Here we go. Okay. I need a good sound effect. Like an electric splash.
Play the car. Here we go. Let me get a good voice for this one.
Ahem. I'll be taking that one.
Let me play. I'll be taking that one. This is doing it too many times. Okay. Let's get that
and the splash. Huge splash sound. That's it? No, I need a huge one. Big splash. Here we go.
In there. I'll be taking that one. It's a legendary. Come on. No, get this, get all this
shit off the screen. Get off everything. I need a Hearthstone board. Give me a Hearthstone board
image. Give me like a full hand in Hearthstone. Hearthstone board. Here we go. Okay. Doesn't
matter. This. Open Hearthstone. No, I'm not gonna open up Hearthstone for this shit.
Okay. I'm playing my card. I'm gonna tilt it a little. No, it's all right. I can just grab it.
No mana. It's three mana. It's enough. Here we go. What should I play here? I'm thinking maybe
end turn. No, I don't think so. I think I'm gonna play. The Greed of Grinner is a new
card. Seems pretty good. Let's just try it. I'll be taking that one. All right. So he's pretty good.
I think I would... I'll trade with the... I think I trade with the... Oh, I can't actually click
this. I'm a fucking idiot. There you go. Open... I'm not gonna open Hearthstone. No, I'm not gonna
play Hearthstone right now. That was the worst stream I've ever done. I don't even have to write.
I can't open up Hearthstone. I don't even know my password. The fuck is my Blizzard password?
I have no idea. Is that right? Got it. I have to update Hearthstone, guys. There's a new one.
Are you gonna make a hole? What did the stream become? I have... It's not gonna even work.
I have to wait to how Hearthstone is downloading right now. I have to play the computer for this
to be a thing. I need to get like a slam sound effect too of when it lands. That works. That's
really fucking loud. And I'm like, I'll be taking that one to the bank.
Lands. Okay. Program the card into the game. There's a new card. How many cards do I have?
This one doesn't have any transparency though. I can't use this one.
Why would you ever give your minions minus two attack? Oh, there is transparency on it. Okay.
Give all... Oh, give all minions. Okay. I see. I see. All right. We've waited long enough. I'm
doing it. Here we go. That's a new card though. That needs another sound effect.
That's for too long. This is actual clown stream. Yeah, what's he doing?
I'm not... That's not me doing that.
Okay.
Where am I? Okay. I'm sitting in a chair. I'm mad. I'm like, where am I?
Okay. Why is DOS games activated? Hey guys, did you know that evil miscreant got changed?
Don't care. Solo. Just play. How do you play against a computer? Tutorial?
How do I play against the computer? Solo Adventure? I don't know how to do this. How do you play
against a computer? There's so many things here. Wait, let me... I gotta get the game on the screen.
I'm only doing this once by the way, guys. I ain't doing this shit more than once.
I gotta get it and then I'm done and we'll move on. We're gonna move on.
Okay. Where is it? League of Explorers? Witchwood? Die... Oh, practice. Okay, practice.
Uh... I wonder how much I've played this. Okay. Custom Hunter. Custom Hunter 2.
This is probably not even filled out with enemies. With minions or anything. I don't even know which
one to pick. A classic Hunter 2? Custom Hunter 2. Uh, we're gonna... Who cares? We'll play against
a good mage. This doesn't matter. Custom Hunter Password 2. No, I'm not doing all these. I'm not
doing all these. I'm not gonna do this. Please. Don't do this to me. You know I'll stay here for
an hour and do this. I'm like a child. Okay, hold on. It actually does look like they belong
on the screen. Which one of these do I want to mulligan? I don't know. What is this deck?
I have to get down to no cards. Like one card. So I can have them down here. God damn it.
I'm gonna go. I'm gonna rope against the AI. Is that even possible? Okay, I need to get
rid of these cards. Who cares? Use Greedy Grinner. He's meta. Just wait. I need to get rid of this
shit. I need an empty hand. What am I in here for? Is this a bounty?
I don't know. What does this do? I'm doing like a good job.
I just want to clear the board. Okay, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. There's too many
cards. I'm gonna get this ready. I need a like a whoosh. Electric. Electric whoosh.
I'm just playing random cards. It's gonna be empty next time. Okay, electric whoosh. Synthetic
electric whoosh. Let's try it. Good. I like it. Dude, I'm doing better playing random cards than
I was trying to play this game. All right, here we go. Okay, I'm gonna have an empty hand here.
No, I want empty hands. No, I don't want more of this stuff.
I don't have enough room to play these cards. It's a full board.
No, I'm not playing Hearthstone right now. I gotta do this now. Like quick.
Okay, I need to get a six, seven, eight. Kill everybody. I need an empty board down here.
Good. Thank you. I appreciate the killer. Kill all this. Okay, here we go. It doesn't matter. I can
have one card in here. That's fine. All right, here we go. I'm gonna play my cards. That fits here.
That fits here. Let's get the other cards on here. Where is the other one? Here it is.
Blackwater Bay. Okay, where's that other one? There's one more. How many more of these do you
guys have? Pog moment? Do I have to set up a new sound for every one of these? I have to.
No, no, no. No, that's it. No more. I'm done. I'm done. No more of these. These other two
are coming in and that's it. You can't rope against the AI, right? Okay. Where's that other one?
I gotta like make these in audacity. If the opponent has a meltdown, win the game.
Oh my god. I have to make this full screen. Otherwise, I can't see the fuck I'm doing.
Okay, let's go. Why did I even open this? What was the point of having Hearthstone open?
There is no point. What? Just so this is animated? Okay, I'm gonna play my cards. I can only play
a couple in this turn. Let's try. I gotta turn the music up. No, it's all right. It's at a good
level. All right, here we go. This is important. I gotta keep this. I gotta do this right.
Ready? All right, so which one am I playing? I think I'm gonna play
Pog moment, I think. Give all memes in your hand a plus two term of Venus. Okay,
that sounds pretty good. Yeah, I think I'm gonna try this one.
Look at that fog jam. Preview. Oh, fuck you. Preview. All right, it's on.
Preview. Preview.
It ruined it. Imagine if Blizzard put in just like ripped audio from YouTube and it still had that
shit in it for sound effects. It's a spell. The game froze. All right, I need like a pirate song.
It's just accordion. It's just accordion. That's what it is. It's just the sound of an accordion.
Accordion. Windows 95 startup on accordion. What do you mean Windows 95 startup on accordion?
Accordion pirate. I can't. I have to stop this now. It doesn't matter. Okay, here we go.
All right. Your weapon's crossed too, lad. I'll get you from the. I'll get you from the side.
Check it out, boys. One at a time. Good. Record that. Let me be one at a time. There's only one
person. I'll be there waiting and watching. I don't know. Okay, you're just gonna watch.
I still got playing a mana. Okay, here we go. How about this one? Let's throw it on there.
Chad Jexington. This is legendary. You know it's gonna be good. I think I'm gonna place it.
Should I play it? Yeah. No, that's not what I wanted.
I want the sound. I want like that.
I don't think I should do it. I don't think I should do it. I'll play it.
Yeah, let's put it over here. Sounds like a plan.
Not funny. Not funny at all. Get it off. It's not funny.
That's not funny at all. It's already on the board, though. All right, this last one. Well,
there's two more. How about this one? Here we go. This will be good. Okay.
Your time is out. Like it. Print it. Here we go. Your time is up. No, time is out. No,
your time is out, right? Yeah. Your time is out. That's not as loud as I thought it was gonna be.
It's not what I wanted. No, not relaxing. All right, I'm done. That's it. The joke's over.
It's fine. It's over. I don't have to do it anymore. That was not what I wanted.
How is this not a sound? I just typed in electric shock and the first like 10 videos or at least
the first three videos are about G fuel. Is that like a flavor? I think that's a flavor of G fuel.
All right, how about this? This doesn't matter. I'm gonna play this card instead.
Hey, I'll be taking that money from you.
Hey, why can't I grab this shit anymore? I think I played Chad Jackson. Your time is up.
Oh my fucking god. I'm trying to lock it. Never mind. I almost just closed the whole screen.
I don't even know where whatever the metal wolf is still here, right? Yeah. All right. We're good.
Here's the entrance theme that you wanted. I'm walking on a call to arms. Tyrion forgery. Oh,
there it is. What is this sound in the background? Get out of my way.
I could be a fucking actor. Well, that was fun. Like the last three hours of the stream.
I could be a fucking actor. I think I could do it. All right. I gotta let I have to close
Hearthstone. At least let me just beat this though. I can beat this. Why are there two of these?
What the fuck is happening? This shouldn't be happening. There's two. I don't know why
there are two. This is supposed to be Hearthstone. Let me just finish the game. Hearthstone. That's
not Hearthstone. Oh my god. All right. Let me just win. I can do it still. Can I do it still?
It's still possible. He's gonna use it. I wasn't even trying to win. Give me a break. That was
not it. That's fine. I thought I can lose to the AI. I was doing a stupid thing. All right. What
is this capturing? Metal wolf chaos. There it is. That's the game that we're fucking playing. Not
this one. Yeah. That is actually dying to pinwheel. I know. I'm aware of that. I know some of you
are disgusted. But come on. What do you want me to do? I don't remember a single thing I was doing.
I don't know. I'm pretty certain that I was I wanted a better than missile launchers, right?
Sixty five thousand dollars. That's a lot. I have level two assault rifles. Oh, that was a lot of
bits came in. Yes is online. Give $50. Thank you. Thanks for the 5000 bits. I shouldn't have done
so much damage in one turn. God damn it. It's true. You shouldn't. I don't know. I shouldn't
have done that. You're right. New E mode. I don't know about that. All right. Machine guns. I want
better machine guns. MP7 ST. Where's the audio? Oh, right. I turned it all the way down.
There we go. There's that music. Okay. That looks good. Should I do it? No. Now I need to actually
buy these things. Should I do bazookas? I'll do bazookas. No, I have plenty of missile grenade
launchers. No rail gun. The flamethrower kind of sucks. The M72A3 is now available. I need to go
through these and see what they even do. Okay. Back up here. So this is 700. 7600. These are
energy cost zero. Starting capacity. Precision targeting. Fires high powered rockets.
High explosive rockets. Heavy arms. Standard rounds. Firepower. This thing sucks.
Is this range? Why wouldn't you just use the default? It doesn't use a warning. Okay,
I have new ones. No, I don't. Go back to Hearthstone. No, you don't want me to play Hearthstone.
I can guarantee you do not want me to do that. All right. MP7. 100. More capacity. Rate of fire.
Intercepting. Oh, this is... Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm going to need that.
Give me this thing. Energy rounds. That sounds kind of cool. Let's try it. I also have assault.
Here we go. I got the SG552. Upgraded range and firepower. I'll take it. Oh, no, I can't take it.
I'm blind. What's going on? I got... No, that's fine. I'll come back.
Let's equip. Get on there. Let's actually play the game. I know people are going to start snoozing
once we go from Hearthstone cards. I want this. I don't want the shotgun. It's all right. You can
snooze if you want. All right, here's the regular bazooka. We'll wake you up later. Don't worry.
Keep that there. I need to... I feel like the handgun. Why would I even use the handgun?
I think this is fine for now. Yeah, this is good. This is good. I'll be all right with this.
Save the game. Now, technically, I have been playing this game for like two hours,
but that's not true. See? That's not true. I've only played this game for about an hour and 10 minutes.
Wake me up before you go. Okay. Enemy forces occupy Alcatraz Island.
Jodie, what is that daunting thing? The Alcatraz cannon. How original.
You'd never make it on Madison Avenue. Stomp and surrender, Metal Wolf.
Surrender? If you fail to comply, the Alcatraz cannon will zap you backwards, coach. Will it now?
Not if I zap it first. So just take out the cannon? That's kind of cool.
Mr. President, the Alcatraz cannon just started to recharge.
I'm on the move. I'll smash it faster than a Florida Rico.
Siri, what's the weather like today? A gun battery. 65 degrees and charming.
Five minutes? In the center of the island. Wait a minute. This is DNN's Peter McDonald reporting.
That's the heinous terrorist, Metal Wolf, as seen from the air.
He's trying to take over the Alcatraz cannon and destroy the west coast. DNN is coming to you live
and exclusively as these events unfold. Forget him and keep your mind on the mission.
Mission. Mind on the mission. Let's go. I got five minutes to get up there.
I know. This device also seems to supply energy to the Alcatraz cannon.
You should destroy it in order to decrease the energy recharge supply.
I need a... There we go. The ham. Damn, this thing is beefy. This thing's beefy, man.
Oh, clocks. Clocks. Clocks. Clocks. Oops. Sorry. Oh, shit. Clocks. Clocks. Clocks. It's blocking up.
Clocks. I gotta have to move, man. Bang. Watch this one. Even set cool. Oops.
Oops. Gotta be quicker. Mr. President.
I can't move. Come on, get it. I kinda just keep telling you that.
You may or may not already know. There's two of these.
I didn't surrender. What happened?
Come on. If you lie down and sleep here, you'll get sent by the Alcatraz cannon.
Mr. President. Is this scripted?
It's a battery. That thing should take five minutes to recharge.
It was the landmines.
Oh, right. It was the landmines.
Mr. President, keep your mind on the mission, Mr. President.
Laugh with me. Laugh with me. Mr. President.
I was watching Germany yesterday and I'm kind of like a fan. He's like,
I, I, I, he's like kind of fucked up yesterday, but I didn't like that one.
7200 fucking uploads. Yeah, I agree. Something was weird about that stream. It was like, not very
fun. 16,000 uploads. On the page, on the page, all slash all. Yeah, I just like saw this on all.
Like, I don't know who this guy is. But like, I guess I'll check it out and that's weird.
Didn't hit. Get it. Cool. You can't fall off yet, can you? I don't know. Can you? Is that,
does it count? It actually does count. I just had to test. I didn't, I didn't know. I had to
test it. I had to test it. I had to test it. I had to test it. I needed to know. I needed to know.
I watched that stream yesterday and like, I wasn't a fan. I just, I didn't know if you'd,
of course, it's a Dark Souls game. A gun battery that big should take five minutes to recharge.
Until then, head for the Alcatraz cannon in the center of the island.
Forget him and keep your mind on the mission, Mr. President.
I know. Come on. Yeah, I'm from all, like, I know. Is he a YouTuber or something? Like, a streamer?
That's kind of fucked up that his streaming didn't do fun today, though. I'm getting the
creeps. Musician was among the POWs you rescued. He was forced to perform to entertain the troops.
More. Actually, can I put the assault rifle on here? I think I need it.
Of course you can. What a blasted game, huh? The helicopters are the worst. They don't want
to shoot the missiles. I have to get them done immediately. They are the worst. Don't fall off
the edge like you did last time. It's not that hard. Get with it. There's two, right?
It's the landmines. Watch out for them. Blow them up. I can blow them up, right?
No? Yeah, I can. This is tricky here. This is tricky.
Let's get some of those on here from distance. Pretty good. They can't even fire.
That should be enough. Is that not enough? I'm sorry. My real voice is coming out. I'm from
Boston. Fucking dude. Military is being decimated. Platoon after platoon. That's it, right? Be careful.
Where's that new weapon? Did I not equip it? I didn't even equip the damn thing. You serious?
No, I did. Didn't I? Oh shit. Oh shit. That's gonna kill me. No, no. The stupid missiles. The airborne
missiles. Okay, hang on. Don't forget. When the going gets tough, the tough get going, Mr. President.
Yes. Hurry, hurry, hurry. Activate.
I gotta hurry up. No, I'm taking damage. Stupid. 70%. Come on.
How do I get up there?
Your cruelty won't go unpunished. Did I go all the way down to the beginning of the level?
I did, didn't I? Come on. Are you serious? Where was the way to go?
Down this way. Can I still do it? Please don't make a gun. I think I can do it.
Come on. Hey, get that on the news. Open the door. Open the door.
So the U.S. military has had something up its sleeve. Those who interfere will be eliminated.
95%. It's already charged. This doesn't just shoot, right?
Oh god. Destroy all of them. I have to destroy all of them. All of them. It's getting 97%.
If you shoot, I'll hold it against you forever. Get us out of here.
That sucks. I just have to go. Forget about everything else. We have to go fast now. Hurry.
Oh my god. No, I want this. Hurry. Oh shit. I'm screwed up. I need this thing. The interception
one. No, I didn't want to fucking do that. I hit accidentally. Come on. Double it up. Double it
up. Double it up. Double it up. Double it up. What's hurting me? What's happening? The game
is so broken. If you die really fast, it doesn't matter. Mr. President, you're too nervous.
You've lost the first step. The faster you die, if I'm going to die, I need to get hit by like
a thousand damage. Why is this taking so fucking long? I'm shooting the two rockets at the same
time. 40%. I'm not going to do it. The U.S. military is being decimated.
I got to use that. I need that thing to be charged now.
I know it takes forever to kill everything. I'm in. Let's go. Come on.
The POWs you rescued. They were struggling. Shoot it. Okay.
Go. The army has been completely vaporized. Metal Wolf, your cruelty won't go unpunished.
Open the door. I have. That's the super thing. Open the door, please. Why does it take this long?
How do I? Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Justice. Range. Oh, fuck. I forgot that game's
like no longer relevant right now. It's not 2016. Shit. Come on. It's almost done. Got it.
You could seize the area. Under military orders, the soldiers blew up the Alcatraz cannon.
Simply amazing. Clap for me. In real life. The U.S. military gets the job done no matter what.
You better all be doing this. Better double check his back. Today, once again,
U.S. military forces were dealt a lethal blow by Metal Wolf. But thanks to these heroes in our
military, Metal Wolf and his conspiracy have been held in check. Our hearts go out to the men and
women who sacrificed their lives in battle and to their families as well. Any further reporting
is too dangerous. Our news team is seeking refuge. Be the first to know as we continue pursuing
Metal Wolf because yes, the pen is still mightier than the sword. This has been Peter McDonald for
DNA. It's exhausting to listen to. What the hell? But at least the west coast is safe now.
Yeah, that helicopter was a toy. Mr. President. It reminds me of old Star Wars movies when they
used the real models, the real miniatures. A, E, D, D. I'll get a C. No, I won't. $70,000,
$80,000. I got some scientists. All right. Brought peace to the west coast and gave the
resistance a new momentum. But Richard Hawke's messaging continued to have a stronghold on the
American people. Destroy Metal Wolf, we cried along like hysterical. Brainwash children.
And that ignorant chorus became the battle hymn of our presence. In time, we would be made
painfully aware of just the line we were. By the way, Jody, what happened with yesterday's email?
The information management department succeeded in contacting the source of the email.
Really? Let me hear it. Inform the resistance to put a stop to Richard Hawke and his recklessness.
Is this me talking? Right now, I'm aiming for a united uprising and seek volunteers.
What about those events? Metal Wolf, we eagerly await your rampage. Great. They haven't sold out
hope yet. Mr. President, I haven't been this happy since... My anniversary. My birthday.
When I got the job. When I went down a really tall water slide. When I went down the rollercoaster.
Since that supermarket going out of business sale. When I was searching for my favorite candy and...
They had a... It was 60% off and I got to buy like 10 boxes of it. And I ran into a celebrity
and we had a conversation. I found the last at the back of the... And the expiration date was still
good. I know the feeling, Jody. Sure, Mr. President. Oh yeah, I know the feeling.
All right, let's go to the Grand Canyon. Operating out of a massive helicopter base
constructed in the Grand Canyon, enemy continue to oppress the American west.
The target area terrain is sure to be confusingly fierce because the enemy army has taken over
guerrilla bases from the Arizona insurrection days. Please watch your step so you don't fall into the
one mile deep ravine. I'm gonna die here like three times. Use artillery with long range firing
effectively and destroy all the target areas. Long range. This mission goes by the call name...
Don't look down.
Next week. These are all next week on X anime.
That also is a next week anime. All right, let's do... I need range here.
I'm gonna do... I'm doing it. It's insanely expensive but I'm going for it.
The ml14 jaw. That's all I... I can't do anything else.
This thing... $46,000. 1820 damage. That's pretty damn good.
Lock on speed F. They're all F. What's the range? B? That's not that. What? I need
speed. Yeah, I know. I need range. S. I'm gonna get two of these. I want one in each hand. So ham ham.
Uh, what? This is... this range is terrible. So I'm gonna replace this with something that has
better range. I'm not sure I have anything that has better range. I guess I do.
Yeah. I want the interceptor. That works really well. The range on this is
absolutely terrible. I mean, I guess I just do... Sniper? Just because. I guess. It's got range.
Okay. All right. Let's go. Begin.
No. I don't know.
All right. Let's rock and roll. So I need a range for this. Why? Mr. President,
the view certainly is grand. But stop with the don't look down joke, please.
I made one of those before we even started the level. Didn't take it out. I'm gonna say how.
She just did a minus two here. I... yeah. I know. That's what I'm saying.
Okay. So it's under here? Underneath? I don't know. Come on. Tap it. Oh, that was actually
pretty cool. That was cool. There's the target over there. Get double ham on this. It's not even ham,
but... Can I fly over this? Oh, shit. Hold on. Get it. Come on. Hit it.
So now I have to go across this. I can go over there though, right? I hope so. You're gonna make
it? Go free. I need boost for this. I don't want to fuck this up. I want double ham. Oh,
okay. I was not holding down space. I should shift. I don't know. I died. That's not,
that's not worth dying for that. Get rid of the chopper. Scientists to maintain helicopters.
That's what you're saying? How was I only hitting one person?
What a stupid way to say that. Shoot it. Shoot it. This interceptor is so good. How did I ever
live without this? Oh! They're dead. They're dead. Double ham. Oh, you can just ride them
to him too. No, no, no, no, no, no. You're me? No. You're me. Lock on. Go hard. There's
somebody that can react harder. Go harder. P-hugger. React more? That shit is so fucking
ridiculous. I want more reactions. Be louder. Talk louder. He actually wants that. Oh, boss?
Oh, great. It's a helicopter.
Well, I'm keeping out the interceptor. No doubt.
Oh, yeah. Are you kidding me? Shit. I look more into this fucking thing, aren't I?
Oh, God. He dies before that happens. That was so easy. Oh, my God. I didn't even have to play
the game. I thought it was just a mini-boss, guys. That wasn't the real thing. Just a mini-boss.
I only have rockets. I just don't love rockets. Look down. There's still stuff over there that I
gotta get across the way. Where? Where is this thing? Where? Where is this? Oh, it's above.
How do I get up there? Just shoot? Just shoot it? Just take out the bridge?
The chat is more entertaining with Jupiter than with me. I guarantee it. Oh, I am going.
All right. What did you get for having fun in chat? Yeah, you guys are funny. You guys are fun.
The game's not in what you like. You know, just have fun. Just chill. Talk. Talk to each other.
Communicate with each other. It's pretty fun. It's fun enough to play. You know, communicate.
Down to the Colorado River. Double ham. The defense strength is high against live ammunition.
Stay behind the wall. That's an instant death if I get to by this.
I guarantee. You guys need to be communicating. Still live? I'm shooting them out of the air.
This drama is short and bald for anybody else. Like, your TV's fucked up. Come on.
Got it. I'm just not going to put up with it anymore, you know?
Why would I do that? I can say, hey.
How is that possible?
Yeah, I'm just not going to stand for it anymore.
Yeah, no, you're not going to stand. Because you have to stand to be able to see.
Not ideal, but I'm good. I missed the old drama that played Hearthstone an hour ago.
The enemy has been annihilated.
Now I'm turning it over to relief. No more Hearthstone.
Easily brought to Arizona. It really doesn't suit these lovely surroundings.
Jodie, nor someone as lovely as you.
Sure, whatever. Nice work, Mr. President.
What the hell are you talking about? S-B-C-D-A. First A. $200,000. Nice.
Victory in the Grand Canyon proved to be significant. Without the enemy helicopter
squadron to pin them down, the resistance fighters were able to continue their march.
Peace had returned to Arizona, where folks came up with the saying,
where there's a Wilson, there's a way. The man they had mocked as a rebel army major
had elevated himself to presidential standing again, and people were starting to believe
this man had a chance. DNN correspondent Peter McDonald.
Any word from the resistance? Yes, I'll play it for you now.
Wolf, we applaud and appreciate your efforts.
Our leadership has started to rise one brave soul at a time.
You got it! The efforts and our activities,
hoping that the day we revolt will come soon.
I'd like to see that day too. Yeah.
I feel like a mother hen. Okay, Mr. President,
you best hurry and get to the next battle theater. Battle theater?
All right, Phoenix. What's over here? Oh, right, I did that. All right, let's do Phoenix.
The enemy force is apparently carrying out co-campaigns based in a ghost town in the
Phoenix suburbs. I feel like a mother hen.
I feel like a mother hen. This is the voice.
I could have done a much better job. I feel like a mother hen.
I feel like a mother hen. No, that's not good.
The Raider's fleet. This mission goes by the convoy operation.
I liked it. I thought it was good too. Good luck and godspeed, Mr. President.
All right, you want me to develop some multi-missiles?
Let's take a look. Multi-missile launcher. That's expensive to start.
MMLA. Let's do it again. Again.
MMLA-QLS. Do it again. No, I want some money left over.
MMLA-QLS. What are you talking about? Check this pole. What pole?
Check the pole. What do you mean the pole? What are you guys trying to say? What are you
trying to say? What are you saying? Pole, pole, pole. I'm not going back to play that.
What do you mean should I go back and play? We don't go back. We go forward.
No, we already had a chance with that game and it's over. We go forward. Go back and play the
acid game. No way. No, you guys got to sleep in this bed. I was told, get out of this.
I don't like this. Next, next, next. We didn't ask for this. Oh, yes, you did.
I did a poll before the stream started. This is like 80% of people said to play this one.
I was told to play this one. This one's episode is from Toby at the beginning of the stream.
All right, let me look and see what these do. Look, you guys just like talk to each other,
communicate with each other. This is just better. Is there another one? Why is it level three?
I'll give it a try. I'm going to get two of them. I also wanted to do,
it was a couple of these that I wanted, right? No, no, no, this one here, the SG, this one.
It's expensive. It's good though. Bazookas. I didn't need, I had another one of these too.
Range B, starting capacity, high explosive rockets. I'll try this one.
You guys just have to talk to each other, you know? I can't get this one. It's all right.
La Cranda, thanks for the $50. 5000 bits from La Cranda. Thank you so much for the huge amount
of money. And they say, uh, do something funny like the acid game. Guaranteed. Oh, it is too.
Playing that game. That double hand is still fine. I don't want this anymore.
Did I get the flamethrower? No, I need the, uh, the interceptor. Interceptor and,
I mean, are you a furry? I, you know, that's, but I don't care. All right. I'm ready. Save the game.
Stream's not bopping anymore. Yes, it is. This stream is bopping right now.
Look, let me, let me play my game that I want to play. I want to play this fun game.
You're becoming unruly and we're in the wild west. Like a town in an old western,
a radar jamming station is located here. The number of target areas and enemies seem limited.
If you have to say something bopping, that means it's not bopping. I know that's true.
That's like you throw a party. You hire like a DJ and you have a big space. You rent out like a
club for a night and the DJ is playing, just spinning records. Sounds awesome. It's you,
your best friend and like one or two other people that actually accepted and went to the Facebook
invite. There's nobody else there. And you're like walking around like, this is pretty sick, huh?
This is bopping. You've tarnished the good name of the U.S. military
and your reputation as a hero. And now you'll die for it.
Whatever. Am I going to play this for the rest of the night? I don't know. Once I get like done
with it or bored with it, maybe we'll do something else. Maybe we'll do something else. I don't know.
Wanna find out who gets to play Wyatt Earp? Here we go. We got Paul, Randy and Shaq.
Uh, I don't even know who they are.
Paul. Hey, what's up? I'm out of missiles. How is that possible? Who's this guy?
Stomp, for God's sake, stomp. I don't know where he's going to play this for another four hours.
I don't think I'm even going to scream for another four hours.
Hey, sir, you're corrupt. You were never. He's to relax.
There's no victory for a man who loses his pride. Have you had enough?
But I put you out of your misery now. All right. Right now I may as well be loaded into like a TV
show. Like I'm just watching it on my screen over on the right. It's like a radio show.
Roger that. Leave the good stuff for me. This is like a daytime drama.
The best medicine for that kind of headache is pumping it full of a heavy dose of lead.
I think it's all people that are saying, hey, dude, this game sucks. I don't think they know.
This is from stop working. No, I meant to say, oh, fuck. No, I have to like every one of those.
That's all right. I like it, I think. Dude, who made this fucking shitty game? It sucks.
So it's fucking stupid from software. What I meant to say was, oh, whoops. It's not my thing.
It's not my kind of game. I don't think. No, I'm right in front of you, dude.
Maybe it's not for me.
I don't even know where they are. My mini map is jammed.
Oh, that's what's happening. I can't. I'm going to go around and display.
You do rescue. He was forced to sing the blues for the truth. The defense strength is high
against live ammunition. I probably should just go and kill the one of them.
This thing is invisible. Going somewhere to destroy targets or something before I can
probably like. Yeah, this thing is jamming. Installation is the best medicine for that
kind of headache is pumping it full of a heavy dose of lead. Now, you're about to have a headache
when you play this game. Summer morning were among the POWs you rescued. They were probably
used to develop new type mobile unit armor. I don't come. I don't look. It's like if you come
in the light. Never mind. As I say, like it might be a plain game. Like your brother comes in,
friend comes in, sitting there like, hey, what are you playing? Oh, I'm playing Metal Wolf Chaos.
Oh, cool. This game's stupid. OK, I think it's all right. I think it's kind of fun to kind of
run around and just like kind of walk on. No, this game's bad. This game's stupid. Yeah. All
right, man. You want to go home or you want to stay? No, no, I'm gonna stay. OK. You want to go
get food or something? No, I'm going to sit here and just tell you every five minutes that I hate
this game and I don't like it. Why are you here? Why are you doing this to me? I don't know.
What did I do? Are you upset with me? No, no, not at all. I think our friendship is very,
very good. No, I think that too. Oh, and by the way, no, by the way, not only do I not like this,
you're doing it wrong. Am I? Yeah, yeah, yeah. This game sucks and you're doing it wrong.
I thought you didn't like this game. No, I don't. But you're doing it wrong and you're stupid and
you're bad. Oh, and yeah, dude, by the way, I'm like back here right now. Kind of sitting behind
you. You're bald as fuck. OK. Oh, are you sure we're friends? You're really bald today.
I would like to call my mother and be like, Mom, can you come in here and like tell him to go home?
All right, let's see if I can get through here. Get your pork chops ready.
I don't know if it's just me, too, but there's like a smell on this room.
Is that you? Is that your body? Your body smells. I've been sitting here for a while,
dude. Maybe I am like, I don't know. OK, now that one I could forget because I mean,
if you like smell bad, like you don't like it. Never mind. That one's fine.
All right, let's go with the real deal here. Can you shoot him? Nice. One more of those.
Diaper check. Diaper check. Hey, man, like, yeah, you having a good time by hanging over at my house?
Yeah, yeah, I'm having a good time. I guess the game's not that bad or whatever. I just I like
hanging out with you. I like, yeah, just like kind of hanging out with you, too. Yeah, it's
fun to know what you're doing. You can be playing something, you can be eating something, hanging
out. I like being I like when you're here, too. Oh, by the way, show me your diaper.
Can I diaper check? No. What are you talking about? This is not fair, though, because this would be
this is not fair because I did like shake around and pretend I had a diaper on. So like if I
was if my friend was over and I'd like shook around and pretended to have a diaper on
and then later on he was like, dude, diaper check. Come on. Like, what the fuck's going on here?
Okay, yeah, that makes sense. He's just talking to himself at this point.
I'm just like, manically talking to myself.
It's personal personal payback for you betraying us. What the fuck is wrong with you?
Special mobile armor units have been put six feet under town, Marshal.
Feel to be an old west hero. I want to hear the claps, please.
Not too good. I'm not the hero type. I'm just doing my job as president.
I'm good on the chaos. Not much else. The precariously positioned Arizona resistance
base had come under heavy fire from the two three trio of ultra mobile to armored suits.
But when the dust settled the fires the resistance still burning. However, let us never forget the
noble souls who perished under the name under the sun in President Wilson's name. But as we all know,
the government has since built a road that stretches as far from the desert of Phoenix
all the way to the East Coast, the Michael Wilson Highway straight as an arrow and serves as a
reminder to keep our country on the path of righteousness and never become lost again.
Jody, what's the situation on the ground across America?
In the west, areas where the army is pulling out are on the nation. The situation isn't so good.
Don't worry. I'll free the whole land soon enough. Any email from the resistance?
Yes, sir. The man's voice is as cool as ever.
Wolf, thank you. Our membership is steadily
more reliable. Trustworthy sympathizers have joined our fight to revolt.
The day will come soon. When we're ready to rise up, I'll be sure and let you know.
Anything but tear lists. The resistance leader sure. I'm playing this for like another 30 minutes.
Tough as nails. I was going to stop after about 30, 40 more minutes. So that sounds fun.
Now I'll head out to liberate the west. I think I'm going to get a major boss fight here. That's why
I want to wait. The enemy forces strengthening their suppression of Beverly. While the number
of soldiers equipped with heavy firearms is great, if you pay higher attention to their attacks,
there are no threat to your mobile articles in this battle theater are violent. Consider the
advantages and disadvantages and the geographical features as you destroy all the target areas in
the town. It's been an hour and a heart stone joke. 30 minutes actually. This mission goes by the
call name to fashion back to the street. It's a weird name for a little art. Invest in
probably another, a better assault rifle. I like the assault rifles. The SB and missile launchers.
I can't, I'm not going to look for it. What should I do? Probably save the money.
All right. If I buy this, I won't be able to afford the new, uh, no, go back into that one.
Let me see. Try to do two of these assault rifles. If I stun rounds, that doesn't sound very good.
Stun rounds. What's that good against? 80 damage, 200 capacity. This thing's terrible. What does it
do? Try to buy one of these. That's a lot of money. Non-legal. Does non-legal mean anything?
It doesn't sound like I want that. What is this FIFA 08 music? I don't know. You tell me.
You guys, it's, I can't even, I can't even right now. You guys are too much.
You guys are too much for me to handle right now. I like this. All right. Get it together. I can,
I'm fine. I want the big one. You always want at least, you want two different types of each hand.
That's fine. Double ham, but I'm going to replace this with a different missile launcher here.
Yeah, this one here is fine. All right. Looks good. Let's go. Boss time.
Enemy explosive devices are planted all over the city of Beverly Hills.
Destroy all the bombs and liberate the town. Can you tell the Kim shits the bed story again?
Just go rewind like an hour and a half. This is DNN's Peter McDonald reporting.
What you're looking at is the heinous terrorist metal wolf as seen from the air.
Just what will become of Beverly Hills and its stately mansions with a street smell of money.
Stay tuned as this camera and I bring you all the news you want to know. Not him again.
Embed that journalist in the ground. Forget him and keep your mind on the mission, Mr. President.
This is a reverse meltdown. Bombs have been laid out all over town.
Reverse meltdown is like, I can't handle it right now. All right. Let's try this missile.
I like it. That's a lot of damage. Takes a long time to reload. Let's go.
I love this thing.
That's a lot of people.
That's good damage. I'm going to keep my eye out for other ships.
Oh, okay.
The metal wolf has annihilated the troops and plans to capture Beverly Hills.
His end game must be money. This could be the world's biggest heist.
It was Norton. It could be.
If approached carelessly, it will detonate. Destroy it from a safe distance.
Safe distance. Where is it? It's right there.
Some scientists were among the POWs you rescued.
They were used to develop new weapons for the military.
Oh, that takes that. Okay. That's some huge. All right. Whatever.
Missiles. I'm on missiles. Bad.
Oh, this looks promising. The pride of the U.S. military.
Blackhawks raise their ugly heads.
Are they shooting? Let's go. Hurry up. Get out of here.
Bomb? It's driving into me. What are you talking about?
Closer. Come on. Get in there.
Another bomb behind.
Don't get too close.
I wonder if the vice president wants to go as far as to control the music in America.
That would be odd. How many bombs are there? Two more? Three more?
Good. Good work. Good.
Oh, but how many bullets left in that thing?
Is it going to explode? Nice work, President Jerva.
Can I shoot through that? I couldn't even have done that if I tried.
Dude, I did it again. How is that possible?
What the fuck is happening? Go. I don't know why it's doing that.
Bomb. I'll get it. Is this a bomb? Got it.
Any more? I don't think there's many more.
Oh, I guess I'm in fourth. Is that enough? No, it's on SG.
Oh, check this one out. Bingo.
Oh, good. YouTuber and streamer 101.
I'm looking for something to do, per se, when you don't have anything to say at all.
And you're just playing a game? Use short, quick adjectives.
Like, you got it. Bingo. Take on that one. Nice.
Huge. Get smoked.
Whatever they are. Advert.
Cute.
Don't worry about his yammering commentary.
See? Listen to her. Don't listen to my yammering commentary.
Just listen to my one line that I say every three minutes.
All right. Is that not it? What more shit to do?
What are the bombs that I'm not destroying? Cute.
M? Oh, damn. Okay. I gotta go this way.
Shit. I'm gonna be thinking about that now. Got it. Boom.
Fuck. It's that I'm concentrating and, like, I have nothing to say because I'm concentrating.
International superstar. Money, money, money, money.
What business does Metal Wolf have with a 3.2 billion dollar man?
Maybe he's going to take out a loan. Oh, man, he's destroying the mansion.
Add destruction of personal property to the breaking and entering charges.
The U.S. Constitution is downright powerless against Metal Wolf's evil.
Get that radar gun, please. It's messing up my game.
Watch it.
Why did that not happen?
What planet are you from? Wait, are those?
Yes, they were.
Oops. It's okay. I thought it was a bomb. I thought it was a bomb.
It was, but I didn't, you know, I just messed up. Sometimes you mess up. It's okay.
Metal Wolf has control of the entire town. Any further reporting is too dangerous.
Our news team is seeking refuge, but our coverage of these events will continue
because, yes, the pen is still mighty. I hate this thing. Get this fucking like
Paw Patrol looking thing the fuck out of here. It's annoying me now.
Wealthy fat cats will repair the damage, making their homes even more beautiful than before.
Nice work, Mr. President. That one was pretty good. It was all right.
I did that pretty cleanly. Yeah, I'm only studying for one test.
All right, so now that should open up. I've done all the ones that are on the map.
I think we're going to get our first major boss storyline boss.
would do yet another about face jody what's the situation across america
the coup d'etat forces have retreated from the western state yes this should kick the
resistance movement into high gear i can't wait you got a voicemail from the resistance
he's so excited over this thanks to your efforts the stage is set for a united revolt in the west
i'm considering moving ahead however before this takes place i'd like to meet you in person to
talk don't meet in contact you with the details later mr president what do you think i've been
wanting to meet him too so let's get you two together sure but before that we'll head east
until we take back all of america there's no rest for the wicked you said it mr president
well jody at long last we head east we'll reach the east coast in a flat yeah i know we will we'll
try uh-oh metal wolf planning on wiping out new york this time you enemy of the people i
richard hawke won't let you get away with it me richard hawke i richard hawke he will uphold
america justice without you puny be strong
yeah suck missile punch we kind of just skipped right to the end here huh
get up lose and the reason is i yeah the best thing about your talk localized great american
hero so that's a ton of sound effects going on right now that we don't hear because they
drop the audio track from the original put on music and then just talk over it
with like a truck driving sound in the background
that's rumble eat my flame of justice there's a bunch of cool sound effects here that we're not
hearing this is the original justice is always victorious in the end this is original the usa
hey shit all right i guess it's the original dear fellow americans good evening this is an
announcement from the government policy promotion department where freedom in the united states
wasn't built in a day good news finally finally the evil has been crushed this evening finally
metal wolf who suddenly showed up in new york was thoroughly beaten to a pulp by
richard hawke piloting a special heavy mobile armor unit he annihilated the evil
occurring at the same time from a confidential covert operation we have also learned that
underground terrorists and metal wolf sympathizers in hiding were captured
in succession all around the country although martial law will continue until we are sure that
your safety can be completely secured for today and today only let's celebrate this victory
this has been an announcement from the government policy promotion department
your freedom
wasn't even me i already know i can see this i already know what happened they put a guy in a
suit just like a an actor and just pretended to beat him up and that's right what's the special
effects don't even beat a hollywood b movie richard's up to his old tricks again mr president a
special intelligence group this from the anti-coup data forces has ceased actually
we've lost contact with the resistance leader too we have it appears all the resistance activities
have gone south jodie those that died are imposters i am still here so believe in your own justice
did she not think that she was talking to me i won't lose to that false prophet
and the reason is because i'm the president of the united states of america
mr president there's no time for self-pity jodie get me up to speed on the situation in the east
oh my god waging war against more than just the resistance the american people too came
fire hawk called it the citizen citizen reeducation program this friend revolved
private property to a government-controlled rationing system your citizens were trafficked
overseas where he uses lab rats and weapons testing that's probably ridiculous the week and
i'm with her we're trampled down soon all of america and its bedrooms were paved over by
thick oppressive asphalt tyranny it was hawks eugenic wet dream and an unprecedented constitutional
crisis what else is the next chapter president wilson's saga as he continued to rise up against
his former running mate's injustices let's go this is new york my houston chicago let's check
out chicago the enemy force has concentrated strength in the center of chicago intelligence's
most educated guess is that the purpose is to re-educate the citizens and strengthen their
support for the vice president though there are many target areas it is possible to annihilate
by effectively using the train to move from building to building jump on the train destroy
the target areas and let the citizens wake up to their town with its tranquil this mission goes by
the call name not for much longer this is probably the last mission i wanted to do at least the whole
west coast president because i was thinking maybe we'd see like somewhere like other than phoenix
you know maybe we get some like nevada somewhere i don't know like area 51 or something right i'm
sure that would be like making sense in this game with me sorry uh i do want to do like one more
though i want the best of the best which is not gonna have to look i want another tier of assault
rifle sg-552 lr i want another one there it is i got level six assault rifles let's check that
up let's see sg-52sb that's the stun one an advanced assault rifle with outstanding range 175
versus 170 pretty good then there's uh energy rounds that's pretty good 1800 capacity here's
the big one a supreme assault record with incredible range and firepower i don't quite
have enough to buy this but i'm gonna get the energy one all right so i'm gonna do one more
after this one what one more after this there is there is a dangerous level it's later on in the
game well we'll see how far we get so two more so three more so four more i'm actually gonna keep
that on but we're going to remove this and put on that new stuff let's move right here
yeah and get this on there too ham ham good so this is good save it enemy forces occupy chicago
just beat the game i don't know i think this is a lot longer than that target areas and liberate
the town of chicago copy that
well if it isn't the heinous terrorist public enemy number one richard oh you've done excellent
work michael how about a reward to show my appreciation the poison gas will annihilate
the city in five minutes and metal wolf will be blamed for the slaughter of chicago
have a nice day or not michael
now don't start that
oh i gotta do this fast right now then coming to you live from the skies over chicago this
is dnn's peter mcdonald using poison gas as his weapon of choice metal wolf seeks to obliterate
the city of chicago that powered definitely even cruelty has a limit look it up but rest assured
i have faith that the u.s military will put a stop to this that journalist is up to his old
misinformed tricks again please hurry mr president i gotta do this fast here we go
oh i need more firepower than that we'll go ham and nl14 what's that what is that
yes filled with poisonous gas neutralizers that soldiers must be tired of being left in such an
obvious place poison gas neutralizers or kill it are you still alive i gotta get up top poison gas
neutralizers got it i gotta get up top do i have to walk up this oh my god get up there
i just want to get on top of the train what the fuck are you doing there's no time for this
bullshit seriously i need another one of those uh ppms come on hurry up why did i jump down
i saw shiny things in his life pick it up
oh no according to our own dnn human fatality density measuring device the density of poison
gas in the city has already exceeded 50 parts per million metal wolf is a villain down to his last
mecha bolt well these guys hurt so don't get up to 200 300 parts per million
is a symbol of the city and its rivers seeing it open is quite a sight but if we can't cross
we'll be in a jam hurry up but what about the but what about the other stuff i'm overheating
i'm just gonna
things are going the gas will reach a fatal density in another three minutes
metal won't even give us enough time to make instant noodles that journalist is always a day
and a dollar short hurry up mr president all right i do have to hurry up move out of my way
i think more of those gas can things hurry up i need it i need it i need it i need it i need it
on the other side what a mistake i'm in so much trouble now was it gonna get to what is it what's
the lethal 120 live ammunition sorry turn the gas tank thing over here it's not
shit the military the military only has three operating bases left come on where's one
do you see anything i don't see any is it one back there i think there might be one behind here
it's not i'm in trouble please why do you take so long the blast first one took like one hit
gas gas gas gas gas looking for the green thing on the ground drinking go go go go go no green
no green no green don't see any green don't see any green density of the poison gas reaches fatal
limits no i'm trying what do you think i'm doing right now only one remains it's in here get out of
the fucking way it's right there it's up there just shoot it 67 come on no
do it it's gonna blow come on oh no oh my god density has exceeded the critical fatality rate
an utter nightmare it's over chicago is shrouded in a mist of evil
certain death is imminent metal wolf i won't let you get away with this you did this
i gotta have faster shooters i didn't realize i had that fuck enemy all right come on i know
that i know that
middle mouse click then middle mouse
be tired if they let that out in such an obvious place
i think i gotta change something i gotta have something else to be on the other
don't even attack people just go take out the little canisters and get out of here
i need to go i'm gonna go over here this is one of those back here
here shoot the gun
go backwards
hey we're waiting worth using this you just have to use the slow missiles
let's get going right in the middle bang right any and i mean any boost
like the super movie oh why is it not building according to our own dnn human fatality density
the density of poison gas in the city has already exceeded 50 parts per million
metal wolf is a villain down to his last mecha bolt
oh shit i was in the explosion i didn't know it was that much explosion was gonna happen
look at this fucking fps on the mouse too by the way like oh my god enemy each target area has
started up their poison gas control if the density of the poison gas exceeds 181 parts per million
human death is guaranteed destroy the target areas before the density reaches 181 what's that
don't let down your guard hurry up mr president
oh god never say that again i'm gonna turn voice off in such an obvious place
i turned cutscenes off his crazy chin
i showed it why is it doing that mr president i'm trying don't die by the explosions here
mr president be careful out there relax i'll be fine
why won't this gun fire the gun has to cool how much does this gonna have to cool it's gonna
happen again why can i fire the it's the energy gun that's why military only has three operating
bases left okay no no i gotta go across this bridge where's that customer
great to the right yeah wait doesn't it is okay there it is why
i think that was bullshit you guys saw that
look at how slow this is going you saw that i didn't even need to pretend i don't even need
to act you know what i'm saying i don't even need to pretend i don't need to get my like acting skills
out you know what i'm saying i gotta bring up this i gotta i have to is there any more of those things
96 i feel like i'm behind
no don't fire that all right all right there's only two more straight ahead now it's on the other side
i this time i actually have i have um
shut up i where is this one i have to go around here down and through this alley to get in here
is there above the train i'm confused on that one just take it out hurry up i have i got time
don't hurry up please god oh my god i don't need to do that
i got it
where's the last one where is it there's nothing on the screen where is it nightmare the u.s military
has been demolished once again by metal you scared the shit out of me however his plan to gas the town
ended in failure could it be that the hand of god reached down to save us
i've just looked into the eyes of metal wolf any further reporting is too dangerous our news team
is seeking refuge this guy but our coverage of these events will continue i hate this guy
he's the worst because yes the pen is still mightier than the sword this has been peter
mcdonald for dnn i'll say one thing for the guy at least his mis-reporting is consistent
as long as the city is safe who cares i hope he could just strangle him in the end
oh
guys make me like laugh way too much today god is made of steel did you get in touch with the
resistance that's not even what that said no captured by coup d'etat forces he'd never let
that happen i'm sure he's out there waiting to make his move i'm fucking in a laughing mood
tonight i made him a promise oh mr president up to the next battle front all right let's go to
down let's go here the enemy army has dried up the nation's resources and put the people on a
rationing system to construct the space plane launch and landing that sounds pretty good is
gonna be a mcchicken stream absolutely react swiftly as paratrooper react harder predicted
to be dropped in from super assault heavy attack helicopters the objective is total destruction
of all target areas and the super assault heavy attack olajuwon have this mission goes by the
call name winner takes all olajuwon versus metal wool what's the best way to burn body to burn
body fat eat less food and move around here we go i did didn't i want to buy one of these new ones
i didn't have money for it right now is the new assault rifle i'm gonna do missile launcher
sam let's take a look an advanced missile launcher intended for service to airstrikes
that's a lot of firepower
i'll give it a try this thing is good for panic oh shit moments
i like this combo although this is used to be the you know that's the best one i have
i can i can buy the other one but i haven't done it yet the two hams let's replace
this energy weapon thing i'm not liking it it takes too much i don't like it
i'm gonna put on the sam here it is better than this though by a lot
let's go when am i going to come back to canada this is tnn's peter mcdonald reporting i'm coming
to you live today from a u.s military base in the outskirts of houston texas scarce natural
resources sent from the space plane center are collected and kept here the u.s military is
collectively managing these goods under martial law acting as the defense for this area is this
super assault heavy attack elijah one helicopter boston well my boston accents is is an act that's
pretending look at this firepower 44 millimeter m197 anti-aircraft guns 80 millimeter bow force
anti-aircraft cannons two 10 millimeter grenade launchers and finally 12 missile containers
in addition to this heavy arsenal it has the capacity to hold over a hundred soldiers
a veritable flying fortress as long as the elijah one is on the scene
metal wolf get off the winds here fly this little helicopter this little
that's a pretty good car drop sound effect
all right let's go what are those those must be some new kinds of weapons mines they're being
dropped one after another from the elijah one metal wolf will have no choice but to deal with
this firepower swap to our next group i got you sniper unit and the pride of the elite
power troopers snipers this is a scene of biblical proportions a modern day
david and goliath okay mr president well you know what happens like doesn't david win
david wins he throws a rock at the giant's face and hits him right the skull
right by reducing the strong attack that device seems to have improved the guidance
function performance of the Bible Bible spoilers all right sure
all right that does look pretty elite these things gotta go
oh
you get down here then you see what i'm dealing with i'm fighting everybody by myself i don't have
any help not as well all right all right that's it right just gotta go for him now i don't think so
so maybe i can ah what i guess i could it did take damage
it's getting a little bit closer i wonder these breach
let's get the sand i'm just gonna hang up back here is that not reaching why are these not
reaching what is trying to escape from the base
they got to kill these things just gotta do it um i guess maybe it has to lock on
let me try to clear these out these little like crabs you'll get close when there's no more left
going forward or backward it's apparently something behind over here i guess i have to
destroy this thing of course i was doing damage last radar and comes in in the way that you
destroyed his radars this is the only other target on the map
so
take a look at that all right the u.s ground forces have been totally decimated by the hand of metal
wolf but we still have the speed ace up our sleeve that trump card being the super assault heavy
attack elijah one helicopter that's the guy that announces that it's his turn
it's my turn he just that's the name of his attack rushes in and he goes like yeah
and then gets fucking knocked out of the air like you go like dash forward dead
that happens in every single cartoon doesn't matter if it's japanese anime or not
they could be an american anime cover and let's end the mission right now
the elijah one fuselage has been damaged the elijah one i don't know why it is great but
giving up is not in the u.s military's vocabulary and the reason is the super attack elijah one
helicopter is still in action how about destroying the launch me doors mr president first start by
reducing the strong attack how about i just kill it why didn't i just see elijah one's armor plating
has taken an awful beating the dreaded metal wolf fights like a demon on a rampage what's this
the super assault elijah one helicopter this aerial fortress has been destroyed by one single foe
dressed in mobile attack armor but i will never give up hope and hope will never yield to violence
i believe in american justice and my journalistic convictions because yes the pen is still mightier
than the sword this has been peter mcdonald for dnn hey mr journalist take a good long look i
think it's time for a new pen quick strangle before he gets away yeah 220 200 and 300 000
262 we're taking the space plane center president wilson put an end to hawks control the nation's
aerospace resources spoils were funneled to cities across america ending that rationing system
sea to shining sea freedom rang i saw the smiles on each of the american people's faces and i
started to wonder have i been getting this man all wrong jody what's the situation on the ground
across america cruel oppression of u.s citizens still continues all over the nation are we done
yet i guess neither of us will see any time off soon we're very close i'm off to the next battle
zone yes mr president i we're almost done we've almost got the entire united states
safe and reclaimed the enemy force sends out over 1 000 citizens a day from miami
trafficking them into overseas white slavery i'm ready the command cruiser moored on the coast
direct troops in the atlantic it has long-range high-powered missiles on board stay art you're
not halfway done many helicopters join the defense am i not done your attacks on intercepting these
cannonballs the objective is the destruction of all target areas this mission goes by the call
name fully and clear sea once more good luck and god all right i need some more data here
i want to buy the next assault rifle in fact i think we're just going straight up just buy
the next one too how much is the as they saw rifle like 60 70 i'm going for it who cares
oh i'm almost good i have it all i keep pricing myself out i'll get it next time
this thing is ridiculous incredibly long range and firepower fires rebounding lasers
and i saw it with the longest range of any standard arms weapon
and i saw it used by cyborgs yes cyborgs i'm bought that's the first thing i'm buying i just
got this one how much is it to upgrade this one more time
i can't do it again uh i'm just i'm gonna i have to stick with this is kind of what i got
enemy forces occupy miami beach that battle cruiser is the command ship directing the
atlantic ocean troops in this area attack the cruiser and the coup d'etat forces
legally enjoying their holiday and sink them to the bottom of this grand ocean
copy that for their sakes i hope they enjoyed their last rnr the navy cruiser will fire powerful
long-range missiles you'll need sure it will warning mr president bombers be on alert this
is gonna kill you in one hit right received a request from the target area and is on their
way we'll begin all right you have to say the same thing before i know what you're talking
about that's good i want the hand unless you wipe out the launch source i'm trying 12 o'clock
and you got land mines on here too
oh
mr president every time i step on a mine she just goes mr it's like oh just stop
watching the screen just turn off the screen is that the eagle of the atlantic
brigadier general robert i'll like call you if i need something
know what your is inside of there i can tell you this your public enemy number one
i'm going head to head with this kind of firepower isn't the smart way start by crushing
the gun that defense strength is high against live ammunition a musician was among the pows
you rescued he was surely forced to play the ukulele on the beach all the target areas have
been destroyed all right what am i looking at here i'm thinking to him what's the weak point here
i just i gotta get stuck in the way please do not be caught off guard
i didn't even hurt it and this is barely hurting this go up to the radar knock down that tower
wow i got frozen damage rate is over 70 percent
mr president i couldn't nothing so that's how you instantly die
the navy cruiser you'll need constant warning mr president
receive a request from the target area you should cover the rivers and vacationers
this is still here
can i take them all around i'm not sure again like one more thing to
go ahead all right that was quick isn't the smart way i have a full of garage thing bingo
were among the pows to the bomb without any vacation maintaining that battle through
a lot of people over here all right watch out for that shit now it's a question of give me the
the sam shit that's so many i'm gonna reach boys are you aiming at what is this let's just go
all right this is fucking blowing my mind right now oh fuck
oh fuck dude from that navy cruiser are on a collision course yeah i know
um i i did something with way more missiles than i do
it's time to just dance around if you can hit by a barrage with games oh i can't even target
this isn't
what am i aiming at well the thing is i can't even describe it if the game has a target
they they will shoot there no matter what pain in the ass i'm out of bullets on this thing
well it's on this thing too
chin that's all you need to say it's just chin
until the end now carry out your duty carry out your own justice
vacationers uh yeah hold off on that for those who survived great going
mr president it's like broken glass everywhere no one's gonna come vacation here for a while we
need to clean this fucking place up this damn place has got glass and shrapnel all right i'm
buying the assault rifle and then we're doing the final mission i'm not gonna forget about the
cyborg rifle something cruiser rich ecosystem that teams with marine life including new species of
coral which i'm sure you've heard of sea forester in honor of brigadier general robert forester
what does tragedy never be okay what's the pulse of the nation say about all this
citizens have already begun to wake up to the vice president evil intentions he's evil they
couldn't stage a revolt in time just the thought of a revolt is enough i'll take back the nation
soon full speed ahead i'm with you all the way mr president all right let's go the enemy force
super weapons on the people of new york with unmanned super weaponry it treats the eight
million citizens who run about trying to escape like information has been obtained so this is one
of those big giant hands supplying the massive weaponry for taking the huge weapons head-on
destroy the energy supply for this mission goes patient we love nyc fuck and god speed mr president
buy that weapon upgrade it laser rifle we're good and this is probably one of the last missions in
the game but it seems probably a few more no no no no no not investment this one here enrf cb
got it might as well get one of the other ones too longest range rebounding lasers
we're gonna do longest range this one i don't think i have enough i don't have enough rare
metal for that although i can do missiles one more time right yeah let's do it p is available
see if it does the advanced missile launcher capable of penetrating multiple targets that's
pretty good i might get that but in the meantime let me put on that new thing that i got it's fine
uh i'm gonna replace this with that looks kind of cool
uh
hams i'm getting rid of these or everyone told me these are the worst that's even worse i need
something better and this one qls yeah no no no no what should i put here instead i could no i'm
gonna get yeah this is very very useful it's good just to clear out little things i will keep this
sg55 replace yeah just yeah yeah no no the other one i have was better wasn't it
what was it it was not yes it was no it's not this is the better one 800 yeah this is the better one
save it let's go this clock is wrong what is it final mission enemy forces occupy new york city
the dlc's forces are experimenting with an unmanned super weapon to suppress the town
people spider destroy the target areas along with the super weapon talk about massive arm what is
that novel right hello hello how's life treating you richard what do you think of my toot little
pet thanks to him the people of new york city are right now festively uh running around and trying
to escape it's like a big old carnival it's like mardi gras in new york or something
you are a sick take a bite from its super energy wave phaser it'll get you high enough to reach
heaven richard so right in the middle goodbye goodbye goodbye
definitely shoot me though as far right
oh he's dead it already almost instantly killed me all right well so um
the same as him broadcasting those phony news stories mr i know judy get out of the way
this will be dangerous run away how mr president
recharge facility there's a power recharge facility i'll go get it
armor energy the origin of the energy supply should be cut off mr president
so you can weaken its electromagnetic armor that's what i'm doing judy i already see it
where is that spider thing right now oh god
oh
he's already here he's close he's too close oh shit i can't i forgot background these little
spiders we're being like this they must be out of their minds it's destroyed and weakened daddy
is it his power cells or something a lot of power cells
i'm right under him oh my god what has to go for a recharge is that what
he's doing we're gonna charge his battery the energy station is a priority
fuck i thought i could do it i had an opportunity i thought i was gonna take it
if i had that thing i thought i had that um the super charge thing and it's so aggravating i
thought i had it what he said is true i was gonna be dangerous run away for now mr president
oh it sucks that daddy long legs get this energy wave fire power from a power facility
each target area of these powerful electro magnoi should be cut off first is that rocket number like
15 it's like that's rocket like number fucking 30 is it my shooting up air gas or i don't understand
way ahead of us to research weapons of mass destruction
okay i gotta run
why am i using a red candy i don't know is he here yet there he is just
i guess i was still too close
away for now mr president
what the fuck happened the spider's not even near me i don't it's something what am i missing
the guy was down the street if what he said is true
this will be dangerous run away you have to go so fast and then you've run out of fucking boost
you just sit there overheated i should be cut out first here he is i'm gonna get i gotta get out of
here straight ahead i had the target a second ago i didn't even move i'm so disappointed i didn't
even move from the spot and i lost if i don't beat this game the u.s is finished after i do new
york we'll see get away from to recharge i guess it makes sense i'm gonna avoid this dickhead
he's not just gonna turn the corner and be here right he's walking which way is he walking
i'm gonna run into him am i that's far away okay jump what are you doing oh fuck
he's
fucking half mile down the street it's a super long what
i just this this thing just said fail better i gotta cheat me this is fail better
why did they remaster this game what was the point of this
why won't they remaster like king's field or something or like an armored core game why this
one i'm just genuinely curious why why this he's never released outside japan oh that makes sense
all right where is he does he even show up on the map i don't think he does
he's still here no oh god he's still right here though let's get to ski around and try to take
out one at a time because it's gonna go across the whole damn map get out that's where he's
been going you know give me give me give me give me give me out crickets oh shit i'm not being very
funny i'll hear crickets who is the next one up into the left xd is he now is he gonna go
straight or is he gonna go this way straight ahead
yeah i got time destroy it before it gets any closer where is he this is freaking me out that
he's not here where is he right now he's probably coming there he is okay get out now i can do one
more shot please target that not the guy on the ground out of time i don't care i'm not gonna get
killed by that fucking thing i'm gonna wrap all the way around i'm gonna run out of ammunition too
ammunition is gonna be gone i gotta switch weapons okay now straight ahead he's gonna be up here
isn't he you just see i know he's yeah he's right there he's gonna wait for him get that last one
down all right this way cut the corner
eight shots left in this thing where did he go i don't know where he is
uh i'm just gonna go straight ahead hope i don't run into him
be behind me come on this is exactly he was he was right here before where did he go
did he just follow me down oh my fucking god i'm going to scream in this game's face
no i'm not actually are these things everywhere what is shocking me
i'm about to rage for the game i'm about to turn it off i'm so confused
what is going it's my shield low that's what that's trying to tell me pretty distracting
there's a big snake thing there's a big spider thing i don't see him that's not him where is he
oh you've done you blocked me with your shield that's unbelievable you hold that up as a guy
there's a 50 000 pound mech charging towards you and i bounce off of your riot shield
what that's that's impossible impossible i'm going this way
go recharge
what happened what they've exploded on me okay that's it they're all gone
there's only a couple more left no it's not it's still there it's still over there
where is he all right he's going to the field station
that gives me an opportunity to do this right he's charging i don't know if he's charging i can't
even tell i think he's on the way back over here i'm gonna wrap around and blow those all up
i have no more ammo anything anything in it blocks for me anything bonus funds i don't
mr president mr president mr president oh my god
if what he said is true this will be dangerous like i'm just going i don't know where i should go
first i'm just gonna go to the recharge facility first or i think i'm just gonna delete the game
for my end process game in the day that sounds like a better idea just literally remove this
game and uninstall and pretend i never bought it that sounds good too i'm not sure which one
of those things i'm gonna do first where's the recharge station all right hi spider i'm
gonna destroy all your stuff stay away from my nest i'm just gonna pretend i beat the game after
if i even come close to getting it really powerful glad i spent 300 fucking thousand
dollars on that thing what a powerful gun why did i ever do anything besides missiles what was i
thinking what's wrong with me so i can shoot the guys of the infantry faster what on earth was i
doing there he is wait do i have a second here where is he dude all i care i'm so paranoid about
the spider because he can kill you from a mile away i wish i could hang up on you i really do
i would pay a thousand dollars to hang up on me right now there he is hey it's me hey there's a
fucking plasma cannon i missed a shot into the ground whoops first time i've ever missed you
are you down the whole street i'll get you now what the fuck is this goddamn game enemy forces
occupy new york city the coup d'etat forces are experimenting with an unmanned super weapon
to suppress the townspeople destroy the target areas along with a super weapon talk about
massive bar what is that carnival rock if what he said is true this will be dangerous what's
this game have for a rating for now fucking i'm so angry like windows what is going on
i put games on the other monitor i can't see i can't see wait no no what happened to my game
capture it's like all fucked up why can i not move this window i'm gonna do it this time that's it
i'm done after this well now i'm gonna do it watch this shit watch me watch how fucking stupid
this is never mind i'll get it i'm i'm just gonna kill the fucking thing straight up watch this
i'm gonna go behind him any time watch this
mr president mr president if what he said is true this will be dangerous
the origin of the energy supply should be cut off first
oh
meme game they got every bastard demon souls drum software didn't make this oh yeah
they did 20 years ago i'm changing my i'm changing my stuff there there's nothing
to say i'm working i have to beat this fucking spider i'm gonna lose my mind i don't even do
about this i have to beat this motherfucker i have to i'm gonna make some more money no no
this one's stuck this sniping good idea oh what a great fucking idea that is i can't wait to do
that i'm gonna i cannot wait to grind and no no no what don't why would i ever be happy about that
no i'm gonna put i'm gonna get a sniper right but i'm gonna shoot him for 5 000 meters away
i'm gonna win the enemy with stealth capabilities cannot be picked up due to radar in fact let me
just go see if that doesn't mean anything i'm not gonna rage quit the game i have to i'm gonna lose
my fucking mind i think it's time i'm gonna fucking go crazy i'm done i'm done this is a fun game
this is wasn't that fun but it was kind of fun for a while it was it was for a little while
i'm gonna try um hold on i'm gonna see what this does upgrade my health there is no health upgrade
if there is they hit it very well let me see i'm just curious
good luck and god everything's fine i'm just i'm gonna just go i'm gonna see what the sniper rifle
does and from there i'm just curious sniper cannons let's upgrade it let's get another one that's
okay we can just relax no big deal all right let's just i'm gonna use all this shit
okay let's go to sniper and i'm gonna make them and i'm gonna cheese this boss or whatever this is
that's fine i got two sniper rifles i'm fine you can upgrade health look through the menu
what do you mean what are you talking about develop many there's only investment in manufacturing
am i getting baited energy pods upgrade your health it's not like in here this is like
background music and stuff be a true jack streamer and beat this no thank you killer
crockmeyer for the 5000 bits 50 bucks i'm not gonna beat this game i've had to drink pee for a week
and then play the last three missions of this game i think like if you said hey dude do we want to
keep playing this and like beat this game or drink pee for a straight week i'd be like i'd probably
rather do that what does IGN give this game that means let me i'm curious i want to know i'm just
curious i just want to know five and a half out of ten it really makes you feel all right i'm
this is my last mission and i'm going to bed i'm going to bed at 7 30 like an old fucking man
all right equip equip that stupid sniper rifle and shoot it through the spider's
face i will cheese the fuck out of this i don't care i will dump melted cheese all over this thing
i could care less if what he said is true this will be dangerous run away for now mr president
mr president
i'm done with this game i'm not playing it anymore i'm done i don't want to play
i don't play anymore i'm done this is fun for uh it was a fun it was a fun game it was
all right that's it i'm done i'm playing this anymore i'm playing this fucking five out of no
i'm not gonna do that that was a fun game it was fun it was worth playing it was an interesting
experience so they just played hearthstone you never give up that's what i was told when i was
younger don't ever give up i'm beating it right now this is the one check this out i'm gonna do
something different here this is the one i ain't gonna fight i'm not gonna lose this one guaranteed
no sniper rifle get it out of here i got the my saw i don't want these saw rifles i'm gonna take
this i don't really have any better but i'm so annoyed that i upgraded these saw weapons
there's no those things have no purpose i'm just gonna equip it all right i just need the all i
need is a loaded ml14j i'm ready i'm gonna win right now check this out i ain't fucking around
now
i know i have to take the wall out first but i have to get there
and i might as well take this shit out in the meantime there's like 20 fucking cubes on that
wall you can't do it on your first go i'm trying to jex it out here relax thing right he's probably
he's gonna follow me down here there he comes all right let's go yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
what how did he get here this quick how did he get here this quick guys
how did he get here this quick he wasn't even on screen this is what how did he how did he
why it's impossible go to the thing back go to the thing first go to the thing in the back
wall first mr president mr president kill the thing in the back mr president go to the
thing in the back first okay mr president why why are you not at the thing in the back first
i don't know judy can you tell me
this will be dangerous yeah the thing that everyone's been screaming at me to go to first
cut it off first all right i've been screamed at judy for the last like two hours are you sure
you want me to do that judy you sure i'm just gonna go there let's fuck this this mission well they
this mission they dialed it up so hard it wasn't it wasn't even this bad but like the first
10 missions all of a sudden this one becomes like oh yeah by the way this one's like fucking
have fun the last one he did was like kind of fun and like he shot stuff
good luck he's already behind me it's right there bad idea let's do it again just follow
me all the way down here and i'm gonna turn around a little spawning shit in that stuff just spawned
in what's that nonsense didn't come out of a helicopter and you're actually gonna come down
this way just get down here
come on will you walk down here or do i have to all right keep going there he goes keep going
coming i guess he's gonna turn around come on just get over here what the fuck
just get over here please he keeps turning around to try to stop me he's trying to i
which one of us is going to get baited first i wonder mr president yes that daddy long legs
electromagnetic armor is tough i know the target area so you can weaken its electromagnetic armor
i wonder if i have enough time to at least get something
what are you aiming at i'm gonna just aim up you just aim straight in fucking air
i just bounced off that stupid guy's shield what am i aiming at i'm the auto aimer
when you shoot it just it auto aims or whatever it wants to automatically aim at
i can't control it it's a double i have to pull them down here huh okay come on
just follow me this way keep going as someone who beat this game back when it was on the xbox
this is the hardest and least fun mission the final commissions are my favorite
so
what a great remaster 15 goddamn years later i'm gonna make this eat better just get rid of it oh
my god i hate this guy i just want to shoot the thing behind you but you keep like linebackering
me every time i turn just keep going i'm just gonna i know i'm just gonna walk down this one
little behind me i don't know not this way stuck somewhere okay go
this is my opportunity go go back around this way and there's one more right
okay come on it's right there just get rid of it it's right there it's just like tucked in the back
i get it did i please time to die for a counter offensive now you're mine you failed robotnik
piece of shit robot energy no no energy beam now oh boy you're so strong so tough now
not so fucking strong are you oh wow that was so much easier when you just he doesn't have the
stupid beam i may have overreacted overreacted that's why you don't give up you call the game
of five out of ten like six times and then you talk about how you're going to delete it uninstall
and refund it and then you beat it and then you fly yeah you do the best you do the last two
and always was built to last right jody i was so angry remember when she said get the fuel
station i know and i tried but he has like this fucking detonation thing the game is impossible
i know i'm just saying it was fucking that level was dumb i'm just gonna say out loud if that was
a dumb level it was a stupid level i mean i'm we're just gonna agree with that i know all you're
gonna agree i'll tell you the best part about that was so i'm sitting here like oh fucking this
game is like what this level sucks it's like game with the first game like sucks you go like fucking
IGN five five and a half hey games get five five point five out of ten it's not my fault game's
stupid i just wanted to pull out like oh what's this game rated right like pull out the what's
the rating to chat what's this game rated guys i just what's what's it it's not like i have it
on my other monitor i'm just curious because what do you say what this game traded
there's the IGN one
okay we're good it sure has been a road to victory yes it has
oh that was so tilted fuck that spider fuck that level the white house
yes mr president when this battle is over i'm taking a paid vacation
i haven't seen my parents for a while and you know how it is that's fine with me you deserve
some extra time off too imagine someone playing bloodborne and getting frustrated over and over
and looking up the rating only to find nine because then you can't like justify your anger
last stop washington dc mr president information management department just contacted me
the coup d'etat forces are making an announcement on national television
bloodborne has a two out of ten on some site doesn't really
dear fellow have a scratched up cd this is an announcement from the government policy
promotion department where the password is no more metal wolf metal wolf who escaped from
military custody through cruel trickery continues to agitate various parts of the country
sympathizers to these acts appear to be on the rise as an american this is most regrettable
please try to remember the names and faces of any of the ring leaders who instigated this
terrorism a heart of justice is a heart that loves america so like i i would never have given this
game surrender now while your crimes are still not so serious but if you refuse surrender
based on article 48 clause four in the newly enacted u.s constitution metal wolf sympathizers
and or any blood relatives removed four times or less as well as schoolmates in all educational
institutions such as high schools and universities as well as any co-workers or associates for any
and all related people a public execution will be carried out so to any terrorist sympathizers
if an ounce of justice still remains in you give up on that man and surrender by 5 pm today
this is our final ultimatum uh but no sir two out of ten this has been an announcement from
the government policy promotion department where the password is we love richard hot a five or
six out of ten is like all right this game was like made me angry and i didn't like it but you
know it was still still all right it was still okay if you give a game of one or two out of ten
it means that you crashed to dex uh desktop when you do double click you know what i'm saying
you can't even load the game the president was alone the man who did it to him had come to
rub salt in his wound
oh he hacked him richard left all by your lonesome richard what what changed you
what do you rank kane and lynch probably a four or a four and a half michael four point six
has gotten too fat for her own good what would i give this one a 40 30 minutes ago i would have
given this like a five point four these incapable pigs are eating this nation alive
the death of these freeloaders leaving only the capable behind will help me create a new nation
after like getting over the that last mission i'd give this like a like a six four
six point four right now oh and michael i forgot to tell you but
what your presidential staff those backstabbing idiots well i've decided they can die too
this game is a five seven oh my god you guys are fucking you guys don't push me right now i'm i'm
very very fragile right now i'm very sensitive at the moment and watch those worms wiggle in
vain i'll cry you'll watch you'll see me cry
see you when i see you all right here we go liberty island i'll head to liberty island to
rescue my men and the reason is because i'm the president of this great united states of america
yeah what's up with dashes all right well now let me get in here i think i want to do
i didn't do grand lunches at all what a waste of money what a meltdown purchase these were uh
i'm thinking i'm just gonna go straight up mr launcher i think i'm gonna do it rail gun let
me get this let me i want to get down one more tier here is the real gun that good let's see
rg-30 actually getting sp how much do they cost rg-50 okay let's go look at it
rg-30 firepower increases the charge a rail gun that could be charged for different projectiles
and then an advanced rail gun that can be charged up to for increased firepower i don't have any
metal i can make this one but this is the default one i don't have to end game late game here it's
probably that idea i'll do i'm gonna go get not do another level get some more money what
did i make the most money that was the easiest level i'll be down here miami what's a good grind
level that boat right yeah i ain't going to i'm not doing new york the enemy force sends out over
one thousand is this the one good luck all right i got this would be fine just to do it for money
anyways skipping the lower we already saw it the navy cruiser will fire powerful
all right boat i'm just looking for like two three hundred grand
musician was among the pows you rescued he was surely forced to play the ukulele on the beach
oh watch out for aerial attacks just behind them that's all
i'm back here uh to grind the money because i want to have the better stuff lots of money
offensive augment those poor soldiers more long-range missiles these attacks will rage
on unless you wipe out the launch course yeah i got it
oh really
evasive maneuver that was heavy you ammo let's get it i'm gonna die on the grind level and that's
where you say the time for a sandwich
people get sandwiches if they feel like making a sandwich in their own damn house in my house
i'm gonna make a sandwich if i want one that doesn't matter if you want to lose
you don't lose the baseball game and then you uh no can i have a sandwich no
you didn't hit two home runs today you get nothing the team lost this is where i gotta be careful
as far as my title makes no fucking sense anymore does it i haven't had like a
stupid thing strange thing i haven't done i'm trying to get close enough to do this
that out no way don't you dare oh man i can't fucking believe it
oh it's the guy he instantly died
it's time for a sandwich i was trying to make money just get over here
it seems to have received a request from the target area and is on their way
yeah i'm sure they have you should sever the reinforcements ahead of time
so
in fact if i don't do it this time i'm just going to play free unless you wipe out the launch
source i thought i got rid of those four soldiers
yeah they're just little fucking toilet seat covers
that's far enough metal going head to head with this kind of firepower
isn't a smart way start by crushing the gun battery
excited i wouldn't be not yet until i show that we're gonna do something crazy
the thing i started at one o'clock all right get done bombing this guy actually sucks
all right i don't know but this was this wasn't even easy this was annoying i can't even
70 mr president please put up a good fight you didn't come here to go swimming this is
hitting no day i don't think it is mr president you don't want to get stun locked and die do it
i believe this is still spinning around
welcome three gun battery tickers one through five are flooded repair crew get on the scene
do not withdraw fire sailors abandon your post escape all right where do i do that
i'll head to liberty island to rescue my men and the reason is because we already saw this
all right develop what investment manufacturer where do i do that um it said i could do it right
said oh you have enough to upgrade your suit but where do you do that
is it equipment it already did it automatically did it maybe i don't know that's weird all right
let's make that a real gun rg-50 should i make the next one good no no no no no i want to do
i'll do missile punches again m i m 204 i see it a supreme missile launcher that fires four missiles
at once 120 000 and all right let's just try this is one of this is one of the last levels
in the game we're just gonna go through it put it on what's this what one of these is a piece
of crap i think it's this one yeah this thing sucks now it takes up two slots lose my sam what's
better visit the sand this thing kind of sucks too huh these both aren't really good what's worse
over this no this is worse let's keep it i got the rail gun let's see what it does
washington dc mr president why did you come to save us after we betrayed you jodie
i can't turn my back on a friend and the reason is i'm the president of the united states
mr president don't come near it's a trap hey there michael are you still playing the hero
witcher you just don't get it do you drop this thing like three or four times freedom is dead
you and your men and this symbol of freedom
okay that way we protect the statue go ahead and cock your weapons if i direct these missiles
behind me that goddess of liberty and you're gonna get a secretary will all be blown to smithereens
i'm gonna stop the missiles don't stop stop shooting i have to get up there and protect the
it's already dead uh you're definitely missing something here
what is it to shoot him out of the sky damn it i thought that i would have been great if i could
just kill him i'm gonna kill them i gotta shoot the missiles let's do it again
um
right but should we should be standing somewhere else so i just sit here and just shoot him when
they come out i guess i really should get the uh the thing that can take it out
that interceptor one whatever it is it's kind of what it should be
they go all the way back let me see what happens when i like go is this just like a dps race
do i actually have to shoot all these out of the sky why am i not getting a good lock on
two i didn't i wasn't even really in wow is on the move michael he'll bite you if you don't move it
it now i tail it out of here
my car door is open i'm sorry i almost forgot time for my afternoon tea
nothing like sipping some delicious darjeeling tea and watching you getting your clock cleaned
all right we'll see you next mission whoa that just kind of started um same deal
oh he's just bombarding this thing what the fuck what are you supposed to do about this
just keep i guess um what's the best weapon for this dude patches not just a badge railgun
mr preston charges you're alive us resistance soldiers are known for our resilience
uh
i can't just stand here with this railgun
we have knowledge of how to escape i we're good helicopters are limited be careful
i can just i mean you move too slow with this thing to shoot like the missile
yeah this is way too slow
i'm gonna use the rail gun you walk away
all right let's go
and cock your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me that goddess of liberty and your cute
little secretary will all be blown to smithereens give me another do i have i need to get two assault
rifles for this i think unfortunately yeah that's probably a better idea i should go back to the
garage because this is not no you just need to even be a self rifle so much easier
use the rail gun now it's too slow too slow i can't no the rail guns are not good here
too slow he's gonna just keep firing missiles with the statue of liberty charge it the whole
way just shoot it at the tank okay do you want me to just do this like 10 times
is it actually gonna work no this is not gonna work too much damage to the statue of liberty
already i'm like i'm saying this is not gonna work i'm gonna get run over by this tank
the damage rate is over 50 watch out
oh
part one yeah maybe i could see that part two all right maybe i hold on maybe it is part two
maybe okay hold on this might actually work why'd you have to die and cock your weapons
if i direct these missiles behind me that goddess of liberty and your cute little secretary
will all be blown to smithereens
wow how much do i have to load it up is it like 10 20 more than that 50 all right
when it flashes yellow the first time i'll get it next time restart restart restart restart
go ahead and cock your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me that was it that god
is the liberty and your cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens
he's making me so angry yeah i don't think this is very effective i have to hold it for too long
it takes too long i'm gonna i might get to the end but i don't think it's gonna work out very well
he has no more missiles can i take off the top ones too let's see if i can get these ones too
am i just making him completely useless before phase two
uh what is this last one oh i'm over here the game is broken just kill him can i do it in time
how many bullets how many will he shoot how much damage is one missile due to the statue of liberty
too much no he's gonna go phase two oh fuck oh my god i should have just listened to myself
i should have just shot it i should have just done it that'll work out though as long as i
this might not be bad no i know i know we're fine i know you're gonna keep saying it
the trade is over 50 watch out in 200 yards between the tank and the statue of liberty
kill promptly and effectively that's an ironclad battle tactic does that mean he's gonna get me
okay look back at the trade is over 70 percent we're down stop doing cut scenes to tell me that
somebody died because it takes away all my charge kill with cool super i don't have
mr president why'd you have to die all right i got a new i'm gonna have to do double assault
rifle i'll try this one final time because i think if i get it the right way the way that i want
cock your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me three that god is of liberty and your
cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens
all right take out the missiles up here i'm gonna stick with that strategy i think it's gonna work
take out all the guns that i can and then i'm gonna get off the rail gun and go to assault rifle and
something else maybe i don't know i'm not sure yet
saw rifle and missile launcher i guess i'm gonna have to rail gun out
do full charge right in the middle okay here comes space two
of course behind a small wooden railing how about defenses great just take the damn thing out
okay maybe the sand here we go oh i don't think this is working
uh it's actually somehow less effective than just using the open
that's an iron clad battle tactic make it stop damage rate is over 50 i don't even see i don't
think it's over 70 oh my god i'm gonna have a meltdown again i don't think that's doing anything
the thing in the middle has to die and effectively that's an iron clad battle tactic
i'm shooting the legs right now damage level is approaching critical mass
danger mr president why'd you have to die uh i don't understand what to do
yeah i was doing much better with the rail gun just put the rail gun back on okay
i kind of want a better rail gun go ahead and cock your weapons direct these missiles behind me
that god is of liberty and your cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens
simple oh is it what how is this simple he's got like 30 rocket launchers i want this thing
gone but i don't think you can can you not get rid of it i'm just gonna fully charge
shot right in space is it destroyed it looks like it is but it might not be
was it gone before i remember there's so much stuff going on on the screen it's hard to tell
these things almost dead they're sitting there experimenting for too long oh all right yeah it is
we did we're not we'll see
stop oh my god it's the worst why would you go into two cutscenes and grow
fuck why is there ever a reason to do that it is over 50 watch out only 200 yards between the
tank and the statue of liberty kill promptly and effectively that's an ironclad battle tactic i
guess that did it it's going slower now it's over 70 we're down to five helicopter sure you
could have just said that i could have just told you that i don't want to see the cuts
i got no more danger oh just die how do i get this i gotta get rid of this thing
in a hurry kill with cool composure that's an ironclad battle tactic this thing's like a
shield or do i just have to destroy this i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead it's over i'm
dead it's over i'm dead it's crushing everybody it's killing me mr president honey how did how
could i fall um so he pushed me all the way back all right do it again i got it same deal
that goddess of liberty and your cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens
laugh i want to fucking strangle this guy so bad i'm here from our all hey man welcome to the stream
we if i have fun here don't be too crazy though get yourself in trouble right down the middle
back launcher i'll get it come on guns right there get this one too
all right rail gun back out again come on got real gun oh fuck he's coming fast all right go
treads one two three got it other tread quick one two three got it okay here we go
back cannons cutscene double cutscene double cutscene shoot it before the cutscene
wins the next cutscene coming up right now right it's right it's soon lid hit the lid hit the lip
rate is over 50 watch out good now what now what just shoot it just kill it
more treads fully charged fully charged to the tread oh shit only 200 yards between the
tank and the statue of liberty i got four more shots did that hit that fucking car
be careful no why come on i can still do it he can't hit any other particle he'll be out of
kill a cornered enemy that's an ironclad battle tactic is that hurting him i can't even tell what's
hurting him anymore okay okay okay okay now what this damage level is approaching critical mass
danger 50 yards till target okay kill it okay okay kill it shooting mr president
there's many a slip between the cup and the lip what does that even mean
why is he going so fast what the fuck what happened why what why did he go so fast
that makes no sense he went so fast
that was ridiculous that was ridiculous un-fucking-believable no i gotta retry it
again why what that was so unfair that was unfair i can't believe it i had it too i got it
it isn't rage time grind out some better real guns all right all right yeah i'm gonna go pee
and then we'll do that god damn it that's unbelievable so i would be angry right now
but how can you be after that you kind of can't be i want to just get rid of all this shit for the
next phase if it doesn't have anything to shoot then it doesn't matter i would break the disc
and shit on it oh really i don't i want to just completely focus on getting rid of the trends
he's not gonna have any more guns the middle one's already gone i got it okay here we go
full blast into the thread one two three good again one three four got it okay slow down he's
done i did it right is that did i do it he looks like he's going faster okay there we go
okay good focus my god what have you done that didn't blow it up
you don't want to do it twice because it's a waste
this one might be a wash this is it how are you shitting me that thing is should be dead
without a doubt all right bring it up good next one here we go we're down five helicopters between
the tank and the statue of liberty kill promptly and effectively hold it longer look at the bar
fills up it's full first fall first fall two more last shot and then it's all hell breaks loose
all hell breaks loose after this one and then what i just rocket launcher rockets
but kill a cornered enemy with prudence that's an iron cloud battle tactic
stop rifles not doing anything lock it on lock it on target lock on lock on lock on lock on lock on
lock on lock on lock on lock on lock on lock on lock on i don't have any i don't have any mother
fuck off who cares nice shooting mr president but there's many assume your mecha damage rate
is over 50 watch out here he comes no mr president i got it mr president no no no
i can do it i can everyone it's gonna be fine we're gonna beat this game and i'm gonna it's
it's worth it what are you what do you keep doing wrong oh i think i'm just i don't have a hot i'm
strong enough like i i'm everything i'm this is fine i'm everything's good don't worry get rid of
the shitty stuff yeah what i need to i think i'm gonna get i want another i want i'm gonna grind
this is i'm gonna get like three of these i think all right i have two of those don't i i do okay
so that's just this is end game this is the end game here this shit is worthless what does
the most damage that's a full-on flamethrower maybe it might flamethrower maybe it's worth the
shot i should buy another one of these will the flamethrower not damage it what do you think
what do you think i think and uh sam is still all right i guess we'll do missile launcher and
this is good i think it's terrible we'll do these two and spam them all right i'm gonna try this one
more time with the new loadout same as intended for aircraft yeah but i just have hams should i
just use the other this this bazooka the bu kind of terrible the hams do more than 600 damage
they do this actually is better than that this does 18 okay we're good let's try this again i'm
going for it this time i'm going to change up the tactic a little bit i'm not going to use the rail
gun immediately i'm going to use go ahead and no i have to i have to so much more precise behind me
that god is a liberty and your little secretary will all be blown to smithereens i restarted i
fucked it i blew it i can i just gotta get up i gotta get it just one you see what i mean by this
here we go it's got you have to get them each in one shot
i direct these missiles behind me that god is of liberty and your cute little secretary will all
be blown to smithereens okay that's i missed but it's all right that's sponge bob that's not
pitch it's pitch shifted down sponge bob's lap i have to restart here we go
go ahead and cock your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me that god is of liberty and
your cute little secretary here we go all be blown to smithereens
sponge bob all right we're going good so far i just have to get them each in one individual shot
there it is same with these ones same right in the front door
that your liberty is going to be fine forget about the hp
just worry about the mechanics involved in here done aim up a little bit make sure it's fully
charged it takes two to get rid of these you know this you know this here we go okay cool
just making sure that i get it okay good treads treads and then guns okay good guns good stop
gonna do it again don't screw me over like this please i'll have like i'll have like 12 shots do
this good good this is it i'm gonna shoot that thing i'm gonna shoot the i'm gonna shoot the
stupid overpass thank you for getting rid of that here we go bingo this is it fully charged only
the same thing happened to me last time i got stuck by the car we're down to oh you mother
fucker why did you do that it's okay i still have funny shots only 200
and i've got that entire i got the two uh qrs's on the taxi was tiny it's not that small stop
laughing at that seven shots oh no this is too slow i got two qrs's 50 yards here we go
but don't be in a hurry kill come on no how did i do less damage than the last time
he's shooting mr president here we go but there's many a slip between the cup and the lip
get it oh fuck he's dead one more shoot it i lost i should have stuck with the plan
i should have stuck with the plan all right i should have stuck with the plan
new tactic
if i direct these missiles behind me that god is a liberty and your cute little secretary
better tactic it's better what a better tactic this really is now i got enough energy supplies
and now i have more and i'm just gonna stick to the fucking plan i will have like 20 shots
is this thing destroyed it is now oh fuck oh that's not good okay this is very bad actually this is
horrible worst plan confirmed he's already on the move yeah he's already moving this is worse
this is way worse wait is the statue what statue liberties can take that's great i think the
statue liberty is fine going straight in the middle so yeah forget about the top missiles and
shit i can i think i can do it right now damage rate is over 50 watch out he just put up a shield
for me that's fine i'll take it only 200 yards between the tank and 200 yards though man you're
already here and effectively that's an ironclad battle tactic stick i can stick to the plan i have
a hundred meters
i just need to shoot it like five times i'm already how am i so close to
being dead that's an ironclad battle tactic does he have thorns just restarted oh my god
mr president let us down i keep taking missiles i have to walk to shoot the okay i got it
same thing just gonna do old plan old plan only old plan the same thing i did before and i have to
do it quick this time missiles do too much damage they're too annoying
clean it up
i couldn't i try i have i can't take my hand off the controller i was trying to do a thing where
you put your finger up to your throat and you shake it around wasted you got beyond i'm beyond
angry at that that's two shots it didn't take it down get rid of the rest of the missiles that
is almost dead it's not just that's what is almost dead the thing i still hit something
it is almost dead am i not gonna do this
this is my last attempt before i go grind another how did i why was it already over
go ahead and cock your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me
that goddess of liberty and your cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens
uh
i hate this game literally with the fucking coffee coming out i hate this thing
i hate the company that made this game no you don't i bet you don't you definitely don't
i can assure you you played something that you were like sick yes i do no you don't do you
you might from software games are for everybody what if i just start shooting at it now
well it's not moving yes i do yes i do
this game's too stressful i apparently didn't hit the tread either on that one
show me where i missed i need to know where it was how did that it's not even it's that is
impossible to not hit that i hit it there cool it's over for me it's out it went through the tank
it's over for me damage rate is over 50 watch out
i need a better weapon and it's still there it's still there it's still shooting
between the tank and the statue of liberty your mecha damage rate is over 70 be careful
you're down this shit's over
it's not even possible to miss do you fucking understand it's i the cross here was sitting it's
not even possible to miss that shot it was lined up it just went under the thing it's not even
possible oh
if i don't do this time i gotta get a better one otherwise this is just never gonna happen
okay get this one too aim at it it's aiming i'm gonna fucking scream i'm gonna scream
i'm gonna scream no okay i gotta go i need money i need money i need money oh i hate this game
but i can't stop playing it i'm not only i'm not halfway through the game no way there's like two
more missions no this is a this is a this is like an eight out of ten game in like a four out of
ten games body that's my theory on this i'm doing the i'm doing the boat again
uh no i'm not all right with this the boat didn't get me enough money
how much should i do no this actually might not be bad here i'm gonna stick with this this is the
loadout i'm good let's go check this shit out you'll need constant warning mr president
the bomber group seems to have received a request from the target area and is on their way i don't
know what to pick bombing will be dangerous you should sever the itchy eyes are approaching
watch out for aerial attack all right don't even hold that down for that long
okay no keep going keep going forget it just take out the targets this is a target destroyer
use missiles now no don't even need to get it
they come all right watch out just watch it they come where are they i don't see them you lied
you lied you lied they're not here where are you watch this one eat shit i didn't get it
why is this taking so much damage with this kind of firepower isn't the firepower start by crushing
the gun battery that goes all right one more no more shoot after the third yellow one two two
three after the third yellow this is where i come in here and i drop the absolute fucking
nuke over here watch out all right get in there close thing is in the way here we go and
go one two third yellow go nice get this turret over here one yellow two yellow and here comes
the third yellow two yellow incoming third yellow yellow activate say it with me now one yellow
two yellow activating the third yellow i guess i missed um excuse me who cares just stand still
how is he so good at video games lots of practice lots of practice get on the scene do not withdraw
fire fire okay i will how much money is it and i'm just gonna do it again c e d e i didn't get any
points oh that's not a lot of money at all actually that's a really really bad um which
one had more money than that maybe i can i'll get a combo do the this love the new york level
the enemy force except in good luck i'm sure i just almost ripped my mouth because i'm playing
this but hold on there's a way to do this i'm gonna do assault rifles i'm gonna ski around and just
get a ton of multipliers don't worry about me i'll be fine i did not want to select that what
a broke ass game i'm good this one will be easy because i know where to go i know what to do
let's get that assault rifle assault rifle and spring it again
just trying to get points and spring to get the money and destruction damage bonuses and all that
whatever that does imagine leaving the screen like an hour and a half ago and coming back and
thinking like holy shit he's lost his goddamn mind i can't believe he's still here like hey
dude you don't have to do this you don't have to do this it's all right you know just don't
stop playing this level you don't have to be here before it gets any closer all right now we're gonna
go straight right straight right we can bring out the uh the other you know what i'm saying
where is mr spider i need eyes on the spider i've got eyes how much you take one
not very much doesn't take a whole lot oh shit he's right there i got eyes
so you can weaken its electromagnetic armor can i get a collateral all right it's cool it's cold
i'm touching it it's cold stop mercy lighter not sure
back over to the wall of power-ups watch out for that spider he'll get you he's gonna come get you
of course he's still here this would this of course he's still here why would he not be here
can i snipe it from all the way back here come on nope get over here be careful he's charging up
his laser watch out for the laser why is he going that way his brain is just all over the place
right now he comes finally to me to me i know you can do it there it goes no no no no no no no no
keep going this way you buffoon oh you you buffoon he just doesn't know what to do how do i get rid
of ants uh it's actually kind of easy so you put uh take a little bit of water and put sugar in
the water like four or five tablespoons and shake it up bring it like really do uh make it dilute
the sugar in the water and then go around the baseboards of your house and drip that sugar
water all over your baseboards and like under your couch and maybe a little bit um like on the bed
in the bed that probably will get rid of me probably a couple days
okay can you please come over here
he won't come over here that's it i've had enough i'm going to him i've had enough i've had enough
get over here i've had enough it's time for you to crawl over here find me over here good you're
doing great keep going good all right here comes the charge not quite yet here he comes he's going
to charge up he's going to one hit kill me and i'm going to brb and go to the bathroom this is it
turning around again
i'm gonna kill him because he's so stupid i'm gonna kill him he's he doesn't know where to go
i'm gonna win he's so stupid i'm gonna hit him in the back and he's gonna kill him
this is gonna work get up there with the boost right in the back i can't believe it went over
his shoulder that's un-fucking-believable that's you almost can't miss that shot
i'm gonna lose here it comes it's over i'm it's just that i gotta i gotta go
you're just overworked but are you okay
no please please no no don't do it don't do it just go like this
okay all right i made it watch out for the mines
and get this energy wave power from an energy fill station destroy the energy fill station in
town detroit doing anything else i'm getting hurt which psycho trolled him into playing this
me i'm the guy that trolled myself into playing me i did this nobody else did this don't worry
blink twice
derma derma blink twice if you don't want to play this anymore and you'd like you don't you
really don't want to be alive anymore playing this he's right here please no why does he have
to do this to me hey tremor blink twice if you have it a little bit of anything two three four
or five just give me like a shield or something anything i wish i could just pull him down here
but he keeps turning around it's almost like what is this what is that supposed to be what is that
what is that right like return like why did you get over here why is happening in this level
what's happening here i have to do this i have to go closer apparently
i'm trying to get him to turn around just push past him i have got i don't have the help to do
that i gotta go this way now i should be able to make it run and then i can go this way where is
he now all right maybe he'll get stuck over here now i've already beaten this shit you know
he's already back here he is he's here i have to just get through him i have to get through
him we're dashing right now go hug the corn get up if be the same as him broadcasting those
phony news stories why would i play this level it's just look why would i play this one this is the
worst mission out of any game in the last 30 years why would i do that one that's worse than the
donkey kong mine level why would i do that let's just go over here the target area target area
destroy annihilate the enemy army by destroying the target areas where the troops have a mass
destroy all the target areas and take back the town i'll take something over 20 you need someone
to come take the game away no i need to beat this game so i can say i was one of the sorry
motherfuckers that decided to beat it i want my shit ragging rights
oh yeah i'll be i'll be at like i'll be at like twitchcon next month
talking to people would you stream like uh like last month anything cool well yeah i mean like
i've you know i beat metal wolf panic i think you know that's like a game the game like has like
it's like you know that one you fly around with a mag and like there's fucking spider level and
it's worse than donkey kong mine designated targets in each area yeah i know that game i didn't buy it
because i didn't think it was gonna be good why did you play that all the way through
you know because like i flex in front of them yeah as long as i did it try attacking from another
okay winning by retreating why do you think i care about i played minecraft and like build a
house it was pretty calm how many bits you get on that stream i don't know i didn't keep calm
how many let's let's let's look i don't think we should do that on my stream i was playing
fortnite i got you know fucking 65 million bits did you how many did you get i don't know i don't
care i don't do that and i like fucking slam my drink as fast as i can like didn't fucking walk
away when communications are made i know they do okay
that hurt my head in real life hey yo germa hey what's up hey what's going on hey what's
up how you doing it's good to see you again uh streamer xyz whatever hey how you doing like i
heard i heard something about you yeah what what you hear i heard that you uh you have like a
meltdown on playing that game that like nobody really is that you know that you i don't know why
you care so much about are you playing that full metal wolf panic game yeah i was playing it earlier
i heard you got 5 000 unsubscriptions to your channel you like all right
hey i gotta go what's even left oh so much a thousand dollars no that's not that much
a hundred dollars from velemy they say fuck you germa i love metal wolf chaos i'd like it too
so you and i both we can we we can like go to twitchcon and we can like be like
i just want to get an energy pot now thank you that's a lot of fucking money
100 bucks is a lot of cash shock that anyone will give it to me almost done here it's got to go up
here and then we can do the next rail gun and then i can beat the game and then at the at the end of
the night at the end of that then you know hey what's going on hey the germa get over here man
i've had like 10 like like slam chugged nervous chucks right germa oh you should you gotta see
this guy man like all my cool friends on twitch get over here look dude this guy can chug like
you've never seen before it's ridiculous every time i have a conversation he just slams out it's
crazy he's so fast hey dude germa can you chug and i'm just like what are you talking about
no i don't know chug chug okay chug chug okay i'll try i can't
it's fucking puke all over the ground all over the fucking table and it's incredibly
embarrassing i have to go home oh what the oh disgusting disgusting what the fuck jeremy
i thought you were cool man i thought you could chug
inches were among the pow you can fail let's go with the uh let's get this done
you can do any damage i'm gonna beat this game and i can say it i'm gonna be i'm gonna do an
announcement i did it i'm gonna have a panel at twitch it's gonna be i beat metal wolf chaos hd
and that's it and people are just gonna come they're gonna sit down they're gonna get in
their chairs all right what's going on here what does this mean is this like a little is
this coming another thing oh guys please welcome uh germa 95 he's gonna have the here comes his
panel and i get out there and they give the time everyone claps that the people are just clapping
and that's really happy sit down i'm gonna full suit on it just sit down i shake my shoulders a
little and i get real close to the mic and it goes like thanks everybody for coming i beat
this stupid fucking game on stream like two months ago here's the whole bud
just play the vod on a projector the enemy forces have usurped a building making it a target
the building was opened two years ago on april 26th here this part
no this game's not stupid i'm just i'm just taking the piss
it's fun yeah why would i still be playing this way
oh this game i'm having this game it really is i'm just except for the spike that really is the
worst thing why are you british it's an easy way to say that you're messing around just taking
the piss right that's like an easy way how much did i get paid to play this game i'm not sure i
don't know what that number would be 60 to 75 000 i forgot about this i forgot about the tank
oh my goodness i forgot about tank i forgot there's a boss in this i don't think i'm gonna be
able to do this what do i need here uh okay i need i need um i'm just gonna do it to slow down
i just need the money this thing does a lot of damage i'll be all right
be all right
charge it up easy the cannon he didn't shoot the cannon give me the new bro down all right
hey why isn't the mission on anymore all right so now that we've settled down
we're able to relax and just continue playing the game thanks everyone for joining me on this
trip i hope you had a good time i know i have the enemy force it's been fun is that enough
to give me some money a branching zero damage points i didn't do any damage i guess not enough
down 140 000 all right that's enough for another raid remember i said i was gonna start pulling
screams back so they wouldn't go that late all right develop i think i need more investment
i'm gonna need more g50 sp that's not even an upgrade that's just like a side grade
shit how much does it cost additional projectiles how much is it 65 plus and again need 65 000
i'm just gonna go to the first mission level one i don't even know what mission level one is
this one here currently good luck yeah this is fine just go get out my special op suit
suit
i thought he was gonna rage for a while ago yeah he was but he fought through it
fought the demon in his mind he decided it was worth playing through and doing it beating the
game and he's gonna beat this game monster however long this takes by the way oh wait i should have
said that what if the game is like only 10% okay if the next two or three missions are not the
final missions in the game so let's shoot the statue doesn't work mr president the eagle star
is beyond here get going before the enemy chases after you proceed ahead while destroying anything
that stands in your way pushing over your weapons depending on the situation is the main
speed of fighting try out the weapons in your backpack as you like
energy pod i found another energy pod
lacronda 50 bucks from lacronda thank you so much for the 50 dollars and what do you say you say
dude you're barely finished with this game bro you have to conquer europe and then fight russian
bots and hack into china i think that's what i have to do but if it is then i'll see you guys
tomorrow mr president there's an aircraft hanger beyond this passageway now let's hurry the aircraft
hanger is behind the barrier i'll open the barrier now please wait a moment let's hope that projectile
weapon is another this nonsense scream tomorrow yeah tomorrow is it's gonna be a wild one
i thought this one was all over the place just wait till tomorrow tomorrow's a wine
terraria no terraria is in the sunday i already talked to starboard
the barrier has been opened air force one's launch preparations will be complete please
am i going to get at least 20 000 to this here more gas well i guess they won't be voting for you
next term mr president the enemy is taking aim at air force one please be careful well
duty they're all gone i'm trying to do the slide bonus offensive argument all right let's go that's
it give me 20 000 and i can finally get to the end of this next edition with a love of goodness
yes there we go damage points 167 165 000 oh yeah load it in there wait that was it hk69
is that enough i'll head to liberty island to rescue my men and because i
what is the hk79 grenade it's a grout to grenade launcher all right well let me develop let's see
if i can get it 69 000 i wish i could just sell something rail guns there it is no i can do it
there it is rg50 sp advanced railgun that can be charged up for additional projectiles
give it to me please time it's this is i know we're getting late and i said i wasn't going to
do late streams anymore but here we go there it is see if i can do it now this is longer than
the two streams i said that i was gonna do last week let me see what this does go ahead and cock
your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me what does it do though the liberty and your
cute little secretary will i mean it's kind of ridiculous i'm gonna stand back and see what
happens when i shoot it i might be able to take out a whole grill here kind of that's good i'm
gonna keep doing it right down the middle oh fuck that does too much damage maybe it doesn't
matter maybe it doesn't matter maybe i can still do it too much damage i'm gonna have to use the
second okay now i take i can hold on we're good wait hold on a second i might have to get the
whole back row here this is never going to work with this low slow charge i need to get rid of
all this stuff first yeah no way this is impossible without getting rid of everything
first damage rate is over 50 watch out yeah we're gonna do the original rail gun in phase one
this one in phase two go ahead and cock your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me
that goddess of liberty and your cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens
oh
i don't understand like that was seriously why would you take that much that would that that
that's un-fucking-believing i'm just gonna stand up here can i jump on the tank i'm not sure i
want to do that oh boy i may have done something wrong what the fuck happened why did he start
moving why did he start moving it's like i don't know is it the amount of damage you do
fuck this go ahead and cock your weapons check this out these missiles behind me that god is
a liberty and your cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens what if i just don't care
and just shoot the tank and just who cares will he kill the statue of liberty in time i don't know
maybe i'm gonna try to take on this whole back row they went i'm trying to split them
that's your liberty's dead oh my goodness i'm gonna lose my damn mind playing this thing i mean i
already did but like holy shit maybe i should just start to maybe i should just try to catch
you try this go ahead and cock your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me that god is a
liberty and your cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens
all right all right hold on right down the middle get rid of the beam okay now the hold on i did
that really quickly i might have some time here fuck that was a genuine fuck that was a genuine
like heads like sneeze forward fuck my head went back forward hard okay i'm good
not bad it might this might work switch out to the big one after hold on this is it right here
i can get both you stupid motherfucking cutscene why does that have to even happen oh my god this
game is gonna drive me fucking up the wall this is this is just this is just you can't say this is
not done with a capital d it's just dumb how does a fucking almost full charge shot take that up
not take that up there's no explanation this is worse this gun is worse i spent the time grinding
to get this and it's not even as good i just popped my elbow that's how you know it's real
that was a good start too that's so sad i'm gonna have to do this again i'm
only i'm just gonna use the original weapons if i direct these missiles behind me that
goddess of liberty and your cute little secretary will all be blown to smithereens
i'm back to these original one machine guns i'm gonna go for the top okay i got i gotta get rid
of these things the tread has to go now like right now watch out watch out please don't shoot
it that's the cutscene i got it okay let's go oh you gotta be fucking kidding me which rate is
over 50 watch out i'm just going for the tank i'm just going for it that's a lot that is a lot
just so we're clear that's a ton of fucking damage only 200 yards between the tank and the
statue of liberty and effectively that's an ironclad battle tactic
mr president let us down um i wonder if i should just get your weapons if i direct these missiles
behind me that god is a shit ain't working and your cute little secretary will all be blown to
smithereens maybe i should hold on to this and use this for the missiles i'm doing that yeah i'm
gonna try that just buy a bunch of the missile launcher i think i could probably take out the
ones in the back quickly with that other launcher it's possible let's go with the cannon in the
middle all right let's try to get the machine gun here and then i try to get the missiles back
waiting up i mean the treads first treads first treads are more important
i just didn't even do the thing i said i was gonna do lost my fucking mind i i don't think
this is physically possible for me to beat this without different weapons without getting the
perfect storm i think i have to grind this shit ain't working go ahead and cock your weapons
if i direct these missiles behind me that god is of liberty and your cute little secretary
will all be blown to smithereens i can stand back further to blow this up
so
did i get i don't know if i got it i think i got it is it going faster i can't tell
amateur rate is over 50% i know i know it is i know it is i can't
i'm gonna try that again all right no no no no i don't know what to do
i think i think i just kind of have to go ahead and stay up there and shoot the missiles
missiles behind me that god is a liberty and i was so close with the rail gun and rockets
yeah it's so hard to replicate though just so fucking you gotta be it's not even being perfect
is you just have to be in it's like the timings are weird i had it almost twice but then for some
reason with no treads this game decides that it's going to go 100 miles per hour with the last like
20 meters for no reason this is just it's just gonna do it but i don't know why once we get the
cutscenes i think i have to change because it's just ruining everything it's ruining everything
that's your liberty zone today and that didn't have three rail guns that you've been done three
hits direct three fucking direct hit with like almost halfway charging it's inconsistent what
the fuck what is that what else do i have here i can't use this because this gets cutscene so
it's just not gonna work they give you a cutscene every single time somebody gets hurt so i guess
we're gonna go with we're gonna get rid of this and the bazookas sam maybe double bazooka i want
should be sam bazooka i don't i don't i think all right let's try this now
i'm just gonna check the other ones this i can't even how much damage does this do
missiles and bazooka are the key i guess i'm gonna do the sam and just these two
let's see which ones are more effective i guess i'll keep the rail gun just for shit i'm just
trying to try to target everything i guess just target them individually keep the rail gun for
maybe the end i'll try it i don't have these don't work on
why was i using the other thing why was i using the rail guns why was i using the rail gun
oh why was i doing that i don't know people told me didn't people tell me to do that
weren't people telling me people telling me right people telling me to do that was it two people
it was not two people it was like six thousand you guys told me to go back and grind for the rail gun
tears are streaming down my face it was a it was a shitload of people that was a lot of people
that told me to do that you and i i believed you because i thought it was for real too
i just killed that thing so easily just by using bazooka
i apologize for saying use rail gun i don't know anything about the game
mr president my boys were successful in saving your princess i'll connect you
mr president how can i ever jodie yes sorry to be late mr president
i was i was individually targeting peter mcdonald reporting each piece of the thing
make that the world was individually targeting each piece of that tank dnn did you witness vice
president richard hawks dreadful it's a mystery who is he as i have been stressing who could it be
metal wolf was the truly righteous one may have doubted you i always believed in you
thank you metal wolf and thank you michael wilson whatever
did i get enough money did i get some money give me some money
no no no no i mean like in the game not you guys just where's my money
no that's a lot of money that's 439 000 i can't believe that i'm i was individually targeting
pieces of the guy's fucking legs and arms and stuff the hell was i thinking
how was i doing this hair but i like i like a volcano is erupting from the
fucking front of my head there's no fix in that here i'm just gonna buzz it hey see on the next
mission zip cam i don't have any zits today where there is it there's no zits today just grind this
level 50 times hey hey guys oh yeah i think i showed you this before this is making it real
easy too a razor look at the razor death adder sticky shit over here and if things just fall
off of it yeah it's sticky it's like a grip it's like put on with like fucking masking tape
that was the day i realized the pen is not truly mightier than the sword
why would i ever buy a razor death at it because i have like these big fucking gross hands
look at how big these hands are they're huge like people don't realize like the i have gigantic
fucking oven mitt hands when i grab a mouse it's like oh that was so fucking loud why was that
so loud that was loud in this room too it was like the perfect like i told you i've got these
fucking earthquake hands holy shit hey look ronda thanks for the fifty dollars use railgun with a
funny funny face uh thanks for the fifty dollars five thousand bits it's a shitload of money thank
you volemy fifty dollars jeremy i don't have much more money to give you but since you said to give
you more money here you go ps chat did you know that the guy can chug yeah i can't
oh
tough yeah these things are great i'm not who cares ocean spray what's good they're delicious
they're small they're easy to handle they're easy to drink air force one had been cleared of any
wrongdoing now there are sites where once again permit said on the white house i told you i got
these big watches i'm not gonna try this is a regular sized camp don't you understand i can
almost go around the whole thing can you do that with a can of coke i can crush it
all right mr mcdonald said something mr president i jodie yes what is it mr president
you sure you don't need any more time off
oh mr president i've had enough t.o.s oh god do t.o.s now time to take back the last piece of ground
white house all right so uh we are there looks like there's a lot more video game here
retake the white house i don't think so maybe not but first i am going to do that again
which was it was this one here i'll head to liberty and because
just go i'm gonna do this like two three times go ahead and cock your weapons if i direct these
missiles behind me that god is a liberty and your cute little secretary will
oh don't fast still take out the treads please thanks first that's an iron clad yes yes yes
shooting mr president but there's holy shit s okay that's fucking all right do it again
okay i know i know look after seeing me do this now
imagine being a vod watcher and then seeing the last hour and a half
and knowing that you could skip to that supposed to be watching the vod right now
just i'm sorry i'm sorry that you had to watch that for like 40 straight minutes
i direct these missiles behind me that god is like there's like 2,700 people like 400 people told
me to use the rail gun and to like grind to get the rail gun so i listened it was it was it was
like four or five hundred people a lot of people and i thought that you were giving me tactical
information the caterpillar things first that's an iron clad battle tactic or i was just pretending
the whole time use what you're shooting mr president but that's so bad knowing that how
how easy this level is can you imagine not even not only forget about the people that are watching
the vod right now can you imagine the people who are watching the stream right now who have
played through this game and know that and were lost in the sea of get railgun and they know how
easy this was
i'm absolutely happy to have it mostly 95% of it be this game what a journey it's been it's been
fucking wild you've heard me say like fuck you've heard me say like shit you've heard me go
it's just ridiculous this game is fucking crazy you've heard that a few times we've got a few
things here nice shooting mr president but there's many a slip between the cup and the lip
what's happening wait this is oh yeah no i won first i thought it was all right we went
it's like what happened there all right that's it i got plenty of money it's time to get the enemy
seems to be the best rail gun no i don't want to skip this shit we don't know what this is
the enemy seems to be concentrating their power around the white rub defense forces predicted to
be on hand the shape of this underground base is highly complicated there is a strong possibility
that the target area is closely coordinated skillfully attacked to prevent reinforcements
and coordination between target areas this is the grand daddy grand daddy battle of the mall
annihilate the target areas and take half the white house by the call name the call name take
the white house i'm home generation white house good luck and god fucking god damn it all right
here we go investment level six visual launcher i want it boom m i m 204 lr is now available
that was a long horn missile launcher seven the m l r h is now available for purchase oh yeah
rail guns get it the r g 50 dmv is now available keep going the r g 70 is now available
the r g r h is now available bazookas get this shit too i'll just blow the tank up two more times
into pr and to ex the tvbz yeah i'll just go get the i'm gonna go blow up the tank
i'll head to end because i didn't cock your weapons if i direct these missiles behind me
that god is a liberty and you're cute little second
oh just like silent i'm gonna how long have you been here
really bad was this a melt downstream this was even though it was it's been a while when was
the last like true just absolutely fucking yes vr stuntman iceland right but before that
it's like been three days there's many a slip between the company
i gotta like settle down the mountain blade stream the difference between mountain blade though is i
straight up gave up and i didn't even attempt to keep going i'll do one more time that should get
us to where we want to be because hotline miami i thought hotline miami was truly actual upset
like truly angry truly upset and that's one of the first times i think i've ever really truly been
upset on the camera actually today too and like skate three and arizona no i have whatever
mario maker yeah no no you're right mario maker 2 that did not do i regret playing hotline miami
no i think it's great here hotline miami 2 is awesome and hotline miami i think hotline miami
is better than hotline miami 2 i think it's just a better game overall i will be out of
tower i i think clock tower was more of a complete complete just total
termination screen
you didn't like the coin game i thought i'd love that all right let's buy things that i just
upgraded good luck the coin game was awesome that's like one of my favorite games of the year
what's it's clock tower all right i think i can do one more
row here rail guns all the way up bazookas all the way pr is here and the final bazooka
the t w b z r h let's see what that does right wait what how is another one the vps go to bazooka
double-barreled and capable of repeating fire uh yeah i'll take one of those what about the
rail gun missile launches what's the best one here m l r h the vps go to missile electrophores
and missiles that split i don't have any more material well it's gonna have to be that bazooka
i need more material repeating fire rail gun i might as well make the other cheaper can i make
the cheaper ones no i can do this one rifter bombs i'll take it i might as well take no all
right no that's good that's good let's go back there it is and on the other side we'll do
yes i guess i could put that there uh i'll just put the other rail gun here
good to go it's the best uh missile launcher in the game in the whole game
final mission it's been a journey let's party it's good to be home
it is ridiculous i'm not even gonna use it and save it what's this uh what's the dump dude
the above ground route has been sealed off but if you take back the underground bay
the enemy will surrender and open the barrier now aim for the target areas got it now get out there
and rock their world what it just shoots a balloon it sucks i won't be using that
there's a bomb in here
let's try the dump one more time just get getting bigger and bigger and bigger and
bigger and bigger should i just launch it it's a giant beach ball that's not very
even a full charge it's not i can't it won't even get rid of one of these little towers
rare i don't like this uh loadout i need a machine gun or something
i'm like a not a big fan of this loadout sorry guys you know it's gonna make somebody mad
me go back and grind the tanks i'm not sure i'll need to
okay
right
Oh, I got it. All right, fine.
A lot of trees. Cold. Snowy.
I mean, I can French, so...
It's a really nice place.
I love, uh...
I miss, I miss Toronto.
Some good restaurants.
It's a good place.
There's a couple of great, there's like four or five really, really great barbecue places in Toronto.
It's like bar, if you like think like barbecue, that's a great place to go.
Game's too long.
Fixed it.
I said that, I said that, uh...
When you think barbecue, you really want to be there.
It's got some of the best barbecue places in the country.
I'm too quiet? What did I do?
All the way through here and then...
It's not too quiet, now it's... I've got it.
I gotta go in a different tunnel, I think.
Close. Oh, a bomb.
Why did I blow the other one up? Why would I do that? I don't understand.
Poutine? Oh, yeah.
For those who didn't know, I'm not from Canada.
Poutine is a dish, it's a french fries gravy.
And, um...
Sometimes it depends on what the certain restaurant...
My mother used to make it.
With gravy and little like kind of dollops of cheese, like chunks of cheese.
Oh, let me do this again.
I have to do this shit again.
Well, I have to do this now.
Destroy it!
I win. Did I actually do it?
They surrendered, why are they still attacking?
What's next?
Leave a level?
Secure a path.
Secure a path. Calm down, you just got a bomb.
You hear me right now? I'm doing just fine.
Right there, right there, right there, right there, right there.
Here?
How did I trip and explode?
Here's the final fight.
I don't want to blow this.
God damn it.
I have to do all that again if I lose.
And this is a bad loadout.
This is a terrible loadout.
I don't know what the hell I'm going to do about this.
Mr. President, the fuselage damage rate is above 50%.
Mr. President, the fuselage damage rate is over 70%.
A scaredy cat missile is being protected in a sturdy shelter.
When the shelter opens, that's your chance to win.
She's dead.
That didn't, I can't believe that didn't kill her.
What the fuck?
What?
Oh my god, what just hit me?
I need health or something right now.
Health, somewhere.
Shields, anything.
I don't want money.
There we go, thank you.
Bullshit.
Well, this gave me a good opportunity to get rid of literally the $800,000 beach ball ray gun.
That doesn't do anything.
I'm going to kill the tank like three more times.
Three more times.
I'm playing Diablo 3, you hear this?
Bastion sucks.
I'm leaning back in my chair.
I think that's enough, I think.
Manufacture bazookas.
So this is the thing that I currently own, right?
I still have no metal.
It sucks.
Rare metal required.
I'm going to piss my pants.
I've got to go pee.
I have to.
I'll be right back.
Usually when I come back from peeing, I'm like, I feel better.
What is this rare metal dog shit?
What is the point of this?
It's just money.
It's just like a number.
Alright, I am going to...
I don't know.
I need to think of something.
I bought everything I can buy.
Get the Gatling gun.
How far down?
Where is that?
934.
Well, I don't have enough to get it.
This is going to be a better loadout.
I'll try this again.
I'm only going to seriously give this another couple of attempts.
I can't stream for like 10, 11 hours.
I can't.
My brain will fucking melt.
I'm going to stick with this.
Get rid of this thing.
I need some assault rifles because...
Alright.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
The game would not let me select this item.
It was glitching out and making it impossible to click.
So I had to do it manually with the keyboard.
I'm not sure this is going to be very effective here.
Maybe I'll just run around with the flame thrower and just hold it down.
This would be better.
I think this is alright.
Get the Gatling gun.
Manufacture.
The VP's go-to machine gun fires multiple powerful rounds.
I need $22,000 worth of metal.
Getting rid of the beach ball gun and two machine guns should help a lot.
I'm going to go for it.
Let's go.
I got to go.
I got to get out of here.
I'm streaming tomorrow.
Tomorrow is going to be an intense stream too.
So why the fuck am I streaming for 10 hours today?
Tomorrow is going to be all over the place.
I'll try to make this clear.
Yeah, we're going to start at the regular time tomorrow.
Probably closer to 4.
You forced yourself to beat this.
I know it.
I'm upset about it.
What is that guy doing?
At least he's like the car in the game.
Did he actually get in?
He got in.
Put on the regular machine gun.
I'll take this thing.
I should go this way.
We're doing jazz dance tomorrow?
No, we're doing you're in the movies.
The gas one.
Yes, it's me.
Speaking please.
Who is it?
Alright, that's it.
Now we go straight down.
I have to take out the helicopters.
Those are things that cause so many problems.
Why can I not lock on?
Alright, let's go.
I got to pick up some shields.
I'm going to need them so badly for the next part.
I need shields.
Please drop a shield for me.
For me.
Did I get one?
Shields.
This whole thing is black and yellow.
I don't even know if I'm still streaming.
Am I?
I am, right?
Yes.
To the left.
We're a pre-recorded chat.
At least you're here.
More bombs.
I can't detonate these on my own.
I guess I can, but you have to really do it precisely.
I remember this part.
It sucks.
You can't move carelessly until the radar jamming station is destroyed.
Can you marry me?
Nope.
Says you.
Whatever.
I think I'm doing a good job.
What?
What's the matter?
That's cold.
How is that cold?
Hopefully I was not downstairs.
I'm going to do it, guys.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it this turn.
And there's going to be celebrations.
I would marry Jerma and then divorce him so I get half of what he gets every stream.
That's not...
And you guys are calling me cold.
Me cool.
All right, I'm good.
It's time.
I'm ready.
Let's get...
I got full health bar.
I'm going for...
What do you think?
Super launcher.
And just a standard...
Faithful here.
Are you guys still alive?
Arms.
Ammo.
Good.
Okay.
Here we go.
I got to get ready for this.
I need something that can lock on, though.
So I think I'm going to have to stick with this.
I need something to lock on to those helicopters.
This is it.
This is the one.
I am going to do it right here, right now.
It's time to...
We're good.
Let's get rid of all the bullshit ammo in the place over here.
We're halfway there.
Take the hand.
Make us win.
To boomer, I will divorce you.
Right?
What?
Was I not supposed to do this?
What happened?
Was I not supposed to do that?
I destroyed the White House?
But why?
I can't shoot it.
I just...
I was doing fine.
I was doing fine there.
I really was.
I had to...
I can't hit the White House.
You can only destroy the armor.
Why do you think it had a health bar?
Because I thought I had to...
I don't know.
I didn't think I was going to kill the whole thing.
Fuck.
I was so close.
I didn't know that, though.
Hold on.
I'm going to do it.
I'll be fine.
In Canada, there was a saying growing up.
My mother, who's French.
I think you guys have it in English, too.
I think it's in English.
It's...
Which my mother told me that translated to,
if at first you don't succeed, try, try again.
That's a little saying we have here in Canada.
I'm going to beat this.
And it's going to be the end of my channel.
Because after I beat it, I'm going to be so exhausted
that I'm going to scream.
They're going to have to take a real backseat.
I'm going to have to go to the spa after this.
I will beat this.
Can't beat this.
We just crossed the 10-hour border.
I was going to give up.
Remember, I was, like, raging.
Like...
It was just like a five.
What did Ajin give this?
That's all.
That's all I heard.
Not anymore.
Turn him.
I'm going to...
Yeah, that's good.
It was three hours ago and you almost quit.
That's so bad.
He's so bad.
Has he even stomped one time?
Guys, I just can't...
Has he even stomped?
He's fucking bad.
Let's just keep going straight through.
All right, so if it was...
If we were, like, in a real-life scenario,
where, like, you know, you...
Oh, hey, welcome.
Come to the German 95.
Twitch, meet and greet.
And, like, I'm like, hey, what's up?
How are you?
And we were kind of waiting to say hello and show up.
And would you say, dude, you're fucking bad at games?
I don't think you would.
I think you'd be like...
I think you'd be like, oh, Jeremy.
It's such an honor to meet you.
Remember when you full cocked your head backwards
and fully catapulted down to your head
and pushed through your desk?
That was...
Wow, that was ridiculous.
I can't believe you actually could do that.
The desk went in the hand.
You didn't even need to use your hands.
86.
So when is the German meetup?
I'm not...
I'm not doing one on Twitch, please.
This is a bomb.
Wait up.
Find that meetup.
Go find Dr. Bob.
I'm gonna find Dr. Bob.
I'm sorry.
We may able...
We may be able to...
We may be able...
Your income is over.
Oh, all right.
So don't destroy any...
Just do it now.
You know, like, why...
I'm not gonna use it on the actual White House.
Why don't you just do it now?
I can't use it on the White House.
I mean, you know...
Should I stop swearing?
My mother...
Actually, my mother told me recently.
She said, you should stop swearing.
I was like, yeah.
I was like, I've tried that before, mom.
She was like, it's not a good book for the former.
I was like, you know what?
You're up.
From now on.
Oh, no!
Oh, my...
Please.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Why did I do that?
I tried...
I didn't have enough boost.
Oh, my God.
And I have two things left.
I can't fucking believe it.
I can't believe it.
I just want to get out of this stupid area.
Oh, my God.
I need to look for a shield.
I have to.
Otherwise, there's no way I'm going to do this.
Mine's in the hallway.
Sloppy goddamn hallway.
Look, mine's in it.
Just in case.
Let's just lay him down.
I can't believe it.
I had full health too.
Mine's do like two full bars.
Why would they...
Why would they do that much damage?
I got the offensive augment.
I'm so happy about this.
Ten hours, and I can't manage the boost.
Yeah, I've been sitting here for ten hours.
Albert Einstein, if he was sitting in the chair for ten hours playing this game, would not be able to do that.
Thanks for the warning.
Albert Einstein wouldn't even have my stim right now.
Are you serious?
He'd write like a few theories and then go to bed.
Oops.
No, no, whatever.
He's probably here.
Peace.
And I'm dead.
Somehow.
I got like sandwiched.
I thought these guys were dead.
We have to do this whole thing again.
Presidents.
That's going to be a Christmas miracle if I'm able to do this.
Look at my ammo.
All this shit going on in this next area.
Trouble.
What am I going to do here?
I have to stick to this.
The thing I was doing before.
Except this time don't like accidentally destroy the whole White House.
Like I did before.
Somehow.
I'm going to go actually look around for ammo.
This box is back here.
What are you fucking doing?
Okay, I found a couple.
I found two.
I'm going to actually go to the other side.
There's more boxes over here.
What was that?
Some help.
Got to get rid of the helicopters.
Oh, there's the tanks.
There's two tanks.
They just spawned in here.
Not destroy the White House.
I see a shield over there.
I see one.
Got it.
Okay.
Do just fine.
Just relax.
Pull back.
Go to the right side now.
Here we go.
Come on.
To the knees.
Oh shit.
Bullshit.
Percy.
What's that mean?
Don't hit the White House.
I got so much more important stuff going on than that.
Here we go.
All right.
In a good spot.
Do not shoot the fucking under the armor's skin.
Clear the whole area.
Dumb.
I am intensely focusing right now.
There it is.
I got plenty of ammo.
Get rid of this little base over.
Don't see that one.
Come for missiles.
Just relax.
It's not a big deal.
You've handled way worse.
Okay.
I could be very upset about it.
I could be very mad about that.
But I'm not going to be.
Nope.
Doing just fine.
Good.
Nice job.
I would shit my hand right now.
It's nice and easy.
Just nice and easy.
Don't hurt anything.
It's nice and easy.
It's going to open again.
Wait for it to open.
Do not shoot that.
Why is it on my display?
Why is it on my heads up display?
Off the side.
Clear the trash.
Right there.
Open up.
Come on.
This is the perfect weapon for this.
Shit.
What's firing at me from over here?
I don't have time for that.
Clear out the trash.
I have to.
I'm going to get dumped on.
It's you.
All right.
Get rid of this tank.
Enough.
Right side.
Done.
That's it?
Is there one more?
Where is it?
On the top?
It's up top.
Go too crazy.
Wait for the next one to open.
Do not.
Okay.
The White House is going to hurt.
Come.
I did it.
I beat the game.
Got my pods upgraded.
The White House was back in the hands of the American people that long last the United States had won back its freedom.
However, the mastermind of its misery remained at large.
The stage had been set for a final clash to determine whose version of justice the history books would honor.
The dice were about to be rolled one last time for America and it wasn't clear whose side Lady Luck was going to be on.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Yes.
Lady Luck.
My treasured has disappeared.
Showdown.
The special intelligence.
Wolf.
In Las Vegas.
The vice president is in Las Vegas.
Let's go.
Really?
Nobody rivals our intelligence gathering abilities.
Head for Las Vegas with me.
Well, not just me.
Everyone in the resistance will be rivaling support around the country.
I know.
Thanks.
Mr. President.
Good luck.
And Godspeed.
Jody.
Prepare Air Force One.
We're heading.
Yes, Mr. President.
Let's go.
The vice president, Rich.
My only advice to you is this.
Beat him to a pulp.
This mission goes by the call name.
Good luck and Godspeed, Mr. President.
That's the name.
Did I skip it?
No, I didn't.
Okay.
I need to buy something here.
Missile.
No, no, no, no.
What was it?
What was I going to do?
This is going to be just like on rails or something.
It's not going to be hard.
The Gatling gun.
Right.
That was right.
Okay.
How much is this?
Gatling gun has been acquired.
Also, where's the next one?
I got the best bazooka, right?
I already got it.
Missile launcher.
This is the best missile launcher in the game.
I'll take it.
Put it on.
Okay.
That's that.
I'm going to put the other side.
It's going to be this thing.
This crazy thing.
So this is the big one here.
Okay.
Next is going to be.
I'm thinking.
Let's put the Gatling gun here.
32 Gatling guns.
I don't have enough.
Should be another machine gun then, shouldn't it?
Let's try with this.
I got all.
I got really good stuff.
Let's go.
Final mission.
Final mission of the game.
Let's go.
Richard, come on.
Oh, Michael.
You're so sweet.
Richard.
And for that, I owe you.
You canceled all my dreams and plans.
So now I've got a nice little present for you.
Here.
Do I have to.
Wait.
It's a gauntlet.
Here.
Do I have to.
Wait.
It's a gauntlet.
Let me ask you one last thing.
What do you want on your tombstone?
What do you want it to say, huh, Michael?
I think this is a block.
Oh, no.
Oh, please.
What do you want on your tombstone?
Hmm.
I can't catch that briefcase.
I killed him too fast.
I can't get the.
I hope that's not a valuable item.
Lovely footwork.
Richard.
Oh, it was a dummy.
Now try dancing with me.
This show's gonna run all night.
Richard.
Please, not all night.
It already has.
Where is he?
Is he just flying around?
Oh, my goodness.
Just hold on.
Wait a minute.
I got locked up here tonight, I think.
Where is he?
Almost caught.
Gatling gun.
Let's go.
I don't think I hit him one time.
I gotta get close.
That didn't hurt him.
He's bad.
Stop.
I'm fine.
Sweet.
You are so sweet, Michael.
Like gulping a cup of condensed milk.
What is going on now?
Think you can kill me, huh?
Sweet.
All right, let's take it outside.
I'm gonna keep the Gatling gun on.
This is fine.
I thought you guys were lying to me when the last level was Vegas.
That's so funny.
I did not think that that was gonna be...
Where'd he go from here?
Did he go inside?
This is not an epic fight anymore.
Oh, wait.
...were among the POWs you rescued.
Further in?
I need him to, like, clap his hands.
I am.
Good challenge.
He went out that way.
Okay, good.
He's out here.
Richard, you can run, but you can't hide.
Catch your dream.
Banana.
You gonna complain?
He's a coward.
I can't win.
So shoot me, Michael.
Who's mocking who?
Or are you a chicken?
Knock that jerk off the roof.
Show him who will have the last laugh.
He's a jerk.
Hit him.
Did I get him?
I didn't get him.
There it is.
You break it, you bought it, Michael.
Michael, you'll pay for the damages with your life.
Out of ammo.
I can't get off of this.
Killing you is easier than breaking a baby's arm.
Holy shit.
What the hell did he just say?
Jesus.
Phase three.
Shall I take you to the next stage?
Yeah.
He's on the move again.
I do need ammo.
I wonder if I can get it from anything in here.
Offensive augment.
I'm going to take my time here.
I won't go in like a dumpster.
Go boxes with his heavy weapons.
In the arms.
Good.
Not any Gatling gun ammo, though.
That's a real bummer.
There are crates behind me.
Oh, fuck.
All the way down.
How did I miss that?
Because I was scrolling through to see what ammo that was.
Actually, that's worth it.
The vice president moved behind the passageway.
Mr. President, chase after him.
I know.
Light arms.
All right.
Heavy arms.
Shield unit.
Is he going to cut me off?
How lovely.
Doesn't knowing that it all ends here kind of get your adrenaline going?
I wonder those crates.
Richard.
Michael.
At the stage all to ourselves.
Uh-oh, it's final destination.
No weapons?
It ends here.
I don't know where to go.
I thought I was going to fall off here and die.
Like Virtua Fighter style.
Get it.
Oh.
Cracking.
I'm starting to crack.
I got to hold on.
I'm cracking.
Take it and dodge and take it to your grave.
He's doing his, like, super move.
Thank you, Mr. President.
It's not over.
This is, like, phase five.
Like hell it is.
I have to fight this space shuttle?
Oh, my God.
Space station?
Mr. President?
The scene is pointless.
The reason is because I'm the president of the great United States of America.
Yeah!
Mr. President?
Jodie, I'm going to step out into outer space.
See you soon!
Let's do this again.
E-E-A-S-E-A.
Gold to play on Vegas.
Given over 10 years of my life to this profession and no scene has ever engraved itself upon my mind the way this one did.
Two men, two ideals, one outcome.
I cannot imagine where we would all stand now that things have gone the other way.
President, are you all right?
Yes.
I've been very pleased about my first flight in space.
But I just wish I had brought my camera.
Mr. President, be sure and come back now.
The American people are waiting for you.
She says Mr. President as much as I say, oh, my God.
I am the president of the United States of America.
Be back.
Mr. President?
Please continue to update me as the battle goes on.
Sure.
Oh, and contact the Japanese embassy.
Tell them we can hold that wildlife protection conference.
He's not in space anymore?
Wait, did he take the helmet off?
He took the helmet off.
Mr. President, don't take off the helmet!
What are you trying to do?
In sinister nature, I predict he has some unexpected trump card up his sleeve.
But Mr. President, be victorious at all costs.
The reason is because you're the president of this great land.
This mission goes by the call name...
To the moon.
Believe in justice.
Best of luck, and Godspeed, Mr. President.
All right.
What am I missing that I can invest in?
I like what I got now.
Assault weapons, right? Assault rifles.
I'm going to get the best assault rifle, like, in the world.
The RFRH.
Assault, where is it? Assault, assault, assault, assault.
Assault weapons, there we go.
What is it?
The RFRH.
I do want...
If I can get it, I want two of these.
I can't get it.
Well, I got the Gatling gun, and then I'm going to put the assault rifle, that RFRH, here to get double, triple firepower.
Give it a flamethrower.
Check out the handguns.
Maybe. I'll check them out.
Handguns.
Might as well do it, all right?
29.
9PA.
DE91.
DE91EN.
DE91PA.
M45.
Don't have enough money.
I don't think I can even make it.
Am I still going to stream tomorrow? Yeah.
I'm just not going to stream at, like, 12.
I'll stream at, like, 4.
I'll be all right.
I'm not going to do a 10 or 11 hour stream. I don't understand how these happen. They just do.
Yeah, I mean, today, it's almost been, I can't believe it's almost been 11 hours.
What the hell am I doing?
All right, I'm going to try it with this, but I'm going to take off the trash here, which is, like, absolute trash.
Put on Sam.
Actually, no, put this on. I feel like I could get use out of that.
Yeah, this looks all right.
Let's give it a go.
I know, you even commented earlier on keeping Eastern viewers up until, like, 3.
I know.
Final mission, here we go.
Richard!
Chasing 15 million feet after me.
Now that's love.
Well, I love you too, Michael.
I love you so much, I can't stand it.
So much, I want to kill you.
Hold it, Richard!
Take a long-ass look at the 200 billion stars in the Milky Way.
Of all man's achievements in the 21st century, this is the climax!
It's a big cannon. Two big cannons.
I only have 300 seconds to beat this.
I don't even know where to start.
Mr. President, the barrier is shut.
You won't be able to advance if you don't destroy it.
Let's go!
Almost out of time!
I'm at 11 hours, man.
Give me a break.
Give me a little slack.
I think so.
Mr. President, do you think you can just run away?
Mr. President!
I need to lead a little bit of strength.
Full of energy.
I'm not playing the game right now.
I'm going to check in as well.
Just kidding, it's me.
What am I supposed to be doing?
Up, up, up, up!
Shit!
I can't destroy the ladder.
Alright, let's go!
You guys all going up there too?
Cool.
You know Richard.
What's going on?
I'm fine.
I'm fucking...
God, how do I get out of here?
Okay.
Oh my God.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm just fucking laughing really hard.
Sometimes I look over here, man, and I fucking see something so stupid, so funny.
You guys kill me sometimes.
Richard!
What do you stand for, Michael?
Be certain now.
As certain as the blood gushing out of your mouth.
As certain as the blood gushing out of your mouth when I bash it in.
Be certain of your death here and now.
Okay, I'm good.
Now I have to fight this thing.
Now, come at me with all your body and soul.
I'll hug you to death.
Okay.
Mr. President, the fuselage damage rate is above 50%.
Jesus, come on.
I have so much of this shit.
You didn't break any of them.
Dude, no, he does.
But I have the super thing.
I see health over there.
There's health over here.
Oh, fuck.
There's a health over there.
I'm going to get it.
He's standing now in this tiny arena.
Oh, God damn it.
I have this health to my left or right.
Left, I think.
It even matters.
Like, impossible.
Literally not even possible.
It's scripted, it's scripted.
I win.
Way to go, Mr. President.
That is like unbearable.
That fight is fucking unbearable.
It's just like obnoxious.
Like, what the fuck?
You gotta give me a break.
That's just dumb.
What a dumb fucking fight.
Spam daddy a little bit.
Just spam.
I'm stuck the whole thing.
It's like a musician's face.
What's the strategy with this guy?
You just hold spray and you don't get hit by a random bullet?
What is that noise?
I'm beyond the point of my return here.
Here we go.
I'm saving my super for the big fight.
The real one.
A speed upgrade or something.
I feel like I'm so much slower than these things.
You know what? I gotta get a thing that destroys all incoming projectiles.
Actually, I can't fucking believe it.
I'm desperate.
But I'm still firing.
I think I'm firing still.
What a joke.
What the fuck was that?
What?
I have to get the thing that destroys...
This is not even a video game.
This isn't a video game.
I'm just coming to that realization right now.
This is not even a game.
I need one of those laser beams that destroy all projectiles.
This fucking game.
It's like...
Why?
Ben Boss is just...
I'm not allowed to say it.
Am I allowed to say it?
Should I say it?
I think I'm just gonna say it.
This game sucks.
Somebody look at the ratings for this game.
What does it have right now?
Alright, I need to do...
Wait, it's a machine gun. Right here it is.
Intercepting fire.
I just want like three of these.
I think that changes everything. I really think it does.
I think this thing here...
Should help.
I'm gonna do this one or two more times.
Never let the joke die.
Out of here!
Oh shit, I forgot about the ceiling.
I can't look at the link right now.
I'm busy trying to complete this game.
It's taking all of my attention.
Look at the virus.
Wait, what?
Oh, right.
Let's get out the big ones.
Target, target, target.
Why is it not locking on?
No, that's not gonna work.
I'm rolling up.
So it's on my left side.
This is gonna be what's necessary.
I'm gonna skip this part.
I have 167 seconds.
If I get up here without with 150 seconds remaining.
Let's start from here.
I have to play the game.
Okay, here we go.
It's time.
Bring it out, the MP7.
And then the...
This thing.
Let's hope it's enough.
Will it be enough?
Only 20 bullets on this thing, keep in mind.
I'm going. Go.
It is a little bit better, I think.
Although this is probably...
This might just be a placebo effect.
No, no, it wants back, please.
I gotta get rid of all the assault rifles.
I got nothing else, do I?
In the fucking other hands. Oh, this is bad.
This is really, really, really bad.
I need ammo.
Please. Get out of the corner.
Here we go.
There cannot be another phrase.
Where is he going?
Did I do it?
That was easy.
Was that me or him? I did it.
Shooting star.
Jodie, who am I?
I'm the president.
I always make
the impossible possible.
And I'm gonna keep on doing so.
Michael.
Richard, it was your methods
that were flawed. Our love
for America won't change.
Richard!
You're just gonna kill me!
This is how I'm sitting.
I'll show you after.
Tomorrow's gonna be
another busy day at the
White House.
That was fun.
This is how I was sitting during the cutscene.
My fellow Americans,
good morning.
As Americans, we love
freedom. But true
freedom isn't a given like the air
we breathe or the water we drink.
About 240
years ago,
our forefathers fought greatly
giving their blood, sweat
and tears. And in the
end, they won our freedom.
And we must
never forget this.
If anything appears
that threatens
our belief in this freedom,
we will oppose
it. We will crush
it. In fighting
to gain our freedom, we
need no reasons.
We require
no just cause or flowery
words. In order
to protect our neighbors who love
freedom and this faith in freedom,
we continue
to believe in our own justice.
We
won't abandon any battles.
And the
reason is
because we are
all citizens of the United
States of America.
I will be a vanguard
leading this fight.
And the reason is
because
I'm the president of
this great United States
of America.
Welcome.
What would you score this game? A 3.
Out of 5.
2.5 out of 5.
I would eat here.
I would give this 2.5 out of 5.
The 2.6 out of 5 just because
of the funny voice acting.
52 out of 100.
Hey, I played it, didn't I?
If I hated it, I wouldn't have done it.
Now I'll click the link.
That was Metal Wolf Chaos XD.
Let's look at this link.
Oh my god.
I look like the main character from
Number Bunchers.
By the way, that wasn't even from McDonald's.
That was from Wendy's.
What a scammer.
Alright, I'm
leaving. I'm outta here.
What about the
tier lists?
That was fun. It was.
For all how bullshit some of the
stuff was in this game and how over the top it was
and how weird some of it was.
I still enjoyed
myself.
5.9 out of 10.
There you go, just barely below 6.
Almost a passing grade. No, but that's still alright.
5.9.
That's alright. That was worth it.
Some teachers
actually will pass you if you get a 5.9.
If you get a 59,
that's a 5.9, but if you
nostalgia factor,
it could probably bump you up to like a 6.5.
6.4.
I'm gonna do the bits tomorrow.
I actually like am dying
at this scene.
We'll do the bits tomorrow.
We'll do a little just hangout session at the end of tomorrow.
Tomorrow is not going to be
an 11 hour stream. I can guarantee that.
I can promise you that.
So we'll go over these bits tomorrow.
The stream's not gonna be...
The stream's gonna start in like
16 hours.
14 hours or something.
I don't know.
16 hours. 14 hours or something.
I'm just wrecked
right now.
We're not gonna go that late tomorrow, I promise.
Because tomorrow is
gonna be a little more elaborate.
Tomorrow I'm playing You're in the Movies.
It's gonna be an on camera
stream with a green screen behind me.
It's a whole game based around being on a green screen.
Yeah, sorry I'm not doing
the bits. I hate to...
I really hate doing this, but we'll do them all tomorrow.
Kinda like we did last time when the
stream got cut off. We just kinda hung out.
Played a game and just kinda chilled and
went over them and talked about stuff.
The credits I can do, because the credits are
right here. The sub credits.
Wow, we're here though. I do wanna catch the
community subs that I did miss.
I do wanna say that.
Say thanks to those people, because there was a bunch of community subs tonight.
Here they come!
Can you see them?
Why can I not see these?
Roll credits, let's go. Holy shit, that's a lot.
Thank you everybody for the subs.
Seriously.
A lot of fucking resubs, a lot of community subs.
Speaking of community subs.
Magellan gave 5 community subs.
Kazzy gave 5 community subs.
JermaSucks gave 5 community subs.
Thank you.
There was a lot of random $150
bits we went over. I think we got all of them.
And we will absolutely
slowly go over these tomorrow after
this stream. Am I quiet?
Oh yeah, that's right. Why is this so quiet?
Sorry about that. And then Tingy right now,
thanks for the 5 community subs.
That game was good. I liked that game.
Enough to give it a 6.3.
What did I say?
5.9? 5.9.
I think 6.1 is fair.
I'll meet you in the middle.
Keeps going up.
Rank all the FromSoftware games.
Bloodborne, Demon's Souls.
Dark Souls 1.
Sekiro and Dark Souls 3
are kind of tied, I think.
Dark Souls 2.
I said Demon's Souls, yeah.
Demon's Souls is at the top. So Dark Souls 2.
Every video game
that released for Super Nintendo.
Nintendo 64, PlayStation 1,
PlayStation 2.
Every putt-putt game.
And then Metal Wolf Chaos.
Is this worst
or best? That's maybe.
He's still bad.
No I'm not.
Ow.
This is one of those strange moments.
Sometimes
you just lock in
and decide you're going to do something.
Love of Sekiro
destroys people's egos and makes them
really mad at it. It did that to me.
I was so
frustrated in Sekiro.
I did it though. I completed it. I got to the very end.
This had like
3 meltdowns. It was impressive.
Oh it was big. 11 hours.
It's almost 11 and a half hours.
That's like almost two streams.
No. It was more like
one funny pretend
laugh out loud meltdown.
One real meltdown.
One of those meltdowns
was just for fun.
Alright goodnight guys. I'll see you tomorrow. We'll do the bits tomorrow.
And the stream tomorrow is
going to be all over the place. I cannot even
describe what we're going to have. It might
just be a disaster.
But I don't think so. Should be a lot of fun.
See you tomorrow. Or see you later today.
Probably around
4 o'clock Pacific.
3 to 4. We're going to do regular time tomorrow.
Goodnight.
Try it yourself. Metal Gear
Chaos
XD
Give it a try. It was a little hard. It was a little
crazy.
Interesting money mechanic.
It was alright. I had
some fun. I did. But I didn't like a lot
of parts. But I did like some parts.
That's my review.
See you tomorrow. Have a great night.