All right, convinced myself of something very recently here right now.
I'm certain, you know a cow has four stomachs. I've never had an x-ray before on my, you know,
bladder. I bet you I have three or four bladders. Some kind of genetic mutation.
Well everybody's messages are getting deleted. What are you guys doing? All right, let's do it.
Create skater. Skater one. Site. Name. Who does this- what's this? Because you put like stat points
in and shit, don't you? I can't make Thanos right now. It could be me. This is just going
to be Jeremy. Why would it be anything else? Enough room? I don't have enough room. This
character career is going to take two hours? This- not a very significant amount of things
you can do in this character career. Jax Albertson. I got it. That's actually a pretty
good idea. Thank you for the suggestion. All right, there is Jax Albertson. My real name.
Name. Uh, hometown. I'm gonna spell it like that. Age. Style. All around. Vert. Street. All
around. Hmm. Vert I believe is air. Height. Street is being able to jump around. It's
grind on shit. And all around is kind of your style is all around. I'm gonna say,
uh, no Goofy. Goofy is just, uh, you sitting out the other way. Street is probably better,
but I don't know. I think I like all around. Street. Street. Weight. I don't weigh that much.
I don't weigh that little- oh my lord. You can literally make a sausage with it. Thank you
Herbert for the five community subs. Thanks a lot Herb. Herbert. I'm like- I'm like 154 or
something, so that's close enough. I'm not gonna make him a hot dog. Complexion. Uh,
let's load everything. Okay, roll easy. Head. Slick. I think that's just Tony Hawk's face.
Suck. Suck too. I actually kind of like this one. Striped shirt. Uh, what do I got on
right now? I have like a gray shirt on. Camo. Tank top. Jersey. Sweat bands.
Three. Sweat bands. Sweatshirt. T-shirt. That's kind of boring. I wear kind- I wear shit like
this. I do. No logo. The one I have on right now is gray, but I'll do like a blue.
That's all right right there. The same color. Pants. If they have a Star Wars logo pants,
I'll do it. If not, I'm just gonna do pair of jeans. Really wear shorts.
Uh, regular pants. I'm just gonna make them blue. There we go. Shoes.
All right, that's- that's- that looks all right. That's not what I look like though,
at all. That- that kind of looks like me. The guy with the helmet on. Or one of these.
Maybe. Yeah, that looks like me. Okay, I'm gonna keep the helmet on. You can just pretend
I'm bald under there. Whatever. All right, this is important. I've got five points left.
This is very important. Hang time. Olly. Speed. Spin. Landing. Switch. Rail. Bail.
Lip balance. Rail balance. I need some like- ah, no. Rail balance. I want at least a couple.
I love riding manuals as well. Speed. Maybe air as well. Or hang time. That rail balance
is so important. All right, that's all right. That's okay. I think that's good. 100% into
Olly. I'm gonna get points as I get cash. Is rail balance more important than manuals in the
first part of the game? Yeah, you can't take points away. You can just add. I think it's
all right. I'm good. I'm good with this. Trick setup. I forgot you could do all this shit.
I forgot about this. Up and X. I got no money, but we can. Okay. Inward heel flip.
Heel flip. And some of these are worth more points. Yep. Up, up, X. What do we got?
Possible varial kick flip. Let's put this on. Do I have any? No, I have varial heel flip.
No varial kick flip, though. No, actually, I already do.
All these cost money. Hard flip. No, I still, I think I pretty much I have
everything. You can buy shit. Let's see. Inward heel flip, varial, X shove it, kick flip,
hard flip. Flip all the way north. Inward heel flip. Yeah, I gotta buy these.
There's the mute, the whole other mute. Got a stale fish. Indy, stiffy, crossbone.
Close beef. Grab. Grab tricks. Yeah, actually, that's really not. These are the grabs.
Up, up, and B. These are, we're getting into the, not necessarily, they're not that important.
Lip tricks. Yeah, nose stall. Disaster. What else is there? Something else.
Specials. Now, this is important. Dark slide. Can't do it? Oh, it's already assigned.
Right down B is kick, flip, kick, twist. Up, up, 540 flip. Bang, bang. Okay, I gotta remember
this one. Left, right. Left, right, grind, dark slide. All right, well, we'll just go.
Let's get, let's just get it going. I'm ready. Oh, let me just crack open.
You can only pick tricks that you can do in real life. Well, then I wouldn't even stand
on the skateboard. These are all just dog shit boards. I can't afford anything else.
Save skater into career file. Yes. What am I drinking? This is a, it's a Coca Cola.
It's just a Coke. What the hell was that? No, this is my VMU. Career mode. New career.
There he is. Jax Alberton. Let's see how bad he is compared to everybody else.
It's not bad actually. I mean, yeah, everybody else is more balanced, but
let's do it. Buy stats, buy tricks, skate shop. All right, he did all that.
Let's go. This is the hanger. Mullet Falls. Minnesota, Kentucky. So the goals here.
What do we got? Get a high score of 10,000, 25,000, and 75,000. Let's skate.
The nose grind over the pipe. Hit the hang time gaps. Secret tape. 100% goals. Let's just go for
points. You kind of have to do these in sessions because they're timed. And let's like try to
remember how to play this video game. Let's go. Welcome to Tony Hawk 2 for the Sega Dreamcast.
RIP Vaude. Oh, first fall. Manuals. Oh my God. I forgot how great this was.
I'm going to just get used to the controls. Is there no uh, is there no bar
for when you're on the reel? I just thought there was. It's been so long. Turn it up.
All right, I'll turn it up. Sound levels. Music. That's good.
Oh yeah, I'm feeling it. I'm feeling it. One thing I gotta remember how to do
whole jumping. Yeah. That was perfect somehow. So what did I get in my in my tutorial run?
So I gotta work on jump speed. Definitely. So high score, high score. So maybe you're
noticing my ollie and my air. That needs a little work. Let's go for 75,000. I'll get it.
Okay. Audio delay on the PlayStation. On me or the PlayStation 2?
Dreamcast. Retried. That's the best part about Tony Hawk is you can just do it again
right now. Oops. I gotta get used to the uh, here it is. You got the multiplier up there.
Dark slide. Tony Hawk is fucking back in town baby.
Wait. No. Just wait till I get like a couple of hours in here, man. I'm gonna be fucking
rubbing. Shit. Oh god damn it. I'm so happy. I got the barrels at least. I can't hold on to
the lip for long. I'm just a bum. Got it. Dammit. No. Oh, you can keep this. You can
keep it going. Do it again. One hang time. Get the barrels too. Shit. I need enough points.
By the way, this is not going to be a very talky game because I've got to concentrate.
Daisy. One thing I'm trying to get used to is when you jump off, usually you can as you
jump off and do another trick even more easily. I can grind it because it's like I'm tripping.
That's how you like string together shit real well.
One fifth of the way to a million. Yeah. That ain't gonna happen anytime soon.
Like almost a tenth of the way to a million. You got to get it like started immediately.
There it is. This is the song. This is the song. You know, it also is just stats too.
Stats too low to do anything crazy. Just got to work on just doing it. Forget about
stringing points together. Just get them in the kind of normal. Oh, what was I thinking?
All right. I'm so obsessed. Shit. All right. Yeah. Yeah. All right. I got, I don't, I don't have
enough points yet. Just do it the normal way. Jeremy, you can't string things together with
three points in one. Fuck. You know what I'm saying? Let's go. Thanks so much.
Oh, you know what it is? There is, I don't have one set to up. Okay.
Damn it. Okay. No, no, no. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
I don't have anything set to up X. The tricks would reset.
Get it. Oh, I didn't get it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I love the hang time.
I should have done more hang time. Grab the edge there. I got the points.
Okay. I got it. One 10th of the way to a million. Sound is not synced. Let me see.
The sound is happening too early. See if that helps. This is on PlayStation 2. Yes.
But this is the best version of Tony Hawk. This is the most, this is the most polished
Oh, did I get it? I got it. Let's go with the, uh, I don't, let's get the barrel.
Wait, I can go across there. Holding up. There it is. Okay. Secret tape. Barrels. That's it.
Not quite. No, I got them, didn't I? I got the tape. No, I didn't get it.
You open school to the best map across the entire series. But we're not, I want to,
let's look at one, one place at a time. There was a string from school two a long time ago
that I used to be able to do. Starts at that first staircase going down. You go down,
you jump on the two benches on the left side. You can string together a million fucking points
in school two. It's the best map in all Tony Hawk. I need pilot wings and skate. Okay. Yes.
Flames.
There's a secret in there, a secret up top too.
E is up there.
Got it. Hold L and R in the air to even out.
L and R are spinning in the air.
Two more pilot wings. This way. You skate or you die.
Oh, there it is.
Got them all.
I think that's all I can do for now.
Ain't hot no more.
Turn the sound effects down. So we got barrel hunt, all the hang time gaps, and nose grind.
Turn up the effects. Where the sound level? Is the sound level too high? Five, eight, and nine.
It's not, is it all right? Make sure it's not terrible. Yeah, that's one. Two, I believe,
across this, didn't have much speed, but okay. That one hits it right here.
And no. The last one? All right, it's through the wall, right?
So
I thought it was the helicopter.
Remember, you can spend your, yeah, no, not yet. Where's that last jump that I'm missing?
All right, let's get the barrels. Tony Hawk and Chad?
This is seriously the best skateboarder game ever.
I really wish, I really wish you could get another one of these plastic.
Come on, done.
As the grind the nose pipe. Which one is that? That's the question. Grind the nose pipe. Up there?
Oh my god. Great Canadian Fuck Club just came in with 20 more community subs.
A thousand of them essentially at this point. Thank you, great Canadian, for your $50,000 probably.
Now that means a lot. Thank you so much. You've given so much money to this channel, man.
Thank you. Nose grind over the pipe and then we're done.
Nose grind over the pipe. Over the pipe. This one up here?
Oh, it's dry.
100% we did it. Level one complete.
Let's get a, get a dark slide here.
That's not it. Left, left, right, right?
Left, left, right, right?
That was such a loud noise.
Wall exploiter.
Got it all. 100% goals and cash. Wait, I need cash. I mean I don't have to 100% every level.
The helicopter. There's the cash up top. I need cash up here.
Wow. I gotta get up. I need a bunch of speed. I need to get up here.
100 bucks.
Is there any more money? I think I got all the cash.
Big bits. Big bits.
Pellar grind? Grind the propeller grind. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Like the propeller on the plane?
Okay, on the pipe itself. Half pipe.
50 bucks. That should be it.
Oh, there's so much more money in here.
That was a gnarly wipeout.
Holy shit, that was so high in the air.
One more pill right here.
Going too fast.
Leveled. No such thing as too fast.
Now we just free skate for a little bit.
And then we're gonna buy some points. Maybe a new skateboard.
I love this game.
I got 2,500 bucks.
Save career. Let's go buy some stuff.
This music makes me feel like I want to punch something.
So what do you think?
Do some points?
Or tricks?
I'm gonna say stats are probably more important first.
Points.
Manuals.
I mean air.
Full rail balance.
Music is so loud.
I'm sorry.
Speed.
All the air and rail balance.
I think that's pretty good for now.
Landing also could use it.
Maybe take one off of all the important landing.
The rail balance is the most important thing.
That's how you stay
moving forward just to string more shit together.
100% level goal on the hangar.
Let's move our way to school 2
in southern California.
100,000 points.
Let's skate. Wall ride the bells.
Ball passes.
Find secret tape.
This is where we're probably not gonna 100% everyone.
I'm willing to give it a try.
Let's see if I can remember the route.
To do
a shitload of points.
Nobody's made a new skating game because peak skater
counterculture hasn't had as much traction
since the Tony Hawk era.
Yeah that's true but doesn't mean that I don't
necessarily...
It's right here. There it is.
That's how you do it. That's it. Do you see what I'm talking about?
You go across and you keep going.
You need more speed though.
I'm not sure I'll be able to do it.
That's 50 grand.
This place really is so awesome.
There's so much to do here.
Throw skater. I didn't even do it right.
I gotta get something on up.
Up and kickflip.
That's like one of my favorite ways to grab.
That rail balance though. That's why we buy...
That's why we bought it.
I got some...
What the hell happened there?
I need to do it but...
It's a long ride.
I'll get the high score right now.
That's good.
Try to do the special.
Oh yeah.
And then you go across these and you end up across this.
It's so much. It's amazing.
The one more try mentality.
It's so evident here.
I'm gonna be obsessed with this.
It's a lot of money too.
So we need to grab skate.
Five bells.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Do it again. I gotta make something up.
I don't have anything on up or down.
One more try. Come on.
I don't think I got it. I think I need some more stats before I can attempt it.
One more.
Stop skipping music. I'm just restarting the level.
Alright. Alright. Come on.
I'm obsessed.
I didn't even do it.
Come on. Why did I not do it?
I'll do it later.
I've got no stats.
Alright. Ride the bells.
I see one over here.
Across the dumpster.
Five. Where are the other five?
Any of the bells over there?
Up top maybe?
I think I'm gonna go buy speed and ollie.
I'm pretty slow.
Is this way to go down too?
Possible? It might not be possible.
We'll see.
Maybe you can actually grab onto that part.
School bell. We'll give her a school bell.
I got some money.
I'll spend it.
There's so much in this level. I love it so much.
I'm overwhelmed by all the awesome things
to do.
You end up over here.
And then initial string going off the bench.
You come all the way down. Up there.
That's how you get a million points.
Let's spend some cash.
I need to go faster.
Let's see.
Speed.
This backs out speed.
Speed and air.
Or speed and ollie probably.
Change the one for up.
Up and x.
Down and x.
Empty.
I'm gonna say...
Let's try it again.
There's a new skating game on Steam.
There's a lot of
skating games that have come out since.
But even after
something like Skate 2 and Skate 3.
Like somebody was mentioning that
the skating culture is...
Nobody really cares anymore.
But...
I don't really care about
skateboarding.
But skateboarding games are just
fun.
They always have been.
That's what I'm talking about.
I need to get this bell over here.
One more bell.
What do you think?
I heard it. Where was it?
There's this bell.
Is it up top?
Got stuck in a wall.
One thing about Tony Hawk is
you really need to start to memorize
the maps.
It takes a while.
Then you'll know exactly where everything is.
You really just do it by skating around.
I shouldn't really be looking for them.
Just skating.
I always have skate.
T.E.
This one.
Whoops.
He'll do it for this game
but not hit and run.
I don't think
it's a fair comparison to compare
Tony Hawk 2 with
The Simpsons hit and run.
Beautiful.
Get up there!
There's a lot to do up there.
Shit!
I'm trying to grab it.
How many songs does it have?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
Probably like 15.
Three of five school bells!
There's another one over here.
Where's there?
It's up there.
How can I reliably get
up there?
I don't think it goes from here.
I hear the bell.
Where is it?
I can hear you.
Where are you bell?
I just heard you.
There it is.
One more.
Where's that last bell?
I hear it.
Where's the bell?
Where is it?
Where is the bell?
I don't even know.
Was it this one?
Did I not even get it?
Skate around.
That's all I can do.
I think the music is too loud for me.
I can't hear any sounds.
Sorry guys.
I can't really hear what I'm doing.
Yeah, that's better.
20 community subs from Freudian Weapon.
You guys with the community subs lately.
It's been so many of them.
Just hundreds.
Almost a thousand probably.
In the last five or six days.
Get it?
Ah.
Walride is so finicky with these.
Some of them are just stuffed in a corner
and you really have to just...
There's no real reliable way to get some of them.
Just stop what you're doing and go get them.
Holy shit guys, seriously.
I'm always missing one.
Because this is four.
Now let's see what this is.
This is down here in the little school yard.
Let's try to get them.
Is this one?
And down here.
I'll just grab everything I can.
That makes it down here.
It's not one itchy fucking neck.
It was so bad. It was so itchy.
What is going on with my neck?
It's like
under my chin area.
That's getting like bit by a fucking
scorpion? What the hell is going on?
Speaking of what's going on.
Ten more community subs by getting the clown car.
Ten
more on top of everything else.
Fucking ridiculous.
Unbelievable.
Ah.
I didn't get it. I get it.
Let's see if I can just hop over.
Right here. Shit. A little too far.
Five more from Juno.
Juno. On top of the
probably two, like there's probably
two thousand community subs on this channel.
I'm not even going to lie.
I really think there are probably at least
fifteen hundred to two thousand community subs on the channel.
That's insane.
Forget about just getting speed to do it.
Oh I made it.
No no no. Stop stop stop.
There's something down here right?
Not really. This just kind of ends the trick.
Ah coming at an angle.
That's the worst one to get.
Because you have to go at a slight angle
to get the bells.
And that's just plopped right in this weird spot
in the corner. You have to get it almost from this side.
Because trying to reliably get it
this way is sort of not
really feasible.
What else we got? Money?
Hitbox is dumb.
Yeah it is a little dumb but it's alright.
I think I want to try the other level first.
I'm going to hop past this other.
Some of you guys seriously
have so many subs.
There's almost seven thousand subs on this channel.
In the last three days.
Do you understand how insane that is?
There wasn't...
There's been like almost a couple thousand
added in the last week and a half.
That's absolutely ridiculous.
This is all
really seriously has been in the last not even
thirty days. I really hope
you guys can like afford it.
Because that's a lot of money.
That's like a huge
amount of money. My God.
Thank you.
I just hope you take care of yourself first.
Visual Warlock
ten community subs. I'm going to try
the other level. I want the points.
Thank you so much guys.
That's twenty from AmScoots.
Thank you AmScoots for twenty community subs.
Dropping sub missiles.
This is France.
What was the point? Things for France.
Alright, not again.
No, not again. No.
Every stream can't be a money stream.
That's thirty-three from
Soft33. With the namesake.
Thank you so much for the
thirty-three community subs.
I don't even know what to say. It's
shocking to me.
You guys are fucking too much. Thank you.
Five more from getting the clown car.
He's
complaining about getting money.
No, it's just
those of you that have been watching the channel for the last
week. It's been
an uncountable amount of money.
An extreme
amount of money.
Thousands of dollars. Like probably five or six
thousand dollars.
I don't know how to react.
It's so much money.
It's super overwhelming.
The more money the more taxes.
I wish there
was more I could say. I really wish
there was. Some of you guys are
so generous that I don't even know what to say.
Let me restart this.
You're just telling him to stop because you're going to blow it at the casino
anyways.
So this one is in heats. I'm in direct competition with
other people. But you guys are
incredible. Thank you so much.
Fucking incredible.
I gotta string something together here.
No!
I had it. That's ten songs in
one minute I know.
That's the nature of Tony Hawk though. You gotta restart.
You have a good string going.
I'll close it up there.
Oops.
Shit. Don't restart.
Stay on it.
It's ruined for like fifty thousand.
I think that'll be good.
Special.
Oof. Got it.
Ninety-three thousand.
That should be enough to give me a cross, right?
Ninety-five point three. I'll take it.
Ninety-five. Ninety-one.
Fifty-seven. I win.
Boomer becomes expert skater in an hour.
And I like to see myself
skater myself.
I gotta make this one better.
Over here.
This one has a lot of rails.
A lot of strings you can do in this one.
Going for a hundred thousand.
Ow.
Shit. I'm trying to get too funky with it.
I need like at least
I gotta string it together right now. Let's go.
Alright. Here we go.
Ninety-five. Ninety-six.
Thank you Haunty
for the community subs. Five
community subs. We're gonna have more
subs than viewers.
We actually do. Still in first place?
The math works out.
Last heat. I need a hundred thousand here.
Alright. End it. End it. End it. End it. End it.
Hop off. Let's try it again. String it up
around the bench.
I didn't get the dark slide. Come on.
I need a hundred thousand. Oh no.
I can get something right now.
Go. Go. Go. Go.
Fuck. That should still be
enough.
Thank you Tyga for the five community subs.
Hopefully Tyga it's enough for me
to stay in first place.
But much love to you. Thank you all
of you. I did it. Got the gold medal.
Congratulations.
You got New York City.
I was gonna turn up my quality but I realized it's just
the Dreamcast.
It is. Also
is from great canadian fuck club 50 dollars and nearly a thousand subs belong to great canadian
fuck club just one we gotta be kind of aware of that that's insane and another 50 dollars from
great canadian fuck club truly the greatest canadian uh jerma tell a funny joke when you
read this so it looks like i left a funny message oh whoops i'm sorry i blew it but
holy shit man thank you so much thanks for all the money thanks for all the support
responsible for so many subs already so many like at least there's like two or three dozen
people that are responsible for almost probably half the subs in this channel at this point
probably thank you guys new york city read that all the way around okay canada owns you now
no i can switch around the other side watch this one all right too far trying to just not
jump so far to the left is it impossible i guess maybe not all right this is my last retry
easy watch the turn okay but it's okay for the score at the moment t subway token the a
oh you got the million points on the hanger i think i got i mean i know i keep saying i got
a million but it might even be true where's the e i'm pretty sure it was school it's all
the way up there i reached that d this way hey look there we go it's not it though
where's the e e where's e no e too late i do have 12 000 dollars not yet let's get the
top points did they get a manual is it 125 oh shit
that would have been close it would have got like 90 000 right there
i can reach the commanding instinct to do dark slide yeah it's there
i gotta look at the tricks though because there are some other ones that are worth way more
points
well too big of a drop
in a case
skipped hey i'm not i'm not trying to go for uh the letters trying to get to 125
thousand points well apparently i stayed on somehow
that's good
big drop again
big drop again speaking of big drops uh juno another 10 community subs from juno
10 community subs pushing well beyond i believe 40 or 50 at this point thank you so much
big frame drop oh did we get a did we let me see one oh we did damn
10k drop 10k drop on uh
uh thousand dropped on frames 10 you know i'm trying to stay here but i can't i can't talk
play i need like 5000 more points hold on oh boy this is not good to get it thank god no did
i not get it how much was it 50 oh shit what was it hold on did i get it it's 150 oh fuck
that's why i slowed down now let me let me start whatever i couldn't really do much after
that how the fuck did i get that one oh there it is
dark slide do it again dark slide do it again two dark slides do it
we have five more community subs came in right now hold on let's get to 150
you might as well
no come on i need like i need somebody sneeze on my board fucking jesus don't fall here
we have even more community subs 10 more from juno thank you juno for the 10 community subs
10 10 10 and then and and then never trust nanners with five community subs thank you
and then an anonymous anonymous sub gift my goodness anonymous thank you guys again
for your insane contributions let me see we got personalized love letters for everyone in chat
so what's worth the most secret tape is the most 50 50 joey sculpture subway tokens all right
let's let's try to get skate okay he's right here it's gonna jump across i didn't get it
okay anymore any more letters up here that we can see maybe that's a letter or is that money
well i fucked that up 100 bucks you want to play crazy taxi because it was
that's a great game let me just see let me just find where the other letter is
it's t's over here is that here is e that's e t okay i got k earlier and where did i get it
that's the worst part about Tony Hawk is you'll you'll get them all and then forget where the
like it was e last time now it's uh it's right there come on go down down down down down down
i'm not gonna get it let's try one more time i should be i don't i don't want to i'm not
gonna grind the rail here i'm gonna grind this one just jump that brings us over here it brings
to t and e is over here then the other one's right in the excellent there it is
hey go this way other direction i gotta get some speed it's not gonna happen
maybe how how did i get this last time what angle did i come over from i get that last time is there
like a better way i can come across and jump off is this technically not it's not a ramp
do it again shit i got too focused on that combo i'll get it later
i gotta pee too i drank i drank like a full Macaulay Culkin soda from what's it home alone
the kid that pisses the bed all the time that's gonna be me i'm gonna piss my scream
yeah i gotta pee too i have to pee too much that i can't play
all right i'm gonna pee my scream that should be a thousand bucks sounds pretty good the
rest of this uh i wonder if i can get anything else subway tokens on the bridge never mind
and then can i look at the no i can't i guess i could just end the run right
i have p time these are right next to each other oh i'll try to get token why the hell not
ollie the hydrants well we'll do that in just a moment i gotta pee so bad
right back see you all right what are we going for spend some cash i'm gonna say let's go to
tricks let's get some new stuff in here i'm feeling it eleven thousand nine hundred dollars
in community subs trap trick rocket air definitely have a air walk burial what about slip tricks
hold on i do this one all the time eggplant let's go this is a lot of money we're gonna
do eggplant nose pick it's not good to me i don't have money for a special
i already have a grind special what about the other ones i haven't even tried to
really do them it's a 540 flip x but any of these triple kickflip holy god i think that's
good for now let's go to the skate shop do i have enough money for a board weight 15 medium
lisa cap injury what am i scrolling through here so these are all mockable boards so that's a
photo of a bird's ass okay pony did i just kind of have a go 18 team deck birdhouse team seal
this has more weight to it silhouette foot new wave brace powell logo medium shorties monster
yes sponsors use the old man board is that the old man board this is another competition
200 000 i got the new tricks let's try it there's a rocket you just kind of hop off
and spin around huh holy shit that's awkward oops i'm not getting enough height anymore
i need more air and ollie to do stuff like that 200 000 this song sucks what what song is
it i haven't really been paying attention to it i think you can you do this you can like spin
around this thing like crazy if you're going fast enough i need 100 000 more points right now
i'm gonna get it i got at least one of them though is that pop a roach didn't they only make
like two songs 200 000 let's go oh do it oh do it shit i gotta get back around let's go i need
100 000 more points get it back up top there that's a good spring shit all right don't get
too fancy just get it dropping around just do it it's only five it's actually a lot
oh jeremy what are you thinking
in front of me that's actually a good place to go i would say so i need more ollie speed all right
just get the 20 000 points i don't have enough stats to do the things that i'm trying to do here
i'm just trying to do too much and i don't have the stats to do it so i don't know why
i'm doing it do it again ow get the slim gym guy that's uh dave mirror isn't it dave
mirror that's not a 20 heart bad start not very good but it's okay i'm gonna keep it
what happened to my speed i'm not hitting this right there it is come on tilted no gamer fatigue
tilted would mean i'm mad gamer fatigue is i just my my hands are not translating to my brain
all right last free try and that's it love letter for arms two why am i not hitting that
right all right fucking let's just go power stone stall the juice it really did that was
literally one of the most absurdly difficult things that i've had to do in like the last
couple weeks i'm addicted i can't help it what is going on right now it's my it's the new moves
i did they're they're too slow that ollie north is like it takes an extra couple seconds to do
i need to just do kickflips all right i can get 200 from this all right let's go oh fuck
i might have to take a break i think it's time i think we're getting there
i need to go like eat food or something my brain is so fucking mushed right now
yeah why is my brain such a mush i don't understand i think i'm just getting fucking old guys is it
happening am i actually like 34 years old and getting just old i think it's happening
grab it midlife crisis on stream no i'm just like just like my brain is just tired
weird maybe if i get string let's see if i can get this
try again i can do it this game is almost as old as you are it's very old game it's very very very
good no not enough ollie what's this can i'll take it oops a daisy i get to restart it
i don't have speed but i can just do this damn it almost there let me get one more good
string where where where where benches benches benches no no no no no no god damn it still
possible no it's not i'm watching my brother do this eventually what's my favorite skating
game but this one this is definitely my favorite skating game of all time it's ollie north is
just fucking me so bad right now it really is whoa manual there whoops a daisy
yeah i know nhl 2003 is your favorite this is a good game too
like tony hawke three i've come to the determination that there's no way i'm
going to be able to do any of these strings without more ollie and more air because that's
what's actually the problem that is the actual problem but tony hawke pro skater 3
was very good too it was really good actually
i like the stages in this better than i do in three though
yeah just end i'm gonna go to the next level oh no let me uh
i need more points should i have some more 25 000 dollars let me go back to school can you
beat darth maul i think you yeah i think you actually can i need skate skate bells all passes
this way
this way there's a couple things i think a little bell there's three okay now this is the
there's another bell down here i think there's a bell up top left it's pretty certain i'm not
over here i'm gonna get up top i can hear it
i can hear you but i don't know where you are where is it i can hear it
i just heard them right okay i hear it right here
i take it not over there where are you i just heard it again there's one down there but that's
not the one i'm hearing oh it's not this one it's oh it's right there whoa why was i hearing
these bells i'm hearing the bells all the way back there shit okay well i know where they are
let's go it's just ambient noise i'm like where are the bells i hear them they're somewhere
over here speaking of bells it's like freaking me out i already got it
first of all take the other headphone out because i can't breathe with the two headphones in
all right let's go after this i'm gonna i'm gonna end the stream i think i think i'm like
getting a migraine i think a migraine is coming on i'm feeling it like in my face
sometimes it happens like i i can feel a migraine coming on here
irritating but not yet let's go get these down here
okay they call them oras it's called an aura when you just know you're gonna get a migraine
and then you get a migraine it's really fucking weird all right where is this last
bell it's uh i got the two that are down here
there's only one more like this way right
i got that one over there that wall here i think right
five bells do i have enough to do anything else
yeah sometimes uh the weirdest thing that's ever happened to me with a migraine
is like sometimes an hour or two before i get a migraine i will get like splotching vision
almost like i'm people when i look at them they look like they're a Picasso painting
and that's not really happening right now but i'm getting like i don't know i feel like it
i feel like it might start happening here soon i get that with every migraine it's really weird
it's called allison wonderland syndrome that's not happening right now i just have that like
kind of heavy back of the head feeling what was that what else was here let me see i got
that gamer nerd neck going a hangover i haven't had any alcohol i didn't drink today didn't drink
yesterday this is a coke i'm drinking a coke coke but yeah i'm gonna call it here
that's probably the smart thing to do for my health i thought it was gamer fatigue i wasn't
the last like 45 minutes or so i i really thought it was gamer fatigue it's probably
migraine yeah i gotta save it save the career it's already saved i think right
but you will see me again uh i'm going to and i'm not going to scream tomorrow
so the next time you guys see me you'll see me on monday and we will probably do
do the resident evil 2 or like sonic adventure or something but yeah sorry i'm kind of
a little off the last like hour or so probably gonna have a headache in about 30 minutes
oh somebody clip it somebody clip it i did it right i said it let's see it it happened
i mean it's completely different circumstances but it happened i said i'm off today didn't i
i did different circumstances completely but still i still said it let me see it definitely
so stupid how i i clearly was grinding that rail no i didn't say that i just it's so unbearable
okay no i didn't say that one is it the controls are fucking dumb like i try i pressed the button
it didn't do anything like just get it just doesn't really hold up i don't i didn't say it
oh my fucking god this is so stupid how i i clearly was growing is this it
but yeah sorry i'm kind of a little off the last like hour or so music really is so fucking
loud i said it later on than that oh that's all right but yeah thanks a lot for watching
guys um yeah i usually like to go for at least six or seven hours but i'm gonna get
out of here i'm gonna go preemptively take some ibuprofen uh there was an absolute shitload of
community subs which shocks me even i can't fucking believe it that there are people that
want to give me that much money thank you so much everybody it's incredibly overwhelming and
i'm honored and forever fucking grateful i hope you guys are taking care of yourselves too
don't just worry about me worry about youtube thank you so much
and we'll do the bits from earlier because i don't think this i don't think there's very many
in the line up here i'll see you guys on monday you got me running in a cyclone what a great
game though i love tony hawke so earlier we had let's go to the outro here you playing
this on the dreamcast oh yeah yeah this is on i have the hardware it's all on dreamcast
plays well looks well smells well all right let's get to the bits which are down here
the website all right so thank you too it's time for slime thank you so much for the five
dollars there's an image here that's awesome hey come on i showed you by 10 percent of a
million 126 000 right for a point system that's not a gnome but thank you it's time for slime
thank you for the 10 dollars it's time for slime smooth smooth smooth thank you
freudian weapon thanks to the five dollars always prioritize your health man it's important
no i do i do i'm not i can't just i can't force myself to stream or talk or it's kind
of very just creeping up on me that something was off up here in the skull everyone i told you
i was like itchy i don't i think that was just like i don't know that was weird it was like my
back yeah i don't know weird very strange and that was like an hour and a half ago so it
wasn't gamer fatigue but uh thank you for the concern and i yeah i'm i'm absolutely going to
prioritize my health and that's why we're ending early because i'm trying to escape this
potential uh future issue for sure but thank you thank you uh soft for the 10 bucks soft 33
and 33 community subs as well hey germa sorry i've been too busy with work to watch the streams
lately i've been wanting to give back to this awesome community and you for a while
thanks for the years of laughs thank you yeah i get fairly stuck and overwhelmed sometimes
when a huge amount of money comes in and it happened it's happened this this is kind of the
third stream in a row of monumental money and support and i i'm sorry i don't i don't necessarily
sometimes i don't take it very well not necessarily take it well but sometimes it's
hard for me to um mentally accept it sometimes and i know some people would just
say well whatever you're gonna you're gonna be upset about somebody giving you money no it's not
it's not that it's just it's it's a lot of support and a lot of money from people
and sometimes it can be i i just want to make sure that it's worth it's worth it it can be
very very um i'm trying the word i'm looking for is it's not it's not a bad thing but when
i look at some of these numbers and i and i see some of the amount of money that people
give and the amounts of subscribers that are on the channel it's kind of light kind of goes
into my eyes and it's like holy shit what the fuck this is fucking crazy and it happened very
very quickly i do appreciate it it's it's a huge deal the hyper growth monetarily on this
channel over the last two months three months is just it's wild and sometimes i just don't
kind of don't know what to say but i i'm i'm incredibly honored and happy that people
think this is a good community to be a part of and to spend that much money on
thank you so much please excuse my sometimes shocked demeanor when it happens but thank
you novi for the three dollars and 33 cents road to 10 000 subs i can't even imagine i
can't even comprehend that number so you don't have to say anything just
yeah but also keep in mind sometimes when uh the string of the last few streams when thousands
thousands of dollars come in i i mean i don't want somebody to think that i'm just glazing
over the donation but it it's it's it's difficult because i don't want people to
think that like oh you don't have to say anything whatever here's just here's like five
grand it's like wow so i want to address it and but sometimes i kind of lose it a little bit
but it means a lot thank you all of you thank you uh jess homeboy for the one dollar tony
hawk status in 2003 i was requested to meet with warner brothers about doing a film
about it's called skate jam so there was going to be a tony hawk space jam that would have
been ridiculous that would have been so good probably not though it would have been kind of
i don't even know how good that could have been this potential there but i'm not sure
where the ceiling is for that potential thank you dork cube for the one dollar another
game for you to look into is thug pro it's a modded version of tony hawk underground 2
that has a handful of maps from every game in the series and an awesome character creator
and online is fun i forget just how many tony hawk games there are there's a lot of
tony hawk games but that's cool tony hawk's underground 2 was it playstation 3
you just started watching and i mean yeah i'm sorry for the end i was gonna go for like
another couple hours but something in my i'm getting a like a little bit of of a
headache-y feeling so i kind of gonna go relax but sorry for the five hour stream
i like to go for at least six to seven nowadays uh but thank you dork you began
for the one dollar you better play sonic adventure in its entirety including big the cat missions
i'm not sure i'll get that far but maybe thank you peter for the five dollars actually beat
valgas on stream i went kicking and screaming but i did it peter thank you 15 dolls from
peter beat valgas on stream that was me uh thank you tar alecran for the two bucks hey
germa now that we've got the dreamcast out is there any date on if when you're going to
play shinmu i'm super excited for that stream and i don't want to miss it yeah i actually have
shinmu now on pc so it'll be a little bit more higher fidelity you can probably expect
the shinmu stuff to happen i would assume i'll probably start shinmu one after
resident evil 2 and resident evil 2 will probably only take one stream
because from what i've gathered it's only about a seven to eight hour game to do
there's like two campaigns right so at least for one of those campaigns bring back monster rancher
but shinmu will happen eventually i own them all i own both of them uh thank you anon a list
for the one dollar hey germa it's the guy who runs the exotic animal rescue here i've been
watching a long time and i want to say your streams always lighten the mood when we get in
some real injured animals oh also now have a twitch stream of 24 7 rescues right now it's
baby ducks thanks again for the always entertaining stream that's awesome baby ducks 24 7 is it your
channel is just on your stream your channel or is a different stream uh i don't have a link here
is it just your anon a list is it just that channel that sounds pretty fucking cool but
thank you for the one dollar you still here maybe you can give a link people i'm sure people
will be interested hey smelly boy thanks for the one dollar also if somebody who works at
a bowling alley they stay alive through leagues and kids birthday parties thank you smelly boy
again for the one dollar just heard the news are we gonna have to start paying six dollars
instead of two to get our bits read no how did six dollars come about six dollars
well it was three who's spreading the six dollar lie that's not true thank you door cube
for the one dollar not only did domino's pioneer the stuffed crust this is how they
advertised it domino's did not really think this is the right thing for us to be doing
divana what do people think let them talk it's wrong isn't it but it feels so right
then it's a deal yes we eat our pizza the wrong way this is pizza introducing stuff crust
pizza from pizza that's not dominant that's don't that's pizza that wasn't there's pizza
hut thank you for the one dollar thank you for the one dollar again door cube
when i think of bad games the good bad games i always think of these dreamcast exclusives
you can tell the developers wanted to do so much but the system was holding them back
maybe a lot of these old games a lot of the developers are still making stuff you really
only had it's like a goldfish right when you're in a tiny little bowl you're a tiny
little goldfish you're yeah it is just the bowl you're in not necessarily i mean some
ai has come so far physics have come so far it's completely understandable but thank you
door cube thank you sly 161 for the two dollars hey germa missed the last few streams so i don't
know if it was asked but i highly recommend playing resident evil 2 i am i'm gonna stream
it uh potentially on monday you will probably see it on monday freudian weapon thanks for
the three dollars back in my day we had to walk 10 miles up a hill in the snow to play
bad games well it was uphill but it wasn't necessarily in the snow sometimes it was
snowing c4g thanks for the one dollar germa pride thank you i'm tired of all this dreamcast
slander yeah i've been trying to dial back the dreamcast just slander you know i'm i
power stone i did say i hate this game like three times no i didn't that's a lie i'm making
that up power stone i beat the game it was a lot of fun it was very challenging at the end
and it's a great game tony hawk 2 gamer headache fatigue one of the best games i
think i've ever played power stone is a great game it really is and then this power stone 2
which i'm just gonna i'm gonna order it and i'm gonna beat that on stream too
i don't know why i just said that binary man thanks for the one dollar and the youtube link
of thank you thank you dork cube for the one dollar i missed most of last night's streams
so maybe somebody already brought this up uh the floygan brothers had 12 pieces of on disc
oh my god somebody didn't mention the dlc but not that much
not all the dlc could be released before the dreamcast discontinuation so the developers
eventually released a vmu save file with all the dlc unlocked that's insane but thank you
for that tidbit of information i did not know that second part uh savs guy thanks for
the one dollar pew pew appreciate it hole of one zombie thanks for the one dollar gave a
gift sub yesterday but it didn't show on stream twitch charged me so i hope it went
through i hope so too because that's really annoying some guy nine thanks for the five
dollars i am back and you know what that means this meme video uh is wondering why you bought
toy commander hi you're being sent this video because someone wants to know what the fuck you
were thinking what the fuck was going through your head what did you think was gonna happen
it's just that's a it's just a version of i love how it's someone's sending you this video
don't be sending you this video what were you thinking man well uh not very much apparently
thank you divas for the two dollars timmy tim tim for the one dollar you know what time it
is i don't know what time is it oh of course it is can i drive there what time is it it's
three o'clock oh no i'm late where are you going to the dentist can i drive you there sure that
will help do you have a toothache yes and it's very bad i'm sorry to hear that i've had it for
weeks and this is the first time that i could get in my dentist is always so busy i guess
that's a good thing it means a lot of people like him can i thank you for the english
lesson timmy tim tim two dollars from something or other thanks for the two bucks yo germs i
was gonna tip yesterday but fell asleep here's my rent money take care of yourself first thank you
for the two bucks but thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank
you yeah i definitely have a headache because that last thank you i felt that like in the back of
my head yep no this is probably a good idea to tone it down tonight uh alec thank you
for the one dollar alec they say hello sir thank you and only a couple more we had right
now we had dr stein gave 15 dollars thank you so much dr stein put all this money to good use
germo we all love your streams and every ounce of content you produce keep it coming because
we're ready for it thank you thank you that means a lot that's fucking incredibly nice
thing to say about somebody and i can't wait to put forth some more stuff thank you void
space thanks for the one dollar hey germo really appreciate everything you do i'm so proud
to watch you grow from mediocre tf2 videos to almost almost watchable streaming content
real talk you deserve everything you've gotten we love you bunches thank you
almost watchable streaming content freudian weapon thanks for the one dollar how about sonic
adventure 2 i don't know i don't know let's do one first before anything else
and then gondor lane for a dollar hey germo i love you as always i'm a big financial stick
right now with college eating my money but i still want to support you somehow also i know
you have a huge backlog but as always i advocate for you to try out sam and max
you've been recommended enough so it needs no explaining uh it'd be it'd be so happy i'd be
so happy if you do a playthrough of my favorite comedy point and quick series on a semi-related
note here's well jimmy where's this big score that's gonna change everything where's all the
money that's gonna save our dear tiny timmy yes daddy where the fuck is it oh it's hopeless
the doctors say his Tourette syndrome will kill him if they don't operate no love jimmy
what is this oh this is from sam and max and they were okay they were rats i get it i get it
keep it on the uh keep it on the docket it looks interesting dork cube thanks for the one
dollar meant to say that pizza hut pioneered the stuff crust i'm on your side of the
dominos versus pizza hut argument i wouldn't call it an argument ten dollars from demis demis thanks
to the 10 bucks ever thought about playing war of the monsters i don't even i don't know what
that is more of the monsters is a fighting game playstation 2 this looks kind of crazy
it's like a mech kind of fighting game that's interesting well i do have a ps2 so
i was planning on doing another playstation 2 amazon run
because there are a handful of more recommendations that are on the console that i haven't done that
people think are really great and i'd love to give them a try but thank you for the suggestion
i will definitely put it on the list and then finally here thank you tingy for the two bucks
in a couple months my best friend might come visit me and we plan on hanging out and
drinking but this will be my first time consuming alcohol since you were since you
drink alcohol uh what's your best advice for first time drinking go slow go slow a lot of
people do this thing when they first start drinking where they want to look like they
can handle it to a point where fault you know no i'm good i'm good i'm good you want
to take a shot yeah yeah yeah and you overdo it so nobody no one's gonna be like no one's
gonna care if you have like two you know what i mean so you don't worry about what somebody
might think and especially in the chat people are saying it already uh every pretty much every
one drink you consume you want to drink like a glass of water well maybe every every two drinks
if you let's say you go into a bar after you've had two drinks order the third one
and just be like hey can i get a water they'll just it's free they just they
and drink the water now you don't have to like suck down water every 10 minutes because
i mean that's not good for you anyways but you really look into maybe like every two or three
drinks make sure you have a water if you're at the bar and if you're not at the bar then just
take it slow you still drink water and yeah and self-control too you just want to make
sure you don't go too overboard but again that feeds back into the first thing that i said
which is you don't you don't have to impress anybody just take it slow and then finally clue
the sniper for one dollar and shinoda for one dollar hey germ i thought about playing
resident evil 4 also raid joel he's crying nobody's crying let me put the credits on
here though thank you everybody for all the subs you guys are too much thank you everybody
markey comes in with five dollars thank you markey raid the baby ducks
so should i just raid the baby ducks i mean the baby ducks let me see what if one of the
ducks just looked over and was like oh oh thank you thank you so much germa for the raid
germa raid and they all started saying it oh wow they really are just like sleeping they're
sleeping we don't want to wake them up why would i raid the ducks if only there was a
the ducks all right let's go it's time to raid the 24 7 baby duck animal stream
duck raid oh joel oh what about joel all right how about this everybody go right now to the baby
duck stream yeah i should raid joel everybody just go click on that baby duck stream and
give them those ducks some support and then we'll actually raid joel i forgot like joel
is like streaming right now send the ducks to joel tell joel the baby ducks are more important
joel's stream is ending no it's not is it let's see no he's playing getting over it
joel said raid the ducks instead no he didn't did you know this game is shit
it
it is fuck that game i agree
all right let's go raid joel i have we got it the ducks are asleep we don't want to wake the
ducks you can choose if you want to go to the duck stream you can go for it right now
but let's raid uh let's raid joel because they get the name right i do queue up go give him
some support because getting over it is literally just just a horrible really fun game but my god
is it tough let's go and say uh say hello wait wait what what i'm getting challenged to what
we'll see about that tell what tell what it's not the sniffing mustard powder or uh uh uh
we have to start getting over it at the same time of their gamer chair okay
i don't want to do that i'm not talking about those like why do i have to listen at the worst
possible times what's the he wants to do it at the same time a gamer off i could even get
30 of the way through this game big sniffs loser has to sniff mustard powder or is he
hosting i don't get it i'm about to rate i'm about to rate he can't hear me all right i'll
be in the chat i'll see you guys on monday much love to you okay well he better i will see he
better uh accept the challenge or else did it go through listen he he he will not oh there's
am i still streaming okay listen listen people come here from germany