What's up? Oh, I thought I was ready to talk wasn't apparently apparently wasn't ready to talk
I best I guess not and I have to say let me let me re situate myself here. Let me put my seat down
Uh, let me put my seat up. Actually. I don't like that move this
I see it here. There we go. That's better
Uh, so I have to say
This is the first time for everything
And for the first time ever
ever
Since I started streaming regularly, I that's the hardest word to say in the english language, by the way
Regularly since I started streaming regularly
This is the first time i've ever streamed
on the first
Of multiple days that I tell you a stream could happen
Think about that. That's it. This is a huge milestone for us
Let's say I stream on sunday and I go. Oh, hey guys, you know what the next stream?
Maybe tuesday or tuesday or wednesday. I bet it's probably tuesday, but maybe wednesday tuesday or wednesday
It's never happened on the tuesday
It's always the last day of the range that I give you
And now for the first time ever it's it's the first one. It's the it's the first one and i'm early
No, i'm actually like 40 minutes over what I told you I was thinking about but look
You all know that what you do you thought the stream is gonna happen tomorrow
So like holy shit, he's streaming today. Oh nice first time ever. Oh, he's an hour late, but he does that shit every day
Anyways, right that you already know that
Hold on give me one second. I want to rearrange my desk and I don't want it to be loud
Show us the boy show us the boy
Yo, I will
I promise there will be at least one auto appearance before the stream ends
Not right now though. He's sleeping over here. He just came in and he's resting
He's buried his head. Whoa, that was gonna be a huge burp if I didn't have extreme skill to suppress that
He's on he buried his head under the covers and he's sleeping i'm not gonna wake him up for content
He can stay asleep when he's ready
And he's ready to view
We'll see him
Stop burping and talk look how many times you burp a day
You burp probably like six or seven hundred times a day
It's I think it's a little less than that. Still. It's like it's a lot
It's like probably like at least 50 or like 30
You okay?
You never burp. Yeah, right
You're the same person that says
Yeah, I I mean I i've fart sometimes but like not really like sometimes if I have like a big meal or
No, you're the you're the guy that like goes and hides downstairs turns the bathroom fan on turns the sink on
and farts
So I I got you. I know who you are
You're a hider or you're like you you're the other kind of person though. Correct me if i'm wrong here
Or you will go pretend to have a cigarette
to make sure
That like you don't have to fart around people
Yeah, i'll be right back. Just gonna go have a smoke real quick. I didn't know you were a smoker. Yes
Shitty fucking habit. Whatever and you go out there and just rip ass outside
And then you come back and you you don't want people to know that you're doing that
You'd rather have people think you were smoking cigarettes
And like fart in their presence
Because that's me like that. I'm describing me
If we were in a big like area big crowded place and I had nowhere to go
And I had to like I had to rip ass really really badly
I would rather pretend that the group of people know I smoked cigarettes than like fart in their presence
And I know there's a lot of you like me
Or go take like a phone call
All right, fuck. I I I lean my head over and go
I got a call. I think it's my mother
I'll walk outside. I haven't all right enough stalling. Let's go
We're going to continue. Mr. Satan's wrestling empire
If you didn't catch the stream yesterday
Off to a great start during my nice. I'd like to hear that
If you didn't get straight yesterday wrestling empire, it's fucking one of the best games
I played in the last couple of years. I guarantee that's not a joke
I do want to make something really clear
You know time it is you have any idea what time it is?
it's
This time
Because here's the game
Mr satan continues what how much money do I make three dollars a week? That's what I wanted
That's what I wanted it to start and I fucked it all up
I thought that was the beginning of the song but it was the end of the song
Whatever
You get the idea
And you know the more like I hit the more that I listen to this song
So i've heard it like 60 or 70 times in the last 24 hours
I like the song. This is a good song
I want to put this on like a playlist now. This song is fucking pretty. This is an awesome song
All right, let's go
Uh, I had nothing scheduled today so we can
What do I need to do am I under any contractual obligations to do anything
No, right
No contract bullshit that I have to do by a certain date
My agility sucks. Should I do agility?
Look in the top right
Oh, no. Okay. Good. Good. Good. That's good to know
I'm gonna do agility because I feel like it's gonna be like get your agility to 80 more strength. Um, yeah
I lost skill. I lost skill. That's bad
I got a day off. It's fine. All right
Today's the day of rest
No creative control is bad. I know I completely fucked over everything but whatever I look I could just
I can just beat the boss up until I get to leave
You don't keep mr. Satan under a contract if he doesn't want to be on it. All right
I thought that was the joker
So I think that's supposed to be donk the clown
Okay
In nine weeks, you might be able to renegotiate. All right, let's we'll do that then
Also, by the way, if you didn't see yesterday's stream
You're in for a real fucking treat because this is seriously i'm not i'm almost swearing for no reason, right?
There was no reason me to say the f-word there
Like I just deliberately put the f-word in there. I don't know why like I was like, oh, yeah, it's gonna sound cool
No, i'm not gonna do that anymore
Okay. I think this is the charity
event
right
This is for charity for something. What was that?
He just like hit his head on the sign
What's that sound?
vulture with thomas son
and mr. Satan
with motorola champ
I can't walk. There we go
Is this for what's this for?
And this is my oh
Did you come up with a weight?
Ultra die out here much more than just another wrestler left
Ow
This is a special charity event that would raise money for good causes around the world were they mad that I was turned around
Those attendants have already donated bit by bit showing up. So give yourselves a big round of applause. Get away from me put that down
And we hope you'll be joined by many more watching at home who can also pledge their donation
Is this a hardcore match?
Enough talking vulture. Let's give the world what they want. Let me guess a big match for a big donation
Wait, why does the ref have a bomb?
All right, let's go
The map why is it on fire?
Holy shit. Oh, I got him with it. I got him. I got him
So this is just a singles match for charity. All right. Well that was
I'm fine. All right. How much help do I have? All right, let's kick this guy's ass
It's funny every time i'm sorry
It's one of those games where it's funny every fucking time
Can I just count them out? All right, let's do some wrestling
Why did the ref have a bomb? I don't I don't that's the part. I don't understand
Did he throw that into the audience?
I love how unhinged the referees are as well as the players. All right
typically you want your referee to be somebody that's
collected calm
Tries to get order holds the court. Whatever
This guy is just as fucked up as everybody else
Where is he going?
He's not paying attention. I got him. Oh, it's it's
That's another thing these guys do they just get on the top rope the people that aren't even supposed to be in here
Like get the fuck out of here
You fucking little worm
All right, i'm gonna drop this guy in his head big ddt grab him by his jowls and shake him
All right, it's time let's go this is it that's a special move
It's over
I hear those crunches
Got out
That's the match is not over yet. Get out get out here. I didn't win yet
I know we both thought it was a guarantee, but it didn't happen
That's it something broke over on stage left. I don't know what it was
What broke did you hear that?
Who's this?
Wait, who's that lady?
You see this person out here. Who's this person?
I'm so confused
Yeah, what ellie knots? What are you doing? Who is this? He couldn't even get out of the ring
Is a commentator I thought this was a fan. Oh my god, i'm gonna get counted out. It is a fan. Oh no, it's not oops
All right, big move to end it. Here we go. That's not what I wanted, but it's okay. That's a pin got it one
Two this guy is
Stop booing
God damn it. This is budget sting. I think
There's a lot of licensed kind of characters that are in the game in quotes
All right, I didn't want it. Where's my manager and how come he's not helping me?
They've renamed and sort of changed slightly a lot of people that look like characters
So we just saw doink the clown. I'm that's supposed to be doink the clown
Get out. Jesus. This guy's resilient
Get out free. There it is. All right
This guy refuses to die. Yeah, wait, here comes ellie knots
What do you want? What do you want? Why are you looking at me? Get away from me?
That was weird. Somebody said are you gonna kill any more friends today?
I did not kill schmo. Okay, the last match that me and schmo had I did
Beat him over and over again in the head with a bat and like a a garbage can lid
And he died two days later
But it said he died of natural
Causes it didn't say he suffered any injuries. That's not my I didn't do that
It said natural causes
a natural
bat to the head
The bat the bat was made out of wood. Yeah. Okay. Here we go. Hold on. So you had fun out there. Mr
Satan well, you made quite a mess of the arena if you ever want to book this venue again
You better pay two hundred dollars towards the damages
What damages?
Oh because I threw the bomb but the ref had it in his hand. I just took it from him and threw
And look, here's the thing. I
Listen, this is this is where you get weird
Legally speaking, right? So who's real whose whose fault was it referee brings bomb into the ring?
I grab bomb throw bomb guy picks bomb up on ground bomb blows up in his hand
So what happened like the referee didn't detonate it. I didn't that he picked it up and blew up in his hand
That's not my fault
Like that's like collectively we should all have to split the bill in my opinion
At least me and the ref the ref should the ref brought it in the ring
I'm just trying to fucking get rid of the damn thing
Referee brought it into the ring and he's just holding it. I took it out of his hand and I fucking whipped it
I was like get this out of here
And then he picked it up because he wanted to use it and it blew up
That's I I I accept 45 percent of the bill there. Not all of it
I think the referee made out really really well and who brought it by the way
Anyone that can beat vulture deserves to be at hollywood as well
Wait one we feel you'd be a valuable addition to the cast and we'd like to make you a star with this deal
Oh shit, this is way better than my contract now. This is the guy next to me. That's the owner
Okay, when I sign the contract throw him out the window
You know what I mean? Like let's go i'll sign this right now
Only paid for winning matches. That's fine. I win every match. This is this is a good contract
I want longer
I want at least 12 weeks
But that's 3400 a week. This guy's paying me
300 a week
And I I have no control over anything that I ever do
But do you think right now he's side-eyeing me?
It's like almost like i'm kind of I want to give him like a telepathic text
With my eyes saying like mother fucker
I want five grand a week when we go in the car and I decide if i'm gonna do this or not
I'll do 12 weeks. Let's go. Yeah, fuck this guy
Movie shoots don't tend to last that long. We prefer to keep this short
Oh
Damn it
All right. All right. All right. I'll do six weeks. Okay. All right
All right
We'll book you against vulture straight away to reignite you a few ways. This must be scripted
Listen mr. Satan a lot has changed since we first signed you to 3400 a week 30 seconds ago
A lot has changed. We all have to make sacrifices to stay afloat. So how would you feel about taking a pay cut?
Excuse me. I just we haven't even left the office yet
We have not i haven't even gone to the bathroom since I signed that contract
No, you know, excuse me pay me what we agreed. Fuck that
What?
If you insist on being a financial drain i'm gonna have to cut you off
Did I get fired what am I in?
I'm in wrestling school
What just happened?
Like I I what happened what?
You can't do that
Now i'm back in wrestling school
um
Okay. Now I know who my biggest enemies in the world are
I was part of that. Um, what was I didn't know what the name of my card was before
They treated me like shit they paid me nothing but that guy at least fought for me. No, don't touch the bomb. That's bait
Because they know that i'm gonna pay for everything
After I was just talking shit about it
Mr. Satan, shouldn't you be shooting a movie instead of doing something as lowly as wrestling?
Yeah, I would if I didn't um get like the rug pulled underneath me after I signed a contract
Stick to that nonsense because you don't belong in the ring with me. You know, that stings evidently
I'm a little out of touch. You're so far under my radar. You know who the hell you are
I'm like so sad. I can't even do the mr
Satan voice i'll make you famous tonight and you'll realize there is such a thing as bad publicity. Is he counting himself out?
I can't fucking believe that just happened. Did I even get any incentive payment for joining?
No, it was I left my organization joined a new one and they fired me within the first 10 seconds signing the contract
That's so sad
Because you didn't ask for an advance
Well, I didn't think I was gonna have to ask for an advance
Your contract died of natural causes that's a good one
That's actually good. That was a really good joke. I'm serious. That's perfect. I wish I said that
Okay, I keep hurting myself when I do these moves
Hey
It should we go off our injury on this guy take the green contract not the red one
All right. Let's put this guy out
Good night. See you later
How come there's no music?
You know, I was thinking about this last night
And it sort of almost adds to how funny the game is in a way
Because it's just he's just and it's also because i've been in wrestling school as a contract so there's no audience members
Every time I get signed within like a week something horrible happens and I lose my contract so there's no crowd noise
That's what you're missing right now
You're missing the like, whoa
But it actually kind of adds to like how awkward this is
Remember you're killing people. I've not killed anybody
Name me one person i've killed that I killed like in the ring. You know what I mean? It's nobody
Okay, that sounded bad, but I assure you he's fine. All right, give me a new contract
Mr. Satan has reached the limit of wrestling school's popularity
Yeah, I
What the I can't what am I supposed to do about this?
Can I get a contract? That's not a piece of shit
Smoke was a lawyer. He could have helped you
Smoke, okay. Those are you guys saying?
Oh, no, what did I do to smoke? Do you remember the the absolute double cross that smoke did to me?
Where he threw the match and like hugged the opposition after I lost
Ronald wiener feels great today and is in perfect health
Mr. Satan won 82 percent of his 17 matches
hardcore tag team versus blonde blunders team
I
I need to get uh, so
All right, let's go
Hardcore match, you know what that means. Let's do it. What's this guy? Remember this guy from the first career?
I am at let's say this is a hardcore match. All right, i'm going for this guy
Who's my partner?
Mr satan and vendetta
All right vendetta walk intimidatingly to the ring. Oh, we're already going
vegeta
Yeah, it is vegeta vegeta. Mr satan and vegeta
Oh my god
You don't challenge me to a hardcore match it
Okay
I want the I want to buy where's where's vegeta?
Where's vegeta?
Where's vegeta get out here vegeta. I need help
No, I don't want to take the desk
Can I borrow this?
it's a legal
Murder
All right, pit him. Let's get him vegeta. Hold on vegeta. I got an idea
Oh
Can we pin him I can't pin him out here why can't I pin him
This guy's not supposed to be in the ring. I think this guy's I just have to go to super saiyan for a minute there vegeta
No, no, that's like part of the uh, right when we like vegeta upstages me and we have a rivalry
and
Right. It's like we're both strong and there has to be a big rivalry between us
And then we fight a few times
Okay, um, all right vegeta come in here let me see pass that to me
Ask me that
Let me see that thing. I'm gonna use it on him. What did that guy do that for?
Why did he do that? That guy was just showing off at like a trampoline park. That wasn't even him trying to fight anybody
It's like this is murder. This is actual murder but like
What happened? What happened to him? He like hurt his back. What happened?
Okay, all right, okay, so we won
We didn't that's the win
Did we win
What's wrong
Okay into the ring
I'm fine
Why get up? What's wrong with me? Why can't I get up?
Um, he won't he's not coming back in the ring and I can't pin him out there
What am I supposed to do about this culture? I don't know what to do
Oh my god, this is horrible. Um, how do I get him back in the ring? Yeah. All right
Come here in the ring in the ring. How do I throw him in the ring? There we go. All right
Okay, just by the way, this is revenge from this is revenge from the my career
Okay, dude, you all saw that he he could have just easily had taken that fall right there and been fine. Just stay down
You're kidding me
Really? Do you see what the shape your friend is in right now?
I almost want to let this guy pin me because this is awful
Pick him up and just end it. All right, vegeta go for it. That's it
Yeah, all right. Let's this is let's go
Vegeta is upset that he was barely involved in that match
Mr satan has reached the limit of wrestling school's popularity. Yeah, I know
Blonde blunder severely injured his leg in that match and will be unable to wrestle for the next four weeks
Even then he may be a shadow of his former self. Oh boy
All order is upset that he was barely involved
Vegeta has turned face and will now be portrayed in a positive light
The year is now 2022 and mr satan has turned 26 years old
I have an 83 win rate
All right, give me give me some new shit
I'm I have to get out of the wrestling school
How many times do I have to embarrass this guy in a singles match before somebody signs me and I can go fight somebody?
Oh my god, that was funny
This guy's bringing a camera
This guy was this guy's bringing a camera to
I think you can use the roster to approach a company boss for a contract. I might have to try that
Wait benz is back with a uh
He's got a little he's got all right. Okay, you want to play? He's got a pep in his step now
He's been training. All right, fine. Okay, the way I was just running around right there
I had so much intent there. That was like a resident evil
Two speed run
Turn turn turn turn turn turn
I wouldn't stop if items. I was just I just had one goal in mind. All right, come on. Let's go
Oh, let's wrestle. I want to promise my hitch for the chair again
and
Duplex benz is coming to avenge blonde blunder watch me break his leg too. Holy shit. That was awesome. Do it again
Not that way
That was miscalculated by just a small amount. I think big roll up. Let's l and r at the singles menu
It'll change what you do
Yeah, I can simulate events right? I can skip events. I like playing though. This game's really fun
Like all right, so m dicky made this game, right?
like can we
I say this frequently. Yeah, maybe not that frequently but still
Can like can can like a venture capitalist?
Just get to give m dicky like fucking 60 million dollars
You know what I mean? And have him make like a have him get like a a team of people and
I don't know how many people worked on this game
But like this is awesome like imagine if m dicky had like fucking 40 million dollars
50 million dollars
I want that game. I want to see what that game is
Like why can't m dicky just get like 50 fucking million dollars to make a wrestling game? He probably doesn't want to yeah
I know and i'm bad. That's me saying. This is like oh imagine
The charm of having this be the way that it is sure
Well, I hope I really hope this makes him a decent amount of money
And I really hope that he did like does well people like it because like this shit needs to be supported
It really does. All right, let's end it
Get over here. Should I change my finishing move or is this sufficient?
He's been really good at supporting this game on the switch since it came out in january
There it is. Oh wait, that was a scream
Don't forget the chair that you hit me with to win the match
his face
Did I injure him? No, okay. He's fine. He's fine
But yeah, this is the kind of stuff that I love to play
Like I wish like more independent devs could just just be just total creative control and just get like a decent amount of money
To do whatever they want. We've taken each other to hell and back. Mr. Satan
I've had I've had enough of it
Why don't we bury the hatchet so that we can both get back to concentrating on our careers?
I don't know who this is. Is it bad that like i've beaten so many people
Like nearly to death in this wrestling arena that I they're all blended together. I don't know who that is
All right. Sure. Let's make peace. Why not? Maybe we'll end up working together sometime
I'm certainly had enough of working against you
All right, somebody said go to database
I it's a handicap match versus score of bends and canado
No one with money trusts creative people to make creative decisions that will turn them a profit rich people only care about getting richer
Well, that's why I meant like a venture capitalist just somebody or like an angel investor or something
They keep putting a bomb here. What are the rules?
What are the what's going on here? What are the rules?
Oh shit
Nope, but can they both be in the ring at the same time?
Oh, this should be easy then I just kicked this I just kicked his ass like an hour ago
Go go get a weapon reverse it got it now. Let's go for a snap
Oops
And look, there's also there's also the argument that could be made that like if this was changed, right?
like let's say that somebody like this got a team of like 20 people to like deliberate stuff to and
That he ended up being the lead and would it be the same game? Like would it be the actual same experience? I don't know
That's the multi versus four
Oh, come on quick head smash
Wallace victory incoming. Oh my god. I'm unbeatable. I'm gonna get out of wrestling school. I'm fighting like fucking jobbers
Like these are the guys that that wrestled 25 like no I have to get out of here
I'm like I need this is way above below me
These people are just training. They're just rookies
You wonder why i'm hurting everybody's because i'm not supposed to be here. I'm fucking injuring a bunch of
rookies
Oh, i'm going in from out here
This is like a phd going back to kindergarten
That would hurt so bad
But get it. I'm gonna get out of here. I need to go to the roster and like and approach somebody
And perfect perfect perfect go go go go
Oh, come on
Give them a chance
I just I shouldn't even be here. I'm unstoppable even on 2v1. Oh my god
They're trying like they're trying to get away from me. This is the shitty filler episode
Well, that's what I mean like, okay
Like hulk hogan used to come out and he would he would fight like like an hour before wrestlemania
it'd be like it'd be like hulk hogan versus
Steve anderson and it'd be like a guy and just a regular guy and it'd be a guy just to warm up hulk hogan
These are like the warm-up guys like and I shouldn't I really shouldn't be here. I'm gonna hurt him. I think I hope I don't
Yeah, they're called jobbers. I know that's what i'm saying. Like I feel like this is like i'm just against like the warm-up crew
Yet they still want to continue to fight
There's five minutes remaining. They're just taking constant punishment that guy I heard of rib break
Something broke
I need a more violent finisher
Maybe that'll help you're gonna tell you're not gonna test of strike. Mr. Staten. I'm sorry. That's not happening
I gotta get this guy out of the ring. He's a huge problem. Just get the fuck out of here
Oh my god, my arm
Wait, who's pinning who who's pinning who did I just get pinned?
What happened they sandwiched me they sandwiched me
What
I couldn't move. He had me stuffed in a fucking sandwich
too good
He used the other guy's lifeless body
To squish me together and the other guy was holding me back
I couldn't be my character couldn't even move
lost to the jobbers
Oh
Jeremy you suck just throw all connected internet devices into the ocean. No, I you saw how much I was kicking their ass the whole time
What the fuck somebody just give me a contract so I can get out of here
Oh, he's going to maple leaf grappling. We know a guy from there
Nice to meet you. Mr. Staten. We invited you here to discuss working for strong style wrestling
All right, you're not exactly a priority for us right now, but we consider bringing you in with this deal. Oh, come on
That's
Four weeks. Come on, dude
All right, you give me a fucking thousand dollars to not waste my goddamn time
You may have commanded that much in the past, but i'm afraid those days are behind you now
No, what you're referring to is a contract that I signed and they took away from me in five seconds. What the fuck
Is it because I just lost those two guys?
Is it because I just lost to the two jobbers? Is that why you saw that on tv? That's why there's an explanation there
They sandwiched me I got whatever
Welcome to strong style wrestling. Let's go
Of course your friend crucial kennedy is also welcome to join you on the same terms
I don't care about what crucial kennedy does have you ever heard of a wrestler called maddie mcfly from all american wrestling?
What's this? Well, I think we could do the gimmick better
So how would you like to be our version of him?
Oh wait, they they like changed me
Should I imitate maddie mcfly?
What did they do to me? They shaved my mustache
No, I don't want to imitate anybody i'm mr. Satan god damn it
Sorry, did it make it sound like you had a choice? We need you to be more like him. So make it happen
I'll have to be i've missed
What?
They changed my outfit
Hardcore match versus calvin whatever and I that
I've had to shave my mustache
And put a new costume on it's just for four weeks. Okay
all right now
Wait, is this is this for me to change like my identity or something?
Because like i'm the guy that killed like three people in the ring. So I shaved my mustache come back with new music
What is this new music?
You can't whoa
I'm not you're a long way from home. Mr. Satan. You should have stayed at wrestling school
You may have been a big fish in that small pond but strong style wrestling is too tough for a loser like you
This is my yard. These are my fans. Nobody carves out a successful career here without my blessing
That's strange because I recall
I recall signing my contract with russell haystacks and not you
Russell haystacks can't protect you once you step in this ring. So you better watch your attitude
And whatever you say
i'm coming for you
You want to see how much real animal I can be?
I don't belong here, huh? Calvin?
You don't think I belong in strong wrestling?
Oops my head
Get the fuck out of here. Oh
Let's go
You don't belong in here with me
I belong in here with you
That's something I have to do it's very important
I'm sorry
This is hardcore
Get that table in here. Let's go. Goodbye and now he's going through a table and i'm gonna end it get away from me
Midnight's over here trying to fight me. It wasn't even my fault that we fought
We were over there and I just kind of hit it's not what I wanted to do
All right, get him on there and we're gonna end it here get on the table
Uh, goodbye count it. No still in there. All right. Oh fuck. Uh, oh, he's got a mic
Uh, oh damn it. I missed
Well, he keeps kicking out
That's it and i'm game over. I got the respect of Calvin and Hobbes whatever this guy's name was
engineer gameplay
That encounter established. Mr. Satan as a face who has the support of the fans. What?
I got 600 bucks. I'm telling you they don't think i'm the old. Mr. Satan. I shaved my mustache
Literally being a guy with a crowbar brings the respect of the fans
Wrestling school have crowned vegeta as their new postgraduate champion nice
Listen, i'm, not sure the name. Mr. Satan captures the essence of your character
Oh, no, they're realizing that I have to change. How would you feel about being called something like?
Rio mist
Mist
Oh
30s is a corporate meddling
Oh, I don't want to be called real miss. I want to be called Mr. Satan
They'll all be chanting that name one day. Perhaps i'll give it to somebody more deserving. I got nothing scheduled. Let's do some uh training here
I changed my name
Mr. Satan forever
How's that for her name? You like that one?
Agility is so bad change him to hercule
More strength more
Matt shellman has renewed his contract with all-american wrestling
Me and jean has formed a new team
Blood brother has left strong style wrestling to pursue a career at weekend warriors
Bloody lee is sad
I'm sad
They're all they're all sad
All right, maple leaf grappling is becoming popular that guy left it
prematurely
Mr. Satan forever has been booked to face drew turnham in the last man standing match on the first week of march
All right, this is submission match versus calvin steam
We have a tv taping versus I don't know tv taping
A couple of tv tapings and then a pay-per-view
Oh shit. All right
They changed my music too
I kind of like that you look like mike meyers
I know I kind of do
calvin steam
Submission match
Pretty good to say. Hmm. Say it say it then. What are you gonna say? Say it. Oh, you didn't you brought a mike out
What the fuck?
Okay, well he's ready
Submission match that's my specialty
Didn't know if you knew that
Get up. What the fuck? I just did a move to him
Your specialty is murder and submission moves
No, that's not the move. I wanted to do i'm trying to do the super kick. What the fuck
I what?
Why don't they do that?
I just tried to do the super kick and they did did they change my moves?
Hold on a minute. Yeah, I guess I changed. I don't have the super kick anymore. They changed my moves. Are you serious?
I didn't have that before
I don't like this new character. I want to be mr. Satan forever
I got nerfed
All my moves that I was good with oh fuck
Rio mist sucks
Oh shit
Oh my god
I have to resort to just like violence. No, why am I attacking her?
Why was I aiming at her? All right, let's pull this together here
Yeah, they gave me just shitty default wrestling moves. None of my cool moves are here anymore and then do any damage
I have to just rely on my strength just rely on my strength striking moves small moves punches kicks
weapons
Yeah rely on the strength if they're gonna they're gonna take shit away from me do what I know I can do best
Do you think they can't take this away from me? You can't take it away from me. Yeah, go ahead fold me up. That's fine
Ow, I need to use my rage. I do
This is such a bad arc for mr
Satan get back in the ring get back in the ring. Don't get counted up. Come on. What are you doing?
What how did that miss?
That's impossible. I'm as big as the side of the ring. There's one
No, I counted that miss
Use your strength. Oh, I don't did I do this for money? I had to change my character change my moves
So I would stop beating up fucking rookies
They have to nerf me and take uh, yeah, you can't take it all away from me though
Oh, yeah, you're now, you know, now, you know my plan, you know, you can't take the striking away from me now. You're afraid
That's fine. Don't worry. I'd be afraid too if I had to hit these fucking punches in the face
really
I was on the ground for so long. Don't let him submit me
Sorry, i'm too big. All right. Now let's this is gonna hurt a lot hurt him
Yep, lean into it lean into it. Come on
Oh, i'm arching so far back
Wrench it wrench it is this health going down?
Submit
He didn't submit he will this time. You know why because it's time for the mr. Satan bear hug
Get up here here. You want me to change my voice i'm about to change yours permanently. That's not my move anymore
That's not my move anymore. That's not my move anymore. That's not my movie more that move sucks
They made my move a kneeling chin drop. Oh my god. How am I gonna make this guy submit?
Come on, pull it off
Oh my god, no
No
Come on get him. I don't know what move is gonna work on him. Look at his ankle
I have to get him by the head
No, he get back in here by the head. This is the way this is gonna work. Just pull it pull harder
Go. Oh my god. Why can't I get this guy?
What? I've been so nerfed for money. It wasn't worth it. No
All right, give me his leg again. Give me the legs. Let's go. You can't possibly take this much longer. You seriously can there it is
That was intense
Alvin steam status has not been affected. Mr. Satan status has not been affected
What they're trying to hold me down. That's really what's going on
Okay, my contract with strong style expires next week. This is the last appearance potentially
You're gonna resign me
Mr. Satan forever. What do you think of a new outfit for your wardrobe department created for you?
Here's a blue diaper
Sure, I knew you'd like it a change of image could just be what you need to stand out
They're trying to make me as generic as possible
roster, okay, so
Where's the owner who owns aaw this guy?
What do you want? Mr. Satan forever. This better be worth my time. I'd like to work with you
How do you see us working together?
well, uh
You really remind me of the mcdlt briefcase guy
so
I mean, I
Really got really gravitating towards you. Would you be my partner?
We don't even work for the same company. So I don't see that happening anytime soon
All right, who owns this company?
Who owns the company?
manager fool manager fool
No, no, no, you guys it's not not the same type of manager you the
Manager is the guy that just comes out with you to the ring not like manage me
I want to be in your company
It's either like let's be a tag team or you come out to the ring with me who owns aaw
owner he does oh
Russell haystacks this guy owns this company. What do you want? Mr. Satan?
It's better be worth my time
Can I like challenge him to a fight and just kick the ever-living shit out of him?
Sorry, I don't think of myself as a wrestler. Perhaps you should ask
All right, what about derrick switchoff federation online
weekend warriors
thomas son
matt dickie
All right. Let's see. What what's uh, where's wait, wait, wait, wait, wait maple leaf grappling. Where's the owner?
Heaven lee bobby is the owner of maple leaf grappling. What do you want? Mr. Satan? This better be worth it
Um, I want to work with you. How do you see us working together? Can you be my manager?
We don't even work for the same company. Oh god damn it
I'm not free yet. Okay. I see. I see. All right. This is my last week
As mr satan forever with different clothes on
Okay, here we go. It's just a singles match
my last match
And i'll be free
Moves, I don't think I can change them
Until i'm free
Anton apex
I just okay. I just tried I just tried to throw the mic at him and it missed by probably an inch
As you may have heard the news my contract with strong style wrestling expires next week
If rustle haystacks and I can't come to an agreement
This might very well be my last appearance in case that happens
I want to take this opportunity to express how much i've enjoyed wrestling for you
I've had a lot of ups and downs in this ring as well as behind the scenes, but I have no regrets
Anyway, i'm not out of here yet. There's one last ass to kick. So let's make it a memorable one. This guy right now is going like
This guy kills people in the ring, what does he mean?
Why does it have to be me that had to be on this roster tonight?
Mr. Satan just said he wanted to make it a memorable one
Wow, these are just throw dirt in my face death imminent
No, i'm not gonna kill this guy
No, i'm not gonna hurt you
I'm just gonna kill you real I did it wrong, but you know, i'm just i'm not gonna kill you
I'm gonna hurt you real bad
We have deleted 12 and a half minutes of footage of jared leto's joker
And he's never to be heard from again
Just use the strength. That's all I have to do
Can't even hurt me notice how they change my moves from being punches to kicks
Mm-hmm. I only have like one upper punch in the face. That's it
I thought that was a shining reference
Wait, that's not from suicide squad
Is that jack nicholson?
It is. Yeah, it is right. It's been both
That's from the dark knight
Is it?
No, it's not. Wait, who says that?
No, that's him. That was in the trailer
All right. This guy was how what a not very memorable final match for this studio for strong wrestling
Whatever it is. Yeah, what a shit ending to my career here. It's just like a regular match. Nothing crazy happens
You're thinking of this another scene. No, i'm not maybe I am
Make it memorable go after the announcers
Ah shit, this is not very memorable at all. I may as well throw up two by four at the announcer's head
Fine. Hey money mark smile. You're on gameboy camera
I'm just trying to push her off
How t-pose t-pose t-pose t-pose
No, knock him out reverse. I don't think anyone besides you likes this game. Oh
You know when somebody i'm sorry, dude, but like that's just so that was like a just incorrect statement
It's that and that I mean you might I don't know man. I think you might be the first person to say that
No, i'm
Everybody most people are I mean if you don't like it, whatever. That's cool. That doesn't bother me
I don't have to like the same things but holy shit. This is like my favorite game ever. What a not memorable match
Quick, I gotta make it memorable quick
Damn it
I improved considerably
We don't know how to like the same thing. That doesn't matter. All right, am I gonna get a contract?
King david has defeated air miles
I think that's mankind, right? But it's not
Okay, mr satan forever's contract for the strong style wrestling has expired
I'm going to meet with russell haystacks to discuss his future
Okay
I
That I want to see that
That's the coolest wrestler i've seen so far. I want to see that costume
A lot happened this week
Oh my mr satan forever has been booked to face abysmal in an 18 man countdown elimination match
I thought that was a typo
18 man in the same ring or is that oh is it like royal rumble your contract has expired mr satan
So we need to talk about your future. We're pleased with your progress
So we'd be happy to keep you on with this deal. This better be good. Okay. Oh
Wow. All right
All right. This is big. This is 20 grand right now. This is 1100 dollars a week. No clauses
I want creative control
Creative control
All right. We can't trust you with creative control only we know what's best for your career
There's no bullshit in there anymore. I can do whatever I want
Have you ever worked with a wrestler called alan gator here at strong style wrestling?
His contract is up for renewal soon. So we'd be interested to know if you have any feedback
I don't know who this person is
alan gator
We need to keep alan gator. He brings a lot to the wrestling
We'll do our best to keep him at strong style wrestling. He wrestles gators for god's sakes
Sorry to bother you. Mr satan, but i've been struggling with my finances. What is this alan gator?
Since we're such good friends. Do you think you can lend me 1300 dollars to get back on my feet?
Oh
Oh, no
All right
All right. Thanks. Mr satan. This will help a lot. I hope I can return the favor sometime you could
Oh and i'll be asking for it singles versus calvin steam
And then here's that 18 man countdown. All right, I gotta be ready. I hope i'm in shape for that
Oh, thanks. Mr. Green. Yeah
Oh, I can change my shit again, right?
Just exit and change
No, I can look i'm gonna embarrass this guy. You may have won last time. Mr satan, but one win doesn't mean anything in this business
No, it doesn't but like four do
In a row each time we have fought every time a bat's allowed. No, they're not. Hey, well look
I might have a new friend in alan gator
Alligator
What is that? What do you throw? That was weird?
Mike was on the ground. All right
Make it quick
Give us what we came for. Where's auto you'll see auto. I tell you I I you will see auto before this stream is over
I promise. I love the striking in this game
How did I miss going over the ropes? All right, this is it. There it is. There's my special move, which is awful
So we're gonna see what my back special is
That's way better short and sweet
I can't that move sucks
Mr satan fervous progress is being hindered by the limitations of strong style wrestling really
Okay, always the offer from the big dog I just signed 10 weeks. Yeah, that'll go by quick
Alan gator's profile has dropped considerably after being criticized by the press. What did he do?
What are these
Listen, mr satan forever. I've been keeping an eye on your progress and think some changes need to be made
I'm not convinced you'll ever be a champion
Which makes me wonder what you're doing here
Win a championship by the fourth week of march or we'll have to accept it's never going to happen
Well, give me a fucking title match then
Give me a title match
Where's this this dude joel harden? Give me a match. I heard you're looking for me. Mr satan
What do you want to talk about? I'd like to I want to challenge you to a fucking title match
Everybody wants a shot at my lightweight title. So get to the back of the line
All right. Well king what about king david? I heard you're looking for me. What do you want to talk about?
I challenge you to a match
Everybody wants a shot at my world title
Well, what the fuck
How about coder? What do you want tag team? I challenge you to a tag team championship match me
And alan gator, where is he? Where's alan gator?
I heard you're looking for me. Yep. I want let's I want to work with you. Let's be partners
I want to let you let's be let's work together
Wearing this together you and me
I think we'd make a formidable team. I can't wait to talk out to walk out there with you. Yep
Me and alan gator are gonna stick on the tag team title. All right. Well, this is the 18 man
Tag team what?
18 man tag team where's my music? What was it? There it is
Guess what? We can we don't have to change our name
Can't change this
Okay, we can at least do this
I want my big attack
Not that shit
Super kick give me that back
Running front attack. Let's put this back to super punch
Yeah, bingo
Jabs, I want I don't want a straight jab. I want I want the big one the hook
right hook
Right hook long jab
Okay
Let's give my let's get a better move here special knee drop. Look at how awful that is. That is a basic default move
We're going for something crazy. That sounds pretty good
How just how about just a straight up just powerbomb?
Oh alan gator, i'm sorry
I I mean i'll do whatever you want as long as you and I can be in the ring together
Excuse me as a fucking training dummy. I don't care
He's the comedy character in the anime as long as I can hang out with you. Mr. Satan
I could care less what you do to me
spear spine buster
How about just the tried and true? We give mr. Satan the stunner
I think so
I love the stunner new move. Okay, fine
It's a sling blade
Shoulder breaker. It's very painful
That was sick
Oh
Oh, that's awful. I like that one
All right. Oh look at they changed. Oh, look what they did
They changed everything
They gave such shitty moves to me. Yeah, give me these ones. That one's fine
Brainbuster. All right, that's fine
partner alan gator
Story friend alan gator real friend alan gator. All right, we got a real friend here. Okay, let's do it
I don't think I can change anything else
I can't change. No, they took they took my mustache forever. All right, this is the 18 man tag team
How do you have an 18 man tag team? We're about to find out. Oh my god. This is gonna be fucking mayhem
Wait, we have teams
What
And here's my team
Let's go
This is a war
This is gonna be insane. I don't even know what to do
There's too many people
Hugging
Hugging each other
Alan gator and I have joined forces to become even greater than the sum of our parts
And we brought all of our closest facebook friends because we don't know anybody else
I knew some of these people in high school
That's right, but our actions speak louder than words. So let's show these people what we're about
Let's go out wait, it's only only two people
How can you even tell who's on whose team wait that's not my team
Who's oh my god, that was somebody on my team
Wait, whose team am I on?
I'm so confused
Who's this guy
That's too many people
This is never gonna end
Okay, I don't who this I think it's this guy
Is it this person right here?
I don't know. I think it's this person. I don't know what could be wrong
This is fucking insane
Imagine seeing this shit
I have a special I already have a special
Um
This is like the cartoon shit that i've dreamed about
That's not my team my team is over here with alan gator, it's the only guy I recognize
Who's this lady on the top turnbuckle?
Where am I?
At least people are fighting
Who's fighting I tagged in gator I did
Somebody just fell out of the stands
I don't think that person was even here
Who's is is who's playing?
Am I supposed to be in here? I didn't tag in alan gator
No, oh shit. I'm not supposed to be in here
Don't worry. I'll take care of this you pin him alan gator
Who just got tagged in?
I just got sucked up. I just went down the toilet
Oh
Oh my god
Okay, I think
uh
Oh shit, everything is legal outside. Everything's legal outside. Who cares everything's legal
Fuck the ref
Okay, um
Okay, I don't nobody knows what to do because there's too many
It's okay. You know, it just reminds me of
I feel like a bunch of puppies at like doggy daycare, you know
I'll just run around like some of them are fighting each other some of them are like rolling around
This is just puppies like a hundred puppies
Oh, there's a commentator
Why did I get over here? How did I get over here? I don't even know how I did this
I think he just pushed me off
He just picked me up and threw me
I was getting too close
Oh my god, i'm on their team
What?
Wait
Okay, okay. Okay. I think I found the strategy. This is the strategy
It's impossible. This is impossible
Honestly, it's gonna take someone's gonna have to get disqualified because there's no way somebody's gonna get pinned
Who can get pinned in this?
The referee can't handle this
Are you serious?
Why could the referee do anything?
Get me out I need to get okay. He actually is using a weapon. He's actually using a weapon
He actually hit me in the head with that. Wait, is it he's not saying drop it. Did you say drop it?
All right. I'm getting out. I'm getting out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out
All right. This is just okay
This is like the titanic sinking and somebody is sitting there with a pail of water just pailing out little buckets of water
That's you can't think you cannot rule here referee. It's not possible
And she's just like oh no, you go out now you go out now you go out
I'm just gonna start throwing shit into the ring. Fuck it
What that lady just did?
Okay, he all right
It's over. It's over. It's over. It's over motherfuckers. That guy just used a weapon. He's used it. He actually used it
He used it. Yep. Weapons are legal. Let's go. She can't she can't arrest assault. Let's go
fuck oops
Get me in the ring. Oh
My god, I have a headache. I actually have a bad headache now from just fucking having uh, this is so funny
I don't know who's this guy's not even
supposed to be
Tag me in tag me in somebody tag me in
Tag me in
Oh my god
Just put a ladder in here. Who cares?
Who cares?
Oh
Let's get me in there with the chair, please let me just get in there with the chair
Oh, there's never gonna be a winner
By the way, this is the commentator by the way
It's this guy right here
That's that's the commentator
Okay, I need to find a way to get in the ring
Because you get me in that ring. Give me the chair. I'm gonna start bashing people. Come on tag me in
Tag me in
You tell I i'm in it's me
Who's legal who's legal?
All right, it's me versus him. Ow, is that alan gator?
What the fuck?
Okay, wait, wait, it's it's not mankind. It's this guy. It's this guy right here
Drop it drop it. I'm dropping it. I'm dropping it. I'm dropping it. I'm dropping it. Hey, he's
You do understand that once somebody goes for a pin
it's
Everyone's gonna run in
There's gonna be actual mayhem once a pin happens. In fact, let's make it happen now
Where are all my people?
You know what?
This guy was just watching
That guy wasn't even didn't even care
All right. It's the guy in the green pants. I don't even know what his name is
I love how everybody on my team is watching and not doing anything
There's only five minutes left. There's not gonna be a pin in five minutes. It's over
Get in here
What?
All right, it's this guy
Good good, you know what i'm gonna sorry I have to do this. No, I didn't want to tag him in fuck
Everybody get out there start fighting
Get out there and fight get out there and fight each other
We have to make this it's at least something there has to be some order here
All right now
Now I could
Holy shit. She caught it. I need a chair
Don't throw me a weapon
Uh, you know what? We need to see this
We need to see this for a minute
I'm going out. I'm going out. This actually makes it easier
tag me in
Tag me in tag me in those what happened to that guy?
Do you okay? Do you ask me like that guy in the lower right? It's not even supposed to be here
That looks like somebody's son that they brought
He's the legal man, by the way
Tag me in somebody tag me in
All right. I'm legal. Oh you
Nope. No shit. I honestly now. I just feel like i'm playing dynasty warriors
God damn it. No
This is hotline miami. Yeah
This is insane
Okay, I need to
Who is it? It's this guy on the ground, but I can't even look at him. Wait. Demento is seriously injured
Demento
Demento is seriously injured. Give me that chair. Give that chair to me. I just dropped that on his head
I'm surprised. He's the only one that's hurt and that make no sense. How can that be the only person?
I'm gonna laugh so hard if the dementor ends up like coming out and winning
All right. It's
It's okay. It's it's a little it's this little guy here. It's money mark. Just keep him in the corner
Everybody just stomp him. Everybody stomp him
Everybody stomp him
All right. Here we go
special move
night
Okay, he's fucked pin
one
two
I did it
Money mark couldn't end my streak and nobody else has what it takes either
Alan gator's profile has improved. Here's the funniest part about this
Are you guys ready for the 18 in a row?
Updates to players cards here bruiser. Olay's progress is being hindered by the limitations of strong style wrestling. Oh
Ghetto child progress is being hindered by the limitation of strong style wrestling
Amber lance progress being hindered by the limitations of strong style wrestling
Sam sarah progress being hindered by the limitations
Mr satan progress being hindered derry buckler's progress being hindered crucial kennedy's profile profile has improved
Bully may's profile has improved after being on the winning team
Ravi tas profile has suffered from being on the losing team
Demento has sustained extremely serious injury in that match and was rushed to the hospital where it is feared. He may be
Oh the one guy. Oh my god
Oh, this is demento. Oh
I'm trying to keep it together. This is fucking crazy
Air miles just just the transition to this
Just the transition to one guy that got really hurt to like oh by the way air miles
His profile suffered a little bit. He was on the losing team that match
Oh my god
Cas profile has suffered from being on the losing team
Oh
Money mark's profiles suffered
Oh, there are like boogers coming out of my nose
Oh my fucking god
Music just made it so much worse
No, don't twist it
Why is so many okay
I'm just knocked up with coffee that was here
Jigsaw jeremy has defeated matt who cares
Does anybody really give a shit about anything else besides like the 20 people that would just
like
smothering over each other for 15 straight minutes
God
Yes, I know I have to win a championship
The entire sport of wrestling seems to have suffered a lull in popularity throughout 2022
I mean oliver gold as the best overall wrestler in the world
Strong style wrestling have sunk below super lucha libra to become the least popular brand of wrestling
With a rating of only 72 percent
Holy shit
Okay
Um, I need a title shot or i'm gonna get dropped
Oh
Somebody said is demento gonna live. I don't know. I hope so last man standing versus drew dirham
King david
Come on. Yes. I'm looking for a title shot
Everybody wants a shot of the world title. How do I do this?
Oh visit demento
I don't even what I don't even know what um
Oh, I heard you were looking for me miss satan. What do you want to talk about?
I like to work with you. How do you see us working together? Can I like help?
I'm not gonna challenge him to a fight. You guys are fucked
No, like I will let's be like I let's be like a group of three
Partner manager will be three. No, i'm not gonna fight him. Let's let's like work together
I want to help him. Okay. Well last man standing
I need a title match. Oh, let me change the camera
Oops, what was it hard camera or third person? I think it was hard camera
That's hard camera. All right, let's go
That guy has wait that guy's a title. Does this count does this count? What if I leave?
This person's not
Getting mad that I have this
Oh, it's because the last man standing right? Okay
Wow
Shit, I missed
reverse it
Wait, uh, that's money mark over there at the commentary table, isn't it? It is it down here
Oh that he got hit three times. Hello here money mark. Why the fuck did goku let this happen? Oh shit
Villain arc i'm not a villain
Where's mr. Gator on the chair on the chair?
Yes, how are you up? How are you standing right now? What dickhead? How is he holding two weapons?
How do you do that? He's got two items
The mic dropped on him
Why is this guy getting counted or always to be on the ground I get it right right right last man standing
Count him count him
I think he threw something
Stop doing that
Count him. Is there a reason why you're not counting? Um, what are you doing count? Are you stupid?
Count him down count. Okay, like count
This seriously this guy's like made out of fucking metal
Yeah, you think I say you got another guy see you sneaking up on me money mark don't think so
What he's still on the ground. You murdered dimento. I can't believe you've done this
Everybody you did it. I had faith in you
You deserve you villain. No, i'm not
Trump somebody said stop trying to stop trying to summon the count from sesame street
How did he do what the fuck are you dodging? How?
what
title batch
Oh
Okay, mr. I mean i'm hindered here
Alan gator is happy that his client won
Client
Aren't we just friends?
I have a lot of money
Hey
Okay
Oh shit, vegeta, uh went to um rising sun
All right, super lucha libre now is the least popular
Have you ever heard of a wrestler called henryu mist from rising sun?
Um, i've heard of ryu mist
Henry, you missed wait what I think we could do the gimmick better
No, i'm wait, they cut my hair
I don't want to imitate him. I'm not gonna be missed
I'm starting to think I should have signed the real tenryu mist instead of you. Yeah, you should have
confrontation with amber lance
I need to get a title
confrontation
Challenge for the tag title every time I challenge for a title. They just say no
There's so many people in line for this not you
Why am I in just plain clothes?
Peter griffin
I'm tired of being mentioned in the same breath as you it's time to change the conversation
Everybody talks about me like i'm your inferior, but we both know that i've always been your superior
I'm sure you would prefer me to stay in the shadows, but my light is too bright for that
Don't worry about shadows too much because you won't be seeing any more of those
After I knock you out
Don't be worried about shadows anymore
Once you're unconscious
Then you'll be seeing
Only shadows. Oh, why does it keep happening?
Oh fuck get out of the way gator
Oh my god
It really is peter griffin
Slowly just changing into peter griffin. It really is
If they give me glasses
And the peter griffin haircut then I mean this what I can't you want me to fix that. I can't fix that
Oh my god, this guy's getting his ass kicked
The only damage this guy has done has been me ricocheting damage off of him to myself. Oh my god
What did he what happened?
We win I won
I have the support of the fans now
Maybe people hated that guy. Okay. I need a I need a title
We had hollywood challenge strong style wrestling to an inter-promotional contest on the third week of april. Is that hulk hogan?
Yeah, let's do it
All right. I'll see you on the third week of april. Make sure you're ready because I know I will be
Oh, yeah, both of us have similar voices as you can tell mr satan and hollywood hogan brother
Yeah, you better you better better these 24 inch pythons are coming for you. Okay
All right. I need to try them one more time
jake obscene
Title I challenge you to a title match. No, what the i'm not gonna be able to get the title
I don't think I can do it. I'm gonna get released
Challenge just challenge everybody
Okay, uh coder
What do you want? I want to challenge you to a title match
Okay, who's marty wait martini is
Is this the women's championship?
We can't do this
Can we?
No, it's tag team championship. Okay
No, I nobody's gonna let me do it. I'm not challenging demento
no
All right you
It wouldn't be any chemistry between us so long as we're both faces. Fuck. Well, I can't I didn't do it
Oh, well another organization. I tried that before and it said we're not even in the same organization. Why would I fight you?
By the way me and me and gator
We start every match off with a hug. Oh never mind back to wrestling school
Illegal illegal illegal. He's got an illegal weapon
I was gonna hit him, but she turned around face
So wait, what why can a face why can a good guy not do a bad guy thing?
You mean like why I can be good I can be don't you but we've talked about even with fable too
Remember when I played fable everyone was like what the fuck is he doing?
I can be big picture good but small picture bad, right? Like I can like
uh
steal from a guy
Or like punch a guy in the face or maybe like sneak around and like and stab the guy, right?
Well, I like a big picture good
You killed an entire village in fable, too
I but that was the end of the stream though. I don't think that counts
Like that was not canon. I was like, all right guys
I'm probably gonna end the stream here and if in a little bit and like probably like 10 minutes or so
So like at that point when no long it was not canon
That was just oh it's end of the stream whatever like i'm like i'm just talking and hanging out
This guy's actually a pretty formidable opponent
Get it. He died of natural causes. No
Into the corner. Oh, maybe not
You can't retcon your own streams
Why not?
And what about demento's death?
You see you are making your canon. That's that's not even real canon that haven't happened yet. Demento is alive
He just has like a broken leg and he's like hurt
Yeah, like he like broke up his like back or something, right?
You are saying well, I don't think I don't he's probably not gonna that you don't die
You are saying I killed demento, but demento is not dead. So isn't that same thing? That's the same thing
Demento is very much alive
Though i'm everything's fine
He's
No, you don't know we don't we haven't got an update yet. There's no update. He's gonna be fine
This is time to end it
That was a simple little match
He's running away
Fucking run away from me
I need a new contract anyways
Gator was trying to block me
Okay, so now what?
Okay glitter arty that's very absolutely gold dust
So I didn't do it, but I couldn't
I failed to do yeah, this organization just sucks
Slackers like you don't belong in strong style wrestling clean up your locker and get out of my sight
I can't wait to hit you in the head of the chair next time I have a chance
more than once
Okay, did I lose my um match with hulk hogan
Okay, now I can change my shit
All right. Finally
Where is it? Okay. Now I need my mustache back. Okay. Mr. Satan is back. I need
The cape get rid of the tattoos. Yeah, I know i'll get rid of them. All right, there's my chest here. Where is it?
There it is. Okay, make this fight baggy looks good. All right, take that material too. Let's get the tattoos off
Now we need material too. All right. We're good. This footwear needs to change and this has to be purple
Whoa, okay. That was weird. Which one is it? This one? I think it was these ones
I think it was these ones, right? They're kind of like the maroon like that. What about my chin?
Yeah, what happened to my face? Why did they change my mouth my face? I don't want knee pads. All right legs. Mr
Satan is back
God, that's bright
There we go. Okay. Mr. Satan's back. He's going to make his face better big jaw
I almost think I like big jaw better. That ain't jaw enough. All right. We'll go back to the regular one. That's yeah
You're right. Yeah, that's better. You're right. Okay, do 25
25 25
That's better hair needs to be
20 like 35 35 35
All right. Mr. Satan's back
Casual clothes, that's fine. Referee clothes. That's fine. Doesn't matter. All right
Mr. Satan has returned. This is Dementor's manager. You think I care?
Shank has turned face and it's now going to be in a portrayed in a positive light
Okay, I have my my popularity my attitude have gone down. Well, I got released. I tried to do a
fucking
Wait a minute. I'm not sure the name. Mr. Satan captures the essence of your character
How would you feel about being called something like David Petrel?
David
No, I don't want to be called
David Petrel tables and chairs versus the grand bisma
Okay
What do I have coming up training versus training session training session and then a big public show?
All right, let's go
Challenge somebody that doesn't have a belt
Wait, this is a this is a postgraduate champion
This is the heavyweight is for the belt
Ask for a contract. Why is he holding a chair?
All right, i'll challenge somebody I find my back in wrestling school. I'm like this. I'm like the hulk hogan status
Talk to germa. He's in the hollywood roster. What no germa's retired while their stock goes down mine
Will keep going up. You're not good enough to be me. Mr. Satan. So let me show you where you belong
I not I appreciate the enthusiasm, but this is wrestling school. I graduate
Okay
I've already been here before
I graduated
Like four years ago or so and i'm going to show you I don't belong in wrestling school
Oh my god, have I washed up? What the fuck happened?
Oh my god, I don't belong in wrestling school
Oh my god, that was horrible. No, I shouldn't be here
Jesus christ
No, I don't belong in wrestling school
I just break them through a table and I can prove that i'm good
Come here get up here. No get this a tables match
Wait, wait a minute. I thought it was a tables match
Okay, now you now you awoke the violent now i'm violent
I run in a circle. I get even more momentum because i'm sprinting and just gaining power
Was my eighth victory in a row for those of you that like to keep count
Grand visma couldn't end my streak and nobody else can
I am now the champion. Okay, great
Can I just give this to somebody and leave?
We're running short of staff. Could you do commentary? Sure
But I want to get out of here 200 bucks. That's actually much more than I was making before
I just don't care. I'm just gonna get up and just i'm gonna go to back to the stage
Go talk to germa
Didn't germa retire because I got dropped
Wait
Remember lucy lakes?
Germa is in hollywood
Mr. Staten will be joining us on commentary to share his insights in this match
You know how long you know, how long do you think this match is gonna go?
It's gonna take less than five minutes. It always does you heard it here first. Let's find out. It's gonna be less than five minutes
malcolm soul
versus
Who is this who's even in this match? It's lucy legs versus malcolm soul
This is gonna play back here
Just wear the belt and just oh i'm so scared of you. I'm so scared
Don't hurt me
Is that it? That's it
I did it. I was about to sit down and do commentary. I told you I it always is less than five minutes
All right lucy lake status has not been affected
Rupert royals progress is being hindered
muher pelle rosa
Progress is being hindered
Monty python has left all american wrestling
All the ratings are slumping
Oh, nice to meet you. Mr. Satan. We invited you here to discuss your working for all american wrestling. This is the big one
We fear you'd be a valuable addition to the roster if we're prepared to make it happen with this deal
Compensated for any health issues 1800 bucks a week
This is a good. This is good. I'll take this. This is a good contract
I don't even do anything. Let's just go
All american wrestling. This is the this is the big one. I gotta prepare for this
I can get this in 90. All right, nothing's scheduled here
No creative control
Yeah, I look even when I don't have creative control. I don't even listen to what they say. Anyways wrestling revolution have poached tod snorting
From weekend warriors in a deal estimated to be worth 51 000
Damn, okay
Perfect shawn is sad that mike shawshot has left all american wrestling
Maddie mcfly is glad that mike shawshot has left all american wrestling gruesome. Sharon has left all american wrestling
Okay
Hard gainer is now the champion. This is the guy that just signed me. I think that's supposed to be vince mcmahon
You make a pretty good team. Mr. Satan. How would you like to make it a regular thing?
Easy to get lost in the shuffle on your own, but we can make a much bigger impact together. Where's the gator?
Where's alan gator? I already have a teammate and where's alan gator?
Be careful what you wish for. Mr. Satan. It's better to be with me than against me. I already have a teammate
right
Where am I? Where's mr. Satan? He's not with me anymore
What
Wasn't he with me? He was with me here. Oh, no, I left him behind
I thought like that we were partners. I thought that meant like they'd get him too
Oh shit
I left him behind
What?
Heard you're looking for me. Mr. Satan. Uh, what do you want to talk about this time? I challenge you to a match
We didn't work for the same old company anymore. I don't see that happening anytime soon
I hope I get injured
All right versus win stevenson who am I fighting this is a packed arena
But you have the same name you have the same music
It's the same music
That's just a slowed down version of my music. I've waited a long time for this moment
And I can't wait to set about achieving my goals
You just you just pitched it down. I if perfect sean thinks he's the future of all american wrestling
Perhaps i'll have to challenge for the united states title
Or maybe i'll form my own team and give battering ron and bill dozer is something to worry about
In my quest to own all of the gold I might even chase becky lane for that women's title
But of course my ultimate aim is to win the world title
And replace jigsaw jeremy as the face of the company
Sorry to wake you up from that sweet dream, but there's nobody you should be focused on more than me while you're holding two mics
That would be echoing that would be so awful
I'd be like
There's nobody you should be focusing on more than me right now
Let me show you why they call me the killer
It would just be feedback. He would just be like
Oops, it's all right
All right. I'm in the big leagues now. I can't fuck around power bomb. Oh that fucking hurt do it again injury
You know, how many times am I gonna do this? Oh my god, that's awful. It's just injury. Why are they booing?
What do you want booing?
Is that it? It's a satan win
Yeah, it's because i'm going after the women's title. Well, I just no that's not
That's not what happened. I that was just being
In my my speech. I'm like i'm coming for everything, right? I'm enormous. I know i'm fucking huge
All right safari is now heel
Tate madison has been released. This is for the world championship. Are you kidding me?
Four man elimination versus multiple opponents. This is a world championship already. Let's go
World championship match versus paper cut. We're going for 10 wins in a row. I'm gonna try to
Let me prove myself right here. Mr. Satan. This should be with allen gator
Yep, that's right
You can't just take my music
win stevenson
I just won
dfca
Uh-oh jigsaw jeremy the world champion. That's just hacksaw jim dougan
All right, why are they hugging? What am I doing?
Jigsaw jeremy you've only remained the world champion this long because you've been ducking me
Everyone knows i'm the biggest friend
I was just saying out of the fans. You can't put off any longer and i'll prove why you were right to fear me
Let's go
Just like broke his arm
Oh my god, somebody just got really hurt
Somebody just got really hurt. I think was that paper cut somebody's really injured
Nope
All right, let's do this
Just to use everything i've learned testispring versus mr satan sit the fuck down
bang
Oh, we roll. I rolled his head over that get off. No
Wait, what happened? Oh, I was doing a move to paper cut
I think it was paper cut someone that was injured
He's running
Oh shit. I have a special
Oh, they had no match
Absolutely no match for me at all. This is why i'm the goddamn champion after this match right here
You've the screams are insane
Wait, why is there?
What do you mean? What's with the timer timer's going up? What do you what's wrong with the timer? It's only been two minutes
Yeah, why are some people saying look at the timer? Look at the timer?
All right out of here. I am so strong. It's not even funny. I belong with the gods
You know, what's the next federation with like zeus like the sidener in the game get out of the way ref what the fuck?
oh
All right, it's time we're gonna do special to
Here we go. Good night
And then we get you two quickly before I run out
That's it me and you jigsaw jeremy and you don't even stand a chance world champion incoming
What 10 11 wins in a row? This is what happens when you just build strength the whole time
Big finish right here
Lose stevenson
That's it. You're not getting up. That's not fair. All right. I want I'm gonna make a big finish on here. Ready?
Let's do it. See you later
I missed
Nobody you spared onto the chair
Splash him
All right, fine. Get him in the middle of the ring and let's just make him submit
I want I want to hear him say I tap out. That's it. I won
I am now the world champion of all-american wrestling
Did it earth's strongest villain?
All right, let's go. This is it
I got forty thousand dollars in my account big saw jeremy
I was gonna say what's the title?
loser weight
Marchismo has left super lucha libre. Oh petrol did they get dave petrol?
Now what you ever consider getting the fans on your side to become more popular? Um, wasn't I already a face?
Yes, i'd like to turn face. Of course. I was already let's start portraying you in positive light
The fans will appreciate a chance to get behind you. I think they I just keep losing support
Get this to 90
All right, that's true. I've become a face and then I do something horrible and everyone hates me again at the age of 56
Slick dude has retired from professional wrestling
Okay
Uh world, this is for this is her championship
titles on the line here
versus high note
Earth's strongest villain. I love that
Let's go say hi to the fans one autograph
Every single one is now a championship until you lose. All right
I see
I got you
high note
The more I build strength the better
Is that all the punches?
I just become so powerful
Listen up everybody there's something I need to get off my chest before we go any further
Put the camera a little higher. I know i've been a jerk in recent times
I've said and done some things that i'm not proud of but I realize we're nothing without the support of the fans
You're the electricity that gives us life
With your help. I know I can be a better wrestler. I hope I can repay you by fulfilling my potential
Hey, we done with the life-changing crap. The only drama that matters is in this ring
Oh, no
I was gonna quit I was gonna quit I was gonna quit
I was gonna quit
Nine seconds. Well, it's because he has a fucking camera in the ring
And I picked it up and I was gonna throw it out
But I hit them. Ah, whatever
Oh my fucking god, whatever. I thought I could throw it by him
I keep the title
Wait, I am still the champion. I'm still the champion
Listen, mr. Satan. I've been keeping
Your progress
You don't have a good enough attitude. Oh, no, he's giving me an attitude ultimatum improve your attitude to 79% for the third week of june
Or i'll give you a spot to somebody who appreciates it. Okay
We may not like each other mr. Satan, but we drew a lot of money together
It's him. How would you feel about getting me into all american wrestling to reignite our feud?
Yeah. Oh, yeah, let's wait
All right, aren't you canadian?
Thanks for making this happen. Mr. Satan. I can't wait to work with you again
I gotta bring him up
Okay, what's my attitude?
10 man tag team another one of these race against time
last laugh
Oh god
Is this for the title? I need 79 attitude. Okay. This is just a mess. So
I need to okay. I gotta do I gotta no attitude problem here. Okay
10 man tag team
maddie mccly's team
Jesus
It's not for the title. Okay
This is always just such a mess
Wait, aren't there 10 people in the ring right now?
How come I get less people?
Wait a minute. I have one two, three, four five
This guy has like 15 fucking people
This is not fair
Hey duke mini man. Can you believe that we've been booked to face each other in this match?
This is just scripted. Yeah, things could get awkward, but I hope you appreciate that
I can't go easy on you just because we're friends
Don't worry, I wouldn't have it any other way. I can't afford to lose this match either. Who's the ref?
All right. This is so unfair though
Just look at how many people are in this person's corner. This is ridiculous
Who's the legal one?
Wait, it's this guy
You're like the hulk. It's fine
I really am
All right, it's illegal to use that but it's illegal for me to drop him on his head on the way
You know what I mean? I don't think so
Jerma you're worse than rio mist. What are you talking about? I haven't lost a match in like an hour
Duke mini man is so hurt. What happened to him? He's not even
This is my friend
Okay, get him get him get him pin him pin him that's it hey welcome to all american wrestling duke mini man
Oh shitty help mr. Satan's path has improved come on attitude
Why he's not hurt. We're fine. I see you had fun out there, mr
Satan, but you made quite a mess of the arena how if you ever want to book this venue again
You better pay a hundred dollars towards the damages. Oh, that's okay. Fine. What did I do?
Need to agree for attitude gains
All right, that makes sense
Newbie nate. Okay. Have you ever worked with a wrestler called aftershock here at all american wrestling?
His contract is up for renewal soon. So we'd be interested to know if you have any feedback
What would be a better attitude for me to say yes or no? We need to keep him or he doesn't belong here. What would be better?
for attitude
Probably yes
We need to keep him
Look how good my attitude is
All right. I don't have no idea what this one is. Oh shit 79 almost there
This is race against time
And it's a last laugh match
I think we're about to find out what that means. I have no idea
I can't uh, I cannot upgrade attitude. It's one of the things you cannot do. Let's see what this is
Last laugh is it the last person to laugh?
Okay, bart simpson running the chalkboard. Keep the attitude up. I will not attack anybody the commentary table
I won't throw a weapon at anybody. I'm gonna just wrestle this guy
You laugh you lose. Yeah, but
How does that I don't understand this match?
Mr satan, you're not popular enough to be a champion. It's about time that title went to a real star like me
This title is too big for your little waist. You're punching above your weight jigsaw jeremy
How does this work? I don't get it. What do we do?
How do I don't know what this means?
Last to get a pin within the time limit
What?
Two minute time limit and it's the last person to get pinned or to get a pin
All right. Well, just let's just hurt him
That's all I know
Just hurt hurt other guy. You got it
Um, that's by eating something on the way in here and good more punches
He's just trying to get that at it. He's almost ready for a pin
I got a full 60 seconds. That should be good
Get it. Um
What are you doing
This guy's drunk
Really dude, are you kidding me? That was it right there too
Count really got one more chance
Special this is it
Come on
That's it. Yes. Got it
How are you supposed to do this with two minutes?
Come on. Yes attitude. I got it. I get to stay. Hey all american wrestling all american wrestling
Maybe I get to move up. Wait a minute wrestling revolution have challenged all american wrestling to an inter promotional showdown on the first week of july
Rising sun pururisu profile has risen after pretending to champion a fashionable cause wherever it is convenient to do so
I don't know what that's supposed to mean. But okay
Congratulations mister satan. You followed my advice and made your prospects better than ever please accept a
$1,000 bonus as a reward. Thank you. All right
Hardcore match versus jigsaw jeremy and then we have a question mark and then we have
This one I gotta stay I gotta make sure I stick around for this one. That's don't be this probably gonna be a big deal
All right, hardcore versus jigsaw is a confrontation
I know for a fact i'm gonna kick the ever-living shit out of this guy
So we're gonna get this ranked in 90 at least 91 91 91 91 91 9999. Yes
I have so much confidence that i'm gonna hurt this guy. So it doesn't matter
when you give me
Legality to use a weapon. I'm going i'm guaranteed to win every single time
I'm just saying this guy went heel
Did I make this guy go heel?
If you pin him without defense outside the ring, you can kill him. I I don't want to kill somebody
You want your title back? Yeah, you're a bad guy now
That's fine. I'm literally gonna take this out of your hands and kill you with it. Are you ready?
All right. No more. Oh wait, I can beat him. I can beat him without any people are booing
What do people like to see just like wrestling?
All right, let's play to the crowd
People are just silent
And like unhappy
What's wrong with my guy? Is it a pin do I have to pin them? All right. I'm the crowds coming back up again
Come on. I gotta get the crowd back on me clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap
Clap clap clap clap clap clap
Clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap
All right. Yeah
I did it. I didn't even use a weapon that much. So other people will be happy
Don't touch any weapons. Just let them get up
Okay
Profiles suffered. I'm fine
Do a booker of wrestling revolution?
Oh
pacifist percy
Have you ever heard of a wrestler called high yakuza from rising sun purisu? Um
No, we're thinking of bringing him into all-american wrestling and we're wondering what you would think about that
That sounds like a great idea. I'm very happy that you would even consider
Sign hi yakuza. Yes. I'm my attitude is fantastic
Jake saw jeremy walks around like he owns this place and has been making our lives miserable
Do you think you could teach him a lesson? There's 1400 in it for you if you do
uh, can just be retroactively at it because I
I've put I've like put him in the hospital already. Yeah, i'll deal with him
Thanks for doing this. It'll be worth it to see jigsaw jeremy get what he gets what he deserves
Wait, what who is why is there a person back here? Who are these people? Why this is a desk?
Are you here? It's tough. I'm in a locker. Okay
I just don't want to beat him up that bad because people are gonna be mad at me, right?
Okay, well that's off the table now. Don't punch her
Hold it
Okay, we're good. I'm getting out of here
Wait, no, did that? No, no, no, i'm fine. I'm fine. It's already over right? I already did it
There's no timer here. Yeah, I did it already. I'm good
It must have been literally yesterday
Okay, so that was now it's a tag team versus mr. Benjamin's team
Yeah, we're good. I think it was actually yesterday
This I i'm really interested in this one. All right, let me go to roster. I want to challenge somebody wide tide
What should I challenge?
How about high note or get a partner? Who should I who should be my partner?
matt showman
mismatch
jesse bell
Mr. Benjamin paper cut
Will wind
I yakuza
Oh shit
I heard you were looking for me. Mr. Satan. What do you want to talk about? I'd like to work with you
How do you see us working together to be partners? Aren't you supposed to be in the world champion?
Stop trying to get out of defending your title. Really gonna be mismatch. I heard you were looking for me. Mr
Satan, what do you want to talk about? How do you see us working together? Well mismatch, let's be fucking tag team partners
Aren't you supposed to be with the world champion? Why does everybody hate me because i'm a champion
Wouldn't you want to work with the champion? Wouldn't you want to be on the champion's team? Well, fine. I'm gonna
All right pyro come here. I challenge pyro to a match
All right. It's a date. Make sure you're ready by the fourth of week of june because I know I will be
Pay per view, but how do I do it? Can I change the rules?
Versus pyro's team. What do you mean pyro's team? I don't get to make the rules. Oh, well, whatever
Wait, what are we friends now?
Somebody just grabbed that
And sprinted away
That's like the ultimate foul ball to catch at a baseball game. All right, i'm out
Run put that down put that down
I'm sure as you all aware we're the reigning tag team champions here at all american wrestling
Wait, why are these guys in here? Unfortunately, the competition in this division is so pathetic that we've resorted to finding our own
Why they dress as referees?
That's why we're pleased to announce that we'll be granting a title shot to whoever wins this match
Wait tag team title
But they're the referees of the what's up? What's going on?
What the fuck who?
I'm what's happening
There are two referees
And they're evil
Um, wait, okay. It's me and versus
Is that strength look at that damage?
Look at that fucking damage. Look at that. Damn it
My neck my neck my neck my neck get him off me
Oh, yeah
That was a sick play
Use that strength
Piledriver piledriver on top of that thing. Let's get it on the let's get it over here
I'm dropping it. I dropped it
Get off me
Oh get on
Okay, there's another guy over here. But these guys have the why they have the title
Wearing the belts
You don't
Thank you. Thank you. Uh lola. I appreciate it
She's just covering his nose and mouth. She's trying to like fucking make this guy not breathe
He's ruthless
I like her
She's ruthless
perfect teammate
Count count count count count count count two
three four five six
Seven eight nine ten. See how fucking fast I did it
Really?
count faster
Faster
Oh right in the face. I'm so huge. I have his nose
The other guy hasn't even tagged in oh, you know what I should probably tag in
Isn't she gonna be like mad that yeah here come on
whoops
Is it not what I wanted to do? Okay. Well
I may have just like fucking screwed myself here. I was trying to tag her in
Hola, Lola, Lola. Thank you
Lola
Game over. All right. You gotta watch my back here. We're gonna get a title shot
Get him in the right spot and then break his neck
All right, that's it
defend
Really? Wow. All right
You're strong
But not strong enough tag her in all right. Come here. All right, she's tagged in
I need to give her you just do like a do like a walloping on this guy
All right. I'm getting out of getting out. I'm going to going to going. All right. All right. All right. All right
I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. Look
All right, Lola go for it. Kick his ass
I want to get you some time in the ring
So you don't lose anything because we're gonna get a title shot after this
Oh
Uh, Lola, what are you doing?
Good. Yeah
Do you want it? No, don't tag out. Yes, you pin them. Oh shit. I gotta get in you dick get over here
We have a raid. All right. Hold on. Hold on. I'll see you. I got one second
I got i'm i'm i gotta get out get out get out get out get out get out
Who is it? Who is it connor eats pants? What's up connor? What's going on connor?
Just playing some wrestling empire, uh, best game ever made in case you're wondering. I've okay
I don't know. I don't know what happened
I welcome everybody the raid song we don't guys it's it's it's 2021. We don't do the raid song since like
I
December of 2020 but welcome. Hi guys. All right. If you're not gonna do anything then tag me in
Uh, i'm not sure what you're up to connor, but hopefully you had fun doing it
Welcome everybody. Thanks for the raid
Currently the world champion as mr. Satan of the dbz fame
All right, just tag me in lola. This is getting
All right, that's it. That's it
Network andy i'm i don't i'm not network andy
I'm not fucking network andy
Shit i gotta get out before they disqualify
Get out get out get out before they i'm gonna get disqualified because of this
Get out i'm trying to crawl out of the ring
Don't just don't disqualify me. Please i'm trying to as hard as I can
All right, we're fine
Good move lola. Perfect. I'm trying to hit him so bad. All right tag me in
tag tag tag
tag
Tag me in tag me in lola tag me in i'm gonna go in so bad tag me in
Tag me in
How do I say you tag me in tag?
lola
Tag tag come on back here
I have to be in the corner tag me in come on. I'm right here tag. Oh
Reach reach reach just tag me in and it's over tag me in and I will I swear to god
Tag me in
Tag I can't get down
tag me
Tag me in tag me in why are you doing this lola? What are you doing?
Tag
I feel like somebody else is playing his player too and then not paying attention tag me in
Tag me in i'm right here
Please there it is. All right. Now i'm fucking angry
Just get these right hands in here. What is he doing to me? What's he doing?
I do that yoga pose
That's right covers mouth
That seems like so much setup for not that much
Why wouldn't you just use punch in face? It's so much more effective. Oops
Get out of here
Am I I thought I was doing this to her for a second
All right, we need to get everybody out of here so I can go back to what I was doing
All right, at least lola participated, right?
I need to my special is almost there. All right, let's go
that's
I I think lola ran out of energy. She was going crazy in the first two or three minutes
We got to end this now and now she's just like winded. She's not what is she doing?
These guys are not going to get a title shot. I'm sorry
In fact, i'm gonna injure this guy because like this is seriously like this is i'm getting sick of this
lola go back there and and
Get the fuck out of the way
Cover lola has not moved in five minutes
I only did that to just like make the ai know that this is still a match going on. There she goes
All right, finally you snapped out of it. Let's go for the submission
Tap out tap
Help me
She woke up she woke up a little bit. That's good. That's good. She got up
It's having the two refs in the ring. It just bucks us all up
break tap
Get it
All she does are back flips you're making this so much harder just punch him you're hurting me, too
It hurts me as well when you do that do it do it
Roll up. Holy shit. That was unbelievable. But why is he still up? I'm so tired. I can't even move
Oh you idiot
You idiot you idiot
You're gonna make us lose this two minutes remaining. I can't even get up
Oh my god
Look at how close I am to a special, too
Okay, that's i've had enough about this. I've had enough of you and this is gonna end right now
You just wait until I don't come any closer. I swear. It's gonna be painful for you in the 30th
Congratulations, mr. Satan you've earned your shot at the tag team title
But you should be careful what you wish for because i'll turn your dreams into nightmares
All right, what was I doing?
Okay
I don't know what I was on the ground. It's weird
All right. Mr. Progress is being hindered or whatever
Lola's profile. Okay has improved. That's good
She's the tag team partner
Shock. Yep. Okay
We're almost at the huge event but this is the here it is the tag team championship right now
Shit. All right
I'm gonna have two belts
Who the fuck is that? Who's that?
Wreck bill dozer and battering ron
You never asked her to team up
Oh
No matter how many matches I win you ignorant people never give me the respect I deserve
I'll teach you some respect by making an example out of these guys
Oh, it's not about how many times you win. It's how many that wins to define a great wrestler
Even if trouble understanding that just watch how I beat you right now
Uh, I know I want the real partner if I quit right now. That's fine. Right and go partner up with lola
I don't this I don't who is this guy don't pretty sure that's
Quitter quitter
I think you lose. I I don't think you do. I think we did this before
Yeah, you I i'm
75 positive I can do this
Didn't we do that before?
We did that before and it worked
what
What the fuck?
We did that before in the middle of match just to go
Much didn't start last time
Oh god, damn it your buddy alan gator suggested that you might like to join us at strong style wrestling
Come back to us
You've certainly blossomed since we saw you last we'd like to bring you back with these terms
No, go fuck yourself. I don't know fine
I want you don't have to pay me 100 000 a week pay me 99 000 a week
Not getting anywhere. Let's just forget about it. I'm pleased to be joined in the studio by mr
Satan of all-american wrestling. So tell us a little about yourself. How tall would you say you are?
What my height is seven four. My height is seven three. I need to know how tall I am
I think i'm seven four
Am I seven four?
I think so. I don't know. How tall is this guy seven?
Seven three, I think
That's exactly right. Mr. Satan. You obviously know your own body. They liked that
Everybody knows your friends with lola. So tell us how that relationship is going
Um, really would have liked to fucking done the tag team championship with her
um, but I forfeited the match because
It was a guy i've never heard of I can always rely on lola. I can lola would be happy to hear that
I'm sure she feels the same way about you. Tell us how your training is going. Mr. Satan
How agile would you say you are right now? Not that agile. It's 75 percent. I'm not agile at all. That's exactly right
I really enjoyed talking to you. Mr. Satan. Thanks for your time steel cage versus pyro
All right, but first things first lola. I heard you were looking. Yeah, I am
I mean this is will we can work our way back up. Let's be partners
Aren't you supposed to be the world champion? Stop trying to get out of defending your title
So it wouldn't have worked. Anyways, who was the guy that they paired me up with first of all, right?
Wreck, whatever a cage match. Let's go. I've been the world champion for a long time
Referees coming up here. Hold on. Wait, will he uh, whatever
Versus pyro
Yeah
You can you get the you get to hold it you get to look at it. It's not yours though
I'm trying to shake the ring
There's nowhere to run now that I got you locked aside this cage pyro
Only one of us is getting out of here in one piece and it's not you
I'm already trying to get out
Oh my god
That's it I won
Wait, what?
Wait, hold on a second
That's not I don't I was what the fuck happened
What happened? I thought I used to escape the ring. You have to escape the ring
It's it's not escape the ring
Oh my god, I can't get back up. I gotta hurt the ref
wrong match type
I'm seriously trying to climb
I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it
I can't do it. I can't do it. I'm not pressing any buttons but holding up. I swear to god
Oh, no
climb
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. I wasn't pretending. I swear to god
I swear to god
That was legit. I promise you
He kept falling backwards. It kept like shaking on me
That was insane
No, I swear to god if you guys play this game, you'll know like if you try to climb
Sometimes you you you guys just falls down
If you hold up and try oh, I couldn't do it watch ready. It might happen here. I'm just gonna hold up
It didn't okay. I I swear to god. I promise you that was gall drina
Wait from banjo kazooie
Okay, it kind of was a gall drina laugh you're right
Hold on. What'd I tell you? You thought I was a liar. Everybody thought I was a liar. The referee just did it
You everyone. Oh, I'm a liar. I was pretending. We just watched it happen to the referee
Yo get minus two the ref
Oh, come on. I'm not even sure why he why did he do that?
Pull that arm out
Yep
A little bit more. I almost got the special
I'm ending this from the top by the way, everyone's saying no don't don't don't but I can I'll be fine get him on the ground
All right, it's got a special time and i'm going up on the top and i'm ending it with splash
Go really how would you get up that fast?
Why would you you're gonna talk to me on the mic? All right, let's go. I want to get I want to do a from the top rope
The ultimate top rope come on. There it is. Good night
No, I want to splash him. There it is. Good night game over. I win
What's this guy doing? What's that? Why is that guy climbing in?
Mr. Staten doesn't kill people anymore. I don't like him. Here we go. Okay
Don crocket
Yep, I remember hurting that guy
This is it. This is the big one. This is three man elimination. Demento is perfectly fine alive and well checking on Demento
Full recovery. Let's do it wide tied
Aren't we in the same?
Who's not an all-american wrestling? This is the owner of the company
so who's the
from wrestling revolution, it's infinite best
with
Kylie Barrier
Oh, give me that back welcome to the special inter-promotional contest between all-american wrestling and wrestling revolution
First representing all-american wrestling, please. Welcome. Mr. Satan and representing wrestling revolution, please. Welcome infinite best
I'm joel hardin of strong style wrestling and i'm here to be an impartial referee
I know the stakes are high, but let's keep this a fair contest to find out which promotion is best
Um, but isn't it a three-way?
It's a like a three-way
This guy's in all-american wrestling
One two three on top rope. All right, where you going? I don't think so
Get out here again count him to four. Why do I have a four and he has a two?
I'm gonna explain that one to me. Good. Nice job. Oh
I'm gonna get counted out
No, I can reset all that matters is this guy gets counted out. No, he got in
Yeah impartial ref bullshit
Who's okay?
This guy still has this championship belt on he hasn't taken it off
It's probably weighing him down. Don't you think this is like weighing him down over the leg again. Everyone's just watching
um
He's got a weapon
You're dude, you're not gonna get a pin right now. Nice job. Now you get out there too. He's blinded me
I don't know what that lady just did but it was not intelligent keep let's keep him out here you and me
Actually, you stay out here too special. He's oh he it's over
That's a double special on both and they're both gonna get counted out. What it should have been over
Roam out
She's going over the top rope again
Good get the pin. We got to set him up because then we have to embarrass this another uh wrestling company boston crab
There it is. It was one of the most painful things on earth at it again. Nice. Perfect legs again boston crab again
That's just that's the second or third time that that lady's done that at this point. I think it's fun. That's fun for her
Nope, don't you do it?
so high
All right, join me on the on the on the conference table join me up on the conference table. Hey, you dick
Okay
The chair
Go backstage, she's getting kicked out. She's getting kicked out. She's getting kicked out
Good
She's been she's been jumping off the turnbuckle. Honestly
She really wasn't even interfering that much. She was just hurting herself over and over again
All right, just pin somebody for god's sakes pin him
Get off me give me that belt. That's not even yours. He's putting it on you idiot
Get out of here
Get the fuck out of here
Dude starts wearing the belt
All right, go this way
good
Now, let's go for a neck break
No, I want to win not you
I mean I did we're on the same team, but whatever
This guy with the belt is seriously pissing me off. Like he puts the belt on and then he comes in the ring
Get him out of here
He's been more of a nuisance than kylie barrier was that's it. What did I just hit? Are you kidding me?
No, you're not gonna do that. You fucking snake
I don't want to do this to this guy
On the belt grab him twist it turn it pop it do it make the noise you missed god damn it
You idiot. You could have made this so much easier for me
tap tap
My god, the referee's not paying attention
No attention at all to that. Okay, that's all right now. It's over. He's out good
What's bobby hill doing in here? Holy shit. That was ridiculous. What?
Um, excuse me
Excuse me. Excuse me
Excuse me vince mcmahon. Excuse me. I need help. Thanks for nothing
Um, that's it. Oh my god
What the fuck?
Just
one two three
You weren't any help at all kylie barrier. It's almost as if you wanted me to lose
Where is this guy under the ring? Did he go under the ring? I think he rolled underneath
Oh shit, there's a guy that eliminated first. Oh, maybe he ran backstage
This is the steam version. This is the steam version. This is the steam
Remastered edition this is wrestling empire. This is not wrestling revolution 3d. This is new
This is a remastered version of that game if you're curious by the same guy, okay
Online polls non-title last man standing. All right, the pay-per-view is coming up 91 90 strength
Okay, is it auto time? Not quite yet. I'm still i'm still into it. We'll see
I don't well, I don't know how much longer we're gonna go, but i'm still having a lot of fun
This game's so much fun. Oh shit. It's duke miniman
What an idiot is he what are you doing? What was that for?
Oh, wow, it looks good on me. Doesn't it? I'm putting this guy in the hospital. You challenged me to a hardcore match. What are you?
Oh, no, I don't think he's gonna get up
Stop it. Stop it. Kill him. No, I look
Don't they know i'm the master of hardcore? Why would you challenge me to a hardcore match?
What are you doing?
You're not a hardcore wrestler. Look
You haven't even resorted to biting me yet. How would you know? This is not you don't know what you're doing
What the fuck is happening? What's going on? Who turned the lights off? Who's this?
Who is he? What is he doing? Redneck rawstein?
Um, I don't does he have a problem with the ref
Why did you turn the lights off? I I need to know what this guy's deal is. What's his problem?
Was he why did he interfere?
I'm so confused. I mean this this is a joke at this point like this guy's fucking i'm gonna kill this guy
Who is redneck rosteen and i'm about to hurt him
stay down
I'm here from hollywood to challenge all american wrestling to an inter-promotional showdown
If you've got any guts, your best will agree to face our best on the fourth week of july
Sure, we'll take on hollywood
I guess you're not the cowards. We thought you were at least you'll put up a fight before you lose
I'm gonna fucking injure him before that by the way didn't say I couldn't do that. You came to a hardcore match
It's a hardcore match
You'd be lucky if you're fucking still standing by the fourth week of your life
Give me that chair. Give me that chair. Give me the chair. Give me a weapon. Don't let him leave. I want him to be at red health
He just would just hurt yourself
This guy is fucking useless
Poor duke minivan. He just doesn't have one to quit
I don't care about him anymore
I want this guy to have like a back injury. Oh shit. All right. Okay. Okay. All right, whatever
Oh, I challenge all american wrestling to a fight
Get the medal
Did everybody see duke mini man over there like just a larping as the champion?
Well, I don't know but he's looking I can be the champion
Stairs i'm seriously gonna fucking put this guy away
Duke mini man. Oh, no, you got me. Thank you. Get this guy in the ring
I he's hurt. He's really hurt. Okay, but about that match next week
This guy's just crumbling
You're gonna take on the competition in this game, okay
Stay down so the match can end
Duke mini man's just fine. Mr. Satan's progress is being hindered by being in an all-american wrestling. He's not even injured
He's fine. He just says I want to make sure he had zero health for this fight bird boy has left sutra super lucha libre
The entire sport of wrestling has enjoyed increased popularity
This is it right here, right?
All right. Now we're gonna be a good guy
This is dan fever people are watching to see mr. Satan kill people
I haven't killed anybody
Look, i'm gonna be a good guy putting the mic down putting the belt down
That's it. Just a regular singles match
Before we go any further, let's take a look at the rules to make sure we're on the same page
I'm sorry
I don't even know what the rules are
Okay wrestling
Look if you give me a playground, i'm going to play okay
I if you give me a playground, then we give me a sandbox. I'm gonna make sand castle. I'm sorry. It's just the way it is
See, this is just wrestling
wrestling
Got him just like that spin around again
Okay, a couple of quick punches something around my neck
All right, let him get a move in
This is exciting. Okay. See that was his he did that
Right now we are just playing a wrestling game. I'm not trying to do anything weird. I'm not gonna hurt anybody
I'm not gonna like try to break somebody's leg
Just wrestling moves and that's it
Otto is displeased by your murder streak
I have my ability now special move. All right
And that's it
It was just a regular wrestling match
And I won
Yeah, see i'm we're fine. We're a good guy
I did get more popular for that
He tapped out since he didn't want to die
resident sleeper resident sleeper
Look, you can't just go 100 on the gas the whole time. You got to like
popularity
Okay, here comes
May be fortunate enough to have a cushy contract, but not everybody else does
Why don't we all unionize until they extend the same rights to everybody on the roster?
Sure, that's the spirit they want us divided but together we can make a difference
But this is very important, but
I may or may not kill some of you
Uh, that's just the way it is
Steel cage match. Sure. Let's like work together. But like i'm
You give me a chair and i'm gonna be i'm i'm not gonna hold back
That made me more popular. I didn't
slick dude with thomas son
You can't bring that in
I want him to fall so bad
Let's go
By the way, we decided to unionize
I'm trying to grab him. Why is he coming into the cage?
He shouldn't be in here
Okay, why are they both coming in all american wrestling? Please. Welcome. Mr. Satan and referencing hollywood slick, dude
I'm veto soprano of maple leaf grappling and i'm here to be an impartial referee stakes are high
But let's keep this a fair contest to find out which promotion is the best
out
Keep this guy in
They can't I don't think they can figure out how to get out of here. He's trying to figure out how to leave
Leave
I think are they gonna get thrown out or disqualified what happens here? I kind of don't want them to leave
How so is this escape the ring or are we stuck in here? I got him, right?
Got him right by the neck. Oh that hurts a lot. I'm ready to ask derma. This is really important
Do you like antelopes?
I don't know. I don't dislike antelopes
Oh my god, that's a lot of blood
the referee is gonna be so
Focused. Oh wait, vince mcmahon is getting out. He's gonna get out. I think he's gonna actually leave
Shake it on a little make it a little bit harder
Congrats to the guy spamming that finally got his attention. Now. Did I did I give into a spammer?
Oh, so something that I want to do before the stream is over
You can make your own match and I kind of want to make my own match with like as crazy rules as I can before
We stop playing this game
I think I have solidified myself as the best wrestler in the world. What else do I need like a landmine match?
You just fell on me that didn't count
Landmine match. Yeah, we'll play around with that for a while. So do I is it do I actually have to leave?
I think I have to escape. It's a pin. Well, there's your pin. It's called you gotta put him in a body bag
So it looks like there's no real repercussions for staying in
Vince mcmahon got out. Did he? I don't see him anywhere. Where'd he go? All right. I have to pin this guy
Jesus oh my god. All right, that's it pin game over. There we go
Those that like to keep count. That was my fifth victory in a row
Slick dude couldn't end my streak and nobody else will
He's been standing there
That's so funny
That's not a good place to stand
That's the best view in the house. Yeah, kind of you know white has been released by the wrestling revolution
Okay, tom stone a ball
Oh, what's this? Anyone that can beat slick dude deserves to be at hollywood as well
He certainly blossomed since we saw you last so we'd like to bring you back with this deal
Oh shit
I'll take it
You know why?
Because now i'm gonna go kick the shit out of myself
I'm gonna go challenge myself to a match
Entire the champion here
There I am
What do you want? Mr. Satan? This better be worth my time. I'd like to challenge you to a match
There isn't even a show on the third week of august. I'll stop making promises
Whatever
Movie shoot. Yeah, we've done that already. All right. I think it's time. I think it's time to go to the
The editor here
Let's do an exhibition
I want to see this venue
backstage office
studio office no crowd
No, no, none of this props
60 pieces of furniture. Okay, how about let's start
tables standard trash cans
I came here to prove it. I'm lay out random 30 weapons
Random random, okay
rules
singles best of three iron man last laugh
Submission last man standing
street fight
Okay
format individuals teams
individuals
hardcore rules
Calls none aim elimination
I'm limit none stoppage is no health
No count-outs. Um
Oh my god
category
arguments script
Air loss loser leaves drug addict. Mr. Satan exposes slick dude as a drug user
Mr. Satan challenges the loser to leave the company
Mr. Satan tells slick dude to go back to where they came from
Mr. Satan slick dude compare strengths and weaknesses
Mr. Satan enjoys the attention after interfering
Mr. Satan insults the audience
I have to pick who I play as
Where am I you made the biggest mistake of your career by interfering in my business mary claps
You should be grateful that I even showed up into one of your matches because nobody else wants to
You better hope somebody shows up for you tonight because we're about to see how tough you really are
Oh shit
A lot of people showed up
I have no health already. I gotta hide. I gotta get out and hide on the ground
Is this the union?
This is the we've unionized we did it all of us is the same
ow
No, no, no, stop it. Stop it. We need to be working together
Get over here
This is the union
Throw somebody out the window. I can't throw anybody out a window. What are you talking about?
Just beating this guy with a bat
How has nobody been eliminated? I gotta hide
So that was a bomb somebody just threw a grenade. That was a grenade
that was
That guy in the corner is like, oh my god, you're calamity
What the fuck
Why is that guy on his shoulders?
How are people still how are people still alive?
These people shouldn't be alive still
He fell off what well, how do you get eliminated? I thought how were people supposed to be getting eliminated?
I need like, oh, I need something to defend myself. Give me something to defend myself with
Okay
It's good. Wait
Wait, is it because the ref is dead?
Nobody can get eliminated even if they had zero health
Can I pick up the plant?
Somebody died
I can't this guy
Okay
I have to get out of here
This guy won't leave me alone
Out the window I'll do it. I can't go out the window
Somebody's wrenching my arm
uh
Get off of me. My health is slowly going down
Get off
I don't think you can go out the window
No, I don't think you can go out the window guys
Uh-oh people are dropping very quickly
You can throw other people out the window. No, you can't don't tell me I can do that. It's not possible
I can't even see where I am right now. All right, I got somebody
Throw him out the window
How do I throw? Okay, throw him out the window
I don't think so
I have to break the window first
That's a painting
I love the fires. I'm just gonna hide in the plant
What oh my god, I need a weapon a bigger weapon than that
I'm just mowing through them fucking dead rising
Hello
Yeah
I don't even understand where the person got the explosive
Oh should I went up?
What the fuck the weapons are random?
Okay, so what you're saying is we're doing this again, but i'm just gonna do grenades
I kind of want to see who wins this
Go back to the lockers. You'll regen
Oh my god, oh this union meeting did not go as well as we thought it was gonna go
God damn it
Oh
All right. Where are we going? I want okay arena
studio
What ring is a big square ring? How about a tiny ring with a with a cage on it?
Yeah, no huge ring with a with a cage. No, no, no cage big ring
Okay, that looks fine
All right rules
Outdoor, whatever backstage backstage
Okay rules street fight elimination cast is there. Um
script
Okay, we're gonna do
arguments hair loss now we need to do
Back to where was I? Oh shit. Okay rules, right arena props. I feel like i'm gonna crash my game
office chairs
Announce desks everywhere tables
Oh dear god
Okay
Okay. So this rivalry is going way beyond one to see you lose a match mary
I want to see you lose your hair as well. Why don't we put it all the line in this match?
Be careful what you wish for
It's a hair loss match
Okay, i'm gonna get out. Oh shit. Somebody's already out
What was that electricity sound? Did you hear that?
Somebody just got zapped
We're getting the fuck out of here
Fuck out of here
Get up
Oh my god
It was a taser
No escape because of the ceiling
No, i'm up there people are getting out. Somebody just scooped me in the what?
We got first blood wrestlers thrown out of the ring will be eliminated. Okay. I like that
Okay, let's go elimination. No time limit. Wait weapons are illegal
submissions, no
No
stoppage
None count out elimination. No, no count outs sumo contest. Okay
Make weapons illegal. Let's do it. I feel like the game's gonna crash. What is it doing?
Why are we doing an entrance?
Somebody throw a grenade at him, please
where
It's still doing entrances
It wouldn't mean there's no way to win
What the fuck
It's ridiculous
There's still people being brought in
No, let's go. Hurry up
three
Give me no, give me the explosive
This is so stupid. My entrance is never gonna stop if I don't get in the ring simulate result
Ryan schnider his one cool
Okay
Final thing i'm gonna do here is I want two people I want them to be where am I? Where is he? Mr?
Satan is mr. Satan. Oh, I went back to hollywood
This is the last match i'm gonna be doing and that'll be it. This has been an absolute fucking joy
What a fun game. Where am I? Where's mr. Satan? Oh, it's down here
Okay, i'm gonna make this count
I'm gonna do large arena
sold out crowd
No, the ring is gonna be
Uh, normal ring is fine. It can be pretty big
We do a cage
Okay, how about it's a virtual crowd
Why why is it a virtual crowd?
Oh crowd is virtual. Okay. I see I see
Rops, let's do 20 and 20 because we're gonna do tables
actually, you know what I want 60 tables
and like
Just a few weapons
And if you asking why
It's because I want to see how many tables you can stack
I want to see if you can stack like 10 tables because if you can I want to stack 10 tables
We'll do 40
rules
uh
No rules just a street fight
stoppage is a
Uh, wait, no health time limit aim is elimination individuals hardcore
Last minute no
Street fights three fights fine
relationships, uh
Friends reunited
Okay, you ready?
um
Which I play as
I play as me
I have to play as me. Okay
So this is a when your health gets to zero you lose me versus mr satan. He's way stronger than me
So this is already not fair
Um, here I go
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. It's oh my god
Okay
He's nowhere to go
He's already going up
He just did jump off
Oh jesus
Jerma, look how far you've come since we've been at all american wrestling good to see a familiar face. Mr satan
Let's show hollywood how we do things
All right, let's go
I want to get all the way up there and I want to power bomb him through 10 or 15 tables
All the way up all the way up all the way up all the way up meet me up here. Mr satan
If you want to fight come up here you want to make this shit happen get up here then don't do that though. That's
Holy shit
Come on up here
Come on
Yeah
This is insane
I want him to go on the other one so bad the one opposite here
Oh, he's got a weapon. He's gonna pipe
Come on up here climb up
You'll get up here eventually. I know you will
He's picking the tables up
You can't
No, I I got I can wait man. I can wait
Go ahead
You do what you need to do
Oh jesus
Don't fall
He's cleaning up the ring. You're right. He's cleaning up. I just see my face
God damn it keep stacking them. Can we can we
Stop no you idiot. Let's stack the tables
Fucked it all up
The whole thing up
I'm gonna have to play against like a moron. God damn it set him as player two. Hold on. He's staying up there
No, what am I doing? I don't want to climb. I wasn't even trying to do that. I'm trying to connect them
I'm not trying to climb
That was a high dive into the ground
It's over adequate
Somebody just said that that's so funny
I want to see if we can stack those two
You know what i'm gonna have to put them out for a minute go through the table
Okay, hold on quit make the ring tiny ring ring size
Teeny teeny teeny age no props 60 tables. No weapons
Inside the ring. Here we go. Jesus. He picked him up. He's picking him up
I swear to god, there's a snoopy game where you have to hold pizzas like this. You can't even see me
He's coming up. Oh my god. He's coming up. Okay. All right. Here it comes. This is the moment. We've all been waiting for
I want him to do I want to do a power bomb to me
Through all of them in a row and that's how I can end the screen
Come on up here. This is it
All the people watching right now, it's just like what did we just watch? Oh, yeah. Yay
This I can't do anymore
That's it. That's it. I'm done. That's the stream is over
Oh, what a wild two days. I don't think I can laugh anymore. I don't think I physically can look the game broke
crashed guys
All right, that's it. Oh last one that's that's it. That's it. That's it. That's it
Yeah, don't worry. I'm gonna show off though
Uh, this is game. This is absolutely like game of the year 2021 so far
It's gonna be very difficult for something to top this
It's gonna be extraordinarily hard to top this I need to climb. All right climb. I'll climb it climb. No, stop it
This one's taller
Oh, this one's not taller
All right, that's it. Oh
That was awesome. What a fun game that that was like a 9.7
That was unbelievably funny and fun. He caught me. Yeah, that was insane
um
so
I'm going to try
potentially so next weekend if uh
If all goes according to plan i'm gonna probably try to do some vr shooting for probably sunday of this coming next weekend
That's the plan. I'm very excited
I'll be using an index for the first time ever
So i'm really excited about it
And let's get that off
Yeah, uh, let me show you auto
I did say there would be an auto portion of this stream at least for a minute
Just so you can see him he's over there. Let me see. Hold on. Uh, he's so cute
So
Let's take a look at auto
I don't even know what I look like right now
Where is he? Otto
Beard. Yeah, I know. I just haven't shaved
I gotta get out of the way. He's doing something cute
Hello, mr. Toe
Hey, what are you doing over there? What are you doing over there? You look like captain america at the dog
Okay, I I am in like a blue like superhero costume, you're right
You're looking skinny
Skinny i'm 100. I like i'm like
10 pounds overweight. I'm literally like 163 pounds. I need to lose like five pounds
You look good guy from lazy town
The guy that does like all the cartwheels. I don't I don't even know what the guy's name is. What's that guy's name?
Sportacus and now that he's woken up now now he wants uh to go eat
There you go, you got to see auto let's do one more little view go over here so they can see you better over here over here
Yeah, well come here
Yes, you're being very cute
He's very cute. He's he's the best dog and now he thinks he's like, okay, we're leaving the room now
He's like, why did you do all that if we're not gonna leave?
He does sneeze that means he's happy
All right, you ready to go
Uh, i'm just gonna let him out here
And let's uh call it. Thank you again everybody for watching. Is it a beard arc? No
No, once it gets to this point, it has to go another day or two and this is going to be very
Scraggly and itchy and annoying. I know I know he's like looking at me like what the hell are you doing?
Uh, yeah, that was wrestling empire on steam
I would highly recommend that you go buy that if you thought it was fun thought it was funny
Is it I mean the game's really fun just as a video game on its own
Forget about all like the crazy shit that you can do
It's a fun wrestling game too. All right, come on. Come here. Come here. He just wants to leave the room
Let's go out of the room
His foot
Grabbed my mouse cord and he just pulled it down. What do you want? What?
You want to go? All right
He's so excited
Yeah, he like ran and my little my mouse cord was underneath here and he went just pulled it and he ran away
Are you gonna do vr with stir?
Something being stir we're talking about we're actually gonna do but just haven't had to find the time to do it
We really want to do the remake the video stream. We already talked about it a few times
And with the remake stuff, it's gonna happen
It just there's a lot of stuff going on to find time to do it
We already talked about like what it would be and what we would do and it sounds actually really fun
But that is going to be the end of this stream
And the end of this weekend
Thanks for sticking around for the whole weekend pretty much
Saturday and sunday here
We'll see you next weekend. Everybody have a great week
for vr
I don't have a plan on what game
it's kind of gonna be like all the other vr streams where I just
Download like 15 vr games and we just play them for like an hour two hours
Let's see what happens
That was a lot of fun. Also, thanks connor for the raid too. Connor dropped a raid. It was either raid or host
I'm not sure which one
But thank you regardless
And onymos gave 10 community subs. Thank you onymos
Get rick and morty vr. I did rick and morty vr as a joke and everybody freaked out and hated me
It was like two or three years ago
People were very upset that I played that for like 30 minutes
Do it again
I'm not gonna play it again
at boneworks
Yeah, I mean
I'll definitely play boneworks. I want to play some stuff that utilizes those knuckle controllers. I heard they're amazing
Play it unironically this time. Oh, yeah
It was a blast. What a fun. What a fun weekend on wrestling empire
I'll see you guys soon. Have a great week. Thanks again
See you soon. Good night
Bye
Take care of yourselves
See you later