Holy shit, Nightbot caught that. I didn't even press the button yet. Nightbot had my tweet come up
before it was pushed through to Twitter. That's kind of odd. Hey, but how are you?
How are you? How are you doing? Good. I'm good too. Hearthstone, are you sure about this?
I bet you didn't fucking think you could see this. It's alright. We actually talked last
night. Hold on, there's a story here. A long one. This will take about 40 seconds. It's a long
story. Okay, you ready? Just making sure you're ready. The story is, people were making fun
of me last night because of how bad I am at the game. We talked about how Hearthstone I
played in bed and they said, you suck. You're so bad. And I was like, fucking, I know.
So I figured it'd be fun if you helped me. So that's what we're gonna do. The new expansion
came up and chat is going to be my smart click lifeline. This is completely, yeah,
this is totally legal backseating. I am at chicken league. I'm going to reach out to
you guys like a bunch of times during games and we're gonna get to rank like 21. That's
all I care about. I just want to get to, I want to get to like rank like 18 or something,
or rank like 22. How hard is that? That's, how can you, can I do that in like a couple hours?
And I want, I wanted to, this is a mistake. It's, it's alright though. Cooking Simulator
was supposed to be today, but unfortunately I got the release date wrong and it comes
up tomorrow. So tomorrow we're going to play Cooking Simulator. I get, I thought it was the 5th,
it's the 6th. I swear to God that the release date changed. It was the 5th, I swear,
but whatever. We're doing it tomorrow. I'm streaming tomorrow too. So
it's releasing tomorrow. Cooking Simulator is tomorrow. Tonight is it going to be,
this is, I'm going to just give you a fair warning. I'm not going to start until I give
you this complete disclaimer. You are going to get frustrated on this stream. You're going
to be mad at me. You're going to yell at me. You're going to call me names and I'm going to
puff my chest out and be like, yeah, right. I'm already mad. No, I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
Here's, I've got smart clicks ready to go. I've got, look at here, I'll show you.
Are you ready? Here's Hearthstone. I got $45. I, yes, I did. I know. Oh, he's going to open
card packs on stream. He is, he, he's a normie. I know you're going to scream. I know that,
I already told you you're going to be mad. I fucking knew it. I told you. I, I saw it.
I could smell it. I had to do this because if we're going to make, you guys are going to
make me a deck. Look at this. I got Arena 2. You don't think I'm ready to go? You guys
are going to pick all this shit and then it's your fault. Don't you understand the long game
I'm playing here? I involve chat picking all these cards so then it doesn't matter if I lose.
Even if I do bad plays, this is your fault, not mine. You know, a, you got to blame the
tools sometimes. And if you guys are the tools, you know, if you give me a, if you give me
a dull hammer, how am I going to use it? I made a dull sword. How am I going to cut through
steel with it? It's not going to happen. All right. And there's also the solo adventure stuff.
I'm ready just to play, but a new expansion came out. I've been playing this in bed.
Let's open the fucking packs just because that's what you're here for. And then everyone's going
to leave and enable the clicking. Well, not right now. What do you need to enable this
for card packs? I got the bundle, which you get 10 of each. I was asking in chat before
the stream started how many of these I was going to need. I thought I was saying three,
but I think I need a hundred, but it doesn't matter. We're going to do,
we're going to, I already have a lot of fucking cards. Let us click the packs.
No, I'm doing it right now. This is like a big deal for me. I've never done this before
on stream. Only 20. Which one do I open first? This one? I'm not going to spend like
a fucking hundred dollars on this game. I'm going to get run out of town here. I'm
going to get so embarrassed on this stream. I'm not going to open this again. You think
I'm going to buy like $200 worth of card packs? Here we go. I better get a legendary.
I just opened up a card pack and got 25 subs. Holy shit. That's what was in here.
KDK945, 20 community subs. I should open more of these. And C4G, thanks for five
community subs. No, thank you. That's a lot. Thank you. Here comes a normie stream.
I'm going to put a disclaimer. I'm going to put a disclaimer on the screen.
Like here comes a normie stream. No, that's, this is a fun fucking game. I mean the game,
you know, what's happening to me right now. I don't know why this is happening,
but it was. All right. We've got, but seriously guys, thank you so much for the subs.
Ooh, look at that. We got blue. Are these good? Oh, I know this is good.
I've seen this one played before. A fight. Let me see. That's 20 more community subs.
This is just trash. 20 more subs from KDK. This is bad. He goes, hey everyone, let me see.
Oh my fucking God. Everyone's giving so, I should play Hearthstone every day.
That's 50 fucking dollars from Great Canadian. Is it this easy? This can't be this easy.
Use it to buy more packs. Thank you Great Canadian for the 50 fucking dollars.
Oh, okay. I'm, this is turning into a normie stream. I'm not supposed to be screaming.
I'm supposed to shut up today. Thanks for five. Oh, I got five subs out of this one.
All right. And I have to be really slow at my card pack opening, right?
Thank you Gnarly for the five subs. This is how you do it, right?
You open up a card pack and you spend like six minutes in here.
All right. What's in that one? I don't care what this is. I'm using it.
Do I have to be a shaman? Can we make an all-frog deck?
Can we be first to legendary with an all-toed deck, all-frog deck?
What class should I be? Okay, here we go. I'm so, I'm so fucking nervous right now.
My heart rate is like fucking 10,000 beats per second.
Captain Hooktusk, summon three pirates from your deck and give them rush.
Is that good? That's pirates. That's not good.
I mean, six through eight mana. This seems not very good.
That's not going to be the only legendary. I got 18 packs left.
What's in this one? Besides five community subs.
KDK five more subs. Oh my god. No, nothing in here.
I can't, I need to like look at these. Does this even matter?
I just, I'm looking for the good cards. Soup?
Soup vendor, whenever you restore three or more health to your hero, draw a card.
Priest? Just use a net deck. Ah, that's no fun.
Another 50 fucking dollars came in right now.
Why is the Hearthstone stream already the most profitable stream I've done
in the last like six weeks and it's been live for 12 minutes?
What? Ten more community subs. The most profitable.
You guys are too hyped. Why is he doing this?
Ow. Ow. I can't laugh. That's 10 more subs. Thank you.
Why is he doing this? There is a reason.
Oh, chicken! This thing sucks. How do you overkill something?
With one, is it good? This one's all right.
He's doing like the Care Bear thing. Oh my god, more subs.
Five more subs from KDK. Oh, come on.
Five more. What was it? 60? I got two of these now.
That's a shitload, KDK. Thank you so much. That's a lot.
Booty Bay Bookie? Give your opponent a coin. That's not bad.
Three, three, two mana. Blood Troll? Five community subs from Soviet.
Thank you. Five, ten, ten community subs.
Opening card packs just gets me subs. 15 subs just came in.
Salad Guy, 10 community subs. Soviet, 19, 21, five community subs.
Come on, no. Epics? KDK, five community subs.
Oh my god. I'm telling you, I told you guys to get fucking hyped.
What was in that one? Five community subs from Carlos was in this one.
Zoro Carlos, thanks a lot.
Tree Speaker. Transform your treants into five, five ancients.
I don't really like Druid. It's a legendary sub.
That looks all right. That's a good card.
Come on, give me another legendary besides that bad one that I got.
Recommend a good whiskey? All right, hack it fast.
Johnny Walker Blue. It's expensive, but it's good.
Or Johnny Walker Black. Johnny Walker Red. Johnny Walker is great, I would say.
Who was this? Destroy? There's eight, man.
Destroy minion costs one less for each minion you control.
You guys are gonna have to help me here.
I like have no fucking idea what I'm doing.
Grim Rally is good. Destroy friendly minion.
Give your minions one, one. All minions? Ever?
Or just like in the hand or on the...
Thank you for the five community subs.
KDK. More community subs.
For each pack opened. Oh, I got a double rare here.
Just play Clash of Clans at this point.
No, you guys, we're gonna win. Do you guys understand?
We are going to collectively win this game.
They'll be writing fucking articles about us.
About how we came together and we got to rank 21.
Together. Scorch.
All right, the person that shot the yellow beam hit this person with the beam.
Is that what's going on?
Oh, we got a new set here.
This is the Amethyst collection.
Oh, fuck yeah, dude. Not even 12 packs.
How many community subs did I get out of these?
And there's another legendary.
Ryman, thanks for five community subs.
This is a stacked pack, I'll tell you.
Screenshot this one.
Five more subs.
We got a rare epic legend.
We got everything.
Five more from Jamie, by the way.
Give me a golden legendary in here.
Five more from Utopia Fox.
I can't fucking believe this is happening.
I was like under the assumption.
Okay, here, before I turned the stream on, I was like, I don't know.
Are people gonna like this?
Oh my God.
KDK, five more.
Utopia Fox five.
I'll be honest, probably not.
But let's see, look, we're just getting piped in the chat.
Hyped.
Pumped up.
Golden.
Boom Reaver.
10 community subs from Frisky Moose.
And 50 fucking dollars.
What is happening?
What did this, what happened?
This 50 just came in.
Some guy.
50 dollars.
I'm broke now.
Don't be broke by giving me that, please.
Don't go broke.
But Travel Boy, five community subs.
Frisky Moose, 10 community subs.
Adventure MF Dan.
Am I gonna, are you gonna,
am I gonna go into like retirement here?
Travel Boy, five.
What, is this good?
Summon a copy of a minion in your deck, give it rush.
This is a boomer card?
That doesn't make any fucking sense.
This game came out like six years ago.
What?
That looks pretty good.
Oh my fucking God, guys.
There's even more.
Basic Feral, 10.
Invader, Invader Lurr, five.
Hearthstone.
Golden Rare, mad summoner.
Fill each player's board with imps.
Fucking pretty cool.
Magic Trip, discover a spell that costs three or less.
That's kind of cool.
Not stopping till over three K subs.
Like this stream?
Give me another legendary.
You know what, okay, like 20 community subs.
20 community subs in KDK.
Somewhere right now, there is a doctor
who is watching this stream on his lunch break
and he is furious.
Somewhere, somewhere, there is like a business owner
that is watching this stream
and he just had to serve like 30 customers
and like he's sweating
and like he's got like four employees
that really do it.
They got like the bank.
They got to pay their debt down
and then the guy opens up the stream
and I'm making hundreds of dollars
opening up card packs.
Somewhere there's a doctor
who just saved somebody's goddamn life
and he's like, what the hell?
I got to get on this opening Hearthstone card packs thing.
Fuck this, I'm quitting being a doctor.
Give him some of your money.
No, it's mine.
It's my money.
Sorry.
Fuck, ow.
That was weird.
My like head hurts.
Five more community subs, 50 more dollars.
100 fucking dollars.
You fucking kidding me, you guys.
What is happening today?
Some of you guys like hit the lottery.
It's getting to his head.
Uh, 50 dollars for phylactery lich.
50 bucks.
The doctor isn't funny though.
I'm just, I don't know.
I really do appreciate it.
Thank you.
Stream sucks from 1914.
Thanks for 50 dollars.
I opened him in the wrong order.
I'm fucking delete the stream.
I'm never coming back.
Shadowy figure, transform into a 2-2 copy.
Trash.
Bye, thanks for the stream.
Ooh, another golden.
50 dollars.
Press space bar.
No, because that opens it all immediately.
I like to drag it over like it's in my hand.
What's a good card?
This.
The lackeys are good, right?
Bala koala, 50 dollars.
I've never played Hearthstone.
I just want to fit in.
Uh, get like another 50 packs.
I'm not doing that.
Boo, boo.
Boo, you got to click on the screen and help me win games.
He's gone full normie mode.
Alert.
Normie levels are rising.
We got to get him to like click on like people puking on YouTube before he gets to normie.
This stuff sucks.
Ray of frost.
All right, twin spell.
That means so you can cast it twice.
So twin spell is just echo for spells.
I need a reaction face cam.
No, I'm not doing that.
Ray of frost.
This is this is kind of good.
Freeze a minion.
It's very frozen to one mana.
I I'm not.
No, I'm not.
I can't put a webcam on.
I physically can't turn it on.
I will get banned from Twitch.
I got three fucking legendaries.
I haven't.
Okay, you know what?
This is really has to be waited.
You know what I'm saying?
There's no way I haven't like opened.
I haven't bought card packs in probably three to four years.
Maybe.
I mean, this has got to be like Diablo three when you didn't play for long enough.
They just gave you legendaries, right?
We go.
Let's play some fucking hype music.
Like, what's that?
What's that one that everybody always says to play?
Fucking who cares?
Is any good?
Add a copy of each of the battle cry minion.
Now he's turning into a YouTuber.
That's a lot of dust.
Five, four, five.
Add a copy of each of the best.
The game's gotten so confusing.
Battle cry.
Add a copy of each of your battle cry minions to your like.
What have I happened to like the two, three alligator and like deal two damage?
This is too much for me.
That was in 2015.
Double rare.
Destroy minions, summon two minions at the same cost to replace it.
You guys are going to just fucking have to help me here.
Look at this one.
Death destroy.
This looks, this is really good.
This is like the best card I think I've ever seen.
There's a two, six taunt that when it's destroyed, it kills a random minion.
This is like the best card in the whole game.
Is it, am I, is this correct?
Is this the best card in the game?
Because it has to be.
If there are better cards than this, the power creep has gotten too much.
Yeah, yeah.
You're asking chat for, of course I'm asking chat for advice
because I'm going to be having click maps on this whole time.
And just, we're going to make our arena deck too.
Last pack.
Come on, give me your energy.
Give me your energy.
Legendary, legendary, legendary, legendary, legendary.
Whenever you play a one cost minion, draw a spell from your deck.
Cool.
I don't feel complete though.
I like feel like I don't feel, was it connection interrupted?
What the hell did that say?
What was that?
More packs.
I'm not buying more packs.
Try get another pack.
How much is one pack?
No, no, no, no.
Let me make, hold on.
No, I'm not just sitting here and make opening fucking cards.
Can't you, you know, you can get packs.
By the way, don't look at this because this is like from 2013.
And Boo played like 600 of these games.
Like Boo like played these games for me.
I swear to God, that's for real.
See, look, I can get like money.
All right, you guys ready?
We're not doing this yet.
I'm not, no, Boo's really good.
Boo was like legend.
Boo got to legend like at least twice or something.
He's really good.
So I have it, I have this queued up.
You've been waiting a long time for this.
I know you desperately want to click on the screen.
You want to spam the screen.
It's time for you guys to pick fucking hero back.
Why would I click back?
Those votes are not being counted.
Straight from opening decks to building decks.
I got to milk it.
You know what I mean?
Garrosh is hot.
Like as in he's really good.
All right, let's go.
That's by a pretty overwhelming majority at this point.
It's going to be warrior.
Now what?
See, I'm thinking, I'm thinking,
I'm not going to tell you what I think.
Why are you clicking down here?
Stop clicking down here.
I'm not going to click this.
I'm going to refer, this sucks.
This sucked back in 2013.
You don't want to do this.
This looks fun.
I'm wrong.
Actually wrong.
Okay.
If I were me, actually, I don't know.
I don't know what I would do for me.
You guys are too split here.
Don't click this.
This is going to take so long.
All right, we're going to, no.
It's going to happen real quick.
Divine shield.
Let's go.
By the way, I'm going to pick the next five cards.
Pick right.
Wow.
28, 28, 28.
Holy shit.
Gain five armor, draw a card.
You guys sure?
Are you sure?
Shield block?
Okay.
Each player gets a two, three weapon and six armor.
You're holding a spell that costs five more to four damage.
It's a seven, seven dragon.
Don't you have to pay to play in this game mode?
Yes.
Or you just use coins.
All right, we're going to go weapons project.
This is going to take like an hour.
This is going to be worth it.
I click on the pretty cards.
Horse rider?
You know, what about the guy?
Look, you guys aren't going to want to click the guy getting zapped?
Deal.
One damn statement.
If it survives, add a lackey.
That's awesome.
That's so cool.
This is boring.
It's just a two, one attack.
Fine.
Another 50 fucking dollars came in.
50 dollars from some guy.
Some guy nine.
More packs plus doom OST or fucking riot.
Golden force tank.
Oh, nice.
I agree.
I would have picked that one too.
It's riot time.
I'm not doing 50 dollars in card packs.
Gain four.
Yep.
Definitely.
You guys are smart.
I'm not going to do 50 dollars in card packs.
That's going to take like 40 minutes.
Oh, it kind of juries out on this one.
Has plus one attack while damage.
And then, I mean, always knife juggler, right?
All right, we're almost a third of the way there.
Okay, I'm going to pick after this,
I'm going to pick the next five cards.
And you guys are going to have to work with what I pick because I'm not,
this is, this is taking like, no, what do you mean no?
Just open packs until people stop donating.
Mechanically, yeah, he's really good.
I remember, who told me that?
This one, I don't even need your guy's opinion on this.
It's always this one, right?
Always.
Every single time, right?
This is the one that goes, and then has like 40 damage, right?
Yeah, I like this one because it's just going like,
see, I just said that, now everyone's clicking on it.
Armorsmith, two more seconds.
Two, one, okay, come on.
Come on, give me a good one.
Make me a good deck, guys.
This deck looks awful, by the way.
Terrible, you failed.
Oh, look at this one.
I had to click that one, look at it.
Okay, your turn.
Wow, so cool.
Hearthstone's so cool.
Open more packs.
Dumbass.
All right, this shuffle a bomb into your opponent's deck,
when yeah, this one's cool.
You guys are dealing with a toddler right now, you understand?
Like, if I see something that I think is cool,
I mean, I'm about to click it.
I'm close to clicking this just because of this.
All right, each player gets two, three weapons, six armor.
Each player?
Why would I want to give somebody some six armor
and a two, three weapon to the other player?
I don't want to give that person anything so I can destroy them.
I'm not clicking back.
We have to make with complete this.
I'm not going to get halfway through and then not do this.
I mean, I'm pretty biased on this one.
This is an original card.
Yeah, I agree.
Some of you guys are really smart.
No epics or legendaries or anything?
How many rares have we even seen?
One?
These votes are not counted.
Five more community subs from Austin Atlantis.
Thank you so much for the five community subs.
Steel?
I thought this was the worst card in the game.
Play single player?
I am, don't worry.
This ain't going to be like a two-hour long stream.
This is going to be a long one.
This is going to be at least three hours.
I'm kidding.
It's going to be like eight.
Okay.
Guys, you got to make me the deck first before you do anything.
Hopefully these cards are good.
We have too many two and three drops.
My whole deck is going to be two drops.
Give your weapon plus one attack?
Am I going to even beat one person with this?
Two drop OP in Arena.
Is it?
More shield block?
Not the like ninja turtle enemy?
All right.
You have bad two drops.
Do I even have any taunts?
No, I don't.
I think this is the only taunt card that's showed up.
I have a really bad mana curve.
All right, we're getting close.
Final ten here.
Mad bomber.
Big clicks coming in on giggling inventor.
This is going to be...
I got to weight this one up.
Inventor sucks?
That's okay.
I didn't even look at the mana.
I thought this was like a two or three drop card.
It's seven fucking mana?
That's two.
That's kind of not good.
It used to be five.
It got nerfed.
Well, here we go.
All right.
That's how good it is.
Oh, I see.
Three mana, four, five.
Okay, Jerma.
Someone has seven, seven mechanical dragon.
Okay.
Anoyotron is like, is the best, all right?
I'm about to click it.
Just so I can hear him do his voice line.
Snake Jupiter?
All right, here we go.
Oh, yeah.
This is the best card in a ring up.
Behold the might of storm.
Storm, storm wind.
I got it.
Here we go.
You must have to sing when you do these cards.
Ah, ah, another zoo.
I got rid of two zoos.
Fine.
Who clicked that?
Gain four armor.
Someone ran a four cost minion.
That's pretty good.
I don't have any zero or one drops and I have no late game.
Can I get any cards?
I need some like epics and some legendaries.
Two ironforged portals.
Can we make it three ironforged portals?
Armorsmith.
All right.
Crowd favorite.
Whenever you play a card with battlecry, gain plus one, one.
Oh, look.
A one drop.
At least I'll have something to play.
All right.
Only two more.
We're almost done.
Rarity does not mean good.
Yeah, that's true.
Another one drop.
They hurt us.
All right.
What do we got?
Omega Devastator.
If you have 10 mana crystals, deal 10 damage to a minion.
Super Collider.
After you attack a minion, force it to attack one of its neighbors.
What?
That's like unfair.
All right.
I'm ready.
Let's try one.
Let's try two.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
I'm ready to go.
What do you guys think?
Hold on.
Let me just make sure this is...
Is this working?
All right, there we go.
Okay.
All right, let's go.
Oh, wait.
It's not on.
Is it on screen?
Oh, by the way, for all the stream snipers, get fucked.
Get it off.
Oh, shit.
What?
That's my name.
I don't want anybody to see that.
I will.
All right, here we go.
I don't need any help this game.
Ready?
Bang.
Hold this.
Oh, I got a one drop right off the bat.
Cover up your name.
Why?
Come on.
Let's go.
Cover your name.
Why?
What's wrong?
People know that's my name.
Oh, he got a legendary.
He automatically wins.
All right.
So he's got a golden portrait, too.
This means that he plays.
When does this minion take damage?
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
What?
I got roped off.
Hold on.
I want to get roped.
I was like five seconds.
That just like hurt me.
Oh, what the fuck do I do?
The rope is early.
Each player equips two, three weapon and gains six armor.
And then I'm going to hit him.
Pretty good play.
What do you mean order?
What?
What is this one?
Shuffle the bomb into your opponent's neck.
When drawn, it explodes for five damage.
That's not bad.
You're B.M.ing this person.
No, I'm not.
What are you talking about?
Add two 4-4 dragons to your hand.
Okay.
Well, you can see.
All right.
Help me.
What do you want me to do?
Quick, quick.
I don't have much time.
What are you clicking on?
This is not going to work.
Are you serious?
There's no way you play the game.
I told you that I was not going to.
I just go back to the single player.
Okay.
Actually, I just do this.
I'm just going to portal up.
Come on.
That sucks.
He's just going to kill that right now.
People are coming and expecting good Hearthstone gameplay.
I'm going to have to make a disclaimer.
He's got good cards.
All right.
Well, I'm going to kill that.
And then I'm going to mad bomber first.
Well, now, wait a minute.
Hold on here.
Wait a minute.
Super Collider.
Kill the dragon.
Oh, check this shit up.
Hit this.
Okay.
I'm going to kill this guy.
I'm going to hit this guy.
I'm going to kill the dragon.
Bingo.
Oh, fuck.
I forgot.
Okay.
I thought I just did the damage that he...
I got it.
What?
I don't have one of those.
All right.
I'm going to mad bomber and annoy-a-tron.
Or I could mechanical whelp and annoy-a-tron.
No.
Mad bomber, annoy-a-tron.
I just have to last.
I have no draw either.
Is this my serious boomer tactics?
Guys, I'm not even going to look at this chat anymore.
What do you mean attack him?
No.
What?
I can...
Now I'm going to attack Illidan because he's going to kill two people.
Okay.
Watch this shit.
He's going to kill both these people.
Let me see.
Divine Charge.
Hold on.
I could do...
Wait.
It doesn't hit both people?
Force attack one of its neighbors.
Oh, fuck.
Well, here comes the RNG.
Ready?
Check this out.
Left.
Yes.
Oh, what was that?
A secret?
Doesn't matter.
Okay.
I got to settle down.
Guaranteed victory.
Guaranteed.
No, that's not good.
Your deck sucks and you're bald.
All right.
Here we go.
Ready?
Whack into this guy.
They've been kind to me before.
They'll be kind to me again.
Let me see.
I could go right in the middle here.
I'm not going to rope him.
I'm just trying to...
I'm trying.
It's like...
Holy shit.
I forgot that comes out.
I'm in a good position.
This guy has two legendaries in his fucking deck.
Is that even possible?
Oh, get out of here.
I can't...
Do I just get rid of these?
I'm still all right.
I mean, he has more cards, but he's going to melt down?
No, I'm about to freeze up.
What are you going to do?
I'm going right...
Better write this down.
Don't matter.
He's on the ropes.
No, I'm going right to the face.
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me.
You got to rush me down here.
Hammer the face with one damage?
Why would I do that?
This guy's got amazing cards.
I'm going to have to hit this.
So, I mean...
RNG.
Here we go.
It's going to hit him.
It's going to do it.
I almost busted that up.
All right.
Here we go.
I need to get people out here.
It's not over.
I'm going to top deck something.
He had two legendaries.
Remember that.
Three legendaries.
He had three legendaries.
How do you even get three legendaries in a Reno?
My whole deck is two drops.
It's all right.
Here we go.
Top deck.
That's the best one.
You guys got mad at me for picking this.
Give a friendly demon one...
It's over.
Concede?
I don't concede.
They have to earn it.
No, it's well played.
Thanks.
It's all right.
That was unfair.
Unfair.
Here we go.
Your deck sucks.
What am I doing?
I'm pretending to click the button so I can avoid stream snipers.
All right.
This is a better start.
Dump it all.
Does it matter?
No, not really.
Who cares?
Told you to dump it all.
Look at that.
I got a good start here.
And I get the coin.
Coin Anoyotron.
First thing.
Oh, I got a Rager too.
Maybe just delete that from the game.
It's like too easy to hurt people.
All right.
Now look.
We got options here.
All right.
So like Anoyotron or Armor Up.
I'm going to say Anoyotron.
On the ropes here.
What do you got?
Draw a mech from your deck.
I think this is a coin Rager opportunity here.
Oh, no.
This is not a coin Rager.
This is a divine shield charge horse rider.
Or it's a Rager.
Just get rid of it.
Coin Rager.
Did I do that wrong?
That was that wrong?
That wasn't wrong, right?
Well, what would you do in this scenario?
Quick, quickly.
I don't have much time.
I'm not going to click end turn.
All right.
Okay.
I see what you guys want me to do.
I see it.
14%.
18% want me to do.
Okay.
Got it.
What?
I had to get...
I don't want...
It's a hunter.
Hunters have tons of minions.
You missed the lethal.
Let's go get those card packs.
I'm good at that.
I'm good at doing that.
Well, here's a mech, right?
It's in this...
Give a random friendly beast dragon and murloc.
Plus I don't...
I only have...
I have a beast.
Do the weapon here.
That's not bad.
Yeah, pretty good.
You're delaying the stream.
What if you're getting stream sniped?
I mean, everybody...
If you...
Okay.
If you were stream sniping, you watched me build the deck.
So you already know all my cards anyway.
It don't matter.
Let's see.
What do I got here?
That's not a bad idea.
Just go for it.
Four cost minion.
I think that's what I'm going to do.
Come on, something big.
That's...
All right.
I'm okay with that.
That's pretty good.
God damn it.
There's the reaper.
Reaper.
I'm just going to reaper.
Time to reap.
Oh, come on.
Three, six.
What is that thing?
Your death arrows trigger twice.
I think I got to get out the force tank.
No.
Taunt and kill the dark iron dwarf.
Taunt and kill the dwarf.
And then get some armor.
Hey, it's all right.
When you get to 0-2, you play all the other chumps that are 0-2, right?
And then they go face with their spells.
You are the chump.
I'm not saying I'm not the chump.
I'm just saying I'll go up against...
If you're 0-2, we're in the 0-2 chump class.
I don't really have any options.
I don't have any options.
Bottom right is the best option.
He's thinking.
He's thinking right now.
He's not sure what to do.
This thing has been here the whole game.
Well, I can't get rid of it.
I don't have any way to get rid of it.
Smart click doesn't work because people just click everywhere and it confuses me.
I'm still in this.
Oh, what a godsend.
Mad bomber weapons project.
Oh, fuck.
I can do this.
Whatever.
Don't matter.
God damn it.
I'm going to go 0-3 and then uninstall the game.
This is not a meltdown.
This is not...
What the fuck?
It's not a meltdown unless I say it is.
You know, let's just...
He's probably like, holy fuck, I didn't know he had that many.
This deck is not very good.
Look at this deck.
What is this deck?
I got three legendaries in the first game.
I haven't played this game in like four years.
Got three legendaries in the first game.
Second game, I made a little bit of an oops.
You know, I did it...
I accidentally did a little oops and then it cost me the game.
That's what happens.
All right, it's your guys' turn.
You got to pull me out of 0-3 here.
What happened to cooking simulator?
It's not out.
It releases tomorrow.
I got the date wrong.
So I was supposed to do that today.
Let's just dump everything here.
Add another oopsie to the pile.
All right, it's your turn.
Whatever the highest percentage is, is what I'm doing.
And you got to be quick.
And we have one turn for you to figure it out.
Okay, go.
Nice job.
Nice thinking.
Okay, go.
Why would you end turn again?
No, I'm not going to fucking end turn again.
Is that what you were clicking on?
I think that's what you were clicking on.
And then you want me to hit, right?
Yes, you do.
Funny man bad at card games.
It's just like...
It's just too much for me to have to do.
Like, I can't do this on stream.
I just can't.
When I sit there with my fucking mouth open in my bed,
it doesn't matter.
I just play whatever I'm going to play.
I can't.
I'm gonna.
The stream's not over.
You know what?
I'm doing this.
I'm doing this on my own.
I'm going to win.
I'm not going to look at the chat.
Are you ready for this?
I'm not going to look.
I know there's going to be people that have dissenting opinions.
Oh, I'm going to beat this.
Check this out.
I already got it.
I already know Flynn.
This is a fun game.
It is.
This is just a warm-up game.
All right.
I'm going to be quiet.
See, that's why I did that.
That's the reason why I did that.
Because now he had to kill that minion on this character.
That's why I did that.
I need to explain myself.
You guys know the fucking strategies.
But I have seven, seven, four.
No, I can't.
I hate doing this.
I fucking hate attacking and dying into nothing.
It's fine.
And then I can do.
All right.
I can take care of this.
See, make him do it.
This is bad.
This is not good.
Gain five armor draw.
I can draw, but this is not going to do anything.
Just drop every card.
Worst deck ever.
Oh, damn it.
I don't have a coin.
I don't want to put this down.
Just buy more packs.
Is this arena?
This is arena.
This is the first thing I'm playing.
After four years of not playing against another human being in this game,
I decided that I was going to play arena and have Twitch pick the cards
and they gave me fucking shitty cards on purpose for like a joke.
I'm going to go 0-3.
Fucking on stream.
I can't go 0-3.
I'm going to go 0-3.
No, I'm not.
It's not bad.
And then Berserker.
Damn it.
Right when I have an opportunity to like pull this back.
Does this deck just suck or am I like
the stupidest Hearthstone player on Twitch?
I can't go 0-3.
No, it can't start like this.
I'm just going to go play with the funny cards in single player mode.
Nothing even matters.
Whatever.
Thanks for the extra damage.
It's not going to do anything for me.
I don't even need to do that.
I'm just going to go to the funny cards after this.
I got like the extension for this.
Let's go.
No, it's because it's because we got bad calls.
We got bad draw from the arena choice.
We went to arena first.
Don't let the sour your opinion of me.
Nice.
Do you even get a key or do they send you like home?
Do they send you home with like a needs improvement?
Have your parents sign the report card?
Piece of paper.
Oh, I got a card pack out of that.
Nice.
Come on, give me something like pity legendaries.
Two rares.
Well, let's start with arena.
I shouldn't have started with arena.
Arena is like people are very good at it.
They play it and they one of those guys had the gold characters,
which means he has like 5,000 wins.
I didn't even look at the cards that I opened.
I played these are fun.
I've done these already.
I'm going to do the solo thing.
See, I've been doing this.
It's fun because this you don't have to pay cards.
They just do it for you.
It's great.
Heroic or I can't do heroic.
Heroic.
I can't do that.
Baby mode.
Let me just see if I have the confidence to be able to play this game.
I've already done it a bunch.
I'll let you pick this.
If you don't know what this is, it's a lot of fun.
Okay.
I started with arena and what a mistake that was.
Who should I play?
I got to build my confidence back up.
I hate fun.
Oh, also another funny little tidbit here of information.
You know how I said that cooking simulator launches tomorrow.
I thought it launched today.
Well, I was under the assumption that the new week was today,
but that's also apparently tomorrow too.
I thought this was going to be open today.
It's tomorrow.
Week four is tomorrow.
Yeah, fourth week of like the new part of the adventure.
We're going to do rogue.
Tomorrow at 10 a.m.
You're going to do an early stream.
No, I'm doing cooking simulator tomorrow.
Because I've fucking beaten 19 people.
See, I've done this.
This is my number.
All right, which one?
The dagger, the random card from another class,
or two damage to an undamaged minion.
You've only done 19.
Don't be mean to me.
I just play this in bed.
Okay, we'll do that one.
And which deck would you like to do?
We don't have to pick on this one.
Random, a random deck.
All right, that's the way it's going to be.
Let's go.
So it's kind of like a rogue-like.
You start at the beginning and you fight bosses.
It's eight bosses.
If they go down, you complete the run.
If you don't, if you lose,
you have to go back to the very beginning.
You get upgrades along the...
Fine, we'll just go.
For a second, I was about to play this,
but nobody can scream snipe me.
You know, okay, I'll give you...
If I was in bed right now, this would be...
I wouldn't even mind.
It doesn't matter.
I would just be like,
oh, I want to shoot this thing.
I want to play with this one.
There are 3,600 people in my bed and I don't like it.
You know, I feel like this is my bedtime thing.
All right, so every single
turn, we're going to do a, you know,
equivalent exchange.
Swap a random card in each player's hand.
This is just clown shit.
It doesn't matter.
So who cares?
See, like this is just clown shit.
It doesn't matter.
Nobody can like say it was a bad move
because like that was...
What am I supposed to do about that?
I can't stop that.
Draw a card that has Deathrattle cast.
This again.
I don't think I even have any Deathrattle cards.
Let's just steal something.
See, look, it's a total just dog shit mode.
I'm not supposed to have this.
Click the funny sound buttons.
Okay.
I don't have any Deathrattle cards.
We need to...
Okay, we need to pick Deathrattle cards
because they can't even attack.
I'm just gonna steal another card.
What does this do?
Four health to each hero.
I don't have any silences either.
Give me another one.
Give all dragons into our hand.
Three, three.
If I had a dragon, that'd be fucking incredible.
All right, let's get some board here.
Just to get it out there.
I mean, it can't attack
but the computer's stupid
so the computer will probably like attack it.
And there's the shark.
Eat a minion in your deck
and it gains its stats.
Add it to your hand if it dies.
Look, the computer is like as dumb as me.
Pack opening.
Waiting room.
All right, we got some cool here.
Uh, this deck is so bad.
Deal two damage.
Give your C'Thun to...
I don't even fucking have a C'Thun.
I think I should put out the...
Add a random potion to your hand.
Lethal, I can't attack with this.
Deal five damage to all characters.
Well, let's just do...
Minus three attack this turn.
I just did that.
All right, now we're gonna do shark.
Five damage to all characters.
No, I don't wanna do that.
Deal one damage to all other minions.
I mean, I think I'm gonna do shark.
No, let's do shark.
I don't have any more minions.
I only have one card.
Fucking God.
All right, it's time to win.
So that's five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I win.
I beat level one on normal.
Okay.
What treasure do you want me to pick?
Should I pick, like, give me advice?
Don't click that one.
That one is so stupid.
Don't do that.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna lose in the last...
If I get far enough.
Look at how good these other ones are.
All right, I need to...
What box?
What creature box am I gonna do?
I don't even...
What the hell?
What are we...
It's such a random amount of cards.
It actually just truly is random nonsense.
Cold blood three times.
These guys are just trying to give it a lose.
Four, I guess, like...
Four, eight...
Do you have a weapon?
I don't even think I have a weapon.
All right, coming up next is...
What?
We have to do...
We have to fight Wendy again.
Uh-huh.
This is the same thing?
It's the same...
Oh, no.
Uh, yeah.
Game one, one for each other.
Pirate yet?
Well, I don't have any other pirates.
Oh, Wendy stream sniped me.
All right, give helpful advice.
What?
Wait, why did I just get these?
That's not advice.
That's cheating.
Cheating is advice.
No, it's not.
How many of these do I...
I can't even play these.
I have to, like, get a fucking minion out here.
Well, I'll be able to do all kinds of fun stuff.
Divine Shield, draw a card.
I mean, should I just give him a fucking shitload?
I think I'm going to do Divine Shield,
or should I do Prep and then...
Prep double cold blood.
See, this is what...
This is...
I like this.
No pressure.
No stream snipers.
Um, I don't fucking have deathrattle.
Yes, I do, I guess.
Yeah, beat it.
Restore 12 health through a friendly character.
This is our town, Scruff.
Yeah, beat it.
I'm sure...
Okay, if you could...
If you could friendly fire,
I would have just killed myself.
Deal one day and hold...
Let me look at these.
Divine Shield, magnetic rush.
Let me see.
What do we got here?
Didn't even need anybody's help.
Yes, I'm a newbie.
I know that.
I'm aware of that.
I'm so fucking good.
All right, pick a box.
You're doing really good.
Carried by Khadgar.
That's fine.
More combo.
Deal two damage.
Summon a Jade Golem.
An evil miscrant.
Add two random lackeys.
All right.
Who's next?
Soothe saver Zoe.
At the start of your turn,
restore two health to all friendly minions.
That's fucking insane.
How are we ever going to be able to beat this?
Did you just mute Dr. Boom?
That's not Dr. Boom.
All right, I want...
I mean, that's...
Two damage is two damage.
By the way, if you're curious,
everybody's attack and health have swapped.
You probably already knew that.
Let me keep this.
All right, Khadgar.
Give me some more free shit.
Is there any circumstance
where you would ever play this card?
Yes, there is.
What the fuck is the scenario?
Draw the rest of your deck.
Let me adjust the cost of that for you.
I mean, that didn't really help, but thanks.
Silver hand recruit you control.
If you have an empty hand and 10 cards left.
Yeah, I guess.
I guess it is just a huge draw,
but so many crazy things that they've added.
Well, here's the two damage.
Causes zero.
Okay, what do we got?
I got some damage here.
Deal two damage.
Oh, no, I can't do that.
I could do...
I could do this.
What's more important?
Oh, I don't know.
This is all combos.
Two damage into bandit into hit or two damage into...
That works.
One into two into three into one into two.
How many fingers do you see?
Oh, I hate combo cards.
Because I like...
It's too many...
It's too many problems to deal with.
It's too many, like, chains.
All right, so that's two, three, four.
Or we could do two and then three.
It could be you.
It's going to be you.
I'm not going to draw my whole deck.
Here's what we're going to do.
You ready?
Add a toxin to your hand.
Nice.
Plus one attack and rush.
Discover a spell.
Now you draw a card and then...
I got three draw.
I'm not going to draw the rest of the deck.
That's going to kill me.
I'm going to start taking fatigue damage.
One attack, let's say it will be...
Here's what I'm going to do.
Oh, that's nice.
You shouldn't have cleared.
Well, that was scary.
Okay, now he's...
Look, what are you going to do?
This is...
I can take care of this.
Set the attack of all minions to one.
Preparation.
Find shield.
Let's see.
So everyone has one attack.
And that's not going to help.
Prep and draw the deck.
Are you happy?
Do I have lethal?
Hold on.
That's four, eight.
Cold blood.
So let me see.
Hold on.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Do I have lethal?
Eight, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty...
I got lethal.
Holy shit, a ton of subs just came in.
I don't have lethal!
Why did I just think I had lethal?
Why did somebody tell me I had lethal?
I'm not supposed to be looking at the chat room.
Oh, god damn it.
It's all right, I'm going to win.
Uh, twenty community subs just came in.
Thank you for the twenty community subs.
Great Canadian fuck club.
Thank you so much.
Oh, no.
Oh, this is perfect.
What are you gonna do about that?
Ow!
Big brain, big brain, big brain.
Oh, nice card you got.
I've never played this game before.
I have no idea what the fuck is happening.
Well, I can probably join that boat with you.
But anyways, the great Canadian brick club Cersei gave.
That's a lot of money.
Thank you for the twenty community subs.
There was also fifty dollars earlier from Toxray.
Thank you for the fifty fucking dollars.
And they said, play against Stirr at least once.
No, he plays this game all the time.
That would be a mistake.
Which one?
Master Scheme Super Simeon Sphere and Flyby.
Shuffle a Kaboom bot into your opponent's deck when joined.
It explodes for a fit.
So you just instantly kill somebody.
If they draw that, you just win.
That seems, I mean, that seems pretty cool.
This is cool.
Summon King Moogle.
I give it immune and can't be targeted by spells and hero powers.
Seems like the indecisive some of you guys.
But gonna have to click on the one that has the most votes.
What just happened?
Oh, God damn it.
We have to do this again.
For some reason, it reset itself.
Anybody could click it an infinite amount of times.
You ready?
Here it comes.
This one's for real.
I looked over, there was like ten thousand clicks.
People were just like, maybe I'll press that.
Maybe I'll press this one.
Super Simeon Sphere is looks like it's gonna win.
That is the one you get.
Don't worry, don't go anywhere.
You get to pick again.
I don't want more combo card.
There's like a legendary over here.
How many cold bloods am I gonna have?
All right.
Eviscerate, cold blood, and then Vile Spine slowly destroy a minion for combo.
I guess we can take it.
Oh, this is this thing, right?
So this is a friendly encounter.
We get to pick something or change something.
You guys can pick this too.
You get to modify the deck.
Let's see.
All right.
So we got the shark, the Disciple of C'thun, the skater bot, and the Vile Spine.
And then these up here.
Lotus Agents, Malygos, and Lower Walker Cho.
Choose a friendly minion that always starts in your hand.
So I can get one of these to always be in the hand.
Discover a legendary and add it to the deck.
Or look at four spells from your deck and reduce the cost by one of their cost by three for the whole run.
Always have the shark or all add everybody and give them all one one.
Which one do you want me to do?
I can do two of these.
Well, the ones that cost.
I don't think this is going to work without a zoom in.
Yeah, I don't think this is going to work without me zooming in.
Hold on just a second here.
Try it again.
Add all or choose a friendly minion and remove it from the deck.
Looks like we're going to do this one.
Add all these enemy minions and give them all plus one plus one.
Here we go.
Okay.
Now what?
What should I do now?
Discover a legendary.
People want me to get rid of...
What do you want me to get rid of?
Let's discover a legendary.
I mean, everyone's going to want me to do that.
Of course.
Why?
You know, why the heck not?
Well, you can't go wrong with that one.
They're a regular.
Okay.
Let's zoom out for a second.
Can you zoom out, please?
Tack, gnaws, whisker, ysera, or mogre the ogre.
Mogre the ogre is terrible.
Nobody wants tack.
Not one person.
All right, ysera.
Anything else you guys would like me to do or is time to end?
Remember, if you click down there,
there's only one thing I can do.
Dismiss.
All right.
Dismiss?
Who would you like me to dismiss?
Thank you, Dora.
Oh, fuck.
Hold on.
No.
Oops.
Do it again.
Skaterbot.
Disciple Cthulhu and the shark.
Dismiss the shark.
Skaterbot.
Okay.
Interesting choice.
I'm not sure I would have done that.
Get him out of here.
Let's go.
That's what you say, Jerma.
That's why you're chicken league.
But you can't stay here.
Because you suck.
But it's still fun.
Okay, so this lady.
Both players summon a minion from their deck and they fight.
Pretty cool.
Why are we trying to win?
I don't know, because sometimes winning is fun.
I do have both of those dragons.
13-5 because they're swapped.
You can't hold them, ysera.
No, that's not how it goes.
You can't hold on to a nine cost.
You gotta get somebody in here.
No, I can't.
I gotta get rid of...
No, I can't do that.
Not this early.
I need, like, a minion.
Hold it or die.
Wow.
That was...
There we go.
There's Cho.
Immediately play Cho.
A 5-1 Lorewalker Cho.
Thank god I did the 1-1.
Otherwise he would just be dead.
He wouldn't be able to play him.
Perfect.
Let's go.
I'll take it.
He's immediately dead.
Okay.
So, um, I could do that to him.
Or I could do...
Maybe I should just put out...
No.
Just combo, eviscerate.
I could just...
Yeah, I could.
Yeah, fuck it.
Wait.
Yeah.
Check this out.
What the hell was that?
What just happened?
She played her thing in two...
Okay.
Oh, deal three damage to all minions is the thing that plays.
Okay, that was all over the place.
All right.
Let's go with...
I'm just gonna steal and then put out this monkey.
That's...
I can handle that.
Don't worry.
Two damage.
Oh.
Holy shit.
Are you serious?
Wow.
All right.
Hold on.
That's a lot of damage.
Go for face or do I...
Let me see.
Hold on.
Deal two damage to a friendly character.
Discover a demon.
Let's get this out here.
Oh, you're screwed.
I'm gonna make you draw your whole deck.
I think I have lethal.
Yeah, I do.
Three.
Yeah, I got lethal.
It's just fun to do this.
I'm V...
I am V-aiming.
That's fine.
Pretty good.
In there.
See, aren't you guys having fun?
It's fun just to play these little games.
Who says no?
Remove them.
Oh, what do you think?
Should I get two more eviscerates?
There are too many to ban.
They're rising up.
It's the mutiny.
It's this stream.
That's a lot of vanquish.
And we get a Sneeds too.
That's pretty good.
I agree.
Uh, passive hero power.
You choose one cards and powers have both effects combined.
What's going on here?
So how much more difficult is heroic from here?
It's really, really hard, right?
I don't think I can handle that.
It's baby mode.
Heroic is very easy and much harder than this.
What does that mean?
What?
Uh, let's just get a minion out.
No!
May as well just concede.
It's like you were saying last night.
This is baby mode Captain Crunch Hearthstone.
But that's all right.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Um, I think I have to just get rid of this.
Preparation into...
Oh, yeah.
Preparation into Jade Shuriken.
Preparation draw deck.
I'm not doing that.
I couldn't even do that.
Ooh, okay, hold on.
No, nope, nope.
Um, no.
Corrupt every minion.
Destroy them at the start of your next turn.
Oh, I can't.
Why would I do that right now?
Destroy them at the start of my next turn.
That is really good.
See, now I would use it.
Because that thing's stealth.
Click the towers.
Oh, Futurama theme.
Nice.
Okay, uh, I'm gonna do this.
And then I'm gonna put out...
I don't know, maybe I shouldn't do that.
Is the Earth Mother listening?
Yeah.
Where's the...
He's just gonna end up killing it.
Let's just get the fucking shark out here.
Pretty good.
He's not...
Okay, just going for face?
What's up with that?
Well, now that changes things.
Kill this.
And then...
I don't want to corrupt though.
Oh my god, yes.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
What?
Oh, the death rattle.
Oh, fuck.
It's all right.
I get plenty of good cards.
All right, we got one.
Uh, I can just...
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Summoner Empt two cost minion.
Combo.
Could do a couple combos here.
I don't think this is not lethal.
Six, ten, eleven.
Twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen.
That is nineteen.
Or eighteen.
I'm just gonna do this.
Damn.
I wish I could do that.
I'm gonna spread it out.
I'm gonna spread it out a little.
Fuck.
Why did I do that?
I can do one damage to somebody, right?
One damage to all of the minions.
All right, get out there, you motherfucker.
And I can do bang.
Freeze this idiot.
What a huge play.
Pretty standard.
I think he's dead this turn, right?
You're just gonna heal over and over again?
Never mind.
All right, hold on.
I'm...
Hold on a minute.
I think I have it.
Six, eight...
No, I got it.
I got it.
I need to do this correct.
Six, twelve, eighteen, nineteen, twenty.
Twenty-one, twenty, two.
I need to...
Yeah.
He doesn't know?
I saw it.
It's not BM if you're against the computer.
The computer doesn't have any feelings.
The computer does not have feelings.
It's mathematical code.
All right, what do we want?
You hurt my feelings.
You have permanent stealth.
At the start of your turn, give a random minion a hand plus one plus one,
or you start with an extra mana crystal.
That one's good, but boring.
This one seems broken.
I think that's what we're doing.
You minions have permanent stealth.
What?
Creature box.
And I'm the number three Hearthstone streamer?
Well, I really might put a disclaimer up that I'm not very good.
I'm just having fun.
Two of Thoris?
That makes three Vancleeps.
The title already explains it.
Yeah, I guess it does.
I remember when Emperor Thoris seemed unbearable.
He was so good.
Is he still in every single deck?
Okay, what do we got?
Always starts in your hand.
I could do Vancleef to always start.
Reduce the cost of a random card in your deck to zero.
Oh my god, what the hell is this?
2020?
Starts dormant.
Battle cry.
Shuffle three candles into the enemy deck when drawn.
This awakens.
What?
Okay, so that's insane.
It never happens.
Four mana, zero, zero.
Yeah, you just spend four mana.
It's just a coin that doesn't do anything, but it's four.
All right, well, you know what to do.
You're all fired.
Is that what you guys are clicking on?
Is that?
No.
Is it?
It is.
Don't you know we want a bunch of Vancleefs?
We need to, we might need to enhance this again.
Yeah, I need to enhance it again.
Go for it.
Okay, I was about to throw everybody away.
All right, so we're going to take them all into the enemy deck.
All right, yeah, let's go for it.
Take everybody.
All right, now what?
That thing's really interesting though.
Four mana, zero, zero.
Unfortunately.
All right, that's that one.
Okay, let's see what it is.
The thing that we just got.
All right, are we good?
That was four mana, right?
That's not bad.
All right, let's go.
Here we go.
I'm fucking excited.
Is anybody else like just absolutely boiling with excitement right now?
And if you're not, then that's pretty normal.
Okay, so I'm going to 2-2 Treant with Taunt.
Is that two mana?
This boss is overpowered.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Guaranteed win right here is zero, four, five.
Deal two damage to all undamaged enemy minions.
Instantly going to win.
Only hard and heroic.
Save it for clear.
But it's so easy just to throw them out there right now.
But zero mana.
Okay, I will hold off.
Okay, steal or draw Deathrattle?
I went with my gut.
That was the wrong idea.
Okay, now I'm going to have to play this.
Oh shit, this is bad.
Not yet.
It's killing me.
Oh, not yet, but they're getting this too many on the board.
Do a Chad move and draw the deck.
No, not yet.
Oh, fuck.
Now I'm going to use it.
Here we go.
That is so good.
That is just ridiculous.
Deal two damage to a minion if it survives.
Give it poisonous.
I could do that to somebody on my team.
What did that do?
Convert your mana into minions and gain an empty mana crystal.
Okay, deal.
No, that's not enough.
That's bad.
I think I'm going to just put out minions.
Or yeah, let's just go with the shark.
That sucks.
Can I eat this?
How many turns can I eat this?
Never mind.
That's all good.
So now, yeah, it's just a DPS race.
Let's see.
Give me something crazy.
Damn it.
DPS race.
Let's go.
I want to get 2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12.
Did he just go twice?
Okay, hold on.
4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19.
Oh, no, I thought that was a pick.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can I have it back?
I thought that was a combo.
It's all right.
I'm going to win.
We shall block your path.
God damn it.
That was such a bonehead move.
All right, I win.
Let me think about 4, 5, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
I got it.
It's over.
Thank you, Khadgar, for the 17 health for no reason.
Where to?
Look at all these wins.
I know.
Isn't it nice to win and not go 0-3 in Arena?
So we got this is the one.
Unearthed Raptor, Anub'arak, and N'zoth the Corruptor.
All these are so new.
I've never even seen half of these.
More death rattles.
All right, Oxana.
After minion attacks, you deal 2 damage to it.
So just every time somebody attacks with Cho.
We haven't seen Cho in...
I don't want to play him.
So many of these.
That's too many of these.
He died last game, but yeah, thank God.
All right, should I hold it?
I love how he's so nice and helpful.
All right, not yet.
If your deck has only odd cost cards, draw a card.
Do people build their decks around having odd costs?
That seems just strange.
Not anymore.
It was overpowered before.
Damn.
Well, I would put it out, but maybe...
Is this the opportunity just to get control right here?
Or do I just send the cat out to die?
Let's get it right now.
And then let's get Vancleef out there too.
You know what I mean?
Like, fuck it.
And then here we go.
Rush into the bandits.
This is a good run.
Cold blood on...
Do I have any heals?
Should I pull your hand into your deck?
Draw that many cards.
What the...
Wait, you can do that?
You just throw your hold hand away and...
All right, let me think about this.
I need to...
I can just get rid of this.
I might just...
Hold on, let me think.
I could just get rid of this and then face again.
Or get rid of this and then do another cold blood.
I could pull something.
Let me pull something.
Damn it.
All right, well now I have to do that.
Oh, I could have killed it.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
I could have killed it.
It's all right.
I still can.
Everything's fine.
Two lackeys.
All right, let's do the stupid cat.
And then the lackey or...
Yeah, I want the lackeys.
All right, now...
Is it worth doing eight damage to face?
Or should I just hold this forever?
No, I have to do it.
I have to go to the face.
Plus one attack and rush.
I still have this.
That's not fair.
Restart your computer.
Maybe that'll fix it.
I don't think I want to do any of this.
I can't play this.
This just is a dead card.
It just dies.
All right, so lackey and then we'll do the bandits.
And then I'm gonna give cold blood to somebody.
Who should I give this to?
You.
And then I'm gonna trade you to you.
And everything's gonna be fine.
But that's the thing I was talking about.
All right, well, that's gone immediately.
I mean, right?
I feel like I'm gonna get rid of that too.
I have to get rid of this.
This thing's gonna keep doing this forever.
Face is good damage, but he's gonna keep bringing everybody in here.
If this minion survives damage, I'm gonna copy.
Don't do the spin thing.
Combo, destroy a minion.
Perfect.
Lackey.
Into.
Yeah, lackey.
Destroy the five, three.
And then we're gonna go like this.
Bye, you.
And then we hold.
What?
Yeah, because they'll just die.
Play the totem.
The totem dies.
It doesn't do anything.
Well, here we go.
Give me something good.
That's really fucking good.
Here we go.
Oh, damn it.
What's going on?
Hey, hey, there it is.
Summon King Mukla.
Give it immune and can't be targeted by spells or hero powers.
Thanks, Khadgar.
Appreciate it.
Now it doesn't even matter.
If I have, I think I win.
What is he doing?
Why did he just do all that at the very end here?
Thanks for nothing for the first like 12 turns.
What do you guys think?
How am I this good?
Well, it takes a lot of practice.
All right, shuffle five random treasures into your deck.
I don't think I've ever even seen what this does.
Take an extra turn.
Your opponent takes an extra turn after.
That kind of sucks.
This one's pretty good.
Draw this every turn at the start of every game you draw this.
It has taunt and it gets plus one plus one every turn it's in my hand.
Taking this.
What do you think?
We're getting close to the last like two or three.
Usually the last two or three are usually pretty hard.
They're just so just random all over the place.
It's hard to beat them sometimes and I don't this is kind of split here.
58, 20.
There we go.
Draw!
You want me to start getting some draw?
Is this the last one?
We got some pretty good shit though.
Okay, now this is it.
Code a minion and blast powder when it takes damage destroyed.
I remember this.
There's something, there's some wires and stuff.
I'm gonna fuck this up.
Yeah, if these two wires touch you take five damage at the beginning of the turn or something.
But the stealth is just so overpowered.
Permanent stealth against this character.
It will never activate.
It's never gonna activate when I get him out there.
That's so funny.
He's not gonna be able to do it.
Wait, did I give you the wire?
All right, well let's...
The only time that this card has ever been useful is right now.
Well, I can't really do anything so...
And I got Ragnaros.
Random Ragnaros Lightlord.
I'm not, it's impossible for me to lose.
It just isn't.
I, there's no way.
It's impossible.
It used to be about the explosions man.
What happened?
Okay, but hold on.
Don't get too overconfident because I still have to like do this.
I still have to get here.
So this is actually a really terrible start.
Four, one.
This is bad.
If I play the miscreen I'm not gonna get the combo though.
And he's just gonna...
I guess it makes sense.
He's starting to load up to a point where I actually might lose.
I'm getting way too high cost cards.
This is very bad.
All right, four, who's...
Okay, I gotta get rid of you.
So I gotta take out you.
So I'm gonna do that with an cold blood.
That will give me able to clear it.
Okay, that's what I'm doing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's okay.
It's fine.
Everything's good.
It's all right.
I can, it's all right, it's all right, it's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
I'm just gonna get the darkness out there and everything seems fine.
Oh no, should I do King Wukla?
Maybe I should just do King Wukla.
Or...
It doesn't work like that?
That won't work?
Oh, it spawns over here.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay.
Does this count as a minion?
Okay, at the first second I dump...
I just gotta make it to round eight.
All right, this is how we do this.
We go.
Bang.
Knuckles?
No, I need to get rid of...
I'm just gonna shuriken the zombie.
And then I'm gonna eviscerate him.
And then steal.
What the hell happened?
Oh, come on.
Thank God, nobody was stealthed.
That's no stealth card.
All right, now we've got King Wukla now.
Or...
Yeah, that's time for Wukla.
What?
Why are you doing this?
Oh my God, this is so bad for him.
That was so bad.
Holy shit, that was terrible.
That's the...
Hey, is that...
Hey, is that Jermadonite V playing on the other team?
But hold on.
Ragnaros time.
No, I can't lose!
That was a voice crack.
It's okay.
Yeah, now I guess I'm fine.
How do I take care of that?
What do I do about this?
Hold on.
I can't be...
I can't have him taunting because he has permanent stealth.
Nobody can taunt because they're stealthed.
I lose.
I'm actually gonna lose because I can't put on the weapon.
Play Edwin.
Just attack with it, but he's...
I'm in trouble.
Yeet him!
Seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven!
It's not...
I got it.
What?
Is this gonna counterspell me?
All right.
We're okay.
We're back to normal.
So I'm like scared.
Can you draw a candle already, please?
Thank you for that.
I'll take it.
Shuffle five random treasures into your deck.
All right, give me these.
I have 28 cards in my deck.
I'm never gonna see those.
I can't even kill this!
Four, five, six...
I'm gonna...
Where's the...
Discover a druid, rogue, or shaman card.
Let's see.
Deal two damage to the enemy hero.
If you control a treant, discover a spell.
When you overload, I don't...
Headcrack is the only thing I can do.
And then just get out the raptor?
Well, give me the heal.
Now draw the fucking candles.
What did I just get?
What's going on?
Your opponent summoned a minion from their deck and I got...
Sneed!
All right.
Hold on.
Do I have like one damage?
Is this thing gonna get...
Sneed?
Give me the shit.
Okay.
What?
Go dormant?
Play four cards?
What's with all this dormant shit?
I need to make space.
Oh, right.
I have to make space.
Let's kill this guy.
And then you die here.
So now there's enough space.
And then Thor is sent.
I'm in a pretty good spot now.
I'm pretty...
This should be it.
Free and real.
Holy fuck.
That would have been awesome.
All right.
So now just give me that.
Now we're gonna just load him up.
What happened?
Doesn't matter, motherfucker.
It doesn't matter.
Hey.
Draw two minions from your deck.
Set their attack health and cost to one?
This is baby shit.
Uh-oh.
No, he's not scary.
All right.
Do I win with an extra turn?
That's seven.
Fourteen.
No.
I don't win with an extra turn.
I gotta clear this though,
because he has no cards.
I gotta play this right.
Three damage.
So get your text off the screen.
I'm trying to focus.
Headcrack.
I don't win with a headcrack.
Two turns of 26...
Head...
What do you mean?
Wait, what?
It is lethal.
Seven.
Fourteen.
Nineteen.
Twenty-four.
Twenty...
What happened?
Oh, okay.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I'm miss-clicking.
I thought I had to do it afterwards.
Tuber.
LOL.
So funny.
Hey, run complete.
I did it with the rogue.
This is fun.
Hooray.
Alright.
Again.
Now do that on heroic.
I'm not ready for heroic.
You are?
Alright, I'll try it once.
Okay.
Chapter one, heroic.
I'm not going to be able to do this.
I'm not ready for this.
Play anomaly mode?
What is anomaly mode?
Alright, we got druid.
Looks like people want to see druid.
Anomaly is more random rules.
That's cool.
Alright, we're going to do druid.
I'm going to pee.
So, you guys can pick.
There's nothing for you to pick, so never mind.
And there's just this.
Okay.
Well, I'm not going to pee.
Well, I'm not going to pee yet.
Let me see if I can get through the first person.
Okay, so this is swap the leftmost card in each player's hand with one in their deck.
So, you just everybody on the left swaps out.
Let's see if I can even do the first level.
I'm not embarrassed if I can't do this on heroic.
Do I pee?
I will.
After this.
He's going to get embarrassed.
Maybe.
This is the one with the coins in the middle.
Alright, what do you think?
After this minion attacks a hero, add a copy of it to your hand.
That's not bad.
Add two 1-1 squirrels.
Yeah, definitely this.
Oh, shit.
You're going to pull that.
That's alright.
Give a friendly minion 1-1 and gain armor equal to its attack.
Shit.
I need to play this.
Because this is going to disappear.
I already lost.
And then give this the 1-1 so it can't die from here.
Yeah, let's try it.
I'm not going to attack.
That's actually really good.
I'm happy that just happened.
Minus two attack until your next turn.
What the fuck.
After you summon a minion, give it plus one plus one.
Shit.
I'm just going to have to...
Do I even attack?
This is going to kill me.
Shit.
Okay, that's not horrible.
Gain six armor, recruit a minion that costs four or less.
Or do I shapeshift into this?
Because then they'll get...
Okay, and then...
That's pretty good.
Should I do them all?
All right, this is where it gets to be...
I have to get rid of that.
Value trade 3-2 in face of 2-1.
Yeah.
Thank you, guy in the chat.
Appreciate all that good stuff that you just told me.
You know, it's heroic, so I'm just...
I don't know why my brain is like,
no, no, no, everything needs to be...
Be careful, I need help.
I think that's it.
Yeah, that's it.
That was easy.
It was.
I'm overthinking things.
All right, I'm going to pee.
Well, you vote for the...
So difficult.
There you go.
Let's see what it's going to be.
Draw two cards at the start of the game.
Gain two armor when somebody dies.
Or your death rattles trigger twice.
How many death rattles do I have?
I think one or two.
Two.
Three.
All right, yeah, I mean, if we're going to pick this,
then we're going to go straight up death rattle.
Is there a death rattle here?
Gruul.
Well, there is one.
The mulch muncher?
Big friends.
Summon a minion from your hand with five or more attack.
Yeah, that doesn't do anything for us, unfortunately.
But Gruul is just Gruul.
Yeah, that sucks.
Summon five minions with five or more attack.
And we have to start working on this shit, too.
Well, the people want Gruul.
So they're going to get Gruul.
All right, OEP.
I'll be right back.
Haven't been playing Hearthstone for three hours.
Damn.
I'm having fun, though.
It's a fun game.
When you have 3,500 people help you make decisions on every play.
It's fun.
I'll be right back.
Okay, sorry I was going for a little bit longer.
I wanted to get a drink because it's been like four hours
and I haven't really had anything to drink.
So I had coffee sitting here.
But I needed something a little more substantial.
All right, let's go.
What's the drink?
It is just a sparkling water.
It's not anything too interesting.
Just a little bit of bubbles.
All right, so do I even play this shit?
I don't think I even have these in my deck.
Pineapple juice is going to kill you, you know.
Ooh, that's good.
All right, what does he do?
All right, add a random magical feat to your hand.
All right, so he puts feet in his hand.
So death rattles trigger twice.
Let's get the...
Let's get him out there.
Get that.
Ooh, give me millions.
One, one.
Well, this thing is free.
So here, just play it.
All right, summon two.
Or, yeah, let's just get rid of this.
Do I want the one, one?
No, because it's a twin spell.
Did it bring out the trance?
Just bring them all out.
I'm going for it.
I'm going for a kill immediately.
All right, that was a good outcome.
Jesus.
Give a friendly mini one, one, then gain attack equal...
The armor equal to its attack.
So I gotta think about this here.
So we get two, two.
And then I could get rid of that.
All right, so hold on.
I can...
Two fucking goddamn math.
I can't do math.
Yes, I can.
Was that wrong?
That was okay.
That wasn't completely wrong, was it?
Was it wrong?
No, it was right.
It was a little bit wrong.
Wasn't that wrong?
It was okay.
All right, I can do this twice.
Again.
So we're going to one, one onto six armor.
That's insane.
I think I...
Do I have it?
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
No, I don't have it.
Oh, it's all minions.
Oh, I thought it was give a minion.
Minion.
All right.
Three mana, give a minion, one, one.
Yeah, that would be absolute dog shit.
What the hell am I talking about?
Look at how desperate he is right now.
He's trying so hard.
He's going to lose.
Am I going to get to play?
Jesus.
Get that squirrel BM.
Not a big deal.
All right.
What do you guys think?
Do you not need to kill the gold treasure thing?
No, what it does is it gives both players two coins.
So, you know, you could...
Time for arena.
Now that was so embarrassing.
That just was so...
I can't.
I can't do that again.
All right, we got big friends.
Should we try it one more time before I stop?
I have to redeem myself.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll try it.
Not now.
After like another run or two.
I'm still having fun.
It's just fun just to...
I'm not very good.
How many times is he going to say he's not good?
All right.
We'll take this.
The Amazing Boomer.
Cast a random spell that was cast this game
chosen randomly on targets.
Okay.
Cool.
Interesting.
All right.
I still don't have enough.
Maybe I do now.
How many minions do I have over five attack?
I think I have it now.
But they're all late game cards.
What happened to Cooking Simulator?
Unfortunately, I had the release date wrong.
The game doesn't actually launch until tomorrow.
So I figured, hey, I'm just going to play Hearthstone for some reason.
Odd that that's the thing that decided...
I just felt like it.
And on this channel, we just do anything.
Even if it's to the detriment of my channel.
It doesn't matter.
Let's go with the...
What are you doing?
I used to be my favorite card in the game.
I still love that thing.
Doesn't seem like a detriment.
No, I'm just kidding around.
I'm just kidding.
One, one.
And then gain his attack and armor.
Maybe I should do it to you.
And get the coins and then do...
That's what I'm going for?
Could be the wrong play.
Might be the wrong play.
But it's what I'm going to do.
We have many secrets.
Have you ever played...
Tried...
What is...
I don't know.
What's it?
Hearthstone?
A good way to win at Hearthstone?
I feel like that's a...
Is it a thing?
I'm not saying that.
I don't know about it.
What am I...
I'm not reading that.
It's...
Talk to the S.
Okay.
I don't know what that is.
And I almost said I don't know what it is.
Well, that's a perfect exact mana cost card.
With a mage secret.
Oh, shit.
What is it?
It's going to be like Vaporize, right?
It's Vaporize.
So many squirrels.
It's not a beast?
Damn.
Twin spell?
No, I can't do that.
All squirrels?
And then get Vaporized?
All squirrels and then...
Wait a minute.
And I'm loving it!
Holy shit.
Calm down.
Let's see what this is.
Three...
Hold on.
Four?
Five?
Six.
So then should I get twin spell twice on the squirrel?
Oh, shit!
You motherfucker!
You just ruined everything!
Why?
No!
It's all right.
I can do it next...
I can twin spell it next turn.
He's not going to kill all this.
Yeah, coining...
This is bad now.
At least I get two of them.
Actually, it's a good thing I didn't do this.
Although, man, it sucks.
Too bad I still...
I wish I had that fucking other coin.
I could have done Gruul this turn.
Oh, that's not a beat.
I just get the tiger out there again and then...
Oh, look at this loser.
What did you say to me?
I got lots of armor.
None of these beasts.
All right.
Coin Gruul or Coin Chromagus?
I'm going to say Coin Gruul.
And then I...
Ah, hold on.
Can I get rid of the Sorcerer's Apprentice
or get rid of the Karantor Mage?
I'm going to say Mage.
Or I could just hit him.
Hopefully that was right.
I didn't trade.
Not good.
Should have traded.
I was supposed to trade,
and now it's going to come back and bite me.
Chromagus is gone.
I didn't get to do it once.
You control three menus of seven health
and deal seven damage to all enemies.
Well, it's time for Gruul.
Ouch.
This is so bad.
Put SP in the title.
Or, I mean, this is not...
Nobody gets sponsored to play Hearthstone.
What?
I think I'm just going to go with the 777.
That's a lie?
Do people actually get sponsored by Blizzard?
I'm just going with seven.
Blizzard pays people to play this game.
Not like tournaments,
like actually just to stream it.
Oh, it means single player.
I just jumped immediately to conclusions on that one.
Did you use the Twitch bounty?
No, no, I don't, I don't, I don't.
No, I did this because I'm a fucking moron.
And this is my own dumb decision.
I'm going to own my own shitty decisions.
This is a good decision.
Plus, I win.
The game's over.
Eight, nine, not yet.
Is that a beast?
Do the bounty now.
There is no...
I don't have a bounty for Hearthstone.
How does that not have a bounty for Hearthstone?
Yeah, I don't have a bounty, a bounty for Hearthstone.
Well, I can't do this yet.
Oh, we get to do this.
Next turn, we get to win.
Quest?
That's going to be too late.
Why not now?
Nobody died?
Freeze an enemy?
Well, now I'm going to do this.
Never mind.
Shuffle it back in.
Twin spell?
Quest now.
Twin spell.
Make it so I stay alive.
No, that's too much spell damage.
You don't have anything in your hand.
Nothing.
Yes.
All right.
Oh, come on.
Hit me in the face fucking five times.
That was so dumb.
Oh, God.
Your minions cost one.
Now, well, that's good.
I'm glad.
Yeah, it's a guaranteed victory.
Unless you pyroblast me or something, somehow.
Am I going to lose?
No.
I just won.
Oh, yeah.
I always have to do the BN on the computer because it doesn't matter.
Heroic isn't that bad.
The enemy's fatigued because he's so slow.
But I play slow.
What are we thinking?
50 damage to guaranteed win and a random one out of 30 chance.
Or add three random cards to your hand and they all cost zero.
That's fucking incredible.
Deal four damage to all minions and you shuffle it back in.
These are all good.
But you're going to make me pick the meme card.
So all enemy minions.
And it's a death rattle and we get it twice.
You really want me to do the joke card?
We're not going to see that the whole rest of the run.
Oh, goddamn it.
Why do the clicks do this?
There's been like five...
I'm not changing any settings.
There's been like 5,000 clicks.
You can't...
No.
Ah, whatever.
That's all right.
Elder won.
Yeah.
Elder is still winning.
I mean, that's amazing.
Or that, too, is so good.
All right.
The people have spoken.
The muscle is probably the best card here.
But Elder, that...
I mean, come on.
That's unbelievable.
Please continue to make your selection.
Big friends, pharaoh, bite, or legends?
Two avianas.
Aviana?
I don't really like aviana.
You have to wait till the very end of the game
to be able to throw up shit all over your board.
You already lost at that point.
Big bad arc mage.
That's pretty good.
Some of the five, five ironhide runt.
Two bites.
That's not bad either.
These are all good.
Cenarius is good.
Lowethep is really good.
I remember Lowethep.
He was like one of the best cards.
All right.
We're going to go with big friends.
Bite sucks.
Is bite bad?
Hey, welcome.
I can do better than that.
No, that's...
I shouldn't even...
Just stop.
You gotta...
Sometimes you gotta take the fucking loss.
What do you guys think?
I only get to do...
What?
I can only do...
Oh, it's because it's heroic.
Choose an enemy minion and add it to your deck
or give a friendly minion plus two plus two.
Just do them both.
Doesn't matter.
Or remove somebody from the deck.
I think you guys are clicking in the middle.
No, you're not.
You're doing recruit.
I mean, we can do them all.
All right.
Let's...
I'll make this easier.
Let me start from the left.
Because I mean, we're gonna probably do them all.
So forget about this.
Be easier this way.
So...
Who do you want me to recruit?
We've got giant anaconda.
Duskfallen Aviana.
Aviana, like evil Aviana.
That's like dark pit.
Kel'thuzad and then Ragnaros.
So who would you like me to do that to?
That's a better question.
How to beat you?
And no, I cannot take the innkeeper.
Seems to be a split between Kel'thuzad and Ragnaros
and the innkeeper because I said the word.
I said the word innkeeper and everyone's like hand
just Ouija board over to his face.
So it looks like it's gonna be Kel'thuzad.
All right.
Thank you for voting.
Kel'thuzad is coming with us.
All right.
Now, who do you want me to give?
Plus one, plus one, two.
Well, plus...
No, who do you want to get?
Plus two, plus two, two.
Who do you want me to give plus two, plus two, two?
Feral gib?
Astral tiger.
I mean, that's three, three, one drop.
That's pretty good.
That would also be a five, seven astral tiger,
which is insane.
Three, three, one drop.
That multiplies.
Yeah, that's true.
That's really good.
All right.
For the story before, it's a good one.
Okay.
Do you want me to remove anyone?
Do we still want to do that?
You know, let's...
Okay, click.
You know, who...
Are we removing anybody?
I don't think so.
I think these, they all have a place here.
The death rattles.
No, we can't...
No, I'm not getting rid of any of these.
I'm not gonna remove me.
Replace the streamer with a better streamer.
No, we're good.
These are all death rattles.
Why won't it work?
Let's go.
Once you say it, Twitch repeats it.
Whenever a player plays a coin, draw a card.
I'm gonna forget about that.
I'm gonna give him so much money.
I just realized...
These kobolds just look like human skin alligators.
It's weird, right?
All right, I don't want that.
We're gonna actually hold on to the quest this time.
Give me some low cost, please.
That's okay.
All right.
Whenever a player plays a coin, draw a card.
So I'm assuming he's gonna give me coins.
Definitely gonna do this.
I think I popped the treasure once.
Is this guy gonna play a card?
There it is.
Why would you play that now?
It's gone.
Right?
Why would you do that?
Shit!
He's gonna give me two coins.
Send it back.
I'll take the coins.
I don't give a shit.
Send it back.
I gotta get two of them.
Look at all that.
No, I'm not gonna coin.
This guy's dead right now.
It's all right.
I'm gonna coin out Gruul.
I'm putting Gruul out right now.
Or coin out bone mare and give the taunt to the astral tiger.
I like that.
That sounds fun.
I can still kill questing adventure.
The coins are gonna grow questing.
Fuck.
They don't?
I was the one guy.
I was listening to the one guy.
Let's do this.
And I can kill questing and be fine.
All right.
Now we're in a good spot.
I'll take two tigers.
Overkill.
Well there's the big bad archmage.
I could do scribe or I could hit and kill
or bring out the direhorm.
Yeah, let's direhorm face.
And we get a coin.
Oh, fuck you.
Okay.
I think I gotta bring out Gruul.
I think I have to.
Or the scribe.
I can kill that with this, but then...
Yeah, we'll do this.
I have too many coins.
I need to get rid of these.
What did you just do?
What did he just do?
Did he vanish?
Why did you vanish?
This is heroic.
This is on heroic.
Oh, please.
I don't even care.
And here comes Barnum.
I didn't even know what was happening.
He summons...
Oh, he summons six cost minions.
Uh-oh, you had to get rid of Aviana.
It doesn't matter.
Reduce the cost of your minions in your deck to zero.
That's so stupid.
I mean, like, let's...
Okay.
Do I just win?
I just win.
But I want to see that, though.
That's fun.
I'll take him down to one health.
Yeah, that's dangerous.
Never mind.
Yeah, this is heroic.
I can't...
I don't want to fuck around.
That was awesome.
Just like that.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
That's what you live for.
Roar.
Beasts and buffs are big friends again.
Another Dire Horn.
Malorne.
That's just double.
Rush, overkill.
Summon a beast from your hand.
I don't really have any beasts.
I mean, I guess maybe.
Adapt means that every turn you get to do something else, right?
Or every...
You just change it to, like, divine shield, taunt, rush, right?
I do have a ton of beasts.
I guess I do.
All right.
Sounds good.
Banker Biggs.
Return a friendly minion to your hand.
Then give it plus four, plus four, and copy it.
That sounds kind of ridiculous.
How the hell are you supposed to deal with that?
Just play it.
Shit.
Oh, that's a disgusting, awful start.
Oh, yuck.
I lose.
I want to start really making money.
I'm calling security.
What?
I didn't...
Why would you call security on me?
I didn't do anything.
This is bad.
I need these coins.
If I have my stand any chance.
I don't stand a chance.
I need the coins right now.
Die.
It's invader zoom.
All right.
Two and one.
No, that's bad.
That's not gonna work.
I have to just get the coins.
Or I could...
Tiger's not terrible here.
This is a gamble, but it might be all right.
Literally, what did that accomplish?
I don't...
Nothing.
I don't know why.
I just...
Some...
I looked over and I saw somebody say it.
No, I don't...
I can't use the coins enough.
Fuck.
I have to put something out here.
It was me.
What the fuck?
I forgot there's people that are writing things specifically.
So I'll look at it and then they'll go.
You might do it.
Oh, I need to focus on me.
Literally, what did that accomplish?
You're right.
Damn it.
Okay.
This is...
That's the best card in the whole game, right?
Isn't that the best current card?
Like the broken meta card?
Okay, I have two coins.
Seven.
I could do four and then twin spell them.
No.
I could do tiger.
Come on.
Was I gonna like draw that next?
Why do I keep pulling this?
I have to like coin and hit this.
Right?
I mean like this is horrible.
No, I mean just it takes the shield off.
So I don't get guaranteed.
I would do that.
That's what I would do.
That's what you would do.
I think that's what I would do as well.
Go face.
I don't...
I can't.
Oh, this is so bad.
Uh-oh.
Anonymous five community subs.
Thank you.
There were an insane amount of community subs tonight.
And somebody else just gave five more.
Thank you so much for the subs.
What the hell am I gonna do about this?
Chromagus?
Chromagus is probably the best thing I can do.
Or I could do...
I could wait, but I'm gonna take so much damage.
Next turn bring this out.
Kill somebody and summon Chromagus.
I'm just gonna have to pop the shield.
Pop shield.
Kill you.
Bring out the tiger.
Should I maybe just...
No.
That's the...
That's the dream right there.
If I can get it.
I need to draw that.
Right now.
That clears up everything.
Draw it.
Come on.
Top deck that cra...
Top deck the elder right now.
Top deck elder right now and I still have a chance.
Does that change things?
That might.
Ugh.
Coin bone mare?
Or coin coin rush into like you pull out...
Astro Rat.
I'll get Chromagus or Ironhide.
Just looking up your account number.
Who do I kill with this?
The 2-4 or the 4-3?
What?
Just go face.
You can't go face with the rush.
All right.
I got a chance.
Next turn I do...
This is all right.
Now we pull out bone mare and we go face.
Oh shit.
That thing's gonna have 4-4.
That's just gonna be horrible.
I gotta...
I have to start doing something now.
I mean, uh...
I gotta just go for the win.
And then I can do...
I can do this.
Oh no!
That's not good.
This is not good.
What can I get from this?
All right.
12, 13...
I can get a shitload of armor.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Is it lethal?
3, 6.
I have to put chromagus out now
because I fucking didn't do it right.
That's 3, 6, 9, twin spell.
I have to clear somebody.
No, I can do it.
I can do it.
6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12.
Don't...
No!
Hold on!
All right.
Now draw.
Can I do it?
Oh, you motherfucker.
If only he was the elder.
Hold on.
6, 7, 8, 9...
9...
No!
It's not enough.
Go for the roll.
Shit!
Oh no!
I had a chance.
You know what?
Fuck the RNG I got in the beginning.
I pulled the elder twice.
Wait a minute.
Do I get...
Hold on.
Do I live?
Do I live one more turn?
6, 12, 18...
Fuck you, game.
Oh, there he is.
Wait.
What?
I need him to die.
Maybe he'll be an idiot.
Maybe he won't kill me.
Damn it.
It was this thing that screwed me.
That's why I had to get rid of him.
Oh well.
Oh, I have to beat it.
I have to do it.
No, wait.
What's the tavern roll?
Nefarion Rises?
Oh no.
All right, let's do Anomaly.
Where is it?
Oh.
Which one of these is it?
Is it this one?
Which one of these is Anomaly?
Oh, it's above go.
Anomaly mode.
Gain a random effect for this run.
Minions gain plus 1 plus 1 at the end of their owner's turn.
So it was just random every time?
That makes it easy, right?
Ah, I don't want to do that.
It's random every run.
Anomaly is a little easier.
It works for them.
All minions get it.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Let's try...
Let's try that.
Let's do Heroic on here.
Let's pick a new class.
Mage.
Sounds good to me.
Gonna be Fireman.
Okay.
Easy enough.
Thank you.
Fire Blast.
Can only do Apprentice.
What's my favorite class?
It was Paladin when I played years ago.
All right, Alchemist Wendy.
We did this already.
The deck that I used to play when I attempted...
...was the Silverhand Knight deck.
Where you had that guy that gave everybody 3-3 and it was pretty fun.
All right.
This is different stuff.
Sickening.
Yeah, it was Agro Pally, right?
So this one, this was in there.
Your Murlocs cost 1.
Draw two cards.
Uh, destroy it.
That's fine.
Was that the deck that was so used that bots could get a high rank with it?
I don't know.
It was.
Whatever.
Deal 2 damage.
Add a 1-1 elemental.
I'm gonna say we just get the...
Could just kill it.
Or bring out the Fairy Dragon.
I would put out the Fairy Dragon right here.
Or I would do that and skip.
No, it was Secret Paladin.
Yeah.
That wasn't that one.
Uh...
Chaos.
Why are you saying chaos?
Oh, because of Jebel.
One more turn and I get Scargill.
Well, I can do...
Eh.
I would just kill him and hit him in the face.
Or you could do Salus to Secret and...
I can whack him, you know?
Thanks for the dubs.
Thanks for the doubles.
Stupid.
Now that gets me this for free.
Free 2 damage, but does that really do much for me?
I got my dubs!
Doubles!
That didn't really do much for me, though.
I mean, like, fucking die.
Who cares?
Checked.
Check him.
What does checked mean?
Like, checkmate?
Yeah.
Checkmate, motherfucker.
Does that suck?
Am I gonna lose?
No.
Earthen Ring.
What's that?
Whenever your spells deal damage, restore that much health to your hero.
Okay.
Well, we're gonna polymorph you.
And then we're gonna kill you.
Just like this, I'll show you.
It's gonna be so easy.
What am I doing?
Yeah, that's what I want to do.
Freeze.
I can do it too.
See?
I'm gonna lose.
No, I'm not.
It's Calcigos!
Your first spell each turn costs zero.
Uh, I want this.
It's impossible to lose at this point.
Let me tell you something.
It's possible.
It's very possible now.
Well, actually not anymore.
Yeah, it's not possible anymore.
You can't hurt me.
I'm immune.
Wait, I want him to die.
Watch this.
Level up.
And I got a golden mirror image.
Cool.
Some good ones here.
Play Classic WoW.
I don't have access to it.
I told you guys that eventually when I got access to it,
I was gonna try to just beat Molten Core with Chat.
But I mean, that would take months.
Where are you guys clicking?
Your minions that cost five or more cost five.
You can use your hero power twice each turn.
It costs one or death rattles.
So all the minions that are five or more just cost five.
Dude, you're never even gonna get to level 60.
Who are you kidding?
All right.
We need big minions now.
Babbling book we got.
What do we got for minions?
Calcigos.
Where do you want me to go here?
Can I ask?
24% of everybody that's clicking the screen.
Where do you want me to go?
Quit the game?
No, this is what we're doing.
Cooking simulator tomorrow.
Because it actually releases.
No, I'm not going to start here as it might magic through now.
No, this is a Hearthstone comfortable stream.
Didn't I just?
Dude, why am I doing this twice in a row?
Play Constructed?
I can't do that.
After Arena.
It was it was an absolute disaster.
I will try Arena one more time.
Getting deja vu, but I don't mind this start.
Should I start doing Bane?
But to get chat under control?
Do viewer games?
Can you do viewer games?
Wouldn't I have to like add a bunch of people on battle net?
I don't think you can do that.
Can you?
I have to add everybody on battle net.
All right, what do I want to do?
I want to after you cast a spell do one damage to a random enemy minion.
That sounds pretty good.
Make a guild in Classic WoW.
I was thinking about it.
What do I think about Magic Gathering?
It's too complicated for me.
It's just too much for me.
I can barely handle Hearthstone.
All right, so here we go.
Ready?
I'm going for it.
Yep.
It worked.
Too complicated.
Yeah, it just kind of is.
So a game like Hearthstone I can obviously just
dick around and play it like once in a while.
But yeah, you kind of know what you're doing in Magic the Gathering.
You need to know a lot, don't you?
Should I bring out?
Let's just get a magic trick.
I mean, just do that now.
Maybe I'll get another free one.
You have to learn the basics, but Magic Gathering Arena is autopilot.
Just autopilot.
You're not going to attack me, huh?
Well, there's Kelsagos.
I can.
All right, here we go.
Watch this.
Your first spell each turn causes zero.
Three damage.
Freeze the character if I was to freeze the minion if it's already frozen.
Destroy it.
This one.
And then we're going to sheep you and face.
Thanks for the free spells, Kelsagos.
Yeah, for the most part, the last couple of streams have really just been
I needed low-key stuff.
And I mean, we've been dicking around and I've been making
fucking loud noises, but I really was supposed to take it easy.
So tomorrow we're going to be doing cooking simulator.
So don't worry.
I think I win.
Four, five, six, seven, eight.
Nine, ten.
I could get good RNG here.
Here we go.
I'm just going to, who cares?
Is that it?
Four, five, six, seven, eight.
Ah!
Am I going to play Dreams again?
Yeah, I'll probably play Dreams once I hook up the PS4 again.
Because at that point, oh, he just goes for his first spell.
Um, once we have something else to do on PS4.
Because by this point, I think there's a lot more stuff in Dreams.
So yeah.
I think so.
Yeah, we've played it a few times already.
It's really, really fun.
It's really interesting.
It's fun just to channel surf.
Well, yeah, we kind of have to go big because these will all be five cost.
Go big.
100% click.
Look at that.
Oh, I also have to check on my, um, I'm going to check on the, um, what is it though?
Didn't I release the worm to the public?
I wonder if anybody did anything with it.
All healing is doubled.
What's wrong?
Hey, what's wrong?
What's going on here?
You all right?
That was weird.
They having server trouble?
The worm.
Ban for BM.
Who, me?
Who are you referring to?
Try to say 3095C because I was supposed to delete that at a thousand.
I need a new number now.
Do I have any elementals?
I don't think there's any elementals even in the whole deck.
I guess the flame geyser will make one or two.
Double healing.
Not going to play a card.
All right, I'll just take it.
Fine.
All right, let me, let me summon an elemental.
That's an elemental, isn't it?
This is an elemental, right?
It's not.
Oh, shit.
This is an elemental.
Arcane Anomaly.
Should I just get it out there?
Read the card.
Well, I know, I just saw like the fucking goo.
Eight health to all minions.
All right, I'm going to have a pretty big hand for this.
I'm just going to go face and then next turn have like a huge minion
because that will be
one, two, three, four, five, six.
It'll be a seven cost minion.
Do I get this?
No, yeah, next turn.
What is it?
It's a taunt.
All right, here we go.
Seven cost minion incoming.
Oh, damn it.
Oh, they're going to kill it right now too.
Shit.
Oh well.
What does he get from this?
I know you're going to kill it.
Yeah, I don't get to see the fun thing.
I get a taunt now and we can do it again.
Give me something else.
All right.
Maybe I don't even do anything.
What is the rewards thing?
Freudian weapon.
Cheer.
Shared rewards to three others in chat.
What happened?
What does that actually do?
Share rewards.
I have no idea.
Oh, he's going to inspire.
I get two of these things, man.
Really?
Well, now we fire lands.
God, kill somebody.
Any elementals in the hand?
No.
Six.
What is this game?
All right, got a taunt restore eight health to your hero.
That's pretty good.
We can just take one damage at a time.
I can cast a spell.
We get one damage to a random enemy.
We're just going to go with the face.
Whenever this attacks and kills a minion,
summon two murlocs for me.
I don't have any murlocs in my deck.
I mean, just do this.
I don't want that here.
Murlocs?
No, I don't have any.
What's my voice?
Am I eating something?
No, I was just going like this.
Oh, fuck.
You don't have two of those.
You're not going to do that again.
Good, good.
Okay, we're good.
Deal two damage.
Add a one, two, uh-huh.
And you, whenever a friendly minion is healed,
summon a three, three whelp.
I don't think so.
Sorry.
Did I miss lethal?
Oh, God damn it.
He's going to do this fucking four times.
Remember I was talking about this last night?
I mean, that's an elemental, but who cares?
I have to kind of, what do I do?
I might just go face.
I kind of have to, right?
No, but he's going to heal everything.
Oh, my God.
I mean, uh, three, eight, seven, six, five, four.
What do you mean?
What did I do?
What was it?
What was the other one?
Didn't get shatter?
Oh, that's right.
This thing freezes people.
Oh, fuck.
I forgot.
It should be called ice water elemental.
I haven't seen this card in four years.
Aye, I'm going to lose this anyways.
I think I'm just screwed.
What am I going to do about this?
Let's see.
Oh, my chest.
Hey, how about this one?
Oh, whatever.
Didn't get very far on that one.
Do arena.
I don't have any coins for arena.
I have to buy arena.
I'm not doing that.
I got I got you want me to spend $1.99 to go into the arena.
Do it.
Don't buy arena.
You never buy arena.
You really don't ever purchase arena.
Purchasing arena is what a grandmother would do.
Like an addicted grandmother would be buying arena over and over again
and losing oh and three.
Oh, that was really fun.
Now they're going to do that again.
No, I just have to do some quests.
Hunter, pirates, and weapons.
I'm going to play hunter and I'm going to play weapons.
So play 20 hunter cards and use six weapons.
Is there such thing as pirate hunter?
Okay, pirate.
Draw two card overkill taunt.
Okay, now we need hunter, just hunter cards.
Okay, let's do um, I'm sure I didn't rank.
Rank 25.
Let's go.
I'll show you.
Oh, this person has a cool portrait.
That means that they're good.
All right, I need to play pirates and hunter cards and weapons.
This is only to get to arena so I can embarrass myself again.
Thank you.
I can get the pirates out even faster.
Okay, has Charger and weapon equipped?
Well, let's just play it smart.
Let's get the weapon on and then let's put these guys out next turn.
No, I'm not gonna idiot.
Okay, I mean like let's go.
That was wild.
Get six mana.
Let's see what you're gonna put down.
Dead three damage.
This is you're playing against a baby.
This is a kid's game.
No, it's not a kid's game.
This is a family game.
Attack with weapon.
No, not yet.
No, if you put something down it needs to I need to be able to kill it.
See that needs to be I need to be able to kill that.
Oh, look at that.
No, I don't need to use that.
Well, maybe I should.
Why do I keep saying that?
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Don't get me.
Come on.
You want to see what that secret is, don't you?
Give me I'm gonna do it again.
I'm gonna freezing trap again.
Oh, yeah.
How's that sound?
Rank 25.
This.
God damn it.
I can't like just get rid of these.
Somebody came in.
Somebody just gave me a road.
Pirate hunter with a question mark.
It's bucket.
That's so funny.
Oh, this is it.
Five, six, seven, eight.
This is it.
I'm gonna win.
Yeah, I know.
Don't heal to full health.
We're gonna be rich.
No, it's all right.
Five out of five.
Oh, you have to restore five health.
What?
Oh, fuck.
It's all right.
I can get four, five, six, seven, eight.
Should I release the hounds?
Okay, come on.
Discover friendly death rental minion.
When an enemy attacks your heroes,
it attacks another random character.
Just misdirection or explosive trap.
The explosive trap, I think.
And then put it on and release the hounds.
If I release the hounds.
Oh, shit.
If I release the hounds, then I can...
Well, that shouldn't be trade.
But I need to trade
because now he doesn't have any minions.
Why do you have so many of these?
I swear to God, I've seen this seven times.
Freezing trap?
I'm the top Hearthstone streamer on Twitch right now.
Oh, no, no.
Three, six, seven.
It's over.
This is not a sponsored stream.
Oh, just...
This is so embarrassing.
Wait a minute, did you screw up?
I just won.
No, fuck.
No, stop healing.
He's gonna get these two again.
Why?
Oh, shit.
What else do I even have in here?
Now I'm gonna rope him.
Stuck in chicken league forever.
All right.
We just have to do this a couple more times.
I'm gonna...
Six pirates to play as...
We're just doing this to get to arena.
Unironically stuck at 25.
Yeah, but we just...
This deck is awful.
It's just...
I just put pirates together just to throw them in here and give...
Until we get to play arena.
Pirate hunter.
You think I'm...
He's buying more packs.
Maybe in some other lifetime.
If I...
Yeah, I haven't...
No, I haven't played Cal Drogo yet.
Let's go.
Buy packs with your sponsorship money.
Put the pack opening on your main channel.
Oh, you got this guy on the ropes.
Two turkeys.
Who's gonna make it out on top?
I wonder.
Oh, no.
Don't do that.
That...
I could like...
I was gonna just kill Commandment's face.
It has ranked 25.
Hold on, it says...
It has ranked 25 next to his name on the stream link.
What do you mean the stream link?
Wait, what?
Why does it say that?
Ranked 35.
That's fucking ridiculous.
Why would it say my rank?
I don't want it to say what rank I am.
What did he just do?
Uh, I'm just gonna put on freezing trap.
This is the...
Oh, Jesus.
Everyone on Twitch knows now.
Yeah, people are gonna scroll by and they're gonna know.
Everyone knows now.
I can't hide it.
I can't get over that in the tags.
It knows.
Ranked 25 is the best rank yet.
Ranked 25 is the highest rank you can be.
You can't get higher than 25.
You can go...
What happened?
I'm confused.
Hold on.
Can I get someone besides spells?
Yeah, no, you can't be...
This is the highest rank you can be.
You can...
Sure, you can go lower.
You can drop lower in rank.
But I'm the highest rank in Hearthstone.
Why do I have all these fucking spells?
Just get...
I don't want them anymore.
Just get them out.
Because you auto-completed your deck.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
We were just doing this to get to Arena.
Whenever this minion takes the...
What is that?
Summon a 2-3 mech with taunt.
He's waiting for that one.
This is the kind of shit you can experience
on the number one Hearthstone stream on Twitch.
Number one.
Ranked 25 plays.
This guy's pretending to be a noob
and he's going to pull out an OTK combo?
Like, dead in one turn?
I will laugh my fucking ass off
if I lose in one turn.
If I get one turn super comboed,
one turn...
I will cry laughing.
No, there's nothing wrong with this.
You know, the game is free
and anybody can just get it and play it.
And you've got to start somewhere.
Yeah, but you didn't just start.
Yeah, I have prob...
I'm not going to lie.
I'll be honest with you.
I absolutely have like 400 hours in this game.
I mean, maybe like 200 hours
of those are opening packs.
But this is like back in 2013.
Oh yeah, what a trade.
What?
What's happening?
Oh, the...
Get out, leave.
Don't come to this stream.
This stream is not one you want to watch.
The viewers have gone up by like 240.
You don't want to be here.
There's a stream like right there
that you should probably watch instead.
It's like over there.
Am I having fun?
Yeah.
He just got this game for father's day.
Yeah, my son told me to try this on.
It's called Hearthstone.
What do you got here?
Shuffle a bomb into your opponent's deck.
Well, I need a fucking minion.
Anybody die this turn?
Can we get a professional hand cam?
No.
A fucking hand cam?
Oh my God.
We need to see the inputs.
Did I actually just get echoed here?
Deal three damage, overkill.
So I'm gonna five-five Devilsaur.
That's all I need.
What is this?
Here comes a bomb.
Put on a professional foot cam.
What does that even...
What?
I'm not playing like the drums.
I think it is one.
No, God damn it.
Overkill.
Come on.
That's not it.
Three, four, five.
I need to kill something.
I didn't lose yet.
Not yet.
We lost.
No, not yet.
It's not over.
Oh God, here it comes.
No, I just need to get a damage card and I can do it.
I think it's still possible.
No, it's not.
Oh, oops.
I didn't mean to do that.
There's a couple of chicken league plays.
Not a big deal.
I'm dead.
He just has to click on me.
I'm getting BM'd, aren't I?
This is great.
Concede before he kills you.
No.
I'm gonna concede right when he's about to hit me.
50 gold, 50 gold, 50 gold.
Let's go to arena, boys and girls.
Where we going?
Who?
You want me to be Uther the Lightbringer?
Uther it is?
All right, we got the last arena deck.
You can call me terrible all you want, right?
Like obviously I was playing pirate fucking hunter,
but this is important.
The last arena deck was not very good.
It was very bad.
It was maybe like a one and a half out of 10.
So, I mean, you've seen me play heroic single player.
I was, I did all right.
I went through a couple runs of the normal one.
You've seen me play with the right cards.
I think we can accomplish something here.
Come on.
Give me some good ones.
Flame Juggler, you died on heroic.
Yeah, but I got to like the eighth boss or seventh boss.
Splog just gave five community subs.
Thank you, Splog.
All right.
Can I get banned for people playing on,
well, picking cards is I don't think is,
it's not like people have control of the game.
What are you doing?
Why are so many people clicking on this?
62%?
That's such a monster amount of people.
That what's wrong?
What is wrong?
70% of every person just clicked.
There has to be something going on.
What is it?
I'm not buying cards.
When two thirds of every person clicks on back,
I think that there's something wrong.
I'm not buying card packs.
Choose one of these.
I'm already opening card packs.
Every time you click on one of these,
you get to see another pack of three and you pick one.
All right.
So the only card you want me to pick is this one.
It sounds like a fucking plan, guys.
What are you doing?
I'm not actually going to click on lowly squire.
I'm not actually clicking on this.
Really?
This deck already has got trouble written all over it.
Hold on.
This can be influenced here.
Try it again.
That's better.
He's being disobedient.
I'm not clicking on the shop.
Scribe is the best one.
It's not even close.
You know, I wish I could click on it,
but I have to work with what I'm given.
Just for anyone that's curious,
this is the worst card in Hearthstone.
So I would veto if you even picked this.
Just pretend this one's not here.
People are voting for manor rate.
I feel like the people that are clicking on manor rate
and the people that are clicking on manor rate,
especially not manor rate,
especially the one in the middle there,
I think they were just doing it to make like a laugh.
You know what I mean?
You can't believe I paid for arena.
How much am I going to get there?
All right, this amoeba is starting to get together.
All right, so little exorcist, taunt, battle cry.
That's pretty good.
We have too many of these.
This is the best card in arena.
I know everyone's clicking on this.
Hey, what?
Oops.
Everyone was clicking on it.
I know you were.
Everybody clicked it.
By the way, guys, can we get a...
Excuse me.
If you're going to click,
please click like in the middle of the cards,
not like here or here.
You're making it...
You're making a big balloon.
Okay, now that we've had the discussion, go for it.
93...
What?
Oh, I guess I'm...
Okay, that was a...
All right, go for it.
I guess I'm just going to pick this one.
I'm going to say it's going to be...
How about...
I think it's going to be...
I need some one drops and it's going to be Glowtron.
Wrong choice.
I'm sorry, but I'm going by what I see on the screen.
Always Yeti.
Oh my fucking God.
I'm just going to pick the cards.
I'm just going to fucking pick them.
I'm just going to pick them.
He's literally crying.
You're doing this because you want me to open packs.
Is that what you really are saying right now?
Try it again.
Oh, fucking God damn it.
It doesn't matter.
I see you.
I see you guys right here.
I was going to pick the Yeti anyways.
Yeah, I got you.
You want Spellbreaker?
It's splitting up a little bit here.
Spellbreaker it is.
Always Antique Healbot.
You have to zoom in more.
Why are you clicking up here?
What are you guys doing?
Have I lost all faith in this right now?
Webinize Pinata.
I'm going to go 0-3 again because of this.
I'm about to step in here.
Choose a card equals Jerma's Choice.
Oh, nice.
That's a good idea.
Not like it matters.
12 of these cards have been awful.
You're going to go 0-3 because you're bad.
Now I'm going to go 0-3 because I just picked Weaponized Pinata.
Light's Justice.
Now I know you guys are just fucking with me.
What a joke.
This is worse than the last one.
This deck actually might be worse than the first one.
All right, we don't have very much.
We got like 13 more to do.
This is a tough one.
Actually, all these are good.
People are just clicking the golden card.
Three, two, one.
You gave us this power?
Yeah, and I'm going to try to at least win one game.
If I can go like two and two or two and three, I'll be happy.
Do three damage to all minions.
Jesus, this is close.
Say the name out loud of whichever card you want them to click.
It's not that hard.
I think you underestimate this community, okay?
I'll show you.
Please everybody click on Muster for Battle.
No, no, no, no, no.
Click on any other card.
Any other card.
I don't want that.
I want Minibot or...
Hey, please click on Shielded Minibot.
See?
Only 9%.
Hold on.
We're doing this again.
Everyone click on True Silver Champion.
If True Silver Champion does not have at least 40% of the vote,
the stream is turning off.
See, look at this.
Look at these anarchists over here.
15% just want this to turn off.
38% are just like, is he bluffing?
We got 47% good boys and good girls.
Hurry up.
This is part of the experience.
Bomblobber or Argent Protector?
This is very mid-heavy.
This experience is boring.
Hey, what?
It's boring.
It is.
Well, it won't be long now until it's over.
Which one was it?
Argent Protector, right?
We can't see the deck.
Well, if you had not been goofing around so much,
we wouldn't be so zoomed in.
You guys were goofing around.
All right, only like seven more cards to pick up.
You're the kind of person that punishes one person,
the whole class for one person's mistake.
I'm fairly certain it would be...
Okay, hold on.
I don't know if I don't agree with that.
It was like 38% of people in the classroom
were all throwing coins at me.
I'm going to keep everybody
and we're going to have a long discussion about it.
It was like more than 40%.
Sun River Spy.
Do we even have a secret?
I'm just being sabotaged.
We can't see the deck.
Okay, hold on.
You guys have learned your lesson.
Secrets.
Sacrifice.
All right, let me pull...
Hold on, let me pull this back.
There you go.
Now you can see the deck.
So, see?
This is what we got to work with.
Pretty balanced so far.
I almost just instantly clicked the zoom up.
I mean, why are you punishing all of us
for the mistake of one person?
Oh, but yeah, I threw a rock into the blackboard.
And so did the person next to me,
to the right and next to me to the left.
And two people behind me.
And three people in the front.
How many people are in the classroom?
There's like 26 people in the classroom.
Like 13 or 14 of us threw rocks.
Why are you punishing me?
One person.
These last ones got a count.
Kick out...
Yeah, half you guys are getting
going to the principal's office.
Jeremy, we all hate you.
This deck is fucking terrible.
This is randomized cards.
I'm taking the crocodile.
I'm picking the next ones.
I'm going to try to salvage this.
It's over.
All right, you can pick this a lot.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I don't know half these do.
This one's...
Murloc Knight is like really, really good.
50-50 split.
True Silver Champ.
Consecration.
All right, we're good.
Boys and girls, it's time.
Check hero portrait.
What about it?
You took the last three expansions
through dice in the air.
Like 200 dice and just gave random cards.
None of these work together.
I'm going to go 0 and 3 again
or like 1 and 3.
And everyone's going to make fun of me.
This is what I...
We're going to have to work with.
I have to bake a cake with cement
and feed it to people.
Let's go.
Quick retire to redo the deck.
I'm not.
You're not going to get me with that one.
I'm not going to sit here
and get berated by a teacher
who picked Steel Ranger.
We'll be alone.
I'm going for it.
And you know what?
Even if I make bogus plays,
I'm going to trust myself
and I'm going to play.
This deck is so bad.
So bad.
It is the worst deck
I think I've ever seen in the game.
I mean, you guys have truly outdone yourselves.
I picked this one.
But I'm, you know,
I'm going to block out all the negative energy.
I'm going to just play
even if I make mistakes.
You guys aren't even here with me.
I'm here.
I'm just looking at the screen by myself.
It's just me and this guy in a room together
with a chess board in front of us.
So with that being said,
I'm just, it's just me in the game.
Me in the cards.
I got the sunglasses on.
All right, that's fine.
Let me take a look here.
Okay, bingo.
Don't silence that.
Don't listen to that.
I can hear them,
but I can't, I can see their mouths moving,
but I can't hear them.
Wrong, wrong.
Not going to get it.
Absolutely fucking fantastic.
Keep it up.
I'm not in reading chat.
I'm playing this as if it was me in the bed.
Let me see what you guys say.
Let's all leave.
Oh, no, I'm not supposed to be looking at you.
I'm going to silence that.
No, give each player a spare part.
I want one.
I don't think there are any secrets
in the whole deck.
Miss, hit the 1-1.
Do it again.
That's perfect.
I'm fine with that.
I got avenging wrath coming up here.
This is a, like when you take a picture
of an avenging wrath turn,
it's this one.
I'm not looking.
I'm not looking over there.
Okay, now I think I'm going to taunt up this.
Or no.
Um, no, get it up.
Get more.
I'm going to fucking 100 all.
I'm busy.
I can't.
Mom, mom, I'm in the bathroom.
Mom just comes over
and slides a hundred dollar bill under the bathroom.
I've been in the toilet for like fucking 45 minutes
and mom slides a hundred under the bathroom door.
Mom, stop it.
Get out of here.
Uh, no, that was flutters.
Thank you so much for the fucking hundred dollars flutters.
Been a fan of you and stir
for the better part of six years.
I love your content and keep it up.
Thank you so much.
Glad to have you.
You've been around for a long time.
What do I do?
And then I'm going to taunt.
Which one do I taunt though?
I'm itching my head.
I'm turning fucking crazy.
Taunt the storm and I think that's what I would do.
I win.
You said it couldn't be done.
It's one game.
Relax.
Melanie is okay.
He's getting a little desperate.
Okay.
We're so close.
Here comes the murloc.
I ran him a legendary minion to your hand.
I can do them both.
Job done.
Greed is good.
1 and 0.
Oh fuck!
That did 25 damage!
Not 0 and 3.
1 and 0 actually.
This deck is giving me the middle finger.
You guys didn't even try to do that
and that's what you've done.
It's going to be 1 and 3.
Not yet.
1 and 0.
Let the hunt begin.
Night with honor.
See this is to trust myself.
Even if the plays are not perfect.
This is 2, 3, 4, 5.
I shouldn't do anything.
I get a perfect mana curve every turn.
I was gonna say if that was a 1.
All right.
Again.
Focus.
Coin out the exorcist.
No.
Good.
Play the curve.
I'm not looking at you guys.
Hold on.
I'm just gonna play the curve.
That's okay.
Although I could true silver this.
I got my steel rager.
The thing that everyone was laughing at me for.
We'll see if they're laughing now
when he drops a fucking thick 2, 5 right now.
They're not laughing.
Let's see.
I'm just gonna taunt.
Let me taunt and kill this.
I don't want him to have any minions.
I don't care if he kills this.
He's a hunter.
I got boulder frisk coming up here
and I've got jouster.
I got jouster right now.
Oh, that's not good.
I mean if it is snipe then
will this trigger it?
If it is snipe.
Come on.
Give me that health.
Yes.
Wait.
Somebody say snipe is not in arena.
I'm gonna go with this.
It's not.
What's going on?
All right.
Here we go.
Okay.
We're good.
Was he being mean?
Was that mean?
No.
I get the minions out of here.
I gotta get rid of those minions.
Oh never mind.
We gave it rush.
I was gonna say the steel erasure
seems pretty good right now doesn't it?
I'm gonna do bear into silver moon portal.
Excellent.
So what is this secret then?
I'm not familiar with some of the newer secrets.
Is rat trap the one where if you play
too many cards in a hand return
it'll summon like a big rat.
Three cards.
Okay.
He's thinking.
There's another one.
All right.
So we're gonna test.
I'm gonna send him straight in.
All right.
And it is explosive.
Bring out the rager.
Rager gets rid of this guy.
Uh oh.
It's snake trap.
Interesting.
I thought it was rat trap.
Why did it have to be snakes?
You don't get to do that twice do you?
All right.
I got I still have some pretty great minions here.
I got ogre and uh and stalker coming up next.
Silence the snake.
Why I'm not gonna do that.
A lot of rush.
Well all right.
Let's see here.
I could just flood the board and just go face and win.
That makes more sense.
Let's see.
Got anything else?
Or did I did I win?
You got a taunt?
You got a spell?
Are we two and oh?
All right.
Okay.
Um game over.
Let's well play.
Two and oh.
Now he's gonna go two and three right?
That's what you're gonna say.
Yeah there it is.
Even if I get to like 11 and oh.
It's not gonna happen.
Well there's the squire.
Here comes a mirror match.
That's not good.
Oh that was a juicy one.
Juicy one buddy.
Coin taunt.
That's oh there's only it's supposed to one attack.
Okay I'm not paying attention.
I know they're probably making fun of you right now.
But don't let them make fun of you.
It was the right call.
It's okay.
Gotta get in there.
All right hold on.
Hold on just a second.
I mean let's not be hasty here.
Not the time for equality.
Why is this so much mana?
Did it just be two mana?
Uh do I hit?
I don't.
No don't do anything.
He's gonna get greedy.
He's gonna hit me in the face.
Okay not greedy.
I have a consecration in here.
Where is it?
Oh fuck I forgot what that thing did.
Um do I kill this or do I let him kill it?
Maybe.
All right now just attack me in the face with that 5-1.
I'm in a good spot but it's not a terrible spot.
Could be worse.
Why is everyone doing the flat liner?
Oh you're saying here the flat liners.
If I get a consecration right here this is...
I remember you could do the quality consecrate.
That's not good.
I mean this is the only play is this.
2-1.
You guys aren't very supportive are you?
Shit.
I need consecration.
It's in here.
That's not consecration but it can at least take out the mechanical yeti.
How did this happen?
I started out with bad plays.
I started out with bad cards.
This is not over yet.
I just have to draw a consecration.
We're back to square one.
If I draw a consecration right now the board is empty.
That's not consecration.
That's it.
2-1.
Sometimes you lose them.
It's all right.
We'll get it back.
We'll get them next time.
We will.
Yeah we have exponentially improved.
This was a 0-3 stream.
It's now a 2-1 stream.
Imagine improving by 2-300%.
Over the course of five hours.
That's a large increase.
200% of zero is zero.
Now the zero and three was like...
It wasn't actually zero.
It was like zero point...
What the hell was that?
Oh.
It was like 0.4-3.
So 200% of that is like...
We're doing fine.
That's the wrong one.
You picked the wrong one to do that too.
Mathematically it was zero but emotionally it was a bigger number.
Yes.
Okay.
I think I'm gonna just throw out the weaponized pinata.
In fact I am.
This is a good Fortnite reference.
Have you guys even ever played Fortnite?
I see so many references but I don't think you guys even play it.
Ooh.
All right.
What's more important?
Two and two and a two cost minion or getting a taunt out and hitting the face?
That's cooler to me.
Things are looking up.
A good bolderfist ogre coming out next.
Do I get these next turn?
My remedies are all natural.
No he has to trade.
He's gonna lose both.
I mean yeah he can draw all he wants.
He's dead next turn.
Where did he get this like synergy from?
This is a pretty good spot.
He drew a bunch of cards.
Right now he's thinking oh fuck he's got big damage.
See I'm all right with that.
We're getting the legendary out of this.
He had to take a lot of hits for that.
What do we got?
Varian Rin.
Hahaha that could be the victory right there.
I mean we're gonna obviously we're gonna divine shield the ogre right?
I mean we got a good play here.
Divine shield the ogre taunt or taunt divine shield the taunt.
And then get it out here.
Next we got Varian.
That's that don't matter because you ready for this?
You still have to get through that.
I'm not gonna I'm not no no no no that's a mistake.
I'm not gonna play Varian.
No we're just gonna go face.
You gotta get through and I got I got the quality.
Six get rid of you.
That's there's too many people on the board.
No I'm not playing it yet.
I'm not gonna play it.
No no I'm not playing it.
There's four there's gonna be I've just draw.
Should I play it?
Next turn next turn I'm doing next turn.
God damn it.
It's all right.
Check this shit out.
You ready?
I'm gonna I'm gonna equality right now and kill everything.
And then I'm gonna play Varian next turn.
Don't do it now.
I'm doing it right now.
Good.
Not good.
Pretty good.
All right now we just go face and fucking win the game.
I got too much with this too much going on here.
It's too overwhelming and I still have equality.
16 what's he got?
What the fuck is this?
How did you get two of these?
Hold on what do I have for health?
How much does this cost?
That's a six cost minion.
All right so we've got three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven.
Twelve.
Shit.
Do I just equality and kill everything and then put the face just go off.
Oh I'm fucking panicking.
This is okay.
Yeah this is okay.
I still have equality.
If he can summon anything you want.
No the game's over.
I don't think he can kill everything.
Oh god give me a break.
He's got so many fucking healing synergies.
Well can I have my consecration now?
Four five six seven eight nine.
If I played the stealth goblin I would have won.
All right I'm gonna kill.
What the fuck do I want to get rid of here?
Extended BM.
Got to kill that seven one.
What am I doing wrong?
That was okay that was okay.
All right you have to remember I'm not very good at this game and I look over here and I see
like a wall of people fucking holding up notes.
Sticking them to the wall.
Hey look at this.
You have to do it like this quick.
You got like fucking sticky notes all over my fucking windows.
And I'm just like panicking.
Where's my avenging wrath?
Oh my consecration and I win.
He forgot about the dragons.
Oh and then you get equality.
Equality.
Dead.
Two dragons.
Or face two dragons.
Noble sacrifice and fuck it.
I can't like play this with people like watching.
I seriously.
I look over I just like I can't focus on the game.
It's like I need to like concentrate.
Well there it is.
Thanks for it fucking five turns late.
I should have even used the equality.
Now we're just topdecking against each other.
I could have won.
Yeah and I'm also playing with like fucking anvils on my back.
Look at this guy's deck.
It's so good.
I've I've like dragon anvils with this deck.
I finally played the goblin.
Oh well.
I think he's healed like 14-15 times this game.
Does it still be impossible?
Why do I have coins?
What else do I have in here?
I really could have won too.
Just I get too overwhelmed.
This is why I don't play this game.
Not over yet.
Hey it ain't over yet.
It's this this turned into a top deck war.
Because I didn't play the goblin and half lethal.
One of us gets something big it's over.
Believe in your deck.
All right let's draw.
All right what do we get?
What?
Well I did I did did somebody say I can't can't he he fell for it.
Fucking hilarious.
Coin and you got a legendary too.
Where are my legendaries?
I can hold on top deck something crazy.
Come on come on come on.
Here we go.
Come on come on.
Let me just pull this out of my asshole right now.
So let me I'm gonna take this bear.
I need to get rid of justicar and then.
All right and then should I hit you too.
Should I just completely trade everything and then do it.
Bad play we're talking about.
Wait wait what's going on.
If I pull this out of my ass.
If I win with the silver hand recruits.
No there's no way you're gonna he's gonna get two armor every turn.
I'm gonna get fatigued.
He only needs two turns to win three turns to win.
He's gonna hit me twice.
I need to heal.
Do I have any heals?
All right come on a taunt.
I don't lose though.
Hold on because that's this is dead.
I have to trade everything.
Use the coin.
The coin doesn't do anything.
This is the most clown dog shit fucking game ever.
I need something I need something ridiculous.
I have one health.
All right come on something.
Would have been three and one.
No I really I'm gonna be two and fucking three.
Let the hunt begin.
I will fight with honor.
I'm so sad right now.
This is like watching a car crash in slow motion.
This is like watching a car crash in fast motion.
All right I'm gonna throw five and three.
Coin croc-a-lisk.
No wait it's 20 minutes per match not high motion.
It's all right it's okay.
Coin.
Uh what does that do?
Some of the three too big bad wolf.
Yeah get the taunt out here.
It's like watching a car crash that keeps happening.
Well I have divine shield now.
Divine shield get rid of this and then play the gloatron.
You know what this kind of feels like.
So I went to a I went to a cake competition and I brought with me um boxed little Debbie cake.
By the way I've never made a cake before.
At this cake competition there are like 500 other people here
that have been making cakes for 10 years and while I'm making my cake
just over there I don't plan on winning.
Everybody else making their cakes are like shouting out
hey your cake sucks your cake is gross my cake is delicious.
All right what do I want to do here?
Uh this is my responsibility.
What do you got in here?
He's gets it's definitely explosive trap.
Oh I called it called it I called it.
You have 400 hours I have 400 hours I had like lying.
I had like 200 hours in this game in 2013.
The cars that I played with don't even exist anymore.
I remember this one.
Do you remember that one?
All right we got another trade here that I don't really want to make.
200 hours of making terrible cakes.
All right I get a focus here.
I'm going lights you got it in my head already.
Lights camera cake.
Can I say I can silence that right?
Is that that is that kind of a spell or a hero power?
Is that a spell or a hero power?
Sorry got you.
My cake's not good but you haven't even eaten it yet.
It was just deal three damage to all minions.
Well this is not going to be good.
He's going to clear everything.
I mean I just have to do this right?
If only I had the silence.
Yeah get that coffee pasta shit out of here.
Get that coffee pasta shit the fuck out of here.
I don't want to see that shit.
Justice.
The single most predictable result in the chat room.
I know I know.
I get it put it in cake only mode emote only.
I don't want us to get emote only.
I don't want to they don't deserve my cake.
Somebody got to fuck you in right before it happened.
You don't deserve my cake.
What's what's going on?
He just released a house?
Well that's all right because I got bang bang.
It's kind of on the ropes.
Just don't kill me.
Let me go three and two.
That's a pretty good KD in a server.
That's above 500.
All right three four five six seven.
Any of these mech?
I'm dumping everybody four five six seven eight nine.
I gotta go for it.
I want a legendary.
You know what just do it.
Justice.
I have lethal right now.
He has to kill something and I've got doctor blast.
He has to get rid of everything.
That's a fucking mech.
Did I just lose?
No I didn't just lose.
I can't fucking believe it.
Oh my god.
That's great synergy.
I don't have a single fucking synergy card in the entire deck.
In the whole deck.
I don't whatever it's over.
No I won.
I just won the game.
I just won the game with one health.
Wait wait wait just make sure I have it.
There you go guys.
Oh yeah okay he's not even very good at the video game.
He's not even I don't think he's very good at this.
All right take it off emote only they're behaving.
You guys.
Would you like some of my cake?
I made it special for you.
I made it special for you guys.
My stream was crashing because of the emotes.
See I'm saving you.
I'm okay with three and three that's even.
No that's not hello.
I tried to say where's hello.
That's like ultimate ultra BM.
Like I but I did not turn one coin.
That's right not gonna really okay.
I can do that too.
Am I gonna get absolutely fucked if I start playing this game without spending money?
No they give you they give you packs.
They do you get like five to ten packs.
I mean you could do a Reno.
Actually rank 50 is pretty fair.
Let's keep the control up here.
I wonder do you think he's got like a polymorph?
Should I get this out there right now?
Or should I throw out the herald and face?
I'm gonna herald and face or spell word and haste.
Go back to Mario Yahtzee.
I already dominated that game to a point where I don't even care anymore.
I'm gonna bring in a gurubashi berserker.
Now this is a scenario where I'm gonna potentially equality this.
No I could.
It wouldn't be that bad.
I'm not sure that would be the worst thing.
Or to get the tuskar out here.
Okay next turn with murloc and hero power.
Next spell we got oh that's not good playing cannon.
Fuck.
No okay I could do sword and I could do sword and equality and kill this.
That keeps me alive.
Or sword and oh fuck equality's four mana.
Shit I don't know what to do.
I think I'm just gonna have to do murloc and hit hero power.
I'm itching my head again.
It is sending just stuff to die but I need to put I have to have something here.
Otherwise he's just gonna start to destroy me.
And it is a terrible murloc but at least it's not terrible.
Still plenty of cards.
Interesting.
He wants to keep this alive so he can do that.
Okay.
All right.
Ogre and gloatron I think is the only thing I can do.
You have to get rid of it.
I'm happy I'm here for Jeremy to teach the game.
Yeah I've got some strategies here.
He lost every game.
That's a lie.
Don't listen to that.
I'm three and two right now.
At least be truthful about it.
He thought about it.
He's not trading.
Huh.
So just get some minions on the board and fucking what does this do?
Whenever you cast dispel summon random three cost beast that's not good.
I think it is time for equality.
It's time for equality.
Trade first.
I mean doesn't it does not matter.
I guess.
Not that one.
Wrong trade.
You guys saying the robot and I thought it was the rope.
Whatever.
I'm gonna stick to peeing my pants on stream.
That's probably easier.
That's it.
I lose.
Should have drawn I wish I drew consecration in six games.
That would be fun.
All right.
That's it.
No no more arena.
Arena just like I was like happy and chipper when we were playing
in the solo adventure and then I go to arena and I play against players that have cards
and it becomes a disaster.
No actually I had a lot of fun.
I'm so happy that I streamed this game for one reason for the comedic purpose
of being the number one Hearthstone streamer on Twitch for like 45 minutes
or like a couple hours or something and having ranked 25 next to my name.
That was just worth it completely.
It just was.
I was in the number one spot for like what 20 minutes or 30 minutes or something
but that's gonna be it.
That brings us right to like a nice perfect clean six hours.
It's fun to do this every once in a while.
Play like the game that a lot of people play.
Even if I wasn't playing that well and it was just kind of all over the place.
I still had a lot of fun.
It was fucking great.
So tomorrow we are never going to see this again.
I'm gonna get...
Good night everybody.
See you next time.
See you tomorrow.
I'm gonna play Cooking Simulator tomorrow.
Have a great day.
Have a great night guys.
This dream is gonna turn up and I'm just gonna scream into my hands.
No.
Tomorrow we're gonna come back.
I was supposed to play Cooking Simulator today but it wasn't out.
So tomorrow is gonna be even more probably of a shitshow
but the game actually releases tomorrow.
It's the only reason why I'm not playing it today.
Do you have any plans to play...
Okay, I'm gonna give you my actual classic wild plan.
I probably am just gonna play it off stream.
And on stream maybe sometimes when we do something fun.
Maybe we'll try to like raid Ogramar or something with like 50 people.
Just try to take over the capital or something for like certain streams.
Might be fun to do.
But off stream I plan on just kind of casually playing it.
I'll probably make a guild.
I'll let everybody know the server I'm on if you guys want to play it.
Just have like a group of people that just play it off and on.
Should be fun.
Looking forward to it.
Try to actually take down like Onyxio or something on stream with chat.
Whatever the guild is try to do it without any voice over IP and like no communication.
It would be fucking hilarious.
But I'll see you tomorrow if you take it up.
I'm gonna go just take a quick pee break.
I'll be right back.
And we'll do the bits and the subs and everything.
There was a shitload of subs.
There was a ton of fucking money.
I know it was like a little like sub train and stuff in the beginning.
And we were making jokes about it.
But that was a lot of subs and a lot of fucking money in the beginning of the stream.
Hope you enjoyed it.
As always, I had a blast.
At least I got to three wins.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you tomorrow for Cooking Simulator.
Don't miss it.
I will be right back.
See you soon.
All right.
Hey, what is this mic peak?
Save it.
I've been a manual save in a while.
That kind of wasn't mic peak.
You're right.
Angry chat.
What are these clips?
You are going to get frustrated on this stream.
You're going to be mad at me.
You're going to yell at me.
You're going to call me names.
Anything else?
And I'm going to puff my chest out and be like, yeah, right.
I kind of did that a few times.
All right.
Let me get off like that.
Let's get the correct screen on.
Why not, right?
Let's go over the bits from earlier.
We had so many...
Just wait till you see the subs fly by.
They are going to...
Oh, my God.
This is ridiculous.
I'm scrolling fucking forever.
How many subs there were today for community sub?
Wow.
Yeah.
When you see the credits, just wait till you see these fly by.
Anyways, let's start back here.
About six plus.
A little six over six hours ago or so.
We had a cut tag for the $8.
Thank you for eight bucks.
Whoa, dude.
Nice card.
I got like three legendaries and 20 packs.
That's actually really fucking good.
That's really good.
But thank you.
Cut tag.
Oh, gee.
Jeff Durr.
Thanks for the $10.
Says he doesn't want to get hyped and energetic,
but then today he is screaming in the first 30 minutes.
Yeah, but like my brain is hyped up, but my body isn't.
I get to just kind of...
Whatever.
The other way around.
It's comfy.
I'm comfortable, you know?
Even if I yell a little bit,
I use my nasal patches just for the air to come out,
not my stomach, so I'm fine.
Hopefully he did well in Hearthstone.
Nobody tell him.
But thank you, OG Jeff Durr for the 10 bucks.
Really appreciate it.
And then I think I missed this earlier.
Some guy gave another $50 earlier.
It's a Doom OST or Riot.
Thank you for the huge amount of money.
It was $150, I think, today.
Yeah, just look at the fucking board.
My god.
There was hundreds of dollars just running in at the same time.
I'm sorry I missed something if I did.
But thank you nonetheless.
So many community subs.
Thank you dot me.
Dot is me.
Dot see me for the $5.
And they just say hype.
Hype.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
They also say pride 100.
Thank you for the $5.
Thank you hack it fast for $10.
Hack it fast.
Recommend me a good whiskey.
Also, I eat ass.
Oh, I got that earlier.
Yeah.
If you want to spend a lot of money, Johnny Walker Blue.
If you want to spend a little bit about like $30, $40 a bottle,
Johnny Walker Black, Johnny Walker Red.
Johnny Walker is just good if you like whiskey.
Mike said about E3.
I'm going to come covering E3.
We're getting a full on professional coverage from me.
Don't suggest red.
No, it depends.
You know, some people just want to,
you want to spend like, you know, 25, 30 bucks on a bottle of alcohol.
Johnny Walker is like saying to drink Budweiser if you like lagers.
What?
Johnny Walker Blue is really good.
Johnny Walker Blue is a very, very high quality alcohol.
I mean, it's not like Jack Daniels.
The dude that does two different kinds of,
those two different things, but.
Jack Daniels is the Budweiser of whiskey.
I'm going to have to disagree with you on that.
It's all the same shit.
Just go get a jug of vodka for five bucks.
You could, but thank you.
Hack it fast.
Also, Glen Fetich is another great one if you like whiskey.
Whiskey tastes like a house fire.
Hey, quats or cats.
Thanks for $5.
Sorry.
I'm just a, just a common $500 bit donation in that pack.
If you were here in the beginning of the stream,
when I was opening the packs, $50 would come out.
I would open a card pack and like 20 community subs would show up.
Sorry, just a common 500 bit donation in that one.
$5 is still a lot of money to give anybody.
Thank you for $5.
I'm honored to accept it.
Oh, I hear a little barking auto.
Thank you also to cats again for $5.
They say pride 500 and then.
Uh, beater, beater, auto.
What are you barking at?
He never barks like this.
Listen to him.
He doesn't.
I've never heard him bark like that.
Hold on.
Can you hear that?
He never barks.
Hold on.
Let me go.
Let me go see.
Let me go investigate it.
We're back.
Yeah, it's just, it was an intruder.
I just like, I fucking punched him all the way.
He flew all the way to the police station and they put him in handcuffs.
That was Kim.
She was just, uh, she was outside.
Now she's back inside.
I got my Hearthstone sponsor check.
I, no, I did not.
No, I did not.
No, no, no, no.
All right.
Thank you for the bits.
Here we go.
Uh, we got $19.50.
50, it was $50 so many times.
You guys are fucking so generous.
Thank you.
Jamie, 2803.
Thanks for the $10.
They say, Jerome Hart.
Thank you for the 10 bucks.
There's a little room right there.
A flair pancake.
Thanks for the $2.75.
Hey, Jerome, I'm back from my trip to the Philippines.
I had a great time, but the whole time I was worried that without my constant attention,
you'd turn into some normie streamer.
Sorry, Jerome, I won't let this happen again.
It didn't happen.
It was you.
It didn't come true.
Whatever.
I played Hearthstone on one stream.
Oh, what's the big deal?
I played Hearthstone for like fucking five and a half hours, one time.
I just wanted to do it.
We just fucking throwing the feelers out, guys.
I had a good time.
No, you did.
Yes, I did.
I thought it was fun.
I had a lot of fun too.
This is definitely not the worst stream.
Yeah, what?
You're going to put this in the 2019 worst stream category?
No, I call bullshit on that one.
Worse than days gone?
I'm sorry, but that is not correct.
Days gone was fun too.
There hasn't even been a candidate for 2019 worst stream.
I'm on a roll this year.
What was that?
There really hasn't been.
Has there been like a worst of 2019 stream?
We are going into the middle of June.
I did.
I played Mario Tennis last year.
I'm on a roll this year.
I could give you at least two or three by the time we got to March last year.
Must be that fucking fresh Vegas air.
Vegas air quality is like some of the worst in the country.
I think it's up there somewhere.
Air is overrated.
But anyways, I have a lot of fun.
I did.
I really did.
You can tell that I'm not having fun because I'm not like engaging
and I'm just sitting there like whatever.
Okay, so yeah, I think I'm going to move on.
I'm going to do something else.
Great fucking time with all of you.
Okay.
There was a moment where you screamed at chat.
Are you excited?
Yeah, like I was excited.
I was just checking to see if you were also excited too.
And at least 40 people wrote it.
But anyways, let's get closer to the end here.
But welcome back.
That was FlarePancake for $2.75.
Hope you had fun on your trip to the Philippines.
And we also had Tingy.
$2.50 from Tingy.
I'm sorry this is a little too low effort.
I did only a couple minutes to make it.
This is your chat in a nutshell.
Chat in a nutshell.
Let's see.
Doesn't it seem a little harsh to kill someone over a crown?
You don't understand.
My crown is a symbol of my king-like authority.
And between you and me, my hair is thinning a bit.
Oh, your highness.
I'm sure it's not that noticeable.
I'm not even fucking bald.
All right.
I can understand if I had like a fryer tuck on the top of my head.
Thank you, Tingy.
That was funny.
Show the hairline right now.
I can't.
I'm naked.
Your deck sucks and you're bald.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
Somebody wrote that.
So vicious.
So mean.
How did I raise such vicious children?
We've learned it from you.
No, you didn't.
I said, have a great night.
Hope you have a good time and take care, guys.
How did I raise such vicious, vicious children?
Am I going to get a Death Stranding stream?
Maybe.
Probably.
Looks interesting.
There are a couple of big games that are coming out that I know I'll be playing.
We talked about Cyberpunk 2077 last night.
And whenever that comes out, absolutely.
Can we get a Pac-Man stream?
I'd love to just go back and play that Super Nintendo Pac-Man is a moron game
and try to actually beat it.
It would be hell on earth, but I would try.
But yeah.
Uh, Tom, Tom York's sleazy eye dot.
Why is this all in lowercase?
I'm just going to say Tom.
Thank you, Tom, for the five dollars.
I can't wait to, like, have the update where I can see actual capital letters.
But thank you for the five dollars.
And they say Pride 500.
Thank you.
Slade King, thanks for five dollars.
Also says Pride 100.
Pride 100.
Thank you, Slade King, for the five dollars.
Both of you back to back there.
Thank you.
Oh, the music's not on.
Fine.
And we also had a Heartache Cubed ten dollars.
Jerma, I was the guy with the healing deck.
GG.
Good game.
That deck was fucking pretty good.
You're a pretty good player.
Hey, nice job.
See you on the field.
But Heartache Cube, thanks for the ten dollars.
Jerma, it's my birthday in two days.
Please be my dad.
I can wish you a happy birthday, but I cannot be your father.
Thank you for the ten dollars.
And happy birthday in exactly two days from now.
Please.
All right, dad for a minute.
Here you go.
You got ten seconds of dead.
Son, nice work.
You played good out there.
See you on the field.
And then a little, like, just a little, like, I put my fist down,
and I give you, like, we bumped.
And it's just, there you go, son.
But I got a motherfucking one.
See how tall that grass has gotten?
And I got a call from your teacher.
You fell asleep in class, and then when you woke up,
you made a fart noise with your mouth.
Go to your room.
I mean, with my Johnny Walker blue.
How did I raise such a vicious son?
Go back to the wall, dad.
No, I'm not going back in there.
It smells in there.
Hey, but hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
And you look over your shoulder.
And I give you a wink, and I go,
you're my one and only.
And then we both nod.
Let's go get hot dogs tomorrow.
I think I just, yeah, somebody just said,
is that a coming-of-age movie?
I think that was, like, a movie.
I think that's every movie that has, like, a dad in it.
That was a long 10 seconds.
Yes, it was.
Okay, but happy birthday.
It was a pleasure being your dad for 10 seconds,
which was actually like four minutes.
But no, seriously, thank you so much for 10 bucks.
Freudian weapon, thanks for five dollars.
Maybe it's because I think you're insanely cool,
but I always have the uncanny need to play games
that you streamed.
I played Hearthstone once five years ago.
Didn't care for it then,
yet now I found my cursor gliding toward the download button.
Uh-oh.
But seriously, keep doing your thing.
Have a good night, Jermaheart.
Yeah, I don't know.
I just got, like, bit by the bug for some reason.
A few old games that I used to play
more than, like, three, four, five years ago,
I've started to creep up into my brain again.
And I'm like, yeah, I remember that was fun.
Don't be surprised if you see some more of it
thinking about downloading Hearthstone again.
I really do like their, this solo stuff.
It's so replayable.
The other ones, the first, like, two or three years
of the game when they made those adventures,
they were cool.
But these new adventures,
you can just play them a million times.
You just ignored a wave of, uh, something in the chat.
I don't know what it was.
The fuck?
People saying, like, the fuck, like, what the fuck, two?
Like, times, like, plus two, minus two?
I don't know.
Whatever that is.
I think it seems like it might be fun.
But thank you, Freudian, for the five dollars.
I guess when you see somebody just doing anything,
you kind of remember the time that you also did it.
And then maybe you weren't even thinking about Hearthstone today.
And I just happened to put it in your brain.
And then you're like, yeah, why not?
Happens to me all the time.
Thank you, Trampston, for the five dollars.
Game sucks.
I'm going to bed.
Have a good night.
I hope you have a good rest.
Thank you for the five dollars.
Freudian Weapon, thanks for two dollars and 50 cents.
By the way, I can't wait for Cooking Simulator.
Neither can I.
I've been waiting a long time for it.
I am very, very excited for tomorrow.
Hey, Smelly Boy, thanks for the two fifty.
Imagine being a Hearthstone stream watcher,
clicking the most watched Hearthstone stream,
and seeing the TF2 Spie guy from four years ago
getting his ass kicked constantly.
Wait, hold on.
First of all, you make that sound like the TF2 Spie guy.
You know, I made more than one video.
Oh, hey, oh, that's the TF2 Spie guy.
I have like a thousand uploads.
You are the TF2 Spie guy.
No, that's not what I am.
I'm so many other things.
I'm so many.
I'm so much more than that.
I'm going to go delete them.
It's time to delete those videos, yeah.
But yes, thank you for the two.
That was so funny.
I hope people save those screenshots
because that'll get a good laugh out of me
in the future when I forget about it.
Podcast Listener, thanks for ten dollars.
Back at it again with the bits, boys.
Germa checks.
There were a lot of them tonight.
I highly appreciate it.
You guys hand over huge amounts of money
and I fucking graciously accept.
Thank you.
Also, and then a couple hours ago
was a hundred dollars from Flutters.
We touched upon it,
but Flutters has been around for a long fucking time.
More than six years.
So thanks for being around.
Glad you still think it's interesting enough to watch
and be a part of.
Invader Z, thanks for the 250.
Hey, Germa, have you ever played Magic the Gathering?
I've been playing Commander a lot recently with friends.
I was wondering if you played it
since you're playing Hearthstone, which is similar.
I think I touched upon it a little bit,
but just in case you weren't here when I did.
I'm not really that into card games.
I don't really play a lot of card games.
Hearthstone is just very easy to just do random stuff
and have fun and open up minions
and have random acts.
And I don't know if I would be able to get into Magic.
Lives in Vegas, doesn't like cards.
No, that's a different kind of card.
MTG is definitely more involved.
Yeah, and I mean, obviously Hearthstone stream,
us hanging out and me dicking around
and going three and three and like oh and three
and like losing on heroic and just hanging out.
That's fine.
And it's fine.
And obviously, I don't think I'd want to do that
with like Magic the Gathering
because I'm not sure if there's any opportunities to do that.
Can you just like open up a game of Magic the Gathering
and just like not know every card
and try and get destroyed?
Would that be as interesting as Hearthstone?
Because I don't know anything about MTG, zero.
MTG might give you a heart attack,
but probably not.
You need to be really good at to have much fun with.
Yeah, and Hearthstone is right at that kind of layer
of casual and fun,
but still has like a good skill ceiling in it
in various ways.
There's still a meta in the game.
There's lots of things you need to know,
but not like Magic.
It's got a Magic has a lot more going on
that I wouldn't even be able to comprehend for a second,
but probably not.
And I still got destroyed in Hearthstone.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
That's kind of kind of what I'm saying.
Tingy, thanks for the 250.
I'm sorry, Dad.
We love you.
Jerma Pluto.
I'll be sorry, son.
You're a good boy.
You're just such a smart young lad.
Thank you.
M Weldo, thanks for the three dollars.
Think we all know what happened on that phone call yesterday.
Keep up the funny bits.
What happened on the phone call yesterday.
All right.
We'll put my agent on the line then.
I don't know why.
Is this like, is this Dr. Disrespect?
Why do I have to go?
Yeah, I don't know why, ladies and gentlemen.
I don't know why I have to go through his secretary
every single time.
Hello?
Hey, yeah.
So, hey, I got some inside knowledge.
Shroud's trying to tease me about potential revenue share,
some sort of battle royale experience.
You got any inside info?
No, I'm at a movie.
You still driving that Prius?
I just like spit all over the screen.
All right.
This isn't new.
Hold on.
You still driving that Prius?
It's like.
What was that?
Oh, no, I'll call you back.
I'm going to put it on the screen.
That's fucking funny.
No, I'm at a movie.
I'm going, I'm going.
I'm getting it on screen.
Look.
All right.
We'll put my agent on the line then.
I don't know why.
Like, why do I have to go?
Yeah.
I don't know why, ladies and gentlemen.
I don't know why I have to go through his secretary
every single time.
Hello?
Hey, yeah.
So, hey, I got some inside knowledge.
Shroud's trying to tease me about potential revenue share,
some sort of battle royale experience.
You got any inside info?
Why would I?
No, I'm at a movie.
You still driving that Prius?
Yeah, that's like.
What was that?
Oh, no, I'll call you back.
Oh, a Team Fortress Classic with Star.
Fucking hell, yeah.
Oh, you got any inside intel on that?
And am I the secretary?
I got to go through his secretary and it's me.
Here's a link for those of you that want it.
That was funny.
That was M Weldo.
Thanks for the three bucks.
And thanks for the video.
And what do you say we get the credits on the screen?
This is going to be pretty wild.
You ready?
Here are all the subs from this stream.
As a rumor right there.
Jesus.
It had to have been at least a few, like more than a few hundred.
Opening Hearthstone card packs.
It's going so fast that it's lagging the plugin.
I'm losing, I'm dropping frames.
My frame rate is being dropped here.
But thank you all of you.
Thank you to all the community subs.
There was a shit loader in that first 30, 40 minutes.
You guys are too kind.
Thank you.
What do I say in the phone?
Somebody's screaming, put the phone down.
Well, it's me screaming it, but thank you to all of you.
We do have two more bits that came in.
We have Spooge for three dollars.
Hey, Germo, still nine months sub.
Where's the baby?
Also, what are some games you're looking forward to seeing at E3?
I know you had a rough time with Mountain Blade, but was that 2019?
It was, wasn't it?
Okay.
Yeah, we have a candidate.
Yeah, well.
But, uh, give multiplayer a chance because that's where it really shines
and keeps an eye out for its sequel.
Or keep an eye out for its sequel, Bannerlord, if it ever comes out.
I can't, this is still going this fast.
Yeah, this mod's for two.
I just got so soured on it because I just, it was, I don't know.
It was half of me trying to figure out what to do
and the other half of trying to, you know, having people telling me things
and what to do and where to go.
It's kind of a perfect storm of things.
There's a lot of systems in that game that you have to pay attention to.
Bannerlord 2040.
Yeah, something like that.
Allmu said, I have surgery coming up and they're going to put me under.
It is my first time, so I can get some support.
Yeah, hopefully it goes well.
Hopefully your surgery goes well.
Anesthesia is a lot scarier the way that it seems rather than the way that it is.
So don't worry about that.
When I was put under, it was really comfortable.
I just kind of fell right asleep.
You don't really even, you don't really even know.
You're just lying there wherever you are
and somebody's like, okay, hey, you comfortable?
You good?
And it's like, yeah, I'm all right.
I'm okay.
And they, you know, slowly give it to you
and you, it just kind of, not in like a weird, scary way or anything,
but you just kind of, almost like you just kind of wake up.
You just wake up.
It's strange because you'll feel, you'll have the,
if you have an anesthesia in an IV, you just start to drift a second
and one, two, you're awake in the recovery room.
So that's kind of the way that it's happened to me
the last one or two times that I've had it.
You'll get some food if you can eat,
depending on what you have in for surgery.
But it's a lot, and they all know this,
these people are pros, right?
They know that people are nervous.
They know that, you know, it's kind of stressful.
You've got like five people.
When I had my colonoscopy this past week,
it was, you know, there's like four or five people
in the room all have masks on.
Like, okay, like, come over here.
And it's just like, oh, okay, all right, all right.
How are we doing?
But they're all, they want to take really good care of you.
They care about it.
Then most surgeons, most doctors and most anesthesiologists,
they've been doing it for a long time.
They know exactly what to do.
So I wouldn't worry about it at all.
You're going to get up
and you're not even going to realize it happened.
But I wish you luck.
All the love and support to you for real.
And let us know how it goes.
And finally, we have potato trapdoor
for $5 come in right now.
Six years of watching German on YouTube
and I finally watch a stream.
Glad to be here.
Welcome.
Hope you had fun.
Hope you enjoyed the stream.
And thanks for being around for six years.
Time flies.
Flies, flies, flies.
I will see you all tomorrow.
Same time.
Well, we started a little on the earlier side today.
Yeah, between three and four, same normal time.
Cooking simulator.
It's going to get rowdy in here tomorrow.
I can tell you that.
I'll do some stream legends for those of you that want it.
See you tomorrow.
Get some sleep.
Have a great rest of the night.
Goodbye, everybody.
Take care.
Ta-ta.