Okay, hamster playground it is. Somebody, we were talking about this the other day, right?
Somebody in mod chat put this in the mod chat. Let's see, let's see how it is.
I don't even have the game installed. This game is 12 gigs? Wow. Well, let's try.
We're gonna, you're gonna F a little bit because I'm downloading a game.
I just, oh, okay, I won't move so there won't be like a lot of data.
40%, 53%, 80%. Yeah, that's the power of fiber. When it works, it's great.
I just downloaded a 12 gig game in like maybe one and a half minutes straight. That's it.
Back to normal. Okay, so this is called hamster playground. We made the hamster joke before.
Hopefully the game's not too loud. Let's just double check that it isn't.
Hamster playground. We might actually leave this in 10 minutes tops.
Can you see? Okay, I select your house. Why can't you see it? Um, it's like my house.
House one. Great. Um, hammy zone. Ham zone to play.
What kind of hamsters or their cards to select them? Use arrow keys or WASD on the...
Uh, we'll click on the floor and hold the mouse button to move around the house.
You need to take care of your hamsters. They need to eat, drink, play, sleep, groom, and poop.
You can click on... Okay. Select a hamster and then click on a device to tell them to use it.
You can also train your hamsters to make them stronger, more agile, intelligent, or determined.
Click the mouse button as fast as possible to reach the green field before the time runs out.
Click to stop in the arrow field. Find the cards from the top row. What is this?
Oh, what is this? What is so dirty? Do I even have a hamster?
It's just my house? Where's the, where's the hamster? What is this? It wants to play a lot.
Wait, okay. It's definitely this one. 100%. It likes to play a lot. That's fine. Booty.
Clean freak. Was there one on the page? All right, this game just, I thought that
it was going to be a realistic game, but now it's like a cartoon game. Um, I don't know. Howard?
Okay. Stop. Okay. Easy. Be careful. All right. You want to eat food? What we got?
The snacks over here. It is butt. Okay. Where's water? I mean, what? Hey, look at this hamster
butt. It's, he's got like this poofy hamster bum. What are you eating? Huh? What? That's, why is
that weird? He's got like a little funny tail and he's got like a funny bum. What are you, what is,
what are you guys on about? All right. Come wear a hat. How much money do I have?
I didn't buy that. Did I? No. Um, yeah, I think so. I don't need to see anymore.
I don't see anything else. Why would the hamster have this on? They wear clothes?
Hold on. They wear like t-shirts? This is just Winnie the Pooh. Okay. All right. Whatever. Red
shirt. All right. Go take a, take a bath and then go use the bathroom. Done? Okay. Quest complete.
Okay. Put your hamster to bed. Play a race. Train strength, dexterity, intelligence.
Why are there stat points? Wait, where's my gift? Where's my gift? I should have a gift,
right? Go to bed? All right. Go to bed for a minute. Okay. That looks like fun. This song,
I don't know. Okay. So now what? We play a game? What's this? This is like, wait, we're strength
training? Wait, I want it to be intelligent and strong. Oh, that's determination. All right.
What's intelligence? Dabba dee ba dabba. Dabba dee ba dabba. I have to get out of here. Dexterity?
How do you train? Where are the books? What does this train? Oh, okay. Going down the slide.
Nice job. All right. We need, I need intelligence. Wait, is gaming playing, is this an arcade game?
Is this it? Dabba dee. I fucked it up. I fucked it up. Level up. Is he tired? No, not, not at all.
Not tired at all. In fact, he's having a great time. Is that his brain growing when he's done?
When he's like, is that his brain growing? Wait, 20 out of 20. I, I can't get smarter than this.
This is as intelligent as I could possibly be. What does that mean? All right. We're going to do
intelligence and determination. How are you doing? Still fine. Are you certified with a forklift?
No. What happens when I get to level 20 for everything? I get to level up the character?
Has it been 10 minutes? No, not yet. Oh, okay. Wait, now. Does that mean? All right. He doesn't
want to do this anymore. All right. Let's go. Go jump on the trampoline for like an hour or
whatever. I mean, what if you want to do? Oh, I can't afford it. Would you ever own a tiger?
Oh my God. No tiger. A tiger would just one day randomly would be annoyed the way you were sitting
on the couch and would just attack you. All right. Water deserved. Yeah. The way that you
lift up your arm to change the channel would be like, let's see what is on. Let's see what's on.
Okay. Anything would just be like, it's like, no, no, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Well, what do you, what would you even, how do you, what would you feed a tiger?
Just like raw chickens. What do you, what would you do? Is it just like an alligator where they
just throw like the raw meat in the alligator's mouth? Is it one of those scenarios where it's
like, okay, okay, take it. And it's like, right. Just raw meat. That's what I mean. Like raw meat,
like raw chicken, raw, you just like have to sit there and be like, okay, here's a raw steak.
Take it. Take it. I don't want it. But what the hell you'd be doing?
At a taste for human meat. Well, then you wouldn't last an evening with this cat.
Get down from there. Get down. Oh, that's it. That's very naughty. Very naughty. Naughty.
You shouldn't be doing that. You're going to be in trouble now.
How do I make money? Oh, I need to, I need to paint the walls. How do I get a new floor?
Where'd he go? Where did he go? You didn't Augustus yourself into the tube again, right?
Oh, there you are. What do you want to do? It's kind of fun to a race. I have gifts. Oh,
I can afford clothes, I think. All right. Take a shower and then
I'm good. Go to the bathroom. You don't want to do that? What do you want to do?
What do you want to do? What do you want to do? Oh, you're fine. Okay. Okay. So what are we over
here? Oh, that's how you do it. Can I pee? I'm going to pee. I'm eating a candy. All right,
let's do it. Let's race. That was a Heath bar. Anybody know what this is? What's this? What's
that? What is it? Let's check the middle. Fluffy, super delicious nougat. That's a three musketeers
and it's an S tier. All right. So what do I do? Are there players? Do people play this? Only two
players? I don't think anybody's playing. You're going to get streams. It's me and Mr. Broom. Mr.
Broom, you very, very clearly just probably downloaded the game. What do we have to do?
Wait, it's me versus Mr. Broom. What do I have to do? Tap? What do I have to do? Oh, Mr. Broom,
you're in deep shit. Now find this card. What? What do I have to do? No, I'm going to get the
crown. I don't, I didn't understand the games. I actually, I did not understand them. I did not
get the games. I want like five more Heath bars. So bad. I'll get it this time. Whatever. All right.
There we go. It looks like people have downloaded the game at this point. Come on. Heath bars to
Heath bar. Somebody say EO to Heath bar. You are out of your mind. You really are. I ate that.
Are we good? Click the mouse button as fast to reach the green field. Stop the arrow,
find the card and click to stop in the shrinking field. All right. Let's go.
Kill bro, Albert whiskers and Mr. Broom. I'm the strongest out of all of them. How does this one
work? Tap. What? I'm leaving everybody in the dust. Oh, you're pissed. Nice job, Howard. All right.
This game I thought was stupid. I was about to just leave until right now. And I've been shown
that that's, this is a fun one. I was so wrong. I did not think there was like a multiplayer
like maze thing. That's cute. That's very cute. And it's adorable eating contest. I just spit
in his, I just spit in that person's mouth. Wait, I don't lose. That's a tie. That we,
how did we not tie? I spit right into that other hand's mouth. We're good. We're good.
I eat paper for that. Did I eat paper? I ate paper. Did I eat paper? Sorry. Why did I not click?
You heard it. Was I playing against another player? I didn't. We're good. I didn't eat paper.
We're good. I just did not expect that. So I'm just to walk in. Heat bar is so good,
but don't put heat bar on anything else. None of that bullshit. Just right out of the can directly.
That's it. I don't want an ice cream. I don't want to just put it like a souffle. No,
I just want it out of the wrapper. That's it. Are you guys ready? Not even close.
Oh, wait. I wasn't here. Batman. Oh, that's gross. We didn't see. Good. Worst moment on the stream.
Why? I was trying to do the Jack Nicholson Joker. It's close. Is this what it looked like?
That's not what it looked like, right? That's what it looked like. That looks like I don't have any
teeth. I think I got booted from the lobby. Sorry, guys. This looks like I have no teeth.
Hold on. I'll show in a second. Fucking click. I swear to God I'm clicking. Oh, come on. Got it.
Careful. Careful. Oh, shit. This music. You'll never beat me on that. I'm sorry. Jesus.
Let's get back from the dentist. Yeah, just this new procedure where they take all your teeth out.
All of them. Yeah, I just got sick of them. You know, I just don't want them anymore.
I'm really into it. I'm really into soups. You know, getting gummy worms, you know.
I don't want to eat anything else. Round teeth. I'm going to do one more of these and I'm done
playing this. This was cute, though. I'm going to try to get Disney Infinity to work for tomorrow.
I just ate four Heath bars. Is that bad? How many calories are in a Heath bar? Oh, I'm AFK.
That's my bad. Sorry, sorry. In one of these Heath bars, how many calories in a little Heath bar?
200? No, it's not. 200? Oh, come on. I'm getting distracted. Somebody just farted a lot.
It's 210? No, that's in the regular ones. I'm talking about in the small ones, the little ones.
It does not just eat a thousand calories of candy. 120. It's definitely probably like 110, 120.
Fun sizes are usually like 100. Yeah. Fortnite Kyle and then Jerma Balls. That was fun. Thanks
for playing. All of you that downloaded the game eight to nine minutes ago. It was fun. It's cute.
I'm going to buy some clothes first. Hold on. Dabba dee ba dabba. Wow. I could be so cool looking.
Here we go. Oh, wow. Yeah. Little mustache and a clown nose. Looks pretty cool. I like it. All
right. All right. That was fun. What should we do now for a little bit? I could do. What should I
play for like 30 minutes? I'm not playing Breath of the Wild for 20 minutes. We're going to do
that tomorrow or Sunday. Maybe I'll add tribes to the list. Turmoil would be about 20 minutes.
I feel like I'm going to get addicted. That person said that because I'm going to get addicted to it.
I'm not going to turn the stream off. All right. That was cool. That was a hamster
play the Disney game. Disney Dreamlight Valley. All right. Let's switch to it. Not that.