Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Scare Saturdays.
Tonight, we're gonna be playing a game called Eyes, which is a pretty intense game.
It's one of those games that I can put in the same category as Slender, where you're being constantly pursued by a monster.
But you can actually see through the eyes of the monster that is chasing you.
It's a feature in the game, and it makes things a lot more ridiculous, as you could say.
But anyways, two things, very important things before the video gets started.
One, I'm changing Scare Saturdays to every week, to every other week.
So you can expect Scare Saturdays not next Saturday, but the Saturday after that.
I want to give myself time to prepare these videos and to get some good scary games.
Maybe go back and revisit some of the scarier ones I played in the past.
But I want to give myself some time to get these videos at the highest quality they could be.
And the second thing I want to say is I scream pretty damn loudly in this video.
So just be prepared for that.
If you have like a heart condition, then this is a warning.
Warning! Scary stuff ahead!
Let's go ahead and start this, huh?
Something that I just noticed.
This is actually on the various app stores for iOS and for Android.
And I think it's $1, but it's completely free on the PC, or Mac, or Linux, whatever you happen to be using.
Just letting you know if you want to scare the hell out of yourself on an iPad, you can do that with this game.
So let's do it.
Just want to talk about this break-in business.
Already checked it for you.
You could get at least 20...
Who is talking right now?
Hold on, what conversation is going on?
Oh, okay, the green is not me.
All right, so I'm going for a break-in.
Level normal.
Find at least 20 money bags, then get back to the exit.
Hide and or run from threats.
Preserve your stamina for dire situations.
Use a map and eyes to move safely.
Okay, let's do it.
Okay, WASD is move.
Wow, these are really wonky, awkward controls.
All right, let's get the money bags.
Let's like find the Monopoly man.
Can I turn this TV on?
Okay, whatever.
Whatever.
Let's see, money bag in here.
Push the door to open.
M is map.
That's a pretty crude map.
Oh hey, here's like my little kid's drawing of what it looks like.
The mouse is kind of weird too.
Oh, okay, so that's what the bags of money look like.
Don't even tell me this game is like Slender, where the more bags you collect,
like she just chases you around the house.
Because I know it's a she.
That's what I've read.
All right, that's the bag from that room.
Let's go.
Push to open.
What, you just like walk into the door?
Why is like grandpa on the wall?
Yes, I'm very mad today.
This is like a bad...
I'm pissed at the person that's a photographer.
Fuck you.
There's even an older guy.
This is awesome.
Look at these two old-time son of a bitches.
Any more pictures?
That's like Hitler.
It's weird.
Let's go.
So you just push your face into doors to open them.
Okay, sounds about right.
I'm so confused.
My field of view is so small.
Basement key.
Any money bags in here?
Ah, 220.
Ooh, there's two money bags.
Ooh, money.
That's good.
Can I turn my flashlight off and on or does it have a battery
or is it just the way it is?
Whatever.
Don't walk under the ladder.
That's like seven years bad luck.
I don't want to like...
Can I walk in the attic or something?
What?
I don't understand what's going on.
I don't understand what's going...
Run!
What do you mean run?
Where am I running to?
Ah!
Jesus!
Bruised!
Oh!
I don't even know where I am.
What time zone am I in?
Holy shit.
I don't even know if I want to play this again.
I really don't know if I want to play this again.
So when it says run, where am I supposed to just run away?
There was nowhere for me to go.
There was seriously nowhere for me to go right there.
Do I...
How do I hide?
Oh my God!
Oh my God, what do I do?
What are the controls?
Oh my God, this is horrible.
Is there a way to turn the flashlight off and just hide?
I don't even want to go out this door.
I don't even know where I'm going.
I only got like one bag of money.
You got to get 20 bags.
What is this thing?
Press Q to see.
Hold on.
This is the...
This is the monster's sight.
I can see where the monster...
That's one of the most terrifying things ever.
I don't even know where that was.
I'm so lost.
I haven't found...
Have I found like one bag?
Where's the money?
This is the worst break-in.
This is the worst robbery idea ever.
One, one, one, one.
For the same...
That's a pretty easy combination.
Give me that bag.
All right, I got two bags.
Three bags.
Everything's starting to shake.
That means she's somewhere.
Jesus!
Mother Mary!
I am not doing very much commentary right now
because I am genuinely terrified.
Okay, that means she's around.
I don't even know where to go.
Go, just run up this way.
Where is she?
I don't even know where that is.
Money, here it is.
Eight out of 20, eight out of 20.
Anything else anymore?
We got like George R.R. Martin,
the guy that wrote Song of Ice and Fire.
Don't blow it.
Halfway there, halfway there, halfway there.
I don't know what direction I should be going in.
No, no, no.
I don't know where she is.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Oh my God.
I love how it tells you to run.
It tells you to run,
but you don't know what direction you should be running in.
Third time's a charm.
If I don't make it this time,
it's over.
I did not get a very good look at that.
I got a money bag and another thing.
You click these things on the wall and then it's Q.
Hold on a second.
Is she already over here?
What if I hide in the corner?
Okay, she must be gone.
No, she's not.
No, she's not gone.
God.
God damn it.
She can't.
Well, that's it.
I'm not going any further.
I can't.
This is intense and I can't handle it right now.
So thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
This game is again called Eyes.
It's on the App Store.
It's only a buck.
If you want to hand this to one of your friends on like your iPhone,
I think it's iPad or actually maybe you can get it on your iPhone.
If you want to hand this to one of your friends and say play this game,
it's pretty fun.
You go and you like collect money.
This is one of the first iOS games I've ever heard of that's
that actually has been like a true horror game.
The only thing I can think of Year Walk was kind of a scary eerie type game.
This game is insane.
So thank you all so much for watching.
That's all I can do.
I'm done.
Take care everybody.
I love you all.
Stay safe.