Wait, hello there. How are you? Happy Father's Day to all the fathers.
Let's just get that right out of the way. Happy Father's Day. Happy Father's Day.
Well, I'm a dog, Dad. Oh, thank you. Hope you're doing good. Welcome.
Said today or tomorrow we were going to stream and well, I was going to stream.
It was going to be either Sunday or Monday and it turned out to be Sunday.
We are going to play for a few hours. I'm just going to probably play for,
we'll see. We'll see. This game is called only up. The game is impossible.
I don't, there's not, there hasn't been one person that's played this game that's gotten past the
halfway point. At least that's what I had a dream about. So I just figured it was true.
Did Lud beat it? Did Ludwig beat it? Well, yeah, but he's a gamer. Ludwig is a gamer.
Lud crushed it. Squeaks beat it too. Well, who didn't beat it? What streamer didn't beat it
and rage quit it in an hour. It's like, what category can I be in? Like who rage quitted
in like an hour and a half? You. Am I going to be the only one? It's just going to be me.
Well, whatever. I beat Jump King, the base game. So that's fine.
XQC alt F board. I'll probably do that too. Honestly, I bet that happens here too.
Although I don't think I'll alt F4. I will just stop moving
and complain about the game for like 25 minutes in the end stream.
You have to restart entirely if you close the game. Wait, does it? Well, don't spoil it for me.
I don't, I don't, I haven't seen anything. We're going to do face cam today. Yeah,
sure. If you're good, I'll make my assessment if you're good or not.
And if you're good, I'll turn it on for exactly 15 minutes. Why is this moving?
Hold on. This is something's not right here. Hold on. This shouldn't be moving.
Can't hear me, but I'll explain in a minute. Over here. Heck. What the heck?
I tried to plug a controller in. This game does not support controllers and I got immediately sad.
I was like, oh shit, I have to do keyboard and mouse. This is going to end very poorly.
So the thing that my chair sits on is it's on to make it so I don't ruin the carpet in the room.
It's sitting on top of this like wooden thing and the wooden thing was touching the desk and
the desk is touching the mic. So the mic was shaking. Are you guys ready? Let's go.
This is only up. We're going to start with no face cam. No face cam begin. There's one thing
that I want to talk about very quickly. Grotto beasts. The starter kit for grotto beasts has
fallen under 10% availability. We are under 10% stock remaining on the kits. The packs,
there are a lot of them. There's a lot of them. But the packs we did a reprint on,
the starter kit is not getting a reprint. Kit is not getting a reprint. If you care,
you care. If you don't, then let's play only up. But I did say that I was going to tell people
that when it became a thing. I want to make sure people knew that. Also important, the kits,
the packs that are in the kits have print one boosters in them. They always will be print one
because we're not doing a second print. When he said, no, I'm good. Okay. I did, I said I was
going to, when we got under 10% of the remaining stock, I said I was going to bring it up and I'll
probably bring it up again when we go kind of under 5% because I know people were waiting.
It's not a, it's not an inexpensive item. I know some people were saving up and they were like,
Hey, can I, is this still going to be available in a few months? And I was like, let's find out.
Turn the face cam on. You'll get it if you're, and that's not being good.
You're already proving that you're not being good today. Okay. I guess there will be no face cam
then. All right. This game's probably going to be pretty easy. Oh, don't look up. We need to get to
the top, the top of that. Sure. We'll make it. I wonder what awaits us there. The unknown is
frightening. All right. This is going to be a scenario where you wait 15 minutes, like Far Cry
four. There's an elevator that like spawns. Just watch. All right. Only go up. Do I need to know
anything? Elevator. What? Actual elevator, actual elevator. What? This is, I did not pre-play this.
I swear to God, I promise you I didn't. What? Is this actually in the game? How do I use it?
I did not pre-play this. I promise you. How do I activate it? Go up, go up. I don't think that's
going to work. Should I start here? How do you go up? How do you play the game? Oh, okay. Slow
walking, slow motion is hold right mouse, sprint is shift, jump is space, crouch, camera, first person.
Okay. Well, how do I play? Can I hold that forever? Secret elevator bug fix. I've already managed to
use the secret elevator and get to the very top. What? Why did I not play this three days ago?
I could have just ended stream in 10 minutes. All right. I see I can go up here. Like only up,
right? Is there a starting point? Where do we go? Press one. All right. When they do the streamer
breakdown of how high every streamer got off the ground, I'm going to be at like four meters. This
is not good already. All right. I got it. What are you playing? What the fuck is a meter?
Must be American. You're finally playing Tears of the Kingdom. What you forgot to say was,
you could be playing Tears of the Kingdom instead of this, right? Whatever. Dude, you could be playing
Tears of the Kingdom. I also could eat a BLT on stream. That promise is fucking gone. All right,
let's just go. Do you automatically grab onto edges? What the fuck is going on?
What? Why is it? Is this a distraction? They play distractions. All right, dude,
they play distractions at you. There we go. I'm already almost halfway through the game.
I'm doing good. Stop. Does everybody else game do this? I mean, hurry up.
You can always repeat your mistakes and learn from my mistakes. This is fucking me up so bad.
How do I get up? Turn. I got to turn. I'm turning the music off because this is,
why can't I still hear it? We'll just go away if I get high enough.
Can we get away from the person practicing the song? I mean, if you're practicing songs,
wait, what's this thing? Check that out. Yeah. Just keep going. Keep going.
Why is it repeating every sound? Just turn it off and put on your own music. I just turned it
all the way down and it didn't work. Just restart. I don't want to, I don't do this all over again.
Fucking whatever. Like what the fuck? All joke number one. No, I'm trying to reset the game so
I don't get the... Okay, turn it back up now. That was easy to get to that point.
Is he going to have a meltdown? No, I just, I don't want to get too far in the game and have
it actually be, I can't turn that off. Where the hell did I even start from?
You got one guide? Did I? Was that one guy? What do you mean yes? That shit happens to everybody?
Is that actually part of the game? What? No, you guys are full of shit. There's no way that's part
of the game. It's definitely a bug. See, it would have started by now. I think I'm in the clear.
It started right here. I don't hear anything. It hasn't repeated. Oh god damn it. Why?
Why? Is that seriously part of the game? It can't be. I don't make mistakes. Okay,
there's a lot of god rays in this game. The worst possible time to climb a gigantic structure with
no harness is absolutely when the god rays are in your fucking face, dude.
Do you go in one of these pipes? It's very hard to make a choice when you don't know where it will
lead. That's so high. I'm gonna go, all right, I'm gonna go left. This is, okay, I cannot look
over a chat. I can't look over a chat. If I look over a chat, I'll fall down. I'm gonna go very
slow. I'm gonna take it very calmly. What the fuck did I do that for? I'm fine. I was supposed to
go this way anyways. They definitely wanted you to go middle. Wait, I can walk. I forgot about
walking. All right, where am I? Geez. Okay, get some sunglasses. What the fuck? I can't see
anything. I'm gonna go up here. God is calling you. All right, I'm going that way. Wow. I forgot.
You don't have to hold it. You just click once. Be very gentle. Okay. Oh my god. I forgot to run.
He's doing the same walk that you did in the Christmas stream. Now, you're referring to the
sounds. They're like fucking dress shoe Andy. Oh, that's so stupid. I'm just gonna look down.
Stop reading chat. I know. I'm sorry. I'm so bad. I'm doing all right. Where do I go from here?
I don't have to jump from here, do I? Oh shit. Down here? I mean, how do I get up to that?
Go up. Yeah. Where's the correct up? Down there. Fuck it. I don't care. Sometimes you gotta take a
risk. I think it actually put me in a better position. I gotta turn the volume up now.
Can you guys hear it now? Or if I walk forward, will I just grow? Oh, there we go. Yep.
No, you have to jump. Okay. Wait, what about here? Um, I think I'm going the right way.
Look down, but go up. That's the strategy. Yeah. Look, I got myself in a much better position.
Oh dear. Okay. This is a big deal. Don't even think about it. Just do it. How? I guess I couldn't make
it. That the perspective was, the perspective was weird. I thought, so what was the point of that?
Is that just full of shit? Can I not actually go that way? What? Oh, come on. It's all right. I'll
get back up there in one second. Sometimes it's hard to choose the right path, but don't be afraid.
You can always repeat. We learn from our mistakes. And he said, God, I hate this game. I'm all right
right now. I'll get back up there in no time. So there's no checkpoints. So if I beat this game
with no checkpoints and when they add checkpoints after a bunch of people complain, I get an accolade,
right? You're never going to beat this. You have to beat it first though. Hey, I beat pre-patch
Radan. I think I can beat pre-patch only up. Wait, I didn't go this way last time. Maybe I
just shouldn't even go that way. Can I go up this way? No! Okay, I'm fine. Yeah, I just see somebody
bobbing their head with a guitar pick. Just nodding around. You know what I mean? All right,
here we go. Back to, back where we were before. All right, let me get a good, how do I do first
person? Because that was obviously wrong. So let me figure it out. First person. How do I do it? C?
Is it binoculars? I can play the game in first person. No, that's a bad idea. That's actually a
terrible idea. Okay, that top right up there is wrong. Maybe I need to go right. I'm going to try
going right. We've been good. Can we have the face game for 15 minutes? Yeah, yeah, you've been good.
Yeah, you've been good. You get it. Okay, when are you going to do the Peewee Herman dance?
When there's an opportunity to do a Peewee Herman dance and that's not right now.
All right, straight ahead. How the fuck do you do this? I'm just gonna go this way. Uh, smart.
Smart. All right, walk. Do not run. Dude, this game is so bad. People just want to like freak out
and move their mouse around. You know what I mean? Sometimes I just want to just move my mouse fast.
It's just like, this is bad for me. You know what I mean? It's how many of you guys just kind of sit
there and just go like move your mouse just wildly for half a second sometimes. I probably
should turn the sensitivity down too. You said you'd do the dance next time you were on cam with
any music playing. I can't do the tequila Peewee Herman dance to that guitar riff.
Why am I not turning the right way? You see, that was weird. I didn't like that. All right,
so look, what the hell? Let me get a better look. So this is too far. What about down a little? No,
I can't, I cannot go this way. Can I jump up and grab the edge here? Wait, can I jump up and grab
the edge? Dude, all right. I, you gotta use logic. That doesn't do anything for me. Wait, I need to
get on that one there. Whoa, that was way too far, way too far. Well, all right, I'll do it.
No, I'm just kidding. How does, how, I didn't know how far the jump went. I just did a full sprint
jump. I didn't, I can't, I'm not doing it. This is not, this is not Peewee Herman music.
This is not Peewee Herman dance music. This is not Peewee Herman dance music. I'm not doing it.
Shit. All right. Well, I had, that's what I, it's just one. Sometimes it's hard to choose the right
path, but don't be afraid. God damn it. No, go on the elevator. The elevator doesn't work. Do the
lion pose at least. No, is this, what is this 2017? What do you mean do the lion pose? Is this like
2018? Do the lion pose. All right. I'm going to get up there really quick. I get it now. So I wonder
if it's a full regular run jump and not a sprint jump. I just, I don't know. I don't know what the
trajectory, I don't know what the, the physics are. I don't know how far you go with a full jump. I
don't know how short you go with a small jump. This is all things I have to figure out over the
next 20 minutes before I all F4 and take like three months off. What the fuck just happened?
Okay. My boogers almost just flew out of my nose because people want me to do the Peewee Herman
dance. It's hard to choose the right path. Don't be afraid. You can always repeat. We learn from
our mistakes. All right. I got to get to where I just was. Good luck. Okay. How do I get over there?
That works too. Jerma's Peewee Herman promise. No, this is not the way you think. This is not,
this is the wrong, this is the wrong tune. Okay. This is the wrong tune. All right. I'm here. I'm
actually here. I actually made it. I made it. Look. All right. Burn this into long-term memory.
Where did I go? That was right up the middle. That was right up the middle and I don't remember.
Just don't lose. It's okay. I just don't fall off. I don't win. Is there a crouch or anything?
Because this is freaking me out. Oh God. Wait. Is this bait? I don't know what this does.
That's bait. That doesn't mean it. Wait. Is this a checkpoint? Does this do anything?
I think it's just a place to just sit for a minute and take a drink of water. Oh, that was
good. What was that? Experience. You know how fast I can move. Here I am. One second. Next
second. I'm gone. What? I don't know. I'm just, I'm coping because I think I'm going to fall.
Okay. So in games like this, sometimes you just have to go. Oh, this is bait too,
because I'm going to grab this and fall off. It's going to squish my fingers. That camera
is not fun. Okay. Now once I get up to this pipe, I'm going to just take a second.
There is something strange going on in this world, though there has always been something wrong.
Would everyone come to the stability has been shaken. Maybe this is a chance for me.
Oh dude, there better be an arcade up there. That's what I would do. I would put like classic
games up there and they're free. You don't have to, you know what I mean? Just get, once you get up,
what do you mean minus two? What I'm saying? Like that's a milestone. You get there and it's like,
I can, I can play like a bunch of arcade games. Now I can play like minus two silence. All of you.
That's why I wasn't making a joke. I was making a statement. I wasn't, that was a statement. That
was not a joke. I'm not touching that bed till I know where I'm going. What do you mean? What do
I, I said, it'd be cool if there was an arcade up there. That was a statement. All right. You,
I know what you're doing. You're fucking with me. Cause this is like the part where every streamer
falls down and everybody goes, the steam come out of this shit. Do I get blasted with steam?
Oh, okay. Okay. I feel safe up here. I made it. Look how I got to test his theory
and then fucking jump off. See who hits the ground first. Do a victory dance. Not yet. Can you grab
and like kind of shimmy on the thing? How are they floating? It's a video game. There's not even that
much left in the game. It's not like that goes up for like another four hours of gameplay.
All right. It looks like, hold on. Let me get a good view. Can I change the day night cycle?
Can it be like noon instead of 5 PM permanently? Risk. Okay. Risk off. Risk on. If you want to go
quickly, go with friends. If you want to go far, go alone. Oh, what do I do? Oh shit. I'm going to
land on it. It's fine. Okay. Can I, can I move it faster? Do I have to like sprint to move it or
something? How do I change it? How do I change? Okay. I'm fine. Here you have a great view of
the favelas. Oh no. This is where everyone lives in poverty, which is hard to get out. Okay. Okay.
Okay. How do I, how do I, how do I, how do I, should I get off? The whole life and the lives
of my goddamn parents have been. God damn parents. I think this is all bait to scare you.
I think I'm good. I want to look up to see. I think this ends. I don't know what to do. Should
I just keep riding it? What does this take me? In a game where you can fall and lose an hour of
progress? I'm freaking out right now. I'm just going to ride it. This is all bait to have you
freak out and jump off. It's all bait. I made it. Okay. Can you fail that? Or did I somehow
accidentally do everything correct? I don't know what I did.
You have to be with them and not stand out. You won't make it. You're a weak kid.
Go back to the favelas. Your friends are there. Your destiny and life is there. R1, R1, R1, R1, R1.
Happiness there. Get a job in the favelas and live there. Okay. So obviously that way.
Put some music on. No, if I put music on, then I have to do the Pee-wee Herman dance. I know
what you're doing. That's a Gotham scenario. That's a Gotham scenario. Okay. Let me just
assess this. I'm not doing too bad. Hold on. This is an Omega jump, right? I hope so.
Holy shit. Why did I just fall? Oh my God. To get to the new one, you first have to make a jump
and get off the ground, not knowing what the future holds. I thought I missed that. I was
going to say, how is that possible? Okay. Just have confidence. The only thing that matters in
this game is confidence. Even if you fail, if you go, you're going to fucking miss.
There's a jump coming up. Jump. Go. Now. You've seen me do it a few times and it's worked out,
but sometimes it doesn't. What do you mean wait? That was the worst sound you ever made?
No, it is not. You've got like 13 years of audio clips of me talking. That's not possible.
There's like a three or 4,000 sound library of all the fucked up dumb sounds I've made.
That is not one of them. That's not even on the tier list. That wouldn't even get an image.
Like a PNG at the bottom of the tier list. Sorry. You're just wildly inaccurate.
I wonder if that was a bad idea. No. All right. Where am I going? We don't think. We just go.
I thought I was slipping. I thought I was slipping off. What the fuck? Sometimes it doesn't catch.
Okay. I got to go slower here because these things are weird. Can I climb this pole?
No way. No, we'll go on the shore thing. We'll go on the shore thing.
I'm not messing around right now. Are those balloons up there? Okay. I want to get to at
least the balloon part. What are you talking about? What are you talking about? Why did it do that?
Why did it do that? He just went and then just fell. What the fuck was that? That was...
You showed me what was wrong with that jump. He just like scrunched up and put his head into his
neck and then... You've got to be fucking kidding me. What? I didn't make a mistake.
What mistake did I make? That was clean. That was... And I told you. I knew that was... It was weird.
The collision on those trains is like fucked up. I got there once. I can get there. But that wasn't
even that hard to get there. It's just pain in the ass. It's a slow-mo feature. Yeah, but I
forget about the slow motion. I literally just jumped onto the train and it did that.
You jumped on the... Give me... All right. What was the... I forget everything. I forget everything.
I was too... Where's the... There's a car that I jump on and then I go from the car to the...
Over here. Where is it? I don't remember. This was an hour ago. There's like a fence and a car.
Get wrecked, pleb. I didn't even get wrecked. I did a good job. Where is the part...
Get... Turn this fucking sun off. Turn the sun off. Go in the elevator? Did I actually unlock
a checkpoint? Are you guys fucking with me or is that real? There are no checkpoints. No.
Why can I not find the car... Oh, it's over here. That was such dog shit. Hey, you all know.
Everybody knows it. We all understand it. I don't even feel bad about that. I would feel bad about
that if I did something wrong, but we did a poll. There's 21,000 people here. 20,850 of you said
there was a game bug and 50 of you said that I was a stupid gamer. It was overwhelmingly
positive on my end. You ran a poll? You were one of the 50 people that... That sucks. This is all...
I'm just trying to not freak out. Stop spreading misinformation. How close is the sun in this
universe? What the... Stop. All right. It was right up the middle and then I can go quick.
I can do it quick. That's hot dog shooter in, I don't know, the Northwest. You know what? At
least for what I know. It's like one of the best videos ever. It was this way, right? Was it a game
bug? I'm just saying. I know how to get back here. Everything's fine. I don't want to rush
because there's more... Look, if you rush, you'll end up as an image of whatever the fuck that image
is. All right. I made it. Don't rush because the time that you lose rushing and falling versus just
doing it correctly. I just need to get to the balloons that I'm going to alter for. I'm going
to get to the balloons, do the tequila peewee Herman dance, and turn the stream off. That's
the goal for today. Show the image. I can't right now. Alt-tabbing and copying and saving and then
exporting and rendering and then putting it into OBS. And I think OBS put the bitrate at
certain kilobits to make sure it can be seen and then watch the rendering on the OBS.
I got to focus on this. Otherwise, I'll fall. And then do the necessary legal paperwork to show it
and send out all the consent forms to be able to sign and everything for
showing it on stream. And it's just a lot. Shut up, nerd. You're plus two-ing that guy.
I crafted a joke. And it was like a fucking fine French cuisine meal.
A guy calls me a nerd and I lose the comedy war. Just shut up and go. All right. Here we go. I'm
back to where I was. Pretty much. I have to ride the thing again. Let me just see what this does.
I'm not going to- doesn't do anything. It moves you forward. All right. We're not doing that.
Chad chatter versus the virgin Jeremy. Shut up, nerd. What the- what? You- it's not funny when I
do it? That's not fair. What do you mean that's mean? Somebody just called me a nerd. It's not
mean? Okay. I will show this one because it's really funny. I'm going to show this one because
it's good. It's good. I'm just going to- might as well. I don't even look human. I look like
a different species. All right. Don't distract me. I'm working on something. Do you look like
the Teletubbies? What about over here? There's something over there. Am I too much of a coward
to go look? Yeah. I think so. Let's just do what I did before. Once I get off the rollercoaster,
that's when I'm pretty much back where I was. Teletubby's son? Yeah. Risk on. Risk on. Risk off.
All right. We're just going to sit here and just hang out. Can I actually fall off this or
my good just to hang out and look at chat and stuff? Is that okay? Am I going to get like
just jump right now? No, don't think so. No, that's good. Oh, I have to choose the directions. I
didn't do that last time. I definitely was not doing that last time. I just look at it. I wonder
if people are lying to me. It's probably true. I'm good. I'm good. That was a dangerous thing, kid.
Don't do that again. Why is it so quiet? The volume's even turned up too. Why is the volume
so low? Did you see the live action One Piece trailer? They go, yeah, yo, yeah, yo. Do they?
Really? Do they actually do that? No, they don't. They do not do that. I wouldn't bet any money,
but I would friendly bet you that they do not do that. No, I'm busy. This is where I was before,
and this is where it all became a disaster. Slow down. The game, this part of the game is
fucked, okay? Risk on. Risk off. There's a little bit of momentum when you land.
Okay, slow it down. Where did I get caught up? It was right here, right? We're good. No, wait,
it was after this. It was after this. It's up here. Up there. Oh, up there. I'm almost there.
All right. Yeah, yo, yeah, yo. Give it up. Give it up. Give it up. Give it up. I don't even need
to be up here, do I? This is kind of a mistake, but I'm kind of terrified to go any other way.
This is the only way that I know. Risk on. Risk off. All right, this is it over here. I
got to make this. That is exactly where I lost last time, wasn't it? No, it was up here. All
back to the beginning, it would be really funny. All right, so pay attention time. What the hell
even happened here? It was right here. We're good. All right, there's going to be a hole that I can
fall through, or one of these is going to open. One of these is going to open up. A window is
going to open. Oh, shit. Is this a full sprint omega jump, or do I walk on that? Risk off. I
forgot to say it was on. Where are most of the balloons? That's going to be so bad. That's going
to be so bad. Jesus. All right. Assess. Assess first. No, I have to do this. So I have to go all
the way over there, and then, well, I could go risk on and go that way. Let me look at it. Do not. Do
not. Do not. Should I go? I could go risk on and do a full jump right now and just jump on that.
Risk off. Risk off. Okay. All right. You sure? I think I'm doing it. Risk on. Risk. All right.
Fine. Risk off. Risk off. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Oh, my God. This thing is really fucked up.
Okay. But do I want to go all the way over there, or do I just drop here and go that way?
Now, there's nothing over there. This is the, is this the only way to go? Yep. Oh, that does not
look good. Drop. Oh, you soft locked yourself? No, it didn't look right there. Oh, this is so
fucked up. I actually can't even walk this way. What about right there? What about I'm so,
that's a long way down. I can fix it. Oh, thank God. Oh, thank God. Thank God. Thank God. Thank
God. Thank God. Thank goodness. I'm going to puke. I thought I was going to fall. All right. Risk off.
I don't know. Why would this even be here? This to me looks like a shortcut. It probably is.
Risk off. Do you see how weird this thing is? Do you want a secret tip? I'm not looking at
anything else. The only thing I care about is this kid's hat in the middle of the pipe.
I'm not looking at anything else. Why would I pay attention to anything else? Uh-uh. Uh-uh. I mean,
I'm just not going to do this. Do you know what I'm saying? No way. I'll miss it. I'm too far up.
My God. Just focus on the hat. You fucking idiot. I'm there. I'm right there. You can't
crack under the pressure right now. You're literally 85% of the way done. Now where?
Fuck. What's worse? The scary pipe. I know how to do the pipe. Wait, can I just do this?
I know how to do the pipe. I've done it. I just did it before. I know how it works.
I'm going for pipe, but I got to do an omega jump from here. Oh, I just do it. Just do it. Risk on.
Yep. Don't even think about it. Just go. Okay. Give me a second. Captain Crunch is up here
and he's laughing at me. And he's like, fucking with me. I got to get rid of him.
Just give me a second. Captain Crunch is making fun of me right now. He's just like,
oh, my Captain Crunch cereal is more nutritious than this fucking dope.
He's up there and I got to get rid of him. He's like laughing in the chat. I don't know why. It's
like the white and blue hat. I just saw the white and blue hat. They're playing quop. Just do the
fucking snail strategy. It works. I'm about to turn the risk on and just fucking run. This is
a very effective strategy, but it's funny looking and like, hey, hey, hey, why is he turning this way?
I didn't turn him that way. I didn't turn him that way. Oh, oh, oh, oh. I'm not jumping from here.
I'm not jumping from here. That would be a huge mistake. Did I just punch the bike?
Oops. I'm sorry. I was doing the roar. Okay. Now what? I was doing the lion pose from 2018.
Be careful. Don't go too fast. I'm going to take a second here because I'll be honest with you.
It's time for me to get a little, uh, just to toot my own horn a little bit.
A lot of you thought I was going to fail at the pipes like 40 minutes ago,
and I deserve an apology. I can't wait. I think I deserve, I think I deserve an apology.
We are not sorry. No, no, no, no. I'll get it eventually. If I get to the top,
I'm going to see a bunch of sorry. I'm so sorry. Oh, my God, dude. I'm so sorry. You're so cool.
Okay. Obvious. Oh, more pipe shit. Um, yeah, that's the right way. It's very obviously the
correct way. Oh, I'm so scared to jump and grab this. I feel like I'm not high enough.
Am I high enough to grab this fucking thing? Oh, my God. I almost dropped. Shit. All right.
He's high. I actually said to Holly before I turned the stream on. I was like, if I like,
would I even be able to get past the first jump high if I did this high? She just shook her head.
She just went, okay, maybe I shouldn't do it. I just want us to remember this moment when I
got here and we're just like hanging out. You were going to? No, I was just saying like,
would I even be able to? I'm not talking about like, I'm just talking about in general. Um,
let's just, can I just savor this? Because I'm probably going to fall in like 10 minutes.
All right, let's go back to walking. And I feel like I need to jump onto this. And we're just
going to go straight. And I guess I have to go up that pipe, which is going to be unbearable.
So don't do anything stupid. I've got plenty of time. It's not like I'm on a time limit.
I would make a comment on, you know, the world and the environment and shit, but I,
I'm, this is, I've, I've, I've, you know what I'm saying? I cannot fall off of this. Somebody said,
okay. I would make, I can't make any comments right now. Turn risk on. Oh,
am I going to never mind? Am I going to say it? But again, am I going to get it or is it going to
glitch out? Wait, what? This is not world of warcraft, dude. You can't turn the camera to
get a better view and then use W to go forward. I almost just did that. My fucking heart.
Holy shit. I almost just did that. I almost did the world of warcraft. Get a better angle.
Only go, only look forward. Don't look back. Don't look down. What's with this camera? Stop it.
Camera. What are you doing? Stop doing this. What's with this camera right now? Oh my goodness.
Everybody fails at that part because they don't get it. I do. I wonder if I jump from here or do
I go from the end and try to catch the side or do I try to catch the perpendicular, you know what
I mean? Perpendicular shave. You monster. I'm just going to go until it's like all the way down to
my fucking chest. If I was, if it were me doing this and it is I'm going from here and I'm actually
terrified right now. The other part of me is saying go to the end and grab onto the edge. Well,
we just got to risk on. That's what you do. You just turn risk on. Sometimes you just have to do
it. Just stop thinking about it and just go. Uh oh. Just risk on. What the fuck is going on here?
This is fucked up. Where? What? Okay. What? Hold on. Let's assess this. Risk on? No, no, not yet.
Not yet. I don't know if I can, I can't grab onto this. Risk on. I was completely risk off there and
that was a, that was stupid. Let's fucking go. I, I thought that was the end. Oh dear. No way.
Okay. My hands are like kind of shaking. Jesus. Where are the balloons? Am I almost, I'm almost
at the balloons. We're good. I'm literally shaking. I'm going to go. Stopping now is a bad idea.
I'm just going to go up this pipe because like there's a bunch of shit over there. I could go.
No, I see, I see where I'm going. I'm going this way. Do it. Do it. Do it. This is a boat. Oh,
it's like a factory. Take it slow. I, yep. I'm going to take it slow. This is, this is here to fuck
with you or no, it's not. Is it though? It might be here to fuck with you. This might be a sprint
jump. No, it's, I don't think so. This is a sprint jump. Holy shit. I thought I was done.
No, what? Oh, YouTube thumbnail. What the heck? I know, but seriously, like what the fuck? Dude.
I did it. I made it to the fucking factory. Geez. All right. Settle down. This does not look too bad,
but who knows, right? There's a shit load left. I'm almost at the balloons, which is where my,
okay. You know, in Hearthstone battlegrounds, when you, uh, if you get in the top four,
it's considered a win. That's my top four. That's the, I placed top four in battlegrounds.
I don't care if I lose. I don't care if I get number one. Okay. Balloons is like the energy
win thing. This is not even 40%. Stop looking up. What are you talking about? I want to,
I need to see where the fuck I'm going. Nothing else up here. No, this is the right way.
I could go that way too, but no, that looks horrible. I almost just fell off right there.
What a fucking blunder that would have been. Fourth place is third loser. You still get two
points in Mario Kart. That's two points that number five doesn't get. I'm good. Your nose
is sweating. Wipe the sweat from your nose. I wipe the sweat from my nose when you wipe the grease
from your hair. Birth, kindergarten, school, army, institute, factory, death. What? We're bouncing
back and forth today. I'm, I'm giving it back. Is it really bad? Hold on. Why are you so mean?
No, I'm just bouncing it back. That works better if your hair doesn't look wicked greasy.
Your hair is 10 times greasier than mine. It only works if I'm clean. Please. Come on. All
right. No more messing around. I expelled a lot of that like nervous energy, right? Just like you
got to get it out because we're, this is about to get fucked up. So I got to pay attention.
Okay. We're just bouncing it back, dude. We're good. I should, I said shiny, not greasy. All
right. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. This is way, I'm like halfway through this game that nobody
thought I was ever going to make it to the piece of American cheese. And I'm sorry, but you were
wrong and you're seething in chat right now. Jesus. Okay. No, I think it's all right. This is
all right. I can't fall through the middle. I don't think that would be weird if I could.
Is this an omega jump though? I, it might be, go. I just scared the shit out of myself to do it.
What the? Jeremy, not you, me. Stop that nonsense. Balloons.
I almost just lost to a stupid slow motion joke. Train onto the train maybe. I don't think there's
anywhere else to go. This might be a bad idea. Let me go. I want to look. Did I miss something?
I think it on top. This is probably really stupid what I'm doing. No, that's, that's definitely
right. That's absolutely correct. Happy pride. That's right. It's pride month. Happy pride,
everybody. Happy pride month. Am I doing this wrong? This, that I glitched through that.
That felt, that felt fucked up. No, I can't even grab onto that. I'm paranoid to go in there,
but I'm guessing I'm going to. Oh shit. Okay. Well, I found where I need to go.
I don't think this is right. I don't think I can make that jump. Even if it's an Omega jump.
Risk on? Fine. This camera sucks. I'm stuck. That's not, that's not correct. Thank God it
stopped me. There's no way that's correct. I got, it's, I went, I went, I went into an invisible wall.
I don't know where to go. I'm paranoid to do anything. I feel like I had the right idea here.
It's not. Rail to that, to that. Is it about this side? It's right here. How come I didn't grab on
the last few times? Um, well, even if I miss, it's fine. Why? I thought that was a scary
horror movie sound. I don't like this. I don't like this Minecraft spawner. Yeah. I am terrified.
Risk on. Okay. Now what? This way over here off the tractor. All right. It looks like there's a
couple ways to go. I can go over there to the right and up. Let's get a good look. Yeah. No.
Okay. This is right. It's really stupid for me to jump from here to there to save what amounts to
four seconds. My brain is trying to tell me to hurry the fuck up and go over there and do it.
No. Risk off. You need to know when to turn it on and when to turn it off.
Should I go to the cheese? What do you think? No. How do you go from, where do you go from the cheese?
What is on the cheese right now, actually? What is that? I don't see any way up there.
Is it a bed? So that's harder, but it's essentially a shortcut. I don't know. Uh-uh. I'm way too far.
No. Risk off. Risk off. Sorry. It's not worth it. It's no. Uh, how do I? I think I have to do it.
No, I don't. I thought I had to do the cheese. I feel safe moving pretty quickly up here just
because if I fall, it doesn't matter. I'm going to land right here. Where the hell am I? This is
not connected to anything. Don't I? It's a strange feeling. I've never been this far away from home.
Risk on. Oh, yes. My undertaker. Destroy him. I didn't know that happened. It's a good thing
I fucking jumped. Holy shit. It's a good thing I jumped when I did because I would have just lost.
Wowee. Wow. That was horrifying. Okay. I've gotten kind of lucky the last couple of big jumps.
Where am I going from here? I can fall through this shit. This is not going to be fun. Can I
fall through this? I guess I can't. It looks like I can go right through here, but I'm not falling
right now. Why am I not falling through this? You cannot. Okay. I hope you're not lying to me. This
is like an hour and four. This is an hour and 10 minutes of progress. Please don't lie to me.
Okay. Where is this one going to go? Oh my God. I had to release some gas right there. Okay.
Everything's fine. Holy shit. I think I'm getting, I might be getting kind of close to being in a
position where I might be able to finish this video game in like another hour. If I do good,
just don't make any mistakes. Let me be the first streamer on Twitch to fall like once really and
beat the game in like three tries. Let's go for it. You know what I'm saying? Let me get like an
accolade for once in the last like three or four years. That bug just got on me. A bug is on me.
Spider, it's a huge one. Okay. These don't be stupid. Jesus Christ. Oh no, no, no. My accolade,
my accolade, my accolade. No, I need my accolade. Oh no. Oh, big mistakes. This is bad.
My accolade. I was, holy shit. No, I just, I risked on and I wouldn't risk off and I was stuck.
I couldn't walk forward. The cones, the cones have collision that are a full fucking rectangle
around them and I thought I was stuck and I freaked out. I couldn't walk. There was two cones and they
had a gigantic collision in front of them. I thought I was going to slip off. Risk on for the
rest of the fucking stream. I was doing so good too. It's just like, look at this. I'm back at the
fucking roller coaster segment. I didn't do it on purpose. I thought I landed on it, but God
fucking damn it. I thought I screwed it up. When I slipped back that time, I thought I was going to
keep going. I was like, fuck, I'm going to jump on the bed and just go for it. This was 25 minutes
into the stream. Don't worry. I'll get back there in 10 minutes. Time it. Watch this. I was going to
zone out and fucking risk on. I'll get back there in 10 minutes. I'm going to risk on
big time. You don't even know. You better believe that this is going full risk on right now and I'm
going to get to the top in 10 minutes. I'm not fucking around. Here we go. Do it to the
supermarket sweep music. It's a good idea. Supermarket sweep OST. That doesn't come up
with anything. No, I'm not ready yet. We're not ready yet. Settings, loop. How do I loop it?
Right click it. Will he reach the crane again by 745? You had better vote yes. What do you think
about urinal cakes? They smell. Where the fuck am I? Where am I? We're good. So I think what I
have to do is just go risk on, keep the risk on and just go. I'm sweating.
What the hell are you doing? I just had to go because like that's the hardest jump and I was
like, I just, I didn't realize I was still holding shift. I was still holding shift and I didn't
realize it was still holding it. It was the, it was just, my finger was still on it. I was, I was
good. I threw so hard. I don't want to hear anything from this person. Don't be afraid. You
can always repeat. Oh, my accolades. Oh, that's sad. That jump is not shift. The one before it
can be. Oh, I'm so sad. I'm so mad. My accolades. No, my accolades. I can get back there. I can,
let me get back there. I just didn't even get to the balloons. Why are the stupid crane?
That crane part I'm fucking furious at. Don't let Captain Crunch win. Yeah, he's cracking up right
now. Get it out. There's still three minutes left. Yeah, my problem was that that's a regular running
jump. Fucked it up. It's all right. It's all right. We're hanging out. We're here. Just say,
God, go, go like pet your dog for a little while. Come back. Like 10 minutes. Sometimes it's hard
to choose the right path, but don't be afraid. You can always repeat. We learn from our mistakes.
See that save right there? That's from experience. That's from playing this game for an hour and
having experience. Shut up. OK. Oh, some of those jumps were so hard, too. And I was nailing them.
I was nailing some of those. You know what I mean? Like you were watching you were like,
holy shit, he's kind of nailing this on the second time he's ever seen it. I was nailing it.
Any other like game show music to fucking get me pumped up? I got to have like game show theme
songs. That's a good one. Family Feud theme. That was kind of like goofy, though, isn't it?
It's like it's like it's like circus music, isn't it? Yeah, this guy is too goofy.
American Bible Challenge. Yeah, absolutely. That's now you know, you're speaking my language.
OK, American Bible Challenge theme song. This is 20 seconds. This is going to get
become unbearable after a little while. All right. The American Bible Challenge theme song.
Oh, I can't. This is not going to work. We need something else. We need something else.
That's not going to be OK. We'll go back to Family Feud. Whatever. It's not like I'm going
to get back to her. This is for it. I don't need to loop it. It's already an hour long video.
No, guys, why would I listen to this version when I can listen to this one? This is fucking good.
Holy shit. This is great. I thought it was a bird at first. I love this so much.
This is actually fucking great. Why did I look at chat? That was awesome. All right. What else?
I need something that I can just put back here. Who wants to be a millionaire? No,
that like we need something with a beat, something old to supermarket sweep. I don't know.
I mean, I'm going to my whole channel is going to get shut off, but I don't do the fates.
I feel like that's a pretty good one. Whatever. I don't give a shit. I'm putting it on.
I just want to just one and that's it. What's going on? What's going on? That's so low.
The beginning is really quiet. Oh, I should probably turn it down then.
I don't care anymore. This month for like five seconds. Um, I need like
catchy something that can sit in the background. Oprah's theme, the crystal light aerobics theme.
This is good. I'm into it. The 1988 crystal light national aerobic championship.
Excuse me. What the hell was that? Oh, my accolades. What the fuck is happening?
Why does that keep happening? That hasn't, I, that's not, that's a twice in a row.
The song is cursed by accolades. So that song's cursed. I like it though. Um,
the smash brothers pac-man music. Ooh, that's a good one. That's a really good one.
You know, one that goes, risk on. I got to ride the roller coaster though. We can't even get
hyped up yet. I'm saving this because we have to ride the roller coaster and I,
uh, just give it a minute. Give it a minute. Why are these games have to be so addicting?
These games with total complete failure, they have to be so addicting. And it's like the heck.
Okay. So what keeps happening here? I've been standing in the same spot each time. It's right
here. This just kind of goes kind of completely off the rails. The game's bugged. The game's bugged.
The game is bugged. There's a bug. Am I going to have to walk the train track?
Walk the tracks. Dude, that sucks. I guess I could. That's not a problem.
Some of those jumps are going to be hard without the, without the train. Aren't they?
On camera. What are you doing?
Music on. Not yet. I got to get to a spot where I'm comfortable. Why am I doing this?
Because the cart is bugged and keeps kicking me off. I can be, I am my own cart right now.
All right. Here we are. I just smashed a big peanut butter and jelly sandwich. Nice.
Oh, wait, which way do I go? Okay. This way. Oh, why am I looking? I hope you enjoy your sandwich.
I just ride the car. Oh my God. My hair just dude. And that's not where I want to be, man.
This bugs out again that I'm just going to reset the game accolades by accolades.
Oh, don't give them to me. So is it something in the road? I've done this,
ridden this thing like five to 10 times already and I never get like launched out.
That is a bug in the game and it needs to be fixed whenever the developer has time.
Making a game, patching a game, the whole operation. A lot goes into it. A lot of code and
shit. Why do I look like Jesus? Centrist Andy. All right. What do you say we wake up a little
when I get here? I'm going to wipe my hands. I'm going to wipe my face. Wipe your ass too.
This game is, can you hear that? You hear a fucking fast, my heart is going and
Oh, and wipe your ass too. Quick name your four person video game party.
Pac-Man, Star Fox, Link and Solid Snake would be in mine.
What about the portal companion cube? Yeah, I forgot.
Excuse me. Sorry. I need a new song that got me up here. We need something better than that to get
me to where we just were. I need something better than that. It's going to be hard though.
Pizza tower would be pretty good here, but I feel like we overuse it.
All right. We'll do the, what's, what's the one that goes like
that's game of the year by the way, unless Final Fantasy 16 is like better
that in Res, uh, Resident Evil 4. Uh, was it called hurry up or something? This is it.
All right. I'm going to be fucking crazy right now. Are you ready?
You're going to think my hands have just like sticky tape or sticky glue all over it. Whatever.
I'm not going to miss a single jump. This is where it counts. This, this part is fucking hard.
Risk on. Oh, I just stepped in dog shit. Oh, this music's changing. I need something better than
that. This is not bad either. Do lap two music. I'm not doing fall guys. Oh yeah. The sans theme
song. That's a good one too. That might be too, that may be too much city escape. That's the, uh,
I feel like that one's going to fuck me up, but I'll do it. That's going to, that's going to screw
it up. But look, we're going to be fine. I want to see bat chests only. If you just came to the
stream right now, you would be like, holy shit, this chat is fucking toxic. This chat is awful.
He's playing a song he likes and they're just fucking roasting them. This chat is so bad is
what people would say. Just like, man, holy shit. He's just getting completely fucking roasted.
I'm going to start it over. Oh yeah. Get up there. I'm not in it anymore. All right. Important right
here. Can I turn it up? I'll turn it up louder. What the hell? I'm stuck.
I got stuck on something. What did I get stuck on? Do you see my character was like,
well, I got fucking strapped on something. What was that? My character didn't even jump. He just
went fucking. God damn it. Where do I go from here? I'm it's, but we're fine. I've, this is not that
far. How am I? This goofy ass music. Now it's not, this is Mario brothers. This is not goofy
ass music. It's, it's, it's a little goofy. Okay. It's going on my voice today. That's a little
goofy. Where, how do I get it? Shut this off. My character, I was running for the jump and he just
went like, he just like, how do I get back over there? The left, I can't make this jump. Oh,
there you mean like over there. Fuck. Oh no. You only get one of those this year. Perfect.
This is not that bad. I got stuck. Oh, I would be so much more angry at that if it wasn't really
funny. That was like the 11th one you've done this year. Well, there's a long, a year is a long time.
I got this. I got this completely done at this point. It was so stupid. Yeah. We're going music
list for right now. Let me just get back to where I was. Why don't I just like skip this whole thing?
I mean, that was what I did last time. Let's do it again. The music is helps you though.
How about this goofy ass music back on? Oh no, that's it. That jump is the worst because no,
turn it off. Um, how about, I love Super Mario. I grew up with this game. Don't forget that.
I grew up playing Super Mario World. It was like the game. Super Mario World was the Fortnite when
I was like fucking 10. Come on. This is my Fortnite here. Don't you tell me what my Fortnite is and
isn't. Was this back in the forties? Chrono Trigger battle music. That's not the one I want.
I want the original. I want the original. Where's the original? Okay. I'm going to, I'm going to,
I'm going to add that to my likes on YouTube. I'll listen to that one like five to 10,000 times
later tonight. Where's the original one? These are all like the remake in the remaster. I mean,
I've got a way better one. Uh, this is, I'm not going to say what, um, what this is, but this is
a good one. This is, don't be, people are going to say, say in Chrono Trigger spoilers. So just
fucking relax. Okay. Be careful in the chat. Cause when I play this, this is, this one is a banger.
This is an absolute banger. You can bad chest me. That's fine. But this is one of the final themes
of the game. Here it comes. And it's going to get me to the top. This shit's going to get me to the
fucking top of this game. It's not the right one. Wait. No, it is. It is. It is. It is. No, it is.
Let's go. Oh, freaking Chrono Trigger. This is wrong. Here's the right one. It's going to get
loud. This is like a four minute intro. Hold on a second. How long is this part? Let's go.
I got to get out of this fucking industrial area. It's going to get loud. Oh, don't look at chat.
Don't look at them. I just, I just ran into the collision. What the fuck? Can I even save this?
I was running, running to jump and then fall. Why is this a slowed down version of the song
I was just listening to? It's mocking me. Use the elevator. I don't think the elevator works.
Sometimes it's hard to choose the right path, but don't be afraid. You can always repeat.
We learn from our mistakes. I didn't make a mistake. I didn't make a mistake. Clip it.
Clip it. You fell on purpose. No, I went to run on the barrel and I've done that jump like four
times. This time I apparently was hitting a weird collision part of the barrel and I Super Mario
mid animations got stuck in and fell. He's, he's actually angry. I got it out of my system.
I'm going again. This is, this doesn't do anything though. All right. This time we're going to slow
it down. We're going to play like fucking piano, like royalty free piano, and I'm going to go slow.
Use night mode. It's said soon. Should I just go get water and put tears coming down my eyes
and just have a cry face for like 30 minutes? Hold on. Should I say like watching like a sad
movie on my other monitor? Hold on a minute. Watching Titanic on other monitor. I'll just like
glance over here all the time and just be like, this needs to be a little bigger. Give me one
second. I'm going to pee. I'm back. Okay. So let's do this. Can you like, can you see if I do this?
Can you see it? You can't see it? Hold on. I'll turn the light on. Give me a sec. I'm not going
to pour it on my face. Okay. You should be able to see a little bit better now. I put a bunch of
tears. Hold on. Hold on. Just wait. You can see better now, right? So if I go like this,
is that showing up better? Kinda. Fuck. I can't see it. You need to look wet. You just look wet.
I just look like I'm covered in fucking water. Just stick your whole head in the, no. Hold on.
You just look sweaty. God. I'm sorry guys. I've never seen this fucking movie before.
This is fucking awful. I'm turning this off. I'm turning this off. Why would I? This is awful.
This is the worst fucking thing I've ever done. This is not funny. I'm just wet. I'm just wet.
I've just, it's like I got hit in the face with a water balloon. I need red eyes. I'm just
fucking sweaty. Oh yeah. I've never seen this movie before. I'm like really sweating. I actually
kind of feel good. I can't even listen to this song anymore. Let me turn, hold on. You need to,
no. I'm fucking done. I'm playing the game now. Why would you even stream at that point? Did I
tell you guys my bit that I wanted to do so bad? It was to do, you know, whatever. Steal it. Whoever.
It's just, I get, I get 5% royalties. I want to do full cam react to a movie that's not happening.
And it's like an hour and 35 minutes of me sitting there reacting to like the Mario movie,
but it's, I'm not actually watching it. And you, like, we're going to watch it together.
I want 10% royalties if you do that. Just sit there and I'll be reacting to shit like, oh dude,
Toad, what the fuck is Toad doing? Toad might not even be on the screen. He might not even be on
camera. And I sit there for an hour and 30 minutes and pretend like we're doing a watch along of the
Mario movie. That's pretty good, right? Or make it generic. We're going to do a watch along.
I can imagine like, hey, hey everybody. Today we're doing a watch along of whatever movie you're
watching, whatever movie you care about. So right now we can, we can queue it up if we want to start.
It doesn't matter what movie you're watching. You and I are watching it together. And three,
two, one. It doesn't matter what movie you're watching. I just sit there for an hour and 40
minutes and I fake watch a movie and queue it up with everything and anything. Queue it up with
the Smurfs movie for all I care. Get up and go to the bathroom and come back 30 minutes later.
I don't get it. Neither do I, but I think it's funny. Well, okay. Would you guys play along?
Would you guys, if I did that on stream, why would, why would it be a stream? I would just
upload this video. I would just give it to you guys and you just put it on anything. I don't care.
You, you'd play along? Why does this camera look brighter? All right. All right. All right. I'm
going to give one more attempt. I said I was only going to stream for like, like three hours today.
So let's, let's get back to it. I would, I would. The edits of that to various scenes would be
fucking gold. I think it would be really funny. I'm getting booed. Three hour stream. Yeah. Three
hour stream. Your light is on. Oh, it's, no, it's off. I think I just, the color corrected the camera.
All right. Let me, I'm not messing around. Let's actually go for it. I'm going to try to win.
I'm going to try to actually do it. Peewee dance. Liar. Go back in front of the green screen. Okay.
What if, what if I go back in front of the green screen and just sit facing a movie theater? Like
as if I'm facing a, you know, the projector's behind me and I'm sitting there and I just keep
looking back and keep talking to you and stuff. Like you're, you're sitting next to me or sitting
behind me. And not like MST 3K. More like I'm just your annoying friend and I'm just reacting
to the movie that I don't know what it is. Okay. All right. Just, just public domain. You know,
here's the thing, here's the thing though. That's a galaxy brand idea. You would crack up in five
minutes. No, I would, I would be dedicated to it. It would have to be exactly, or how about this?
I got an even better idea. I react to a movie that you do not know. And you have to figure out
what movie I'm actually reacting to. And I don't give you very many hints. I think that's kind of
fun too. How come this guy talks so much? Um, it's my, one of my only skills is talking well.
And sometimes I don't even do that very good. Bro, this is what? I'm good. I'm good. I've got
plenty of skills. Don't worry. Green screen was bad. I could do it more than once. Who cares?
I also have that video that I'm working on that I'm just going to premiere it on stream. And I
might not even upload it anywhere. Imagine him reacting as if it's the Mario movie and someone
puts it over saw. Well, here's the thing. It would have to just be for fun only because you guys
wouldn't be able to upload it anywhere. That's like, you know, copyright infringement DMCA shit.
You can't just upload an entire movie with me in the corner. That's just not how that works.
So, I mean, maybe just for fun for you just to kind of put on whatever. I don't know. Dude,
it didn't even be Yahoo yet. The Truman cut. Well, the Truman show cut was essentially the, I was,
I was in every scene replacing actors and stuff. This would just be me in the corner watching
the movie. You can't do that on any platform. You can't do that. What about the peewee promise?
All right, I'm going to play the game now. I'm going to go one or two more solid tries and then
we'll call it there. Short stream today. Short stream. He loves lying. I don't love lying. I love
making up shit. That's lying. It's coming up with weird ideas lying by its very nature. It's like
making up shit. I like to make up scenarios. I like to make up stuff, make up like stories and
characters and stuff. I am a, am I just a liar by trade? That's just a, is that a story? I'm
not a liar. I'm a storyteller. This part of the movie is so sad. I'm not lying. I'm just making
shit up. All right. Let's try. Both headphones going in. Nice piano music. No copyright,
except the whole stream is coming down anyways, because the whole stream has been copyright
music, but whatever. This one's nice. You sound like a super villain. I'm just a guy. I'm just a
guy. Stop jumping up and down on the same wall over and over again. Play the game. Play the game.
Oh, that is the right way. He's just, just a silly, a silly little guy. You have a terrible
tension span. You don't have the attention span of a, this is actually kind of intense. I don't
have the attention span of a regular guy. I, I'm just a regular guy. How do I fix hip pain? I don't
know. A lot of my pain problems are up here and like the sternum. I would go to a doctor. I don't
have very much I can tell you. Sorry. Unfortunately, your heart, uh, no, it's more sternum.
I had my heart checked and it was fine. I, dude, I had every, every single system in my whole body
was checked when I took that break in 2020. Oh, I was like, what's going, what's this competing?
All right. I'm going to try to keep a straight face while I do this, but it's going to be really
difficult. I'm putting on three or four different piano royalty free tracks. They're just going to
be competing. Imagine being at a bar or like a club or something and like a lounge.
This is like three people on pianos. By the way, can we talk about this for one second? I know
I'm supposed to be playing the game, but who cares? Did we already talk about who, why the
fuck would you have a P like a big grand piano in your house? You know, like, oh, well, I have
a big piano. We already talked about this. Did we do that? Did I talk about pianos yet? No. Okay.
All right. So when you have a house, like you still say you buy a house. It's like, oh yeah,
I got a house now. Okay. Yeah, I got a house. You know what I really, really want in a room in the
house? Just a giant fucking piano. I don't, but if you don't play it, I don't know how many people
play those pianos. Like, oh, the, the paint on the wall. Maybe I'll change the floors. Maybe I'll
redesign one of the rooms. Grand piano. If you don't play, if you're not a pianist, they take up,
they take up an entire, they take up like a huge amount of square footage in a house.
A pianist. You immature little bastards. All right, let's go. It's a pianist.
I'm not saying it again, but I've never once in my whole life been like, you know, I really looking
like I want a big grand piano in that room. I forget how to play the game. Everyone stop.
Can I do my stupid little routine now?
But don't be afraid. You can always repeat. You learn from our mistakes.
I like your Batman hair. Ludwig beat this game. Ludwig beat this game. How long did it take Ludwig
to beat this? How long did it take Ludwig to do this? Nine hours? Eight hours? What the fuck?
How? Did Stur beat this? Oh, the piano songs. All right, here we go. This is going to be unbearable.
This is just one of those streams. Vinny, did Vinny beat it too? Who, who, whatever. All right,
this is going to be awful, but I don't care. I'm just imagining like three people
and different pianos all trying to play different music over each other. All right,
we'll see if this is funny. This one's called soft piano music. All right, let's try it.
Here we go. No laughing, straight face only. This is just what it was like inside of every
Radio Shack in America. Every single Radio Shack in America sounded like this. Every one of them.
It's just people like playing keyboards in every aisle. I can't fucking do it anymore.
We're going to leave one of them on. More, more pianos. You're going to crash my computer.
My computer's hanging right now. Once I have eight open, I'm done. This sounds like someone's
shit face playing the piano. Like they're good, but they've had like eight cocktails. Okay,
last one. I can't do more than this. This is like when an orchestra is about to start actually
playing a song. They all like play at the same time. And then it's like, it kind of sounds
fucking weird. And then they stop. All right, that's enough. I'm going. No emotion. Add a
cheering soundtrack too. Like it's like a stadium. Stadium cheering sounds. One hour. I forgot where
to go. All right. Add car driving sounds. Wait, it's picking up. I've heard this one before.
One of them. It's Club Penguin. That's what it is. I feel like I'm going to have a nightmare
later tonight. They're not happy anymore. They're not happy. Oh shit. Then they're very unhappy.
I keep closing tabs and it's still going. You know, I think about like, man, like our youth today,
like all these crazy videos and Tik Tok and all like the big brain rot and stuff. Look what I
just did to all of you. You know what I mean? Like all the youth today, all the consuming
Tik Tok videos. I'm going to play 10 piano sound effects with cheering and booing and
farting and screaming sounds. It's me too. It's me too. I kind of miss it. And only a thousand
people left. That's actually kind of surprising. I don't know why I'm going for like a high score.
Okay. Let's try it for real. No jokey shit. No bullshit. I got it. All right. Tell me the truth.
No messing around. Did I do a good job as high as I got? I got to pretty much where the balloons are.
Did I do a good job? Did I do all right? I think I did okay. I actually surprised I got as high as
I did. That one crane kind of, when I fell off the crane all the way up where the balloons are,
that's when the pianos were starting to play in my head. It was just like, oh shit, it's over.
But we're good. I'm having fun. That's like 15% of the way through the game. It's true. I did say I
was going to try to get past 10%. Charlie Speed runs this game. I want to watch that. I feel like
that's very interesting to see. Put on club. Okay, we're good. Please, subway surfers. No.
Charlie's life. Is Charlie, is he playing it right now? How much further than me is he right now?
Like 5%. Those bits sapped him of all of his energy. Yeah, they kind of did.
Too many like funny sound effects. Is your discomfort? I just want to, I want to get back up
I'm going to try one more time. Somebody said funny in quotes.
Yeah, I'll allow that. I will allow that. That doesn't mean I'm going to not.
No, I'm not going to time you up. No, I'm going to be nice today.
No music. I'll turn the actual sounds back up though.
I think I just fell off. Okay, back to normal. Geez. This is fun though. See what I mean? See
what I mean? That's happened a few times in a bad spot. Risk on. Maybe when we get up a little
higher. Please put public domain movies in the corner. All right, so you can go like this on
your iPad and just zoom in on that movie and not even watch the stream anymore. Now you're,
I'm here right now. You know what's crazy? The part coming up here with all those little
jumps, the really, really scary ones. I flawlessly executed, but then I'll just fall off the edge
over here. Weird. Subway servers, please. A public domain movie instead of a face cam.
I actually like that idea. That's funny. That's very humorous. All right. If I get across this,
don't go fast. This is my last attempt. So do it right. Oh my God. I'm so I guess with repetition,
you kind of just burn into muscle memory, how to do all this stuff. I do wish. I mean,
I'm a checkpoint, Andy. I like checkpoints. It's also possible that I haven't come across
a checkpoint because I haven't gotten far enough. That's very possible. Oh my goodness. I didn't
grab onto anything, but I'm so good. All right. The worst is here. This is like technically one
of the worst parts. Slow it down and get it right and good. Right here. All right. This part sucks.
Every time I get here, I look and I kind of gulp like a cartoon because it's always stressful.
It's very easy to screw this up. Did you see the new spider verse? I did not.
I want to though. I want to. Careful. Get it right. I've done this jump like five times now.
No reason to overthink it. This part is the worst because I always feel like I'm not going to make
it, but somehow I just do every time. Scary. Okay. Almost at the industrial area. That's the
hardest jump of this whole map. Actually might be this one here. All right. Oh, I just scared
the shit out of somebody, but I scared the shit out of myself. So we both got scared. Okay. That
one is deceiving because it's really not that it's really not hard. It just looks hard. All right.
Breather. Jeez, dude. What are you doing? Okay. The last couple of times this is this has been a
disaster. The last couple of times I was here, I have progressed like 30 minutes ahead of this.
For some reason, it's this stupid area right here. Up there is what I'm talking about. This
part's kind of hard too, but just be careful. Not that big of a deal. Really not. You got further in
10 minutes than I did in three hours. Well, I've been streaming for three hours and I've been
streaming this game for three hours. So we are at the same spot. Think about it. This is what
screwed me up last time and it was fine. What happened the last time I got there? Honestly,
what happened? You lagged out. I'm almost at the awful jump that screwed me up last time. I might
not even do it. I might just sit. If I stay on it, it'll throw me off though, won't it? It'll throw
me off. You don't jump off the platform. Won't it toss me? It won't. I feel like it like threw me
last time. Or am I just crazy? It will not toss you. You need to jump. Well, that's what I tried.
I tried to jump last time and it just kind of like, don't jump yet. God. Okay. Well, here we go.
You've got to be shitting me. Thank goodness. I hit the wire. God damn it. That's the end of
I better not be soft-locked. Okay. We're good. I wasn't going to make a big deal out of it because
I didn't think I was good. Well, I thought I was good. So we're good. This part is freaking me out
though. I've gotten here two, three other times and just falling off. Yeah. You fell off. Yeah.
I know. It's whatever. Yeah. You peeked at Shpee. I know. I've heard it all before. A little bit of
Shpee. A little bit of Shpee. That's one of my favorite streams just because I've said it a
million times, but I'm going to reiterate it over and over again. It's just like that. I say that
all the time, right? I say that all the time. Those actors were given just like a little
20 minute package of things to study and like, Ooh, hot cup of cider. As if those are my catch
phrases. Ooh, Shpee. I haven't said that in nine years. I love that so much. They got such a small
window of what like I've done in 12 years that like most of it was from like 2012. Perfect. I
love it. Okay. Here we go. Don't hit the wire. All right. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. We're back
and another 10, 20 feet or so. And I'm, I'm game progress. Well, more like a hundred feet. I got
way higher than this last time. This is a weird thing. I did this. This part was a little weird,
but I'll be good. Just do it slow. There's no reason to go risk on right now. Holy shit. I
almost didn't get it. This is where I failed. That's I know what happened. I know what happened.
Why did I fall? I know what happened though. Stupid. Oh my God. Those little things that look
sick. That's true. That's a kaizo block. That's a fucking kaizo block. You got to be fucking
shitting me. That's a kaizo block. There's like a little thing on the ground and it makes you
fucking just walk off. It's a kaizo block. You're going to be shitting me. There is like a little
tiny staple on that thing that just pushes you off. If you walk into it as annoying,
I'm annoyed now. I didn't walk off. Go clip it. Go look at it. The things collision is as big as
10 people's feet. I'm annoyed now. You have to jump over those or they just push you off. Now
I know that and I'm pissed. Come on. You got like six inches to walk and there's a little
staple sticking out of the ground will push you off the map. You have to jump. There's three of
them. I saw them. I even said to myself, I was like, that thing is weird and sticking out of
the ground and I walked into it and kaizo block die. Well, now I know. Now I know that the
little fucking speed bump sticking out of the ground, the little like it's a little tiny little
thing. If you touch it, if you walk into it, it's just what the fuck I was and that's what happened
last time and I was confused last time too. I was like, why did I, why did I fall off? Why did my
character walk off the edge? And now I know a little staple. Oh, I could, I could repeat myself
a hundred times. That didn't happen in the third time. I'm getting up there just to just to fucking
fight this game. Walking over a speed bump. I mean, no proof, Andy. I didn't walk off of it. I
literally, it pushed me off of the fucking thing. I'm watching it right now. That's, I know what
happened. I'm telling you right now. Why would I walk off the edge like that? You've seen me walk
on. I just put, I just, my character just fucking went over the edge. I promise you,
there's no reason why I would have done that. You've seen me walk on smaller ledges than that.
Oh, hey, I'm at the area. That is like, I got to it. I was really happy I got back to the area. Let
me walk off the edge now. Let me just like walk sideways. You should have adjusted. I'm going to
wait till you play it and you're going to, you're going to have the same Larry David response that
I had. You're going to go, that stream is an idiot. He doesn't know what he's talking about.
You're going to walk right over it and then you're going to go, and then the fucking music's
going to play and then you're going to understand. That was the best Larry David impression I've
ever heard. It wasn't really an impression. It was a noise. It was a sound effect. Oh, that,
and it's so hard. The little staples sticking out of the ground is what they're, you gotta be
fucking kidding me. I was at the same exact spot. I was three, two hours ago, two hours ago. I was
right there. I'm furious right now. Fucking staple. Happy father's day. Happy father's day to all
you fathers. If there's any fathers here that includes dog dads too, by the way, that includes
dog dads. Okay. Actually last attempt. I've done this so many times that I can just do it now
without a problem. I think I can just make this jump right here. Do this thing. Look at that thing.
Watch this buddy. I was about to go risk on, but yeah. Okay. Sunk cost fallacy. I would agree with
you if I didn't get back there a second time. Me getting back to that spot a second time means I
can get back to it a third time. And now I know about the kaizo block. So I'm prepared now. This
is the hardest part of this area. I'm ready to go. Ready to rock and roll. Just do it. I've done it.
I've not fallen off of this the last four or five times I've been here. So just keep at it. Keep it
going. It didn't jump. It didn't even, it didn't jump. I just like fucking slid off. I jumped in
it just so he just didn't do it. I've made that jump five times in a row. It's like your feet,
your feet are their own physics objects. Look at this. And they like, you're a weak kid. Go back
to the favelas. I didn't fall all the way. That means we do it again. It's not that far. It's not
far. It's right there. The elephant just upset him. You can tell. That was my fault too, right?
I'm fine. Put the fucking piano music back on. Right. Scream. What's a good thing to try one
more time? SimCity SNES. That sounds kind of good. How about Bill Collins? Final Fantasy
battle themes. How about the Final Fantasy 16 battle theme? That one has been stuck in my head
for, it won't go away. It will not go away. I can't get rid of it. So I'm going to do it now. Great.
I love it. What a fake fan. Final Fantasy. I love it. Yes. I haven't played a Final Fantasy in 20
years. Hey, it's really good. I really like it. I'm looking forward to playing it. How could you
not like this? Yeah. All the Batchesters. Yeah. Oh, did y'all, sorry. Are you getting a little
pumped up right now? Is that what's happening? I'm going risk on the entire run here. I'm not
going risk off ever again. Somebody's playing the game. Oh, no, no, no. That's the industry
thing right there. I thought somebody recorded the in-game footage.
All right. Final Fantasy 16. Releasing on June 22nd for the Sony Station 5.
And you might be able to see German 985 play Final Fantasy 16 on June 22nd yourself. Oh, it's gone.
I miss it. Final Fantasy 6 battle theme. You know what? Oh, Mario Galaxy is a good one.
That's a good one. I have a major crit- You want to hear my criticism of the Mario movie?
Here it is. It's all a Mario movie. I'm going to give you a three sentence take. The Mario franchise
has so many songs that they could remix and stuff. A lot of the musical tracks of that movie are like
Take me on. Take on me. You're watching a movie. It's just you're watching a movie.
You're watching a movie. Here's a movie. All right. Let me put it on. I was waiting for this
and it was just like a licensed movie soundtrack stuff. Every time it would do a licensed like
rock song. I'm just like, I'm watching a movie. This is a movie. Hey, honey, honey, this is a movie.
Now I, I know it's a movie, but like I, it's almost like I'm being reminded that,
that I'm watching a movie. This is not the one I want. Where's the, where's the one? You know,
you know the one. This one. They could have just played this for an hour and 40 minutes in the
background the whole movie and I would have been probably happier. Don't you think so? Like this
could have just been in the background for an hour and 20 minutes. Should I gotta go?
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes. No, not yet. Oh, also, is it a shit take to say that? I don't
think Chris Pratt did a bad job. Is that, is that a shit take? Is that a shit take? I was like,
I was sitting there being like, I can't, I can't, I just, I can't, this sucks. It's all right. This
is okay. This is okay. This is fine. Yeah, I'm okay with this. I'm all right with this. It's all
right. Yeah, this is cool. Better than what I expected. Yeah, I, I thought it was, I thought
it was all right. What do you say? You've been what? You've been extra hairy lately. Um, yeah,
it's all right. All right, let's put the music back on. All right, now here it comes. I think.
Aren't you doing the be as gross as possible challenge? Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
This is the, okay, this is the one I'm talking about. Yes, it is. I'll turn it up for you. All
right, I'm turning it up for you guys. Let's just vibe out right now. What do you think? What do you
say? This time I'm getting there. You fucking beautiful. Why are you not streaming in 1080p?
Um, my computer sucks. I'm on an i3. Sorry, sorry. Hey buddy, we meet again. Oh, it's a bug. It's a
bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug.
It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's an actual bug. It's
an actual bug. It's a bug. It's a fucking bug. It's a bug. It's a bug. It's a bug in the game.
It's a bug. It just it just pushes you off. It makes you fall off. It's a bug. Is it a bug? I don't
know, dude. You've been fucked up by my whole body yards. I can't even walk over here. See what I'm
talking about? It's a bug. Do I have to use the bed? Is this intended? Oh shit. Stop. Stop. It's a
guys. It's I didn't do anything. This this this area is fucked up. I'm telling you right now this
area is fucked up. It wouldn't let me stand on it. It was just like pushing me off. See what I'm
saying? What's happening here? It won't let me land on it. You're going the wrong way. What do you
mean I'm going the wrong way? You have to jump to the cement blocks. What are you talking about?
What do you mean? You mean up here? What do you mean? I'm slowly doing a split and this looks
very painful. The gray things in front of you. Um this is gonna start to hurt. To the balloons?
Where are the balloons? What do you mean that way? I'm so confused and I can't move. I'm gonna pause
it. Jump over here? Yeah but I can't travel that far. You talking about right here or down? No.
What do you mean? You've been going the wrong way? Just the rectangles by the no down down down down
there down wait down here. I don't know. That's where I just was. I was just here in this building.
Wait what? So this is just bait? This was bait? I don't think I can move. I'm in the thriller pose.
All right. Fuck. My balloons! Okay I'm fine. Am I all right? Yeah I'm fine. Everybody relax.
I'm a tuber tonight so this is like the most tuber I've been. This is probably the most tuber I have
been in like probably two or three years. Okay I gotta get up there and jump off of that. That's
the best way to get up there. Like what I was just doing. My balloons! I gotta get down. My balloons!
What a person really needs is not a state of peace but the striving and fighting for some worthy goal.
Fuck all that. I don't even know. I don't know what they said but I'm talking about the cinder
blocks. Risk on. It did it. I actually didn't go that far. I think I can get back up there.
You jacked too hard. I went right in the middle of all of them.
Shit. I'm not upset. I'm not that far. That's not a reset moment. I'm right here. This is not that far.
All the annoying shit is done already. I'm so... This music is the only thing keeping me from
screaming. Fuck as loud as I can. It's just like all right okay a little star is flying around and
they all go like it's it's cute and okay I'm I'm fine it's cute I made it to the balloons
I'm happy no matter what happens when I was all the way down there looking up I did not think
I didn't think I was gonna get to the balloons but I wanted to I'll take that as a win you should
stream Mario Galaxy uh maybe we will that sounds like fun if I get to the balloons then I'll be
really happy like actually staying where the balloons are we're already right there we're
already back it's like as if I didn't even fall what's up next
oh there we go how's everybody doing you guys doing all right you guys doing good
I didn't ask you that today you doing all right I don't ask you that like well maybe like once a
year oh hey sunflowers are about to open it'll be an update there soon all right let's I'm pretty
much where I was before there's no reason to get angry or annoyed I really haven't even been that
angry I got angry at a system that I thought was like kaizo blocking me but it just I went the
wrong way and I was hitting invisible developer walls so that's my own fault you influenced Vinny
to check out this game because you streamed it didn't Vinny play this already wasn't Vinny
wait Vinny played this already didn't he no not yet oh you all told me you beat it you told me
Vinny beat this oh I see what's going on I get it I was explicitly told that Vinny
beat the game always scary grabbing this one I just had to go left that's so funny and I
was sitting there just just seething and just complaining I just went the wrong way what's the
best way to get up from here wait do I have to use the bed is there a way to get oh no we're
hey you tell Vinny you tell Vinny that balloon berry you tell Vinny that balloon berry is is
going for it right now he's gonna look up and he's gonna go what and I'm gonna look so cool
on Vinny's stream for like 10 seconds tell him it was wicked hard too okay oh can I go that way
if I just launch I don't think so yeah I'm good balloon berry huh balloon berry get a screenshot
quick get a screenshot I was gonna turn this you can fall off the don't tell Vinny that you
can fall off the roof it's slippery that would have sucked so bad where is this gonna go was
it worth the screenshot let me look this is gonna move where does it move to I might just put on
the final fantasy 16 battle music again is that is that weird you care uh it's gonna go that way
or that it's probably gonna go over here I'm gonna take my time because stream is getting
close to being over I mean I'm either gonna beat it or I'm just gonna get to wherever
I get to on like the thermometer going up cell caliber Vinny's watching the clip it was so
stressful Vinny spoilers don't Vinny spoilers hmm this is important because this has to keep
me going because this is uncharted territory I don't know where I am it's got to be something
really good oh my goodness that is true uh snake eater the one that goes
it was out of tune but you know what I mean then when you smoke the cigar that's a good one
that's a really good one no that's that's from five that's not from three
let's go
I just something fell
from
not gonna fool me with that bullshit that song is great blood-borne now blood-borne now blood-borne
now Ludwig's theme oh yeah I listened to I listened to this all people are so talented
isn't it interesting it's like humans are able to create so many things isn't that cool what we
are capable of doing on this fucking planet all right this is a stressful part and I'm gonna let
the because I usually just skip right to the Ludwig part what do you think did we listen to
the whole thing okay let it build let it build I that means I can't fall for six minutes all right
it's gonna get loud can I stand on that oh my god oh yes you are on my side all along my true mentor
my guiding moonlight it's not the right part of the track anything to make you cope
with what you're doing I got it wrong there's a little more I jumped the gun a little
Jesus that's why I went slow oh yes bugleberry can I walk on that what do I jump
can I walk on this here it comes
sorry I I can't hear your donation sorry oh
that's completely missed I completely missed it I completely missed it I completely missed it
I completely missed it I completely missed it what the fuck no
I thought it was much further and I had I was holding shift
and that I oh one more oh it's so far at least I did it to the music I you know what it was it was
the perspective when running up I thought it was much further that's just a regular jump but
honestly a regular jump probably would have gone over to a regular jump would have probably gone
over to that's like a jump I don't know it's deceiving damn it oh I'm all right with that
a few spider verse jumped shit you're so red right now because I'm just like all that energy
just like expelled all right yeah no I think that's a place to call it I don't know if I'll
reliably get back up there I'm okay with that that was fun though that's a really fun game
I had it I all right now that's it I was only gonna stream for like three hours today anyways
I had fun this is a good run you did I did the peewee dance like an hour ago you missed it
all right guys I'll see you later hope you had fun I had a good time that was a fun
game to play on stream I will see you guys again in a couple days maybe like Wednesday
raid yeah Vinny just started doing this where's Charlie right now he was somebody said he was in
space Charlie is way way out of all of our leagues and all of our gaming leagues right now
let's uh we'll raid Vinny see how he does he's a real gamer yeah those no credits oops press the
wrong button that was fun what game on Wednesday hmm I don't know we'll figure it out I was just
kind of grabbing random stuff this week you probably would have had it if you wiped your ass
yeah my face went no accolades yeah we'll figure it out I'll be in pre-stream we'll just kind of
figure it out thanks for hanging out uh I think Vinny is getting close to ending but he did say
he was going to do it until he fell so let's go omega lol laugh uh when he does maybe he won't
maybe he'll just beat the whole game all right we we know we know by the way we can tell Vinny
Balloonberry was upgraded to Windmill Winston Windmill Walter yeah Windmill Walter is better
it's true thanks for subbing thanks for watching as always see you next time call your mother
take care of yourselves probably start at 4 p.m on Wednesday not later this time 4 p.m pacific take
it easy go say hi to Vinny watch him play this game ow I gotta move this arm thing
cool game fun game see you soon take it easy