Hey, what is happening everybody? Jerma here with a Counter-Strike Global Offensive Gameplay Commentary.
And this is going to be on the map, the new one, because I actually forget what it's called, but it's a new map on CSGO.
And this is going to be on Arms Race. That is the official title for CSGO's gun game.
Yes, this is gun game. This is the old school gun game, not the new one.
I think Demolition kind of has a new version of gun game, where you spawn with a new weapon every time you die or something like that.
But this is the real gun game, which if you don't know, I'll explain it right now.
Every time I kill somebody, whether it's one bullet, two bullets, it doesn't matter. If they die by my hand, I am going to level up, so to speak.
The instant they die, I get a brand new gun, and that happens every single time I kill somebody.
After 26 times I kill someone, I'm going to pull out the knife, and that's how you end the game.
You have to kill somebody with a knife kill. And how the progression works, it starts out, you get an SMG.
Everyone starts off with the same SMG. Everybody has the same progression as well.
It's not, oh, you have a different path, you go down this path, you go down that path.
Everybody has the exact same progression. So you all start with an SMG, and as you progress, you get the best SMG.
Then you go through the shotguns, then you go through the assault rifles, sniper rifles, machine guns, and then you start at the pistols.
And that's where this game mode gets really interesting.
Because obviously, if you have a pistol, and you're going after people with machine guns and assault rifles, it can be kind of difficult to get that shot on them.
And then after you get through all the pistols, you have to use the knife.
And that can be insanely hard to kill anyone with that thing.
I have gone probably two or three minutes with that knife out at the top of the leaderboard, and I lose the game.
Our team loses, because I don't end up killing anybody.
And I just brought up teams. I'll cover that for one second here.
Teams, the way they work in this, it's counter-terrorists versus terrorists.
And there's no adding of points, it's just individual.
So if I get 20 points, and my teammate gets 20 points, it's not like, oh, we have 40 points together, we're going to get better guns.
So it's just individual, and whoever gets that last kill on either team is going to win it for their team.
And something I would really love to see in this game mode is more fleshed out, and not so quick, not so crazy.
I wish there was a game mode, like gun game, or like arms race, whatever you want to call it,
where you had to kill like two or three people before you could level up, or you had to get a certain headshot, or you had to get a certain amount of criteria to get the next gun.
The whole shoot somebody, go, go, go, go.
As you'll see, I go through like four guns in a row in a less than five second time span.
And that's cool, that's interesting, but I like to enjoy the guns for a little bit.
I like to run around and get some kills, get some shots with them.
But you can't really do that in gun game.
Once you start to, oh, I like the P90, oh, I can't wait to, oh, it's gone.
And I understand that's the mode, that's how it works.
But it would be cool to get a different kind of gun game, where you get, like I said, different criteria.
So it was a little longer, a little more interesting, maybe like capture the flag or something.
I don't know, maybe I'm going way too overboard with what I think they should do with gun game.
Nonetheless, this mode is amazingly fun.
You get like three or four friends into one of these lobbies and get on different teams.
And you will see some real rage, you will see some real hilarity.
I mean, Burger Boy, if I got Burger Boy into one of these games, he probably would throw up on his computer because he wouldn't be able to handle it.
He would probably scream and punch his monitor through the, oh, it would be ridiculous.
But regardless, if you get a bunch of friends in a lobby, it is a lot of fun.
Everyone's talking trash, everyone's laughing, everyone's having a good time.
And that's what it's all about. That's why I love this game mode.
Just pure chaos and pure fun.
Before this round is over in the next minute or two, I want to bring up something.
I get this asked a lot about Counter-Strike.
And I want to answer it, I can't really answer it, but I would like to give you my opinion on it.
And it's how much is CSGO going to cost when it releases?
Now, I have no idea.
The only thing I can really say about that is there is no single player.
There is nothing in this game besides the multiplayer.
So if you take that into consideration, I personally do not think this game will be more than $50.
I don't think it'll be more than $40.
That is my prediction. I'm going to say, German prediction, $40 for CSGO.
That's what I think.
Now, this could be totally incorrect, because obviously they're developing this game for the console.
So this could be $50 or $60 at release, at least for the console version.
If you remember Portal 2, Portal 2 was developed for the PC, PS3, and Xbox.
And it was $60 for the console, but it was only $45 for the PC.
If you pre-ordered it, that was.
Which I'm assuming everybody did. I know I did.
So assume it'll be something like that. Same type of hierarchy there.
It'll be somewhere around that range, in my opinion.
So that's going to wrap up this video, guys. Thank you so much for watching.
I don't get the knife kill. I went like 26 and 13 or 14 or something, which is pretty good.
It's okay, at least.
But yeah, this is going to be the end, guys. I'll see you all next time.
And take care, everybody.