Hello ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of Germacraft, the series where I play
Minecraft. This is going to be a single player let's play. And when I say let's play, I use
that term pretty loosely because I'm an idiot in this game. You're going to see lots of
fails. You're going to see lots of triumphs, at least I'm hoping. So go grab yourself a
nice hot cup of coffee, hot cup of cocoa. I got apple cider right here, freshly brewed.
Let me take a sip. Ah, that's good cider. All right, so let's get this started. Create new world.
World name is going to be Germacraft. Sounds about right. Yeah, okay. Game mode is going to be
survival. That's the most interesting, I think. More world options. Seed for world generator.
Okay, this is important. I got to name this something crazy to get cool structures and stuff.
Going to name it, how about Diamonds are Forever. LOL cheese burger. All right, that's our world
generator seed. Diamonds are Forever LOL cheese burger. Done. All right, let's see what happens.
Create a new world. Let's do it, guys. Building terrain. Oh my god, this is so exciting. This is
episode one. I wonder where we're going to end up. Where are we going to end up? Okay. What, what?
Where the hell am I? I spawned on top of a mountaintop. Okay, hold on. Sound has to be lowered,
definitely. Okay, lower that, lower that. Maybe a little lower. That sounds about right. All right,
so apparently I spawned on top of a mountain. This is a good seed. What's that? We're going
to explore it right now. Go! All right, we're going to try that again. This time I'm not going to miss.
I want to get down to that. That's the home right there. I want to live right there.
No, I don't even have to explore. See if I can't do this. I got a, hold on. I got an idea. I got a
plan. Germacraft episode one. This is how we do it. You guys ready? I don't know if you, I don't know
if you guys are actually really ready for this. Here we go. I'm going for a skydive. Remember,
if you hold shift, you don't fall off. That's something I didn't know when I used to live
stream this game. Are you guys ready? Ready to go see our new home?
All righty then. What the hell's that? Oh, it's an octopus. Look at this little quaint little place.
I love it already. All righty. So, oh, I'm so stupid. You see, this is why,
this is why I'm an idiot, guys. You see, why would I, I need to get wood and I just jumped off the,
okay, remember this. Where are we? Pointing east? I have no idea. Gotta get some trees. That's the
most important part about Minecraft. You gotta get trees. That's the first thing you gotta get.
Let me take a sip of my apple cider. Oh, that's good stuff. Hopefully you guys picked up a
thing of cocoa like I told you to, because that's the most relaxing thing in the world. Sitting down
playing video games doesn't get much better than that. Okay, come on now. Oh, we get sand too.
Now, explain this to me, all right? All right, I want Notch to send me a personal email
and explain to me why there are cows that are acting like mountain lions.
I'm gonna kill each one of those cows in just a minute. You watch.
Oh, well, at least there's one tree over here. I gotta remember, I gotta go back that way,
because that's where the house is gonna be. My awesome dirt house. So, if you are an old subscriber,
I mean really old, like at least four months, four or five months, you'll remember the original
Germacraft. It was like two episodes and I built a dirt house. This is gonna be completely different.
I'm going to actually spend time and make some cool stuff. At least that's what I'm pretending
that I'm gonna say that. Got some wood. Oh, I got Gino still from Mario RPG, one of the best games
of all time. If you have never played Mario RPG, I suggest you play it. All right, got some wood.
Any more trees over here I can dig up? I'll get this one too. One more and we'll make our way back.
So, I guess they added a hunger feature now too. If you're hungry, you die or something, I guess.
Who knows? A little bit more wood. And in my live streams, I was always a tradition that when I
played this game, I would sing a song when things got really boring. So, that seems like the perfect
opportunity right now to sing a song. So, let me just prep my vocal cords for a second.
Okay, so we're getting wood right now, right?
But chopping wood down every single day. I gotta get my tools any which way.
I can't seem to reach this stupid piece of wood, so I gotta put some blocks down to get where I
should. I'm gonna chop. I'm gonna chop right now. All right, that's enough. Got it. Let's get the
hell out of here. Yay! So, those of you that don't think that's gonna be a good spot, you'll see.
I'm gonna build that up to be like a castle. So, here's the goal. By Christmas time of this year,
2011, I want to have a giant castle like as big as that mountain over there. So, let's clean this
up a little bit. Why don't we, huh? All right, all right. Maybe put a little bit of dirt down here.
Make sure I can, you know. Did I really run out of dirt? Wonderful. My first wooden tools.
It's just like going to your first day of school and getting punched in the face by the bully.
Speaking of bullies, I got a funny story for you. First ever story on Germacraft. Well, I do this
mundane stuff. So, when I was in like the fourth grade, there was a kid that lived down the street
from me. His name will stay anonymous because, you know, I don't want him to like, if he watches
these videos, I don't want him to come like beat me up. Not that he would ever remember this to
begin with, but I was probably like the fourth grade and I was a little, I was a little s-word,
guys. I was a little, I was a little, little jerk when I was younger. So, essentially what happened
was this kid, he was a big, big fat kid. Scary. Not very nice. And my brother got in like a fight
with him like a long time before this. When I was like the second grade, my brother's a little bit
older than me. And let me pick this up. So, my brother got in a fight with this kid and, and like
I heard about it. And so, at the bus stop one day, because we were at the same bus stop because he
lives right down the street from us. Oh, he, at least he did. I don't know if he does anymore.
So, I don't know why, I was in the fourth grade. This is how much of a little jerk I was. So,
my grandmother used to pick me up from school after I got from the bus stop. Because, you know,
obviously you don't want to walk, you know, the mile and a half back to your house or whatever
it is mile, because the bus stop wasn't that close. So, my grandma used to pick me up and he was at
the bus stop as well. And one day I decided that out of the back window, I was going to give him
a double middle finger as I was driving away with my grandmother one day. I don't know why,
I don't even know why I did it guys. I can't, I can't tell you one reason why I gave this kid
the double middle finger. And from that day forward, he just kind of gave me the weird,
like a weird look, like what the hell are you doing? And from that day forward, I would run,
run as fast as I could to the bus stop and away to the bus stop to where my grandmother was going
to pick me up. And it was like that for almost six months. And he never beat me up or anything
like that. I was like overreacting. Actually, hold on a second. I don't, I don't need this.
What am I doing with this? I was just putting blocks down. Actually, no, no, no, I was doing
the right thing. I want, I want these because I want to make like a wall kind of let's keep that
going. So yeah, so I guess the moral of that story is never give the double middle finger to a bully
because you'll be scared for the rest of your life. And I still am scared when I like open my door to
like go get like groceries. I'm scared that bully is going to come get me from me giving him the
bird. Yeah, that is actually a true story. I did not make that up. I was scared for like at least
six months and nothing ever happened either. And then I didn't get beat up or anything. So
all right now, is there, is this all, is this just going to go straight down into?
Okay, cool. Cool. I'm going to make a little mine here. It's getting late. It's getting late. And
when it gets late, that's when Jerma starts to lose. I don't think I've ever made it past one
night in this game when people are watching. I really don't think it's happened.
Does that? Oh, there's a mine somewhere around here. Pretty sick. Oh, gee, it's right here. Oh,
nice. Maybe there's coal right here too. That'd be pretty awesome. Oh my God. Creeper, creeper,
get the hell out of here. I'm going to kick your butt. No, blow up. Go on. Go on. What do you think
I care? You can't hurt me. I got a shovel. I'm going to shovel your face in. Okay, well that's
done. There's not coal just right here somewhere. There has to be. See, this is why they always tell
you right when you start, you need to go get coal and you need to go get wood and everything. But
I was too busy talking about a bully, me giving him the middle finger. So I'm trying to see if
I can see coal. Sometimes it's just right on the edge of these mountains. I am not pleased.
Let's at least do this. I need a sheep too. I need wool. I'm being a real piece of crap.