Hey, good afternoon. Hi, everybody. How's your day gone so far? Mine's good, I'm a little heavy.
Just a little. That probably needs some explanation. In fact, it feels like I'm a softball,
like in my stomach right now. Just a little heavy, you know, a little bloated, but it's okay. I've got
some nice tea here. It's not tea, it's coffee. The laxatives haven't kicked in yet. Well, that's the
thing. They have, they have very much so. It's been, it's been very fun, but they're not even,
okay, I don't want to get into this. It's not like what you think when you think of that word.
Trust me, it's not what you think it is. There's like a, there's comedy, you know, comedy like
laxative. No, that's not, it's not what's happening. If you've seen any movie from like 1992 to like
1998, there was a, it's not like that. I mean, some of them could be,
but this one isn't. I literally just joined. Anyways, that's a good way to start this stream.
Why don't we bring in the two special guests? It's Star and Ashley. I think I said that before
muting, unmuting. I said Star and Ashley. Here they are.
Hey, Ashley. I muted at the wrong time. I unmuted at the wrong time. But yeah, we're going to do
Trine, Trine 4. Wait, what? I thought, I thought this is three people. What? How does that, doesn't
it break the game? And then once you get to six, once you get to Trine 6, it's 3 v 3.
No, there's not that many people in the world. Trine like six is just like a 3 v 3,
it's like Dota game. Yeah. And the developers are pissed off about it because they want to make it,
but they have to make Trine 5 first so that the joke works.
So I remember we did this, we did a video on this. Yeah. Finally, I got to be one of Steve's videos.
That is one of the most popular videos you and I have ever done together.
Yeah. I was just saying before this, how recently like today I walked into a McDonald's and they
were showing it on the screen. Yeah. I couldn't believe it. Yeah. It's ridiculous. I know.
That's weird because I was at, I was at a Burger King two days ago and they was showing this video
too. Really? Yeah. That's his joke. He just took that right from him. What the fuck? You can't do
that. Steve, you can't let him do that. Okay. Mine wasn't a joke. Is yours a joke? Or did yours
also really happen? Just like, just steal your joke in front of you. Yeah. Yeah. That's bad.
That's, that's just how we do it. Come on. Come on, Rowdy. Cut it out. Are we starting the game, Rowdy?
Yeah, I'm ready. I'm ready. Okay. Okay. And by the way, my name is KettleCorn. Call me KettleCorn.
What do you mean KettleCorn? My name is Frozen Buttwagon. Once upon a time, Amadeus the wizard
was waking up in a cottage. I got a sweet spot for like wizard voices. Attending a wizard.
My volume's too low. What if I hit escape button? And that morning, he decided a trip to the mail
box. He has flashes on his shelf. Even if this box was located at a very inconvenient distance,
time to find that mailbox. Wait, who does? Okay. No, I don't want W-A-S-D. Why are we all wizards?
I don't have a hat. Why do I get a hat? My control was plugged in. Why did they make me the pink one?
This is the tutorial. You remember? You got to play each hero one at a time.
Now we're all wizards. Remember when we were on the beach? And I, cause I know,
cause I just saw this from the McDonald's. Wait, what? Hold left and okay. I'm ready. Right.
So get on the cube. Do I have to do these on screen to get them off the screen without A and D?
Actually, we could just walk out the door, but we have to walk out the door.
What? Oh, which one? Oh, I'm purple. Dude, I got the Twitch. I got the Twitch skin.
I think it actually is zoom in. No, it's not. Is it zoom in? Oh, there is a zoom. I'm zooming.
Is there, how do you zoom? Look at my shoulder. Hey Rowdy. What's up? How are you? Oh, I got a thing.
Okay. That's how you do that. They, they nerfed the wizard. I was saying,
because normally you make, you draw a square and the square appears there,
but now it's always over your head. And also if you jump on your own square,
then you can't manipulate your own square for a duration after touching your square. You guys are,
you guys are training, aren't you? Yeah. All right. So A is jump. I've gotten that far.
No, it's space bar. What? I have a controller. I have a controller. I don't care.
Yeah. A-W-A-S-A jump. Break them. Oh, there's instructions. Cool. He has to do this every time
he leaves his home. That tree just keeps growing. What about the, what about the secret up there?
You got to smash it. Yeah. Nice. So you get what? Three of these in a level or something?
Do we all, I think we all have to use our power at the same time. No, one person should be able
to do this. Come on. If you weren't touching it, I think you could just lift it. Well, somebody put
up. Oh, why is there a snowball in here? Oh, we're losing them. We're losing them.
Run. Hurry. Oh, get up. Highlight levitation objects and then switch targets. Okay. So if you,
I get it. I'm trying to give you my box, but it doesn't fit through.
All right. Somebody left that and stick it in the way like the traffic game. Good work.
Oh, here. Here's the, here's the secret technique.
Get off. No, you guys are doing the centipede from Super Mario Brothers to me. Get this out of here.
Thank you. I'm so good at balancing snow. Wow. This doesn't look like it should be possible.
When is it going to come to life?
It's like start screaming. Yeah, I know. It's a very, it's a very nice looking game.
Well, I turned my graphics down all the way. So it looks like I'm a little weird.
You can do it, honey. So we're going to have to go through each chapter as the,
the first level is going to be each character. Yeah. It makes sense.
Okay. You can rotate. Oh, all right. That's cool. I'm the wizard. I've always been the wizard and
I'll continue. Yeah, I got it. We have a side role. If you put weight on something,
it falls. Yeah. They nerf the wizards. But if you go fast, it doesn't matter.
There you go. I mean, I think we need one of those. How did you get it? What though? I guess I think
we're supposed to use that here. Nah, but it's okay. Again, I stress this is his trip to his
mailbox every day. All right. This is a puzzle. Everyone worked together with our brains.
Stick that up. Wait, did you already leave? Yeah. Are we supposed to be doing puzzles together? You
just like jumping. There wasn't a puzzle. You just make a box and climb. You come up here, you make
a box puzzle. I thought this is. Yeah, I know. Okay. Oh, we can't. Oh, hold on. Did I just like
push you off the level? I'm Donkey Kong here. Hold the box still so I can jump on it. Thank you.
Did you lose your hat? I never had a hat. What? We're the same guy. We're the same guy.
Conjure a box. Um, I think we should probably just all make a box and all use it together.
Same. Secrets. Secrets. Get the box. They didn't think he would get those secrets.
Oh, I don't do it. No, no, please. Let me do it. Please. Please. Okay. So the box goes. Okay.
Just do it. Just do it. I know you can do this. Just put it in there.
I figured it out. Wow. You didn't. You didn't fucking figure it out. I figured it out.
Oh, is it a launcher? I think it's a launcher. I think it's a weir. Is it a weir?
Why is that snow glowing? Why is that snow glowing? Can you break it? I can't like scrape it off
like an ice scraper. Um, all right. We'll see. All right. Jump on this and then yeah.
Do we need weight over here? As low as I can put it. All right. Ready?
Nice. Now I have to do this. Wow. Look at us. We are very athletic. Secrets over here.
Kill it. Kill it. Hey. Wow. Wow. Go forward. What if an alien just like flew their spaceship next to
your window and just leaned over to their friend in the cockpit and just said, kill it. Wow. Oh,
my God. You guys. Come on, guys. I thought you were going to like lift me up over to the ledge,
but I was wrong. Oh, no. What? Why? I don't know. Oh, it's a snake. Attach. Attach. Yeah.
I have to. Come on, rowdy.
Located. So wait, so I'm going to grab this thing. Yeah. You got to hook it over the woods.
All right. So somebody that has to stick it there. How do I hook it? She's blocking you.
I can't hook it. You're just going to have to run. I can't move this thing back. Hold on.
I got to like hook it right here, right? It's not hooking.
Okay. Well, I'm just going to do this. Just stay there. Okay. It's hooking.
Just jump over it. Wait, I got you. I got you. This is a wire rowdy.
The glowy snow is sticky. Nice. Well, he does that every time I have to go to my mailbox.
Somebody said, oh, great. Another pretending to mess up puzzle stream. We're like speed running
this level. We haven't even attempted to do a puzzle. Look at how fast we're going.
There hasn't even been an attempt. You have three wizards. We're kind of too powerful.
Oops. Did I get it? Got it. I did the stir thing. Wow. Jump on the box. I already beat this level
in my mind. Now you did. You did. There's something down there. There's two of us down here.
Get up here. I'm getting boxed in. Here. Take it.
Ooh, nice. Thank you, Taylor Swift. I'm bringing it. I'm bringing it. You bring it. We got our mail.
Oh, I got my mail. What's it say? Fucking evicted.
How far it is.
Oh, Disneyland. Two years ago.
Academy. He has vanished under mysterious and troublesome circumstances.
And Lord, I am going to learn magic. Constant conflict. Yeah. Turn himself into a snail.
A snail. He's missing, but he's actually like under that table.
Oh, that's actually pretty good.
Caught a giant quest.
All right. I remember this guy.
You get to wear his hat in TF2. I don't even know what you just said.
What did you say? You get to wear his hat in TF2. Wait, you actually do? Yeah. You buy,
try and you get his hat. Wow. That's where every single steam release had a TF2 hat tie in.
Whatever happened to that? You can ride pumpkins. Why are you guys pushing me?
A speedrun. Wee. What? Oh, it's bouncing. No, it's not a speedrun. We have to pretend to mess up
puzzles. No, we're not. We're perfect. You died in a pumpkin accident. Oh, shit. Wait, can we all
smash? What? All I've wanted is to smash. Wait, we didn't get the thing. You didn't get the thing.
What thing? Do you really want to get the things in the tutorial? Who cares? Yeah,
can we all smash? Whoa. Stomp on that. Wait. Oh, you jump and there's a Yoshi stomp.
Do you remember this now? Yes. What? I need a block. You can't make a block. You got to smash.
Well, where's the wizard? What? I need to be launched.
Knock that. There we go. Knock that wood over here. I'm making it up now.
I need this thing to launch me. Now you have to get launched. No, not me.
No double bouncing. There you go. Okay. The secret was to do nothing. How do we get those?
Oh, that's out. All right, go. I get them. What about over here? Hey, what about over there?
No. Is there a sprint? You have to unlock it. You have to beat the game once.
No, you don't. That'd be very strange if that were true. Okay. My controller unplugged.
He's trying to create stream content. He's like already bored of the game.
Break the ceiling. Break the ceiling. Yeah. What? This game is cute. It's good. He hates streaming.
That's like my, that's like my new favorite thing. People will just write,
he hates streaming and then like a sad face. Whoa. Star, can you give us,
can you give us regular people a second to even know what the fucking thing does?
Okay. Oh, you, okay, you bounce light. That's cool. Oh, let's play. We could,
we could all bounce it. I can bounce it to you and then you can bounce it back to me and then
then we can make the, the triune. Oh, no, let's do it right now. Come on. You can get it.
What if I jumped? We have to like burn it or something. How do we burn that?
What about the green stuff? Oh, no, let's see. We know. Yeah. The green stuff behind it.
Shoot the beam at me. We got it. We got a double beam. That's no excuse for your evil doing.
It's working. All right. I'm aiming at you. Oh, look at that.
There we go. One for each of us. Nice. What are these jellies even doing? Third wheel,
trine third wheel. What? Oh, you're talking about, you're talking about me. We're getting it.
We can make a tower. Oh, my fuck. How am I supposed to drop the thing for me? Hey,
drop the thing for me. Yes. So disrespectful. Hey, we're going to get this. Projectile is
going to be blocked as well. Nice. Stop. Stop. Hey, he's trying to do this stream content.
All right. I'll go. He's already bored in the game. No, it's funny when I do it.
Yeah. That's how it always works. And I remain. Okay. I'll do this way. How did I die up here?
Killed you accidentally. I don't know. I'll do it back. All right. I'll go forward.
Okay. Didn't know. We didn't know. Oh, no. No, you were in front.
She's not. All right. I'll go forward. Wait. You have to wait. Okay. Whoever is. Wait. No, stop.
Whoever is in front. I'm going to go forward. Go. All right. Somebody get across. You did it.
All right. I'll go up. No. I can't. If I put this down, I die.
All right. We have to. No, no. You have to bounce it. No, you got it. You have to bounce it this way.
Shoot one at me. All right. I don't think you can. I can't. No, it won't reach from there.
This one's tricky. Just I'll die. Who cares? I'm good. Oh, he took it for the team. Let's go.
Hey, I'm back. Oh, no. Skeleton King. Is it a boss? Do they have bosses? Yeah. Yeah. Remember
those dragons? Do you remember this guy that we're fighting right now? I don't. Oh, yeah.
Give him a light beam. Oh, wait. I didn't need to hit his. You have to hit his like swords.
You can't stand light, sir. Wow. It's the same way you could defeat me.
All right. How do we break that? Oh, okay. That's how. He's in so much pain.
All right. I'll keep him there. You hit his back. All right. We got to break the thing up here.
I think we have to. I have to bounce. All right. We have to do like a three or four person bounce
thing here. How am I the only one that jumped on that? All right. Here we go. Oh, it'd be easier
to do that from that side because then you just shoot it up. There we go. Got to do it again.
No, you don't. All right. Kill. I have a note too. Oh, okay. So I had to, as the wizard,
destroy three trees and like a friend of goat to get my mail and he just gets it brought to him.
How long? Okay. So this is trying four. How many years have gone by since trying one?
I don't know. Use Google. We have an unfortunate case of a missing. We have a trying story.
2009. That's when the game came out. Not how long has passed in the game universe.
Oh, in the game universe. Yes, that's what I'm saying. I thought you were talking about like
when did they make that? No. Are you trying to figure out if the characters are still like
bangable or what? Yeah, it'd be really funny if they switched to the archer and she was like in
a grave. Oh, and what happened to our noble archer? Oh, oh, they got to find another guy.
Oh, no, it's the archer section.
Why did you do that? Skip.
Oh, she's the assassin's creed. Yeah. I was going to say, is that, is that a tie-in or is it just
what? It's a tie-in. Is it actually? Yeah. Yeah, the makers of this game are friends with the
assassin's creed. Are they? The prince guy that we have to stop is a templar. It's the whole thing.
Wait, what do I do? This character is kind of fun. This is your character. So this is my character.
This is your character. That's why I liked it. Okay.
Uh-huh. Bath beads? No, they're definitely bath beads. Oh yeah, you have the grapple hook too.
That's why this makes this character the hardest. So why do I have to have the hardest character?
It's not the hardest. Because you're the best. I make a box and you grapple to the box and then
I throw you into a pit. Don't you remember? Oh, now it's coming back to me. Yes, I do.
Are we capturing the objective? I don't know. Yes, you have to capture it. Somebody has to
stand there long enough to open the door. Okay. Okay. Bye. You gotta let him learn.
This is his only chance. He's never gonna. Let Rowdy do it. Wait, are you guys talking about me?
Yeah. Let Rowdy do it. Your little brother's gotta learn. I'm like four years older than you.
Oh, you got them both at a double.
All right. But seriously though, like, you know, I'm going to get these.
I'm making you do it. You do all the grunt work. We'll keep doing the level.
Somebody has to pull this. I guess I'll do it. Yeah, you do it. Enjoy your date guys. I'll
just like do all this stuff. Bye. Let's go make out. Oh, hold on. We got us Rowdy. You have to
help me. Here we go. All right. We need to look at this highlight. You can highlight targets.
Okay. So pull that. You pull it and then you attach it to this. So it stays here.
Like, so you got to pull it forward and then, then put it on the other thing. Oh,
but the camera scrolls. There we go. Yes. Oh, come on Rowdy. Oh, you can walk on it.
Oh, come on Rowdy. Well, you guys all ran away. Uh, can I, can I just do in the dessert menu?
Why is my rope growing? Yeah.
I just realized what you're doing. Please don't bully.
You guys are so bad at this game. I'm missing dinner. We're doing it so fast though.
How can you call this bad? It wasn't me. It wasn't me. It wasn't me that said that.
Oh, your chat. I'm getting, it's been long enough to make references to Spider-Man movies.
Uh, yeah. There's another room over here with a mystery box guys.
Mystery box guys. There's a mystery box over here. Whoa. Nice shot. No Rowdy.
Oh, and the, and the, he went in the tank. Oh dude, that happened to me.
I can relate to that stuffed animal. All right. So now I'm going to do, uh,
ropes of bridges too. So go, go on. Yeah. I think we're doing one at a time and then I
got to capture the flag. Oh wait, hold on a second. I can like, that's kind of cool.
Well, no, now, now I detach it. Okay. He's learning. Yeah, that's cool. Let's go.
All right. Now attach that. Attach that to that. Okay. Now I can let go of this.
Wait, no, you can't. No, you can't. It's bridge. I, yep. Okay. Oh, now you can let go of it and
climb up. You gotta be quick. Balloons. Nope. Drop down B. That's a huge cat. Yeah.
Should we ring the bell? You have to, so that the hunchback comes out.
All right. We'll open the thing. All right. We did it. I don't know how we did this. Take it.
Oh, we were, we're a mercenary thing. Oh yeah. Jerma is the bad guy. That was weird. Get it.
I get to be the first. I thought it was the other guy. I'm the one that's disturbed about them.
It was just the one without a hat. Maybe the masquerade can show you extremely hapless. Like a
new TM two player. No. All right. So then attaching this. Yeah. I think you got to wrap
it all the way around. Do I? I can't go that far. How did you get up there? I just jumped up. No.
Okay. Then. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I was already attached to it. Oh, there's one on the floor.
Yeah. It's this one here, but why can't, don't unattach, unattach. Okay. Everybody
unattach everything. Please stop. Stop. I'm not moving. I was about to ask who's rowdy.
Don't do anything. Let's start to it. Let's go. Hey, are you Brad?
It's an old meme. All right. So if you go, I don't think that's what we do. I think
unless one person, I think one person just do it and then there's a lever on the other side.
There is a lever on the other side. So I think somebody just runs it. Just go. Oh, and then you
can. Yep. I'm trying. Oh, you make the bridge. Yeah. Somebody said to make bridge. That makes
sense. Yeah, we were overthinking that. We already have 72 drops of virgin blood.
I just was going to say it was like simple syrup and red food coloring, but you fucking psycho.
While she was on her way to the masquerade, Zoya happened upon a place that brought back the town's
orphanage. 72 drops of germ of blood. What's your blood doing all over the trine world?
That person's also fucking psycho. Oh, she's sold the paintings so that she could fund the orphanage.
Bees. There's bees everywhere. Bees. That's funny for like one second when he then he stopped doing
the thing that was bees everywhere. No shadows. Clearly got stung. It was just a nightmare.
Oh, he's dead. He killed Disney. What happened?
Many letters sent by the master wizardess directed our three heroes to a rocky and
wind-beaten heath.
Whoops. He's talking to MLC's stealth. What? Beginning of level. Go.
Many letters sent by the master wizardess directed our three heroes to a rocky and wind-beaten heath.
Oh, it's for. Yeah. I thought it was. That got confused. So do we get to pick our characters
or is this just who's logged in first? At last, the enchanted heroes of trine
together again. Zoya, if you've given up your Oh, we're officially our role. We are roles.
Now we have to role play. Can you stand on my box when I hold my box?
Oh, no, they nerfed the wizard. Sorry.
No, stop. I was practicing. Now I know where I head swirl or you. You see how many head flips
you can do when you drop it. Two is it's very hard. Yeah. See me when you get 100 super jumps, buddy.
That's not that impressive. That's the end game. I don't want to rush you guys there.
Oh, nice job, Rowdy. Yeah. Thanks. You coming, Rowdy? Oh, man. Nice slam. Wow. Nice. Oh, dead.
I can get that. Everyone's doing so well right now. I know. Really? I'm really good. Really
good. I can't tell if you're trying to kill me because I think he's trying to find muted so that
he could tell people. Am I muted? I was unmuted. How long have I been muted for? Probably like an
hour. Hey, we missed blood. Everyone's freaking out. Oh, we didn't miss. Yeah, we did right here.
Well, we haven't gone yet. Oh, hold on. We need my smash. You got to break it. Yeah. Wait, wait,
this with you. This upgrade points. Yeah, you can. Yeah, you can. What the heck? Oh, my God.
There's a skill tree. Oh, there's always been skill trees. Starting skill. Next upgrade. Hey,
Ashley, I have officially replaced you. Oh, yeah. My box is as good as you are.
Okay, greater damage to enemies or a quick roll. Oh, now I'm more annoying.
How do I do it? There it is. That's my new ability. It's Sonic the Hedgehog over here.
Actually, you go pretty far too. You guys need that? Do you guys need a bridge? Let me know when
you need a bridge. I'll be useful. Rowdy touched it. Despite not needing it, Rowdy really made
her to drop it on you. What? I didn't do anything. When someone touches it, it falls.
But what are you going to do? I'm going to do the same thing. Excellent work, everybody. We need a
box. But hold on a minute here. Secret, secret. Yeah. Can you lift that box up a little? You can't
if you're on it. Oh, wait. Yeah. Oh, the whole teamwork, dude. Wow, look at this. Look at this.
It's a super. Oh, my God. That's a super. Shoot it. Oh, super. Wow. This game's got fun.
Oh, I think you might have to get it to touch this. This thing down here. Do we have to swap
characters? No, there's no swapping allowed. We get no swapping allowed, no matter what. I thought
I mean, it is allowed, but both packed. OK. No swapping allowed. Well, what do you want to do
here then? I don't know. I don't know. You should be able to do everything with only one person.
OK. Oh, no. What about this big lever up here? Yeah. No, there has to be something with this
mechanism up here. Yeah. No, maybe that drops the mechanism. Maybe when you actually shine
the light in there. Oh, I might. Yeah. All right. What are you? What? Wait, wait. Hold on. What if
you stand on the box like put the box here? Can you like stand and bounce it?
There you go. Like, can you do it from there? No. Hmm. Hmm. That's not how light works.
We got like a physicist.
What if you jumped down and aimed like as you fell? No, that's still.
Whoa, wait a minute. What if you did this? Hmm. What? Hmm. Stand on my thing. It's not
that I can't. I can't reflect it backwards. What if I do it the other way? Can I attach
another way? Wait a minute. Hmm. Oh, hold on. Let me let me let me move you down a little.
Hmm. If you were standing right above it, wouldn't you get it? Maybe. Right there. Right
right around there somewhere. There's an angle. Oh, hold on. I don't think there is. Remove box.
Get rid of the box. Right. Now do it. No, still wants to go that that way. Damn it. Hold on. What
if I go here? Does it reflect off of the metal above you? Oh, it's so close. Hold on. Let me let
me. Can you like skate on it from here? What? Look at that. Come on. That should count, game.
Oh, it briefly is counting. I see it like lighting up. It's so close. Oh, and we can't stand up there.
Oh, damn it. That's some shit. We did it. How are you supposed to do that? Nice work.
Uh, I need to like. Oh, sorry. I guess I just ride this.
Come on, Rowdy. Um, I have to do it. I can only get there by riding this.
Come on, Rowdy. Oh, wait. It's okay. It's a bridge. Whoopsie. We both jumped over.
Right. It's a bridge. Okay. You're right. Sorry about that. Sorry. I thought I don't know why I
thought that was in the same plane. Wait, what's up here? Secret? Potentially? No. I already went
over there. Oh, we have another light thing to do. Maybe this one will be not as ridiculous as the
last one. Where? Where am I trying to? Up here. Up straight up. Oh, is this wall a thing here?
Thing? I don't know. I feel like we're missing something that can reflect the light in something
else. Well, I can't. I mean, I can do this. I guess I can attach to your box and I don't know
if that helps at all. This again? No. No, it's blocking away. My forehead can reflect. Oh,
get the fuck out of here. You motherfucker. I did. I did pick the mode where we can have multiples of
each character, but I don't think that should matter because this is this is so easy. Just
wait doesn't change. Yeah. As far as I was aware, and I don't know if I could change to this point
because I mean, yeah, I could just also do that instantly. But I don't want to do that.
There's a no switch mode. So there is a no switching characters mode. Yeah. Oh,
but I don't think the game changes depending on whether or not you've selected that mode
the game changes. I'm saying I don't think that it does. Well, that's somebody didn't just said
like I just watched somebody do this and the game does change. Really? Yeah. Apparently the game
changes. There's less objects. Okay. How about if we go to main menu and I re-invite everybody and
we see? Yeah, let's do that. Wait, they're lying. Are they lying? We're confirming. Are they lying?
It's okay. I made it. We could switch all solely because I forgot in the beginning. You all get
to be the guys and I all want it to slam. That's just like the old. That's all I want. That's like
like the old school. Yeah. Yeah. That's that's the one thing I wanted. Okay. So let me know when
you're ready. I invited you guys. Okay. Okay. There it is. You're gonna trust his chat way too
much. No, no, I'm telling somebody. People have like proof apparently. This better not start from
beginning. I'm gonna fucking scream. Apparently this video proof. Yeah. Oh my god. It's the whole
thing. What? No. No, it's not. Attending a wizarding conference with his fellow wizards.
Hold on. Hold on. I'm seeing if I can. It's not letting me change levels. It's like we never even
did the other ones because it's because it's a different game time to find that mailbox or
different mode. Yeah. I knew this was gonna fucking happen. Speedrun. Speedrun. Anyone who just joined.
You didn't miss anything. Fast. Go. Oh no. But but but we have to do them all. We have to do all of
them. We'll skip the cutscenes. It'll be really fast. Okay. Very fast. Very fast. You could just
talk to your chat about like life and stuff. You were driving down the road the other day and you
had the coffee. No, no, no. I've had too many coffees. There's no more. What? In the world?
There's no more. I drank them all so I can't do those stories anymore. Uppy. Uppy. I don't understand.
The world has made more coffee since then. You would think. Are you swearing off coffee or do you have like
a heart condition now? I didn't actually. I still can drink coffee. It's the one thing I still am
allowed to do. You just. Nothing else. Nothing else. Sticky snow. All four boxes are the same color now.
That was a very genuine. My god.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
I'm just trying to get up there like fast. You know what I mean?
I'm going to solo this level. Oh, we got to recollect all the things.
It's only right. Got it. Just die. Just die. Die. Die. Just die. How do I die? I don't know. You
just get over here, right? You can just like teleport to me. I don't know how. Wait, we need
these. My trustworthy box magic. All you have to do is reach the mailbox and then it'll end. Just
reach the mailbox star. I'm doing it. I gotta go get my mail. Oh, poor girl. I can't believe
we would do this again. Well, now we. Here, you guys collect the things. I'm going forward.
I need another box. I really should have sent this postcard earlier to market. Why isn't this
nearest mailbox located any closer to civilization?
Oh, this is the tryhard sounds of keyboard clicking and sounds.
I need wait. Waiting for other players to continue. I need you guys to activate the
goat cut scene. What? What? No. I'm like stuck in this one thing. Fuck. No. Hold on. I'll get you.
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. We should like disconnect. Oh, no. I got it. I
glitched out and I got it. All right. Good. Because we need each other over here. All right.
Run. The speed run is taking longer than the actual run. Yes. I mean, it kind of sort of.
Okay. Now you stick that one on the sticky one over here. There's a sticky one here.
Yeah. $500 bounty on anyone who can figure out goat skip. Right there. The snow is sticky. Now
we need to weigh it down. So weigh this end down. Like this? Yeah. Like over here so we
could jump to it. Started. Did this one last time. How are you guys still back there?
Yeah. We need to know here. Go. Well, you're going to be stuck here. You're going to weigh
yourself down. Just jump off the map. There is no pit here. Jump off the map. Are you not even to
the fucking the bridge thing yet? There you go. All right. No, no, just stay. He's going to make
it from here. I'm not a wizard. I'm a warrior. You're time to open up the drama stream to see
where you're at so I can give my helpful tips and tricks for trying for. Wait, what happened?
Okay. There you go. Now. There you go. Yeah. You got it. Yeah. Shut up. Shut up. I don't want to
hear it. I can ban you all and I will. All right. Let's go. We're almost there. We've almost made
it. Yes. Oh yeah. Right. We just die. Yes. Death warp. That's how you do it. Okay. Now we need a
goat. How do you activate the goat? Dude, this is taking longer than the last one. Why don't you
guys just stay near a pit so that when I get forward, you can. Yeah. But some of the stuff
you have to have to more than one person do. No, you don't. No, you don't. No, you don't.
It's trying. You don't. Everything in trying can be done with one person. Oh yeah. If you can
character switch. What about the game mode we just played? Get those. Well, Jerma, we've already done
this level. We got the letter. Oh, wait. We need. All right. Here we go. Where are you? Come on.
It's spawning me back from the pit. Oh, it's spawning you back at the pit. Oh shit. Well,
I have a levitating device here. All right. Now I'm going to do this. Come on. Get it. Get it.
Oh, no, you got it right there. I figured I figured out how to do one person light reflect.
You picked the wrong skill. There's a dream shield where you can leave an
ethereal copy of your shield in place. And so you pick the wrong skill.
And I think it was a bonus. I think it was a bonus objective because we could continue without it.
Can we just confirm? I mean, you already got the joke across everybody in chat. Is this real?
Well, was this just like a like is this did they actually have less objects
in this motion? You already got us. So might as well just come clean here.
What? I'm just asking if this game both things actually real.
What? It's not. It's not. What's going on? I'm not doing this. You're doing it.
I'm not doing this right now. I don't know how to start a game that's not at level one.
A shame about the endless kill us back in the day with tended feels.
What the fuck is going on? Are you stuck?
I just my character just like lagged out. I'm dying.
Well, no, I'm actually somewhere where you can die and I'll be done.
I'll I'll be done to say, OK, I should teleport to you know, it's a haunted old man.
What? I don't know how you do this doesn't make any sense.
Switch it to the PS1 quick. Yeah, it could work.
Do you guys have this on PS4? We could switch. Of course, I bought a copy in every system.
Same. That's how much preparation I put in for the stream.
Now, can I get some people dances in the chat, please?
You put better.
Can we all agree actually that it was Ashley's fault?
Why? Because she picked the wrong skill.
Well, how did you pick those corrected?
How a good night to turn. I picked the first thing that
looks like it wasn't locked on my screen. How are you supposed to know that?
It's her fault. It's really her fault.
I feel like all right because we get to experience like the big like
hog moment of when we get the huge one again. You know what I mean? Remember that?
Oh, yeah, I remember this moment.
OK, I'm forward. One, two, three.
Why did you say go? Because it's a speed run.
Well, I'm backward. One, two, three.
Got it. No, I didn't. I went too high.
All right. I'm blocking the I'm just standing here. You just shoot it.
OK, let's go. Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.
Again, make sure he bounces it towards you.
You get it then go watch this.
Got it immediately. Oh, we're so good.
Oh, world's first. World's first.
Is that like six seconds? Skip, skip.
I almost just exited to the main menu.
It's going to be really funny when we do this for every stage,
even the ones we haven't seen yet, because we actually practice this on stream.
I'm talking to myself.
You know, actually, I was thinking you can tell me what the scale of comedy this would be.
I was thinking of like a long time ago, you know, like Dark Souls one speed runs.
Yeah, I was thinking, what if I just opened up Dark Souls was like, you know what, guys,
I'm going to like play Dark Souls. This is before I even played Dark Souls one like on stream, right?
What if I practiced the first like 12 minutes of like the Dark Souls one speed run
and got it perfect and just turned it on, just started fucking going.
I kind of did that with Dark Messiah where I didn't say I was going to speed run it,
and I just knew all the speed run tricks.
Yeah, but I'm talking like actual, like you learn the actual route.
Like you hate them.
Oh no, he hates us. Sad.
Wait, wait, so I gave an example of me doing it and your counterpoint was no, but actually.
No, no, there's a difference. No, there's a difference between I just play this game a
lot and know some of the routes to I'm doing the actual like any percent route on Dark Souls one.
There's a difference between I know this game pretty well.
No, no, I knew the speed run route. I did the speed run route.
Was it the first time you ever played it?
This is your joke and you're not giving me credit for it.
He didn't do that. Did he do that guys?
No lonely, sad man.
He didn't do it. All right, hold it back.
No, he didn't. I'm seeing a lot of nos.
Dark Messiah. Dark Messiah doesn't have routes is what people are saying.
They're calling you out.
You're not going to get the germ of blood.
Those balloons have things in them.
Now you agree it's germ of blood. Oh no, we fucked it up.
No, we had it. You had to get the blood.
But I was yelled at. Everyone was like, dude, blood.
I get yelled at all the time living with this guy.
Eventually, you just learn to live with it.
Now I'm going to pull this. Okay, now you pull it.
Now you make sure I can get across. Next I got it.
He's actually not getting these in the route. You get those because you need to have at least
15 to get the one skill. Yeah, he thinks he knows the routes.
This is actually like, I really like them. I need these.
All right, whatever. Who cares?
He's made the decision for us apparently. Hey, Steve, we hate you.
Yeah, I know. Why can't you be more likeable?
Hey, what have I happened to? I can do this all by myself.
Everything can be done. I got here.
I was doing everything by myself and I was trying to figure out how to do that one.
I'm sure there's a way. Actually,
probably if you connected the rope on both of them, you could probably do it.
If I told you to open Dark Messiah up right now and do the first 20 minutes in a route,
would you be able to do it?
Yeah, I think I could. I think I could do it.
Unfortunately, we don't have time for that.
And Jerma, you think it's like, oh, you just you didn't even the beginning of Dark Messiah.
One of the skips requires you to break cut scene, break, go out of like,
like the whole cut scenes happening and you're walking around outside of it.
Then edge clip on the edge of the map, but pause the screen.
And while the game is paused, you pause for an exact amount of time.
And then it launches you forward over a castle wall, specifically into one exact window.
And I did that without mentioning that I knew any of this.
And this is your joke. And I know this for it.
Why did why did you do that? Why did you why did you play it on stream?
Then just trying to prove how much better you are than everybody else.
I thought I loved that game and I thought it was funny.
It's your joke. You get it.
You get why I did it.
Oh, no, no, I'm the wizard. Why am I the wizard?
Players.
Rowdy wants to switch with Ashley. What?
What? No, no, you don't.
How did I do that?
You want to switch with me? How do we?
I just pressed like our I just pressed red.
Okay, I press red, red, red bumper.
Red Rover.
I was about to say red, red bumper.
What? Right bumper.
You got monkeys on the brain.
Okay, remember, remember to pick the right skill this time, Ashley.
Red rum.
Oh, murder on the brain. Oh, shit.
Hold on. All right.
We're actually playing the game now.
This is no longer the tutorial. We want to get the stuff.
I think you need to do the super launch, right?
The butt launch on here on the other side.
Do the butt launch. Do the butt launch.
Nice. There you go.
Oh, wait, I need those.
We got to go down. There's a lot of things down.
Oh, yeah, there is.
And you got a rope over here.
Uh huh.
Yeah, this is what I'm freaking talking about right now.
All right, now we have a level up.
We got a treasure.
Yeah, I got that before.
None of you were optimized.
I'm so far ahead of you doing the speed run, doing the joke, not getting credit.
I was thinking about this new series on YouTube telling me if this is interesting or not.
Where I watch a movie or a TV show that it's weird.
And I make a video that breaks it all down and shit.
But Pog!
Pog moment, hold on.
Shoot it.
Don't want to break it.
I got it.
I mean, you're going to call the series.
What are you doing?
No series is going to call like, dude, what is this box?
Where was this?
This is called. This is a different game mode.
We didn't know. We did not get you baited by Chad.
It was real.
Okay.
Okay. Well, go down, go down here, go to the bottom.
All right, we can do that.
That works.
I can't believe we cheesed it.
It was up here the whole time where I was poking around before.
Okay.
What's so urgent about getting this boy back?
Wait, maybe they want stuff.
Yeah.
I'm mad.
Hey, you picked the game mode.
I did.
And it's my fault because I really just wanted us to all pound the ground.
And we briefly did anyway.
It was really important.
Look how many of these they give us.
Yeah, this is a different game.
You can get off of it, Rowdy.
I don't even need both of those.
I don't even need them.
That's offensive.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's why.
Okay.
Level up, but maybe don't level up.
All right.
Hit tab.
I guess you don't get those till later.
Yeah.
You couldn't actually get dream shield.
Oh, yeah.
I took the other skill because it was the only one that I could take.
Thanks for blaming me for nothing.
I can't believe Ashley would fuck this whole thing up.
I mean, what are you talking about?
Buying the lightning sword again.
Found a new letter.
I hope you have found the missing prints by now.
You can read them.
I don't want them.
If not, please be warned.
Oh, reading the story in Trine.
I mean, like, really?
Reading the lore snippets in Trine.
What a big bird.
But wait, hold on.
Yeah, because then I need to go down here
and get these little gumdrops.
No, Star, you cannot recreate the video.
I'm sorry.
I know it was a funny video,
but we can't just try to recreate it.
That season already exists on TV.
I should have dropped the whole thing.
That was the real video inside us the whole time.
Inside of you?
Yeah.
Pepehands, old German, old Star.
The video was like 2014.
That's what everyone says.
I missed the old star.
Okay, I can attach to this.
So what does it want us to do?
Stick it up there.
Stop.
Just for a second.
Like we had it.
I missed the old star.
I'm trying to recreate it.
All right, I get it.
What about you?
What about me?
Are you confident with your hook?
So I got one attached and now bring me up.
When you are attached to it, I can't lift it.
What am I supposed to do?
Just stand on the left and jump across, but don't attach.
It was the explosions.
It was like it was the stomping that freaked me out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm giving you motivation.
What is this?
Monsters.
You actually have to fight in this game.
These are the things that stole the prince.
This is like a little secret area, I guess.
I guess, man.
Oh, I see.
Wow, that's that's one tap.
Okay.
Why don't you just bring it over here?
Maybe you go to the bottom.
Then you can do it more.
Can you make a rope for me to stand on, Jeremy?
I can.
Maybe I can give you the box.
I mean, you can stand on that.
It's gonna work.
All right.
There we go.
See, all three of us.
That's a true Trier moment.
Another big one.
There's a word, there's a word I'm gonna say.
I can't, I don't know what it is.
The chat's already doing it.
It's fine.
That's what it was.
What was the word?
I'm not in that chat.
Say the word out loud.
Loud and proud.
I don't know if I can right now.
Nothing happened.
Oh, my God.
Here, more of these under here.
Cool.
You gotta get the blood.
Yeah, I did.
Get off, get off.
You really are the like little brother, aren't you?
Get off.
Get up here.
Ashley, up top.
I'm getting off.
Get off of it.
It's mine.
Get off.
Get off of it.
Get off of that.
Okay.
Yeah, I didn't like that one.
I don't like that one either.
Somebody said, wow, you all suck.
This place is a freak show.
You fucking guys are so bad at this game.
Like, I'm missing dinner now.
What are you referring to your chat?
I don't know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Who are you talking about?
The freak show.
Otherwise known as German's chat.
Yeah, the insight, the what an inhumane psychopath.
You guys need this ball.
True.
I'm going to be true.
What?
All right.
Now, if you do the super blast,
you can launch the ball up.
Here we go.
There it is.
Do it again.
No.
Oh, nice one.
Do we even need that thing for now?
Nope.
Now we don't.
All right.
I'm going to attach this to this.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
Oh, it's just I see.
Oh, I got to jam this.
Can you get off that block?
Okay.
You got.
You know, you got.
I was holding still.
Okay.
I wasn't.
Yeah.
Okay.
I fucking love this guy.
German985.
They call him.
Steve, please.
What?
If I was running away from school,
I'd go somewhere with more entertainment prospects.
Wait, what does that do?
Does that like activate a button?
Did you press that?
No, I didn't.
What?
I think we can pull the thing down.
Guys, remember when we went to the trampoline park?
Yeah, it was fun.
Steve clipped split his pants.
Oh, yeah, I did.
Whoa.
Help me.
I'm such a simple.
Does that help us?
Well, it lets you do this thing to get up on the thing.
But then you guys have to get up here, too.
So how do you get up here?
Uh.
Do I need you?
Wait, I might have to do it.
Okay.
He's just a gamer.
That's all it is.
That looked totally wrong.
Let go, German.
Do I?
Yeah.
Well, there's a little hook on it,
so it makes me want to participate.
You go there.
Where he's standing.
Smash.
Yeah.
It's very satisfying.
Dude, I just love smashing.
Remember when Star spit on German's pizza?
What?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
Remember when you spit on my pizza?
Yeah.
Did you tell like a story or like laugh out loud?
I spit on Jeremy's pizza.
I didn't want you to find out like this.
It's actually really funny that this is the first time you're hearing of it.
Yeah.
This is often you walk in a train.
Yeah, I can't get those.
I can't get the bonus.
Bonus bits in there.
What do you mean you can't get the bonus bits?
Ashley can get the bonus bits.
Wow.
Imagine that's the only person who isn't a streamer getting the bonus bits.
Hey, we were going to do a thing.
Do you remember the like you spit a huge disgusting loogie in my drink and I drank it?
Do you remember that?
Yeah, that was weird, though, because you wanted it.
This one you didn't know about.
It's your idea.
All right.
So you guys remember the like the Star comes in by breaks in my window stream, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're going to do a thing where when he was sitting down, we were talking.
He was I was going to get up to do something and he was going to do a disgusting, real,
huge like Skittles loogie into the drink that was on the table.
And then I was going to come back and without changing a frame or a cut for it,
I was going to drink all of it.
Like whatever.
It was going to be like a like four or five gulps left in my soda.
And I was going to do the whole thing and it was going to be in frame the whole time.
Oh, that's tastes different than I remember.
And then I was going to say you missed that taste, don't you?
And then I was not allowed to say that.
Yeah.
No, you were not.
That's why we can't because I knew you could do that.
So that's why I was like, no, it was going to be we try and kill each other.
Yes.
We were like trying to poison each other, but it evolved.
We I was I was going to go get like a cup, like two cups, like, hey, here you go.
We're what are you?
Are you thirsty?
And you know, we're going to do the two cups, one of them's poison thing.
And each time that one of us for the cup.
No, don't do that.
And we were going to be switching the we were going to both know,
like I was going to try to poison star.
Right.
And he was going to be like, I, you know, chat, like, I know what's going on here.
What?
And he was going to switch the cups around and then he was going to poison one and switch it.
You guys ever seen Princess Bride?
Yes.
Great movie.
You know, that scene where he's like,
and then I switched the poison because you switched the poisons.
Therefore, I've got the poison in front of me.
That is a classic.
It's a classic piece of cinema.
We're going to do that.
Both of them are going to be poisoned.
And it was just the whole stream.
We're going to be switching back and forth poison cups.
And we've all can drink them.
Why didn't you do any of this?
Because we were just like, we probably can't like do this.
Why not?
I forget.
I forget why we didn't do it.
Because there's probably something in like the Twitch Terms of Service
where you can't pretend to poison each other on stream.
I'm sure there's something exists there.
Where was the harm?
Star wasn't going to pretend.
You actually bring poison.
Yeah, it's funny joke.
Who's going to drink the poison?
Guys, I haven't done anything for like two full minutes.
Are we good?
We're good.
You know how hard it is to order poison on the internet?
I would hope impossible.
Well, it's not, but it's pretty hard.
Okay, I can attach.
There you go.
I watched like a murder trial.
This guy was like the most unsure murderer of all time.
Coming up with all these different very schemes to get rid of this guy.
He did a lot of research.
So I thought a lot about ordering poison on the internet.
Why does she know?
Oh, there's big ones up there.
Oh, we need more bounties.
We need more bounces.
Launch me.
All right, here we go.
You got to shoot it.
I got to shoot it.
Okay, let's do it.
Those weren't even big.
Come on, this was a lot.
Hog incoming.
Get down.
I'm main ball.
Oh, I'm this ball.
Can I shoot through?
I can't get off of it.
What does this do for us?
No, you need to pull that.
Ah, yeah.
Oh my God, the brain.
You didn't say to do that.
He was complimenting my brain.
I was complimenting Jeremiah.
I think he is much smarter than anyone gives him credit for.
Who else would tell other people to spit a drink so that they could drink it?
We need to get there.
Yeah, because I wanted to have it completely in frame the whole time.
Like that soda does not move.
I think if you don't do it now after you describe it, that makes you a coward.
Like there's no...
Guys, there's all kinds of shit up here.
Yeah, are you getting it?
You guys have to get up here.
There's like all this light and bouncing and spinning and...
I need Steve to stop that.
Every time I think you're going to grab something, you grab the opposite item.
That would be disgusting.
Hold on.
Jerma is on weapons-grade laxatives right now.
Jump up.
What?
Steve?
What's going on?
What are you guys doing?
I can't...
Oh.
Me jump.
God damn it.
We're such fucking...
Get on.
I can't move.
Me jump.
All right, now let me...
All right, I'm holding it.
Oh God, that helps.
Star?
We're good.
We just had a moment.
Just look at all this stuff in here.
There's like a key in there and shit.
Whoa, what does that do?
Well, it causes the light to be black, so you have to grab this thing.
And then I think...
Nope.
Yeah.
I'll hold it the other...
I'm holding it.
It's pulling me.
Wait, I have to attach it.
Got it.
No, that's not how it...
Why is that not working?
Why did it get longer?
There we go.
Whatever.
What's in there?
I found a part of my door.
The whole quest was for home improvement.
We got points.
I got a skill.
Did you get a skill?
The rest is Prince and then redo his house.
Oh yeah, we got skills!
That's what I...
And that was a smart thing.
I don't want this skill.
That skill's dumb.
I don't want to upgrade the other people.
I want to upgrade me.
Yeah, I want to upgrade me too.
I don't want to just upgrade somebody.
Fuck you guys.
I don't want that skill.
I think you just like...
There's like five skills in these trees.
I think you just take them.
All right.
No, I want to...
I don't want that skill.
I know, I'm just...
I was doing my parts.
It'll move it.
Just give it some...
Just give it some time.
Give it a minute.
There it goes.
Does anybody else feel like they've been on this first level for like three hours?
This is not the first level.
Well, I mean like the first real level.
That was last level.
Oh wait, let him stand on it.
The bird?
You're being kind of stupid.
No offense.
I think he just...
Yeah, just jump.
You didn't even held it with arrows?
I knocked one arrow over there.
Like...
Well, that's so funny.
I wanted the bird to do a reaction video.
Massive bird!
A reaction video.
Have you been watching reaction videos?
You keep bringing them up.
No.
That usually indicates that you're secretly watching them and are guilty about it.
I'm not this linear of a character, Ashley.
You are though.
Am I hurting my back?
Jeremy, you gotta go get this.
Yep.
I weigh like 300 pounds.
You can't expect me to do things like this.
Whoa, he lived for...
Well, I jumped too early.
Too late to me.
Oh, he got the credit for living.
Hey, by the way, speaking of like the react videos,
I saw your like Star React stream.
I know, you were there.
It was pretty good.
What would you rate it out of ten?
Four.
Four out of ten.
Wow, that's better than usual.
No.
Four out of ten.
No, it was like an eight and a half.
What would have made it a ten, in your opinion, if you took your shirt off?
Maybe like a...
Less music.
Jazz, you're not a fan of the jazz?
No music.
Durn it all.
I got him.
We can go.
Found him.
He's here.
Wow.
Get him over here.
You must be the prince we're looking for.
Good thing too.
I was afraid you'd been eaten by wolves.
We missed Bloods.
I'm being rushed.
What do you want with me?
We're taking you to the safety of the Astral Academy.
What?
I'm not going back there.
You think we'd leave you alone in the middle of...
We're here.
Look, I don't care if you're a prince or a pig keeper.
You're coming with us.
I'm not a child to be told what to do.
Red eyes.
Okay, so the next cutscene we have,
we have to mute the whole game.
And then each of our characters,
each one of us has to do the dialogue on the bottom of the screen.
Am I muted?
Okay.
Yeah, no, okay.
You have to turn subtitles on.
Yeah, turn subtitles on and then...
Oh, hold on.
It's like a giant.
Why can't I fucking move?
Oh, why does this happen?
There's a wolf eating you.
Okay.
I clicked in the window like five times.
You got a rhizome.
I do.
I don't know why this does this.
Exclusive window, except I clicked in it.
I'm dead.
No, you're not.
Oh, a giant nightmare wolf.
That really is literally its name.
Giant nightmare wolf.
That's our...
Not the one, a one.
Oh, I should have blocked that.
Harder than stiff.
Yeah.
Almost dead.
This doesn't count.
Uh, I say we knock him unconscious and carry him back to the Astral Academy.
Um, Ashley, how come you didn't run up to the prince and drive your sword through his chest?
I did, but the cutscene lagging in place.
Hello?
What?
In my mind, I did.
All right, everybody.
For a second, just quickly, can we hit start?
All of you.
Go to options.
Just hit start.
Go to dialogue.
Bring dialogue to zero.
And then, uh, confirm.
Because the next cutscene, we're going to do our characters.
Voices.
Okay.
I can't wait for this to happen, though.
I meet one, by the way.
You just do meet one.
I mean, I'm a bad impression of meet one.
That's what it is.
What's with the snapping?
Look at this.
Come on.
Wait, hold on.
Everyone was just on board with this 15 seconds ago.
And all of a sudden, I hit...
I go in the options and actually turn it off.
And now we're not on board with it anymore?
We're on board.
What are you talking about?
No, I'm talking about the fucking crowd.
Oh, the crowd doesn't want this?
Cringe.
Cringe, dude.
You're going to pretend to be a cringe, dude.
That's so cringe.
What the fuck?
I don't...
Do I attach to this and then attach to that?
Uh, go up there and push the top one in.
To the top right.
Can I just...
I don't think I can do that.
Jump on top of this box.
I mean, I can't...
Oh, but you can just grab it.
All right, I'm picking one of them.
Can you shoot the top one?
Wow.
Oh, that worked.
Whoa.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Well, now I'm never noticing when the characters talk.
Because we turned it off.
Yeah.
Well, now it has talked because the subtitles are on.
Yeah, no, our characters have said things.
Stars are really watching his performance.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, no, no.
I have to put it on the wall,
otherwise we're going to jump forward and die
and I can't move it because Jerma's on it.
Well, go for it.
Now it's roped so I can't move it further.
But now you got to rope it.
There you go.
Uh-oh.
Bugs.
The nightmare spider.
As I feel, I do more damage than you.
Than me?
Than Ashley.
You're the wizard.
The wizard can get nerfed like 10 times.
Cringe spider.
See, your character's talking.
The wizards.
No, no, no, this doesn't count.
No, it doesn't count.
Okay, it doesn't count.
It has to be in a cut scene.
All right, we'll turn it back on.
You gave up?
Well, just into...
Wait, once we get to the end of the level, turn it off.
This is going to be like...
Always these gigantic $20,000 schemes.
Fire arrows?
What the fuck?
Holy shit, I'm way cooler than everybody in this game now.
How'd you get fired?
They just gave it to me.
No, I just gave it to them, dude.
They just gave it to them.
Ice arrows to freeze the rotating pla...
Oh my god, they're just giving it to them.
This is so cool.
Freeze the platform.
So I think you have to get off it.
Because I have to freeze it, right?
So it needs to...
Huh.
Yeah, get off.
Get off it.
Watch out with your noodly wizard arms.
Now I go like this.
And it's frozen.
And now we can get up there.
I don't know why it wasn't...
Is it...
I can't get my box through.
Hold on.
Oh, shit.
Ah, shit.
Well, it's frozen, so we can do that now.
Just need a box or something around.
I don't like that Jerma's character is going to be doing things.
No, I know.
What a disaster.
He has to freeze them.
Come on.
Oh, one at a time.
One at a time.
Yeah.
Just stay on the first one.
And then...
Yeah.
Like, I mean, I can...
Like...
Yeah, just...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Well, let me at least get on here.
Yeah, you can just make the jump.
You don't have to do that.
You can just make it.
Just stand on that one for a second.
And, yeah.
No, just stay...
Just let him do it his own way, Jerma.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to control your friends.
If I want to do something a different way, I get like...
Jerma!
What are you doing?
Jerma, get over here!
That's what we sound like.
We sound like bugs.
That's what he thinks we sound like.
Jerma!
Hey!
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Hey!
That's right!
Wait!
Come on now!
Whoa!
Hey!
You guys are fucking Beetlejuice!
He said it once.
No!
I'm still alive!
I can't get it?
Yeah, I get it.
There you go.
We don't go this way.
We have to go this way.
Great.
Nice fucking bottle!
Why did I read that?
What?
Get in here!
I can't.
Yeah, you can.
What are you talking about?
I didn't realize what part of the movie that is.
Oh, shit!
Jerma, you're not doing the joke at all.
No, you don't.
Something else happened.
There's something else a little more...
I saw honk in the chat.
And I was gonna move on from that one.
There's things up there.
Every time you go like,
Oh, Jerma, I think you have like a bathroom problem.
Well, same.
We worry.
We worry about you.
Do you know that I...
You do realize that I'm on like an actual prescription grid laxative right now.
You know that, right?
That's not a joke.
Oh, no, it's not a joke.
Every time you show concern.
Where my thoughts go.
He's on a weapons grade laxative.
Oh, I froze it.
Skill point coming up.
Can I freeze your box?
I don't think so.
Oh.
How are we supposed to do that?
Get off my box.
You can rope my boxes so I can stick my box up here.
Oh, shit!
Oh, I didn't know that was gonna come down.
Wait, you can stick it there.
Okay, I can hold it up.
It might still drop when you wait.
You waste so much.
Okay, so then...
Now what?
Now nothing.
This isn't it.
You gotta get off.
No, it's not dark web laxative.
No.
Can that stay there?
Now, what if...
Yeah.
Is there anything I can...
What about freezing it?
Can I freeze it?
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm talking about this thing.
The platform?
Yeah, the platform.
There you go.
Okay, now get off of it, Ashley.
You're ruining it, Ashley.
Now you got me.
Now you gotta grapple up.
Look at you.
Look at you, man.
Oh, a blue quill.
That's what I'm talking about.
Upgrade point.
You have two available upgrade points.
I can upgrade...
Ooh, what's this?
So many things.
20 more drops of germa blood before I can get something else.
So I think you actually have to put points into other characters.
Have to?
You don't have to.
I don't think you have to.
Well, because...
Don't let them talk.
Don't even let them talk.
The ones that are in squares, you get them as you play.
The Nightmare Prince is in the background.
Steve!
What?
I need your help.
No one's listening to me.
We don't want to hear you.
Germa, tell us about your day.
My day was pretty sick.
I need to... hold on.
Spiral arrow.
Freeze that one real quick.
Can you guys all get up here?
Spiral arrow.
Oh.
Whoa, did you just get like an illusory wall?
No, I mean, you couldn't...
I mean, yeah, sure.
Whoa.
Let me just freeze that one real quick.
Oh my god, he froze it.
Oh my god.
Oh, shit.
No!
Can you break through this gate?
How do we open it?
How would...
Yeah, there you go.
And you get the spoils in the middle.
So spoiled now.
You never told us about your day.
I thought you wanted us to listen.
Wait, hold on.
Use ice arrows to make ice raft.
What?
Ice car.
Okay, so that's cool.
How come your character gets to do everything now?
Because you chose wrong.
So stick it on there so we can do it right,
or I'll just jump on it.
Yeah, you don't even need me anymore
because you get ice arrows and fire arrows and...
Yeah, just wait till we get to the wizard level where I can...
Oh, do the voices.
No, it's too late.
It's too late.
Do the voices.
Because we don't have an actor.
He doesn't have a voice.
The wizard gave you a magic talisman.
What does it do?
He doesn't have one.
You were just the demon inside of that guy's head
while he was talking.
You were feeding him blinds.
That was great.
That was great that we all collectively did that
during the next cut scene.
That was awesome.
I'm turning my dialogue back on.
I'm so glad I got to be the wizard to talk.
Like I said, I got a big one and nobody cared.
Wow, you got a big one.
I can actually freeze them.
Oh, wow.
Holy shit.
They made this character awesome.
You can do everything.
I call that perfect timing.
What would you call it?
If that was one of those like arcade machines
where you got to wait for the lights to come around the circle
and then when the light is on the right light,
then you just go to stop and then you get the prize.
If you stop it on the light,
you would have got the prize when you touch the light.
Yeah, probably.
I love the warrior's voice.
It sounds so stupid.
You can't do better.
Why would you freeze that?
Unfreeze it now.
Why would you?
Jerma's throwing.
I would like a please.
Jerma's throwing?
I shot an arrow at a thing.
Oh, man.
You may as well have walked into the tower six times.
Who even knows what that puzzle was?
Who even knows?
Uh-oh.
Geiso.
Cool.
So where does this need to be frozen?
Or is it just a...
Hold on.
I think it's a butt pounder.
Is it a butt pounder?
Oh, we got to touch a thing out here.
Oh, okay.
Throw me up.
Okay, active.
And then that's a butt pounder.
But then how do you get up?
I don't know.
I think that is how you get up.
Yeah, okay.
So you get...
Is that working?
It should.
Kind of.
Whoa.
Try to...
Can you do it further away?
Yeah.
Yeah, there we go.
Dude, look at us.
The three triners.
Oh, hey, I got this.
Wow, you're so useless, Steve.
Wow, my character.
Fuck you with your ice.
It's supposed to be my job.
Not anymore.
You're not even nice with your...
Hold on.
There's something over there on the left.
Over that way.
Yep, secret.
Wow, and only you can unlock it, Jerome.
Stop throwing that in here.
I need to...
I think that actually helped somehow.
I think so, too.
Get me out.
Go up around.
And then...
Now I'll pull you in.
Nope.
What?
You gotta walk all the way to the right.
Okay, yeah, you go.
Okay.
Big brain.
Not even an ice wizard.
That's very humiliating for him.
My favorite wizard is ball lightning.
I'm a wizard.
You're not a lightning wizard either.
I am lightning.
I'm ice and fire wizard.
You're just guy that can pick stuff up...
Up ground.
I make box.
Yeah, make one of my box now.
Well, I just...
I did.
Because now we need your box to hold that down.
Do you see what's happening here?
You need your box in there.
So then she can get in.
Wow.
Box guy.
Hey, take it from an ice wizard.
Oh, wow.
Thanks, Jerome.
That was cool.
Remember that time you gave me your sandwich?
Princelius, why are your wolves and spiders attacking us?
Do you really want us dead?
No, I don't.
Nightmash just appear on their own.
I control them.
That's we lost it.
Satan.
Reading for the character.
Satan's audition tape.
We're trying for...
I am Asmodeus, wizard.
Sorry, Satan.
We think we're going in a more lighthearted direction with this one.
Okay, I'm a better wizard than you,
but you kill things faster than both of us.
Because you just drop box on head.
It is true.
You do a shit ton of damage for no reason.
I've one shot every enemy so far.
Put box on head or pre-recorded.
Well, you have to do that one.
I mean, that's just proves it at least.
If you were if you guys were here earlier,
you know that box on head is the end game.
Oh, that's right.
There might be a thing up here.
Is there?
One up.
Maybe.
I think you're gonna have to like it.
I'm gonna have to do the worms.
I'm gonna do the worms ninja rope.
Yeah, this guy knows there is something up here
and it is an elaborate thing that we need.
I think more than one person for.
Oh, okay.
Hold on.
Wait, can I drop it somehow?
Is there a thing I can shoot?
Actually, actually die already.
I don't want to die.
It hurts.
Oh, we're going to need your help to get over.
I think you got to make like a rope for us.
Do I?
Yeah, please.
With all your usefulness.
Okay.
Well, please, as the OP character,
come make come make a bridge for us to cross
like I would normally be doing.
Yeah.
Okay.
So that all right.
Now we all have to go over there
because then there's this stuff.
Sorry, I will unfreeze.
Get out the way.
I love how you're already frozen.
Get off my box.
Get out the way.
I got this.
I'm going to solo it.
All right.
Let him solo it.
Let him do his thing that he wants to do so bad.
All right.
Cool.
Nice.
That would sound like.
Yeah.
All right.
Call.
I don't I don't remember sounding, but all right.
Miss the collectible.
All right.
Did you miss the collection?
Did you really get up there?
You cared so much about your ego
and how good you are at video games
that you didn't get the collectible.
I just want to feel like my character can do something.
You know, not something.
I feel like when they designed to try
and they knew I was going to be the wizard
and they wanted me to feel bad.
Had a phobia for driving and getting through this garden.
German's more of a Patrick than a Squidward.
I would say star is a Squidward.
Let's stop talking about this.
Yeah, I'll agree with them.
Then we really shouldn't be adding any arrows into this.
I want to be Mr.
Fred's.
Maybe we'll be lucky and there'll be no other monsters to contend with.
Amadeus is hopeful.
Optimism was.
It's the one doing nothing.
Ban that guy instantly.
Come on.
Where are my muds?
He dropped like a rope or something.
What do you need help?
All of a sudden you need help?
No, I don't.
I don't need any help.
Jerm is the one who needs help.
I was up top the whole time.
No, I don't.
He doesn't need help.
I don't.
No.
I just stay there.
Spongebob do this.
All right, let's go.
Spongebob kind of does do that,
but except instead of pounding, it goes.
Hey guys, remember this?
Here, you stand on my box.
Run up.
Does that even work?
I jump.
Hold on.
Okay.
You have...
You jump and...
Everyone hated that.
Jerma has to shoot Jerma.
Stop.
Ashley, go to the left.
All right.
I mean, that one worked.
I have to freeze it.
I know.
All right.
And then I shoot a normal one.
Jerma could just freeze all of them.
Just not hold it up there.
Watch this.
Okay.
Never mind.
Jerma does the whole puzzle.
Yeah, nice character trying for...
Oh no, there's a combat sequence.
I wonder if Starb will kill everything in less than 10 seconds.
Should I even fight?
You know, that goes both ways, right?
You can freeze them.
I don't want to hear shit from you.
We missed a secret.
Over this way.
Or something.
Where is it?
Are you listening to your chat right now?
And you're making out?
No, no, no.
Look, look.
It's right here.
Is it up?
It's up.
There is.
Coming, big boy.
Thank you to Squirds for the five community subs.
Thank you, Squirds.
Appreciate it.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Congratulations to those who got it.
I'm up.
There's so much blood in here.
But we need you guys...
Well, at least I need Jerma.
You need me?
I don't know about Steve.
Yeah.
Thanks for the boost.
Hey.
Okay, what's up here?
Ooh, one of these things.
I think I can give you a bridge.
That'd be cool, wouldn't it?
Can I do that?
Yeah, I can.
And there's a treasure in here.
That's cool how you guys needed me.
Well, you are turning into like the third wheel here instead.
Can I get some more water?
Yeah.
Happy.
Also, can I see a drink menu when you get a chance?
Oh, yeah.
Today our special is lemonade.
What a shitty restaurant.
Oh, okay.
You have lemonade today.
Now?
It's poisoned.
Oh, I got you, Ashley.
Today's special, bread.
Our special, bread and lemonade.
What is that?
Our dessert menu, we have a bag of Oreos.
Is this prison?
Is this a prison restaurant?
Would it be cool if the two of you went to prison together?
It would.
We should film that video.
No, they've made movies about that kind of shit before.
But not with us.
Yeah, but it would be the same movie.
But better.
Well, two guys, two guys are unprepared for prison.
Go to prison.
And whoa, I wasn't ready for this.
Nobody's gonna read that.
My mistake.
I think this is a boss coming up.
Oh, oh, mechanic.
Oh, cool.
I'll just wait.
You got to charge.
Oh, you have to charge at this thing.
Okay.
That was fucking cool.
Whoa.
I get a super arrow now.
You guys.
This looks so.
Oh, my God.
You guys are doing such cool things.
Wait, do you need a box?
I need someone to go in there.
Do we need a box right now?
Yeah.
My salmon was fucking cold.
Salmon.
We don't serve salmon.
You have to freeze the water there.
Freeze gun.
Did I bring this?
Is that why it's cold?
Was this in the car?
I just love it when you start role playing out of nowhere.
Imagine going to a fucking restaurant and like bringing like a whole plate of dinner,
like salmon, like a whole, you bring, you bring this in and it's like freezing cold
and you set it up there and like, excuse me.
Ashley, come back here.
I don't want to bother you anything, but like this is freezing fucking cold.
Touch it.
Sir, we don't have salmon on the menu.
What do you do?
That's when you say, yeah, it's, oh, it's cool.
Oh yeah.
Cause I, it was in my car.
I'm sorry.
Can I get the check?
Yeah.
You haven't ordered anything.
That's all right.
Can I still get one?
I kind of need to prove that I was here just in case I did an alibi.
She has a blink.
Hey, do you need a box?
Oh no.
All right.
Anything under here might need a box here.
Oh, one head twirl.
How come I can't grab that?
Oh, wait, did we go up there already?
Throw me up.
Sorry, sir.
We don't validate alibis here.
Well, there's a big, there's a big like 12% tip for you.
No, no, no, no, right here.
No, please respect that box guy.
I need to freeze that.
I respect it, but can you please put it where I can freeze it in a good spot?
Thank you.
Put it in a spot where I can freeze this.
She can, she can fucking air dash.
Yes, but let me like flex on you too.
I can't, I can't put it anywhere else.
I'm useless now.
What is you freezing this going to do?
I still made it.
Help.
What are you going to do for you though?
Here.
Oh, thanks, journal.
You did it again.
You got it.
I just pulled it.
Did you not get it?
Keep pulling.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, there's things up here.
You guys, you're going so fast because your characters are so powerful.
You missed the secrets.
So wait, is this, is this a case of they nerfed the wizard so much
because they were afraid of how powerful he was
to now the wizard's not really that great anymore?
I think the next level, I get my ability, but I'm just being,
I'm being dramatic until then.
Are you, is there anything else up there?
Yeah, there's a big one up there.
Oh, it's a big one.
Big fatty.
Yeah.
No.
Give me a boost.
I didn't need it for the record.
You get it?
Okay.
Yeah.
Nice.
I'll just, just wait until there's some combat.
Oh, and then we'll use that.
Oh, wait.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But you're blocking it.
There's a box in the way.
Oh, we need to think about this one.
I think.
We need your point.
No.
Somebody can stand on it.
I can stick my box under it.
No, somebody can just stand on it.
Yeah, and then put it under.
There we go.
See?
Box guy, box guy.
Here comes box guy.
Can I freeze that?
Let me see.
It's like the Mario level with all the invisible blocks that show up in the first spot.
I'm the kaizo block.
Oh, I can freeze that.
Okay.
Lift me up?
Hold on.
Push it up like high.
And then, yeah, now I'll freeze it.
Can you lift this or do, do I?
Is that enough?
I can if someone wasn't standing on it, but someone keeps standing on it.
I can get over there at the back of the line.
Give it a good lift.
Lift.
There you go.
See?
No doubt.
I mean, we were trying to freeze it and then we can get up and the whole teamwork thing.
You might, you might feel like you don't need the wizard anymore, but I need you.
The wizard.
Oh, oh, oh, okay.
There's a bunch of stuff up here.
There's a whole nother way to go.
What the hell is this?
But wait, get it.
Got him.
What's going on?
I'm not entirely sure what's going on over there.
Maybe you, I think we need to break this.
Come on, Steve.
You good?
Yeah.
So what do we do about this?
You got to get the rock from the top right and then Ashley has to smash it at the wall.
Watch out, I'm going to smash.
Smash.
You got to smash it upwards.
Get out.
Look, you need the, you don't need my ability.
But you need me to tell you that you're wrong.
Tell a joke or riot.
Oh, well, whatever.
Need a box.
I need a box.
No squad stream.
Yeah, that's because Jerma doesn't want it.
He's sick of, he's sick of sharing viewers.
He said it's not fair.
He's not fair.
You're just going to leech off me every time.
So he said he didn't want to do it anymore.
This is absolutely untrue.
This is total fabrication.
I got to defend myself here.
Jerma won't even talk to anyone unless you have a stream.
I can't, I can't smash the guy.
He's got box blockers.
Kill him.
I froze him.
Star, drop your box on his head.
I can't, those walls block the box.
By the way, a squad stream on this game would be you opening three tabs of the same stream.
Let's just be clear on that.
Yeah, you have to, I have to bring this rock up top.
Can you freeze it?
Oh, sorry.
I froze it.
Yeah.
You hear that in this song?
Is it doing that?
It's the ding fries are done.
Ding, what are you talking about?
Can I freeze the water coming out of there?
I actually don't know what that sound normally is.
All right, I've got that frozen.
And now bounce the water from here into the, into the wheel.
I did that already.
What about the up, the up wheel, the wheel up there?
Oh, what about the up wheel?
How do we get the wheel?
How do we get the up wheel?
What's up wheel?
Okay, then freeze that.
And now.
Oh, okay.
Hold on.
Sorry.
If someone's going to talk shit about me now, stir confirmed family guy reference.
That was like an e-bombs world.
Joke, meme.
Is this going to work?
How do we do this?
Oh, you know, okay.
It kind of did for a second.
Oh my God, that worked.
As intended.
Star, what's, what the fuck is Spider-Man's name?
A fucking, what the fuck?
Why can I not think of this name?
Oh, Parkle, Parkle Pepper.
No, no, no.
Peter Pickle.
What is it?
What's the first one?
Peter Parker picked the pepper.
Oh, fucking family guy over here.
Fucking Peter.
Nice.
Oh, people, people, Peter.
I got him to say it.
Now you can, you guys can take that.
You guys can clip that one second that he did it.
Well, there you go.
Now he said it for real.
Who's your favorite family guy character, Steve?
Who do you identify with?
If you're going to like clip me and put me in like the German green screen videos,
just have me show up real fast and say, anybody need a box?
I need to skip jump.
Nope.
No, stop it.
I can, I can do this.
Oh, stop participating.
Okay.
All right.
This game is on you now.
Can you get up?
I'll wait till I meet it.
Okay, good.
Ego maniac.
There you go.
It's safe.
What's your favorite family guy character?
Adam West.
Hey, there's a whole thing up here, guys.
Are we doing the thing still?
We're doing a top left.
Come up here and do the thing or?
Oh, it's kind of high up there.
How am I supposed to make it up?
You need help?
I think I can grab it.
Nope.
It's just Adam.
It's Adam West because Adam West was just cool.
Like, is it?
He was a Batman.
He was.
Some would argue he was the best Batman.
All right.
I can freeze that.
So, but that doesn't help.
Wait, maybe we should free.
I should freeze this one.
Check this out.
Freeze that one.
And then.
Never mind.
Freeze this one because I can only freeze one thing at a time.
Now unfreeze the other one because we're in.
You're in.
Unfreeze the wheel.
Then freeze the wheel.
And then get up there.
And then do it again.
And then do it.
Then do it again.
And I'll do it again.
Oh, all right.
Wait, but now you're stuck in there.
Shit.
No, wait.
Do the bottom one.
Bottom one's easier.
All right.
I'm going to shift out of here.
Do it.
Yeah.
I missed the chest.
I got the chest.
You did?
Yeah.
The whole thing showed up.
Chat.
Oh, you got it.
I'm banning like seven people right now.
Hold on.
They're all fucking gone for good.
And while you're not in my chat anymore,
do me a favor and look for those emails.
How many permanent bans have you given out on your channel, do you think?
Ow.
Uh-oh.
I don't know.
They're all gone now.
I removed them all.
All right.
So we got, what do we got here?
We have water, which, okay.
I tried to grab the thing, but it didn't work.
So if I do this.
No, I'm trying to stop it.
I need to attach this to that.
Okay.
I see what you're doing.
All right.
You need to, hmm.
Maybe, actually.
We need to bounce the water.
I have to free something here for Ashley to stand on.
I think, I think I know what needs to happen.
I think you might actually need to have to do a loop around with your rope
to make the water come down the rope.
No, I don't think so.
Oh, wait.
Or Ashley.
You can get into there.
Okay.
Yeah.
You just have to, you could probably, yeah.
Now you just bounce it up there.
It didn't open the gate or anything.
Well, no, I put the box back there and then turn this way.
Oh, the wheels above.
Yeah.
The wheels above you that have the water go shoot up.
Or if you have Ashley just bounce it up from there straight up.
Are you muted, Ashley?
Yeah, I was.
Not quite far enough, but hold on.
I can do this.
Is it going to work?
It worked last time.
Come on.
Can you bring this box in here so she can stand on it?
Yeah.
What?
Why?
No, I can't.
Look at this.
The box denied.
I'm trying to think of what, hmm.
It's like bouncing the same droplet over here.
Distract.
Yeah.
Can you stand on the box?
No.
Can, can she stand on the box?
Not while he's holding it.
Not while you're holding it.
Can you just do it?
Just hold on.
Just keep, keep it.
No, no, no.
Keep it like, um, tilted.
Yeah.
You just had it for a second.
You guys, it's physics.
Get wet, Will.
For what?
I don't, I don't get it.
And then your rope doesn't do it.
Now, I don't know.
Put the box down here and I'll stand on it.
There it is.
Kind of.
Oh, that's strong enough.
As intended.
Almost.
I don't think so.
Unless it's like this.
What if you freeze that where it's coming out of?
Will it come out of the other pipe or something?
I don't know.
There's some weird-
No, no!
Sorry.
No.
I just froze that.
Wait, shoot ice about again?
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second.
Give me the, give me the box.
Give me the box, give me the box.
No, you didn't have to do that too.
Give me the box.
Give me over there.
Give me the other side.
Okay.
Get, oh, fuck.
Do it again.
All right.
Now, now get, give me the box.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, I don't, no wait on here.
I need to like get, I need to put this on top.
No, stop.
Why did you do that?
What?
You wanted the box, right?
I need to.
Okay.
I thought you were going to attach it to my box.
Get up there.
Wow.
This guy.
Who deserves a trophy?
Do I?
Take one.
I can't do it.
The ceiling's too low.
I'm not even like trying.
We have fight sequences.
I'm sorry.
Oh, he said it.
He said the name.
I'm not even trying.
There it is.
People have been like minus twoing my like shitty dad jokes this whole time.
Plus two.
Can we get plus two?
That's unbelievable that I'm even seeing even five plus twos for that.
That's unbelievable.
I'm ready to go in.
Okay.
Now I'm going to freeze this and let this go.
I'm prepared to enter the room.
I need a box.
We all had the same exact idea.
That's funny.
Jump on me.
I want to be the box.
Yes.
Is that a different?
That one's like yellow.
Why is this one yellow?
It is.
No, it's not.
Is it?
I got them all.
Let's go.
Let me attach this to that.
Is that the wrong way?
It's not turning.
I think it has to go up.
But hold on.
Can I spin this?
No.
Can I pull this?
I can't like pull this.
Hold on.
I mean, I'm...
You got it.
But we have to open the door.
The door is open.
Wait, should I?
What?
Okay.
Cool.
Is that too far?
Sorry.
Hey, you know how like I lift the box up for you
and then you go ahead?
Can you like...
Can you get used to roping them
and maybe helping a wizard out?
Maybe.
I need...
We need to like pull this over here.
All right.
Do it.
Lift it up.
You're on it.
I can't.
Can you get this?
Yep.
Here we go.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
We have to...
Yeah.
How are you here?
What?
I've been here.
All right.
Can I get a little bit of a pop?
Oh, you want a little bit of a pop?
Oh, you got...
Oh, she's the box.
I'm the box.
All right.
But then how do you get up here?
We need to help.
Oh, there you go.
Uh-oh.
Fighting.
This is my realm.
He shot my box out of the air.
That did?
He's anti-airing my box.
Well, now he's frozen.
Freeze.
Head box.
Oh, it's off the screen.
Sick.
No!
The platform is gone.
Yep.
I feel like there's something else up here.
Screenshot that and read it later.
Nope.
I think we should be reading other people's mail.
It's kind of weird.
It was mail for you.
But we got like this really important looking letter in the mail for somebody else.
We still haven't given it.
Oh, yeah.
It's like open immediately.
Why did that just happen?
That's actually a lawsuit letter sent to us for someone else.
Oh, my God.
All right.
There.
It's not my fault the postman doesn't understand what numbers are.
Isn't that the first thing you learn as a mailman?
This is a long ass level.
Right?
I can freeze that.
Pull it back up.
Put it in like a good spot.
Now I think we're good.
Nice.
I want that ability.
No, it looks like fun.
No smash.
Oh, I found a player to continue waiting for just waiting for the drops of virgin blood there.
What did you get?
That's actually a lot.
It must be upsetting to see what happened while you were away.
My nightmares ruin this castle.
It's why I was sent away and locked up in the dungeons of the Astral Academy.
Let's do them all.
You have the changer.
Oh, it's best you let me go.
Will you leave me behind?
That's me.
He said do them all.
I'm trying.
No, there's one way.
I just I give up.
Hey, breaking the gym.
Old reference skip skip skip.
Hey.
Oh, no.
Are we here again?
Tell me this is the whole game is one just long level.
We're in the dream world.
I was the only one not doing voices today.
Are you sure?
I can't actually just spit all of my screen.
No, it's so so impatient teleportation.
Ooh, that's cool.
Wow.
Cool.
Wait, this is where it gets a little weird.
You good?
I'm good.
Wow, the castle brand new.
It has all the old cobwebs back.
I stopped listening to everything he was saying like 40 minutes ago.
I don't know what he said.
You get out of my dream.
And he's just a Charlie Brown adult right now.
I don't I no idea what he's saying.
And me and Ashley.
I mean, actually, just do this puzzle.
So I'm going to freeze it.
Does that freeze?
What about down below?
The door doesn't stay open.
Here, we're going to get off of it.
You're muted again.
Can I freeze it when it's open or closed?
Yeah, you are.
There's a double mirror.
No, it's my box puzzle.
Fine.
It's your box.
I didn't need you something in the water.
Whoa.
Oh, don't touch the floor's lava.
The floor's lava.
It is.
I just proved it.
Oh, you got to pull this table.
What about those?
Oh, you want them?
Yeah.
Too far.
No.
OK, now I need something to attach this to in front of us.
Because then you're going to move it.
Check this out.
Now you're going to move it forward.
Oh, I thought that was going to be it.
I mean, hold on.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Just connect it to the box, not the hook.
Unconnect hook.
OK.
Now connect the box.
Well, you said connect to the box.
Yeah, now connect.
OK.
You're trying to make a bridge with this.
Yeah, I'm trying to make a bridge.
OK, well, you go then move it forward.
Ashley's on top of it.
I can't.
I'm on the box.
You can't do it.
Hold on.
If I attach it to this, you...
What the fuck just happened there?
That's another box.
Yeah, OK, now.
Damn, we don't need any of this shit.
I just had a plan and you know what to work.
You shouldn't even need my box.
I need another weight.
No, that's fine.
Oh, fuck.
It didn't go all the way.
I already have that one iced,
but I guess I'll do this one instead.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
What the fuck was that?
Ow.
That was me.
I helped.
Some of the portals can be levitated and rotated.
Hey, new mechanic for you.
All right, now just do the portal thing.
You have to do the portal thing at least once.
Let me go.
Flip it over.
You guys, you got to go into the other one.
Yeah, but how do we do that?
Hey, we need a box.
Look, this is a total wizard level.
Look at this.
All right, you ready?
How come my ability is only for one level?
It's probably introducing it,
so it's going to be here for the rest of the time.
I want to be cool.
Are we open the door?
You need to move that.
I can't.
Only some portals can be moved.
No, no.
What about the box through the wall?
Can you box through the wall?
Thank you.
And then Ashley needs to.
I don't know how you can get it up, though.
I can do it higher.
What?
Freeze it.
I hit shift.
No, you can't freeze airborne things.
Higher.
There we go.
We can just get in.
But why?
Well, we can go top left.
That was like the whole reason there was a wall.
Okay, no, actually charge through that.
Like charge through the portal.
Oh, okay.
For some reason, I thought that was too much to cross.
I have no idea.
Why do we move?
I think these things spawned in.
It took a long time to spawn.
Where am I?
Got him.
Yeah.
All right, freeze it.
But this can be rotated, though, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll get it.
That wasn't that funny.
Wasn't that funny.
It can't be rotated.
So freeze it.
Unblock.
Sometimes it's just that simple, isn't it?
Sometimes it's that simple.
Sometimes.
Not every time, but sometimes.
And it was funny.
I don't want to hear it.
All right, this is your puzzle, Steve.
Here we go.
I'm going to stand over here and hide.
And then blink.
And not help.
Is he how spiteful she is?
You say like one thing one time,
and then she like holds it over you for the rest of your life.
That's what marriage is, it's my job.
But there's a cool thing over there.
Be accountable.
This is a cool level.
I just like the way it looks inside.
Can I get a box so I can...
Yeah, this is all you.
This actually is like just a wizard portion of the game.
Hold on.
I'm confused.
We'll see how long it takes for you to do it.
Well, wait, wait, wait.
Ashley, you're...
I cannot freeze these, can I?
If I can shoot through.
I don't think that does anything for us right now.
Where do I put it?
My brain is broken right now.
I can't think, where do I put it?
All right, so listen, let me help you out here.
So, okay, so...
Flip it around.
I can't do it.
It doesn't work that way, Ashley.
Hold on, someone's driving a car into my house.
Let me give me a second.
Okay, yeah, you just had it.
Ashley, if you angle it...
Yeah, angle it a little bit.
Oh, that doesn't matter.
Oh, it was working a second ago.
Yeah, I can't do that.
There you go.
I can do that.
Fuck, dude.
Oh, your box.
Fuck, you guys are so bad at this game.
Like, I'm missing dinner now.
What?
You don't deserve dinner.
What is that even from?
When did I say that?
I had to have said that recently for you to capture it.
That was a clip that's...
Yeah.
No, it was the BA toxic Overwatch player thing, right?
You, like, want it to do it.
And it was right before we had played Dwarf Game.
Oh, no, somebody Ashley dot, dot, dotted me.
Oh, well, like, okay, I guess this works.
Why does this game even bother with combat?
You know what?
That is actually a really good question.
What's the point of even fighting stuff in this game?
Filler.
Is it just...
It's extreme filler, right?
It has to...
That's...
I don't know.
It breaks up the action a bit.
I guess.
I mean, if it was any way challenging, it'd be all right.
But this game only has easy and normal.
All right, Steve, look.
Oracle.
It's your playground.
Where is it going to?
Oh, in there?
Well, I have access to put like a rope bridge.
So there's one.
All right, so it has to stay.
So hold on.
Do that again.
Shit.
Can I, like...
Just keep jumping on my box.
Sorry, it's so tempting.
Let me...
I can't freeze the door.
Just stack them up so it's high enough.
Get another of these.
All right, just put the boxes on top of the boxes.
Put boxes on top of the box?
And just stack them up and then just make the angle right.
But you got to have it be the right one on the right angle.
Oh, that didn't work.
The third box has to be the one doing it.
Oh, okay.
So then wait.
Hold on.
Just go up.
Just climb up.
Oh.
But what about you guys?
Figure it out.
I mean, I can put the rope up.
I guess it's still working.
I guess.
Whatever.
Dot, dot, dot.
Maybe it means we have a dungeon down there.
It's lore.
No, there were things up there.
Were there?
Well, I...
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Elevator fight sequence.
Oh, what are we going to do?
Quick a bunch.
I'm going to do fire on this one.
It's going to feel like it's cool.
Yep.
Never mind.
We just have to move.
What about this?
There was a terrible old scare over here.
There are a lot of secrets in this game, though.
What do I do?
You missed a door with a hookah.
Door with a hookah.
Door with a hookah?
It can be opened?
I'm pulling.
Oh.
It goes up.
Okay.
So, yeah.
Just give me a boost.
Get off the box.
Just let me pull the wire up.
What do you mean?
Oh, I see what you mean.
Okay.
I don't think that works.
That has always worked.
It was for a second there, see?
Why are we on different planes?
Yeah, see, now it's...
Okay.
Never mind.
But we have to get in here, though.
We do.
You have to get in here.
It's taunting me.
Put your shield up.
No, I can't yank it up.
We were doing it before.
I could have made it in.
Try to do the thing where you push me up again.
It's kind of working a little.
It's staying.
All right.
Keep going.
Come on, game.
Just brute force it.
All right.
Do it again.
Get in.
Freeze it.
Was that it?
I think that was it.
Freeze it.
I got it.
I think that was it.
No.
I can even go in now.
You can't even go in there.
I froze the door closed.
Good job.
No, but this...
You did that before, too.
Oh, whatever.
Someone else will get it one day.
The next set of adventures.
Yeah.
Someone else will do it.
Later.
Oh, God.
All right.
I'm just going to do it regular.
Wait, what?
Oh, you've lowered the poison.
But we didn't even go in here.
Look at the stuff in here.
Where?
There's three...
You got them?
Okay.
Well, we're over here.
And then I think now you have to spin this
so we can jump into it and launch ourselves up.
Mm hmm.
Can you do it?
Now you're thinking with PODL.
Now you have to go up this door and go to the right.
Now you have to fight a wolf.
Hey, Nightmare Wolf.
Hey, Wolf.
Whoa.
What?
Were you just doing that?
Yeah.
That's my cool ability that I unlock
is moving the pointless enemies around.
I froze it.
Sorry.
What are you trying to do here?
Yeah, I can't put a box there.
No box guy.
Well, you guys are now down there
and you get across
and then you can get across
and then I can get across because of this.
I can grab this thing.
Just give me a box for a second.
Fuck.
You need to be on the ledge.
I have to make a bridge like that.
Oopsie daisy.
Oopsie.
I can't really.
Oh, now I can.
Oopsie.
I don't know how to help you.
Jerma probably does not remember that he can roll.
I know how to help you.
I can put a box on that.
Wait, why is that coming out like halfway?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You put the box down there.
All right.
Lift it up.
Press button.
Okay.
Now wait.
Hold on.
This is going to be hard.
Oh, you can just go down the second thing.
That's what I'm trying to do.
I forgot Jerma could roll too.
Why does he get to roll?
Okay.
Now do it again.
Thank you.
Now.
No, no, no.
Put it over here where I can do it.
You can just roll from box to hook.
What if it falls?
Well, you look cooler that way.
Yeah, I know.
I can roll, but I roll into a waterfall.
Water.
I don't know.
Whatever.
Yeah.
How funny.
How can you do that?
Huh?
I mean, I know I have to roll, but the roll doesn't give me like extra.
Like I can roll like this.
But if I was ready, like I just roll into the arm.
What are you guys saying?
I want to roll.
I've been rolling around the whole time.
It doesn't give me like extra momentum.
All right.
You do that again.
I'm going to do the SpongeBob laugh again.
And everyone's going to be pissed at you because you made that happen.
I haven't heard you do the SpongeBob laugh.
Oh my God.
We have to have this hit all of them.
Come on.
Oh, almost.
Just make it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go.
Look, it made a ladder.
All right.
Cool.
Instead of moving boxes, I can move one other object.
Uh, I'm about, I'm going to, I'm going to light this up.
So it's going to move.
Oh, wait.
I'm very right.
That's how that works.
We did it.
I, uh, I can freeze it.
Oh, you got it.
Doesn't even need our help.
He's a big boy.
Guide the two light beams through the yellow crystals on the sides of the cube
to combine them into a single stronger beam.
Interesting.
Thanks.
Like it boys.
Oh, it does make a super beam.
Pardon me.
Oh, we all fell off.
It looks like.
No, perfect time for the demon voice.
And it didn't do it.
Yeah, it's true.
Uh, why are we?
What?
We're all wizards.
I don't even know how to use the wizard.
Well, you know, he only played through his tutorial twice.
Oh no.
A problem that I can't smash the head with.
All right.
Hold on.
There's this, the middle thing can be moved.
All right.
Put, put a spinner over here.
Somebody guide the light.
Yeah.
Okay.
Now, um, what do we do with that thing?
She's holding onto the edge.
I can't rotate this one.
Oh, I mean, it's going in, but what I think we have to do a super beam over there.
Yeah, I don't.
Okay.
Oh, actually just smashing the box.
You're not helping.
I'm not involved in this.
All right.
What do you get the get?
Yeah.
Grab that one and then we have to turn.
You can rotate that.
Right?
Okay.
Bring it forward.
Oh, we have to do it to the cold.
Yeah.
It's going to go on the college.
See, like it, it's got to end up shooting up.
Oh, so then I can just standing here watching us do this.
They'll get it.
Any minute now.
They didn't die on boredom.
I thought we were aiming at the wall.
No, don't worry.
We're going to do this like two or three more times.
I actually won't.
What?
I actually won't have to.
I feel like more than two people.
You're just like getting in the way.
Come stand on the left and go take a shit or something.
Oh, I do have to take a shit.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Hold on.
So you just move over to the right and I think I can do it.
Well, how are you seeing that?
It's got to go up.
You got to put yours.
It's got to be you.
You got to be shooting it up.
It's got to go up through the middle portal here.
That thing's got to go over here.
How do you rotate?
Z and X.
Z.
Okay.
Well, I'm using it.
I'm using it.
I don't know, dude.
I'm not using a controller.
So how would you maybe it has to be down here?
Well, two beams have to hit it.
Wait, how do we just have it?
Get rid of this.
If we just get rid of this box right here.
Put this box in the cauldron.
There you go.
Right there.
Nice job.
Good to work.
So this is aiming down.
I actually left a fucking box in here.
It's just in the way.
It's just a box here.
All right.
What about this?
Can you do anything with that?
Can you get like the double?
Oh, no.
All right.
What about if I grab this one?
Anything happen when I do this?
All right.
Hold on.
What about what about?
Wait, wait, wait.
Can you do anything with that?
Um, maybe check it out.
Can you angle it with that one?
I don't think so.
That's blocking them.
They know they're around this one.
You can't do it with this one here.
Like in the center here.
I'll hold this right there.
This fucking box.
Oh, I'm back.
What happened?
Delete your box.
Oh, shit.
How?
We almost got it.
Hold on.
Wait, hold on.
What if I do this?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Put it back up.
No, back up.
Move it.
All right.
I'll turn.
Wait.
All right.
I can't get it to aim there.
Hold on.
I need if I go like this.
I'm either going to have to have the box be here.
What are we doing?
What's the point of the middle?
Oh, that has to be lit.
Or the cauldron to even open.
Oh, shit.
Okay, well, hold on.
Then this one has to go this way.
No, shit.
This one has to go.
Shit.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let go of it.
Let go of that one.
Let go of this one.
Yeah, I think.
And now you've got to double here,
but it's got to be angled up.
Put your box under this, Ash.
What?
Hold on.
Let's see.
No, that's not going to do anything.
Wait.
All right.
Let me hold that here
because I don't know what the button is.
I actually do not know what the button is
to rotate on control.
Yeah, but if I put this here, it blocks.
Still lit up.
Oh, to the right.
I can do that, but then I can't aim it.
Yeah, you can.
Keep going to the right.
You can only do that or that.
Yeah, but how far can you go to the right?
Can you go up?
Oh, shit.
Like, how close can you?
This isn't going to get it.
Fuck.
Um, here, let me try that.
Let me grab that.
Oh, wait a minute.
What if I, what if you put a box under that?
The box is.
Well, I wanted to get this
at a sideways angle to shoot up,
but I guess you can't do it.
So no matter what,
this is going to have to be down here.
Yeah.
So then the only thing that works.
So a box has to be under there.
Ashley, drop your box.
Okay.
Now it's a question of moving this one.
Hold on.
Let me see this.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Because this is just shooting down.
Yeah.
And you can't rotate it.
Well, it went to move that one back to where it was.
What if, um, bring it all the way down?
Does that do?
It just shoots.
Oh, that doesn't.
The poor chat isn't paid.
Uh, okay.
Um, yeah.
But if you do it like that, then I don't this,
this, which is more patient than you guys.
Yeah.
And this, this person's trying to kill us.
So come on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Shoot into this.
Can we do something with this?
Do we, why are we trying to shoot that into?
Because that one's going to shoot straight down.
Why don't we angle it?
And why don't we angle the shot into the fucking bottom one?
What do you mean?
I mean, do, why do we, why do we have to like aim it
and shoot it like at an angle?
Can you reflect the double beam?
It's always, these are always right angles.
Yeah, but you can, we can reflect the,
the super beam off of one of the mirrors, right?
Yeah.
But the mirrors are always right angles.
So this mirror always has to shoot up to get this thing.
We can't have like a weird,
I guess we could have like a half angle.
If we fucking slightly tilted it on another,
like there's no way that's the point.
Just put super beam in the middle.
Sure for it.
That's what I'm saying.
The super beam has to be in the middle.
Actually.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Drop everything.
Jerma drop it all, drop it all.
The top left one has to change, doesn't it?
I've got it.
See, I didn't think that the super beam could open the cauldron.
All right.
Level three.
That's what my hangup was.
I don't, I don't fucking know, dude.
It's tricky.
Okay.
So now we have the super beam.
It's a ball of market now.
Killer.
Burner.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You just got to do that the other way.
We're just going to flip this whole thing.
Well, you just mirror.
No, but we just mirror what we just did and then push this up.
Well, then that shoots this into the ground.
That's not mirror.
Sure for what do we do?
Okay.
Wait, wait, drop the thing you're moving around.
That has to shoot your, it has to go down down.
It has to go up ahead.
Okay.
So then move.
Now that's, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Now you should be able to angle it.
If it, if you go.
Oh, there's two things that I think will be lit up.
So if you, what do you move this one down a little?
Like, can we, that one's not doing much.
This one has to be.
All right.
Let me see.
You know, sure for is on it.
All right.
Sure for what do you think?
Left down.
That's what I was just thinking, but I don't, you have to flip it twice.
Why?
What happened to the German stock?
When did he get a bunch of minus twos?
Because, because us not being able to figure out a puzzle is,
is a bad joke, apparently.
I guess.
Imagine being so jaded at like everything you watch.
Trying to see if I can get this at a sideways angle.
Move right down.
We can do more than one box.
Left down and hit the yellow.
Then move right down.
Then what we do, what do we do with this?
Cause it has to go all the way up to the top left.
It's gotta like shoot into the top left.
Here, here, here, here.
I got it.
Yeah.
But now that has to be this has to be mirrored the other way.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, don't, don't wait, wait, wait.
Nobody move.
Do exactly what you just did.
There's one on the ground right here.
Hold on.
Get rid of this.
How do I get rid of this fucking thing?
Okay, do exactly what you just did got it
Finally you actually did it minus two you fucking guys are so bad at this game like I'm missing dinner. No
Even though which is talking shit. Well, she's a witch. Isn't that kind of what they do? That's her job
The cat
What was the whole thing with the likes wimmy's
Back then you see like on his shoulders like the big swimmies the big like inflated pads
Is that like a there's like a status symbol or something
Yeah, like in blizzard like the better you are at blizzard world of warcraft the bigger shoulders are oh
My god, he looks really weird without a helmet
I think I have to go. I'm just double-checking that
Where you going?
D&D, I think it's it's time. Oh
You're gonna go. Yeah, I'm right sure for he knows he's there. He's one of the boys right? Oh
No stars got to get out of here star and Ashley gotta go
All right, let me uh, this is important though before you leave do you want to play this again? I do
You want to finish this game? Okay. Yeah. Yeah. All right
Weekend trying
Tuesday trying trying whatever it is
One day I'll unlock my second ability conjured a ball and then I'll finally unlock two objects
Trying Tuesday's all right. Well, I just really sincerely hope it'll let us pick up from where we stopped
Well, I keep saying saving in the top right
I'm assuming that means it's saving the game
Right. It's all up to Steve. So it's all
I've got all I can select level from this screen. I'm gonna assume everything is great. It says saving
I'm going to continue quitting to desktop
Okay, and then I'm going to
You know, Merry Christmas on German, I'm gonna wish you a Merry Christmas have fun at your at your sesh
I'm gonna have a Dean Dungeons and Dragons sesh. Cool. I you know, I gotta go
But German is gonna play some old Atari game. You never heard of I think and you're gonna be like, wow
This is he's such a boomer
It'll be great
Now that actually sounds like a pretty good idea. They got an Atari like 2600 scream
Like play the one of the oldest existing football games that were like on the Nintendos
That's that was pretty cool a for all buttons for all actions, but it's hot hot a hike a a a pass a
run to goal a
I'll dig ET out of a landfill somewhere and play that too. I guess. Okay. Yeah, maybe
But hey, see ya see you next Sunday for trying Sundays. Yeah. See ya. All right. See ya. See you later guys
that was us that was star and Ashley both very fun cool people and
I
I'm gonna give you an unfortunate circumstance here
I'm gonna I have to leave I'm gonna go to I'm starting to feel a little
Strange downstairs
So I I have to go. I will be live tomorrow. This is actually into the stream. I do have to leave
So I'm sorry, but it's okay because like I said, we'll there's gonna be less time on stream
But there can be more days. So I'll be live tomorrow
I'll be live tomorrow at the same time. So we're on like one or two tomorrow
I'm going to start the thing. We took a nice little break from horror shit
So tomorrow we're gonna go to the thing should be interesting same time. He hates screaming
I still think that's funny. But yeah, well trying it's fun. It's fun. Just to just play a game sometimes
Brings me back, you know when the three of us played games, so you'll see trying to get next weekend
We'll just I'm sure we'll probably get somewhere close to the end
What is it like a today 10-hour game something like that? I think that sounds like plan to me
But I'm not gonna leave just yet. I am going to just be right back for a minute
I'm going to get some water and I'll come back and we'll do the bits and then I'll see you guys tomorrow
I'll see you guys really soon. Be right back
Sound
Yeah, I'm here
Thankfully, I've been on this medicine for like a week and
after like
Eight to ten days. I don't think I'm gonna have to be taking it anymore
so
We'll go back to normal and probably like another four or five days. I would assume
We'll see. I don't know. Maybe I'll talk to my doctor and he might be maybe he says no you stay on it
I don't know but
See you guys tomorrow. We'll play the thing. I still have to do Parappa the Rapper and Parappa the Rapper 2 and
Talking about PlayStation 1 stuff. I have
Bushido blade and Bushido blade 2 so that should be a lot of fun those
I remember those games being a lot of fun. Those games are awesome. Dermacycle still not there. Not yet
When's Rhythm Heaven when I get a DS
That I can mess with or I'll find another way but let's go back to earlier we had sticks Renegade 250
When is Dead Rising?
After that, we've got the thing
However, I might not even beat the thing. I don't know if it depends on how it plays out
But the thing I've got Siren for PS2. We've got both the Parappa games
and Bushido blade and Bushido blade 2
after that
Then you're looking at probably Dead Rising and then after that we'll see I mean the Halloween stream is gonna happen somewhere in there, too
But sticks Renegade. Thanks in 250 any chance you play crash team racing one day nitro fueled
I know you like driving and games. I saw Vinny played and it was hilarious seeing him rage at the game
It's way better than Mario Kart. I have never played any of the games besides Sonic racing
I've never played any other racing game. That was not Mario Kart
Let me a cartoon racing game and everyone's played cruise in USA. I mean everyone has well Garfield cart was a joke
I played that for like 32 seconds Simpsons hit and run. That's not a racing game
That's like a GTA game. Every mission is a racing. Yeah, but it's not like a 3 2 1
Race the 12 people with you. It's not like a cartoon
Racing game where you race on tracks. It's that's that's like a Grand Theft Auto clone
I mean you can race in Grand Theft Auto
But Grand Theft Auto is not a like a cartoon racing game and you can do them there was a count
All right, but you guys know what I'm talking about. You know what I'm saying
I do good at least one person does two people do cart game. There you go. Thank you
But I don't know maybe time GTA game
Maybe one day if there's something to do nothing else to do or whatever if I don't have any plans or anything
But thank you sticks renegade. Thank you Elizabeth for the 250
So after having I'm jammer Lammy soundtrack on my mind since yesterday
I stumbled across that in stage six of the worst song in the concert hall with the weird green alien
It was actually changed for the US version of the game where in the US version your belt gets stuck on the door and you go
Back in time. However in the Japanese version you get hit by a car you die and go to hell
Yeah, I remember we were talking about that yesterday
Why is that such a I don't know why that's such a big deal for the US sensors that why that's weird of all the things
Like there's somebody like fucked up violent crazy games over here
That's the one that you know, you have to censor they wanted the US version to appeal to more younger kids
I guess yeah, but I don't know if I don't they like go to hell in a Teen Titans episode
Yeah, that pregnancy level really appealed to the kids
Right like what? Why is that the that's fucked? That's true. Yeah, that's fucked up
There's a Disneyland ride that ends with you going to hell
Almost every cartoon from the last hundred years as an episode with the devil or something. Yeah
Whatever, but yeah, thank you Elizabeth. Thank you. Toast fart for the 500 bits
Thank you, sir. Canine for the 300 bits. Jerma. I saw this in a recommended
So this isn't recommended on YouTube on one of your vids and I thought you'd find it funny
Let's find out what do you mean you found this isn't recommended you got a tenth of a second
This is a different YouTube link than the one from last night. Don't start this shit
Thank you rec records
Recor SED for the 250. Hey German inspired by the carnival stream. I went out and got this done
Thanks, Jeremy. Wait, you got a tat. This is tattoo
Are you serious? Hold on a second
Hold on a second. Wow
Why that the um, it's a little confused though
Because why did you get a you got a tattoo of me? That's weird. I mean like that's that's a tattoo of me
I mean, it's cool. I'm yeah, I'm showing it right now. I don't know why you got a tattoo of my face
That's actually a really like cool tattoo
EU date
That's great that's
That's I love it
That you know what? I love I love tattoos that are really just simple and like basic
tattoos
Because that you know, it's like it's like a small little piece, right? You know, I mean, I like the small tattoos the little ones
That just like you know, hey, look at that. I got that. Oh, wow, that's cool. Look at that
So it is a tattoo of you. I kind of walked into that one didn't I but it's alright
That's an awesome tattoo rec
Thank you for sharing it with everybody here and thank you for the 250 appreciate it cool tattoo
Thank you generate blue for the 300 bits. Hey, Jeremy
Just wanted to give you some bits for the quality entertainment you provide. Thank you the streams and thanks specifically
Especially for pulling back the starting time as it's severely easier to catch your streams now
Even if I got to go to work early the next day
Thank you for the 300 bits
Appreciate the kind message and yes, the reason why I pulled it back is because even I
started to see that as the streams obviously not this one, but
The average stream time has increased over the last couple years and moving to Pacific time
When a stream is six seven plus hours on average, it's
It gets so late for everybody else that I just I don't want people to have to stay up to like three or four o'clock
in the morning every time
so
They're like 1 to 2 p.m. Start. I think is a perfect time. I don't think I'm going to change the time of the stream
again
EST is crying. What do you mean? Yes, two three five o'clock six o'clock Eastern start and
That's like prime time in it
That's like, you know six seven p.m. We really get going. I used to start my streams at seven Eastern
Which was about four o'clock Pacific and then when I came over here it's a Vegas
It was I obviously was not gonna start seven Pacific because I would just be too late. I think for everybody
But yeah, I like it too. I think it's doing well and it'll stay but thank you generate blue
Thanks for watching the stream
Vilemi, thanks for the thousand bits ten dollars ending the stream because he's stinky
Thank you for the thousand bits appreciate it Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 500 bits. No message. Just 500 bits. Thank you
Let's get the credits on this little short stream. I actually can move from here
Here is there camera on no, I just dumped this is what this is the camera section
Thanks, everyone summoned for something. Thanks everybody for summoning me from health appreciate it
Thanks for supporting this tree. I'm seriously and thank you for writing with it again for the 500
See VFD. Thanks for the thousand bits. Great stream as always German. Thank you. Yeah
It's it was a fun one. It was just it was it was a just hanging out with my friends
Sometimes I have some of the most fun when I'm just chilling playing a game just talking about random stuff
I've been having a lot of fun on stream
Not that I wasn't having it before but I've been having like a ton of fun
The last like six months and like I said, it's not not even like oh, I wasn't you know, seven months ago
Wow, I really was I hate streaming
No, I think there's just been a lot of fun things going on recently
You ever get burnt out
Nope, because I take a lot of time off. That's by design
I take at least two days off a week at least two three days off a week to make sure that that doesn't happen
I mean for the most part do you this stream is live four times a week three or four times a week sometimes I
think it's important to take all time off not just to take care of stuff in your life, but
It lets you
Unplug a little and I can continue to have fun on this stream and go back and forth with you guys and have a good time
because
It's I have time to be away from it, too
You did how does it feel to die to third wheel?
So I I appreciate streaming more because I do it less and that's the way it's gonna be and that's the way it always
Will be but yeah, it's kind of the way it is
does hate it
No, I don't but thank you
for
Kind message. Well, actually that was Vilemi was the last message they said ending stream because he's stinky
No, see oh see VFD right great stream as always. Yep. Thank you
gnarly thanks for the 250 enjoyed the trine stream had fun watching the three Triners solve puzzles and keep
Willy wonking in all the time. Will I wonk it in huh?
Yeah, no it is fun you'll see it again, but we'll complete it if it takes another stream or two
We will do the three Triners again, you'll see it. Thank you gnarly. Appreciate it Vilemi
Thanks for the thousand bits Jerma lied about Jerma psycho. I never promised Jerma psycho
I said it would be there maybe eventually but I wasn't gonna give a time frame on it
I'm looking for the right image
Yeah, I said it's gonna be here, but I didn't say it'll be here tomorrow
Figs nice. That's all that's actually awesome. I can't wait to eat a fig or a fig spread maybe
I have to be careful though
Well, I'm done that home. I'm fine fig Newton's are the best cookies
I you know what here's the crazy thing fig Newton's are the best cookies that you never buy. I don't know
I what what what's what's with that? Why don't you just get them? I love fig Newton's, but I don't think I've ever purchased them
Don't ask me why you always get like the shitty cookies that you know that you're not gonna eat very many of but I would eat
The whole box of fig newtons then all right the next time I go to the grocery store
I'm going to buy fig Newton's
Or I'll do a 24-hour stream
How about that one and I'll eat one on stream just so you can know you can prove it, but thank you for let me for the
Thousand bits. Thank you. Tay for the 250. Hey German love tonight stream. Thanks for being here. Thanks for hanging out
Thanks to the 250 as well. Keith King. Thanks for the 250. Are you still planning on playing more Katamari games?
We love Katamari for the ps2 is my favorite game and I'd love to see my favorite streamer play it
Yes, I
At some point I'm gonna try to do
At least a couple more of the Katamari games because those streams are a lot of fun
I did the first one all in one stream, right? I think that's the only one I played
but that's another game that's fun just to play and just
Chill and hang out and just talk about random shit. So you'll see it again. I'll do more of the series
Because those games are really fun
Just not right now probably not till somewhere in like November or something because all of October is I've got a
Bunch of stuff that's just lined up ready to go
Hey, it's Shanji. Thanks for the thousand bits to end it out here. They say ADHD family represent
Yeah, I mean I got it. I do have it. Yeah, and
It's it can be
It can be a kind of hard to dance around
But you know, whatever do what you gotta do, thank you so much for the thousand bits appreciate it and
You know what that means. We've reached the end to our short trying stream
I'm going to go and take care of myself a little bit
Maybe eat a fig and go do some stuff. I'll see you tomorrow same time
Season the thing begins tomorrow. Have a great rest of your night or afternoon. It's still pretty early
See you later. Good night guys. Somebody's upset about something. Good night