Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some Paranormal.
Now this game is not out yet. This is in beta. Not even clo-
Okay, that like kinda scared me. The furnace just turned on.
Alright, anyways. This is in beta. It has a Kickstarter project. You can go in the link in the description.
And you can go support this guy. You can get this game right now. 30 bucks is gonna get you the beta.
So, you can check that out. That just threw me off my game. Let's just get going.
Let's begin.
So I guess the whole point of this game is you have a camera.
And you need to capture the hauntings, or you need to go walk around the house and film things that are going on.
So let's do this.
Okay. Left mouse to begin.
Enter the haunting in 3, 2, 1.
Oh my god.
Alright. So let's just start looking around.
Little doll. Hello!
I have a- What's opening?
What door is opening right now?
If there's monsters in this game, like if these little things come alive and start attacking me or something, I'm gonna flip out.
It's a kitchen.
So like I said, this has a Kickstarter project.
It's got a lot of money raised so far. It's actually pretty interesting.
Ah!
Oh, that's not so bad.
It's-
God!
That was the biggest scare so far out of any game I've played. That's a horror game.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What is that thing? What is that guy over there?
Is that guy gonna attack me?
Oh, come on. No way. What am I, stuck in the kitchen?
Turn this off.
Oh, my arm hurts right now from that scare.
What is making that buzzing like a- I feel like my phone is vibrating.
Like, seriously.
Stop it!
Can I go up here?
That, seriously, that noise needs to-
I'm gonna freak out.
Let's go upstairs.
Up the stairs we go.
To try and find the vibrating cell phone.
Oh, thanks.
Whoever's doing that.
Bedroom. Okay, so I have to sleep.
Hi, Fit!
Did I just- Did I just take-
I didn't close that door.
Hey.
So, I'm assuming it's a new day. Camera is charged.
My fish are gone. Somebody stole them.
Which, that's just fantastic.
Get-
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Close the door! Close the door!
Oh, damn.
Somebody was- Why am I not in the reflection?
That doesn't make any sense.
Dude, the beaver- Dude, somebody had a bad case of burritos.
I'll tell you that right now. That's not cool.
What kind of bathroom is this, by the way?
This guy has like a forest in his bathroom.
Painting in the bloody-
That's weird.
Do I even want to open this door?
Is there gonna be like a dude here with like a-
Okay.
Let's go back downstairs.
Let's film some more happenings.
You little-
I'm gonna kick him down.
There's the phone again.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
God!
I'm running. I'm run, run, run, run, run, run.
Run down the stairs. Run down the stairs.
Why can't I move? I can't move.
I can't move right now.
What is that?
They're all-
I was just stuck.
God, come on!
Where's the-
Alright, I'm gonna find that damn phone,
and I'm gonna turn it off, and I'm gonna throw it.
There it is! There it is! There's the phone.
There's the phone.
I don't, like, answer the phone?
Is that a dog?
The phone didn't do anything.
What the hell?
At least I turned it off.
Alright, now I turned off that.
What's going on?
God damn!
I'm outta here.
I'm-
I'm getting the hell outta here.
Can I, like, leave the house?
Alright, I've done. I finished. I got all I needed.
I recorded the monsters and the noises.
Ugh.
Let's, uh-
Let's call that- I can't do it anymore.
My brain is like-
Okay, that guy was not there before.
I'll see you guys all next time,
and go check this game out.
It is the-
It's got a Kickstarter project, like I said before.
And, yeah, that's gonna wrap it up.
First, we're gonna look outside, and yeah!
I thought that was a, uh-
What is that?
It's gone.
Alright, so take care, everybody.
I'll see you all soon.
Run away from this house!
Rest in peace, boy.
What?