Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with an outdoor vlog. I've never done one
of these before, but look, you want to see? I'm really outside. I know, right? It's crazy.
A nerd like me going outside. Yeah, right. But I wanted to make this video because obviously
it's beautiful outside. It's kind of late, but it was beautiful outside earlier. But
I wanted to make this video to give a couple of updates on certain things because I get
asked these questions a lot of times. So, Grandpa. Grandpa is coming back to Machinima
Respawn next month. There's going to be a trailer for Grandpa next week, I think, for
season two. So if you're wondering, Jerma, where did Grandpa go? How come there's been
no Grandpa for like five weeks on Machinima Respawn? It's because it was taken into an
off season and it's coming back. Don't worry. So, May, look for Grandpa. Oh my God, a bug
just landed on me. Bug bastards. So look for Grandpa in May on Machinima Respawn. And I'm
working on it right now. It's going to be ridiculous. So the second thing is a lot of
wind right now. Hopefully it's not ruining this entire footage. But the second thing
is going to be about my server, my Team Fortress 2 server. And I bought it. It's all set up.
It's all ready to go. But I want to talk to somebody that knows about servers. I have
an appointment with Shibby2142. He knows what he's talking about. So before I make the server
public and the server live and all that stuff, I want to make sure it's good to go and I
have all the settings as good as I can possibly have them. So stay tuned. I'll make another
video. I'll mention it in another video. But yes, the server is coming along one week from
today. It should be live. That's my prediction. Otto, what are you doing? My dog is running
around in circles around the yard. And speaking of Otto, I don't know if you can hear that,
but speaking of Otto, a lot of people have asked this. They want to see more Otto. If
you don't know, Otto is my little dog, my little Doxen Doberman Chihuahua thing that
I got like a month ago. And I showed him in one video and that was all it took. Everyone
loves Otto. They want to see him. So okay, here you go. Oh God, he's coming to get me.
Come on. What do you got? What do you got? That's my shoe. You are a freak. Look at
that face. Oh my God. What? Oh, I'm going to pick up this stick that's like 10 times
bigger than my body. This is actually going to work. What an idiot. Hey, don't eat that.
So thank you all so much for watching. I really do. It's cold out. My lips are like all numb.
So like talking is like, but thank you guys so much for watching. I really do appreciate
it. And I will see you guys all next time. So peace, love, and take care everybody. Otto!