I remember yesterday. I remember yesterday. Remember when I said yesterday that, you know,
I really want to start at around like three o'clock. It is the exact same time that I started yesterday's
stream. 3 50 p.m pacific time. The exact same time. All right, but new schedule.
3 50 p.m pacific. Apparently is how that has to be. No, the reason why we started later today
is because I gave Chad a choice either in on time stream at three or delay a little
and instead of Dragon's Dogma set up the insane Dark Souls 3 mods and that's what I did.
So tonight we're going to go through a handful about five to ten and I don't maybe we'll have
them on the same time. Maybe we won't. Maybe I'll just try to beat the game in first person.
There are a few that are on this list here, but first things first, we're going to try to beat
no and not. Don't say that. That's a complete lie. We are going to play Dark Souls 3 in first
person. It's a first person mod for the game. We are going to beat Dark Souls 3 and no,
I'll be lucky to get out of the tutorial zone. Am I going to suck at this game? I,
if you're a new viewer, I have beat Dark Souls 3 on stream twice. It's a running
gag on the channel apparently. I streamed all of Dark Souls 3 when it first came out.
Had a great time. Uh, so level 75 by the way. Give me a minute. I'll be right back.
You know, uh, just make sure this actually loads correctly and I will see you guys in a
minute. Okay, so here we are. Dark Souls 3. Everything looks pretty normal. All right,
what if I was just lying to you guys and I actually just loaded up Dark Souls 3
and I'm just going to play Dark Souls 3 again? That would be pretty dumb, actually,
because I already did it. I streamed this game like 12 times, so that would probably be,
I don't know if I'd want to do that. New game. Oh, yes. Whatever. All right,
let's get a character here. So for the purposes of first person mode,
I think we have to have a very heavy character. Dodge rolling might become impossible. I'm going
to need to be able to take hits. A lot of them. We're going to do shield. I'm getting
the biggest fucking shield in the game and I'm going to hold it up the whole time. So
let's get a good name here for somebody that's not going to dodge roll, that's going to eat
hits. No, not poop master. We got like a poop out of our system last night. And I mean,
in other ways too. I'm sure a lot of you did. Just name him The Wall. No, what? Aimless Dickhead.
How about, no, I'm not going to name him another meme. That's not how it works.
Somebody said, oh my god, I have homework to do. No, that's not funny.
Do I really have to name this character homework? How about homework? I'm not going
to name him be homework Simpson. No, no, no. How about, all right, I got one. I got one. This
is going to be it. No matter what it is, I don't care if I don't like it. How about that? That's
the best kind of good. The hiccups. I hate it. Don't you hate it when you get fucking hiccups
when you're doing your homework? Okay, this is important. Class. I need a shitload of endurance.
Who has the highest endurance base? It's the warrior. Warrior has the highest base endurance.
Why the? I mean, I guess I could. Deprived. This is first person mode, guys. So, no, no,
it's, wait, I haven't played Dark Souls 3 in a while. Is it, is, is Vigor weight or is
endurance weight? They all put weight up, don't they? Oh, no, that's resist, that's
resistance. Vigor is health. So just, I'm going to do, okay, that's not a bad idea. Do this and
just dump every point into endurance strength and HP. Vitality is weight. Oh, right, right. Okay,
okay, okay. Well, there we go. Knight. It's definitely going to be knight. Just making an
FPS. Knight's probably the best pick. I mean, yes, I understand. This is like what everybody
does. I didn't pick this when I first played, but I'm playing, I'm doing something very
specific. We're doing knight. He already starts with heavy armor. He's going to shield already.
Guys, I might not even make it past the third enemy of the game. All right, we're going to go
with, what do we want here? Probably the life ring. Appearance. This doesn't matter. Okay,
that's fine. Everyone's doing the resident sleeper for knight. Okay, but look at all
that vitality. It's got to be knight. Look, I don't have to be the actual knight,
but I need a shield right now. Let's go. Now, this might take a little bit of tweaking
because I tried to make it correct. We're going to see how bad this looks. Is this
your first Dark Souls? This is my first ever playthrough of Dark Souls. Already off the
bat, I feel more comfortable because I have shield. Nice arms. Dude, it's like a VR game.
Come on. This is going to be so hard. I could already tell. Roll. Ooh, you actually can dodge
roll. I'm not going to use it though because how the fuck am I going to dodge roll? I don't
even know. I, where, okay, first enemy. Can I, can you lock on? Oh, you can't lock on. I
don't know what direction I'm facing. This is going to be so terrifying. All right, we're
going to go this way. Easy. Yeah, as you say that now, but I can't lock on to enemies.
I'm going to have to play the whole game without locking on. Well, first item. Yeah,
this is actually really, really fucking cool. This changes the whole game. It's a controller
for an FP. I forgot about that guy. Oh, what? Oh my God. Parry or bad. Just let me take in
the world for a second. This is my first time ever playing Dark Souls. Parry or bad.
It's so different seeing it from this angle. Oh my God. It's so hard. I can't do it.
No, don't die at the fucking tutorial enemy. Seeing it from a different perspective.
This changes everything. I'm not, I'm going to have to relearn how to play the whole game.
Space is an issue too because I don't have to get that close. I'm getting way too close
than I need to. Did I miss any items? I think so. There's people over here. Let me see the
space, the distance here. Look at that. Oh my God. Got it. Control, wait, yeah, I can't use
the mouse. Don't you, you know what I mean? There is no mouse control. I have to be, it's
got to be console FPS for the very specific reason that the mouse does not do the thing that
you want it to do. The motion blur is fucking my mind. Hold on. Wait, is that,
is that an option I can turn off? All right, I'm going to turn it off. Motion blur off.
That's better. Turn depth of field off too. Yeah, that's true because it doesn't matter
because depth of field. Yeah, that's true. Depth of field off. Motion blur off.
Water surface quality high. Yeah, that's much better. This is what I want Skyrim to be is
this. The fucking view. Turn RTX on. I don't even, I don't want to sprint. I feel like
I'm going to have to play through this whole thing with whatever we do tonight. Not sprinting.
Can you turn arms on in the settings? There is an option to toggle like wrists, toggle hands,
toggle shield, but I like it like this because it gives space to my character.
You can turn off all these things, but I need them on. Yeah, you can toggle off the wrists,
but I like it. I like how it looks. It reminds me of like I'm actually playing
a first person game. This is trying to parry. What? What's happening? Oh, I know it's happening.
I know it's happening because I need to be facing a very specific direction
because if I try to parry a guy that's, okay, so if I'm standing like this,
the parry is going to work this way, right? But if I take a look at an enemy over here,
no, no, that's not going to work. You have to be straight in front of somebody.
Tweet that the stream is live? Oh, fuck, hold on. Yeah, just look at fucking Anor Londo over there.
Is rolling in first person vomit inducing? It is not because it does not move your head.
The camera doesn't move. I'm going to just like tweet that. I'll be surprised if I could
beat the first boss here. It's going to take like an hour. We're going to do it. All right,
let's go. Now that looks ugly. That looks so cool, but the shield really is ruining it.
Oh, man. Oh, it's, it's, it is so hard to parry in first person. You just, it's like nothing
you've ever seen before. No, I have to learn. I have to learn how to do it.
I'm not even facing the right direction. Use of mouse. That doesn't, the mouse isn't going to
do. Oh my God. Wait a minute. Is it? No, I can't use the mouse. See? No, that's hell.
That looks horrible. All right, forget about parrying for now. Let's just move on. I'll
learn it eventually. I love and hate this at the same time. I love this more than I hate this stuff,
so that it's good. I like it. It's actually really fucking cool. All right, I remember this
part. I gotta jump to this. Oh my goodness. I didn't make it. Yeah, get out of my way.
Yeah, locking on doesn't do very much either.
Because once you lock on, if you step in a certain direction, it doesn't lock on anymore.
Let me go get that item. Beat the boss first try. I'm going to go for it. I can't
promise it's going to happen, but I'm going to, I'm going to try. Oh God damn it. Attempt number
three to jump, to jump to item. Okay, I got it. Get my first shot. All right, let's go,
Gundyr. I am prepared, but not really at all. It's scary like this. Do I have to be a
role player? So I cast up the sword from your chest. Champion of Gundyr. Oh my goodness,
gracious. It's mind blowing. This is insane. I don't even know where I am. If I get him to
phase two, I'll be happy. Oh, I just can't tell where I am. Maybe I should just bring
his shield out. Oh fuck. Oh my God. He turns into an alien. Oh, it was a decent first
attempt. Died to Gundyr. Yeah, I did. And I'm proud of it. Let me try the shield this time.
That's how I was going to do it before. I'm going to try shield. Let's try blocking and
dodging because dodging is going to be very hard. I'm just going to hold my hand in the
air like this. All right, let's go. What's wrong with his body? What happened? Why does
he have an extra limb? He gained a limb. Oh, I'm facing the wrong way. Okay, now I am.
Oh, not this shit. This is so scary. This is worse than a horror game. I swear to God.
Jesus. Oh my God. This is worse than anything. Oh my God. This is too scary. Nice YouTuber
reaction. I'll get it. I'll get it. I got it. I got it. I got it. This is the coolest
mod ever. You know why? Because it doesn't matter how many times you've played this game.
This is probably character number like 15 for me. It doesn't matter. Something ain't
right here. Something ain't right. He's still like the puppet thing.
Okay, I guess we're going to deal with it. What happens when he turns on his puppet
master thing? I can see him attack now. This is not good. The assets aren't resetting when
he dies. Oh, that's not good. You almost have to go by audio cues for a lot of these things.
Oh, there we go. Okay. Oh shit. Oh my God. Oh, don't do it. Don't do it. Oh, that's intense.
I like this. Yeah, we got to think about weapon. What the hell I want to use for a weapon.
You're going to hate it in an hour or so. Oh, I'm aware. This is going to be fun for like
an hour. Use a face cam. I can't put a face cam on. Dual wield ultra greatswords or riot.
I need something that's got good. I don't know. Reach. All right. Can somebody count
the YouTuber screams that I make over the course of the stream? I need depth. A homeward
bone. Here comes the fall off joke. No, no, no. That's going to happen, but not right now.
Face cam or ice cream. You're going to have to eat ice cream. I'm sorry.
Yeah. Here's a fall off joke for you. Everybody does this to this guy.
Yeah. Now the shot just, can I think? No, no way. I'm going to fight that guy up there.
Get a Katana. I can't go that way. Fight the Katana guy. I have to parry the Katana guy.
And we've seen how disastrous that is. I need to let me, I got to level up first.
I almost just killed her. Everybody knows this. All right. What the hell do I want to do? How
am I going to play this? Just dump it into endurance at first. Or should I just dump it
into vitality? Dex. Yeah. Dex is probably a good idea. Cause I could use a bow, but the bow
doesn't bow go into first person anyways. Luck. There's no reason to do luck unless I want to
get a specific scaling item or. Well, we definitely need, our endurance is terrible right now. So
let me just get this out of the way. Okay. You really get to see the scale of how the
game actually is. This hallway seems so far away. The blacksmith is so far away. When you play this
game from the normal perspective, it's just like, oh, there he is. How you doing? This is a long
walk. All right. Let me go try to embarrass myself at the Katana guy. The shield is so
annoying. I know, but the shield might become very necessary as in like right now.
No, he's, I can't do anything with him, right? I got to get the soul thing from the tree.
It really makes it feel like Dark Souls.
All right. Let's go try to lose to the Katana guy. Just dump it into endurance. And I'm
going to just do like a raw gem. Somebody mentioned that. That's a good idea. All right.
Where is he? Come on. Parry first try. One, two, three. I just like let him kill me. All right.
All right. Back to it. Oh wait. That's right. I can't do it now. I locked myself out for a
little while, didn't I? Come on, load. I'm going to get this sword. Welcome to the next
Farby. At least five minutes of the spring because that's all it's going to take me.
Off the stairs. Come on.
I wasn't ready for that one. Oh shit. That's all off now. I don't even know where I am.
I can't parry somebody on a staircase. Get these people out of the way.
You dickhead. I'm going to lose again. No, I just get the people on the stairs.
This is like the bodies on the stairs in first person. It's so much worse.
I would have had it too if I didn't because they take up so much more real estate on your
screen when you're at this perspective. Get me in there. I'm doing it. He needed one hit too.
Fucking god. Increase the FOV. I don't know if it's possible. I might throw up if I do
because this is already at... I think this is already at something very high.
All right. Just don't move. Just do what I just did. I just did it like four times
in a row. I just panicked because he did a quick swing. What was wrong with that?
He's still hitting me. I gotta heal. Fucker. I didn't even know how close he was.
I think there's a wall behind me. Wait. Hold on. I'll get him. Get the fuck out of my way.
I don't think I've ever seen what that guy looks like.
All right. I'm gonna do this one more time. Last try. Last try and this time I'm gonna...
I'm just gonna fight him the old-fashioned way. Parrys are weird. Let's go. Oh never mind.
That's too hard. Need to control this camera with right stick. Oh no way.
How's he still alive? Oh okay. Why don't we exit the game. Modern problems require
modern solution. Okay. I get this rest of the bonfire, right? Did I miss any other items?
I know there's like a dog down here, right? There's like a place to get. Yeah. Right here.
Is there an item? Oh fuck it. Who cares? I've already played this game like a thousand times.
So I... resting at the bonfire will do the same thing, won't it? I actually need to like
quit the game. Gotta reload. Okay. Bonfire. Bonfire. Bonfire. Chat. Bonfire will work.
Let's see. Yeah. It's right there. All right. So do I... do I put this on? Is the question.
Dark Souls 1 is the... is where you have to reload. Yeah. All right. Let's move on.
I have enough to level up. I'm gonna do endurance again. Or maybe vitality.
What do I need here? Yeah.
All right. It's time to... let me see what that looks like.
I played with this. You need 16. 115. I can't even... can I... I can't even two-handed or anything, right?
I can. Let's... this is... I think... I got the master's armor, right?
No. I don't want this shit on. I need the defense.
Two-handed dex weapon. What? You two-hand the katana. What's wrong with that?
All right. I'm going. Lego island confirmed. What do you mean Lego island confirmed?
This is not a YouTuber... this is not a YouTuber setup. I mean, yes, it is probably. They always
probably pick night, don't they? See, this is the part I'm interested in here. I want to see how
this looks from first person. It's gonna be so cool. Remember when you first looked at this?
When you first played this game two years ago? That's so cool. Even the boxes look better.
I don't want to rush through this. It's too interesting to just run by the bonfire and
go. It's a pretty good E3 demo you're doing. E3 presentation camera. So?
At the high wall of Lothric, your character will start their journey. But be careful.
Dragons and ghouls are amount. Each character in Dark Souls 3 is unique.
Fuck. That happens in the presentation. Fired. Oh no, that guy. I gotta kill that guy.
This is what the shield is for. I'm gonna have... I'm gonna shit my pants during the stream.
I think this is the correct way to do it. I need a big shield and I'm gonna be heavy.
It's too scary to dodge around. No, let's go up here first. Oh god. The default enemies
are even terrifying. Jesus. I don't even know. My back is against the wall.
Fuck. How fast do I run? I gotta keep going. Just progression. Progress up to where that
guy's throwing from. Chat. No, chat. What's going on with chat? What is this? Dermot turns
his webcam on. Dermot turns it on blinking. His eyes begin to slowly wrap into the
Dark Souls audio in the background against the increasing volume. Why is that going on
right now? What does that have to do with anything? Three hits for everyone. Longsword.
This one's new so it's better. Got the binoculars. I'm gonna get lost. I used to
know this area like the back of my hand. Not anymore. Use them? Ah. Let's use them.
What are we gonna look at? Up there? That's it. All that's left is remove my shield and
sword. The only thing I don't like about the visuals is the beige. It is a little
dreary here, but we're not supposed to be seeing it from this perspective. This is not
allowed. You're supposed to be up above, up like there, in like a third person
perspective. It is very interesting to go through this all again though. So, locking on.
I wonder if locking on... Wow. My brain just can't do it from here.
It's never gonna happen. It's just too awkward. I did it like perfectly fine,
like four times in a row, but no, I ain't gonna have them reliably.
All right, now that I explored that area, I'm gonna go refill my life.
2018 Jerma is better than 2019 Jerma? We've had like two weeks!
That's such an unfair statement. You have a full year of streams that you can remember.
It's been two weeks! Oh my fucking god, I'm gonna die. Okay, here we go. It's easier
to be surrounded by enemies. I'll be lucky enough if I get to, uh, the big bulldog.
Where his name is. Bulldog of the boreal valley. Bort? What's his name? This is,
this is what I waited for the whole time. This is what I wanted to see.
Get out of the way. You're gonna ruin the fucking shot. Get out of my way.
You're gonna ruin the shot! Get out of the way! You don't ruin the shot.
Here it comes, here it comes. Where is it? Where's the dragon?
I'm not gonna go up. E3 scripted moment. That's just level.
Ow. No, I forgot about these guys. Get those arrows out. Oh. How do I take the arrow out?
Do they just, it's just in my chest. I'm gonna lose to these guys. This is gonna be bad.
Ohhhhh. I'm gonna get surrounded here. They like, crawl up. Yeah, they crawl up, right?
How did I miss every one of those? How's that possible?
I swung in every single direction. So we gotta go through here. I remember this part.
Don't call me a game journalist.
And who cares? I really should just retitle this stream. Dark Souls,
Dark Souls 3. The E3 experience. That's not a bad idea. Oh, a bonfire! Good find.
Open the mimic so we can see the first person. I'm not reading that.
You're gonna have to find somebody else to read that one. It ain't gonna be me.
It's funny because when I first installed this and I thought, hey, this would be,
so this would be fun to do for a little bit. I actually did not think I would get to this point.
So we're gonna beat, uh, Bort of the, of the Boreal Battlet. We're gonna beat that dog.
I'm gonna beat that boss. What's down here? I forget.
I tell you, isn't there like little, like, jester guys down here too?
There are. There is. No? It's so cool that you can actually see where they're
placing the enemies. It makes it harder, but it also makes it easier in some rooms.
Yeah, that's undead settlement. Yeah. Wrong place. What do I hear noises?
Can I want to try this with a bow? That would be interesting, but
when you go to bow, you go to first person anyways, don't you?
Although I guess it would be, maybe we should just see what it looks like.
How bad do these people smell? Oh, I get it. Okay. First person. For a second,
I'm like, what are you talking about? I remember this part. Okay. All right,
all right, all right, all right. I got to kill the guy right in the middle.
Go get him. Which one is it? Which one is he? This one right here.
I didn't do it fast enough. Oh, no, no, no way. No way. Not gonna happen. No way.
No way. Where's, how about, okay, there's a wall. Go, go, go, go, go.
I didn't do it fast enough. Shit. Oh well.
Does he come over here? This is not a, this is not a coward move. Okay.
This is intelligence at its finest. I ain't gonna fight that guy like that.
And for these guys, those guys attack every quarter of a second.
I would get eaten alive. Wait, I can hear it. Is it weird that my other senses are better
in first person? I can hear that cookie bug from a mile away here.
I can hear better. It's making my other senses.
Told you. Look. Cookie bug is the raw gem. That's all I need. That's so cool.
I am gonna stop and look at all that every time. You know how sometimes you ask yourself
when you fall from a height in Dark Souls? I know I wasn't even that far.
I could survive that. No, you couldn't. Looking at this now from this perspective?
No way. You're dead instantly. Now I, I need to get this shortcut, which is down here.
There's also, oh shit. Didn't they have the spear in there?
Forget about items and shit. I need to just get a shortcut.
Yeah, they come from behind too, don't they? Coward journalist.
Is this a new character that you, that we're making up here, that you guys are making up?
Okay. I think it might be time for a weapon switch because the,
there's a chance that this guy drops the halberd, right?
Or do I just run by this guy and say fuck it and don't even try?
It's down here, right? There's something, there's a weapon here. What is it? No.
Does he see me? Will he see me if I sit here? What the fuck was that noise?
What? Oh, it was just a scripted event. Anything else I can,
I don't think I should fight this guy right now. He's going to kick the shit out of me.
Just bury him. That's way easier said than done.
Ember. Anything else? Yeah, I'm getting the shortcut.
No way in hell am I going to get my ass kicked right here. I have to get the shortcut
first. If I would have died there, I would have been very sad. Yeah, I got the,
I got the weapon. But I, honestly, this is just horror Skyrim. This is just,
this is Skyrim with consequences. Okay, we're good.
The gaming journalist nearly has a heart attack playing New Souls game.
You get swarmed here. Get on the elevator.
These near death elevator moments are going to be fucking scary.
There it is. All right, we're good. Oh shit, I'm out of stamina.
What? How did you do that? What's happening to me?
Get behind, right? Roll into a backstab. Oh, I'm freaking out. I'm panicking.
Do I live next to an airport? All right, we did it. We got the shortcut.
Now we just have to kill the boss. All right, so I can level up.
This is decision time though. This really matters. Choices, my choices actually matter
right now. For real. Because I don't know what's going to be more effective in first person.
Long reach, heavy, quick, and able to move. A spear, a spear would work. Use the broken sword.
That would be so stupid. I would also probably, I would say spear as well.
Why would I use the broken? This is not one of those challenge games
where I need to use no weapons or not get hit or something. Those, that,
respect to the people that do that and play that. It can do that.
I ain't gonna two-handed broken sword this game. No, what am I doing? I have to level up.
I don't know what to do. There's so many options. I mean, I could just raw gem a long
sword. Let me just open the, let's break these all. Maybe I will try just, in quotes, spear.
Long sword with raw gem is 136. It's really not that big of a deal.
You don't have a spear, do you? I mean, that's a halberd, but that's not necessarily a spear.
I mean, it is. 1500, I need 16 strength. The halberd is dog shit. All right. It really,
I, I know, but I need the reach. I'm going to use the halberd.
We're gonna, we're gonna think outside the fucking box. But first, two-handing a long
sword has the reach that you need. It's probably gonna have to do strength.
What is a spear? A spear's decks are strong. They're like a combination of both, aren't they?
Aren't most of the spears in the game have a base dexterity you need of at least like 15 to
20? So then I should probably be putting points into dexterity. Why is she just talking in the
background? I know I do. I don't understand. Yeah, I'm going to, I'm going for spears.
So we're going to do decks. I don't want to do a halberd.
You also talk in the background. Yeah, that's true. I do.
She, she can't tell that I left. The fire keeper is streaming right now. Yeah. She's
streaming just chatting. All right. I'm going for it. 14 decks. I need at least like 20,
or like 18 for a lot of the spears. Plus two reading off chat. I guess I could probably
do it a couple more times. Just break them all. Just give me one more point, right?
Put it into like endurance. Yeah, put it in health.
Okay, and no, let's just try to kill the boss.
This is Jeremy's first time playing Dark Souls, so don't forget to type in all your helpful tips.
Up the FOV. I can't. We're currently at over a hundred, I believe. Let me just see exactly
what FOV we are right now. FOV is at, I don't know if I can change it. No, I'm not sure
I can change this. It might crash the game if I try to change it. Because if the FOV
has changed any more than it is now, you'll probably be able to see by the end of the
yeah, behind me. It'll fuck up the whole thing. All right, let's go. So I got the
shortcut. I have to go down from here, right? I'm so fucking, I am so
de-sotarente, you know what I mean? There it is. That's so scary. No. What's going on?
Oh my fucking god. Why is this on? 10, 22. I mean, let's put it on.
What the fuck did I just do? What's going on? There we go. Now we just got good. Now we got
real good. I can poke from behind the shield. I love it. It's perfect. Don't get overzealous
with yourself. I've already used two flasks. All right, now let's fight the dragon. And by
dragon, I mean the dragon rider, the dragon slayer, this guy. I don't even know what
mode I'm in right now. Am I in? I blame that on the broken sword bullshit. It's okay. Pro tip,
don't panic and run past the spinning death axe. Well, it's easier said than done.
That's easier said than done. Oh, it's not up here. Oh, no. I have to do this.
Where is he? Okay, he's dead. Oh, I don't have it behind me enough. Wait, there's a weapon
over here. There's a spear over here. There's a spear somewhere over here. Let me get it
because that would help. I'm gonna have to just run, get the item, and then run to the
boss. It's up there, right? The high tower of Lothric. There it is. I'm trapped. I'm trapped.
I gotta run. How much is it to wear this? I need 15 strength. I could two-hand it, but
I lose the shield. Let's take a look. Hold on. This just looks like Grandpa's cane.
I'm gonna give it a try. How many times can I spin? I need to take the shield off because
it's gonna get in the way. All right, here we go. What's cousin it? No, what's the hand?
What's the hand from Adam's family? The thing. No, not the thing. No, it's not master
hand. Mr. Hands. No, cousin hands. See if I can first strike. This is the first real test.
This is incredibly medicine. Can I do it? He's getting closer. He's getting closer. Hold on.
I got it. Whoa! Okay, no, he does like a dash, right? Yeah, he does the dash.
I need to heal. Shit. Bad, bad, bad, very bad. It was right in front of me.
Oh, I'm stuck inside of his body. Where is he? Oh, no, no, no, no. This is where he dashes.
He breathes ice. He breathes ice. Run! I have to go to the left side, but it didn't happen.
It's wild. This is absolutely wild. Oh, shit. What have I done?
Whoa! I'm so scared. Itchy nose. Itchy fucking nose right now. Itchy nose. I have to itch it.
Die, die, die, die, die, die! Got it. Oh, itchy. Thank God. That was bad. It got really,
really itchy. That was like fighting him for the first time again. And although I
obviously remember the moves he does, but. Oh, we had a raid coming? Raid. I don't see who
it was. Now fight the dancer. This is so cool. Oh, it was a joke raid. It wasn't a real raid. It
was a joke raid. I gotta get the banner. No, it was real. Who raided? Why are you guys telling
me it wasn't real? Oh, everyone's saying it was not real. From Katie. Well, thank you, Katie.
Welcome. I thought it was fake. Everyone told me that it was fake. I'm sorry to call you
fake. We've had fake raids before. People, there are characters in this universe.
But thank you so much. Welcome, everybody. Hopefully you had a good stream. Really
appreciate it. Thank you. Welcome to Dark Souls First Person. It's a pretty fun fucking game.
That was a pretty good YouTuber intro. God, I gotta welcome the new viewers, man.
Hey, what's going on, guys? Welcome to the stream. Just had a WTF moment there.
I beat Bort first try. Yeah, I'm leaving. Oh, damn it. I'm sorry. Do you think I can fight the
legendary holy man over there? Can't do two. I cannot do two. I can do one. Definitely not
two at a time. I'm trying to get a backstab. Sometimes you gotta run, and that's right now.
I just want to get the item. I can do a GTA rear view mirror. Oh, fuck off. Ah,
the wait has been long. I am Emma, priestess. You will not find the Lords of Cinder here. They
have left to their journey homes converging at the base of this castle. Quick, say something
funny before they leave. I don't got anything funny. I have nothing funny to say right now.
I don't know. What's something funny that I could say to keep them here?
Kill her. Why would I do that? That's not funny. That just ruins the game.
That ruins the video game. I'm not going to ruin the video game. I got the item and I'm going to
what's up here? This is a guy. He's guarding an item, right? No, he's not. He's just hard.
We're in desperate need of an LUL moment. Well, you're not getting any LUL moments because
the streamer is doing pretty good in the first person. LOL. No way he's going to be
able to beat anything in first person. LOL stream. I'm doing pretty good considering.
Hey, uh, wave, uh, bye bye. Hehehe. Fucking idiot. Fucking idiot. Fucking idiot.
Hey guy, guys, put your hand up. Wave. Bye bye. Why is it a trunk impression?
Get the fuck away from me. Holy shit. Get away from me. They're still alive.
No, don't die here. Don't die. I'm right next to the fucking bonfire.
Oh, just travel there. I forgot. I played too much Dark Souls 1. I can actually,
I can just teleport to it. Does the targeting know? Targeting works, but it kind of breaks.
Targeting only works if they're in like a pretty much like a 60 degree cone in front of you
because it doesn't turn the camera to face the person. So if they're in this kind of area,
let's, I'll give you an example here. So this is point A. This is point B. Chair is
point B. If they're in this, that cone, right? That's a foul ball over there.
If I move this way, yeah, sure. If I move this way, yeah, sure.
But if I go like this, the camera does not keep turning. What's the, uh, what does frost dog
have for a boss soul weapon? It's like a, it's like an ice sword, right? The thing's a
piece of fucking shit. So I ain't gonna use it. I don't get the joke. That wasn't a joke.
I was giving, I was telling you how, how it is with targeting. I didn't get it until you put
it into baseball terms. See? The ice mace is good. Okay, but we're going spear. Welcome,
host. Very well, then taken. All right, what do I get endurance to 15? I don't have to
worry about it. Farewell, Ashen One. Okay, should I upgrade? I'm gonna just upgrade this
thing. Sorcery would be good because you can, uh, spacing doesn't matter. Depth doesn't matter.
Yeah, that's true. Uh, should I get this to, I mean, you get tight knight shards, or diamond
doesn't. So I'm just gonna upgrade it once. Or 56, 156 versus what would it be? 38. No,
it's not worth it. Just get an actual spear. I'm not going to kill anybody. I'm not killing
any NPCs. Let's do long sword quality build. I want to stab though. All right, so we're
gonna go back to theirs, put the banner down. I, there are other mods that I have, but
I kind of like this. This is fun. Should we try another one? The invisible van. He's naked.
All he has is two gloves on. Yeah, I have, uh, some other ones. Okay, here's the thing,
though. If I turn on the other ones, it will actually ruin the entire game. Now,
I'm going to get my fill of first person mod before I turn on the randomize the speed
of the game mod. Do you understand? No, I can't. Look, do you see how beautiful this is?
Do them both at the same time. I wouldn't get anything done. Wait a second. Hey,
what's going on guys? No, this is just a reaction to the reaction.
That was just a reaction. Hold on. Is there a voiceover on this one?
One is that we've incorporated kind of things that are going on around you in
the community into the world map itself. So it's a really natural.
Okay, let's go. When you and I were talking a little bit earlier, you were talking about
ways that a player who maybe doesn't have a big pool of friends online or, or isn't super
social when it comes to online gaming, how they can connect with other players in the
world in Anthem. Can you talk a little bit about how me, when I jump into Anthem,
when it comes out, how I'm going to find other players and how the game is going
to alert me that other things are happening? Sure. I love that. So we realized that sometimes
multiplayer experiences can be a little bit awkward or it might be kind of difficult
to find other friends to play with. So we've done a couple of things to try to ease that
experience out. One is that we've incorporated kind of things that are going on around you
in the community into the world map itself. So it's a really natural action. Open up
your world map. And on that world map, you're going to see what other people are doing
too. So if someone else is playing scars and villainy and you want to jump in and play
that mission to just right there on the map, click into it, join their game in progress
and have a great time. Nevermind.
This one's going to be good. I promise. Yeah, this is going to be good. Here we go.
Yeah, this is great. I got my own little TV. This is perfect. Adam's doing a fantastic job
so far. It's been really good. First of all, you're actually playing this right now.
I do want to emphasize how beautiful this game is. Oh, thank you. Brian, tell me
a little bit about what you guys want to show us this evening. So I think, I mean,
the big thing is, again, I think that part of the Spider-Man fantasy is to swing around
New York City and to have not only just a great story but have a bunch of different
activities in that world and we want to, you know, give people who attend E3 an
opportunity to experience that. So, you know, obviously we, it's a big narrative
driven experience, but same time, part of that superhero fantasy, especially that
Spider-Man experience is living within New York City and seeing that. So, you
know, Adam is one of, he's one of our combat pro players because he's a
combat designer and... That one wasn't very good. I was going to try to do it like I'm
swinging around. I didn't use the web. I didn't activate the web. 2000 IQ joke.
That wasn't supposed to be a fall joke. All right, I just get to the bonfire. What am I
doing? I don't want to ruin, I didn't ruin the game yet. I just, I didn't turn any
mods off. Okay. Oh, I can't touch the boss. Let's keep going. Can we just play
Dark Souls 3? I mean, that's kind of what I'm doing right now. Just in a different
perspective. I actually like this weapon. I do enjoy this weapon. A shield is
going to be so desperate here, though, because there's random enemies around
corners. I'm going to get fucking destroyed. Well, this is the parry
shield. Well, not really, but one of them. This is going to be hell. This
room is going to be hell. That's so cool. Cut this guy down.
All right. Is this VR? That would be insane if this was VR. VR would make this
game absolutely horrifying. And speaking of horrifying, I knew you were going to
show up. We've made it into E mode only mode. What happened? Was chat
misbehaving? Were they misbehaving? I can see them, though. So this is
fine. You can't sneak up on me. Little shit. Some of these come alive,
don't they? What happened? Why is chat in timeout right now? Don't ask me why I
did this. I guess it's free souls. You know what? I think I might get a
glass of wine. This is a wine night? Is it possible? Oh shit.
Don't look at it. Just dodge it. Oh my god. It just went through. It went
through his body. It went through his body. I couldn't see it. First person.
That's five community subs from Kazzy. Thank you, Kazzy. Thank you so much, Kazzy.
Five community subs. You rock. Thank you. Congratulations to those in the
community that can now do the Jerma Boomer Emo.
And you don't want to use that Emo anytime Jerma says something but he
sounds old. Make sure you put that in the chat so everyone knows what you're
talking about. If Jerma starts talking about the
Super Nintendo, make sure you put that Emo to the chat.
Did Jerma reference an old Nickelodeon cartoon? Make sure you put that in the
chat too. All right. I'm just spamming right now.
RFLSA thanks for the five community subs right back to back there. Thank
you.
Where am I? I was on the ground still.
Don't roll off the edge. What do I got for real estate? Not much.
Not.
Look at the wall. Holy. I buried it right in her head.
Let her hug you. Why would I do that? Let's just use somebody else's flasks for that.
God damn it. I need to go back. I'm just gonna run by this.
Isn't there a shard over here somewhere?
I know there's a Estes Shard somewhere in this area.
It's right there. All right. Let me go upgrade.
Stupid floating hand. Do a pure faith build. I'm not sure that would be a good
idea. Make sure to hydrate. Yeah, yeah. I
gotta get some water or wine. Which one? Water or wine?
That's a good question. Both? I could do both.
Ah. Okay. Five. Why would I kill him?
All right. Let's um... Do I have enough? I'm gonna just crush the...
I'm not gonna use this. I mean it's neat but I'm not gonna use it.
All right. 15-15. Looking at one in the decks.
Oh yeah. Is there any cheaters in here?
Bits got deleted. What do you mean? All right. I'm good.
And you know what? I'm just gonna upgrade this once. What do you think?
I'm gonna save the raw gem. I'm just gonna put
like a... I'm gonna do high five. Who cares?
Pretty be careful. I do. All right. Who's the boss? There's like two
bosses here. That's the tree. Tree's gonna be interesting in
first person. Hey Jerma, can you say yeah? I'm trying to prove something.
Sure.
Was that good enough? No. I can't just sprint through.
It's not gonna happen. Oh my god. He did it.
All right. There's a nest. There's a shard in the first area too.
It's in like the soup pit. Let's just keep going.
Hi. He just fell down and died. Who? Who is it?
Who is it? There's a guy underneath me. What the fuck?
Let's go down. All right. Now it's time to slow it down
and progress. God. Oh, there's people everywhere behind me too I think.
Don't roll off the cliff. Everyone's gonna laugh at you.
Oh. Somebody skipped 20. SkullyP. 20 community subs. Thank you so
much Skully. That's a shit load of money.
20 community subs. I just got double hit. I'm a sub now. A lot of you are subs now.
That's 20. There's the mummies down here, right? And the
the weird like person tentacle thing is here.
All right. Hold on. I gotta back it up. Isn't there an NPC?
New subs. Try. Oh, this is gonna be absolutely fucking awful.
This guy's hard. Ah. Just increases the
fear factor of this game by like at least three or four Joe
Ruggins. Yeah, I know the trick. Charcoal pine
route. Can you even put that on? That has to go on a blade, right?
Warrior of sunlight. Praise the sun. Drink the estus soup. Sure.
Even more community subs coming in from
SeaBear. Five community subs from SeaBear.
Thank you. You guys are just showering me with money.
Sometimes I just don't know what to say, so thank you. This is a legit horror
game. Yeah, it changes the whole landscape.
Every corner is dangerous. Everything is scary.
What does the plus two and minus two mean? Well,
a while ago, like maybe a year ago,
a buddy of mine, Talix and I, we did a thing where
we played a game. We had to beat the game in one sitting and we had
four hours to beat the whole game. It was Kane and Lynch 2.
So, but the stipulation with that was every time we made a really, really good
joke, we got to add time, and every time we made a really bad
joke, we got to, we had time reduced from the time.
Long story short, we did it. I don't want to spoil it because if you
haven't seen it, it's, it was a fun screen.
It's great. Nudity added like, what, subtracted an hour or two?
So, what do you guys think the wall will be here? Where first person
Dark Souls becomes pretty much not complete? What do you think?
What boss am I about to find? I am the wall.
There's no way I will get to Pontiff, but I would think Pontiff would
probably be pretty close. Unless I can parry every move.
This is a challenge though. This is, this, I highly recommend if you are
bored with Dark Souls or Dark Souls 3. I highly recommend you give this a
look because this, this is great. Where is he?
This dude. Oh shit. Oh, this is bad news.
I only have one flask. I have to see what that looks like in first person.
Is this a whip playthrough? It just looks like,
it doesn't even look like you're using a whip. No, put it away. I'm so
close to just being able to get through this.
Just give me my, give me my Lucerne. Whip and then dab on them. If we don't dab
on this shit. I'm down. I forgot. Oh you mother.
Bye bye. We're close. We're very close to just getting the,
I am so scared right now. I hear a cookie bug.
Where's the cookie bug? Yeah, the bonfire is right here.
Sit down. Sit down. Sit down!
So this is uh, it feels like I'm playing chivalry.
I could see that. The weapons seem to have the same weight,
same movement. That's a really good observation. All right,
progression. Although there are some things that I don't want to miss,
but I'm doing just fine. I've since gotten kind of used to the controls
though. Knowing when to, because if you stay
locked on, I still have to tilt right stick to move the camera, but it's
not as bad as it was before. Say that now and I'm about to lose.
No, we're not doing any more. I'm not gonna say it. I'm not even gonna
say it. Did I break up the wine yet? I have not.
Not yet. Somebody tell my roommate to stop snoring. Put me on speaker.
Hey. Hey. Hey, wake up for a second. Wake up for one second.
I mean, I don't want to be rude and I don't mean this in a mean way,
but this you're snoring and I mean it's hard for me to study. I'm
getting it. I got a very very, I got a tough paper due tomorrow
and I've got a math exam also tomorrow as well. So please, if like you could
maybe go to get a glass of water. Like, thanks.
Thank you, man. Really appreciate that. Like, thanks. I mean absolutely no
disrespect or rudeness when I say this. Thank you.
I cherish you as a roommate. You're a really good fucking friend.
Yeah, there you go. What is that? All right, can I see him from here?
He's on top of that building, right? Wow, that's crazy. All right, well we
gotta go. There's a, there's a bone shard
over there. Walked into a gravestone. Report that guy for stream sniping.
If I could, I would. Next mod? No, no, no, no. We, we got a long night. We
gotta, it's only been a couple hours. It's a long night. What is this guy
doing here? How did you even get over here? How
did he get over here? Come on, help me throw this.
Just give me the shard. I almost just threw up.
Ah, get up! Where am I? Get up! It's hell. All right, give me the items.
Isn't there some stuff here? There's embers, there's some souls here.
Also one of the mods that we have not done yet that is on tap
is everybody is an object. Everybody is camouflaged.
All right, get me through. Patch me in. Just give me the item. Why do I even care
about this item? It's a fucking club. It's a reinforced club.
It's not good. You don't, I don't want it. I got hit
by that on the way in. Side. Might be worth using this.
Idiot. Oh my god, you idiot. Just go. Nope, that's the wrong way. I have to
kill him. I have to.
Let me see. So this is 14-14. 105-18. I don't, I don't think so.
It's kind of ugly to swing it. That's very
just straight up and straight down. It's easier to take a look at, easier to
see. I would have been watching for what
it feels like forever. Me and my friends always quote silly
dumb quotes. Seeing you and Star meet up last year in stream was my favorite
part of 2018. Keep being you. Come visit England. England's pretty
cool. I would visit England, but thank you.
I'm glad you're enjoying yourself. Isn't there a secret wall somewhere over
here? I know there is. I'm going to Brazil.
I mean, whatever. I don't travel that much though, guys.
There's the shortcut there. Just got to get back up. That's really cool
looking. Bye. See ya.
Get me back to the bonfire. Wait, is this even, am I going the right way?
I don't think I'm going the right way. This is not the way to the bonfire.
I took a wrong turn. Holy shit, this is the wrong way.
It's down there, isn't it? No, it's not. Is this open?
Somebody's here. I can go down there, right? Yep, okay.
Drop down here. Whoa! What? No, isn't that, you gotta go up there. You
climb that, you open that door over there.
God damn. Can I run through this whole thing again?
Just don't stop, don't stop, don't stop. No reason to stop.
Lame two-hour first-person joke. I mean, I, I want, I, this is not like,
this is not a joke. I thought this was cool.
I want to see you play the whole, I don't think I'll do the whole game
like this. Okay, did I go the wrong way? No, I
gotta go get my souls. Don't talk to your father like that.
Throw that shit. Dark Souls 1 is the most funky when played in first person.
Don't you want to be able to say that you beat Dark Souls 3, Dark Souls, and
then Dark Souls 3 again? I mean, not necessarily.
I just like seeing the bosses. All right, I need,
uh, I need more strength, right? Or should I just,
no, I have to have at least like 15 strength, don't I?
Play Dark Souls Snap, what is Snap? And then you called me an idiot.
That's not how you get a request fulfilled, by the way.
If you go to the McDonald's drive-thru, or the Burger King drive-thru, or if you
go to any, it doesn't matter. Let's just use the drive-thru as an example.
Hey, welcome to McDonald's, how can I help you? Hey, yeah, um,
could you make me a number one with large fry,
idiot? They're gonna be like, uh, okay, did you want anything else? Uh, yeah,
can I get a large soda too, stupid? That person is gonna
do something bad to your food. They'll season it for me. No, they won't.
I was like, you go to like the customer, you call it like customer
service, and you have a problem with your
computer or something, or you, no, well that's not a good example.
Hey, if you call, if you would like go and get it to like your car
repaired or something. Yes, I think my brakes are making some
weird noises. Can you like to maybe do a check on
on my brakes, you fucking idiot? That's like ultra rude, that's so,
you would not do that anywhere else. Look,
you wouldn't steal a car, you wouldn't rob a bank,
so why would you steal a movie? Hi there.
I can't, he's protected. He's got, he has,
he has like fucking hockey gear on, I can't hurt him.
Idiot. Even in other places, okay, but first of all, you'd be like, well,
here's the thing Jeremy, is you're just broadcasting a live stream
on Twitch, and there's a bunch of people here in the audience,
and we're all here, and we're all watching, so it's like, you know, that
person, of course, is there's a reason for that, like someone's going to call
you an idiot for no reason, really. When was the last time you went to
a play during a live performance, like a
performance on stage? You're with like potentially a thousand people in
that audience. Right in the middle of like Romeo and
Juliet drinking the poison, are you going to stand up and be like, you
do suck, idiots. You're going to get thrown out,
comparing streaming to fine art. A school play
is fine art, like a retelling of like the eighth grade Lion King
is fine art. Is that what you're saying to me?
No, I know I'm lost, because are you calling them an idiot? No, I'm
see, I almost walked into that one, but no, no, I've got a lot going on
upstairs, so I'm able to dodge and swing
around those slippery questions. All right, let's do this one.
This is going to be cool in first person. Come on, activate,
activate. I just want to look at it, I just want to watch.
This is sweet, kill everybody. Wow, that was close,
and you're the one that hits me, really. Holy
shit, that's wild. I gotta like pop his pimples.
Whoa, I can't even move, what's going on?
All right, give me his arm, his wrist, right under there, right here.
This thing should be having a breach too. Where am I, what's going on?
We may have actually hit the wall here.
It's gonna be so hard to get this. Got it.
Barely. If it wasn't for you, I would have probably already done it
three times now. Oh my goodness, and obliterate the
balls. Isn't this fight optional? Yeah, well,
it's probably one of the cooler bosses to see in first person
in my personal pizza, you know. I'm gonna go right for his belly,
but I still have to break the other parts. I'm gonna go try to do this
very fast. I'm going right into his
sternum. I know you guys are calling it something else, but I refuse to
participate in that. I'm not gonna call it the thing
that you guys are calling it. Not nice, it's rude.
Nobody just said idiot. I can, I can smell it, I can feel it, I can
feel it.
I'm getting, I'm in like the liquid. I'm in the liquid you should not be.
Get out of here. Holy shit, he just stepped on my head.
Is he gonna roll on me? Is this music?
Oh! It's scary every time. Back it up, back it up, back it up. Only a few
more hits and you should go down. Shit! I need him to spin around. I'm not
getting stuck in this wall. We're in this way, come on man. Why
has, shouldn't this have blown up by now?
Jesus. I think this encounter might be foggled. We'll find out.
Sweep, you can go for a sweep right next to me.
Hey, there's no music either. Can't see the enemies behind me.
Uh, I'm fighting a giant baby. I'm gonna die to the fucking standard
enemy, aren't I? Turn music on. He's doing it. I'm gonna
get him. There's somebody next to me, there's somebody next to me.
Where are they? Behind me? No, no, no, use this.
Did I use it? What the f- Why? What? I hit use. Shit.
All right, this time, I'm gonna get it this time. All right, get this on the
hot bar because, like get these stupid, what the hell is
this even on here for? We basically died to Pinwheel.
I didn't die to, I just like touched my face four times.
In, no, I'm gonna get it. I don't think we're gonna see those other mods
tonight. No, I'm having, this is fun. I like
this. We got a long night. It's only been two and a half hours. I
really appreciate you giving your best out there.
Idiot. I'm going for it again. This actually is gonna suck if this is a
bugged encounter, because of the mods, and I have to fight
them the whole time with all these idiots around.
It's so hard to keep track of where these people are.
Oh, this is not good. Thank you for doing that. I really appreciate it.
Why are you here? What is he doing? He just stabbed me in the chest. I lost
control of my, what are you doing? Why can you do that?
Where is he? Wait, am I not even hitting him?
Oh, did he actually hit me with that? I can't believe he actually got it.
Let's go. Oh my god, this is hell. This is living hell.
What? Get away from me. Come here. Get, he's too big.
I think we may have found the wall. It's very possible.
All right, I don't know why that, you saw it happen. I took him down to
30% last time. What's up with that? Here we go.
I just actually kind of scared him. So why does it happen that time?
And then another one on his elbow. All right, fine, I'm gonna do it.
Gotta get the one on his back. He rolls,
bumps all down. How to get with the overhead swings. The only way I can hit
it. What have you done? What have you done? What do you think? What have you done?
What have you done? Bump it. Now he's got one more on the side.
I'm trying to bump it. It's hard to bump.
Fuck, away from me. Please don't do it. Oh, judging,
judging the distance. Die. Where's the last one? It's on his elbow.
He has to fall down for that one. Come on, stand up.
Stand up and walk and then fall. Oh, what have I thought about doing here?
You can hit the hand. I don't, I, I'm not risking it. He falls straight down.
I just, am I gauging this? Which elbow is it? Other elbow. Fuck.
I'm so scared. I, I gotta get on the right side.
Wait, it's on his hand? Didn't I get the, I thought I got the one on his hand already.
He's rolling. Which,
The whole hand. Yeah, but this, this is another actual like blood boil.
All right, it's, here we go. He's gonna fall. All right.
I didn't almost die to the pinwheel of Dark Souls 3.
Guess what? If you played Dark Souls 1 with this mod,
pinwheel would probably be hard. You probably wouldn't lose to pinwheel.
Are you calling me an idiot? No.
All right, two and a half hours. I think it's time for a wine break.
I think I'm gonna get a glass of wine.
Ah, tastes good, wouldn't it? What do you think? Should I, does that sound like fun to you?
All right, I need 15. Be careful.
15 strength, and then, what does this even scale off of?
I haven't even paid attention to that. Just D, D, D, okay.
But I can use it with one hand. Welcome us.
A break from whining, this sounds pretty good. Have I, I haven't been whining.
15, and then I'm gonna go 15, 15, 15. Look at this quality build.
Using chat as an excuse to drink. What?
All right, I need a big, cool shield. Physical 100, that's the night shield.
Magic, physical, we're going with this one.
I mean, I know it's really annoying and it's in the way, but come on.
Can I, I can stab. I can't, I need a proper spear for that.
But if VR worked, this would you do it? It'd be interesting, but impossible.
Just the nature of how this game is played is you can't, I don't know if there'd be a way to
bind right stick or mouse to head, maybe. I don't know, but wait a second though.
That's right, that boss soul is a spear. But is it a piece of shit?
I've never used it. I'm not telling enough to jump over there either.
It is? Let me see.
Okay, Arstor's spear. Take a large step forward to make a single focused thrust.
Maybe it's worth trying. Although I was under the assumption that in Dark Souls 3,
pretty much all the boss soul weapons are absolutely terrible. Unless you're doing
PvP. I heard that some of the boss soul weapons are good in PvP, but not for PvE.
Is that what I've been told? That's wrong. Why does everybody have to lie to me?
All right, I don't think I want this. Although maybe I do. It might be worth trying.
The Rotted Greatsword is amazing. Get the Greatsword. Yeah, but I can,
can I even use this? I'm going to try to use the spear. I have, I don't have 19.
I need dex, but I can get dex. 18, 19. But it's probably quick.
This is a great sword though. It's gonna be slow as hell. Yeah, this is not gonna work in
first person. I'm going with the spear. Everyone's gonna be very upset. Very upset
with me. It's got poison on it too. Nice. All right, I need 19 dex. What do I have right now?
I have some of these. How many do I need to level up?
3,600. The streamer has made an error. Yeah, but I mean, we're just doing like,
this is not a full playthrough. This is playing with first person with mods.
It's okay if I pick the bad weapon, isn't it?
Very well taken. God damn it. I need like fucking 45 souls.
All right, well I gotta go get those souls. So this is a full playthrough. What? I might
as well just go get the pickaxe. All right, so now we go to, well what is, what is actually
the next thing? That's optional. Just to get the, what actually is the next boss?
Oh, the abyss watchers, right? Okay, I remember. But I'm gonna just kill a guy and then go
level up because I'm gonna level up dexterity. Let's go. Abyss watchers is going to end
the first person thing. It very well, it very well may, but that's all right. Okay,
where, what the hell is the bonfire? I just was on it. It's so disorienting down here.
Hello? Yeah, abyss watchers could be the wall and then when we will turn on something else.
Overdose. I might beat abyss watcher first try. I did bork first try. Anything's possible.
All right, let's go to the watchers. Wait, no, I was supposed to go get a glass of wine.
Yeah, we're only three hours in, guys. What time is it? It's like 6 30. We're good.
I can drink a glass of wine. Let's give it a go. I'll be right back. I haven't left yet. I
haven't had a glass of wine on stream in like three and a half weeks. Four weeks. It's been
like a month. I can't enjoy a glass of wine on stream once a month? Then once every couple
months? No, no, no, no, no. I thought you left. Sometimes I just sit here and just take
a look at what you guys are saying and I determine if I like what you're saying.
If you don't, then I will ban the words. I will make it so you can't say those things.
I'm gonna first try the abyss watchers in first person, or if I don't, then I'm gonna
not drink the wine. I'll pour it into the sink on stream. I'm not gonna do that. I broke the
fucking cork. It's all right, though. I was just struggling down there.
I was struggling to get this thing open. I have a new wine opener that I haven't used.
I fucked it all up. All right.
It's the first time trying this. Who knows? It could be fucking gross. Why do I have this hair
all over this? I can't even drink this hair in this. A ton of it. Is this glass even clean?
There's like dog hair in here. God damn it. I just wanted to drink a little bit.
Who cares? All right, let's go. Where we going? We're going to under the bridge.
Jerma, if you get drunk, can you sing a Foo Fighters song for us?
You think a glass of wine is gonna get me drunk? What? That's pretty good. All right, let's go.
Watchers first try. All right, piss in the sink. So the question is, ah, I gotta go. I
remember now. I'm gonna go this way. I forgot he did that. He does it like five times, right?
Super charge. Am I thinking, I don't even need to fight this guy. I'm not,
I don't even need to fight this guy. Can I get his bowl? He's gonna go cross.
That was pretty ridiculous in first person. I'm not a dog. They're the worst.
Oh, he just allied me. Okay, cool trick. Where? This way. Stop playing leapfrog. Get out of my
pathing. Help. Bart, what's his name? Bart? Don't. You can't kill him, right? Get the
fucking dogs away from me. Ah, how did that not hit? Somebody is shaking me violently. Good job.
Nice work, Jeremy. Okay. Play Simpsons hit and run first person. I'll do that now. Right
now. Another one of those unkind, all euphem. If you let them go, you'll face death and it
won't be pretty. Enough death to leave you broken. I remember this guy. He's got a cool
hammer. I'm gonna go up the elevator and around and then you've, we're finally, we're
gonna get to see, uh, what's his name? We'll see that. He's not alive? Of course I'm not
gonna do that right now. Donny, can you go? It's like two play. Yeah, it's right.
Whoops. You all right? You actually get to see what he looks like.
Oh, absorbed in thought. I am Siegwert of Katarina. To be honest, I'm in a bit of a
pickle. Have you ever walked near a white birch only to be struck by, well, whoever
it is, but I have to. Well, okay. Well, everybody loves this guy. This guy, we, everybody loves
him, but I'm gonna push him into the elevator. Just fuck him. Just kidding. Don't skip his
dialogue. You've heard his dialogue like three times. Those are you Dark Souls fanatics.
You've almost just botched that one. Wait, no, that's the actual way to go. Shit. I
wasn't supposed to do that. Is there a way I can fall? I don't think I can make, can I land on
one of these brackets here? I don't think so. I could do a homeward bone. Well, you can't do
that. Sorry, I know we don't. That just gave me anxiety. I'm sorry. It is very anxious in
first person though. I remember complaining about this bridge because I'm running back
and the whole bridge is filled with people. I remember this. That's creepy. All right,
close the door. Oh, no, no, no. Zickward. Squidward. Good luck, Squidward. Go up.
He'll be fine. No, I have to wait till they despawn before I can help him.
I didn't get my souls. I didn't have any souls. Who cares? Oh, I forgot about this guy.
Let's run. Just run. I don't need to fight him. Run away. Oh, he can't come out of his
domain. All right. Give me the bonfire. I can't even let them do anything. These guys will
kill me in one second. Bonfire is like right here. Where's the bonfire? It's right here.
Where is it? Don't say boomer vision. It is boomer vision. It's first person vision. Where
is it? It's right here. Actually blind. I'm thinking of the second bonfire. The other bonfire
is up on a hill like that. Come on, it's been like two years since I played this game
and I'm in FPS mode. No, I thought I killed him. I got a backstab. No, that's not clean enough.
Go back. Yeah, I know. Hold on. I'm going to kill this guy. We're going to fight this guy
the way that I should be fighting this guy, which is with the shield.
Died to the pleb filter. That's not. It's different when you have this. I'm not even
going to explain myself. Why would I explain myself? Can this guy even be carried?
I don't think he can be carried. He can be. If we get good. That frost boon.
It's just so hard to turn that fast. It's blocking on. Doesn't do it.
It's possible. Still possible. Jesus. I don't even know what the fuck he is.
I almost got him. One more hit. Two more hits. Damn. With the sword.
Somebody just pressed F. Somebody said F. That was a little early to press F. I need to practice.
Yeah, this thing is cool. I mean, look at it. It looks cool in first person, too.
Be Iceman? No, I can't be Iceman. I could. I could. This doesn't scale with magic at all.
It just has frost effect on it. I mean, I've already got the. It's just scales with
just the D in both of them. For now, though, we're going to continue to use the weapon
that has good scaling and damage right now. Go help Sigward. He's crying. I will.
Yeah, I'm trying to think of the. There are going to be a few moments that will
probably actually be uncompletable. I wonder if they are. Some of the bosses
that move around so quickly that you can't turn to see them. All right. All right, Sigward.
You're up there. The gator dogs. Yeah, I know I have a lot of other mods, but
I'm still very much enjoying what we're doing right now. Oops. Well, actually,
I probably need to go up here anyways. Mr. Giant. Who are you? I help any time.
OK. I help. So cut the shit. Kill. Kill. Kill. Don't say that. Stop saying that.
All right. Now let's do the Sigward quest line, which is this way.
No, I was looking the wrong way. First person. It makes you disoriented.
Hmm. Oh, don't disappear like that. You have me downright worried.
Thanks to you, an epiphany has struck me. I've unraveled the riddle of this inscrutable lift.
All right. You ready to fight the big monster? I went up the tower.
Anyhow, do you see that that humongous beast? He looks even better in first
person. I know coward and I have a steady hand, but that thing. Now think twice before you go
down that road. All right. That means you're going to help. Let's go. I've got to wait.
You weren't supposed to do that without me. I said, well, I've had arena.
He goes, no, I said it's like a really hard strange beginning of the vowel there. He goes,
die Sigward of Catarina. Ready? Die. You should have waited.
Well, it's too late now. Die Sigward of the Knights of Catarina. Fight by your side.
This is awesome in first person. Oh, nice swing. Good job, Sigward.
We can work together. Don't call for flip. Cocktail. Cocktail. We did it. This is when
you learn the toast. You get to have a beer. That was cool. That was quite a performance,
but you must, we unkindled must put our duties first. But for the moment we have a toast to
make. Sigward. To your valor, my sword. And long may the sun shine. Kidding, I'm not going
to kill him. All right, there's some items that I remember. Why are we doing Dark Souls 3
again? Well, because this is a this is a different kind of Dark Souls. This is Dark Souls 3.
But as you can see, there's something else going on here. Interesting mod to play the game in
first person. I didn't toast him. Why would I? Same, but different. That's true. I thought
this is VR. I would go put on the VR helmet and make the VR joke, but I don't have it
anymore. Go back and toast or I'm going to leave. Well, just because you said that,
I'm going to go do a full R2 and hit him off the cliff. There's a really nice ring that's up here
in there somewhere. It's up over that way. I got a full R2 swing this guy. Fine, here's your
taunt. What is it? Okay, toast. Here, here. A toast to our never-ending friendship. There it
is. You're the only competent Souls streamer I've seen this year. That that means a lot
considering I've struggled a lot with this game when I first played it. I am playing in gosh damn
first person. Wow, what a confidence boost. Thank you for that. Seriously, that was a super
confidence boost. I can do anything now. I'm capable of anything. For real, thank you. This
year. Yeah, but there are some incredibly talented, amazing Souls players. People that
beat the game without getting hit. People that beat the game in fucking 45 minutes. People
that get lost in an area that they don't remember because they haven't played the
game in a while and they forget where they're going. You know, there are those streamers out
there and be careful. Don't watch them. If you come across somebody that like is kind of walking
in circles and they don't really remember where to go, like do not watch that stream
because is it really worth watching? Be careful of those streams. There's two ladies upstairs
from what I remember. There's two fat ladies up here. I remember doing this, but there is
something nice up here. It's worth a try. Yep, yeah, sometimes I don't remember
where the enemies are spawned and it's all right. This year. Yeah, but that's okay.
That's a good compliment. I'm sorry, it is. Dogs, right? Holy shit, didn't even see you.
Oh, there's three. There's too many. I gotta run. Come on, now I gotta keep it up. I gotta
keep it up. Like this year, right? Come on. Okay, we're good. I got a reputation now to uphold.
I know there are two ladies up here. I just really hope they don't turn off my stream.
Come on, fall. Come on. All of you come down. I know you will. There they are. What's the
strategy? What's the game plan here for these two in first person? Somebody just gave a ton of
money. $3,500. $3,500. Thank you. I was going to donate a million bits since you're playing
like a pro Dark Souls player, but then I remembered that you died to Pinwheel and it was
shameful. Well, thank you so much for the $35. But the person that said I was the most
competent Souls player this year, I want you to make sure you understand this. That's a joke.
It's a lie. I beat Pinwheel first try on a blind playthrough last year. It's a joke. It's a funny
thing. I'm still your favorite Dark Souls streamer this year. All right, we're gonna
alluring seagull and run. Hello? All right, here's the ring. Flynn's ring. I remember this
being very good. Isn't there something else up top here too? Lowering equipment load
increases attack. Put the damn thing on. So this is it. You take off all your clothes.
All right, we gotta go. Where's the other one? There's another one over here, right?
Gonna make this jump down to here. And there's an item over here. Oh, that's not what I was
looking for. Nudity equals power. Maybe I should just take it all off now. Oh, fuck. Okay,
hold on. If I can go from here to there. I'm gonna die here. It's not gonna be pretty.
Oh, I'm good. There's the vest. The trousers. Okay, that's the ring I'm thinking of. This is
the anti-poison one, right? No, that's the best ring in the game. That's the best ring
in the whole game. Now I remember. Didn't I take my gloves off? Why do I still have
these night gloves on? All right, now we can keep progressing. Am I gonna beat Dark
Souls 3 tonight on stream? In first person? Absolutely not. But I mean, we're still going.
All right. I could probably just bone out of here. Yeah, I'm just gonna bone. What was
the last? It doesn't matter. Oh, yeah, I forgot. In Dark Souls 3, it doesn't matter.
Should I? Maybe I should just upgrade this and just keep going with it.
I'm never gonna be cool enough to have the spear, I don't think. Is it 18, right?
I could get it. Yeah, let's put the spear on. Let's do the thing we wanted to do.
How many more do I need for this piece of absolute shit? Where is it?
19. I can get that shit right now. This thing's really ugly. It's got it. It's got a nice feel
to it, though. It's quick. He lied about having other mods. That's not true.
I have a bunch. Show us then. I can't, though, because we're doing so we're having
so much fun. We can come back to this? Look, I'm having a great time. I can't stop.
I'm sorry. Stop having fun. No, I refuse. I refuse to stop having fun.
Change mods and go back to the save. Yeah, I could. All right, here's what's gonna happen.
Are you ready? I'm gonna go beat Abyss Watchers, and then after Abyss Watchers, sure.
How playable is this mod? From what you can see on the screen, it's very playable. I thought
the dodge roll was gonna be headache-inducing. What it essentially does is it just fixes the
camera in a spot that is always pointing forward no matter where, so it's pretty great.
Oh, the crystal mage. Oh no, the crystal mage. I died 15 times to crystal mage in my first
playthrough. It's probably gonna happen again. All right, let's go. Let's go. I can use this
with two hands, right? No, I can't. I need another level. I have so many of these.
That's almost as embarrassing as Pinwheel. That's fine. You have to do crystal mage
in first person. That's gonna make it a thousand times harder. I also want the...
I love this. Here's the thing about Dark Souls and Souls games in general,
those of you that are here that are big fans of these games. If I could eternal sunshine
of the spotless mind and wipe out me ever playing this game, I would do it like once a
month. I don't know how that would cause irreparable damage to my brain, but it'd be
great. Being able to play this game and experience it again in a way that you never
have is all... it's just... it's really fun. So I'm sort of vicariously living through myself
again, if that makes sense. I didn't realize it was gonna be this much fun. It does not make
sense. Well, it doesn't have to. Get those funny mods on, you clown streamer. But not
every... not every single stream has to be a clown stream, right? Don't you know?
We can do first person Dark Souls. That's objectively wrong. No, we don't have to have
every stream be a clown stream. I promise, like in a couple days, you'll hear me go like,
it'll happen. Really? Yeah. I promise you'll hear at least one or two clown horns. Oh,
fuck. And it doesn't matter because we're about to get to the Abyss Watchers
and I'm going to quit the game. And I'm going to start over and we're going to do
times 40 speed. And then everyone can make their clown noise. Clown horns. You're like
two hours away. Not for somebody that's played this game two or three times. In a row. On
stream. And then off stream. And then as sorcery. And beat the game as sorcery.
Okay, where's the butcher's knife, lady? Not till over here.
Freeze right now? Really, it's not. Jesus, that's scary. Somebody else is here.
And then one inside of the circus wagon. Hurt you? No, don't do it. No, don't do it.
Respect to pure faith after Abyss Watchers. You know, I just might do that. Probably not
though, because I have the spear. You can't, how do you, why is that video thing even a
command anymore? What video thing? Is it video command thing? A spear. Isn't there,
there's a lady over there. Yes, there she is. Found her. Let's kill the butcher and get the
butcher's cleaver. There you are. Come on. Remember I made the Wizard of Oz reference
when I first streamed this game? Okay, all right, calm down, lady. Oh, shit! Oh,
shit! Butcher knife. It's a pretty good weapon. I think I used this for a majority of time
that I played Dark Souls 3 the first time. It's a pretty good weapon. It has, I believe,
A scaling, which, you know what I mean? I got grounded because you cursed. Well, put me on
speaker. Am I on speaker? Let me know when I'm on your speakers. Okay. Hey, ma, I'm really
sorry about the cursing there that I got a little too intense, a little too worked up.
Just want to make sure that you understand that I typically run a PG-13 stream and
sometimes an F word or one of those other bad words slip out sometimes. I really am
sorry about that. Please, please let your son still watch my stream. I promise I'll never say
any bad words ever again. I need his money. I need his money. No, I don't. Don't take me
out of context there. I need his money. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I
remember this part. They all come at you on the bridge. Damn! Shut up. Everybody shut up.
We're fine. I just found a secret. What's that noise? It's getting louder. What is that noise?
Why is there silent hill sounds? Yeah, I'm gonna do the same. Yeah, same to you. Hey, dummies.
Morn's ring. I'll take the free shit. Braille divine tomb of karm. Boosts and miracles.
Grounded. I'm sorry. Ma'am, ma'am, ma'am. I'm sorry, ma'am. Great corv inside. That's a rare
drop. That's a rare like 85% drop. Where? Where is he? I gotta get up. Is there two of them?
There are two here. Where is he? Oh, no, I'm facing the wrong fucking direction.
Listen, ma'am, sometimes you say the F word. It's just the F word. It's not a big deal.
Yeah, I'm not one of those like disgusting streamers that says we grow stuff,
mean stuff. I don't say like bad, mean shit. I don't want to be like that. Sometimes I say
F-U-C-K and even spelling it was embarrassing for me. I'm sorry. Too many noises.
There's too many noises. But there's an item over here. What? Where am I? I'm stuck in the
wall. I'm stuck in the wall. How do I do this? I have to do something drastic.
You're too nice, you piece of re. Well, at least the souls will be on the bridge. Going right. I
got the ember. Embers are so important because it's a full heal. Can you slap yourself again
for a joke? No, I'm a PG-13 streamer. Where are the souls? Oh, they're over there. Alright,
now should I do the speedrun strat, which is make guy jump off cliff and then grab sword.
I've seen that speedrun a few times. Let's take a look. This is C scaling. It needs 16
strength. Great Corbin side. This is the bleeding one. Someone watches AGDQ.
Well, actually there was a time when I was watching a lot of Dark Souls streamers that
did speedruns because I thought it was interesting because it just is. These games
are very hard and very particular. Now this thing is not very good. 16 strength, 18, 97
plus 29. I mean the goddamn whip is cooler. No one cares. No one cares. What? No one cares
about what? About Dark Souls? You wouldn't go to a drive-thru. Pull up to the drive-thru.
Hey, can I help you? And no one cares. Do you want food or what are you doing here?
One guy strikes again. It's one guy. No one cares. It's one guy. Alright, let's put on the
uh, I mean I could kill these two, but isn't this like killing the guy that praises the
sun? Everyone gets mad. Oh, hello. How do you do? I am Anri of Astora, unkindled like you.
This is Horace, a friend and traveling companion. Are you too in search of the
Lords of Cinder? We are well along beyond the floor. We seek that you may go off the
next time made of flames. No one cares, lady. Well, I got the souls. Attack her and then
fall off and let the guy jump up and kill himself, right? Do I have enough for a level up?
It's possible. The real wife. I'm not saying that word. The real wife is the blacksmith.
Alright, now I can use the spear. It's time to see what this thing is capable of. I've
never used it before. Let's see with the shield. How does it work with the shield? Nice.
R2. I kind of like it. Say it. I'm not going to say that. Why not? Because I don't want to say it.
Say it, idiot. Look, you wouldn't go to a drive-thru at McDonald's and order a number one
and when the guy says, is there anything else I can help you with? Say waifu.
Sir, I'm not. Sir, please pull your car up. For the love of God.
Oh, I thought I was far enough away to do the waifu joke.
Sir, you can be very far away. I severely underestimate this. The depth is so hard
to judge here. Hold on. Look at that. Does it look like I could hit that from here?
It doesn't, does it? I can't. But look it. You can. Alright, let's go. Let's go get
Abyss Watchers and let's first buy the Abyss Watchers. This weapon is terrible.
Hurry up and do something funny, clown idiot streamer.
They have bigger spears, it's not fair. Why do you guys have to be so mean, okay?
How much of that can I block? Judging how far away these guys are is absolutely- you know
it's hell. This is hell. Right? How many times have you heard me say that in this stream?
Dude, this is hell. I might as well just do that. I didn't even need to heal. I know
where to go. Me and my fucking candy stick. What a great setup I have. A shield and a
fucking street sausage. No, I know where to go. I know where to go. Don't worry.
Ah, he's behind me! I need to get that other shard from the first area.
Shove it. Did he ever put his armor back on? Watchers are this way. Don't- I'm not going
to worry about the crabs right now. I'm just going to get to the other bonfire.
Shove it. One of the things I don't like about the Dark Souls games is this is going to be a
what the heck moment for the PG-13 audience here. What the heck? Why do they get invincibility
frames sometimes when they get up from the ground? I don't get those. No, I don't. Not
as many as they do. They get like 10 frames. I get fucking four. Now this is a mistake
because I need to- you idiots. Not you guys. I'm talking about the- I missed the fucking bonfire.
It's right here, right? Somewhere right here? Where is it? It's like right here.
Where's that bonfire? I know it's right here somewhere.
What? It was up on the cliff. It's all right. I'll get there. Your mom said that you're
smart. Yeah, I bet you are. Dogs. That's a big shield. I might like that.
Jeremy, next mod please. A different mod. Look, I really don't want to bring up like any
controversy here, but you wouldn't go to McDonald's and ask for a whopper at the
fucking drive-thru. Hey, welcome to McDonald's. Can I help you? Yeah, can I get a whopper
please? Idiot clown. Stop with the McDonald's. All right, let's go Crystal Sage. You versus
me. You know, one-on-one battle. I'll come back and get these items in like a year.
Don't worry. I can't wait to hear the first line that she says.
This is gonna be horrible. This already sucks because I can't see where anything is.
Oh, I'm gonna die here. This is gonna be rough. I might have to put the other weapon on.
No. Here come the clones. Oh, what the heck? Oh my goodness. They're aiming from every
direction. Which one's the real one? Come on, give me a good roll here.
That's not the right one. Hit the ember. Dick, you're in such a weird spot.
Normally he just wants himself dumb, right guys? Don't get greedy. Just one hit and he's dead.
Oh, what the fuck happened? No, the first person camera was not in the right spot and it was one
hit. What the fuck was that? No way. I just like wasn't in the right spot.
You've got to be kidding me. That was dumb.
No, give me a fucking break. I can't even. Oh, you all know what I'm trying to say.
Classic YouTube reaction. It's over now. Oh my god, that hurt my whole fucking body.
I can't believe it. I actually can't believe it. It was that simple. I didn't get greedy on
the last time before he went down and the second time I just completely missed somehow.
I'm fucking deleting that weapon. That weapon's going in the garbage.
Lost to the crystal sage with a fucking ember. No, but it doesn't count because
it's extra hard mode because it's- ahhh! This thing sucks too. I can't believe it.
I'm infuriated right now. That's unbelievable to me. How could I let that happen?
I just like upgraded all of this. It was so- I was already there.
Somehow I wasn't lined up correctly because you can't lock on. Get that-
Mmm. Next to you. Go on, do it. Shoot it.
I just love how it doesn't matter what direction I'm facing something here.
My mom says I can't watch Family Guy. Well, that's all right. Family Guy has been awful
since like season 7. Who cares? You can see where they're fighting me from.
I can't fucking believe this. I did it and I'm just so hyper tilted right now in that first
run. I'm upgrading this thing. Can I even? The Watchers is not even gonna be as hard as this
because I only get to see in front of me so I can't- like when the blue- when the blue
diamond shooters come up, I don't even know where they're shooting from. This is plus one.
I'm just gonna upgrade this like three fucking times. Unbelievable. The Watchers aren't gonna
destroy me. All right. Plus two, plus three. I don't have enough. I got plus one. Plus two.
And I am also gonna go get the- the Estus. Which one is it? This one? Is it tower or is
it high wall? Where the shard is. Didn't he stream this before? Yeah, I did. But not with the
not wearing cinder blocks all over my body. All right, down from here. I don't remember
where it is. I think it's down. This guy blows up the room. How are you still alive?
Didn't I just upgrade this thing twice? Huh? What are you still doing here? What are you doing?
Throw the thing. Focus streamer goes the wrong fucking way. Sorry, I got the mail breaker which
I'm not gonna put on. God. It's because the weapons suck. I care too much about worrying
about the first person shit and I ended up using a bad weapon. Bad character. It doesn't matter.
I'm not going to use that as an excuse. Just give me my Estus. I didn't go the right way.
Bad gamer. Bad Estus. Bad- which way is it? I really don't remember where this is. All right.
Where the hell is it? It's not down that way. Should I- I know there's like another way to
go down. I just don't remember. DS3 GoPro edition. So wait, I was going the right way.
I always swing at the same time that you do. Jerma, GoPro. Stop being such a noob.
I can. I'm a noob. An upgraded piece of turd is still a turd. Yes, it is. But it's a better
turd. See, like, I thought I was facing this way. I guess not. All right, now from here
is the way to go. I think it is actually this way because I can go down through here, right?
There's a spear guy here. What the hell even hit me? Get a load of this guy. All right.
I'm sorry. That just kind of came up. Undead hunter charm. Bye. It's down there all the
way. Okay, down, down, down, down, down, down. Get down there. I don't give a shit about
anything else. Just give me the S to splash. It's right on top. It's okay. It's all right.
Everything's fine. It's all right. It's not all right. Everything's fine. Oh, no. Oh,
no. I'm freezing. Who cares? Just died. I got the thing I wanted. How many jokes
did we miss today? Well, we got a couple going here. We got McDonald's drive-through.
We got, it's been like two or three hilarious ones. I missed the drive-through joke. Do it
again. All right. I got my Estus. Who cares about a thousand cells? It's fine. Can you do a spill
joke? I'm going to spill the wine on my carpet and lose my security deposit. That sounds like
a good idea. It'd be like funny, right? Bingo. Okay. Six flasks. Good, good, good. Now I'm
ready. I'm ready to fight the crystal, whatever the, whatever the crystal knight's name
is. Who cares? When it's fun mod time. I mean, I, this, I am having fun. This is fun mod time.
Let's go. Don't block my path. I have to at least get to the watchers. I mean, Crystal Sage
is right here. Watch us right after. Like two or three hours after. You know, like four hours
after where you were at right now. And it's all right. I'm going to first try this right now.
I've got an upgraded weapon. Did somebody get in here with me? No, it's my hand. It's my third
fucking hand. What? I'm so confused. See what happened there is the purple firework was out of
my field of view. It was behind me. And what it did is it came back and hit me right in the back
of the head. Couldn't see it. First person on top of that. Three hands. Don't explain it away.
I have to, don't you understand? I have to ultra explain things three times in a row
over and over again. See what happened was a few minutes ago, what I did was I,
the first person came up was behind, the thing was behind me. So I have to explain the thing
I just did four times. Welcome to German 985's live stream. See, like right now,
I knew it. I told you it was going to happen. I already explained the thing.
Zero plus zero is zero. You gotta be fucking kidding me. Remember when I died to Crystal
Sage like 15 times in my first playthrough? Yeah, I'll be champion gun to your first try,
but I can't beat Crystal Sage. That's what I get for using a turret weapon,
but there was a reason for the turret weapon. That's not the real one. Oh my God.
Those floating gobstoppers are the reasons that cause so many problems. I can't see them right
now. It's behind me, isn't it? It's behind me. It's behind me. I'll take this one. Get
the one behind me. No, no, no, no, no, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't,
don't get yourself killed for no reason. There's one behind you. You can't see him
because you're in first goddamn person. Full health. All the way over there. You've gotta
be kidding me. You said I couldn't fucking do it second try. Now that was first try with
actually upgraded weapon. I was here. I was here. Yeah. I mean, some of you were here
for this. I need some more endurance. Yeah. I need to get to 20 endurance. I just have to.
What does the Crystal Sage's body orb do? Really? Oh. It is the soul of a Crystal
Sage. It scales with magic. Just ain't gonna happen. Pop it. Let's get that endurance
up. For the Watchers, which I'm gonna first try. Hey chat, my bunny says she loves you
all. That's so sweet. It really is. Little bunny. Well, tell your bunny that we all
said hello. And look, if I can just keep having fun in first person, then fuck it,
man. Next time I'll do it again. We'll just do this again. I'm having an actual blast.
He sounds drunk. I'm on one glass of wine. I've taken in the amount of alcohol
that you get by swishing fucking Listerine in your mouth. What? Alcohol? Alcohol. Alcohol. I
have an accent. Alcohol. All right. Next person makes fun of my accent. I want them permanently
100% IP banned from my computer. What? Say coffee car? Coffee car. Coffee car. Where's
my accent from? England. I was born in England. I was raised in England and then I moved to
New York and then I moved from New York to Boston. I've since have dropped my English
accent. It comes out a little bit sometimes, but I've since dropped it. And it's weird
because when you're around a certain group of people, you take on certain parts of their
accents. So when I went to Boston, I had an English accent for a long time, but
I started to get a Boston accent because I was hanging out in Massachusetts.
I think it's time to get the shield out of here. Just weighing me down.
What's my equipment load? It's 25 out of 55. Am I technique? Am I? I don't even know what kind
of roll I'm doing right now. Am I mid rolling? Yeah, I am. I gotta get this done. Two, let's
see. 23. I'm gonna be lower than that. Am I? Maybe not. It's hard to tell. Fast roll isn't
worth it. Actually, I love fast roll. Can I not get hit by you for the first time? Oh,
all stream. Of course not, because I was speaking.
Let's get to those watchers. I can double hit some fire here. That's good.
Tell them, chat. What is it to tell me that I don't already know?
I've beat this game before. All right, this is not the right way to go to watch.
Yeah, that's right. That's true. Does anyone want to play Super Smash? Dude, where's the
friend code? Come here. Don't disappear. I just... Do you remember Maine's Duck Hunt? I don't.
I don't even know what that is. So I refresh my memory. I don't care if this backs me up.
I've beaten this game 10 times. How do I get to watchers? It's from the swamp. Oh, that's
right, right, right. You go through back here. Right. You go through Farron. Yeah, I remember.
All right, let's get it. Can some of you chatter to me quick? Can you get a couple of
let's get it in the chat? What was that? Did you hear that? You didn't just hear that, like...
There's a NPC over here somewhere. There's also an ember and a black knight, right?
From what I can't really remember. Your dad says I'm a bad influence. Well, I'm not...
My goal here is not to influence anyone. Influencing anyone. Why would I... I don't
want to influence you. Okay, there's a couple of items that I don't want to miss.
Professional Influencer. All right, I want to go... Where's the... Where's that NPC? He's up top.
So I can kill him and take his soul. Somebody's behind me and I'm stuck. No!
No! Who the fuck is this guy? I know he's... No, maybe he's in Farron, I think.
We're back out here anyways. I missed the item. Whatever. My first playthrough, I remember
trying to jump up here over and over again. Oh, have I ever seen this item?
This thing sucks. What does this have? This thing's terrible. Stabil... It has high
stability. It's a parry shield. Why wouldn't you just use a leather shield? All right,
this looks like a cookie. This is a fucking Fourth of July cookie. I don't think... I'm
not using this thing. All right, here we go. I know there are two NPCs to fight over here.
Fucking Dengus and Dungus. There's Dungus. And Dengus is right behind him.
What the fuck I was thinking there. Trying to get killed by Dengus and Dungus. This is great.
Great, great! Oh, fuck it. Who cares? I don't want anything to have anyways. Just
get the bonfire. It's right in here. No! I... What did you think would happen? I just forgot
how far the fall was. I thought it was like only a couple... I thought it was like 10 feet,
20 feet. I didn't think it was that far. Darth Vader's Screamer.
Nice fall joke. Jesus Christ. Just stop dicking around and try to win it. Stop it. You be quiet.
Yes. Yes. Be quiet. Well, I love... Okay, I love how there's a bunch of Pluto's in chat.
Everyone's like, oh my god! How come... Where's my Pluto? Get down the ladder! Does he
actually come... He comes all the way down? Where is he going? Fucking dumbass. Oh, I can't wait.
I'm gonna push you and watch you go all the way down. Okay. I got staggered to a point where I
couldn't even dodge. I couldn't move. He hit me with the club. Whatever. Raging Boomer. I'm
almost there. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I'm trying to remember how this scenario plays out.
I have to light the three towers before I can fight the Watchers, right? Oh, that sucks.
Uh, that sucks. Thanks for watching the stream. What the hell is that? Why is it... Why is this...
Why is Dingus's item there? How does it feel? I'm just gonna run. I'm gonna run and turn on the
fires. I'm not gonna fight any enemies. I don't care. I gotta get to Abyss Watchers. I'm gonna
level up HP one more time. I'm gonna equip the daggers and I'm just gonna dash. I'm gonna
bring six Estes. No, no, no. I'm gonna allocate Estes. Check this out.
Yeah, allocate Estes. You get what I'm going at here? Uh, there they are. Quick step.
Because then when these are equipped, you don't need mana to quickstep? Yeah, do it. Look.
You can dash without mana. What are you talking about? Huh. Look at the mana bar.
What? Am I gonna get banned? That seems like an exploit.
Okay, so you know the drill. You know the deal. We're gonna upgrade our HP.
You don't get eye frames. I'm not looking for eye frames. I'm just looking for traveling.
I just... I don't care about items. I just want to light the three fires.
If he does not first try this, I'm gonna go to McDonald's and I'm gonna do a McDonald's
joke. Don't do that. The whole point of that is you wouldn't do that.
All right. Fire number one. Over there. Let's go. I just swallowed on my own spit. I'm sorry.
I was gonna do...
Where's the other one?
Oh, yikes!
Don't... Just stop trying to be fucking funny instead of what you're gonna do.
Where's the other one? One, two, three. One, two, three. He's still here.
I can get one item. The greatsword. I ain't fucking around here, but I can get one item.
Running is faster. Watch out for the slugs. Estes Shard. You didn't think I was gonna get
the Estes Shard? You don't think I've ever played this game? Get it. Four hours and
30 minutes on one mod, but it's a good one. One more and then that is the last one.
Right there. Come on. Straight ahead. Go, go, go, go, go, go. One item. Just one.
If you can guess this song, you win. Somebody... Ghostbusters. Holy shit. Wow. Nice job.
Wow. You guys are smarter than your average bear. All right. So this next one is straight.
Just straight, straight, straight, straight. This guy made fun of Fortnite? When did I make fun
of Fortnite? Did I make fun? What? I'm trying to remember. It's not a backstab. It's a backstab
in every other fucking game I've ever played. Where's the last fire? Ah, that's not a backstab.
Somebody tell me why. Cracked, cracked peppercorn. It's up there, right? I lost it.
It is up there, isn't it? I get a better view. He's in one of his moods? Yeah, the mood is I
have to get to the Abyss Watchers. It's not this. It's over there. Are you going to beat
Medir in first person? I don't think I'm going to get to Medir in first person. I hate to say it.
All right. Last one. And then the door opens and we get to Abyss Watchers and I can beat
them first try. Fuck the item. I'll get it later. Can you Venmo me $420? I don't. I don't
have that. I don't have that money. Cheapskate asshole. All right. Here we go. You guys
ready? Ready for the Abyss Watchers? I am and I'll prove it to you. Wait, I got to do something
cool here. I'm going to go in a different door. Watch this. Come on, do it before I get killed.
I mean, I didn't get it, but I'm just trying to get the spin. Just give me the item.
That is a bone shard. Very important to have it. And in fact, I'm going to go use it right
now because it's important. Some people are saying die to slugs, but that didn't happen.
I did not die to slugs because I'm still alive. This weapon sucks. Total asshole.
And it's going to be the reason why I can't beat Abyss Watchers first try,
but I'm going to beat them first try. I need, what do I need? I don't have enough.
Died to one tin wheel, two dingus, three slugs, four Abyss Watchers. That hasn't happened yet.
We're in the bone shard. All right. This is the streamer that's overleveled and underskilled.
You can't die to a bonfire. What level am I? 30? And I'm probably underleveled right now because
I'm skipping all this content. Level 30 for Abyss Watchers. That's under. Yeah, don't die.
Don't tell me I'm underleveled when I'm, I mean, don't tell me I'm overleveled when I'm
underleveled. You're making me look bad. Where the fuck am I going? I'm, I'm telling, uh,
the Abyss Watchers are not over here. What is this? A golden scroll? I'm so close to being fucking
petrified. I didn't even go the right way. Did I go the wrong way? Good thing this is not Dark
Souls 1. Does the first person mod exist for Dark Souls 1? That would be very hard. I can't
imagine playing that game on first person. One of these guys dropped a nice weapon though,
don't they? From what I remember. I think it's a little further up. What has actually come good?
Just get out of my screen for one second. I just, all I see are fucking feathers flying around
in my hands. He's died once to every enemy? That's not true. That actually might be true.
Is that actually true? Just, I'm just gonna go. I thought it was nuts right here.
Right? There's some other shit in here, isn't there? There's a bonfire here. Fuck, I'm hungry,
but I had dinner three hours ago. That's all right, just eat again.
There's a black knight over here, isn't there? Who cares? What's wrong with that? That's all
right. Just don't, just have like a snack. Have a little snack. Popcorn, a little bit
of butter on it. Cheese and crackers. That's a high calorie. You're fine. Yeah, these guys
dropped a golden sword. Well, I can't even, forget it. Let's just go to the watchers and
win first try. This looks cool in first person. Look at this area. All right, here we go. Let's
give it a whirl. There we go. That wasn't fair. Now fight each other. Fight me instead.
Why are you not fighting each other? Fight him. You're making this too hard for me.
Will you fight him? Oh, this is my friend over here. Right, okay. Judges so hard. I don't even
know which one is which now. The perspective has got me all fucked up. I don't even know
who's the real one. This is definitely not going to happen first try. It's impossible
first try. I'm doing 97 damage a swing. Is this the worst weapon in the entire game?
It could be. It's possible. You're the worst weapon in the game. I'm not even going to
get into this second phase. Maybe I will. Well, didn't see you there. Tunnel vision.
Jerma, don't spoil what happened. It's the third worst halberd, but it has a good sweet spot.
I'm so concerned about this. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You
guys don't understand. I didn't have a weapon with big reach because depth perception is
hard with the first person. I can't. I'm literally going to burn this weapon in the trash.
It takes too long to swing for 110 damage. It's awful. Just kill me. I'm going to fucking
burn this on screen. Where's the cool ice sword? I told you long sword was the way to
go. Ice sword is the way to go. Back to zone. Here we go. Camera man, it just is.
They move too fast for me to hold right stick in a direction.
You can't lock on to anybody. So I have to hold right stick to see where he is.
Holy shit. I don't know what's happening right now. I'm going to do it. I'm going to win.
Christ. He's spoiled with lock on. Insane. If the lock on stayed locked on, right? So when
you dodge roll, right? When you dodge roll in Dark Souls and you have a lock on, the camera
is always focusing on the enemy that you have locked on. Not here. See here, if you do a dodge
roll, the enemy is gone. Good luck. Turning the sensitivity up. No, that would be horrible
because it would be like, I would throw up. I think the sensitivity is fine. I'll get it.
I'm going to be slow and wait for the opportunity and it's happening.
Just judging the distance. It's like juggling oranges while playing Dark Souls.
I'm going to go with the cookie shield because this will make me want to win. How many bosses
have I beaten in first person? I've only played the game in first person. Only. So the whole game
so far. I just do some testing. I got to do some testing first. Yikes. Where did you come
from? No. I'm too far away. Where the fuck did he go? Oh my God. This is going to take
like a hundred tries to do this. I need to upgrade this thing. I will do this before the stream is
over. Goodness. No, why am I locked onto that guy? What the hell is that for? Holy shit.
I'm getting attacked from behind now. Come on. Come on first person. Suck my bum.
Get out of the way. Move. Turn. I have, I might get him to the second phase.
It's very possible. My God. Just give me the second phase and let me just see what it looks
like in first person. I just want to see. I just want to see. I just, okay. I just want to see
what it looks like. Here we go. I can't get hit one time. Holy shit. Trying to gauge the
distance of these moves. No way. Not in a million years. It's not over. Suck my bum.
Not you guys. I'm not throwing the towel in that easily. How do I fix this? I don't even
have enough souls to do this. What weapon do I have? It might have to be. Use mouse and
keyboard? I'll show you what happens when you use mouse and keyboard. This. As you can see,
this is not, this is not ideal at all. Although it seems cool. For some reason the
mod cannot handle a mouse input like this because it's changing the camera so rapidly
that it's very headache inducing. Uh, I could probably upgrade this weapon.
Let me see. I don't have any souls but I can sell some stuff. So this requires, I could
upgrade this once with a titanite. Twinkling titanite. Either that or I need a few more
shards to get this to plus three. I'll upgrade this once because this is a good, this is a
good weapon just to have. Promises of other mods. I have to beat Abyss Watchers first before
we do anything else. First person. Plus the title of the stream is First Person Dark Souls
3 so. Okay, I'm gonna upgrade this once. I need, how many souls do I need to do this?
Five thirty. It's easy. Sell. Uh, sell the stupid home, home brood that he made. Sell
these dumb alien beads, whatever they are. I could put one of these on too. Can you put,
can I put fire and ice? I don't think I can. That's enough. That would be 138 plus 26.
Let's give it a go. One more level and it turns into a C for strength scaling.
I'm gonna give this to the bird. Okay, let's try it again. I'm ready. I'm going to win.
It's gonna happen. Just give me your energy. No, why not? Can I get this stupid shield off
and put something else useful on? This thing is really good. Let me see, it's a hundred
percent block. That might not be good though. What is that little guy, the energy guy?
Is that Kirby? What character is that? Okay, focus. Let's go. Upgraded the weapon.
Here we are. Have I lost my mind or is this doing less damage?
What? It's not my head. It got worse. You and me. You, me and you, me and you, me and me.
I didn't expect you to. Oh crap, oh crap. I'm about to settle down. Did you change hands?
The smoke, the smoke is, they're smoking me out here. Get back here. Where is it? Where's
the other guy? Where is he? Is he dead? No, he's up here. Let's do it. Florestus,
come on. Let's do it. I'm ready. All right, I'm gonna gauge some distance here.
I don't need to do the fire thing. Oh shit. Wow. It's so hard. It's so hard.
It is so hard to do this in first person. It's so hard. I want my energy back now.
It's mine. It's mine and I got to the first, I'm getting better. I'm doing things better.
Everything's just fine. Shit. Fucking first person. I've ruined the character build too. It's all my
own fault. I would be doing probably twice as much damage if I didn't put three upgrades
into the fucking wood long pole thing. I could just raw gem the looser. No, you're right.
No, they're behind me. I will tell you, having to press R3 every five seconds
is like mind-meltingly frustrating. No. They're right next to me, aren't they?
So here's the thing. Everyone's saying do a new mod. We're at the ultimate wall. I have to
beat this first. You want me to do this in times 10 speed? That's not going to happen.
There's no way. Okay, let me, what would I get if I raw gemmed the lucerne? Turn them all on at
the same time? I can do this. I just need to get the right amount of damage. 136 plus 62,
202. Okay, I'm going to raw gem this. I'm going to raw gem the lucerne. We're going
to give it a go. We're going back to turd. I need 2250 souls. We're just selling my whole inventory.
What the hell is even in here? That doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter. Infuse. Where is it? What am I at right now?
151 plus 39. This would make this a 202. That's as good as I'm going to get.
Doing it. Let's go. Now I'm going to win. Plus three damage. What do I got? 22. How's my roll?
Let's go. And what else do we got here? Can I put, can I use this shit? Does this actually
work? I can actually light this on fire. I'll be ready. Not that one. Where is it?
I don't think I have any gold pine. No, I don't have any gold pine.
He just copied their weapons. Well, sometimes you have to copy to win.
24 hour stream? I don't think so, but I'm still having a good time. So
I'm going to keep going. It's better than it was before. Damn it. Here he comes.
Holy shit. That guy almost killed me in one hit. It doesn't help that I'm under leveled too.
I need, I'm like under leveled by like probably at least five to 10 levels for this.
All right. If I don't do it this time, then I'm going to, I'll turn.
Cause this is just, this is just literal pain. Under leveled first person mod. I may as well just
fucking, I honestly may as well just go to sleep on the screen. Oh, with a backswing.
You're stuck in like the fog. Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Oh,
okay. I got an opportunity here. One shot. Let's go. Fucking camera. What are you doing
to me? No, the camera is off him again. It's so frustrating. I just want to lock onto him and
it just takes it off every fucking time. Oh my God. It's unbearable. Cause every time I turn
the camera, like it's face, it faces the direction you move, right? So if I have him
locked on and I dodge this way, he's gone. Even if I'm locked on. Ooh, it hurts. No,
I got him close. I can do this. Take it out of first person. That defeats the whole
purpose of this whole stream. Summon ghosts. No, I can't do that. I got him halfway. I'll get it.
This is definitely the wall dog. I have to at least beat this. How many times? I'm probably,
I'll die another 30 times. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna, I'm wearing the weights and I'm
running the mile. Don't worry. We're going to go to funny mods after I beat them. It has
to happen. We're going to transition to funny LOL mods, but I'm going to beat them right
now. I can't break out. Cheers to you yet. Cheers to you is a desperate scenario. I'm
not desperate yet because I did bring them to about 50%. Let's get bit by a mosquito.
Here we go. The lock on that's killing me. Put the lock on on them and you just,
you've played hundreds of hours of Dark Souls and you just expect that when you dodge
or you move, it's going to keep them in focus and just doesn't do it. And the idea
that thousands of times you've died in Dark Souls, it's not going to happen. Don't,
not with that attitude. Unplug the key, the unplug the controller and do mouse and keyboard.
I mean, that's a, I'll try it, but I'm so used to playing this game without a mouse.
This is the one right here. I'm not, I don't need a mouse. I don't need an extra
support. I'm going to do this on my own because I know that I can. You understand?
One, two, three, action. Fair. That's not fair. It's it. I can't do it when it's not fair.
This is, you can't, you can't do it when it's unfair, you know, when you got an unfair
scenario. Jesus Christ. I'm going to do it. Oh, is that, you know, it's actually kind
of refreshing. I'll tell you why. Uh, so like seven months ago, I opened up Dark Souls
three for fun and I was like, you know, I'll play through Dark Souls three again. That
sounds like a good idea. Uh, I think I died probably three times. I beat the Abyss Watch's
first try. It was just like, all right, this is just what I'm doing. This is fun.
I know how to like dodge here. It's actually kind of refreshing to lose over and over
again in a game that I've played through at least five times. It's really cool.
This actually is very interesting. It's refreshing. I'm like frustrated again at
Abyss Watchers. When was the last time you heard that? It was the other guy. There he is.
This really breeds new life. I'm just going to run away. You're just being really annoying.
All right, go in. I'm fighting the wrong guy. You're supposed to fight your brothers.
What the hell just happened? I thought you were further away.
Bad angle. Very bad angle. Where's the other one?
Distance man. It's going to kill me every time.
Okay. All right. Come on, bring it on. Let's go. Go fight him. Fight him. Fight him. Hit him.
Hit him again. Hit him again. Good. Let's go. Glass of wine. Come on. Be gentle. Be easy.
It's going to take a little while, but you'll get it. It's okay. All I need is one.
The effects on the screen. Good luck. Jesus, man. You just saw in real time there.
I didn't even do anything. You saw in real time how impossible that is. It's desperate.
What you're about to hear is encouragement and praise with cheering applause just for you.
Acknowledging you for a variety of reasons. I can do this. If there's a situation that
does not apply to you, just listen and see how you feel. So sit back, get ready. Here it
comes. I can only use this once every couple of years because I'm absolutely guaranteed we'll
win. We want to thank you for all your hard work. Then he steps up and gets things done
around him. Deliver what you promise and then you go the extra mile. You're doing a great job.
A great job. If anyone asks, we'll tell them. A great job.
Come on. Cheer me on. Cheer me on. I can't do without you.
Where is he? I need him right now so bad. Ask him here today. We want to tell you that
we have faith in you and we know you can do it. We know you've got everything it takes
to accomplish whatever your heart desires. That dream you're going for. That career you want.
That recognition you're seeking. It is yours. Just listen. Everyone agrees.
You're on your side. Who's on my side? Who is? We believe in you.
We believe. It's impossible. It's actually impossible. No, unplugging doesn't help either.
It's still like this fucked up. It's just like putting, it's just covering your eyes in paint.
Hey, you wanna play the game Dark Souls? Yeah, dude. It sounds like fun. First,
cover your eyes in green paint. Thank you. Thank you for believing in me.
Thank you for a million things. Seriously, thank you for believing in me. I'm gonna go
for it. For your love and your support and your persistence and your patience and your courage.
This is very real right now. When life was the craziest. When I didn't have a clue who I was.
When I kept going down the wrong road. You were always there seeing something in me that I just
couldn't see. And you never gave up hope. You never said good luck. You're on your own.
You've never done that, guys.
I just weren't cheering hard enough last time. That was the problem.
Come on, it's my friend. I'm good. What was the stagger? Come on, man.
He's got a non-LP.
I'm almost there.
It's my turn. It's my turn. It's my turn. I need my cheers.
This is always more than half full. You're smart and you're creative and you're courageous.
You tell the truth. It's too much. It's too much to handle. It's too much to do.
God damn it. Not even cheers to you is gonna make this happen. What level am I?
Fucking 30. All right. Hold on. I get to play binaural beats?
It's too much. It's so hard. You know what I mean? Fuck. But I'm so addicted right now
to beating this boss in first person. I know I can do this. I feel like I'm one of those old
school phone operators where there's like 40 calls going on and I got to unplug Mary talking
to fucking Jacob and plug her into talking to fucking Dan and then Dan is trying to call
fucking Margaret. Unplug Margaret. There's a lot of inputs. What am I even doing right now?
You have to dodge right? I can't dodge right in any Souls game. It never works.
It doesn't matter how much better it will be. I have to dodge left everywhere.
I can't dodge right. This is engraved in my brain. Forward. I can dodge forward.
What do you got? Something? Souls? Why are you fighting this guy? Because I want to like level
up again. And I even went to the desperation. I brought in the cheers to you. You know that.
Like this is a freezer moment right now. The strongest thing in the universe is cheers to you.
And it might be the weapon. No, it's not. Oh yeah. What have I done? What have I done?
I can only bring out cheers to you like once every couple of years and it works.
Not this time. This is when the arc of the story with a hero gets beat and you thought he was
gonna win. Like nobody can beat German 985. Oh yeah, no, yes they can. He got beat.
He was defeated. What are we gonna do? Now we're training for the revenge arc. That's true.
Because I've ran through this whole zone. I thought I was gonna be able to beat him
first try. What an idiotic thing to think. How stupid was that for me to say?
I'm gonna run through a whole zone and then fight the boss in first person.
What an idiotic thing to say. Where am I? Oh god. No, not these guys. Not these guys. No.
Don't curse me. I'll take poison every day of the week.
No, no, no, no, no, no. They're everywhere. I need the redemption arc.
Get a wrist watcher. I got any of your wrist watchers.
How much is one level? Like 2,500? 3,000? Jax is not. Okay, you guys have a seat.
Spoilers for Infinity War. Those of you that don't want to know about Thanos and his
great rise to, you know. Remember in that movie when the Hulk, right? Spoilers. Just turn
your fucking entire house out. Remember in Infinity War, in the Hulk, Jax is not here. I can't get
him. There is no Jax. He doesn't want to come out. We don't even have Jon. We have, we have
I don't have any flasks. I'm not gonna kill him. I've been abandoned by my inner fucking Jax.
Get me out of here. How are you still here? You fucking muppet. I didn't think he could even
come up here. Oh no, it's over. Where am I? I'm just trying to get some. I've done, I've done
a bad thing here. I've fucked it all up. What? Put your knife in my build. This whole thing is
good. I didn't have that much trouble until right now. But that's because this is where
the game actually begins to start to matter. It actually might not be a bad idea
to crystal lizard this shit and get the twinkling titanite and upgrade the fucking other weapons.
Holy shit, that was terrifying in first person. Which way do I know it? Easy, easy.
No, no, no, no. Gamer fatigue. Don't let that set in. You can't let Gamer
Fatigue set in right now. It just almost did. I can feel the energy draining from my fucking
soul. That's not even the right thing I needed. Black knight.
Fucking chest. Oh, I didn't. Please don't. I'm in the middle of my fucking montage.
Get away from me. Fucking out of here. What's going on? Die. I'm ready. No,
that's not what I want. This. Give me a black knight weapon. Game sucks. So short.
Parry the Watchers. It's it's really hard to parry in first person. Oh,
Shadowshow or Twinblade. I just did it. Yeah, but that was because I like just put a bunch of
air into my brain. I just went and just shoved a bunch of air into my brain. These are good,
right? This feels like a VR game. I'm using them. Anything else? All right,
let's go back and level up decks and these. We just had to train leveling decks. Well,
desperate times call for desperate measures and that's called. I gotta be.
Do I even have any titanite shards?
I do. I have a little bit. Okay, this is 108 plus 23. This goes from C to C. I'm doing it.
I'm going for it. I need a few more. Can I buy shards from somebody, right?
Carefully. Who sells them?
Sell everything you got. Start from scratch. I'm in first person already. Don't need them.
I need the ashes. Oh, right. But where is that first ash?
Is it in the swamp? Shit. All right, I'll be back. Like back here. There aren't any more
mods are there? I they're right here. I just I'm so obsessed with this right now.
He's a liar. There aren't actually any mods. No, it's in the poison swamp.
I assure you there are. And once I beat the abyss watchers. Like back here.
If you beat the watchers, I will. I don't care how long it takes.
I will beat the watchers. I don't care how long it takes in first person. If this is
the first ever 24 hour stream, that's what's going to happen. All right. Where the hell am I?
Where's this ash? It's not in here, is it? This is where it just came from, isn't it?
The tower in the swamp. That's the entrance. What the fuck is the tower? Tower?
Oppositely the abyss watchers. It's a huge foot west of that. I should have taken the
other bonfire then. I thought it was going to be a titanite shard. It's near that room
full of slugs. So I should have gone to the other bonfire. You're back from dinner. What
did you miss? Well, you missed a couple of rage moments. Where the hell are you?
Room with the slugs. Room with the slugs. What? This is the room with the slugs right here.
Get away from me. Diagro. Diagro from me. I demand it. Good players can beat this game
five times in the time you play today. But are they playing in first person?
What the heck are you talking about? I made it to the other bonfire, which is probably where
I should have started in the first place. Okay, so from here I need to go... not this way.
Is this fun in first person? No. I'm just kidding. Yes, it is. To the right. Wait,
wait, wait. Also, you gotta remember, when you tell me where to go, there's like a
least of five to ten second delay on the stream. So when I walk and you say go right,
I'm seeing that like ten seconds later. So you talk about like straight and right.
Go left. Like there. Where's the entrance? Don't fucking poison me. Your other left.
Where's the entrance? Oh, that's right. There is an asylum demon up here.
It was there. First person camera. It's hard to see. I thought that was just a bamboo shoot.
The wolf? I'm gonna stab him in his head. How are you supposed to get that? I can't
jump to there. How are you supposed to get that? What the? That doesn't make any sense.
I mean, I can do the tuber voice. My damn will. Please. Okay, wait, wait, wait. This
is the asylum demons up here. Let's kill this motherfucker. What do you say?
I got my double swords. Let's go. The asylum demon's not that hard, although I'll probably
die. About that he spits out meatballs. Really slow swing. This is gonna take forever,
isn't it? I think I have to run when he does that. Yes. Where am I?
Grab him. Don't die to the pinwheel demon. You guys have to understand. My field of view is so
limited. When I get that close, all I see are bird feathers. Increasing the FOV will pull it
back to a point where it looks unnatural and it looks kind of strange. Almost like you're
looking through somebody else's body. Not necessarily. Oh, these are my hands. I can
see my hands and I'm running. It's like the weird VR syndrome where my hands are floating
like 10 feet in front of my face. I'm 32, that's it. Oh, soul's gone.
Did I build the character wrong? Yeah. For a very quick explanation. Judging the distance is
extraordinarily difficult in first person. So I thought very, very brilliantly that I was
gonna use a really long spear type weapon because it would be easier to determine where
I was. Super short record scratch. That was a terrible idea because it don't even matter
anyways. What's happening in forum? Where's that wall? This is an illusory wall. I know
there is. I didn't just read that in chat. No one tell him where. You better tell me.
And there's the ash. Lonely streamer reads in quotes chat. What do you mean in quotes?
Why are you putting chat in quotes? There's a chat here. What? I have to at least beat another
bot. I'm too addicted to first person. I told you. I'm telling you. I'm saying to you. Listen
to me. Are you hearing me? Losing to the asylum demon. It's like I eternal sunshine my brain.
It's great. This is awesome. I'm so glad that I'm losing over and over again. Wake up. I don't
want to wake up. I'd rather stay asleep. How did that? I don't know. He had a fucking scientist
on it. Okay that's better. Locking on is a really awful idea. Not that shit. This hurts
him a lot. I get a bit gritty sometimes. Shit. Just didn't see it. I don't know how far that's
gonna go but far enough apparently. Give me a break. Eat the meatball. I did.
Like three times. You've been laughing just up to six hours. By this point, it's
considerably 24 ounces of water. I'm fine. I drank water on my break. I drank a whole
entire 16 ounce glass. Any of the items up here? I got the ash. I'm ready to continue
the upgrade path. Oh that's where you come in there. I remember the E3 joke.
That seems like six years ago. That was three hours ago. He's reading bot messages.
I'm just homeward boning. I don't care. All right what does the asylum demon have?
This large titanite over there? I'll get it later. Oh fuck. You can get Heval's ring.
I want it. Oh shit I don't have any more souls. I put on some real armor. After I
enforce the flask. Seven seven seven plus two. Here you go. Take the ash.
Tell her where you found it. I feel like I give a shit. All right I'm ready to upgrade.
All right seven seven seven seven seven seven seven seven seven seven seven seven seven
plus two. Your mods are gonna ban us. What? Seven seven seven jackpot. Why is everybody
writing sevens? Chat stop giving him points. He's tricking you. I need souls because I need
to upgrade my new cool weapon that I want to use. Not this dumb not cool weapon. That's
not the one. It's these ones. All right I want my cool weapon to be upgraded. I'm a dumb one.
So I need how many souls do I need? I need 800. I need like 5,000 souls. I just had
it but I got Heval's ring because this is yep yep yep yep yep okay. I need souls.
Stop saying Heval. I have an accent. He doesn't have any mods. Do I need to activate
one of these mods just to prove that I own them? I could sell the embers but unnecessary.
Sell all of them. Now I can get like a thousand right here. These guys alone.
All right and then I'm gonna sell four embers. Who cares. I should be able to upgrade these
twice to plus three. Install a nude mod? For who? I think I have enough to do it once.
All right so this is four to get it to plus two and then I need six to get it to plus
three. You have that's eight. Okay I need I need like 7,000 souls. I don't have any joke weapons.
That's too much to sell. I don't want to sell like six embers.
Just cheat? I can't what do you mean just cheat? I'm not going to use this. I'm certain of it.
What a waste. How many souls do I need to do this one more time? I need. I got it.
All right bingo. Plus three. Let's go. It's time. I got seven estus flasks. I got a new good weapon.
No not the wolf. Who the hell is it? Which one is it? It's which which I don't even
remember where the hell I need to go. It's this one right? Yeah. Time for redemption arc.
We'll see. By the way if you're wondering you I'm doing true glasses of wine which are not even
20% of the glasses full. So you heard me pour that three times. There's not three full glasses
of wine. That's the kind of glass of wine you'll get at a restaurant. Prove it. Here we go.
Let's try it again. And then we get to turn on the funny mods at six plus hours after the
stream has been going. How much damage are we going to do now? 58. Use L1. I am doing L1.
I'm stuck in the corner and it's time to lose it. I can't move. I only leveled up one time.
New mods. New mods. New mods. You suck. If you guys knew. No not if you guys. If some of
you guys knew how hard it was to do this. Maybe you'd be a little nicer. Maybe you
wouldn't have such a mean streak. 120. It's actually not bad. Still probably could use like
another five levels. Bring them on. Let's go. Where's my friend? Fuck. It's just it's
melting my brain how annoying that is. All right let's go. Time to go. Time to go go go go go.
Man. Should have healed. It's just the plane that you're looking at. This makes it
because here okay here's the thing right? So the right stick I have to constantly when I do
this this is me. This is me using the right stick right? So even when I'm locked on right now
that doesn't matter. See I have to always be keeping him in focus with right stick.
It's like scratching your ass scratching your head rubbing your elbows and
fucking patting your tummy at the same time. Like I constantly have to have right stick
moving. Oh shit. Use the steering wheel. Watch out. Watch out. God damn it man. Come on. I
need to hit him one more fucking time. Get out of my way. Got lucky there. Fuck even. Oh shit.
Fucking living hell. I'm gonna come. God. I can't fucking see. I don't even have it on my
why is it not on my hot bar? Of all the things to not have. No sensitivity change will
help either. Just dodge. I wish it was that easy. Try parries. No I gotta just get the
actually I probably should do parries because dodging around a boss is almost
uncompletable. So maybe parries will work. Let's see what we got. Fire.
I don't think I really have much. This is gonna fuck up my rolls. I mean I already have
this on my mid rolling. Equip the embers. This is the worst thing because I've sold
this shitload of them. Like this sucks. See what I'm talking about? See what I mean?
Like that shit happens all the fucking time. There's there's no way to counteract it. He's
just gonna like teleport around and I have to oh I why why haven't explained it? I've
explained it like 30 times already. Not myself. It's time to give up. I'm so close. I gotta
have done like half health and I know what I'm doing is excruciating and is very very very
hard and unnecessary but I'm gonna try to do it. If I pulled out the third person I would beat
this first try. I would put fifty thousand dollars on that. But doesn't matter. I'm gonna
do this. I'm gonna do it the way. I'm gonna do it. It's gonna happen. True wall. It doesn't
seem that hard to me. Stop that. You know it's hard. Don't do that to me. This is
more of the hardest thing I've ever done on stream. Carnage isn't a superhero. What the
fuck? Yes he is. You've done harder things. You can do. I know. I can do it. Don't read
while fighting. I need a little wine. Didn't I say I said this like last stream? No no
no. The stream before that. You know I think I'm gonna take a break from doing
fucking really difficult shit on stream. What happened? It's been two days. I got the guy
behind. Fuck first person mode. Fuck first person mode. It's too much. It's fun for the
first five hours. Put your face cam in one of the item slots. I'm about to. I've lost
it all. This is no way. Not anymore. I'm gonna have to put on the funny mods. This
is just like my tongue is sticking out. Somebody grabbed it. And you just won't
put my, you won't let me put my tongue back in my mouth. That's what I feel
like I'm doing. The like right stick. I gotta keep you in frame the whole fucking
time. Action. Secret show director. Yes will you stay in frame the whole time?
Let me just move you around and make sure it's like oh what that lock on
did this on its own? Let me just like keep you in frame. It's me Stephen fucking
Spielberg. Are you gonna dodge too? Make sure you keep in fucking frame. Make sure
you like keep him in frame the whole time with the right stick. That's the only
way it's fucking possible. I can't do mouse and keyboard. The mod is not designed
to be used with mouse and keyboard. At least for some reason when I do it I have. I'll
show you. I'm like fucking Spielberg this guy. Just switch to IRL and drink wine.
I'm about to. It's gonna turn into a fucking wine drinking stream real quick.
Oh no. It's too fucking hard to do this. If only the lock on would just stay on
and I didn't have to use right stick to constantly keep them in front of me.
I'm about to just start drinking on stream. I need to level up. There's so many things wrong here.
Damn it. I can't help it. I have to do it again. I'm losing my hair watching this stream. I'm
losing my mind playing this stream. You gotta give me a break here. Here comes his fucking
friend. Change the bindings. How would that help? It's still right stick. It's not like it'll
change anything because I wasn't locked on the right guy. Get out of here. Oh nothing to do
with you. Still here. All right I'm not reading chat anymore. I'm gonna focus on the video game.
I got an idea. The distance. The distance. It's hard to tell what the distance is.
I can feel it. I can feel it in my mouth. The saltine crackers that are just building up
and they won't stop. They're in my mouth. This is supposed to be Dark Souls silly
mods night and it turned into the impossible first person challenge somehow over the course
of this evening. What's what is going on? We're going as the invisible fucking man now.
Here it comes. Did anyone even put you up to this challenge? No. I don't know why I continued
to do it. I don't know. I just felt it was fun. I had a great time and I still did. It
was fun and I really enjoyed it. I did. I truly did. But I hit the wall and now it's time to be
the invisible man and I'm gonna beat it first fucking try. I'm gonna beat it as the invisible
fucking man. This is almost as bad. It kind of is. This is not one of the mods I assure you.
Why do I feel like I'm running? Why am I slow? Am I slow? I feel slow. Or am I just
getting like strangely baited by how weird these hands are? I feel like I'm playing
as one of the launchers. I lose as invisible man, aren't I? I can't lose as invisible man.
Somehow this is worse. No, it's not. It really isn't. At least I can lock on.
I don't even know what my character is. This actually might be harder.
Where am I? Fucking invisible man. It's even worse. I told you I was gonna beat it first
fucking try. No, that wasn't a joke. I didn't know. I didn't think he was gonna fucking dash
through. I thought he was gonna do that. I have so much anguish in my body right now.
This is supposed to be a fun stream and I want to fucking, I want to just,
I want to throw this guy into a Joker vat of acid. It was supposed to be a jokey
fun stream and it turned out to be like a tryhard dickhead stream. How did that happen?
That doesn't like to get stuck in a corner, you dick. It's because I've refused it,
but I was having fun. I can't fucking believe it. Like I literally beat it and like I had to just
start talking. This is un-fucking-believable. Even as the invisible goddamn man, like I had it.
It was over. In fact, get this off. I'm so used to like the first person shit. Oh my god,
I'm gonna pee my pants. I don't even care if it's on stream. I'm just gonna stop pissing.
Oh, I'm so sad right now. There's too many emotions in my brain. I have to fucking just
den this. I had it. It was first try third person and I guaranteed it and it was a
guarantee because it actually, I thought it, here we go. No more talking. Beat Abyss Washer.
Fucking the Washer. I can't, I don't think I will. I, you literally came to the arcade
and you took a sludge hammer. You sludge hammered the pinball machine. I am so far
beyond being able to do this. You came in and you just started shaking the pinball machine
and you screamed at it. You put your foot through it. I can't even do it now.
And this boss is not even that hard. It's unbelievable. It's truly un-fucking-believable
that I just let that happen. Abyss Watchers are like the, like the 30% of the way into the
game and I've let first person Parasite attach itself to my fucking cerebral cortex
and it's making me want to punt my monitor 2000 yards. Holy shit people are giving a ton
of community subs. Oh my god. Thank you Great Canadian Fuck Club and Kazzee for the subs.
Somehow I'm still here. I like love this game too. I've beat this game like five
fucking times and we're at that stage of grief now. Where I'm walking around is the
jokey enemy from Warcraft. This is a card in Hearthstone. This is a card in Hearthstone.
It makes your opponent draw a card when he dies. I don't even know what the fuck the thing
is called. Sword card. Dual swords. Where the fuck is the character? I just don't know. I'm
too fucking handsome. I appreciate, I really appreciate all the people giving me tips in
the chat but you have to understand something. I've beat these guys like probably seven or eight
times and it was just like a leisurely playthrough on like my eighth character.
Oh I hate this. I'm so tilted. I'm not even a human anymore. I'm no longer a person. I've
transcended being a human. It might be time to silly mod mode because I am so tilted right
now. I don't think I'll ever beat these guys like ever again. Why can I not see my
character? This would be so much easier if I could. Oh man. You know I sometimes I sit there
and I think about like what's gonna happen on the screen. If you had told me, hey Jeremy
uh on your next stream you're gonna do a Dark Souls mod stream. You're gonna get stuck on
a fist washers for three hours. I'd be like you're something wrong with your rank. Like
there's no way. No way. You're crazy. No fucking way. And here we are. Here we are
in seven hours into the stream. Stuck on the goddamn abyss watchers as invisible man.
Damn. Five flasks. I can't fucking believe this. This build is so bad. Everything about this is
so bad. It was just a first. No why am I still invisible man? I turned it off.
I think I have to restart the whole game. I fucked myself from the very beginning.
All right. All right. Bullshit. Fuck you. Hard to see. Playing like this. No way. I don't believe
it. I don't believe it. No. And there we go. Now I'm a fucking person again. Let's try it now
as an actual person. Let me try it now as a the way the game is supposed to be played.
Not as invisible man. Not as first person mode. What did I just turn on? I have no idea.
I'm so fucking tilted right now. No. It went from like the first four and a half hours
of the stream was. This is fun. This is all fun. I love it. This is a great time.
Oh first person. Let me know. First person is really fun. This is interesting. Look
have you ever seen the game from this perspective before? And now I'm like I should
have just opened up the fast funny mod at four hours. You guys were right. You had the right
idea. You all knew this was going to happen. You knew I was going to get like to like a
boss that you can't do it on and I was going to lose my fucking mind and then here we are.
You guys have the prediction capability of god damn Nostradamus. The first person was
really interesting. It's really fun. It's really hard but sometimes I don't. This
feels very foreign to me. This I don't like how this feels. I'm I don't like this.
It feels weird. This feels fucking weird. It's almost like my character shouldn't be here.
Nobody else feel like that? I might have to take a wine only break here
because everything about the last seven hours has been not this. It's like freaking me out.
What the fuck? I shouldn't be here right now. Actually it's kind of nice to see where I'm
going to get hit. I have to give it one at least solid attempt with an actual character.
Don't blow it here. You got success this time. Just fucking do it. Let's do it. All right.
Let's try it. Let's go. Oops-a-daisy. First fucking time I put on a god damn no invisible
man. No first person bullshit. I beat him first try. That's not that bad of a fight.
I did it first fucking time without the god damn bullshit on it and I've got to see my character
walk around. I just grabbed the bottle of wine. I'm not even drinking out of the glass anymore.
What a sicko. No put that down. Okay that was fun. All I take was just to play Dark Souls.
I just had to play Dark Souls 3 and I did it the first time I played Dark Souls 3.
It's time to get fucking silly okay. You ready for silly? You ready for silly mods?
What time is it? Oh wait we're still early? Is it still early? You still guys ready to go?
Time to get fucking wacky. Why did I do that? Why did I do first person for seven hours?
There's no reason for what I just did. Oh my god. What the fuck is wrong with me?
Something in the water guys. I'm telling you.
Pretty be careful.
All right can I I'm gonna buy these back. All right you ready? I have no idea
what this is gonna do. I'm gonna try it though. Welcome to silly mods. Let's enable this
and see where it takes us. I might have to restart the game. I do. That's what my character
looks like. I don't remember. Restart the game and we're gonna do. There are plenty of other
things but let's be fair. I was having a great time. Even losing. Even getting frustrated. Even
losing my wine mind. It was a lot of fun. So let's go ahead and do this again. Okay open
up that. Dark Souls. Liar and a cheater. God that was my own worst enemy for the last hour
and a half. All right I'm gonna turn uh let's change this to to Dark Souls 3 silly mods.
How about Dark Souls 3 mod night? We just started. Welcome to the stream.
Thanks for joining me. Welcome to the stream. Okay so we've got speed modifier. Well actually
I want to try this one. What the hell this does. I believe this makes every enemy uh a
prop. Well already right up the bat they're just tombstones.
This is gonna be horrible. Yeah this is prop hunt Dark Souls. I just want to see. Let's take a
look. That looks pretty normal so far. Oh I wonder what that is. That's definitely not an
enemy. Can they even attack? Holy shit okay they can. All right I gotta I don't you can't
fight. You can't kill that guy. Why are they all the same thing? They're all just they're all just
fucking tubes. They're just skeleton urns. I don't understand why. There's no other.
I can't walk onto the meter. Oh there's a barrel.
There's too many. This one has eyes.
Mod sucks. What? Let's try another area. I need to see a boss as an urn. Let's head
to the deacons. First person first person first person are no more donations.
Is that one of the big guys? I think that's one of the huge guys.
There's no way to even tell when they're swinging. What's the reason to fight?
This is fucking stupid. I don't want to play this one. All this mod does is say hey you know
those enemies that you fight? You don't know when they're going to do their animation.
Do this and the first person mod. Let's try this with the first person.
Oh hold on. He's addicted to first person. All right here we go. Why is this person not
you shouldn't be here like this. Why are you not a bucket? Who the? Why are you guys not
fucking an enemy object? You're dead. How did you spin around that quickly? Not even fair.
Are these props? It's just an excuse. He wants to play in first person. No those are
NPCs so they have to be free ban for a hundred dollars. What? So does the mod work? Of course it
does. All right that person's a clock. It's a dog. The dogs. I get it. Why is he so fast?
What the hell was that? Why was he that fast? What? I don't know why he was that fast.
Where's the other dog? I saw one already. Just get me in the door. Shit. Next. Put them all on at
once. I will crash the game. I'm just gonna run by. I don't know how many there are but
boxes are just dropping all over me. What is this thing? What is this? Oh it's one of those
exploding bats. They light themselves on fire. They run and they land in front of you and
they blow up. Please do a different mod. Hold on. We've got to get to at least a stopping point
here. Get out of the fucking way. Grandfather clock asshole. Watch out he's gonna explode.
What? Oh right there's a bunch of people here. I'm surrounded. I got the shard. Okay.
All right. All right we're good. I'm not gonna use it. Shut it off. Not yet.
I got to get to the point. You don't want me to get to the point up here and there's like a
hundred skeletons. You think that's gonna be fun? Zero viewers. Please. All right that's the DLC.
Yeah we're gonna go up to the hollow graveyard. You don't want to see that before I turn off
this dumb mod. All right what do you think? Boxes? Clocks? You can't fool me. Is that it?
Is it actually an urn? No. They throw up too. How many more? This was funny for four minutes tops.
Well don't worry. When I get up here we're gonna turn it off. Isn't there a
strong enemy up here? There's an NPC up here right? Ow. Is that it? That's an NPC.
Oh shit. Fucking urn chased me all the way. All right time for a new mod.
What else we got? All right let's take it off first person. Oh boy. Okay let's take it off.
So here's the difference here. What does this one do? This one is supposed to be
player size. I wonder how I don't think I might have to restart this one. What
whatever this one does. What's this one? So this is a speed modifier. This is randomizing
the speed of the game. This is just horrible. This is just lag. I don't want to play like this.
This is terrible. This is playing with 500 ping. Activate all mods at once. I'll do it before we
leave. No I don't like this. I gotta get out of this. All right hold on. Let's try this. I'm
gonna die here. It doesn't matter. Okay what if I do uh let's see like times point five speed.
What does that do? Merciful goddess of the forlorn place to call their own.
Is this my character? Bear witness to our resolve.
Versus bosses? This would be fucking ridiculous. Turn-based combat. But is it just me or is
all the enemies too? I have to fight a boss with this. You can see every frame. I don't think it's
everybody. I think it's just me. Is it? No it's everybody. What? This is I can queue up every
dodge. This is amazing. Wait wait wait don't do it yet. He's gonna jump. What? All right
well that was fun. Let's try this. Oh man. Where? I don't know where. What direction do I go?
Wait hold on. I got an idea. I got an idea. I got an idea. This is gonna be fucking great.
Watch this one. Check this out. Ready? This is gonna be real fucking cool. Okay so I can
control it a little better now. Watch this. Oops. Go back to Andre.
Let me try to get somewhere reliably.
I hate everything about this. This is the worst one yet. No fuck. Now wait wait wait wait.
There's also something else I can do here. Hold on. I need to get in here. You're gonna love
this one. But my weapons. My weapons are still too big. Little like rat mode with huge weapons.
This is normal speed. My hitbox is tiny. First person with this model.
Now hold on. Let me just get to another place to go. Tiny first person mode. Hold on. Gnome
fury warrior. All right I gotta turn my speed down. Hold on. Is it safe? Don't worry he's
not gonna hit me. All right first person. Weapon. Okay here we go. Weapon size.
Uh what are these things called? Are these thrusting swords? What are these?
Are they not curved swords? Daggers? What would these be classified as? Curve swords?
Okay what are they what are they even called? Carthus curve swords? What are they called?
The twin blades right? They're not here. I'm trying to find them. I'm trying to find out
what these are called so I can enable this because they're not I don't see them on any
list. Maybe I can't change them. The fall damage is not significant at all. I don't even
know where I am. I'm okay. I gotta I gotta slow down though. Hold on. Okay player. I gotta
turn down like the stupid mod for speed. That's probably better. And then first person.
Okay well that didn't really work did it? That didn't work.
I'm swinging over this enemy. No I don't. Nice. What the fuck? All right right right.
Okay this is too much. Hold on. I don't know what this does. Green? No skeleton swap. Wait wait
wait wait wait. This is let's let's simmer this down a little bit. Okay come back to normal.
Okay everything's back to normal. Now let's do this. I think this I can be an enemy. Let's go
back to what we were doing. So let's go small. Okay first person. Let's see if we can do it in
first person. Not really. No it doesn't work. Oh that's funky. You can't do small in first
person. It's not gonna work. In fact I think I broke the game. I think it's all fucked up.
Nobody's jiggling around. Oh there we go. All right I'm ready. Let's play. Oh why am I going so
slow? Why am I this slow? That's better right? There we go. All right now I'm gonna do a boss.
Where's the nearest boss? Oh the deacons. Right. I gotta go all the way down for that
though don't I? There's the skeleton king. That's true. Speed it up. The deacons are
gonna be harder at this size. They probably will. What about up here? Not up here? I'm so
cute and tiny. I really just am. Run little buddy. Yeah I got this already. I think I have
to go down here don't I? What? I was too small for the floor.
Change your weapon so you have a Tom and Jerry melon. Well this is the point of the
game where I don't really remember exactly where to go. Go back to Firelink. There's just no
clip to the deacons. I can't do that. I don't think I can even do that. I think I have to
go through here. It's to the right of the cathedral. I'll get down. Hold on. I have
to go around and then I was going the right way wasn't I? Go back to Firelink. What's it
Firelink? Oh Andre. Yeah but I mean who cares? Andre's small so don't you want to see the
deacons? Let me just at least try to get. Okay if I can't do this then I'll go back.
Do a skeleton swap with a normal size character. Well I need like an ID. I need an ID
number. All right is this gonna work? This is not gonna work. I'm in the wall. I need to be
bigger first. All right I'm gonna go the other way. That was the wrong way anyways.
The fall joke returns and I wasn't even trying to do it. I tried to climb back up. Okay so
I'm gonna go through here. I'm trying to just remember where the hell to go for progression.
This way? He's not gonna hit me with this anyway. All right so now uh this way.
Is there a way for me to get up from here? Okay yeah now I remember. Okay I know I remember.
I remember. It's actually fairly hard to control. I'm so small. Put on the Looney Tunes
soundtrack. Don't go that way. Looney Tunes OST. They don't even have an OST. They have
like a theme song. All right we're getting there. Oh fuck! Why do you want Dr. Phil with all
the things right now? All right it's time to make this a little more interesting.
Once I get the shortcut I'm gonna make it interesting. I'm gonna decrease my speed by...
What the fuck just happened? Oh my god I wasn't fighting way enough. What? Oh no that's not
good. Can I speedrun this? I don't think I can. That's so unfortunate. I was right there
too. How slow are these guys? They're very slow. All right so I got the right idea. Oops here we go.
Ready? This should be good. Now we're just cheating. Yeah this is not even a mod at this
point. It's just cheating. You were at the first shortcut literally. I know it sucks.
Just beat the game in an hour? That's a pretty good challenge to me. I'll take that
challenge. I almost fell. Oh fuck. Shortcut! This won't let me. It won't let me. It's just
stopping me. Fucking Jesus we've done this like 50 times. Oh my god just I don't even care. I
don't even need it. Let's go. I don't even need a shortcut at this point. Just get there.
It is late right now. Damn. It's like it's very late for you guys. I'm surprised
there's still this many people here. There's like 34 3500 people here. Holy shit. Thanks for
sticking around guys. Hope you're having a good time. I am. This is just stupid enough to keep
my attention. All right this is a lot. I'm just gonna run right to the deacons. This is
actually making it harder. Don't do that because you're going so fast you can't even
see what's in front of you. All right don't fuck this up again. Just go to the deacons.
I need to beat Dark Souls 3 in an hour. What time is it? All right I have an hour to beat the
whole game. I'll get you real soon. Fuck it. I can fall from this high. Can I? Can I do it?
Yep we're good. This is just cheating. There's no. This is just. Yeah it's a quick silver
mod. It's not even hard. I can just beat everything. All right let's just. That guy
got a shot off. Look at this guy. You motherfucker.
Why don't we make it a little fucking easy. You can everyone say oh you're doing
all your cheater. You're a cheater. Let's see how you feel. Let's see how you feel now.
Where's the deacon? Catch the mouse. Yes. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Oh god. He's too hard to target. Too fast. Too fast. Too fast. It's possible.
Somebody's got fire breath. It's just deacon finfall. All right okay. Okay.
Okay that was fun. This is really funny. Oh that was fun wasn't it? Okay let's change the
player size. That's too big. Uh I don't know why that's still so big. I shouldn't be this
big. It's on my head. Oh my fucking god. I'm gonna lose. And the hunter just became the hunter.
Why can't I hurt these guys? That's the guy. That's the deacon right there.
I can't hurt him. Okay back to normal. Holy fuck. All right let's be the deacon. Oh yeah
what about the one hour challenge? Hold on. Hold on. They sell. They seem a little too slow.
I think it's just because it was so fucked up from everything that happened so far.
All right so the deacons just became. Some of them became chairs. Some of them became statues.
Don't you wish this is what the original fight was? All right where is he?
Who has the glow? Shit. I'm not gonna get cursed. Don't worry.
Oh it is kind of hard to tell when they're gonna do anything.
Holy shit I watched it happen. They're mis-cheating and losing at one of the
easiest boss fights. They're all chairs. Do you understand? I can't lose here though for real.
Imagine losing to a chair and I can't lock on to them. Oh god damn it. What a mess.
What a mess. Die now. Die now. Oh god. Which chair is he? Where was the cursed menu?
Where was the cursed menu? That's the end of the stream. I'm trying skeleton swap.
Model ID. There's like pus of man. Some of these don't work. Player. What are these?
It's like 2000. Doesn't seem to do anything. I would love to be a chair. Model. Because it's
given me IDs but it's not changing to anything. Player model. Cathedral knight.
Oh my god. What is happening? What scarecrow enemy is this? What is going on?
No this is me. It's making my skeleton different. I see. Okay hold on. Let me take. Oh fuck.
This is not good. Let's reload him. Reload player. There we are. So we gotta get off all
this bullshit. Okay. Let's try this again. This time we're gonna do hollow outside a
crystal sage. How do I swing? Can I even attack? I don't think I can attack. Physical
pain. To a passive run. I gotta get back to the god damn deacons like this okay?
I wanna equip the weapon. I can't. Let me see if there's just no animation. I don't think so. Hold
on. Um what the hell is this gonna look like I wonder? It's just a face. That's it. It's
just a face. What about giant rat? Oh what? What is the knife in the back of my head?
The sword is in my skull. What? It's through my fucking face. Oh come on. This is the
stupidest thing ever. I didn't even get the deacon shortcut either. I can't even. No no
no no no no. Can I drink? I can't even drink estus. Oh that's so ridiculous. Hold on let me
just see if I can. Maybe animation override maybe. I need to be able to attack. Uh which
way is the head? Is that a foot up top? I think that's a foot up there. But I still
can't swing a weapon. Let me see. Okay we've got angel, tree hollow, dancer. Here's dancer. Uh oh
that crashed again. Game crashed. Phone's over. Unequip the weapons. Yeah the fun is over.
No that doesn't look right. I thought I just got banned. I was like oh no that's not good.
Alright let's go ahead and try this again. I'm gonna take off my weapons though.
Banned from single player. I don't know. Alright weapons are off. I just have fists. I have no
equipment on. Nothing. Get rid of all equipment. See if I can do anything now. Skeleton swap.
Let's give it a go. So we got dancer. We can't do dancer. Let's try tree hollow.
It's just an extra large foot. Some of them just crashed the game. Yeah that's what he
just said. Parade float. Oh that was good. It was really good. So this is not gonna work.
What else we got? Painter, ice crab, cinder. Here's yorm. Yorm's gonna crash the game.
I would put money on it. No it's not. I'm coming. I'm coming to get you lord of cinder.
God he fell. He fell one foot. Yeah I know. Alright let's see a few more of these and then I'm
probably gonna call it a night. It's been a long night of absolute bullshit. Pontiff.
Animation override. I wonder what this means. Half the stream was you dying to abyss watchers.
Well sometimes that's what happens. You have to bind the animations in order to use attacks.
Really? Hmm. Oh this is gonna crash the stream. Is it? This is the great way. This is the tree.
But wait. We can see the whole thing. Hold on. Come on. I can't make myself smaller.
I can't. I wish I could see. I can't get out of the door. This is just a big piece of wood.
It's a shovel. Did I kill somebody? No that's not what I think it is right?
No it isn't. That's a leg. We just almost got to see the head. Can you see my head up there?
Look at how tiny the head is. Look at the shadow. Pinhead. Alright let's try like one or two more
and then I'm gonna call it. This is a deacon. That's not too crazy. Do the crab? Okay we'll
do crab. Crab. Did you hear this? Uh where's the crab? Uh giant crab there in the face.
You can hear the legs too. Did you force animation override? I did.
I have that on right now. It's a new emote. I don't think so. It's too scary.
No we already did the dog. Stray demon. This one will be interesting.
Really? I can't even walk by this guy? You're not making it easy.
Kick him off. Kick. Do an emote. Can you do mid-ear? It doesn't look like a lot of
bosses are on here. Let me see. Last one crashed the game pretty hard so I killed
that guy by jumping on him. Let's see if mid-ear is here. Mid-ear. Mimic is on here somehow.
That's scary. That's really scary. Crystal lizard. Let's see if we can find mid-ear.
Oh here's vort. Here's a boss. Well I should be able to make it to the deacons like this.
The same bridge. It's too hard to cross it. There's too much going on. You can't go over that
bridge. What? Why did I become a fucking ant? That's way less intimidating. Tree frog. Okay
reload. Let's do. Okay there's vort. A few more. Let's see. Great wolf. Oh here's ice crab.
Maybe this will look better. That's a crash. Fuck. All right I think that's probably a good
place to call it. Boo boo boo. Do the skeleton. Maybe like I'll do like a watch your ears.
It's gonna be love. Andre with speed on max. There are seven hours of first person. Well
to be fair this stream was titled first person dark souls 3. All right so let's
we're normal here. Let's go ahead and activate it again. Is there anything it didn't do? Skeleton
swap. Jojo mod. What the hell is Jojo mod? What did I just do? What did I just become?
What am I? What happened? What the fuck is? I'm like a little burnt turd. Oh that didn't
do anything. Let me try that again. I have the tiny mod. No all the mods have been refreshed.
Okay enable. What the fuck I did? The game is just imploding. Die to reset
tiny. Well what are these? Like a fire startup? Pet cemetery. Come on get outside quick. Well
we're seeing my persona. Get out there come on. Go. Do I really have to make the speed
faster? That's not what I wanted. Oh I almost made everybody throw up including myself.
I think I crashed it. Damn it. No I think I'm all right. No it's crashed. Shit I did
negative. I did upside down mode somehow. Yeah this thing's fucked up. All right that's
gonna be it guys. Thanks for watching dark souls 3 first person and uh extra just cheating.
Thanks for watching the guy plays first person dark souls 3 then cheats for an hour.
You've got all the mods at once. You know what I'll give it to you. I'm gonna give you all the
mods at once and I'm gonna try to beat the game. Let's give it a whirl. Fall joke incoming
that would be nice if uh if I wasn't gonna give myself impossible to die hp. Uh no it's
it's opening. We're good. This guy is addicted to dark souls. No I was addicted to
the first person watchers. Two week video game bender. All right it's time to activate
everything at once. It's 2 a.m. It's midnight pacific which means it is very late for
everybody else. All right first person cam activate. Also size modifier activate.
Oh that just makes okay never mind. Speed modifier activate. How fast? That's way too
fast. Okay looks good. Lighting modifier. Oh we're going with this one. Whatever
okay no not that one. That just makes the whole thing dark. To make it really dark.
I don't want to do that. Brightness. Oh there's a glow. What the hell does glow do?
This makes everything glowy. I don't understand what this one does.
Now that's just your eyes hurt simulator. Just more bloom. All right we've got uh
first pro. Okay that that's we pretty much got everything. Aggression mod is on.
So that's on. They all are going to have red eyes apparently. I'm not turning on upside down
mode. Everybody's barrel. No that one sucks. Uh what else? Speed. Manual control. What is
going on? Why did I die? What did I turn on? It's the aggression mod. Okay he just came.
All right well let's go. I'm ready. You ready? You ready for me to beat the game in 20 minutes?
Let's go. Faster. I can't go faster. I end up in a wall somewhere. Faster. Faster. I can
probably do it faster. Hold on to your hats. Uh if you're motion if you get motion sick
very easily I'm gonna warn you right now. You're gonna puke. You will throw up from this.
So just be careful. You know minimize the window like a little bit if you need to.
Uh speed modifier. There it is. What's wrong with this guy?
Here we go. Time to fucking puke. I'm gonna beat the whole game without stopping moving.
What is that? Oh it's okay it's those guys. Okay that guy is still on fire and he's still
running over here. Stop. No I didn't. I just turned. Let's go. It's because my character is
two feet tall. He's stuffed. You need to restart. This is taking too long. It's because it's the
deacons. Okay okay go go go go go go. I don't know where to go. I have no idea. I feel bad
for anybody that's coming to the stream that has never seen this game before.
They're probably just like thanks for ruining the whole game. How did I get these spells on
my character? I didn't know if the speed or something was gonna fuck up and not let me
out. The game just that's it. That's goodbye. Game crashed for real. This is skip. I just
didn't know if I could just whatever. That's it. Oh that was mentally draining. That was a lot
of fun but holy shit that was just too much stimulation and too much abyss watchers. Too
much first person. That was a lot of fun but those of you that are still around we're
gonna do the bits. That was Dark Souls 3 with some mods. The challenge mods more specifically.
And I will see you guys. I'm not gonna be live tomorrow. Well tomorrow as in today because
it's currently 12 30 am on Sunday. So no stream on Sunday. I will be back and we will do
we're gonna finally do some Dreamcast stuff on Monday or I might do Lifeline.
This is so many options. There's so many fun fucking things to do. And then 23rd we've got the
duct tape goalie stream. Shenmue oh I got this too many things. But thanks for joining me. See
you guys next time. And we're gonna go back and do the bits from eight and a half hours
stream. I wonder how much of it was actually on the abyss watchers. Probably at least two
hours. Rift Dogma? No we'll go back to that. I will absolutely go back to Dragon's Dogma.
So let's uh let's rifle through these bits. Manboy thanks for the one dollar. He's trying to
get ahold of Shido but he's blocked my phone calls. I'm sorry to hear that. He didn't have
his cell phone. I don't know where he got it. Timmy Timtan thanks for the one dollar.
Binary Man thanks for the five dollars. Hey Jeremy here's a music video I made for you.
This file has been scanned with binary anti gnome system. No gnomes have been detected.
Somebody's falling down on a scooter. I have no idea what that is. But thank you for the uh
video nonetheless. Thank you with five dollars Binary Man. Thank you for not gnoming me although
I'm not sure what that was. Alec thanks for the one dollar. Dark Souls 3 was my first Dark
Souls game and it's also my favorite one. It's very good. Hey Binary Man thanks for the
five dollars. Hey it's me again not a music video but haha anyways. Is it gonna be a gnome probably?
Because you said it wasn't a gnome last time. It's a bunch of farts okay. Thank you for the
five dollars Binary Man. Thank you Alec for the one dollars. The one dollars. Bake me home thanks
for the one dollar. Sly 161 thanks for the one dollar. Did you know that it's been almost
three years since your first Dark Souls 3 stream? I think you played it in like March
or April of 2016. It has been a long time. It is a great game. Thank you Divus for the two dollars.
Breambin thank you for the eleven dollars and fifty cents. Are you the streamer that beat
the Simpsons hit and run on stream? I am. I am that guy. Have a wear that. Badge on my sleeve.
I stole your urinal idea already. That's not even it. But thank you for the nearly 12 dollars
Breambin. Hey Pin thanks for the one dollar. Action wheel we meet again Jeremy. Action wheel.
Hey Jack thanks for the one dollar. Keldos thanks for the one dollar.
Smell the... I'm not even gonna read that. Thank you Freudian Weapon for the ten dollars.
I need to clear the air since I wasn't around to defend myself last night.
I don't think Shito is a bad character. I think he's great. I've been framed. I'm an
innocent man I tell you. You've got to believe me. I can't live my life on the run.
No you never said anything bad about Shito. We were just kidding around.
Thank you for the ten dollars. Shito has no ill will there. Don't worry.
Freudian Weapon thank you. Thank you Dr. Epic Frag for the one dollar.
Tri-Finger in... yep thank you. Hey Future Gamer thanks for the one dollar.
There's a VR version for the first person mod. There is a VR version for the first person
mod. How would you even... oh that would be so horrible. Hey Bitslave thanks for the one
dollar. Jeremy it's my birthday tomorrow. I'm drunk drinking with my airmen. Eat my... why would
you write this? Eat my... I think they say you're a cool man. Thank you. C4G thanks for the one
dollar. Mercy wing. German moon. Mercy wing. Seems pretty good. The Shrub Man thanks for the
fifteen dollar Shrub Man. No message just cheer. Fifteen hundred bits. Thank you so much.
Fifteen dollars. Thank you Bitslave again for the one dollar. Check this picture out.
Uh thank you. No message. What a guy. No no I'm just saying like thank you for the fifteen dollars.
It's a lot of money. What is it? It's a picture of... he's got like a perhaps blue ribbon
24 pack on his head. I don't know. I'm not gonna... if you want to share that image you
can. I don't want to share that. Uh thank you Mitsukitty for the five dollars. Message
deleted. Not just kidding. Loving the stream. Take some bitty booze. Thank you
Kitty. Thank you so much for the five dollars. Scully P. Scully P gave a shitload of subs.
Seabare gave a bunch of community subs. You guys are fucking awesome. Thank you.
There's so many of you guys are major community subcontributions contributors.
It's ridiculous. Shocking some of the numbers you guys have. Thank you Nobe for the three
dollars and 33 cents. Praise the German sun sometimes. Thank you Double D for the one
dollar. Is this a streamer that didn't beat Madeer? I didn't. But I also had three other
friends come and help me and they couldn't beat him either. You saw that stream. Hey meme machine
thanks for the four dollars meme machine. Tingy thanks for one dollar. Can I get a large soda
too stupid? Hey welcome to McDonald's how can I help you? Hey yeah um could you make me a
number one with uh large fry idiot? Well I thank you Tingy. Thank you Tingy for the one
dollar. What if I were to go to McDonald's drive-thru and use your voice from the clip
I shared to make my order? Would that be okay? No that would never be okay.
Thank you for the dollar 23 quick rhyme. Just tuned in. This is incredible. It was very
interesting. It was a lot of fun and then I hit the wall. I can't wait to see all the
comments. When I hit the wall everybody telling me Jerma take a break. Jerma you're losing
your mind. Jerma come on man like do something else. I know that's gonna happen and it's
coming. Uh thank you though quick rhyme for the dollar 23. Thank you to uncouth badger
for the one dollar. Thank you. Thank you dork cube for the one dollar. My automaton came
in yesterday and I've decided in honor of Shito to name him Nito. Nito. That's a pretty
good name. Uh docking with friends thanks to the two dollars. Smelly boy thanks to the one
dollar. Proof of Shito now. Shito doesn't move. Shito's always in the same spot sleeping.
A Sharplian. Sharplion thanks for the 13 dollars. Hey Jeremy just want to say you're my favorite
YouTuber and probably the only one who consistently makes me laugh even when I'm down. Thanks for
being a hunk in game and in real life. Sneak man for Germania 2019. Thank you so
much Sharplion. I'm honored to be your favorite YouTuber. Although I don't necessarily
make a bunch of YouTube videos anymore. Still surprisingly people still say that same thing.
It's very very humbling to me. I'm I'm fucking honored. Thank you. All these years later.
Double D thanks for the one dollar. Please stop swearing. I'm gonna be grounded for like a
month if you keep this up. I'm using my family computer by the way. Also do you want to come
over to my house for a sleepover and play Minecraft? My mom says we can stay up until
10. Thank you Freudian weapon for the one dollar. Sad Vega thanks for the one dollar.
Jeremy you're such a good chuckle to watch as always. Really glad you put up with our shit
posting. The fact you read all these bit donations off at the end is crazy. I almost wonder if I
could buy like a hundred dollars worth of bits and make you read off the start of a novel.
You may not want to read that part. Someone may actually do it. Don't do that. Too chunky
to eat thanks for the 10 dollars. Too chunky. Yo Jeremy just like you know, just like you
to know that you're amazing and lighting up my day with your streams. 10 dollars. Just a very
very nice wonderful thing to say to somebody. Thank you so much too chunky. It means a lot.
Thank you. Thank you the Jewish bro for the one dollar. Could you play Fallout 3 modded?
Maybe. Maybe but I need to I need to like just relax and play putt putt bizarre adventure.
Hey FGW thanks for the one dollar. Jerma thank god it's you. He has my family.
Don't read this. He's gonna make them die to pinwheel on stream. Whatever.
What? Mandum requiem thanks for the two dollars. Freudian weapon thanks for the two dollars.
Chicken foot thanks for the one dollar. Pogchamp is calling the McDonald's dry through.
Clerk a waifu or an idiot the official Jerma985 challenge.
No don't do that. Don't. I was telling you not to do that because of how ridiculous it would be
to even remotely attempt to do that. That I don't want that to beat. That's not the
Jerma985 challenge. You know what the Jerma985 challenge would be? When you get your food at
the window give him a five dollar bill as a tip. How's that for a challenge? What if
they don't accept tips? Then you go oh well. Are you sure? Okay well and then you grab your
food and drive. Hey thank you over dramatic toast for the five dollars. Hey Jerma just
want to give some bits for all the laughs you've given my friends and I for the last seven
years. From tf2 commentaries to Jerma rumbles thanks man we're all lucky to have you. PS give
my bestie Nick and Johnny a good beer.
Fucking baby beer. Baby beer peed his diaper. Thank you over dramatic toast for the five
dollars. Thank you man. Dragora root for the five dollars and two cents. They just say pride
502. Thank you. P joke. He said P. He said P and diaper. Cross it off the list of things I say
every stream. Hey Garfield the Monday killer thanks for the one dollar. Hey there Jerma listen up.
It's Garfagraph time. Bring all your pups. I'm talking Otto Youngsoy and Francis too. He's
the first member of the GK crew. GK Garfy Kong. Garfy Kong is here. He's got no style.
He's got no grace. This dog's got a funny face. He can float real high and jump from
trees. He eats dog food and kicks bad guys knees. He's Odie. Odie and Odie too. He's the
second member of the GK crew. Huh I rapped too long and now there's no more Garfagraph left.
Oops. Thank you Garfield the Monday killer. Door cube thanks for the one dollar. We all know
that the Abyss Watchers are tough but we know you can do it and if anybody asks us
they'll tell them what a great job you're doing. You hear that? A great job. I didn't
do it though on first person. I did it in regular mode. Not even the power of a great
job could help. I may as well have been sitting upside down at that last point when I tried it on
invisible man mode. I was upside down. I was hanging upside down. Hey Jules thanks for the
three dollars. Hey Jeremy yesterday you answered my question saying that your favorite super
villain is Thanos and that your favorite superhero is Carnage. I couldn't find anything
from the internet that Carnage was a superhero at one point. Can you enlighten me? Thanks man.
No I said Carnage was my favorite super person. Superhero probably Spider-Man.
Just probably would be. Hey Pugatron thanks for the 15 dollars. There's no message here but
thank you for 15 dollars. It's a lot of fucking money. Some of you guys give 15 dollars almost
every single stream and it adds up to a lot of money. Thank you. Palasonic thanks for the
one dollar. Hey Jeremy last April you gave some advice on stream of getting out of a
dark place by making other people happy that really resonated with me. I've always wanted to
be an EMT or something like that so I joined the army as a combat medic. I finished up all
my training helping people and seeing how proud and happy my family is is the best feeling.
Thank you for that advice. It changed my life. That is fucking wonderful to hear.
Absolutely wonderful. If anything that I say can help you out. That's that's life changing
for me. It blows me away. Thank you so much for being around. If the stuff that I say can help
you out in your life. I mean I'm no professional. I'm not qualified to really give advice
but it does feel good to know that somebody's happier because of it. So
I'm glad you're doing good. Thank you. For real. Good luck to you. Much luck to you.
Here here I still got like a little bit of wine in this glass. Cheers. Cheers to you. Hey Tingy
thanks for the one dollar. Jeremy your doctor calling is worried about you. You should really
take a break from games that boil your blood. It's not good for your heart. Remember that you
have a pacemaker. Jeremy old. I told you it was coming. Hey FGW thanks for the five dollars.
Oh Jeremy I forgot to tell you Twitch ended up refunding my bits that I got mistakenly
charged for and you got to keep the money according to the email. Well that's I'm glad
that they did that. I'm glad you got your money back. Also I'm a red bits badge now and it's been
worth every penny. Sorry Avis Watchers gave you so much trouble. My grandfather had a rough time
with that boss too. Just messing around you the best. Thank you FGW. I did it the first
the first time when I had no invisibility and no first person. I did it the first time
I went in there. I'm so I'm so itchy knowing that I didn't beat that in first person.
It was I was locked in. I had to beat it in first person and then I lost all control. Well
not really. I was it was still fun. I wouldn't have kept going in there if it wasn't. But
thank you NotVega for the five dollars. Just pogchamp. Sir Tardigrad thanks for the one
dollar. Hey Jerma today my friends all made plans to smash.
Hey Jerma today my friends all made plans to play smash.
I'm sorry. I'm fucking stupid. Hey Jerma today my friends all made plans to play smash
and hang out without me. Feels bad but fuck them anyway. Great to get
home and see you playing one of my favorite games. Why why would they do that?
What what's up with that? Why'd they do that? Is it a wait hold on is it a scenario where
you're really damn good? Like they're all playing fucks because they heard it was good
and you're playing this like Olimar and just stomping them. Yeah but if that people don't
want to play a game with you and hang out with you that's that's not fucking cool man. Is
Olimar top tier into ultimate? Really? Maybe I'm too good. I do stomp. Well um I would say
we're glad to have you. Glad to have you watch me uh have a fucking stream meltdown
at first person to this watchers for like an hour and a half. But for real if uh if people
want to exclude you from playing a game and hanging out with them for some reason
maybe reconsider who they are. Maybe reconsider some friendships because that's the that doesn't
seem very very cool. But I wish you luck. Thank you. Thank you suspicious lettuce for
the ten dollars. It's nice to see some of your stream. It's always a treat in Europe.
Thank you suspicious lettuce for the ten dollars and the European message. Doomed RS thanks for
three dollars you brought up Andre at max speed but he didn't make the cut so I felt obligated
to direct you to this work of video art. You're going to love this. Trust me. What you're
seeing now is my normal state. This is what is known as a super saiyan that has ascended
past a super saiyan and that's why there we are. Too bad I thought you guys wanted me to fight
him. Hey plastic glue thanks for the one dollar. Tingy for one dollar. Baby bf for germa rumble.
Maybe I don't think so. Doomed RS thanks for the one dollar. Put a link in my last donation
but a nightbot killed it since I wasn't subbed. I'm a subscriber now. Welcome to the subs.
Anyway you mentioned Andre at max speed. Oh we got it. No we got it. We did get it
because I get to save on I get to save every message that comes through.
Please link. Here's the link. Thank you doomed for the two dollars. And finally Iammonk thanks
for the one dollar. I'm trying to get over being an alcoholic and your streams and
community is something I can't get through with this without. I love you all. Germahart.
Good luck. Keep your head up. That's the wrong link. What is that a link to?
I fucked it up. Whatever. But Iammonk you get all the support in the world from
me and this community. Take care of yourself. One step at a time. Good luck.
You got a whole community here. Thank you for the one dollar and thanks for being around.
Finally finally clueless sniper with one dollar at the very end. Thank you clueless sniper.
And it wouldn't be the end of a stream without the credits so let's see
all those subs flying on by. Finish the stream with an English lesson of course we will.
We eat a lot. Did you see my car keys? They're on top of the tv. You're right. Thanks.
Where are you going? To the supermarket. Again? Yes we eat a lot. Do you want me to go with
you? Sure if you can. Good. The packages will be heavy. There is a new health store right
up the road. Maybe since you guys eat a lot you should try and eat more healthily.
Maybe you're right. We have all put on a little weight. Who puts their keys on? I know why would
you put your keys on top of the tv? But there's there was a lot of people here. There was almost
four thousand people here up until about midnight pacific time. Thanks for sticking around.
The stream has fucking grown so much I can't even believe it. Looking over at like 11 30
12 o'clock pacific time and seeing a number like four thousand. It's it's crazy to me.
Thank you guys and I will see you all again really soon. Specifically on Monday for either
for either Lifeline for PlayStation 2 which is a microphone controlled game
or Back to Dragon's Dogma or Dreamcast or it's pretty much it. He will continue to push
Dreamcast. Dreamcast has been in the work since Monster Hunter 3's stream. I've
I've owned it since the Monster Hunter 3 streams but I run into some nonsense with it.
I talked about it last stream but we'll bring it up while the credits play out here.
Dreamcast games are insanely expensive. They're very rare and a lot of the good ones are
somewhere around 100 bucks each. All the classic games have been ported to PC
and on top of that there is emulation but emulators are very unreliable. So capturing
an emulator and playing it on Dreamcast emulator is really not ideal. Did you get Power Stone? I do
have Power Stone. I got a couple of the really really good interesting survival horror games
that were only on Dreamcast. Power Stone, Dynamite Cop which is one of my favorite arcade
games ever. There are there are some options but stuff like Shenmue and Crazy Taxi and
Space Channel 5 they're all on PC. Shenmue and Shenmue 2 got ported to PC not even
like six months ago. So it's like eh do you spend a bunch of money on the Dreamcast version
that's not even in 1080 720p or get the updated ported PC one and play that instead?
But that's gonna be it. Thank you for joining me. I had a lot of fun as much as I went into
pure fucking streamer meltdown mode. I didn't. I didn't. I still was having a good time even
though I was talking about how how hard it was. I still had a lot of fun. You guys rock. See you
guys on Monday. Have a great rest of your weekend. Take care of yourselves. See you very soon.