Hey, what is happening everybody? Hope you're having a fantastic day so far. My name is
Germa if you didn't already know that. We're gonna be playing some Team Fortress 2 gameplay
commentary. What a different intro. Usually I have the same intro the whole day. That
was a weird intro. Anyways, gonna be playing as the medic tonight and we're gonna specifically
be talking about a couple of points, mainly the big debate between should I throw the
quick fix into the toilet and hit the flush button? And the answer to that question is
no, because the quick fix won't fit in the toilet. So if you try and flush it, it won't
go anywhere. And because it's actually worth something. A lot of people like to trash this
weapon or this item, whatever you want to call it. People like to really call this the
worst medigun. It's not even worth equipping, et cetera, et cetera. And I don't necessarily
agree with that. There's a ton of situations, and I'm gonna really detail one of them in
this video, where you really do need the quick fix. And it's a big deal. And a lot of people
really overlook this fact. And it's something you really have to take into consideration.
So when you're on a team of, let's say just Valve's default, Valve says 12 on 12 is what
we want Team Fortress to be. That's what it's gonna be. So 12 on 12, if there's one medic
on the team, even if there's one medic on the, let me rephrase that, if there is even
one person healing on the team, it's a lot to deal with. Especially when you're in a
game where there's a lot of damage going around. As you'll see in this gameplay, there's
a lot of people taking damage. A lot of people are getting killed. A lot of people are flying
back and forth. Especially, this is like a very small, dense map. King of the Hill maps
are the same way. This is Capture the Flag, by the way. I didn't even tell you the map.
Capture the Flag Turbine. And it's a very condensed map. So there's people all over
the place. And with the default medigun or the Kritzkrieg, you're talking about a slower
heal rate and you're talking about overheal. So you have to put the medigun on somebody
for a lot longer than you would with the quick fix. And let's just say for the sake of argument,
the one medic on that team, if he wasn't there, you wouldn't be getting any overheal anyways.
So the overheal argument is true. I totally agree with the fact that overheal is incredibly
necessary. It's a really big part of the game. But if there's a medic on the team healing
people, he's still doing work. He's still doing his job. It's not like he's sitting AFK in
the spawn or something like that. He's still healing. And it's really, really much easier
when you play with the quick fix if you are one person on a team to keep everybody healed.
It's very difficult. I can't tell you how many situations I've been in when I have not
been using the quick fix and we're turning a corner and there's five people that need
to be healed and I have the regular medigun and I'm just like, I'm sorry, three or four
you are going to die. There's nothing I can do about that. So what you're really watching
on the screen right now is you're watching me play with the quick fix and then you're
watching me play with the default medigun and they're both in very, very similar situations
and I'm going to freeze it here coming up in a second. I'm going to show you that exact
situation I'm talking about where you get into trouble with the regular medigun and
you get yourself killed. Okay, so let's transition to the regular medigun here and take a look.
I'm going to freeze it. There are one, two, three, four, four people here that need to
be healed, all of them which are on fire or at least the two that can be on fire and
I can't heal them. I can try and put it on them for a second but they're still taking
so much damage and if I had had the quick fix, say, take a look at this pyro, I probably
could have filled him up by now but no, a pyro comes from behind us, gets me lit on
fire and this scout I pull out the needle gun probably should have switched to the medigun.
I thought I had the blutsauger for a second but I did not. But as you can see, this situation
turns out very, very badly and I run for the hell that I do not make it. So that's
exactly what I'm talking about. Those group situations where you need to really spread
the heals around when a ton of people are taking damage and there's really nothing
you can do about it. That's where the quick fix is definitely a huge plus and a huge definitely
one up on the other two mediguns. Now, there's a century around this corner and I'm going
to show you a reason why you need to switch sometimes. There is nothing that is more power
full than an ubered class. So obviously, you can't really take out a big sentry nest with
the quick fix. Sometimes you can. Sometimes there's a few situations where you can uber
a heavy or quick fix a heavy and you can get the job done with the quick fix. But with
any other situation, you really do need an uber to push into a room like this and that's
what I suggest. Once you get to the point where you go, okay, there's a sentry in that
room, we have to do something about it. That's when you take out the regular medigun, leave
the critskrieg in its closet for now because as we all know, crits do no extra damage to
buildings. So if you get critskrieg, if you're a soldier, you're still going to do normal
soldier rocket damage to those buildings. But the quick fix is for, let me try and put
this this way. If you are one medic on a team, like I said, the quick fix is the medigun
to use when you're having trouble, when you're trying to keep people alive, they won't stay
alive. The quick fix is the medigun to use in those situations. It's very situational,
yes, but it's not bad. It is not terrible and if there's a medic on your team using
it, try not to bash him and tell him, hey, twitch to a better medigun because really
he might be just trying to solve that situational problem. So just have fun with whatever item
you want to play with, whether that be medic or whether that be pyro, demo man, anything.
There really is no perfect loadout. That's why they add so many of these items into the
game. So just have fun, I guess is my real point of this whole spiel. Spiel, I love that
word. So anyways, guys, this is going to be the end of the video. Thank you so much for
watching. I really do appreciate it and I'll see you guys all soon. So take care, everybody.