Can you hear me? All right. Good afternoon, everybody. How are you? How are you?
Oh, early. No, I am. I'm a full hour late. And one could even argue I'm two days late.
But I'm here. I am now officially fully vaccinated. So I hope I don't have any side effects in the
middle of the stream. That's kind of why I said it's going to be maybe three hours.
Because we'll see. I'm anxiously anticipating what that's going to look like.
What'd you say about my testicles? Fully vaccinated. I don't know. You said something
about like my testicles after being vaccinated. I don't know. I have no idea what you meant by that.
I didn't even read the whole thing. Remember just pretend that the vaccine is the reason you're
acting zonked. Yeah, I have a few things to talk about. Well, one in particular.
Thursday. Well, let's just wait, wait, wait, wait, we got to wait. Did I even tweet anything? I
didn't tweet anything. Hold on. Give me a second. Let me tweet something. Be right back. So today,
this is going to be the last. This is going to be the last day of VR for a little while.
I have to put this in a box for a little bit. Some of you probably have known by the amount
of times I have taken in between these days. VR seems to royally fuck me up. Something about
holding my arms up for more than a few hours. Even with the brace on, it just fucking annihilates
me. So we're going to put it away for a little while. I'm probably going to do more seated VR
in the future. I'm not going to do seated VR today because the whole goddamn living room has
been cleared. And like this would have been a waste of time if I didn't utilize the living
room space. And I mean, I'll be fine. I got my brace on. I'll be all right. But let's talk about
some announcements. This Thursday, so in a couple days, Ludwig and I are going to be hosting a
battleship tournament, which we will be participating in as well. I'm not going to make any bets.
If I lose, I'm just going to fucking walk away and lose. We're not adding anything. I'm not doing
anything. No, if I'm out, I'm just out of the tournament. That's it. So that's going to be on
Ludwig's channel. I'll be hosting him and I'll be part of the commentator team.
And then this weekend on Sunday, you don't want to miss that one. I just want to let you know ahead
of time. I'm going to be making a very, very large announcement on Sunday. So if there's a stream
that you might want to participate in, at least for a little while, is the announcement of the
announcement stream. Here it is. That's on the 1st. It's not Catboy. Nope. Oh no, it is not Catboy.
Just wait until you fucking know what that is. It's not Catboy. No, it's not. Trust me. This is
something. Whatever. I'll see you on Sunday. We'll be back actually sitting down at the chair.
Regular setup. But I think we can go here. I don't need to delay anymore. I've already
delayed enough. In the event that I start to get like a massive headache or something from this
vaccine, I'm just going to run away. I'm going to be like, guys, bye. And I'm going to immediately
lie down. I'm going to do like the Undertaker in my bed. I'm just going to lie down and just stay
straight. Let's turn the camera on. What do you say? This is Medal of Honor Andy.
What? The name of the game is Medal of Honor Andy. I hope you guys are ready. They may as well.
Honest to God, seriously, at this point, like you may, what am I connected to here? Medal of
Honor Andy is the name of this game, I guess. All right. Can you guys hear it? Is a good sound for
you? Does it sound good? Because I'm ready to go. This is the, this is the one I remember like E3,
maybe two E3s ago or last E3 from last year. I remember seeing this game being announced and
I was like, holy shit, I can't wait to play this. So I'm actually pretty excited to play this game.
Should I be excited? This game sucks, by the way. Glad that's the first thing that I read.
All right, let's go. Here we go. Medal of Honor Andy. Am I in the right place? Why is it? I haven't
turned around that many times, have I? Oh my God, that just scared the shit out of me.
I feel pretty good. Do you not know what this is? This is universal for I'm doing just fine.
Okay. Am I supposed to be sitting down? Oh shit. Grab the pistol and shoot. Who, you?
I feel great, captain.
Watch out.
Is that Harry Potter? Grab the pistol and shoot. Look out. There's a bad guy.
It's gonna, it's gonna take me like a half an hour to get out of this fucking tutorial.
All right, I promise I won't do it again. I'm not going to do it again. Why can you do that?
Um, got him. I'm putting it down. Why can you do that? What? Where did that guy even come from?
Was that guy flying? That guy was in like a, one of those squirrel suits. Get that. I don't, don't,
hey, he's like pointing at my head. He was up. No, where was he? I love how my head is just in here.
All the way. I gotta do. Good morning, Lieutenant. Welcome back to the land. You've been through a
lot. So I'll keep it brief. I'm with the office of strategic services. Our mission is subversion
and everything in between. How's the audio? Can you hear it? We're taking the fight to the Nazis.
Can't hear it. There you go. We do some of the most dangerous work of the war. We're looking
for people just like you. Can I have that hat? Now the sergeant and I go way back.
They're like all around me. It's weird. What you did in Tunisia. He's nominated you for the
medal of honor. Trust me, Lieutenant. I hate doing paperwork, but in your case, I'm in an exception.
You saved our lives. You're welcome. Thank you. You guys did good too. Life is usually a pageant of
idiots and fools, but occasionally you find yourself in the company of good people
and then anything is possible. Lieutenant, you are now going to hear the most important question
I can ask. Would you like to join the OSS? Give a thumbs up or thumbs down to proceed. What would
I like to? Should I join thumbs down? I don't think so. Not today. I understand, Lieutenant.
As soon as you're back on your feet, we'll have you on a transport for New York.
Game over. Wait, is that it? Did I speed run losing the game?
That's the end of the game. Are you kidding me? What do I do now? What is this?
Gallery? Introduction to the gallery. What is going on? How do I? Go back 10 seconds. How do I?
What do I do? Can I go over there? Main menu. What happened? Missions. Stay alive. Okay,
this is where we go. Right here. Welcome to the OSS. I want to join it. Okay, here we go. Yes,
I would like to join. I'm joining the OSS. Thank you. Why is there a gun here?
Lieutenant, I'm Dr. Thatch. Welcome to the infirmary. We'll have you back on your feet
in no time. Come on, blink again. I know you're having some trouble speaking after what happened.
No, blink again. I want to change my- Let's just use hand gestures, eh?
Whatever. Welcome to the infirmary. You can set your game options in this interactive mode. You
can also do it anytime. Okay, whatever. Interactive exam? Sure. How delightful.
Going to ask you a series of questions. And don't worry, you can change your answers at any time.
Now, my first question is an easy one, Lieutenant. Are you left or right-handed? Please,
make your choice. I am right-handed. Ah, fantastic. Use the gun. I can't.
Let's confirm your fine motor skills. Please, pick up the service weapon next to you.
No. No. No. No. No. Yes.
Splendid. Now, give me a thumbs up if you're ready to continue,
or a thumbs down if you want to change your selection.
No, that's fine. I like that. Well done, Lieutenant. On to the next question.
We put blanks in your gun because you're a psycho.
Combat zone. Whenever you're in close proximity to an explosion, you might feel a concussive blast.
The technicians call it camera shake. Turn that off immediately.
You can also feel this camera shake phenomenon when firing your weapon.
But through the wonders of modern medicine, I can easily adjust how much camera shake you feel.
I want zero. Let me know your preference.
Zero. None. The worst thing to put in any game. Why don't you test fire your weapon?
Yeah, why would you want camera shake? Now, if you're happy with your choice,
please give me a thumbs up. If you'd like to choose again, give me a thumbs down.
This game lets you kill the soldiers in the prologue, but not the doctor.
Jolly good, Lieutenant. On to the next question.
I was very jarring that you could do that. Now, let's discuss how you want to view an enemy's
threat level. See the two imaginary enemies in front of you?
Note how their threat level is indicated above their head.
Their threat levels? The stars they have, the bigger the threat.
An enemy with one star should be easy for you to dispatch.
Is this like World of Warcraft zones?
Seeing an enemy's threat level from a distance gives you the chance to adjust your tactics.
I have a question. If I shoot him in the head, it still kills him, right?
Some of the technicians in the back say this affects immersion.
I just burped and I hope you all heard it, but I don't.
It never floats your boat, I say.
Lieutenant, please choose if you'd like to see the enemy threat level.
What do you think? No? I don't think so, right?
I'm skipping the checkup. Get me out of here.
I am always here, Lieutenant, so please come back anytime.
You can access my office through the main menu. Good luck and Tally-ho.
Tally-ho. Firing Ranger.
All right, this one we're going to learn how to play.
Remember, every VR game wants you to see how cool they have their reload feature.
Now that you're back, we should give you an objective as well.
Oh my god, that was cool.
All right, right sleeve is current objective. Follow the tutorial prompts.
Okay. Cool.
That feels pretty good.
I like that a lot. Okay.
Controls are pretty good. I'm going to give it that.
The controls are pretty good.
He hates the game that in any game that's not Alex.
That's not true, but it is a little bit.
I have basic training down here.
Oh, cool. What do we got?
Why are you so much bigger than me?
Press this button.
Oh, okay. That's pretty fun.
I'm not going to shoot him. All right.
Oh, sick.
Oh, this actually I like this.
All right, reach over the shoulder and grab.
Oh, fuck. Okay.
Grab the SMG. This is not an SMG.
How do I get my SMG?
Oh, there we go.
You had to do it with two hands.
Okay. Let me help you.
We shouldn't be standing this close.
Okay. Okay. Put this in.
You shouldn't be this close to your ears would be bleeding right now.
How are your ears not bleeding?
What? Don't. All right. I'm fine.
All right. Next station over here.
I've got to be fair.
Probably out of all the games I've played in VR so far,
all of them that includes Alex.
It's it's this is this works.
This this this works. It works.
It works just fine.
And I don't I have no problem with it.
It works.
The box. Here we go.
How do you do it?
Okay. How do you reload it though?
So I can get mad at chat for getting mad at me two days ago.
How do you do it?
Okay. So I people have people are fucking furious
because I was using my left hand.
Let me see.
No, it doesn't work like that.
Hold on.
Okay. I like them both.
You can have this med kit.
Simulate a grave injury.
Sorry, I didn't press the button fast enough to make you get hurt.
The syringe will inject the medicine.
You can store up to three first aid syringes.
Where?
My cuff.
Ooh, I like that.
I you got to give him credit where credit is due.
You have to.
I'm giving him credit.
Everyone said this game sucks.
So far, this is very fluid, easy to grab shit.
Nothing fucking freaks out.
I like it.
I might change my mind in like 10 minutes.
This is very important.
How cool the grenades.
What?
I'm hope.
I thought if I hold the thing down, it doesn't.
Oh, a shtylen.
A shtylen.
Does it count down?
Why was it not counting down?
Did you see it was counting down before?
It was like three, two.
Oh, okay.
What about the shtylen?
You can.
Oh, are we all right?
It stuck on me.
Get it off me.
It's stuck on me.
Oh, no, it's all right.
Is it open?
No, it is.
All right, we're fine.
Practice range.
Cat puke.
Where am I going?
This way?
All right.
Are these people?
Wait, why are there people here?
Why do we have these guys like just walking around?
Why do we have humans?
A guy in the back.
Check this out.
I want another grenade.
Full.
There we go.
You got to do it like sidearm.
Yes.
All right, that's fun.
Cool.
I'm really healthy now.
Hypers.
What is hypers?
Oh, I'm like, where am I?
It's Ali, right?
Yes, sir.
I'm 23.
23?
Oh, sht.
I'm out of the car.
I fucked it up.
I want to do this for sure.
The Nazis didn't bomb Abilene, Texas.
They bombed London, England.
They destroyed my home.
They burned my entire life to the ground.
And now I want to do the same thing to the Third Reich.
Way to get to the front.
How do you think I got to Tunisia?
Forging transfer orders has become a hobby of mine.
Make it to France.
No, you're finally awake.
Harry Potter.
That's what I said.
Don't worry, Ali.
Your secret's safe.
What does it say?
I'm pretty sure the lieutenant isn't going to say anything.
Thank you, Sarge.
Get down and do exactly what I say.
I need the next part of the game to load in the right spot.
So I'm going to go this way.
OK, I don't care.
I'm trying.
The game needs to load correctly when this cutscene's over.
See?
You know what I mean?
I have to be standing in the right spot.
All right.
I'm training and tests.
It's time to go after the Nazis.
Yes, sir.
His shoulders.
Your first mission is to make contact with the enemy.
I just gave that guy like a spine problem.
The cell led by Mendeleev has been destroyed.
Wait, you mean this thing?
Your rendezvous will be along the lines of the St. Catherine legion.
The resistance will give you a signal when it's safe to come ashore.
You'll have three days to assist the resistance,
the intelligence and German activity,
and sabotage targets of opportunity.
I'm talking about a small communications relay or a fuel truck.
I feel like one of the Muppets.
But it has like the real human hands.
You know what I mean?
They're always kind of like moving their fingers and stuff.
It's like the Swedish chef.
Now I want to introduce you to Huxley, our quartermaster.
Where is he?
She'll get you set up with what you need.
That's Huxley over there?
Oh, excellent.
Good to know.
Three days in and out.
Keep it simple.
I'll see you on the other side.
Got it.
Turn up the game audio?
Really?
It's still low.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
There you go.
Now you're going to be good.
Hello.
I'm Huxley, your quartermaster.
No.
I did this.
We just did it.
Why is every VR game a fucking tutorial for an hour?
You just showed this to me.
No, I just,
I already know how to use the guns.
leave please how do I leave I don't want to do another shooting range why's every
VR game have to have a fucking firing range what the oh how do you use a
grenade I don't know it's something like this that was a perfect fucking CS go
flashbang I would have gotten fucking tons of accolades from my teammates for
that one just give me everything whatever I like am I wrong or is this
like another firing range do I have to am I am I going crazy for no reason look
okay here's a gun I know how to use the gun all right I look there's pistol ammo
this is what pistol ammo is this is what a SMG is okay how do I leave live fire
gauntlet I'd like to continue the campaign goodbye thank you it's been fun
but first I need to see if I can grab this I can't
47 you need to get the fuck out of the level whatever make contact with Manon
Baptiste and her French resistance I'm ready I get seasick on these things guys
I'm sorry okay think I'll be stopped keep an eye on the lighthouse we're
supposed to look for a signal all right we're ready eliminate the enemy patrol
investigating the explosion where oh shit okay go I didn't have any time to
do anything what they said what the fuck this is a trap this is a fucking trap he
actually felt for it what is this is this a vuvuzela what is this what is
this oh no put that back on fucking idiot oh my god that was awful
he's not dead he's not dead I had to kill him I have to kill him how many
more people are in this game you I think I did it I want that shovel wait what is
this thing I still don't understand what what is this that's not a code book
what's that toothbrush that was pretty pog oh my dude can I like slash
somebody found it found it found it all right well that wasn't so bad how did
he know you got it it was a rocket launcher but you fired the only shot
accidentally a lot of carrots most people here are good but we must operate
in the shadows the German occupation has turned every neighbor into a possible
enemy that's terrible I would do anything to get the Nazis out of my
country can't eat those carrots the third Reich is ruthless but so is the
French resistance sorry I get I get sick I'm gonna do that one again remember
that joke move it around and stuff like especially out of the water makes me
sick I'm doing it again that's the Bush Lee where my brother worked and here we
are our secret base slap yourself you can't secret base pretty cool that's
just weird I feel like that's the principal that's my mom that's my math
teacher that's my English teacher and that's that's that's like the school bus
driver like what did I do I did something really bad am I getting like
suspended welcome to my bookstore Marcel has a special workshop upstairs for
I can't smoke one of these we have a serious problem something big is
happening inside Gestapo headquarters toys to play with against my wishes
Juliet works inside undercover as a clerk you fucking believe this she's seen
a dramatic increase in radio transmissions and coded messages no I
didn't want to skip the cutscene I was trying to I was gonna do a thing where
I pretend to be like a baby at the dinner table whatever capture Lewis all
right eliminate the checkpoint guards where are they I see him right there
what fucking kidding me I'm dead why do they not die what happened I didn't pull
pin I didn't pull pin did I when did I pull pin what happened I didn't pull the
pin what happened look I was just holding in my hand did the pin come out
no it didn't what the fuck is happening dude I'm confused as hell I have no idea
what's going on I ate it okay all right let's go give me the fucking rifle no I
want the rifle where are they look at the complete wrong way I find this thing
oh fuck this rock is gonna save my life shit oh shit I can't believe I'm still
alive oh shit where is he where's the guy oh my god behind the rock that it
all right that was fucking crazy what we got what's the
damage what happened he travels with an entourage of well-trained troops so we
got dynamite hey put that down we set the trap wait he can do that I can do
that too some spigot guns in strategic spots and our people positioned along
the road we have to be yeah so they brought along a one-to-one full model
this whole mission but why do they bring it here return it let's put the plan
together that's me where do you want the dynamite I would like the dynamite to be
hmm hmm I would like the dynamite to be I'm gonna go ahead and say right I would
like the dynamite to be right oh here excellent choice catch them right when
they come out right Bill Marcel and now our people shaky hands where should we
be placed well I think to be a little bit we get the most out of this explosion
I think Ollie should be probably somewhere in this vicinity right here
you know what I mean right right over there Ollie I think you should be right
next to the explosives I think that's a perfect view of the the convoy coming
out of there yeah it's coming out of there I'll back you up Juliet a perfect
example we also need you to be able to pack up Ollie so if Ollie's gonna be
there I need you here right next to that yep if you go over there perfect and
Sarge you're gonna need to back up Juliet because she's gonna be focusing
on backing up Ollie I would assume you'd have to be probably right over here
right up next to that we get that good to go and you I can see everything no
like all right good luck I can see everything from up there do I I'm gonna
have like a cartoon detonator wait where are they don't fire until they
wait no that's over where wait wait where are they where are they where my
teammates oh there is that them oh that's right there how do I dip got it
why can I kill that guy what the fuck is going on I don't know where I went I
don't know where I went I don't know where it is what was going on the guy
in the car time for the anime thing it's sorry about that somebody might
have been shooting at you yes I feel like we're missing some interesting
discourse here why haven't you reported in it's been two weeks yeah they know
there is a spy poor baby what are the Nazis up to I have zero patience right
now Louie if you think that I'm treating you bad imagine when we tell the
about your nocturnal activities that's right remember I have pictures say some
there's a list a list of all the resistance members and no man see the
Gestapo's been compiling it for months you're bringing in a train loader special
round everyone up what are you signaling you're wasting ammo um whatever
it doesn't matter train sabotage I meant this is fun blow up the Nazi train you
got it so how does one become a collaborator you can't kill anybody
weakness cowardice or just plain self-centered opportunity like you
nobody can die watch I mean it looked like he got rocked but unfortunately for
me we still have it I need to look like I bravely escaped ollie I don't think
my dreams of becoming a concert pianist lieutenant please do the honor you got
it whatever you say you didn't know time to get your train punch me in the
stomach punch me in the stomach good idea oh never mind I can't take cover
of course no I want them to see me fortnight dancing before they die
come on I would they need to see this before they go oh my god that was epic
Nazis oh fuck dang nope that's a good guy where are they I got a new shot and
he died I can't do with the other hand I don't care clear clear how does this
shoot all right all right whatever I got it and about the train anybody in this
train surrender surrender whoa plans secret plans no I want that glass I
don't want this fuck is this I'm just a guy from trailer park boys well fuck
what's going on in here man Ricky we gotta be careful god damn it I don't
have enough blew up what just blew me up what happened what the fuck are you
kidding me dude are you kidding me I need items all right come on I'm not no
more fucking around let's go Morty fuck I didn't mean to do Marty I swear to God
I promise no stupid idiot you what do you go go go go go come on Rick what
happened what happened to my computer whatever my computer we still live what's
wrong with my computer we can't see your screen yes you can don't like Ed I was
in that all right I need to take this I don't want to shoot it because oh god I
gotta shoot the tank plans that was cool all right where's am I uh where's am I
uh where's am I uh where's the tank where's the tank where's the tank where's
it all right I got it I got it where is it what's happening where's the tank
where is it oh shit oh my god oh my god oh my god where's this fucking tank am I
insane where is it where's the tank where's the tank
what the fuck just happened what am I I just pull the audio out can you hear it
no you idiot give me a gun it's right there I see it eat shit I was trying to
do the movie where's my gun okay good right here all right holy shit that was
crazy oh hold on I gotta come back this way I gotta go back this way nice work
Marcel merci beaucoup whoo this gentleman appears to be my pants fall
down here knows the director of special projects for the German I command he's
involved not good for anyone what's it say I'm sweaty
lots of words in German German I said hey German pay attention German in the
cutscene what are you fucking dumb operation annihilation the troops on
this train were being sent to do boss on to round up some resistance members all
over Normandy and not just suspected members missed the raid somebody who
raided who was there was a raid what was the raid RT of extreme secrecy it's up
RT thanks for the raid RT welcome everybody it says that playing some VR
for a little bit I just I've become fully vaccinated today so I want to take
it easy well I say that as I scream and shoot like missiles and stuff sending
trains we need to get that list but it's impossible to sneak in the second floor
is guarded around the clock give a peek a piece of cake on you whatever I have an
I know frontal assault on Gestapo don't we think we should move away from this
proposition than ambushing a convoy blowing up a train we can't do it alone
it's true we need more resistance members but that's much easier said than
done no no no no no no no no they're crazy I'm afraid no I'm the crazy one
what the fuck no it's me I'm the one that's like the crazy one no no no I
don't want those guys I'm the fun one I'm the crazy guy for this one I need to
let me get some we get a hold on not yet the vino brothers make contact with the
vino brothers prove you're on their side
no one knows for sure everyone is suspicious of each other I know what
you're thinking how can we trust this group is truly resistance how do we know
some cells are not as discrete as others and not that bad I wonder if they're
I was getting better view I was getting it I was standing behind everybody what
the fuck I was dropping it okay I was wanting to get a better view I'm the
bit I'm the character that wants to do they don't have cameras on their heads I
do I want to get a good view it's cuz I hit them I touched the book I touched to
the grip button I'm not doing this on purpose I swear to God I touched the grip
on the index controller and he pulled the gun out you have a lot of nerve
trespassing on someone else's property I recognize you and your sister but who
is that with you our friend they've come to help the resistance we don't
have time for games we need your help the real Gestapo is about to round up
every resistance cell in Normandy can I put my hands down it looks like they're
going to start with you please we are on the same side prove it kill him shoot
him let's fight what oh not them we need to stay out of sight hide for the
ambush remember you forgot to wear tighter pants hey can I have this they
hidden I'm not in sight fuck you hey sugar and cream but you coffee
motherfucker no no no don't be a child all right you're hitting the wall you're
hitting the wall I just want to make sure you know that you're hitting the
wall make type two steps to your left are they even here yet or are you bad
guy what's going on Nazis all right cover me one two three we go together
ready one two one two three go we good oh my god get out of the way I can't
pick up a huge rock that's annoying I only have three bullets shit got him got
him got me anybody in the car do something it's my underwear is falling
down my underwear showing my underwear good I'm saying you guys can't see I'm
good thing I'm my underwear is out good thing I'm not standing up you talking
about give me that where is he where is he where are they all right this thing
sucks that it one more I think over here oh my god there's a lot get in the
bathtub fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck don't lose here that was nuts okay we
believe you we need to join forces and raid Gestapo headquarters alright thanks
to the right headquarters we'll do it but we need more than just people we
need weapons and supplies the Germans are for to find what's wrong with this
guy is he okay maybe we could steal what we need from there and how do you
suggest we do that maybe you could use some of these uniforms and that guy
take that truck you could just drive right in this is the best plan ever
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha play something else I'm I'll give this
another another mission we'll move on to something else after and this one's
actually I'm having fun with this one I need to turn though which way do I need
to turn I think this way is that accurate it is all right let me just keep
going to steal weapons from the Nazis okay I'm so fucking sweaty it's
unbelievable
where we are not coming to do anything weird hello hello hello when we get caught
my only request he's so high we're not coming to steal anything from you how
do I wish I could get the finger I want to give the finger so that Wow Wow can I
skip the cutscene sneak into the outpost okay are you trying to get me to throw
up what I got out of the car grab some crates and load them into the truck all
right did they say he is not German just fill it up the back yeah you boys have a
wonderful day have a wonderful evening by the way we weren't really Nazis why
how are we not instantly dead come on catch that oh my god I'm all right
um okay good good good we're good this is too much happening it's too much
happening the same time we good you make on thought that was a personal shit I'm
gonna throw up all right I gotta just run them over run them over who cares
good job my shooting the guy in the head that's next to me they're driving what
duck bill decoying no I'm just making sure the Germans can find that's way
more boxes than we put in here I'm turning around don't hit her we brought
weapons next game yeah we can move on this was fun though I had a lot of what
we needed great work no it was nothing let's just see what's next skip let's
just get whatever I'll keep everyone out of the shop will you find Marcel's
bomb it should be upstairs I gotta find the bomb I'll find that bomb don't you
worry one of these is a bomb how about the statue of Benjamin Franklin whoops
all right I'm go it's upstairs all right there's a bomb upstairs I'm gonna get it
find the bomb I wanted that bomb if I was a bomb bomb behind the bookshelf in
the piano that's fun out of the bed find the cupboard key oh god where the fuck
would I open anything I touch anything cupboard key that was fun cupboard key
where is it it's the rubber book what is it what's this exploded uh nothing no
books nothing in here a key where is it Jesus no key where's the key what it was
right there view bimbo Jerma loves that what why does he look so short I've
explained it already I'm not explaining it again all right I think I'm gonna take
a break I'm gonna switch games I liked this one though this one was actually
pretty fun I want to get some water I want to stretch a little bit wait did
anyone know where it is it's time for Rick and Morty it's not time for Rick and
Morty anyone know where it is it's in a book there's no water in here key you
know these are diamonds in here and shit whatever what the hell I can't use any
of this there are giant holes in the wall yeah but I'm I don't know where
the I need to find a key in here in a book this book hey oh my god what am I
doing I just caught all right new game new game I'm out of here about new game
new game new new new new new new whatever new game where should we go we
got hmm there's a lot of stuff to potentially play I got so many games you
have no idea we're not gonna be able to do even a quarter of these but it's good
to have them I can't see you guys anymore um it's how is Hellsplit arena
any good try play okay it's Hellsplit arena any good I'm not playing SCP no
way not right now I am in far too much physical discomfort to cringe that hard
and scream and shit like that I've already done it like two or three times
already it's not I need I can't do that right now maybe on Halloween why did I
buy it because I bought like a bunch of scary games for VR Halloween this year
play Rick and Morty play the executioner game yeah how long I've been
streaming for like an hour or two oh shit a bit I play for like an hour and a half all
right well I'm gonna do if I how many people are here there are 13,000 people
here I want you I want everyone to pay attention because if this if that number
goes down by a significant amount you know what happened there are 13,000
people here I'm gonna I'm gonna play Rick and Morty as much as I don't want to
I already did this I all right we're playing for like 10 minutes we're gonna
play Rick and Morty for literally 10 minutes but I gotta take a break first
so give me a sec I'll be right back give me one minute I'm gonna take a break I've
been I haven't come out of the headset in like an hour and a half all right give
me two seconds I'm gonna go pee grab some more water right back okay I'm back
I am back so when I came out of the headset I'm definitely starting to feel
a little slower I think I get those of you that have had the vaccine I am I
like freaking myself out or am I like oh here it comes here it comes here it
comes where's this I know they're coming when are the side effects coming I know
that where are they I don't know I might be like I might just be like amping
myself up for no reason just stay active well I feel all right so we're we're
might be on borrowed time here right now so let's just keep going because once
if I start to feel kind of like shit then I'm gonna have to leave so let's
just go let's do it time for Rick and Morty virtual Rick ality why am I even
doing this hello I have returned can you guys hear the game and I need these oh
oh my god this is the couch no way where's Rick Rick and Morty volume 1 no I
want the best season season 2 is the best season for sure
holy shit it's the Simpsons couch hold on point pants up I need to insert a
disc how do I open this we're even are though do we already did that all right
let's just go Rick and Morty is the joke over can I open up the other game why
am I seeing that oh viewers pumping
yeah I know I had to rearrange the entire garage to do it Morty Morty clone
pay attention to me I need you to take this laundry and put it in the washing
machine and if that's too confusing of instructions for you you know there's a
dry erase board on the put up in the garage here the dry erase board area
you'll see I wrote instructions on what you're supposed to do we're gonna play
the executioner game experience it lasts around an hour is not to be played
in one sitting for progress is saved automatically the consequence of your
actions are permanent this contains graphic violence events depicted are
based in historical law and punishment from 16th century Europe as such it is
dictates depictions of crimes which some may find disturbing or triggering and
what oh I just missed everything wait what is happening press to pause press
and hold then release to teleport okay I think this left right touch left and
right to turn I don't know what just happened touch left and right to turn I
think I'm just gonna have to turn like this it's kind of loud too okay so what
the fuck okay squeeze and hold to pick up objects so yeah it's just like a grip
okay press and hold then release to teleport press to pause this is pick up
objects gonna pick up gloves oh so what color gloves do I want green all right
I'll take green oh Jesus welcome I see you've arrived safe and sound I have
as expected law and order thrive here as you'll soon witness firsthand although
the name executioner is hated by many and perceived as an inhuman bloody and
tyrannical office in truth one does not sin if they act on orders out of justice
as God's servant on the scaffold our foremost concern is to deliver a good
death for our poor sinner okay not butchers public execution is a divine
theater of justice and redemption a carefully orchestrated drama designed
to is this the script goodness as well as impress our authority I will announce
the crime and the sentence then the poor sinner will have an opportunity to speak
their last words my right here is fire may God have mercy upon your is this
Justin Roiland you shall strike the neck from behind chopping off the head
with a single great now that by taking this position whoa excellent I look
forward to wait inside wait I gotta read this upon tick I didn't write my name
upon taking the excuse this is not good it doesn't hold up in oh my god oh my
god oh my god I got I can't play this I'm gonna throw up holy shit that was
awful oh my god that was awful all right what
to be or not to be whether it is no blood in the behind stubborn warning
robber he roamed the countryside attacking isolated farmsteads by night
the family Stiglitz and the family my what's wrong with me what's going on
and more he along with three companions drunk tortured and did violence to
innocent people robbing them of money clothes and forcing himself upon women
and girls these crimes being against the law of the land my Lord's have
decreed and given sentence that this man shall be condemned from life to death by
the sword that's my job do you have any final words
Oh you're too kind for an introduction you've given me although I'm afraid my
performance is he talking he's talking how is how is he still talking
the prisoner fucking died behind the couch I fucking missed it oh I didn't
think that was even the same guy I didn't think that was the same guy oh my
god hold on I need to know oh my god that was insane why did he die I need to
do I have to see if that actually happens cuz that's fucking hilarious if
I kill him and then he gets mad at me behind the desk and he put his head fall
off okay players who obeyed players who rebelled players who have resigned
players who were fired wait a minute main menu um give me this I we need to
know I have to know just sign it oh shit my hand my hand okay let me give me the
sword I need to know this is important excellent I'm looking over here by the
fire that is here okay I'm gonna get a good view I'm gonna get a good view of
this cuz I just took his head off by doing this not only do you undermine my
authority he's alive and giving the poor sinner a chance to make the peace before
we show that not only are we in control but that we are there and just this job
is not simply the chopping of heads
designed to send a message keep him down I killed him I killed him that's
impossible how many times I have to kill him that's what you to wipe the blade I
can't even this is cool kill him first you just go up and just slice his head
immediately just run over there and do it holding the sword the wrong way
citizens of Ulrich Sharpen we gather today to witness the execution of this
poor sinner the title of executioner is a sacred charge and unnecessary I so
badly I wish I did one of the most regrets I've had in my whole life just
laughing over here and not seeing his head fall off behind the desk right like
wish I could rewind it and do it again
loyalty and in gratitude let this be an example to all those who might harbor
thoughts of disobeying but I broke it may God have mercy do it after he says
his last words okay executioner you may proceed what do you mean I who where am
I did I already die it's right after he says his say your last words I killed I
got to do everything in the same exact way right I'm sorry we're doing this
welcome executioner he says his little last words I kill him then I kill him
as expected law and that's how it happened last time excellent okay so yeah
yeah he he says it his crime he's like oh fuck you might and then I kill I cut
his head off and then I walked over to him and I cut his I gotta get this right
okay oh what it's just no but in the mind right I threw that cool I took a sip
out of this this morning we gather to witness the execution of this poor
sinner okay the murderer Hensla humson Hensla also known as stubborn Marty is a
thief and a robber okay he roams the countryside attacking I so I was over
here by night the family walked this way the family my snow Krauss are you clear
Merkel and more for an Andy three companions bound tortured and did
next robbing them of money clothes and forcing himself upon women and these
crimes being against the law of the land my lords have and given sentence that
this man shall be condemned he starts talking death then I got to get this
right okay okay okay okay we got it we got it we got it we got it we got it
you executed the prisoner before I'd given you permission by doing this not
only do you undermine no but the authorities and giving the poor sinner
a chance to make their peace before God damn it we show that not only are we in
control and just shit it's all right whatever it is a performance designed
to send a message think on that you will not be paid for today why the colors all
off um I don't all right let me get I'm gonna get it right welcome executioner I
see you've arrived I'm trying to draw a smiley face I can't believe it oh well
at least we know it happened all right it's all good that's so funny all right
wait till he's ready was it what is this a taser this morning we gather to
witness the execution of this poor sinner the murderer Hensla Hoomson
Hensla is a thief and a robber he roamed the countryside attacking isolated
bombs dead by night the family Stiglitz and the family Meisner Krauss
Merkle and more he along with three companions bound tortured and did
violence to innocent people robbing them of money clothes and forcing himself
upon women and girls these crimes being against the law of the land my lords
have decreed and given sentence that this shall be condemned from life to
death by the sword do you have any final words get it
you're too calm what a fine introduction you've given me which is
set to be a short one get on with it good Christian people I income here to
die or have lived a life of a sinner and an happy one at that therefore I have
offended my Lord God I've been told by these kind Lord that I must ask him
heartily for forgiveness sorry God we'll do it again I swear get his head on the
block once and for all
we're just get on with it I've got places to be why is that funny what it
was hello like a fucking father have some friends what was that
command my spirit may God have mercy upon your soul executioner that's me
okay down down there it is okay other powers are between God you man and us
we have to cry that you will be you will be executed very swiftly under the eyes
of God and of this kingdom I decry in three seconds three two one your head
will be removed from your body 1-0 was an exemplary performance thank you here's
your pay plus a small bonus and you're gonna die tomorrow that was very loud a
stubborn man right up until the end I'm gonna golf swing the next should be a
drama of divine redemption the poor sinner acknowledges in the tones for
their crimes except in return they're granted a sweat I want someone to promise
of salvation so I'm gonna sit like this and I'm gonna let it out and I wanted
somebody to add like a fart sound when it comes out like just time to relax and
have a good day and just chill after a nice long day of work I want like a nice
and clean chopping ah yeah I promise I will golf swing this game's gonna be puke
you're in colorblind mode yeah I don't know if I'm feeling it but like we I
think I'm gonna have to change would you like a sip of this before we get started
this morning we gather to witness the execution of this poor sinner the
murderer Mattis Sturz a veteran soldier of three campaigns what 15 years of
service what's going on this is my reward quiet do not interrupt me this man has
been found guilty of stabbing a ditch digger by the name of Mikhail Shulber
these crimes against the law of the land and that's serious decreed and given
sentence that this man shall be condemned from life to death by the
sword do you have any more final words fuck it get on with it
father into your hands I come hey may God have mercy upon your soul
executioner yeah you may post his head came up with a bit of way funnier
it cuts like the mayor's head off oh shit sorry oh my god mr. bean punch him
wait can you can I punch I want to try punch in the next person I'm kind of
getting a headache in this game this is this is interesting though you know you
may proceed I'll tell you like people have interesting ideas for games
especially VR games like this is this idea the executioner like that's a cool
idea I like it all right I'm gonna try punching somebody's death wicked backs
welcome executioner I see you I can't believe we didn't get to see him fall
down at least that wasn't a shooting range tutorial in this one that's true
oh god I hate that when that happens turn off colorblind mode I don't think
this there's this is not a cold one execution of this poor sinner the
murderer Hensla humson Hensla also known as stubborn Marty is a thief and a
robber he roamed the countryside attacking isolated farmsteads by night
the family Stiglitz and the family Meisner Krauss Arikler Merkel and more
he along with three companions bound tortured and did violence to innocent
people dropping them of money and forcing himself upon women and girls get
off the stage the land get off the stage get off the stage from life to death by
the sword do you have any final words
I'm sorry I can't
the title of executioner is a sacred child this game is fantastic
necessary function of society this sorry this obeyed orders in an act of
meaningless violence was wrong with you I don't know there can be only one
punishment for such an act of disloyalty all right I'm something about the I
don't know I have to change games that was that was very good though
may God where am I going on your soul that was so funny you may proceed I
can't see what you guys saying um what do I want to do what do you guys think
where should I go we want bone works no no I'm not playing bone works SCP no no
no no SCP is for Halloween play the poker stars game beat saber tilt brush
no I'm not gonna play trover that's my Halloween bladesmith I kind of want to
try this that I'm gonna play hell split I got this a long time ago and it looked
like it was potentially interesting I want to try it I have I have so many VR
games guys it's insane how many I have we have VR content for like the next
year but going forward I am gonna do it probably seated or like seated in
standing because it just it just absolutely wrecks me every time
especially now I burped again all right hell split did I play this before I'm
like skeleton hands oh and it's an index game all right you got my you got my
interest so far rendering scale get that out get that to a hundred percent please
no vibration wait maybe should I okay game new profile choose your VR
experience standing what I think my mouth is gonna move it tracks pretty
well that's a pretty good track what is 175 I don't know that's can I change my
face all right campaign normal you're two feet
tall so many times you brought peace and justice to your land I did became the
defender of your kingdom we called you the first of equals to your last battle
thousands of other fearless warriors followed you you were so many do you
remember how your people despised death bravely they fought I've six I'm not
five six I'm literally who have bare feet socks on on the ground and it's
based on how tall your base stations are my base stations are huge I have them up
really high pointing down I'm five eight everybody laugh it's fine I did I'm five
eight five five it's the base stations it's the way it's my bare socks on the
ground I'm five eight everybody relax executioner game is fucking hilarious good
artwork I like the tiered layered system they have here
blazed across the deserted lands that time the eternal darkness fell oops
welcome home brave warrior here you can find everything you need this place is
beyond space and time I look like I made it a clay I look like clayvation you are
ready to come out to the arena I was in the bathtub for a really long time okay
am I sure this chapter one cemetery kill all opponents hold on not yet
what happened can I not go in here oh I can that's pretty fun fucking through me
I got to open the jar in front of my girlfriend it was who needs a dentist
okay I'm ready kill all opponents oh I need that I think
you are a best warriors of the path do you want to know who I am oh shit you will soon find out don't you
even attempt to see me and everywhere and nowhere at the same time okay but
this minor circumstance does not stop me from watching watch out with the bird
shit where I gotta go come on dad hey this is fun I like it the banana oh my
god how do I eat the banana how do I eat a banana okay that works too how do I
eat the oh god damn it oh I need that weapon I want the other weapon hey okay
we say about this see how fucking strong I am you wouldn't do this you
wouldn't do it ow ow ow boom I just like almost rip I was pulled my pants off
then I was caught in here and pulled my pants off what's next this fun round one
ooh I didn't get a trophy why can't you just have a face after one no I don't
want to do chapter one again can I do anything else what's this choose your
equipment and opponents for a battle swords Nordic sword one-handed grab
short sword one hand Nordic sword I only do Nordic sword so I don't have enough
1,100 gold how come how do I buy it bye oh it price it's 2,300 fuck 1,200 or a
francisco a double francisco how about a francisco cool all right money can be
exchanged for goods and services good to know chapter 1 earn extra gold armory
wait oh okay I can do this okay how do I get my other weapon excuse me there's a
jump okay we're gonna have to alright let's go how do I climb who's next oh
yeah come on down here this is so stupid that's very efficient my foot just comes
up all right I'm gonna I'm gonna take this thing down I gotta be careful I
won it was the axe all right hold on a second we are very tangled one more
maybe more than that holy shit this is really this is really badly tangled
all right we're good portable VR needs to happen there already exists but I
think they're not as high fidelity as an index right because you can get the
quest but isn't that thing that thing's not that expensive is it it's just like
a wireless headset cemetery round two I want a weapon where's my weapon do I
have to like bring it with me how do I bring this with me
like an inventory I think I just took it with me the quest to is pretty good
there we go all right I don't have my oh holy shit that was cool nice
what's cuz arm off in his head this guy's head is made of steel what the
shit die holy be that back it works oh that was sick oh oh thank you thank you
bird and the spikes yeah I want to go in there spike spike spike get up get on
those spikes yeah get over there oh what the fuck dying light moment oh I hate
that grab them with your hands I gotta close my eyes when I press that button
grab grab him and move around snap his neck come on it's not as easy as it
looks on TV I can't somebody behind me oh shit oh my god
ow I don't have a weapon but at least I have his hand that has a weapon come
here kill him what give me the sword okay stay right there stay stay you
motherfucker come here give me that get it I got it don't you understand don't
you get it don't you get it think into the spikes into the spikes my pants
fall down oh that hurt and there's another one and there's another one is
there a health potion oh fuck got it where we oh my god kill this
motherfucker come here I won all right Windows
firewall you choking I have enough for another weapon fuck I'm draining
losing steam I'm losing steam what else we got I got four thousand bucks there
we go straight sword yep now I can hope I want to hold it with two hands can I
not all right well whatever it's on your butt what's on my butt all right we're
gonna I'll do one more and then I might we're gonna do a chill game oh who's
next oh all right you ah that was easy all right how about we let's do a real
fight one-on-one you and me real sword fight okay just like they do whenever
you'd like to fucking idiot still alive tip on his head I didn't with my weapon
anymore at the back is that a grenade holy shit it's a grenade okay well there
was that one all right I need to I need to assess let me see what we got here I
need something a little more low-key gonna puke I don't think I don't think
I'm gonna puke no I'm not gonna puke what do we got we got is how is derail
valley any good I still have this for a long time all right we're gonna play
derail valley I think you just ride around a train it's like fun all right
we're going in derail valley be careful I'm all right I'll be I'll be right for
like another 20 30 minutes and by the way if you missed the beginning of the
stream Thursday we're doing a battleship tournament with Ludwig gonna be on
Ludwig's channel eight contestants I'm one of them and then Sunday we're
streaming The Sims 2 and talking about that for a while it'll be a lot of fun
and I'm gonna talk about something very important on Sunday all right let's do
derail valley oh man this has been a fun day though I gotta take care of this I
would give the last few games we played a pluses in fun factor there was funny I
even okay even doing anything I think so yeah but this will be the last VR
stream for a little while it's it's absolutely decimating me I can't lie to
you all right one more turn should do it okay that looks good all right derail
valley let me take a sip and we'll see from there that's from good side I don't
think I need to come out any at all I feel like this won't be very long but
this has been a fucking blast as it always is I just wish I had more stamina
for it nowadays I just don't especially now it's sad it pisses me off wrong okay
all right derail valley wait would it be up here I think this is a game you
there you like drive a train right old man yeah playing VR for more than hours
is not just you it's not easy no it's not really isn't even back when I was
like feeling a little better but since this bullshit it's been kind of even
harder to do which sucks guy this is I love doing this shit it's a lot of fun
probably the vaccine as well um I think I'm okay I don't think I'm gonna start
feeling a problem until like probably at least a few hours from now all right
welcome to derail valley engineer let's get you to a train driver's license okay
try turning around flick the joystick great how do you dash hold the mark
button point somewhere and release okay it's teleport oh okay can you get hit by
a train um no we keep it off get you the comms radio oh my goodness pick up the
comms radio drop the radio on the desk this is the way of item interaction yeah
that's fine pick up distant items remotely hold an
aim at that thing and pull it hold the button aim at this and okay flip the
pages hold trigger button okay flip up the fuse box switches put in your
inventory okay now pick it up cool let's store the comms radio to your
inventory okay reach for an item pick it up you can also store items by
dropping it at your wrist right okay you ready to drive the train all right let's
go how do I drive the train how do I get up here with the plug it in am I in all
right let's fire her up take out the shunter
manual and follow the ignition procedure flip up the fuse box switches okay I do
it oops what the fuck just happened what flip up the fuse box switches step
one I did that I'm missing one how do I flip how do I flip the pages again
ignition procedure she's not well grandma's evil she's fine she's gonna be
fine what we're doing how do I flip this how do I how do I flip step one that was
sound like my wrist no that's not take out the manual what the fuck that's the
manual right there's only one page of the manual it's outside it's outside what
the fuck how do I turn the train on everything so dark caress it fuses on
the right side first then toggle the switch yeah I already did that park the
locomotive outside past the switch okay okay how do I make it go read I don't
have the manual anymore I fucking threw it outside it's I can't make out what
half of this stuff says you'll reverse her that's so blurry for me that's like
how do I turn the brakes off what does this say train brake I got it's I had
to go that close to see it okay independent brake you need to plug it
in engine temperature what it's wrong it's good sorry how do I what do I do
drive drive drive it's gonna blow floor it is it gas it was the gas how do you
make a train go just go grab the manual fuck how do you turn on the fucking
train give it to me I can't turn the page how do I turn the page it's
supposed to be trigger I can't turn the page hold trigger and move joystick what
the fuck push the reverser into the forward position get me back in that
fucking goddamn tank no give that to me give me this stupid thing okay hi turn
this thing on all right now put the reverser I don't miss it out of its
misery put the reverser forward forward release the brakes dude I don't know
what fuck I even am in this room but I gotta like move over here put this down
for it I can't teleport with it why can I fucking move give me this release the
brakes oh fucking my god it's so blurry to me just turn on again turn on release
the brakes where's a break break pipe where is it it's that has to come down
and this is to go forward this has to come down this has to go forward okay go
turn it on all right now that's going forward apply the throttle dude the
engines destroyed let it cool down for a second this is open this is open this is
all the way down here okay so we're good chill game read the manual I just did
release the throttle to stop apply the brake flip the fuse boxes go they're up
turn the ignition on clockwise done okay pull the river let me get them to hold
on let me get this all this stuff like in the default position okay so I do
that to turn that on can we pull that forward and then let's release the
brakes I'm gonna do this get it in the right spot so that goes boink boink and
then go okay fuck off here we go train is on pull that back a little bit here
excellent we need to really let's go ahead and release then released slowly go
with the throttle here we go backwards why did we go backwards it told me to do
this it told me to do that okay yeah cool okay why it's off the
rail put it in reverse how do I restart the game push it wait I can fix it get
okay we should be going the right way we're gonna play a hotel hotel are in
our that game is probably really fuck okay size matters lost to the tutorial
it's like really dark for me and it's really blurry I don't know I don't know
what the fuck are you doing party mode is what it was this you stealing my
data okay I do not agree not like it matters guitar what just happened did I
die throw something what just happened objects highlight when they can be
grabbed what am I red for the guitar what's it what's happening am I supposed
to be doing what's the fuck uh high voltage warning I get off the stage I
think I missed something old bottom touchpad and swing your arms to move
push thumbstick left or right to turn touch okay so you got a it's just a
pretty sweet echo effect on my voice don't do it get into the elevator I have
something for you how about let's go to hell that was a baby oh it's the devil
just stick to this talk to me hello and leave the liberal halfwits to me listen
waste of a bloody to pay jeb is a waste jeb is a mess jeb is a big fat steak if
you didn't guess I'm the devil right so you're here because you want fame and
fortune but your music sucks well come to the right place my friend I turn it
up the best of them from panini to page I just love to make a deal with the
musician you're all so debauched I was gonna do it too but it was embarrassed
I've fallen out with a certain hotelier so I think that you could help me so
here's the deal I'll give you what you want
and all you need to do for me is become infamous for smashing up hotel rooms
okay the bigger the hotels and more cash you can make I just break a bunch of
hostels okay that's easy on here and you'll be taken backstage to start your
career please sign here capture I am NOT a robot we have a deal just looking over
the fine print as stated in clause 221b okay that's like actually fucking scary
that was kind of terrifying okay become infamous use the TV and navigate to the
first hotel to start earning cash in infamy zero press a button or something
how do I move and it wasn't a walk like this need a quick fix okay what just
happened when I go into the earth here get up get up get up go how do I move
why isn't this is to use the grip buttons and run right just walk up to
the fucking thing okay that was weird all right we're gonna go to the cross
road hotel sounds good hotel R&R police select not available not available not
available clear infamy challenges okay leaderboard bill rider select this is a
car game I can't walk okay I pick anything up I just destroy the hotel
room that's the whole thing all right just let's fuck this place up whatever
why can I move Oh sunflower dumb I can hurt that one I can't move come on
listen up what this is useful on boarding stuff to get you on board I
guess the member of the star is on their way to your room you do not want them to
fully open the door or that is game over what now pay attention to this or
you might die again how I get them to leave do not get caught exit strategy
you must lock it again but I can't even move over there why can't I not wait I
can't like walk over there why can't I move I don't understand what's going on
oh I'm hoping all right yeah yeah I'm stupid uh stop cut that get the fucking
door closed to close the door hey all right destroy what's in here oh shit a
bathroom can I break it I don't know I'm just fucking press every button I don't
know oh God what all right all right I get it I get it I get it all right let's
go go go go go I'm good give me the TV all right let's go what about the bed
give me the fucking TV what the fuck holy shit I can break the walls no way
hold on how do I get out of here how to kind of leave does that hit the guy in
the face use the briefcase weapon lock the door it's locked this is your exit
what was that 200 bucks okay I win okay let's go oh shit I have what do I need
hotel select there's nothing what do I need to do don't kill the lady why is he
bad at every game man that guy for 25 hours just so he has a full day and then
an extra hour to understand what he said to me okay so I don't have to get just
don't hit the lady I need something heavy something really heavy that's not
fucking heavy stop she oh shit she leaves okay that's not how much this is
like thousands of dollars in damage what are you talking about oh shit knife no I
couldn't close it I was trying to lock the door again give me this fucking thing
I need to like smash the sink thousand bucks okay 40 seconds all right get out
get out get out get out I got 1,500 bucks okay you can go to the pawn and gun
shop I'm interested you need to complete challenges okay okay go down to the pawn
shop what else we got story so far all right so can I go down elevator
elevator where's the elevator parents okay uh let's go to the pawn shop
let's see what it does I was German so good at every game he plays I'm gonna
ban that guy for 26 hours okay ooh boxing gloves a fish microphone 8,000
what else we got a glue gun oil spray see for holy shit 4,000 for like what is
this how much are the guns 1,200 45,000 2,000 I get a power ball what can I
afford play the drums I will I'm gonna get the power ball how do I like say yes
I want item in cart all right let's pay for it
bouncy toy for kids that's caused more household damage than any rock star
let's get it changing room weapon testing all right all right let's go play
the drums oh I can change my outfit that's not that's not worth a thousand
dollars not even you know a chance let's go wish I go backstage where's that
where the drums paper beast is really relaxing this is probably it I'm at the
limit my body is starting to be very very very mad at me for doing VR again
where should I go for the drums backstage why didn't you test the weapon
because I know what's gonna do it's gonna go all right this is drum kit well
there is a drum kit isn't there not quite my tempo can you play the guitar
yeah let's go to the next hotel I don't play fucking party mode what it is do
no I don't get me out of here what the fuck just happened wait what did I just
do I like I want no I don't know how do I get out of here I've restarted what
have happened to like the menu is weird I don't the story so far I can't just
quit you can't read why are there like eight iPad game menus like what I just
want to play how do I get out of here oh my god just get me out go go all right
I'm here I'm playing I can't quit this did I actually just restart the entire
game well why just quit the game if I come back in is it gonna I want to play
the next level I want to do level two man stomps in circles shouting at nothing
world tour this is what I want to do right party mode world toward no risk no
reward pawn to die purgatory the story so far walk this way settings can be
what is why what's the point of this menu what okay I gotta do the like the
infamous things the ball I didn't can I see what the challenges are rack up a
hundred fifty dollars without a trip to the hospital take a take a full rider
to the hotel and cause 800 damage cost 300 dollars of subtotal damages and
escape before the maid tries to get in all right I think I can do it like this
ready that does not do even remotely the amount of damage I thought it was gonna
do why okay I need to do 300 bucks of damage where the maid gets in I need
something heavy god damn it scammed if I can take out that wall and maybe the
toilet okay I'm gonna go I'm going to bath I'm gonna take the toilet out
right I'm just gonna come in here just start swinging you ready come on hurry
up hurry up come on go go go go got it I got it
now close the fucking thing kill her now I need to destroy this shit holy shit I
just okay I'm like really hurt though I got red and stumpy what all right well I
got another infamy thing right I died I died all right one more try and I I
gotta stop it's creeping up bad all right let's go go go go go go come on
come on come on come on what's the best way to just okay I think sucks 300
damage before the maid gets in and then just don't hurt yourself I'm trashing
everything in the bathroom with this let's go shit shit something heavy I had
the chair literature oh my god damn it I'm gonna have to go to the hospital
again I'm too tired I'm too tired I can't do it that's the end I can't do
it take me to the hospital all right that's it I want to keep going but I
can't I'm gonna actually hurt myself this has been so much fun though I love
VR it's like the best thing all right I will see you guys on Thursday Thursday
is the battleship tournament Thursday battleship tournament Ludwig and Sunday
we're playing sims 2 I'm gonna be back to normal here Wow I just realized you
guys can't hear me Sims 2 on Sunday battleship tournament on Thursday and
we'll see you then I really hope I don't have that many side effects of
them but I'm not doing anything to make sure of it I'm gonna be lying down on my
back hey hydrated yeah I'm gonna drink a bunch of water and chill oh I really
oh that's not but I've just I fucked up my wall I'm gonna have to like repaint this
I just saw what I did we don't see you VR let me take this off oh man when you
know when you take your diaper off and it just feels awesome
this this next few weeks is gonna be incredibly exciting I really hope you
guys enjoy it cuz it's it's gonna be fucking wild let me just tell you thanks
I did I miss anything major let me just be here at mystic quests gave 20
community subs easy case gave 25 community subs on emos mystic quests
daddy big bucks all gave 10 thank you guys at speaking of money gonna have to
figure out here what to do with because I just recently got the money from the
bugleberry hot tub stream so the idea was I was gonna pick a charity and give
the money that came in from there which I have that number but I have to pick
one so we will we will figure that out maybe in this week y'all take a look take
a look at some you stole his money oh that was a lot of fun I'll see you guys
on Thursday I'm not gonna be streaming on Thursday I'm gonna host Ludwig but I
will be participating the whole time so I'll see you Thursday if you're gonna be
there if not then we'll see you Sunday for the Sims 2 have a great night as
always thanks for watching thanks for watching VR I'm gonna move my entire
back into my room we'll see you soon take care guys have a great day and good
night or good afternoon wherever you are