I just want to try it. I'm just going to try it. I'm just going to try it. Just a little bit.
I just want to see what it looks like. I just want to see what it looks like. I just want to test it.
I'm just going to test it. God, it's been six hours. I'm just going to test it out.
Ah, I just want to test it.
Other babes. Ghost of the Babe, New Babe Plus. Which one is it?
Oh shit, I have to do window capture.
Oh right, because it's fucked up. I forgot.
Alright, hold on. Be right back.
Is this going to be my first 16 hour stream? No, it is not. It is not going to be that.
Where's window capture?
Where's window capture? I need to do this now. Let's go.
It's not going to be 17 hours.
There we go. Alright, let's go.
What is it? New Babe Plus? Which one is it?
Ghost of the Babe?
No, what? Continue?
Ghost of the Babe. Are you sure? Delete, save, or no?
This is worded very strangely. Continue.
Now, let me see if I can remember how to play.
Alright, it's going to take me a minute to remember how to play.
Alright, I remember. I remember. I remember.
Okay, I don't...
No, I gotta eat food and then do this. No, alright.
No, no, no, no. No, no, no. No, it's too late.
It's like I have to stop right now before this gets any worse.
I have to stop before this gets any worse.
Oops. Okay. I fucked up. It's alright. I can't even get to the DLC yet.
Yeah, I played this game like fucking two weeks ago. I haven't played it since.
I've been dreaming about it.
He's obsessed with it. I'm not obsessed with it.
Alright. You know, it's alright.
Alright, I'll see you tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow. I have to stop this now.
I know what's going to happen and this is going to be bad.
I'll see you tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow. Somebody get me.
Somebody get me now. Somebody come get me.
Come get me. Somebody come get me.
He's trapped. No, I'm not.
I'm just trying to... I want to get to the DLC and save it there.
I just want to get to the DLC and save it there and that's it.
And that's it. And then I'll be done.
I just want to get to the DLC and then we'll take a look.
We'll just take a look when we get there.
Oops. Oops. It's okay. It's alright. Fine.
It's alright. I'm just... I gotta get...
Coin? I don't care.
Coin has nothing to do with the DLC.
Alright, I gotta get this one right. I gotta get that.
It's been pretty smooth so far.
No major fuck ups. Just getting back in the swing of things.
I fucked it up. It's alright.
Oh man. I fucked it up. I have to go.
Alright. I have to leave. Like right now.
Somebody come get me.
I'm trying to go so fast just to get to the...
I just want to get to the DLC and then I'll be done.
Seriously. It's not even that hard.
It's not. I'm just like brushing and freaking out.
I want to do it though.
Alright. Slow down.
I've already beat the damn game. Who cares?
Alright. Let's go. Let's go.
No more fucking around.
Just get up there.
He's addicted?
I mean the game is fucking incredibly fun to play.
Didn't I say I hated this game?
I talked about how I hated everything about this game.
I think I did that.
Show this to future Jeremy.
Let me see.
This is important.
I think I'm gonna go get that coin.
Can I like fucking scoop slam him and take over his place?
I don't understand.
Like I don't care if I'm the new Jeremy.
Jeremy, if you're listening to me in the future, just come do it and be the Jeremy.
That's fine.
I don't get it.
I am me. I am the future me.
What's he talking about?
I don't get it.
I just need to get to the DLC and save the game.
And then I'll never open the game again.
I will never open this game again.
I just have to get to the DLC and then turn it off.
Alright. Let's go.
Oops.
Alright. Let's do it.
Alright. Is that a full jump?
I don't remember.
It's been a while.
It is. Okay.
Okay.
Just get into the DLC.
Not a big deal.
Don't worry.
It's not a big deal.
Not a big deal.
That's the first time.
Oh, God.
I've attempted that before.
It's the first time I've attempted that in a long time.
I haven't attempted that in a long time, guys.
Fix the stream name.
This is not a Jump King stream.
I don't need to change the title.
I'm just sampling.
Don't.
Okay.
I have stuff talking.
Alright.
Fucking I'll change the title name.
Fine.
Jeez.
Alright.
Here we go.
Title name is just testing out the DLC.
And then that's it.
Is it Jump King?
Does it say Jump King?
What are you talking about?
We're good?
Time for the DLC.
Let's go.
I'll try it once.
Just to look at it.
I just want to test it.
Okay.
Let's test out the DLC.
Just give it a look.
Okay.
Let's give it a look.
Let's just give it a quick little look.
Let me get right here.
Looks good.
Just give it a look.
Okay.
Let him look bad.
Looks pretty good.
Alright.
Cool.
Easy.
This way, right?
Yep.
Give it a look.
I remember I did a little bit of this.
A little bit more.
Just give it a look.
Just a fun little six hour look.
I'm not going to do that guys.
Alright.
I gotta slow down.
It's just.
Alright.
I'm good.
We're fine.
Everyone just relax.
Have a good New Year.
Hope you had a good New Year's Eve.
Okay.
We're back.
Good.
Bro.
2020 sucks.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
Hopefully 2020 gets better.
Oops.
I didn't see.
I didn't know they had a top.
Get birdy.
You're going to lose.
That's not true.
Is that true?
Wait.
Stop getting in my head.
Fuck.
God damn it.
You're still streaming this shit.
No.
I'm not.
This is not a real stream.
It's not a real stream.
This is a.
I'm just trying to test out what I think about the DLC content.
If this was a real stream, you would know.
Because I'd be like, you know.
Yeah, I tested it.
I did.
Yeah.
And it's fine.
It seems like it's pretty cool.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, I just want to fucking test it.
I just want to.
I just want to test it.
I am sort.
I'm kind of in the zone with the game at the moment, though.
I will tell you.
What?
No, stop distracting me.
Don't distract me.
Why are you distracting me like this?
Why?
Stop distracting me.
Everyone's distracting me.
Stop.
Just don't distract me.
Fuck.
OK.
People are distracting me.
I got to turn.
OK.
You know what I got to do?
I got to turn on.
Slow down.
I got here before.
I've been here before.
Emote only?
No.
I just have to stop looking over the screen.
I forgot there was ice in the video game.
All right.
We're good.
That's a pretty good test.
Not a bad test.
Close the game now.
No, it's all good.
I'm all right.
I just want to keep testing some things.
Don't go that far.
I got to go shorter than that.
I went fucking around when I told you guys I was like, dreamed about this game.
What?
Come on.
I can do this.
What time is it?
It's 11 o'clock?
It's not that late.
Oh, my God.
What did I do that for?
All right.
You guys are distracting me.
You guys are distracting the fuck out of me.
Everyone's just yelling my name and shit.
I'm in trouble now.
OK.
Here we go.
All right.
We're fine.
I'm back.
There we go.
OK.
Thank you for the non-distractions.
I appreciate it.
All right.
We're good.
What time is it?
It's been six hours.
It's not like...
You guys act like it's been 30 hours.
It's only been like six hours.
All right.
Not too crazy here.
There we go.
All right.
What's up here?
What should I do about this?
Bounce off this wall?
Wait.
No.
From here.