I'm on time. What are you talking about?
A lot of you guys just sit here and wait till 201.
Just start spamming me. How you doing? What's up?
This isn't movie night. No, that's...
That's next weekend.
I'm gonna give you the schedule. Just hold on.
How are my balls doing?
Weird question to start with, but...
They're doing alright.
No spooky games this Halloween.
Well, we're gonna change it up this year.
Instead of playing spooky games around Halloween time,
we're gonna watch horror public domain movies.
We're gonna watch old scary movies from like 1950, 1930.
That's what Public Domain Movie Night 2 is all about.
That stream, I'll give you a little bit of time to prepare for that
in case you don't want to miss it.
It's gonna be the 30th.
Not streaming on Halloween this year for the first time.
And probably, well, it's been a long time.
I'm streaming the day before Halloween.
Not streaming on Halloween night.
I need to go trick or treating.
That's right.
And I don't go back in until my pillowcase is full.
See the people walking around with the little buckets
that can hold like 12 pieces of candy?
Ah, excuse me.
No, no, you walk around...
The guy that has a stick with the knapsack on it.
You just walk around until you fill the whole bag.
You get only coal, you weirdo.
This is if it's not Christmas.
Imagine somebody opened the door.
You're like, oh trick or treat.
And they opened the door, they had fucking, like a Christmas hat on.
The guy comes out, he's like oh ohoho how laid, kids!
Oh hey, Mr. Stevenson, how are you?
These you're kids?
And you see this guy drops coal in all the kids' bags.
Oh, this is not for you, this is for your dad over there.
He keeps letting the dog shit on the lawn.
You go give that to him.
All right, give me one second. I'll be right back starting soon. You're so funny
Thank you. I'll be right back. I
Swear to God some of you guys just don't know but I'll tell you
It's it's like before every stream. It's like the intro to home alone in here. I'm running all over the place. I'm gonna find everything
Like the channels live and I'm looking for my phone. I'm sprinting around that electrocuted tweet now
I know that's what I was doing
I'm gonna get my phone so I can tweet stream overwatch. What what the fuck would I do that for?
All right, give me give me a second. I'll be right back
Give you code. Oh, where's the dog? I'm here my whole my whole fucking family left
I don't know where they are. I'm just beat the shit out of two grown men with like hot wheels
But hello. How are you? Good to see you. They smite. No
No, we're gonna play this actually is what we're gonna do. We're gonna play youtubers life, too
This is a game that I played. I think I streamed this game the first one
Yeah, this is the new it this came out like two days ago three days ago
I just found you and you're my favorite streamer. Well, thanks
I hope you still believe that in a week when I do something that makes you very upset
Oh, I found this new guy's my favorite streamer. How can they can't read the clock? This guy's a fucking idiot. All right. Bye
He's ready. This is this is we're gonna start youtubers life, too
That's not even is that correct then that doesn't have letters on that keyboard. Where's a what is this keyboard?
This is the thing that a stenographer types on. This is not even a keyboard youtubers life. Oh my god. All right
Congratulations, you are the first to complete youtubers life a social experiment to find the most promising future youtubers
But this is from supposed to be the from the first game
So we're getting Peter Molyneux right now
Your potential has caught our attention and so we are giving you a golden ticket to come and live in Newtube city
The city where the best youtubers live the perfect place for you to build your career and become one of the best
Damn YouTube City. I got to the center of the cube. So Southern, California
If you accept the invitation, I'll be waiting there for you to guide you in this new adventure
Do you accept the challenge? I mean in real life. I'd be like, no, thank you
Like I don't know who you are. I don't know how you got on my screen. You like hacked my zoom
Appeared on my screen. Well, what if I was naked what we just saw was somebody playing a game
Just sitting in their room with the lights off. What if I was just sitting here naked or so like get out of here
What are you doing? Leave me alone. That's my dream. Of course, where do you want to live?
City Hall
Downtown or the port. Let's get this right
Why are you always naked because it's natural way to live especially in your own house
I don't think I think clothes
Honestly clothes like if I'm gonna go anywhere sure but to like dress up to be in my own like place
There's like nobody around what I'm not gonna put a suit and tie on
Why would I do that? So you guys all question mark me and call me a weirdo
But I do way less laundry than you do guaranteed app. I guarantee it. All right downtown get a haircut
You don't know what hair looks like. You don't even how do you know what my hair looks like right now?
What are you talking about? All right
Do you want to go downtown the high-tech neighborhood known for its video game stores PC component stores in a gym chill out neighborhood
It's the most modern one and it's known for its hairdressers
Beach restaurants and the members only club or City Hall the most traditional neighborhood it stands out for its luxury stores and restaurant
Traveling fair and the City Hall. There's only one restaurant here stands up for its luxury stores and its restaurant
Okay, I don't I count about more than one restaurant go downtown
I would oh good. This guy's been peeking over my shoulder the whole time. I'm good choice
We'll start preparing your apartment dress up like a real youtuber and I'll see you there like pajama pants
Like a fucking headband and like a white t-shirt. All right, create your character body type
Okay, that's fine. That looks fine eyes
Where's my slate blue eyes? They don't have them. You're a ten-year-old Pokemon character creator
What would you guys say is more like my eyes I think it's these ones all right facial features
I thought these are big thick eyebrows a lightning bolt. It's a big scar. Oh
Is there facial hair? What about mouth? What's the difference? I got a big mouth. Oh, man
I like this one because it's just so it's so weird looking. It doesn't it just looks wrong. It just looks odd
All right hairstyle. This looks like those Funko pops the
Unedited Andy you talking about unedited Andy. Why are you saying unedited Andy?
that's a really fun word to say though out loud say it out loud close your eyes and
Just say unedited unedited. There's a lot of like D's and E's and the consonants bounce unedited
Unedited you want to go with the default go with this one. It's too much fucking work to have here be like that
It's just is all right. Let me be really honest. Hold on a minute. Let me just clear my throat
Comes a boomer take it's too much work to hear like this
You should just have to be flopping over on the side of a really it's like take so this like takes like an hour
I do this. It's too much
That's fine. Whatever
I want cool glasses
No, not really. No, not really. No
Actually, maybe I kind of want this I'm gonna keep it a for Andy
Stop saying Andy just because I say it like once every few weeks doesn't mean we have to say but everything has to be Andy
headphones
No, I don't know
No, no, I have yeah have fun wearing this and then have your ears hurt. It's painful to fucking touch them
This is great though. Let's have huge headphones
I don't know why that became a thing you wear these things for more than an hour and you'll take them off and it's like
Ow and if you touch your hair touches your ears, it's like fuck that hurts. I don't understand these that's true
I got I saw at least two truths. Thank you
I don't want to wear those guys don't you understand as long as one person says true in the chat
I am correct. See, no, I don't this is not nothing
I would ever put on a but let me give you some advice. Well, this is not a device
This is before you think I'm a weirdo a button-up shirt like this
I would you don't wear that to like go get coffee at Starbucks
I wouldn't the amount of time it takes to button those four buttons is too much time for me to go get like a coffee
Now if I was if there was like a event I was going to or if it was like a work thing or something
Yeah, that's just too much. It's too much time. Maybe I'm just a weirdo, which I mean, maybe I am
There we go. Not too much time. Just a jacket. It's a little weird. Just put the seashells on. No, that's that's too wacky
I don't want it. I don't that's way too wacky
They just have like a pac-man t-shirt with wicked stained underarms like stained yellow underarms with like just a white t-shirt with stained
Underarms, where is that? This will do. All right, and like like a bathing suit. I wear jeans
I do I wear jeans or shorts. That's pretty
That's almost too put together. You know, I mean like the white tee and the jeans is almost like you're doing that on purpose
It's too put together. There we go. All right, that looks good. What's wrong with nothing? Just put an X. Wait, what?
Oh my god, you can
Wait, you can't right? I mean, uh, why would you be I'm not gonna walk around like this
The alright, this is my actual real attire every day
I swear to god, it's what I currently am I have pretty much on right now
This is just how I live every day in my privacy of my own place
If I was to make a video on YouTube, but this would be my outfit
That's what that's what I would be wearing right now. I wouldn't wear the sneakers though
It'd be big big white tube socks like your dad wears I don't wear those either they cut off circulation in my legs
That's a lie. I don't believe that
Yeah, this is it. This is literally what I wear every day
I'm starting to become like more aware of this now
But yeah, like just flip-flops a pair of shorts and nothing
This is what I wear every day, but the sunglasses aren't accurate, but then we're doing that for fun
It's very beachy, isn't it? I don't I live on a beach or something. I don't want to do that
My attire every day is like you should be in like the tropics
Okay, new tube after like sign up or sign in or something. Oh, that's that's my contact. That's the zoom hacker
Welcome to new tube city. This is your new home from now on that sounds real
I don't like the way you worded that that seems strange the way to say that
How about like welcome to new tube city welcome home or something from now on if I want to leave?
Isn't very big inside, but don't worry later on you'll be able to decorate and upgrade it as you like
Why would I like I'm gonna like assault this guy with my hand? I'm like my fist is clenched like I'm gonna punch him in the face
Now go inside. I've left you a present. I've got to go. We'll talk later
This is I'm clenched fish. I'm ready to hurt this guy. I'm ready to punch him
German release your nudes when you retire, but like that's
The last thing I do before I'm done streaming. Oh, you know what?
Guys here's every selfie I've ever taken on my phone. It's like it's like 700 images. There's some of them naked
I don't even care. I
Don't take pictures. All right. What we got. What's this? It's like a VR helmet. Oh starting up. No, this isn't accurate
I gotta get this accurate. Everybody here has a youtuber voice even the robots, but I have to make sure I get that right
Make sure I get this correct. Okay
That sounds pretty good
Okay. Hi, I'm a drone cam
personal recording assistant
Beep-beep, please. Give me a name drone name. Whatever. I
Cherry I don't like that
Robbot dynamo X
Jaeger
I don't like any of these we'll make our own
I don't know copper tube. No Otto trouble and
Ron little Ella count drone Kiela. How about you take the take the count up drone Kiela tube. All right, that's fine
It's lovely to meet you I'll be here to record you and help you whenever you need me first step
Learn how to record videos but before you do you need to create your YouTube channel
The platform with the best content creators post your videos people of mine is doing this a lot
This is sound bad. I fuck it up things this voice sucks and the thing sucks. Oh the name. Okay. All right
This is new to your name
Jerma pick a name choose wisely but I can
Insert your channel name. Okay, hold on. All right your channel
Does it have to be like a dot-com or like a YouTube or not a YouTube?
You know what I mean? Like, oh, is this my channel name? This is important Ryder
Caesar 985
Okay, I like that Madden 985 Darryl 985
Gilberto 985
David 985 insert your channel name. We don't know that that's your name. Okay. Oops
There we go. Here's your birthday
Let's do let's do a summer birthday for David
Date second, let's do the I don't know spring 20. I don't know spring one who cares
28 days
What calendar are they going on only 28 days in the year when they cut what just make it yourself summer one beep beep
What a nice name David. Would you like to test me out now? Yes
I'm intrigued. This is a recording point for you to record videos
You can find points like this one around the city. I can do IRL videos
Okay, use the recording point to record your first introductory vlog for the channel. You don't start with a vlog. I'll record you. Okay
Record your first vlog. You don't start with a vlog. Let's go record. I have a microphone
This is dead. I'm gonna edit this part out. This is dead air. Am I recording? Am I new subscribers?
How do I record?
Said anything
Actually, you know what this probably get a lot of views because it's fucking weird. How do I do anything Ohm vlog
Which camera this one? Oh
Okay, you start recording and you shyly say hello. You're full of energy. Hey, what's going on everybody?
You go on and on and then you let out a what the fuck you flatter yourself
Oh, you make a bad joke. You let out what WTF you pout and you're in chill mode
Dronekilla tube is losing battery you ask for a subscriber
But my cameras out of battery. I beg for subscribers. Okay, you're my clips. I watch them
activate chill mode
Okay, this is a normie germa. Well, you didn't say that you said normal beep beep nice acting David
I mean acting as well as it wasn't a vlog. We who's acting on a vlog first
We'll touch it up a bit by editing on your computer
What if I don't want this is not how this works
I have to make like 30 of these in a row before I decide which one I actually want to use
Okay vlog recording trends. Okay vlog this tool is the video editor
You can use it to edit your videos and finish giving them your personal touch
Okay, the goal is to get as many points as possible. Make sure the clips connect to each other
Well, I'm gonna fuck this whole thing up
If you manage to connect them from the start to the end of the video
You'll get a juicy bonus later when you have a better PC with more rendering points
You'll be able to buy video effects and use them in your clips to boost your edits even more and now I'll let the creative genius
Unleash his imagination. All right, I don't know what the context of these clips even is I like see this
Oh, they have like connecting points. This is so stupid
Okay, this is just like a puzzle. I
Need a connector here. I
Can't I editing videos is hard. What do I start with this one? It's the pipe game
I don't think I can even connect these can I I have enough pieces to do this
I don't think I have enough pieces to do this. Who cares just go in order. I don't care
I don't think you can do it choose the video's thumbnail. They're all the same. Everything's the same video bad video
She's clickbait phrase if this was accurate if this is accurate. This person has no idea what they're doing
Okay, that looks good dot web M. I
Can't I can't add anything to it. It's fine. I like this title. Why can I publish video? Yeah, let's go include the date stamp
Oh shit, that's right video posted final score. Oh, no, you're not famous yet. You did one video. What the fuck?
What the hell just what now?
It's not worth it
PP grab your phone and install the new tube app
Check the video you just post and see other youtubers ranking in the city your goal gain loads of subscribers
Okay, check out the new tube app. Yeah
Okay, my profile journal contacts new tube your latest videos my ranking one video published three likes
It was me at least one of those is me. You guys have to understand something when you're starting out
I remember like 10 plus years ago. I remember the proportion of likes to dislikes where
It's when you have three or four likes and even one or two dislikes. That's a potential 50%
Ratio one dislike here is world-changing. I remember when that used to happen
I would have a video go up and it would be like 30 40 likes and there would be like two or three dislikes and I'd be
That's fucking world-ending. That's such a huge percentage
Zero views where you see zero views. Oh shit. There's no views
Okay, let's go back. All right, so I have this my cats are trending
deity of war honey play studios one and adventure games
All right, we need to have a cat in the video. All right, did you know that I can also record it commentary scripts on the computer?
Scripts are a type of video. I don't know how to record without them
Xavier says there's a load of them hidden around the city
Have to go plagiarize people every time you record with a script you improve its quality and this is how you get better clips
And scores shall we try a commentary video to see if you get the first 30 subscribers to your channel
Okay, I just go around and like take steal scripts from trash cans. Let's go 30 subs. I can do it commentary. Let's go
Why am I like
Using mind like powers
To start the video
Shyly say hello poltergeist appears and a poltergeist appears where you have a laughing fit
that's what I would do you go on and on and then
Let's get into chill mode here again. I don't know if somebody likes this and it's over you asked for subscribers and it's over
All right. We're gonna have to sign off we go
All right, save
Remember that you need to edit and post the video on the computer. Here's a commentary. Oh fuck people gonna think I'm so stupid
I'm not supposed to go in order. Okay, so this one has the down down. I can't connect these
There's no way I can possibly connect all these just go in order. There's there's no what do you mean?
You're not supposed to connect all of them. Oh
Okay
Does that get double points get as many connections as possible and not just put them all on there?
Okay, hold on. Can I get more like this?
Now it has to start with this because it's red. All right, there you go
Well, how's this worse editing 1 2 3 4 this 1 1 1 2 there's no 1 2 3 4 it's 1 1 1 2
What do you see 1 2 3 4?
1 1 1 2. Oh, that's 14 14
You have to get to the 10-minute mark so you get the post roll
No, I had it right the first time see that's good. That's good enough. Oh, this is stupid
Video where I'm sitting naked just fucking saying hi to people. This one is 30 points
I try I connected the three and it was like 20
I can what best kept youtubers secret by adding effects to your clips
You can make your video to the stratosphere excuse render points, but you'll have to update the editor and buy them first
Oh, I only have a hundred render points. I can't do anything about this. Let me just see what happens if I do this
18 see the other one was better. See I know what I'm doing. You're a washed-up youtuber. You're never gonna hit it big
No
Probably not anymore. If I started those TF2 videos now people just think I was a fucking moron
I sure did luck out on that one. All right title. No what video?
Excuse me. I think my videos were very interesting and interesting topics. I don't get me wrong. I love all my videos
They're all my children. All right title who cares
This is how you make the best commentary with hashtag home. I play like the metadata
Should I put hashtag cats but that no this stuff never works
If you put hashtag cats in here and it's a trending topic people come to the channel and they say there's no cat here
This guy's a dick. I hate this guy as they make people hate you. I was like
Oh, man, you gotta make sure you're like tags are really like really pull viewers and shit
They'll just lie to people and everyone hates me after like a month
How would I do that? That was better than the last one. Thank you. I got subs
Holy shit 30 scripted video game subscribers that give them to you in the very beginning to go through the tutorial to make sure you
Get to over a hundred
Ring, it's already midnight. It's time to go to bed
Sleeping helps you get back your energy and progress to the next day
You can stay awake until 4 a.m. You won't be able to get all your energy back for the next day. Good night, David
I'll call you tomorrow morning to tell you something important. Don't call me anymore Xavier. In fact, I'm gonna change
I'm changing like literally I'm changing my name. I'm changing everything about my life
I don't like this guy. He's scary. Let's go to bed. Ooh
I thought I was in a bathtub for a second. Maybe they're sleeping with the sandals on. Yeah, that's weird
Seems today is gonna be a good day. Luck is on your side young youtuber. What am I a fucking padawan? Okay
I need to I need to do a video about armored nucleus. Hmm. Hmm
Hey David, I just saw the videos you uploaded to your channel. They're good, but you might have noticed that they haven't gotten many visits
That's because they aren't good. I'm lying to you
I'm a manager agent person that just roped you into this isn't scamming you and it's gonna take
40% of all of your money check the daily trends to record and upload a video on them
You'll get more visits and subs check the trends on my phone. All right, here's my quests
Pay attention to what's currently trending in the city. They're split according to popularity into unknown normal well-known very there
It's their loot its loot colors
So this is okay this high profile. Oh my god now the deity of war game is pretty popular
But when you see any high profile or trending topic, you've got to go for it
This type of mentality to me is just like the ambulance chaser of like the lawyer world
No
I don't just make videos on what you want to make videos on
Like if I wake up in the morning and I see that like cats are trending on fucking YouTube
I'm not gonna rip out of the covers
Scramble to get out of bed and freak out to make a cat's video
They just do what you feel like doing make the videos make this stuff that you'd like to do
I don't I don't like this
I don't that's not don't listen to this popular trends in your content is the key to your videos getting lots of views and subscribers
This is why you aren't successful
This guy this guy over
Okay, well
Hmm
Six or seven million subscribers across all the platforms. I mean, it's like seven or eight million subscribers followers
I mean not was excuse me. It's definitely like not even a million by the way
It's I think it's like two million total
Arrogant have you seen that highest trending videos are about video games to record these kinds of videos
You need to install a gaming corner in your home. Why?
Remember you're a shadowy elite
This person saying it read arrogant prick. Fuck you. We all hate you and watch you to make fun of you behind your back
Well, is it behind my back when you're all here doing it now? Oh, I'm aware. I need a gaming corner
Okay, add furniture add new workspace gaming corner
I wish I put this over here in the corner. I mean it says gaming corner
Oh, I feel like it'd have to be in a corner perfect
Now you've set up your gaming corner now all you need to do is game and a console and you be able to start recording gaming
videos
Alright many youtubers post gaming content try to find the most popular video games by the way
I've ordered you a game and a console so you can start go speak
Why did you buy me things go speak to Blair the girl in the player one video game store?
She'll give them to you. I think this actually is something
Playing the popular games on Twitch and YouTube is almost a guaranteed way to
Not get very much attention like if I would have start playing a game that's in like the top 10 right now
There's potentially thousands and thousands and thousands of people doing that too. It doesn't matter how much it's trending
It's hard to stand out when you play the most popular video games because if I were to start streaming right now
Let's say I don't know what's like a really popular game right now
I don't like League of Legends or something, right?
If I were to start doing that now, there are probably thousands of other people all in the same boat doing the same thing
It's it's harder to stand out when you play like the popular trending topics
Even nobody's looking for youtubers life to content. Hey, you figured me out. You figured out the secret recipe play shit that nobody likes
Check the map app if you don't want to get lost beep beep. All right, it's all I got I have to go talk to this
Person play dragon rompo. I don't know what that is people keep asking me to do that
All right, so I gotta go get the console. Okay, and that is oh my vlog got three coins
All right, the player one video game store. Where's that net flow these all aspiring youtubers? Can I talk restaurant?
Okay, do I have a map? All right, we need to go to player one. All right, so right there
There's my house was literally right across the goddamn Street. Okay. No, I'm kidding
I play the things I think are fun
You guys have seen me play popular games on this channel for like a decade
I'm listening to anything I say it's all horseshit
Player one. Did I play smite if you want to play it and you think it's fun?
All right, so I'm picking up my console that this weird guy that just flew me out here ordered for me
Okay, League of Stars
What do I pick it up? Talk to Blair. Is this Blair? Where's Blair this deity of war? It's Dixie behind the counter
Okay. Hi, I don't help you with something. I'm here on behalf of Xavier
Okay, you're the new youtuber in town. Well Xavier called me to give you this
You are the console honey play studios one in the game deity of war
I would not hold this like this. They're all stored in your bag bag has limited space
This is just how people that go to the midnight release for games that do this
They run out if you're the first in line you run out with the thing you hold it up and everyone fucking cheers
Everyone's like yeah. Hey David. Do you have the game and console yet? Yes, right now. Let's record your first gameplay
Our new wow expansion. Oh, dude wrath of the Lich King. Are you serious Nax is out?
All right, let's go make a gameplay video. Wow. I played wow for like 30 years
I'm gonna make a reference to it every now and then I have talked about this before but listen to this
I have been there's more Wow in my head than I believe
Potentially time that I was in college
You understand like the amount of time that I was sitting in a classroom in college
Probably is the amount of time also that I was in world of warcraft. It was hundreds of days
So, of course, it's gonna be up there
Head is empty
No, it's just it's no, you know
My head the head is too full
I would like to go in to my head and sort of
Defrag it and just sort of delete a bunch of old info that I don't even care about anymore to make room for more
Oh shit record a gameplay you first need to place the game and console in the gaming corner and select the game and get recording
Make me want to quit video. Wait, what do you say? You make me want to quit video games
So I don't end up like you what why?
What I'm not like screaming at you and what are you talking? I'm what does that mean? I'm kind of pretty normal
I'm just like hanging out. I said I what do you mean? I don't want to end up like you
I don't have any consoles. Oh, here we go console storage one. I put it on. Oh, here it is. Okay console and video game
Let's go. All right
It's time to record video with deity of war join prometheus on his mission to save humanity
tutorial first impressions speedrun
analysis
Okay, I have to have gameplay reactions. You start recording and say hello
Yeah, whatever you have to play the game you unlock a new map you ship
I unlocked a new map. I don't understand you play for giggles
Like you your health is at one percent, but you skip you skip you
No, but you skip you ship your health is at one percent. So you ship you skip you skip you ship
What am I what am I doing?
You ship and it's over
Let's get some subs
Skip and ship ship is relationship. I don't but who
I said I unlocked a new map. What am I shipping the monopoly pieces?
Like I have a board or just a map. I don't get it. All right, let's go edit
I'm edit and for everyone to hate me because I do this wrong every time
I'm gonna do this wrong every single time. Just want to make sure people are aware of that
I'm gonna do this wrong every single fucking time. I'm not kidding. All right, let's go with uh,
Double double. No, not that one that one that one. Here we go. Here we go. All right, here we go thumbnail
Uh this one
Become an expert in deity of war in 10 minutes 20 never before seen adventure tricks the deity of war revolution
They hate this though. Is that a good enough title?
So I just skip every cutscene and just ship every character part four
Oh, they like it. They like it
All right. I published a gameplay. I did it
My energy is low
What do I get?
Plain hamburger
There are people buried in my in my backyard. Hey david. I thought you might be hungry after a long session recording and editing videos
Here's a plain hamburger. You won't be able to record or edit videos if your energy runs out for plenty of energy
You eat something or go to sleep?
Bunker w eating a plain hamburger is like that's serial killer vibes for me plain hamburger with nothing on it
Nothing just bun and meat. That's it. I mean if there was ketchup on it or anything. It's weird, right?
Does any of you guys eat just a plain just one hamburger patty and just bun?
I feel like everybody adds something
Whether it's like a squeeze it i'm serious even like a squeeze of mustard like a tablespoon of mustard makes that not weird to me
Monka s chat full of serial killers
All right, luckily saviour just sent you some food. I'm not gonna eat food somebody sent in a box
Tablespoon is a lot of mustard. I've seen a lot of people put way more mustard than that. What do I eat big afk?
An irresistible hamburger with okay, it's fine. Although I would remove the tomato
I would remove the tomato and I would probably remove the ketchup as well
I'm not gonna do look. I don't have to do the tomato sucks rant every like two months
We should have a clip for it because I mean every time I talk about how I don't like tomato people go
What are you talking about? So should I just do a clip so people would take like, uh
Like exclamation point point like tomato. Okay, here we go
Just real quick i'm gonna get this out of the way tomato on sandwiches or burgers or anything if you put a slice of no
Don't get me wrong. I love tomatoes. I love the vegetable tomato. I love tomato sauce. I love
Roasted tomatoes roasted cherry tomatoes. I look like tomato if it's a tomato dish
I love it to make a slice of tomato on a hamburger or a sandwich is
disgusting to me because the tomato is usually wet and slimy and
If you take a bite
It turns to like this weird sludgy water in your mouth
And sometimes you pull the whole tomato out while you pull back a tomato does not necessarily belong on a sandwich for me
It makes whatever you're eating wetter. Let me ask you a question. You know, you wash lettuce
Imagine you took just wet lettuce you rinsed lettuce. You didn't even let it dry
You just washed it
It was soaking wet and you put it right on the bun and you it's gonna be watery watery lettuce and soggy
You really want that you got to let it dry wait for it dry it cools it down
How hot are you?
How are you eating your hamburgers? What temperature are you eating your meat at?
It cools the burger down. Okay, so clip that I love tomatoes. I do
I just don't like tomatoes sliced on a sandwich. It kind of messes it up for me
I feel the same way about some onions, right? I love onions on it
I love onions on a tomato, but I don't want it on
Somebody's ringing. What is it now? Why don't you relax a bit and explore the city?
You're new in town and you need to meet people having good friends, which will definitely help your youtuber career
There are certain celebrities and odd neighbors in new tube city. Why don't you go meet them?
Okay, let me close that out onions are good on a burger
But they have to be done. I don't like it when it's just the big circle onion ring without the bread on it
You know what i'm talking about?
Why do people do that?
You get like you bite it and you get like fucking onion skin and like the whole chunk comes off it
No, no, I don't get that chopped onions. Yes sliced onions. Yes, but that big
Onion ring onion. No, you're a nine-year-old. No, i'm just I don't like weird texture on my hamburgers
Do your teeth not work? It's just no, I don't like it. It's it's what are you talking about?
Do you like tobaccos?
What just order tomato on the side? It doesn't sog up the sandwich burger when you order to go
Yeah, but eventually i'm gonna be putting it on i'm just gonna eat the tomato like a potato chip
Can I have a slice of tomato on the side like just to go yes
That I don't really like tomatoes like that. Don't listen to them. You're right
I just don't like tomatoes like that because like the seed like the tomato like the insides. I don't know. It's just like
I don't like it. It's too mushy to be on a sandwich. What if they put tomato paste on a burger?
You're referring to ketchup, which I think is good. I like ketchup. I think that's fine
Dude, you know if they made like a hamburger
Uh
Tomato paste. All right. I'm gonna go out on a limb here if they made a burger that was
You know like a chicken palm sandwich
What if it was a burger palm and it was just a cheeseburger, but it had like marinara sauce and cheese on it
That might not be pretty good hamburger palm. There's your tomato paste hamburger
All right. I'm what am I supposed to be doing? You guys are distracting me
Okay spicy ren the best spicy dishes in newtube city. All right, so this is the restaurant
All right, we got trends here. Should I make another video? I was gonna make another video. Why not meet 10 neighbors?
All right. We're not i'm making another video. All right, we're gonna do a gameplay and can I talk about cats?
You start and I shyly say hello
Oh a mini boss appears and you make a technical comment. You explain the lore you skip the boss
Uh, oh all the gamers didn't like that. You sense a paranormal presence. You make a technical comment
You add you sign off and it's over should have talked about the lore
Do these have a description? I don't really know what these all mean. All right, let's go publish it
I should do a vlog too. Shouldn't I? All right, let's start with this one. I'm gonna go
This one this one this one
Sure, why not?
I don't care about what the title is. No, it doesn't matter. I just do one of these get the latest the biggest gameplay pro
How about the biggest gameplay pro of adventure when I skipped the boss? That's gonna piss off subscribers though my gameplay on home
I think that's probably the default
For if you save like a playstation 4 video on the ps4 action game play
Another game play the best game play gameplay. What about adventure another game play the best thing about deity of oar game play
Home game play gameplay. What about adventure? We're gonna talk about adventure game play. That's good
Do a two-minute fart prank video with eight-minute vlog about family stuff
What
A two-minute fart prank. I gotta go meet people but i'm tired. Hold on. Why would you read that?
My house is wait a minute. My home's value is increasing because
My subscribers are increasing. That's weird. That's how it works
You leave a bowl of candy out for trick-or-treaters you asshole. Excuse me. That's trespassing. No
Good morning, david
Did you know that the event all the youtubers are waiting for is coming to the city in the last week of spring?
Uh, I don't know what that is
It's the playcon gaming festival and it's celebrated once a year in newtube city
This festival will be full of influential people from the area conferences events
You can't miss the playcon if you want to make yourself known you're gonna get egged
You imagine I had like a note
Imagine you lived in a in a place and you put a note on your door
No halloween decorations nothing and it just said like the act of trick-or-treating is trespassing
I do not support this this this archaic old stupid lifestyle or something, right?
You have like a huge note on the door
That's the kind of person that I would assume would be the person that's complaining
If you had like an hoa or something about like your garbage cans being too far away from the curb
That's who that person I think is right
By the way use the fact that everyone is talking about the playcon festival to your advantage and post playcon content
Teepied or egged would you just wake up to like a completely mummified house?
I feel like that's you'd walk out the door turn around and your house would be just a completely mummified and then it rains
Oh god, what if it rained your house would just be taped paper mache
All right, let's go to the the convention. There's a huge promotional poster in the city
You know how you can post content almost instantly for your followers
How with the insta life app i'll listen to me guys listen to me listen to me
Whatever you're doing right now
Stop what you're doing turn the volume up a little bit and sit here for a moment and listen to me
You don't got to do all that shit. You don't have to you don't it doesn't it's okay
You don't have to do all this you don't have to have like 30 instagram posts a week
You don't have to be on twitter every day. You don't have to do this. You don't have to listen up the fucking video game
Listen to me everybody everybody
Let's get serious do it because I want to
Yeah, I hope that's true. I feel like there's a shitload. Let's get real you ready
I feel like there's a shitload of pressure right now on a lot of people that are in the younger age brackets to constantly
Need to sort of make everybody aware of what they're doing. Just do it in moderation
Trust me. It feels like a lot of the younger crowd is in a constant competition with each other
You know what i'm saying? You're getting political. That's not political. That's just life
I'm so glad i'm not growing up with the social media stuff from today
I can't imagine how damaging that mindset is to little kids. Yeah, just be careful. Don't get too
Into it don't get too don't let it consume you because it can and I especially when you're really young too
Some of like the 10 11 12 13 year olds
I don't know. I just I feel like I i'd be like in this constant mindset of constant
You got a lot of shit to worry about too when you're like a teenager, right?
It's like another thing to have to be in a constant competition about it's limited. This stream is 18 plus. They're not here
Move on it's a social network app for you to share your photos with your followers instantly
This would also help you make yourself a known a known person in the city
You can also follow people you know see what they're posting and they can even send you private messages
They've done surveys that said that yeah, it's a lot to have to pay attention to like guys
I only I post like once every three months on twitter
I have to disconnect I have to germa fans are proto boomers that live under rocks and only watch germa and eat taco bell
It's a proto boomer proto boomer your companion
Dronekilla tube will install the app for you. All right, let's play all right installing insta life
Open it now publish a photo with playcon, but i'm not even i'm not there
Am I gonna like pretend i'm at playcon this year? The playcon is coming to new tube city
I am not going to miss it. I am i'm not going i'm not going no i'm not going
Am I following? Okay, where is it playcon? I'm not going open from seventh to the twelfth
Wait, what?
This convention is like 20 days. Oh my goodness
That's insane
Well now I have to go I have to go for at least one of those days
Blair has some things for you talk to her at the video game store and tell her that you get sent
Did I already do that? Okay publish a photo with playcon. Okay. I gotta go take a photo. Let's go
post oh shit
Not going to playcon staying home with my cats and playing. Oh cats aren't trending anymore
Oh, I just copied her
This looks like a sarcastic mean response to this doesn't it? Yeah
I'm trying to get the like the contrarian crowd, right? It's a subtweet. It's a contrarian subtweet. That's what this is
All right, let's go. I didn't get it. I have to go take a picture in front of the all right
All the gamers are waiting for playcon. Why don't you create content on it? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, where is it?
I said hit m where is it? All right, it's down here
Boxing gym record video. Oh shit vlog in front of the boxing gym
Am I like a reporter? What am I doing here?
Full of energy
Thank you followers for the support and you think it's a good piece of information
Flatter yourself in front of the gym. I gotta get swole
A poltergeist appears and you make a bad joke
Uh losing battery
All right, ask for subs and get up
He's hallucinating
Oh, that's actually a four star video. I'm gonna hold on to this until people think uh boxing is
In like gyms and whatever is cool because I can just hold on to this video for potentially years
And upload it whenever I want I can just act like I recorded it yesterday
All right, take a picture of one of those sign
Oh, wait now I actually hold on
I can't
There we go
This is playcon has me so excited staying home is cool
But I heard deity of war is getting dlc not going to playcon staying home with my cats and playing deity of war
This is like an ai account. These are the kinds of accounts that you see on
Like across like the dating apps. It's like this is this is a really fucking person
Like is this even a real dude?
Should I just do it again and just copy?
This year the playcon is coming to new tube city. I'm not going to miss it
Just do that. Just repost that
Well, if you didn't like that one as much
This account sucks. I need to put all these hashtags in it. Okay, hold on remember these playcon adventure armored
Armored nucleus honey play we got to remember these somebody write these down
Have you noticed that the trend you just got has been captured?
There are trends that when you discover them remain captured and you can talk about them in another kind of script
See which script you can use it in and take the opportunity to record a video of it because only it only lasts one day
I record a video in front of this
post a gameplay with playcon
Shit, okay. Hold on
What's this? Oh playcon?
Am I interviewing or interviewing somebody playcon?
All these camera angles are terrible
Why would this be a camera angle? All right, it's this one. Okay, you're running out of energy sleep
Oh, come on really?
Do you have any food? Let me go eat something. I'll be right back
How much money do I have our subscribers money?
Where's that restaurant? It's down here, right?
Am I it's right here?
Points. Oh, right. That's a weird. I don't know looks weird. I wish there was a sprint
All right record. No, no, no, I can't record a video. I have to get it. I have to eat
Okay, what am I gonna get?
uh
Susie
Oh nice a new face in the city. What's your name dear?
avid
Where are you?
Susie i'm the owner of spicy ren. I would not go up and introduce myself to the owner. I would sit down and order food
Okay. All right take out
Vegetable wok takeout. It's rice seasoned with spicy peppers
Probably just this one. This is the cheapest one, right?
And now let's eat
Meeting with my hands
All right. Let's go make that video because no I have to get the play con video
You have to make a mukbang
I'm not going to do a mukbang
Make a mukbang. No
I don't think you can
All right up here. They say it wrong. How do you say it? That's how isn't that how it's pronounced?
All right, I gotta interview these guys. All right. Okay. What is it? What do you what's your what are you looking forward to at?
Play studios con here we go you start and we're full of energy here
I heard deity of wars got some dlc coming out. You played deity of war yet. It's a paranormal presence
You were merciless with the hater from the previous video, but
You're in chill mode. What does that have to do with an interview?
To finish you sign off this person didn't say anything
All right. Thanks for the interview
All right got that
I'm so tired. How do I go home fast?
I only have eight hours to post a gameplay. I'm not going to be able to
I have a long way to go
Gameplay. Oh, okay
200 new views I can only sleep for like four hours
Where's my fucking apartment? Whatever it is?
I can take the bus
All right. Hurry hurry. Hurry. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go
Can I do it? No, I have to sleep. I can't edit a video
Shit how long do I sleep for? What about all I could eat in the noodles? Oh, no, I missed the trend free ticket play con challenge
Fuck i'm so behind. This is old news now
Good morning, david. I didn't mention it before but the ticket to the festival costs 500 coins
It's a lot of money, but there's a way of getting a little extra money since your videos aren't generating that much
Doing errands for your neighbors. There's an app where you can accept an order from anyone in the city in exchange for rewards
It's the commissions app start of any youtuber's career isn't easy if you need some money. Well use this app
Your companion drone kilotube will install the app for you
Installing the commissions app on your phone
You can open it now. I just want to tell you that I loved your last picture. We said that
We said that it was the grand cars race launch
We said that I got the free ticket to the play con
I won't say how just that there are three people in different areas of the city with the play con t-shirt who might know something
Okay, good to know
the play con
Deliver a package to blare pick up a package of spicy ren. I got it
Let's do it get the get the ticket to the play con. First of all, we have to edit this video
The interview and the vlog let's do the
interview first
Okay right there
Uh, yeah
Right looking good and things about play con that will surprise you the weirdest interview on newtube. Okay subscribers don't really care
Yeah, we'll do clickbait subscriber morale that that means they don't really care that much but visibility is high. Oh
Shit this game takes the most insufferable parts of youtube and ranks it up
I got another video to make hold on damn it
Okay
It has to be this one to start and then I don't think I can finish this one
You can't start with this because the red right no it has to be this one
Damn it. Oh, whatever. I don't care. I don't even care publish it. I don't I don't know what this was
um
The center the biggest vlog pro of center another vlog with center center vlog center vlog laughing about center vlog. Sure
Well, this is in front of the gym. Oh shit. They liked it. They actually liked it
All right
I think I gotta get that ticket put on a shirt. I will after I go to the bathroom people are loving battle royale games
Lately, so I gotta go buy one. How much is it? I have 87 dollars. We're gonna do that first
We're gonna jump on the trend
I don't give a shit about play con going on over here. All right, I gotta deliver that package
We'll do that first and i'm gonna go buy a battle royale game
Do the delivery i'm going for it right now
That person was pretending to be a dev and I was reading it
It was a long message and they got nuked when I got to the last sentence
Give me this package
All right, I gotta deliver this to i'm going to the play store. Anyways, we like fortnight. We like fortnight
No, I don't want to go home. Just take them that
It was an alt f4 joke
Where's this stupid video game place?
Down. Okay. Oh, ooh
Stupid there's a delivery and I gotta buy a battle royale game. Um, don't I have a delivery?
Yeah, what do you want? I have a delivery. How do I deliver this where to go talk to blair?
I have to hold it in my hands
Oh, thanks. I was waiting for it. I'll take 100 bucks and now I would like to purchase a battle royale game, please
The moba it's a shooter. I need a battle royale. No battle royale. Are there no battle royale games league of stars
I have to do at a different store. All right. Well, never mind. I thought somebody has a t-shirt, right?
People have play con t-shirts fortnight is free not in this world
All right. Now I gotta I gotta find people with play con shirts. What's going on here? I need different
Here look at camera this place
Oh fuck I can do this. That's good. All right, that's good. I'm getting a lot of followers
On this platform. This game is propaganda
It's not it's just a game. Don't worry
What do I need to do? All right, when does play con start? I need somebody with a play con t
Can I go in what about just walk over here? Let me in let me in I gotta upload a video on this
Hello, come on. I gotta be the first person to get up to hashtag play con video. What's in there?
I'm steaming up the glass. Oh my god
This is a statue of uh, who's that?
The statue of tracer in there. I can see it. What's that over there? Oh my god. I see all the boots
What do I have to do? I have to record first
Whoa, this is a I don't I can't be here yet
That's too much. I have to find somebody with a ticket to play con. Does anybody have a play con shirt on geek topia?
What is all this storm helmet?
Fifty four thousand dollars to attend your fancy dress party ultra armor cosplay spray paint
Do you guys have any other games vampires werewolves and a lonely young girl? This has never been seen before
banged up sweethearts
human
Dr. E recruits different mutant teenagers to fight against crime
But before they do they'll have to resolve their own conflicts
The new tube league a group of vigilantes joined forces with one goal to fight crime in new tube city
Give me this because i'm gonna make a video on it. I'm gonna read this and make a video on it
Jumanji. Oh
Scrabble you can't enter here. Okay, can you make sponsored videos?
No, but we're gonna make a fountain video. You can't record in the dark
Why do you look like you're gonna kick somebody's sandcastle at the beach?
Good question. You're right
Nobody I can't get play con tickets
All right. I'm going to bed. I'll try in the morning. Have you heard gianna would like to run for mayor
It makes that the man thinks he's owner of the city
Do I have any video files? I do dude. I do what is it?
No, I don't shit. I want to read that book
Old place in home hold it. I want to read it. How do I read it new setup?
All right, we're gonna go and put on the shelf. All right, can I read it new setup? I can't read it
I can't read whatever i'm going to bed
Laughing about the vlog. Okay, the vlog did. Okay, you put a book on the floor and wanted to make a new setup video
Graphics cards date. I have deity of war don't I?
I I watch all your videos to have a laugh and the last one made me sad
I don't even I don't even know what my last video was you can now get watch cats in your favorite video game store
Oh, this is trending. We gotta get it right now. We're gonna go to watch cats all of glitch is playing watch cats
I'm working on it. I didn't pre-order it though. Is that a problem? I mean watch cats watch cats. There it is
It's on the playstation. It's not I know whatever it's they're gonna get sued now that I said that or i'm gonna get sued
I don't know which one of us is gonna get sued because I said that I don't know who watch cats. I'm sorry
I just bumped you trending troy. Well, yeah, I have to do that. That's how i'm gonna play
I have to do it. No wrong way. We're gonna play it. I'm gonna give my first impressions of watch cats
Become the thing you hate the most
Okay, record video. We're gonna play
Watch cats tutorial. I can't do these gameplay start recording and I just got a copy of it
We're really energetic you enter battle royale mode and you explain the lore. This is a brand new game
nobody knows anything about it you get a super strange drop you look at it and
I um
I ship it
I guess people liked that a lot
And then I asked for subs because if you want to see more content from this game
You want to sub because i'm gonna be playing it every day
All right, good
Look at all these trends get this video up immediately
As i'm gonna i'm so desperate to get this video up because it's currently trending right now
There's not going to be an intro. There's not going to be an outro and there's not going to be a thumbnail
In fact, i'm going to just put this into the youtube editor and just press publish
Fuck this video is not I can't connect anything. I can't connect anything. What's the best combination I can do here?
That's eight. It's just the first one
This is the best thing I can do. I don't have a three or four
The video doesn't matter how bad the video is. I try to troll someone and it goes wrong
Watch cats the gameplay of home that will change your life
I try to troll someone. All right tons of visibility though. That's a lot of visibility. Let's see how it goes
Subscribers are pissed. How are we doing? All right. Now let me make an apology video
I'm talking i'm prepared for this
Not even five minutes after that video goes up. The apology video comes out right after I want a vlog
I need oh shit. I have to go to bed. I have to eat new commission
Deliver a package to suzy pick up a package in kiwi. All right, let's get that package. It's 2 pm
All right. I need to eat. Okay. Oh there's closing
You're mad, but you still gained and give me this. I don't have enough money to do any of this shit right now
All right, let's go see i'm gonna deliver this package and i'm gonna order some food
If you see somebody with a playcon t-shirt, let me know because that's who can get you tickets for free. I gotta pee
I gotta pee
I'm gonna go pee. I'll be right back
I have returned. Hello
How are we how are we doing doing good I need to buy on my chair
Sorry, my chair my chair is too far back. I would like to buy some food. What gives the most energy 20
50 delicious spicy noodles. That's so much money. It's funny. Okay, did it hurt peeing that fast? I actually took my time. Don't worry
uh
I don't have to I have to deliver this box. I wonder that you can sell the noodles. What do you mean sell?
Baby bladder. Yeah, i've gotten older. I took for granted just how
Normal and fine my body was when I was in my mid 20s
Okay
Now I gotta make the subscribers happy
How did I used to do that to you guys if you guys were like pissed about something?
What did I do usually right after anything?
Didn't it make shpee noises? I'm not sure. I think i've ever I don't think i've ever really pissed off
Like my subscriber base in quotes. I'm not sure i've ever really done that
That I can think of
I'm pissed off you have
You absolutely have have I oh i'm sorry
I'm sorry about that
You just did sorry about that
all right, uh
um
We need to go to
I need to find a ticket
I'm just gonna make another video. Whatever i'll make another video that makes people happy
We're gonna play this one watch cats again
gameplay
Start the video. We're gonna be very we're gonna be a little bit
On the muted side. You're the imposter you make a technical comment
The imposter like this not everything is you go on and on and then
You play for giggles to finish
you
Sign up sus
All right. That was this is actually going to be the best
This is a four star recording and a three star trend. This this might actually be my big break here
You're running up. Oh my god eat something among us gameplay. This is not among us gameplay. No
Is that the best combo I can do? I don't maybe not I think it is thumbnail i'm gonna be the wave
And we have to we have to clickbait this I think
No, ash tag
watch cats
How about no, okay, but you know the tactic the the tactic you put a sentence as the title
That is one to two seconds of your whole video and it might be a 12 minute video
That's the tactic
That's how you do it. Like for instance
That would be the title for the vod of the far cry six stream. Technically. That's not a lie
Happened at some point. It's there somewhere just make it that are there any alligators even in this game?
Reacting to shooter in a shooting gameplay, honey play studios gameplay. What about watch cats?
Okay, let's do this right right. What about what about hillary's emails?
All right, that's good for me. Oh
Big one. That's a big one
Thank you. I'll take it. There's gonna get a lot of views on this one. Let me go to the app
I need to see it your latest videos. Come on. Let's see the views. All right time to what time is it for night?
It's time for bed. Let's go. Okay. All right. All right, it's not bad. You don't sleep with a blanket
Why are you posting videos at 9 pm? I used to do that
I'm having a bad day. Nothing makes you happier than to see you publish a new video
I never miss one. Well, there's only been five so I appreciate that though
Um new commission
Susie is asking for a photo for insta-life upload a photo with the watch cats trend to insta-life and make your photography talent known
Okay, I want to take a picture. Can I not take him?
This finger thing
Do I have any clothes?
I'm begging you. Please have better composition. I don't I'm doing my best
You have rainbow sigil everyone's talking about that game
I don't i'm still making watch cats videos
It take a pic
What do they do for moves?
This one looks the closest here
Ready, they put their hand up and i'm gonna make it look like i'm doing it too
This one one two
Got it. Okay. What's the game that she wanted? What was the game?
2 000 likes. Oh, all right. I need to go to
How am I supposed to get rain? Do I have to just buy rainbow sigil and play it? Do another interview at playcon?
Get the ticket to the playcon. I gotta find a ticket paint
You need to buy paint a friend of mine goes to the gaming tournaments in afk every sunday
He says there's a lady who always goes there and slays. She humiliates all the young gamers
It literally starts tomorrow. Go find a ticket
Who am I supposed to talk to?
It starts tomorrow. What about I haven't looked at this side of the city yet, though
Playcon playcon playcon. That's just spider-man. It just is
Playcon it's open for 20 days though. Yeah, but I want to be the first person I want to be it's gonna be trending for the first two days
Do you have playcon shirts?
Okay
By fashion. No
Somebody has to have a playcon shirt
innovation center
Shit is that oh, it's a bird
oscar cinema. No
altheus
No
osaf gianna and mr.
Algaria
playcon
Oh, whatever. Just do something. I have to make a video
You answer a hater from a previous video and you let out a wtf
You thank your followers for the support and you think it's a good piece of information
Yeah, we did too to finish ask for some subs
That's a four star recording
Okay, save it. This is a restricted area. You can't take photos. Oh, what are we watching? Can I sit? What are we watching?
Okay, who are you?
Tina. Hi, i'm tina. And who are you?
I'm david. I'm new in town. Oh, I love meeting new people. Welcome to the city. Have you met aaron yet?
He's a celebrity around here and a good friend of mine. No, I haven't you'll bump into him around the neighborhood on an important event
Soon enough. He's called everywhere. The poor guy has a schedule full. All right, gotta go find aaron
I go backstage playcon playcon. Hey there. Are you new to the city? I'm david. Who are you?
I'm rico if you need someone to talk to or hang out with you got me
Wow, your style man. Tell me something. I don't know. What are you doing with your life? I spend my days partying
I see the good life, huh? Good for you
Wait a minute. Hey, come here
Hey kid, I don't know if you've heard anything about the robberies around the city. They're calling the person the new tube city thief
Yeah, I know whoever came up with that name deserves a good scolding for abusing cliches
burglar
Organic water
Did I just buy that? How much was that?
Retro world. Oh, oh my god
bomb raider
Hetrick and a zega max drive
What's this? Oh, please
Well, I can't go to uh, saucon because I don't have any money and nobody nobody has a shirt on that I can talk to
He's gonna go home. Nobody has a shirt. I said look at people. Let me make sure i'm reading this right
Get 500 coins. All right, I just have to do both jobs until I can get it
sock on
These oh, yeah
Yeah
Hey, I don't think I know you you don't do any training. Do you train?
Nice to meet you david. I'm clara a trainer at the boxing gym. All right, what else you know?
Are you one of my fans if you want to say something do it on insta live fan page or go to the boxing gym
I'm gonna go thumbs down
Your last post. Oh shit amazing billboard outside of oscar cinema this week. Don't miss it
My classmates best friend's cousin's girlfriend said that she saw stalker near the port
Is it a movie or is it a person?
Okay, get out of here. I want to get the anomaly
Okay, I need to
Whatever i'm going back and i'm gonna upload a vlog of me talking about saucon. It's not saucon
It's playcon, but whatever does it matter?
This is a vlog outside of I don't even where this was the theater. Okay, pick up this one sucks
Should I play a game? All right, i'm gonna play
Watch cats is still pretty popular. Let's go gameplay. All right. Do I have any food? No, I need to sleep
You just got ratioed. I got ratioed
Oh, man
No, I didn't i'm trying. Let me see if I get this correct when somebody says you've been ratioed
That means that there's more
Like dislikes than there are comments or something. What does it mean?
Or there's like more
What does it mean? It's something like that
more replies or dicks and
More replies are dislikes than one more comments than likes on twitter. It means more comments than likes reply
Gets more engagement. What just happened? Whatever. I can have a i'm slits a slip. Whatever
Mantendo z rumor can make a video about that
Hey david, there's a big rumor going around everyone's talking about this
Mantendo z rumor they're saying that in the mantendo conference on the 25th during the playcon festival
They're going to present a new console that will revolutionize the video game sector
It's also rumored that a few chosen people will be able to get the console during the conference
Can you imagine being one of the first to upload videos on the new console?
You have to go to that conference no matter what I can't I can't I don't have money
Only bronze league level youtubers can attend
You can move up the youtuber ranking by getting followers
So now you know you need to get these followers before the 25th day
By the way, look around the city for any posters advertising the mantendo conference and upload an insta life photo
Or record a video next to it this way you can take advantage of the popularity of today's rumor
I like everything related to david. So I liked your last photo, too
All right, I gotta get in there
I have a thousand subs. We gotta go take a picture of the mantendo board
All the gamers are waiting for mantendo. Why don't you create content on it? I'm gonna
Where's the mantendo? Um poster
first to stan
There it is. Okay. Here we go. I can't uh, I can't oh I can't I can't see what i'm typing
Holy shit, it says 6 000 likes. That's the biggest thing in the day 72 3 000
Even aaron can't get aaron has way more aaron has 600 000 likes super metro. Okay, cool
All right, that had to get me a lot of people. I'm a bronze, uh, tuber now, right?
Just do it again. Nothing is going to be funner than making content
Oh shit
All right. All right. All right. All right. Don't want to overdo it. Nothing's gonna be funner. What bro shade at the other influencers?
Okay, one more. I want to look at the camera. I think i'll get uh, get contacted
Farming likes. All right. I've got it. I got it. I got it. What about the rumor?
What about the rumors of the oh wait, hold on. Can I do can we talk about the rumor?
I have to make a video talking about this. How do I do that? Can I not can I talk about it?
Okay interact record video commentary on these trends, right?
Full of energy. I'm gonna pout and uh, make a bad joke neighbors dog starts barking
You have a laughing fit you say oh, what the fuck?
And it's over you sign off and it's over. I just got five stars and look at these trends
Oh boy, this is gonna be good. Get it up. No, no, no
That's the best I can do right? Can I add any uh, any render video things shit? I can't I thought I had big ears
I was like, what is this? What's this big ear like mouse ears man 10 don't conference secrets revealed
Yeah, i'm on let's see it. That's gotta give me some subs, right? I'm going to bed. Holy shit broke 1k
300 new subs. I got a thousand subs. This definitely puts me in the bronze category, right? It has to interview marquis
All right, you remember getting 1k views. Yeah, I think it was the tf2 uber update
I remember I went to bed and this is back when I think I was getting
200 views video maybe like 400 or 500 views video. I went to sleep. I made the uber update video and I woke up and
the
View count was at like three or four thousand and I shit my pants like what happened that's insane
What happened and I realized that it was it was spread around on I believe the tf2 subreddit at the time
I was like, holy shit. I do remember I think I don't know if that was the first time I ever had
I mean there were videos that I uploaded that months later would get to like 800 to 900 a thousand views whatever
But overnight kind of having be more than a thousand
I think that was the time it happened reaction cards are used when recording a video and to improve the quality
As you get subscribers your youtuber skills, excuse me
What my you I don't that's not what we youtuber skills. I thought it was new tuber your new tuber
skills
Prove and you'll discover new and better cards getting them all is a real challenge
You can view them in the collection app. Okay, beep beep installing the collection app on your phone. You're gonna open it now
Cyberware, I can't find any matches in the latest big releases. We should see blair. Oh, I don't whatever. Okay, I can have reaction cards
Oh, I can okay
You get cards
This is a mission. I need 6500 subs. All right, when are you gonna raffle off your game boy advance?
What the hell are you talking about? Oh my god
Haven't you tried cyberware yet the coolest game since the bone age
Send me a message and test it if you share it with your friends. You will earn a lot of money
Excuse me. Send me a message. How do I send madeline a message?
What is the hit cyberware game?
Reactions you greet the channel
All right. Everyone's talking about cyberware. I gotta get it
Pewdiepie is the talk of the new tube city. You should pay him a visit. What?
Would they have real people in this hold on you can this this actual people
Let me do this first
Look, I know cyberware, right?
Look, we don't sell it here new tube is infected with promo videos and people keep coming to ask for it
The game developer must be selling it somewhere else. I'm afraid you'll have to look somewhere else
Look that guy with the sunglasses in the suit looks kind of suspicious. Why don't you talk to him?
Why would I talk to somebody like that? I can already tell why you're coming
Cyberware can't wait, huh? Okay, calm down
I'm the salesman if you want to know something about the coolest game since the egg age
You'll have to go to the port and look for one of my colleagues
We can't talk here. We'll have to be discreet. Are you coming?
And go fuck yourself this is like a scam
This is a scam. I have 200 coins. I need more money
deliver package
I need a photo for okay deliver package
pick up a package in gianni to take to tina
And take this photo
Uh of watch cats. How do I do that though?
I need money
Is that watch cats?
No
Go to the port. I will let me just say that I need money first. Give me this
Like yep, you're gonna play frog detective 3 when it comes out
maybe
Wait, isn't tina's at the theater?
Which is back there go to the port. I'll go to the port. Just wait
Where is this place?
No subway. Why is she at the subway station?
Where is she? Where are you?
No, no, I want to I don't want to go where I could it's where is she?
She's at the subway station. Is that inaccurate?
She at the port. Well, we'll find out
Bongo's
Oh wait, I can talk about that goal. We got some likes. I have to take a picture of uh watch cats
You hear somewhere now get a haircut. It's okay. There's this guy
Oh, you're a bunch of nerves calm down as soon as you discover cyberware. You'd be amazed
Do you want to know what it's about? Uh, yes, what is it about? Listen with this game?
You'll create incredible live videos every time you blink
You'll see thousands of new views
Gamers are crazy about this game and nobody wants to miss it. Would you like to play it?
Yes
It's gonna be a scam
Comes with one condition. It doesn't just allow anyone to enter. It is a special game for special youtubers
Only the best have access you're out of practice, but you have talent. So i'll give you a hint
I've been told that there has been a superstar youtuber in the downtown neighborhood for a few days a real pro
You can get him to endorse your work
I'll give you a copy of the game
All right. Well, let's go to downtown and we're gonna go meet pewdiepie
A hint if he is who I think he is the youtuber we're looking for is a is blonde and has a beard
Oh
You're not from around here. Are you? I'm new. My name's david
welcome
You'll soon see this neighborhood. It has the best views the best parties and the best food
You'll also see that there's less trouble than in the rest of the neighborhoods. There are no robberies or power outages
You'll love it. I don't live here
I live where you are saying it sucks
right
Okay
Nice. All right. I gotta go back. I get I I I let's go
Where's tina? Where's tina tina? I gotta go back to the other side of town, you know, there we go
All right, you can go to the disco anything for me to take a picture of here city hall
Wait get a picture in front of city hall because I can talk about it. Thank you
No, all right. Where where where it's the map is weird
All right, I should get 100 bucks at 365. Here you go. I'll take some money
465 complete. Hey sweetie, you'll soon see how lovely this neighborhood is dabbing in front of city hall
I need to talk about
the watch cats
Hello new citizen. Welcome to new tube city
I'm the mayor s of the city. My office is always open to the residents of new tube city
except when i'm watching net flow with
Ramon
The guard we never miss a single episode of toby spark series. Enjoy the city
We don't miss a single episode of toby spark series
I feel like that's like a you're giving me code word for like drugs are in the back
I don't what does that mean?
I have to make a video. I need to make a video talking about the the
I need an instagram photo of the watch cats
Let's take a picture of it
How am I supposed to get that in a video or in a selfie?
like oh take a take a picture with the hashtag watch cats, but
Can I do that?
All right. I'm in downtown. We're gonna find the youtuber
Eectopia, let's just just go in the gym. No, okay. I'm just gonna go to bed
Maybe make a video. All right. Watch. Can I like take a picture of?
The game. I don't know. How do I just i'm just gonna I don't care. It doesn't matter
Watch cats, why can't I I don't get it. How do I get a picture of that? It's probably a poster somewhere
What's the topic right now that's trending?
Oh, no, no, no, no
Watch cats as people still think it's cool read the channel
Uh, and let's skip
You died
Maybe I would be giggling
Uh sign off and say it's over
All right
Now take a picture of the screen and send it to that lady that I hear about haunted chocolatier
I can't wait to play that in the indefinite future whenever that comes out. Who knows when very excited for it though
Very excited. Oh fuck. Okay. No, I can do it action secrets revealed. Uh, the biggest gameplay pro
It's the latest. No, they're gonna hate that. Um, what should I do?
Let's see. What's a good grabbing title?
liar
Plug on the plug. That's you freaked out. You had to tell everybody that gets the point across
There's no time to care about the title couldn't even break 1k. Come on. I'm almost in the top 75
Please buy a shirt. I'm not gonna buy anything until I can go to the convention push-ups
Ooh, it's 500 bucks to go to the convention. I need to go. I like everything related to david
So I liked your last photo. Thank you
All right push-ups we're gonna go do push-ups in the gym. It's not creepy or anything. No
Is the ultimate poser exercise?
How push-ups they've been doing push-ups
Since since rome. What do you mean poser? I want to do push-ups
Punch act like a poser. What?
No, I want to push up
Weight training. I want to do push-ups
Stretch like a poser. Where's the push-ups thing stretch like a poser
I want to do push-ups
Then you get a rush at a playing sports. You can increase your energy by training and you'll stay in shape
Act like a poser. What's the difference? Okay dumbbells sports. Um right there
Whoa, is this the subscriber special? I want to do push-ups. You liked that. All right, how do you do push-ups? Nice
Okay. All right, you like it. I just got a bunch of subs for this
You know, I often get letters from admirers but today a super intense letter from someone called
To bercio arrived asking me to return to boxing. What's strange is that it has the elite fitness club scene on it
I think to bercio is the real name of that stuck-up guy who works here boosts or roots or something like that
All right. Well, I want to do push-ups. So what am I gonna how do I do that?
Where do you do push-ups on the ground on the floor? Yeah, but I couldn't do them
Can I do anything out here? All right. Well, I obviously can't so what what's the goal here?
Just do a stretch
I saw on insta-life that the fire serpent boxer might be coming back to fight that chick rocks
Fire serpent take a picture and then do a push-up. There's no push-up pose
Okay, who's this?
gg
I'm gg macaroon. Haven't you heard of me?
um
Not even your own grandmother knows who you are
Yes, uh, uh, yeah, I don't know whatever go away now shoe
The e-sports bar what can I do in here? Let's just start push-ups drink a coffee. I couldn't even get it refreshing
What do you got a burrito mom, which I can't buy any of this stuff. I need to save money
What is an e-sports bar? I don't know. All right. I need I need to whiz i'm looking for pewdiepie, right?
Isn't that what I'm supposed to be looking for pewdiepie. It's like find him downtown. Is this technically downtown?
It's a different city the pewdiepie there he is. Oh my god, it's pewdiepie and his little dog
Maya, is there something better to endorse your work? Is this voice acted? Oh, that would be funny
But what endorse a very suspicious guy was offering access to cyberware this morning
People are going nuts about this and it looks really bad. Has he offered it to you?
Yes, but I need the support of a super youtuber
Yes, but I need the endorsement to access it this one. I have an idea
Take a signed photo of me so he sees we know each other and gives you access to the game
Your drone will let me know when you have it. Let's go to your house. We'll record a video together
This is kind of just like
The dream I think of a lot of young people. I think that may have watched pewdiepie in the past maybe
where
Hey, let's make video at your house and your your camera and you play your game. This is kind of um
This is uh, well
This is a dream come true for a lot of people
Okay
Uh, Maya will take me to where you live. She's got an incredible sense of smell. What do you think your dog can?
Find my address by smelling
Imagine turning this down
No, no, no, no, no. Thanks. Not perhaps another time
Yes, come to open my place record the video great idea. We'll record at my house
I guess this is I guess we're doing this go and get the game. I'll be waiting for you at your house
It's not
This is all right. This is a weird picture
This is the picture that sits on like a gasket
What is this weird just framed photo with the thing in the back?
This is weird. I thought I was gonna get like a like a poster
I have to bring it to that guy
I don't even know where that guy was
He was in the other city, wasn't he? He's down at the port, right?
You have to take a picture with this. Oh my god
Oh, no, i'm just gonna stay up all night
Because I definitely have to take a picture with this. It looks like the portrait of a communist leader
I wonder how many youtubers are in this game or is it just pewdiepie?
You think they have is there a bunch of people in this game? I'm actually very curious. I'm very intrigued
Okay, look I have this take a look
See
Wow, what do you got there photo of pewdiepie himself? This really is an endorsement
It's is it really though
I mean you really deserve to try the game. Here's your cyberware
Searching for a famous youtuber completed. All right, cool. Did I get it?
I got it cyberware
Why is cyberware just watch cats? Is it the same game with a different? I don't get it. This is worth five thousand dollars
Run pewdiepie. Oh, I thought it was like pewdiepie is coming after me
Run pewdiepie is behind you
I this is good. I can't wait. This is gonna be so fun, but it's 10 o'clock. I don't have I don't think I can do it
Do not call pewdiepie at 5 a.m. Should that be the video we make but it's just he's actually just there
All right, I gotta go home quick. Is he just is he actually just gonna be in the house?
Oh my god, you got the game. I'm wondering what we'll find when we play let's record that video
All right
I feel like I would want to clean my whole house four times before he came over. You know what I mean? Like
Okay, record video
Watch cats. No, I don't have it. Oh, yeah, I do it is the same game. Okay cyberware
Is he gonna be in the video? I switched the camera to make sure that pewdiepie is in the frame running out of energy
All right, come on gameplay you start and is pewdiepie's watching me make this video you greet the channel
There's a lot of pressure here while the game loads you
You make a technical comment. Oh, there's a graphics glitch gotta laugh it up
to finish
You sign off. That's a five-star video and I did that in front of pewdiepie
All right. Now here's where the funny part of us would come in pewdiepie says thanks a lot
I'll invoice you
And there's an invoice in the mailbox in like a month or two. That's like five grand
Does pewdiepie help me edit it? This game is so boring. Is this the hit game?
Everyone's talking about it's so short and there's nothing to do. Oh, wait, you got a strange message on insta life
This is very shady. Pewdiepie is a whiz with videos. He'll know what we should do. Pewdiepie. What do we do?
Pewdiepie is a top video maker. He will know what to do. What do we do?
If you recorded the video yet
I haven't told you the most interesting bit about all this if you send a stream of messages to all your contacts
Praising this amazing game will give you a hundred coins. I don't have any contacts. So this is perfect. Yes, i'll do it
I don't have one person in my phone. Sure. Let's go. Thank i'll do it immediately. Your face looks full of questions
Shoot, how may I help the salesman asked us to spam? They'll give us a hundred coins if we spam our fans
I knew it. They want to promote a crappy product by using youtubers who take cheap bribes
You have to enter the message thread so that with your talent as a youtuber you can report the scam
First we have to catch this sales guy wherever he is. Do you know where to look?
It's probably in the port neighborhood almost but not quite. Maya has tracked down the salesman and he is downtown
Okay, we'll catch the scammer. You'll see I have to go and look for Maya first, but i'll see you there
Oh, I do. Wait, I added all these people in my phone
I don't remember getting all these people's numbers. All right. I want to see if there's any youtubers here. Come on
There are definitely other youtubers hidden in here. We have to find them. Okay, uh, it seems
Like Maya found the salesman in an alleyway with stairs. I have to go to sleep man. It's two o'clock in the morning
Did I not upload the video with pewdiepie? I didn't upload it
Oh Clara's trending
Suspected of being a werewolf. What's that? Is it a bird? Is it a plane? No, it's a new photo of my favorite favorite influencer
You have an internal monologue with doge
All right. Hold on. I need to I have that video man. It's gonna be worth a lot
Let's go out here. That's pretty good. Okay, so pewdiepie's here. He's blocked out
Why did he cut his face out? Is he not even in the video? I feel like that's enough, right? That's that's enough
I don't need anything else. All right, almost broke 100. What why is pewdiepie not on there? What's going on?
What he wasn't even in the video?
Wait, I swear he was in my house. I swear to god. He was in my house. He was in my living room
Okay. Yeah, pewdiepie came pew you tell you telling me
That pewdiepie met you on the street gave you a signed picture of his face to use as a currency to get a scam
Video game so he could come over your house and make a video and now you're on a detective adventure with him
Is that what you're saying to me?
Yes
Okay, I think you need a little bit more sleep
It said that suspected of being a werewolf has been seen around downtown neighborhood
Okay, we need to get we need to be in downtown. We're gonna find people that have werewolves
Is pewdiepie in the room with us right now?
Don't forget that pewdiepie is waiting for you in this neighborhood, but where in an alleyway
Okay in an alley
Not that one. I can't believe you've been playing this game for more than three hours
I mean i'm kind of invested at this point. I'm very intrigued
Where is he?
There is all right
Listen cyberware is a four slice pizza
I love pizza gg
And two slices are for me
Too much pizza. Don't you think i'm doing all the hard work?
That's how gg macaroon does business
Is evil
Fine two cyberware slices for you. Then what do you what the hell are you talking about?
I forgot I was naked
Hey, you came maya found the salesperson and look we caught him red-handed doing business with gg macaroon
The two together are less trustworthy than an orc in an elevator
is the implication now that the orc is going to fart in the elevator really really loud or that
We're going to get attacked in the elevator by the orc. Let's record a video to report the scam live
Yeah, let's do that
Pewdiepie make sure you're you head in the frame a little higher
Start streaming
Pewdiepie come over here. Pewdie come stand over here for a second. Pewdiepie come stand over here
They're not going to believe that that's your dog if you don't come over here streaming
Ranking these are streamers. I'm live. Oh shit. Okay
um
What is that?
What is this arrow keys?
I'm doing all right. How to wait for the funny bits of the stream
Can I suggest a topic? How many viewers do I have?
4 000. Oh my god, it's not over. I thought it was over
Save this video
It caught me dough-handed at least i've got other pizzas to eat
Oh, no, you got me. Darn it. You exposed our scam when I was about to become loaded with money
If it weren't for you and that meddling dog
You've ruined cyberware my cyberware
Oh cyberware, how would I get money without you?
Can we call the police?
Team the plan was a success. Have you seen your channel?
There's a flood of messages to thank you for reporting the scam. You're a star
Thanks for not scamming your subscribers to get money
When you're a youtuber and so many people watch your videos
You have to be aware of how important the things you say and do are
I know I could trust you to expose this problem. I have to go now, but a surprise is waiting for you at home
End the cyberware scam
Let out a whoa, bro
Wow david, you're such a hero your courage is inspired. How many how many followers do I have now 12 000 likes
I gotta capitalize on this right now. There it is
And to think that I was so close to uploading a cyberware video david on behalf of all the youtubers in the world
Thank you
Yes, i'll get all this praise i'm getting. If I can get me to play con
All right, pick up a package in the fisherman and take it to blair
I need one dollar. I'm, can I sell pewdiepie's photo? This is worth
Five thousand dollars i'm selling that okay i'm going to um play con ticket
Didn't I just upload my cyberware video I did because I had pewdiepie in it and I thought that would be kind of a big deal
You gotta take a picture with it first. Oh, wait a minute. No, no, no, no, no, what the hell
All right, put this away
No, what's that? The sock on is over here. I have 500 bucks now. It's time to buy a ticket. Oh my goodness
Here we are. Yeah, I can't get out of the way. Do you know who the fuck I am? Nice. All right tickets
Welcome to the play con festival the most important video game festival in the world
Do you want to take it to this year's edition? Yes
500 coins
Sold your digital ticket has been activated. Enjoy the festival
Oh, oh my god
I have no shit. Come on. I gotta make like 10 videos here
Anybody don't have any food anybody have any food? I'll be back
I'm gonna go to sleep and come to the convention tomorrow. I can't put a shirt on because I don't have any money
Um, okay. Hold on. There's a package I need to get what was the what was the package? Whatever. I don't care
You have shirts in your closet. Wait, I have a gift from pewdiepie. What a great adventure. We've had together
We unmasked a dark scamming network. It's been epic. Thanks to you new tube city is a fair city
We will never forget you your friends pewdiepie and my this is a mural. I need it in the camera's view
Otherwise, no one will ever believe me
Can't put it against the wall
Can I just put it as my backdrop? God damn it. I want to i'm moving the bed
I'm moving all this shit because I need to make sure that's in the bed gamer
No, I need people to prove that he actually was over here i'm doing that with wasd hurts
Oh, there we go. Never mind. Here we go. Now I can actually move it back over here
Eating frenzy 2 shipwreck showdown waiting room ban that person for a day. Uh, honestly, how dare you telling me to play a game?
That's really fun. That's really really awesome. Some of the best
Most wonderful gameplay ever to distract me because now I want to play that
That's a huge huge problem for me right now. I think all right, so I make a video before going to bed
That's it brand cars race push-ups clara experiments
commenting
Burger day secret lab. What about the i'm gonna I need to go to the convention
Great. Okay. Can I is there anywhere I can go from here?
I'm gonna have to get clout for this one. You know what I mean? That's it. I'm stuck here forever
I think I can sleep in the bed. I think yeah, we're good. Yeah, I missed a trend
Oh come the fuck on what the hell I need to
I'm screwed
Um, it's I couldn't see but I was gonna do
Booger fuel cancel cancel cancel if I move the bed, how do I move the furniture?
What if I move it like a little bit over here? Oh got it. Nice. Okay. I'm actually i'm afraid to sleep again
What is the ass buffet stream? What the fuck are you talking about?
Can I go in the sewer leave food?
What is an ass buffet? What I what is it? I don't know. What is an ass buffet?
The best the best is when is the ass buffet stream? Oh
Okay
Let me I gotta go to the convention. That's a pretty self-explanatory
Maybe not though. I don't know
Answer me in all capitals. All right. I gotta get good footage here. I gotta get past 2 000 subscribers
I'm gonna go for 2 000 subs. All right. What about this guy with the shoes?
This is a big deal. This is like an invisible person
This guy just has like toe socks
Okay. All right. Um
This is a big deal
uh, let's
full of energy
Your neighbor's dog starts barking
How am I supposed to hear my neighbor's dog from here? Is he here with the dog? He let out a whoa, bro
He sends a paranormal presence
I say doge
and to finish
I sign off
This is great footage
Nobody gives a shit about playcon anymore. What the hell? All right. Well, let me get in here. How do I get in?
Playcon festival starts on the 20 seconds. You only have until then to buy the ticket
Here's the stand where you can buy one. I have one
How do I get in?
Wait, hold on a minute
What's today's date?
in
What I thought it said it was from the 9th to the like 28th
On 10 days early
But there are people in here. It's not a one-day ticket. Is it?
Now, let's get that family friendly, please
More time to stream the ass buffet
Okay. Well, let's go back and make a video on what exactly I don't know. What's the goal now?
Do I even have a goal packages? I don't get okay grand cars race. Where the hell is a grand cars race?
We're gonna go to the subway. I need to eat food and go to the subway. Hey, I don't know you
Are you new in town? Hi, i'm david. Oh, i'm dixie. Well, just wanted to know your name
I like to know who's hanging around my neighborhood. Bye
uh
I've been told that you're getting on well with your neighbors. That's the spirit
Did you know you can see them all in the contacts app?
It has a camera on me. Yes. I knew that perfect. Well, I have nothing more to tell you. See you
Oh nice. I did it. I need food first of all
And then i'm going to do i'm going to get a video of this
race
Whatever it was
What is what's trending? What is it?
grand cars race
Because that's trending right now use coupon code ass buffet on your next green smoothie purchase
all right, uh
crispy noodles and
Hopefully none of this costs money to get in
I'm assuming the race is is over there. It's the one city we haven't been to
All right
Yuck green smoothie. I don't know who's making your green smoothies, but it's not me and mine are good apple
spinach kale
A little bit of coconut water
Whoever's making them for you is making them wrong a little bit of ginger. They're making them wrong for you
Okay, where is this race car thing?
rand cars race
Start the playcon
Looking for a race
Go to the subway station. It's a video game. What?
Do they sell games here? The hell is all this you can buy a drone
You can buy a lightsaber. This is not a lightsaber. This is wipe your enemy's memories
So they forget why they hate you
Only then will you be able to reconnect with them. No, thanks
What what did what did I play? I just wasted energy doing that
So if it's a video game, then you tell me can I just buy it from the video game store?
God damn it
Well, i'm going back
I have to have enough energy because I need to upload that video of that game tonight
No, i'm not stopping the stream till we go to the convention. I'm sorry
And we're not next game. No, we're staying here till I go to the convention. All right
I need to go to the video game store. It's uh
Right down on the left. It's gonna take you like three hours. No, it's not
It's gonna take like 40 minutes. Are you kidding me?
Well, I need content so i'm i'm filming something. Oh my god. I have to go to bed burger king just released
Sus nuggets, I don't believe that and i'm not gonna look it up. Oh, wait, this is the interview. I I have content
It's real. It's not I'm not gonna look it up actually real. I'm not no, it's not
I'm not why did I get somebody dislikes on this video? What the fuck what happened? What sus? No, i'm gonna look it up
All right. Come on. I need to get uh
Monkey king karate girl star invaders watch cats is training again. I don't even have to leave my room
Okay, i'm gonna look this up sus nuggets. It's a lie. He made it up. I fucking knew it. Why did I even do this?
Why would they do that now if all the time
Sus nugget, what would that even be? Why would that I I didn't believe it. I told you I didn't believe it
So what do you mean you baited? I told you it wasn't real for the first time
When I read the title on newtube, I thought your last video would be a little different
Unsub and fucking unfollow me. I don't even care fuck off
All right, let's go
watch cats
You greet the channel. All right, dude. That was a little much you get a super strange drop
You look at it and you make a technical comment
An annoying npc talks to you and you uh, you let out a bro to finish
You ask for some subs and you get yourself a five-star video
Watch cats is trending
Get it up right now. Here we go. The thumbnail the gameplay you would have never have expected
You would never expect me to play watch cats again
Because think about it the video the game came out like four weeks ago. I already played it and beat it
Why would you ever see this bingo? That's our first big break video. I think it's gonna cross 5 000 views
I'm already out of energy. I have to go and buy that game. It's stuck in the wall again
I don't want to get stuck. Where should I put this?
Next to the bed. I wake up every morning and look over at the pewdiepie portrait
I need to pick this up. There we go. You go spin this around like that
You gotta have your alarm like across the room, right? Isn't that what people say?
New setup. I do I have another video. I think I had a second one too, right?
It's interview
Shit this video sucks fun
Pewdiepie the end will make you roll on the floor 10 things about pewdiepie that will surprise you how to get to the top
Thanks to playcon this one. What does that have to do with pewdiepie? Don't dislike me. I'm just i'm trying to work here
New setup. I don't want to buy that game because it's no longer trending
Just i'm gonna keep making videos on the stuff that's look. Why would I buy new games? People love this shit. Look at this
mystery graphics glitch
We're gonna ship it timed mission skip the time mission. Those are annoying
Your hand is cramping start laughing to finish
Sign off. Why was that video so bad? Throw it in the trash. I don't want it. Make another one. I'm too tired. Fuck. Ooh
500 subs i'm almost at top 75 2k andy. Ooh gameplay
Valentine's day monkey king. All right, we're gonna do gameplay of monkey king on valentine's day. This is gonna be huge
This is gonna be absolutely monstrous i'm just not gonna move the bed anymore. All right, I need monkey king
Let's go get it. I need valentine's day shit today. The gameplay content is very popular. Yep monkey king gameplay valentine
How do I do valentine's day stuff get a photo of it?
You're open. Let's go closed sundays. What's today? No
valentine's day
Anybody here talking about valentine's day? Ah, here we go. That's the biggest thing i've done all year gameplay valentine's day
Fountain. I wish I had one of the games. Why is this closed closed on sundays are they open?
Is lead point open on sundays? Why is everything closed on sundays because it's a christian game
This reminds me of like trying to buy alcohol on sundays at massachusetts. We're gonna give we have to work with what we can
Uh watch cats people still think it's cool
It's a gameplay video and we're gonna talk about valentine's day
To start the video you should i'm gonna shyly say hello. It's valentine's day, right? We're gonna be like, oh, hey, hi guys
Uh, you you forgot the script just skip that part. We're just like winging it. Why is everything why is everything suck so much?
Let out a bro. They're in-game purchases, but you look it up on the wiki
Why is this video so bad?
What what happened to my fucking camera?
Whatever. All right. Now i'm gonna just talk about valentine's day. What is this?
What's this clip can be claimed for breaching copyright if you use it new tube might take it down before very long
What did I do what copyright?
Wait, what are you doing? It's me sitting in my room. This one looks like shit. What's wrong with this one?
Warning you can't monetize this clip your video won't generate profit. Although it will definitely get loads of views
Huh?
Why not this sucks? I don't care fucking come after me come after me valentine's day bash
You're gonna get striked
Whoa, that's a lot
Holy shit. That was a lot. Oh, I got that one
That was trending making the most of sunday to see if I can bag any retro game in retro world in the city hall plaza
Today is my favorite day of the year valentine's day
Do you have someone special to give a rose or a box of chocolates? What about money?
Oh, okay. Hold on edgar needs a talented youtuber to record a video about the fountain trend
I'll put a photo with the fountain. Oh, this is easy money right now. Let's go. I need a yeah easy money
It says 83 views. Wasn't that then they get liked 400 times
What four to ten I can't film unless I have food i'm gonna wait in front of this door
Oh, then I have 37 hours. I just go to sleep. Yeah, let's go to bed. You like your own videos
Um, it's like voting for yourself in the presidential election, right?
Yeah, you're going to am I gonna get stuck on the wall again?
2k 3k. Ooh
I ranked up you got a new reward to gain access to althea's vip vp table where only the city's celebrities eat
Holy shit. I made it
Developer day watch cats is currently trending again fountain
Developer day. Where is that? Hey david?
I heard they're having a developer day in the player one store famous developer in the industry will be presenting his new video game there
And people can try it out while live streaming
Don't miss it. You have to know how to live streaming to get the game. I'm i'm fine. Hey buddy
You finally uploaded another video. I was getting antsy
One day let me get the fountain shit done first
Fountains down here, right?
All right, here we go
That fountain
Go blue cool calming crisp waters of our beautiful downtown city. Thank you. I'll take 100 bucks and let's make a video
I'll vlog out here. Sounds good
All right, let's create the channel nice. You make a bad joke
a little internal monologue here
Uh, I need these two
Good piece of minstrel
losing battery
sign off
That's a quality four star video doesn't matter. I don't even need to upload it
I just got over that guy that wants the fountain stuff
You got this video got removed due to copyright
Well, I got the followers. I don't care
I did again
Got it. All right, 1500 likes. That's not bad. You didn't use hashtag fountain. Oh shit. You're right. I didn't
All right. So now
Uh, didn't I oh I have to make the video. All right, I have to actually upload it
Then i'll go buy a shirt. Finally. I promise what do I want to go back to the house?
Yeah, i'm not even hit. Okay, whatever
And then it's developer day. So I have to go there too. Let's actually let's do it
Let's go there right now. Do I have enough energy to actually do anything? Let me eat first
Vague posting. Okay, let's do crispy noodles. I need some of those. I'll eat the crispy noodles. Thank you
He's taking the game too. Seriously. I want to get to 5 000 subs before
I end this stream. It's important
All right, I still have a little bit of time to put that video up
Developer day. I just found the channel. Are you the almond and radish guy? I'm one of those. All right developer day
Where's the developer?
Are you a developer?
Hi, i'm stewart lee the designer of spider bro. I'm presenting it two days before it goes on sale
If you want to try it out, you'll have to live stream it on the console
Do you know how to live stream? Of course I do
Well, I don't think your drone has the streaming function. So why don't you go over to the console and give it a try?
And i'll explain how you can install this function
streaming
Go over to the console and try it out and then i'll explain how you can install this function on your drone
Okay developer day spider bro
A lot of trending shit here. All right, this is the rhythm game. I'm live that person has 3.9 million concurrent viewers
How is that? How many people is that actually?
That's insane
What the fuck is going on? Oh, okay. I'm good. Is this what it's like to stream?
um
Sometimes it can feel like that
I should just stream again
Yeah, that was 150. It's way better than new tube. Let's go
And I get access to the game early i'm gonna do this as many times as I can before I pass out
All right. Good. Hell. Yeah, 150 dollars save that one too. I'm gonna upload like five of these videos. They're super funny
Eat a bunch of takeout do it again. No space available
Okay, whatever. Can I get a selfie with you developer day?
All right, I got that now I gotta turn the videos in oh i'm running out of time seven hours what are your thoughts on um,
Even more. I don't know what that is. I refuse to even say it out loud talk to the dev I did. Oh shit
I just played the game and left that's rude. You're right, but they're closed now
They closed three hours ago and I was still in there exclusive. Come on. I'm a tuber. I get exclusive, uh access
I got three videos to make i'm gonna be pulling it all nighter on this one. All right edit video
I have the streams the vlog in front of the fountain. Let's get that one done now. Are you kidding me?
Are you serious? I don't care. This is like a sponsored video. Do I like this? This guy paid me to make this
I don't care. All right, they liked it. I'll take my I got 1200 bucks now. I could probably buy something
All right, let's go again. I still have a takeout pulling an all-nighter here. Come on. Let's go. This was a better
This was the best stream. This was the developer day. This is trending. This is huge. Um, none of these fit together
When is second david gonna come up? Whatever it's trending
Yeah, I gotta get my hands in there the biggest game stream pro of adventure. Come on more good
When is david craft someday soon? All right, I have two of those I put it together. Do I have enough energy?
Damn it. All right, let's go to bed wake up 1k 2k
2k 3k come on buy some better editing. That's not a bad idea. We'll try that now
Did one of those get copyright claimed you have to buy live streaming function in ertech
Okay, something you would have already solved if you'd gone streaming with steward lee yesterday, but who am I to judge didn't I what?
I did i'm editing the videos from those streams. What are you talking about?
Yeah, what install editor increase the score for the clip complete all output connections complete all input
Connections increase the editor that was a thou that was a thousand bucks. It's gone. Is it gone?
What's happening right now?
Okay, this is really confusing. All right, so put you can put it on each individual clip
You only have a certain amount of render points. I get it so I can do it to one we'll do to this one
Okay
Publish developer day secrets revealed fun. Honey play studios one the end will make you roll on the floor laughing. Sure
Now I will go buy a shirt, but I already okay. I guess we didn't do this
You're so epic and you're my best friend
um
I don't really know who you are, but thanks for watching. That was a bot. It was not a bot
That was not a bot talking
I told you we're we're all just a collective group of people hanging out having fun
Did you get it? That's how it works. I can't live stream here because the person's not here anymore
So how am I supposed to do this?
Find the er
Er
What this is not that much views I got like 3k yesterday. What's going on here? Where's that er tech place other side of town?
Yeah, all right. Let's go get some clothes at least a t-shirt
magic pixels t-shirt
Emoji shirt salamander sweatshirt. How about the emoji shirt? Yeah, put it on everybody put it on
What does this immortal snail I keep saying? Oh the immortal snail the immortal snail dude. I don't know
What's the immortal snail? It's a tick tock thing. Okay
Spider bro still a thing. How is that not a thing? All right, I need to go this way
Uh, you and a snail both get immortality and a million dollars
But the snail is always coming wait, but the snail is always coming towards you and if it touches you you die
I can't
I can't crush. I can't like just kill the snail. The snail is immortal
If I touch it with anything it kills me
Well what you would have to just kind of just hire a bunch of scientists to come up with how long it would actually take
the snail to
Go from one coast of the united states to the other coast
And I mean that that's a very simple question
to answer because what you would do
Is if you had a million dollars, right? I get a million bucks. I would just buy or rent two properties at the same time
one
in california and one in like florida or massachusetts or like maine or something, right?
And we would determine how long it took the snail to go back and forth
and let's say it was like
20 years
It's going to be like 10 to 20 years of the snail maybe more for the snail to do that
So you would just go live in your in your california house
For 10 years
And then once it became like eight and a half years just to make sure you got it right or make about nine years
You just go live in the other house for like two three years like 20 years. You would just keep going back and forth
That's easy
It would probably take a snail 30 plus years to go that far whenever you sleep
You don't dream you just see whatever the snail sees at that time. Well, that would be awful
One million is not enough for that
I wouldn't buy a house in california. Then I don't know somewhere cheaper
Just put it in a box. Well, it could get out of the box if I if you go across the whole country
There's no way a snail can find you that fast
What have you got on a plane?
Does the snail have intelligence or is this just a snail just walks in a straight line across the continent of the united states?
Does the snail have intelligence? It knows it knows to like get on a plane and go on somebody's luggage and get on the plane from
Boston to la does it have that intelligence it is. Yes. Okay, it's hyper intelligent. Um
Okay
And in that case, I would just probably
I don't know hire you can have a million dollars. So I would hire somebody to be at every entrance in my house
Or wherever it was
And just to stay there and if they see a snail it doesn't kill them, right?
So they would just pick it up and get on a plane
Why don't they just pick it up and put it like keep it as a pet or something pause the game?
Oh shit, whatever
Can you keep okay? What if you like get a box? That's a glass
box
and you put lettuce and
A little uh enclosure and it's nice and comfortable big enough where it's comfortable and you'll just keep the snail in there
That's why would that be hard?
Nine to nine shit. All right. Well now I can't do anything
Because I still said it's doing nothing put down a salt circle
Well that that no because it's it's an immortal snail. That's not gonna work cover the snail in concrete
Yeah, but you know, I don't know. I feel like you'd have to put it in concrete put it in the ground
All right. I'm just walking back and forth. I'm not doing anything. I need to go back to the house
Yeah, is it immortal or invincible? That's a good question. Where's my fucking house?
I don't think that would be hard to do
Especially considering that I would just set up motion detectors
In the house, right?
So it would sense any movement at all in any of the rooms
So I would be awoken by like an alarm sound
And if I see the snail just slowly coming towards me i'm i'm gonna the area is it's too slow to get noticed
Just do the tick tock video already. What does that mean? Does that mean?
Have the lady talk for the first five seconds. How would you deal with a snail coming at you?
Seems to be a huge threat in newtube city
Go to the fisherman to find out more if you don't remember where it is looking up on the map. This life is on fire
Don't check your messages
Beware i'm near the fisherman and the tide has risen so high the pier is in danger
Hey bad day for surfing the sea is roaring. I'm is it we are we in a scenario where we're getting what's happening right now?
What is craner? Are we about to get like attacked?
What is it? What is it talking about? Are we gonna be like attacked by water? What does it mean like a storm?
This hits the snail
What about craner? It's the most popular. What is craner?
All right. I need to go down
First thing is first
What was I doing? When is this open from the seventh to the split? This is not open
It's about to be closed
All right, we're gonna go to the beach which is a subway
Okay. Oh my god. It really is
Beware i'm near the fisherman and the tide has risen
Fisherman
All right, the fisherman what the hell is going on down here tide is coming in. It doesn't look like it. I don't get it
You're doing a hurricane vlog
Sunbathe because i'm bathing in a hurricane. He's getting so many likes
Um, what am I supposed to do down i'm by the fisherman so over here, okay
That blonde boy might be able to tell you what is happening. He's got a weird. What was what his weird voice
Where am I? What am I doing here? I feel like I have some kind of troll inside my head
I can't even remember my name. I used to create videos, you know
Craner that's all I know and uh, and that I was you a you you a youtuber
You're a youtuber good. This gives me an idea
If you record a video with him, it might help him recover his memory this way
He will be able to tell us what happened to the tide this morning
What this is like an explosion over here?
start recording
Okay. Um
If this was real, I would say this i'd be full of energy. I'd be pretty much panicking at this
Your phone rings you can't get any peace
I mean, I would say
I would just probably laugh about that like who's calling me. I don't know
You thank you followers for the support
And you have an internal monologue
Okay
You spam your insta life. No
I'd sign up
What happened to the camera? I do I can do it better than that. What the fuck is this?
This is too many. There's another person in the you're running out of energy. What?
Any food?
Where am I?
Okay, is this a visit restaurant?
This is a restaurant. This is still trending. I have to get it. But while it's still trending
I'm not going to screw this up fish and then eat a raw fish in front of this guy
Food. All right. Here we go. What is this the kraken burp soda?
Uh squid ink. No
fried prawns
Sure
And a bubbly soda
Hold on
Oh, it's a mukbang. He's only got four jokes cat puke
And what are you what are you doing out here? Maya? What's going on? Where's pewdiepie? What's going on here?
Out of the way out of the way, there's a goddamn storm. Oh shit. Hold on. Where's he? Where am I? Oh wrong
I'm trying to get a picture of him. Oh, never mind. I'm trying to get a picture of him across the way
Yeah, get out of here. Yeah, that's all my content
well
Some of it. All right. I'm back. All right, let's try this again
That's better. Let's do it
You start and we i'm gonna greet the channel good start
Neighbor's dog is barking. That's okay
bad
Poltergeist appears and I flatter myself
Is it worse than the last one?
Spam my instagram
God damn it. I don't care
I I thought something happened to him that just scared the shit out of me
I just heard like a I heard like a firing like a shot
And I remember everything that was fucking terrifying. That was so loud
Now I remember something savage happened this morning. I was recording an epic video when suddenly the sea turned into a swirling portal
Gosh, it swallowed me up and then spat me out on the dock of the city
In the morning, I heard that a certain captain vane the fisherman's owner is repairing an old boat
And he convinced him to lend it to me
If I sail out to sea I can jump into the whirlpool. This will close the portal
I will return to my dimension and the danger for new tube city will be over
Can I get can I get a selfie?
Let me get a selfie real quick. Let me get a selfie real quick. I gotta get home and upload this video quick
All right, it's boat time
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat. Yeah, i'm a little tired
fuck
fucking
And like you were in class
like fucking such a
Slow filler word. It's so easy to do
And you're like in class at like college or high school with so many teachers like
Yeah, so we got um, if you take a look at the algorithm on the board here
It's four or five x and then you're solving for uh
fucking y
Which will get you to the answer which we're looking to see here
Uh chris, can you can you give me an answer here? I don't know fucking
I do that all the time
What's my favorite cereal captain crunch? That's not what you asked. What's my favorite hotel chain?
One that has more than three stars on yelp. I've not I don't want to I refuse to stay in any others. Okay, let's go
If a hotel does not have at least three stars on
Well, i'm walking in a circle one brain andy. I can't do anything
I can't fucking do anything
I need to go on the subway
Any hotel that is less than three stars on google is I don't want to stay there
Where am I going over here?
most hotels
Are over three stars and i'm look i'm not talking about
The hotel ratings, right? Oh, it's a four-star hotel. It's a five-star hotel
I'm talking about actual reviews of these places
You could be a four-star hotel and have a three on yelp, right i'm talking about just the reviews
You could be you could be at like a holiday in and the thing could be a 4.5 on google, right?
I'm not talking about the actual like quality of the hotel
I'm saying if it's not at least three
On google, I don't want to go there now. I gotta I gotta finish this video
Okay, please
My wings
Are a hurricane
You always I've always found him saying that really interestingly don't you uh this one
I can do editing to these though. Oh, well. Oh, well a big finish. What are you talking about?
Really? I have to tell you what i'm talking about. What was that? Oh fine. I'll do a few more see if you
See if you pick it up. Oh
Uh, I can't think of anything. Hold on
What does he say? Oh great and
Powerful Oz. What's his name? Oh great and powerful smog. Your reputation does precede you
very much so
Okay, i'm going to bed
Did I publish the video I did dildo baggins get out of here. He's choking
No, i'm just i'm just laughing about it a little bit
Okay, he talks about hotel stars and gets 2.5 stars on his video. What do you have to say for yourself?
This is a pretend video game that is nothing to do with real life david. They're saying that walter
Atar the top ranked youtuber is in disguise somewhere in the city
See if you can find him and record a video or upload a photo of it make the most of these trends
When I read the title everyone thinks there is a famous youtuber in disguise
Don't miss the jump guys launch. Okay. I don't know who i'm looking for. All right. I got an is it emoji shirt
How many shoes?
You can finally afford a shirt. I have got 500 bucks
All right, so we're looking for a famous, uh youtuber
hiding
easy
Wait, i'm gonna try to interview. There's so many people here. Okay
Start the video
Okay, your neighbor's dog is barking
Let's talk a little bit. That's a funny joke
you go on and then
Intern a monologue and to finish
I am going to sign off. Maybe we'll get three stars here
Okay
Get a picture too
Thank you. All right. I gotta do this boat thing. Wait upload that video right now while he's still here
You're gonna rake in the likes you better believe it. I need better editing software
This editing software sucks complete all output connections complete all input connections
Um, what does that even mean post productions? Should I buy this? This is four points
I'm confused. Hold on
improve
the transition out
What I don't I have no idea what this is. What is this? It's just doing
Um, I don't get it. But whatever I can see your face cam is on my face cam is not turned on
Shut up
I try to troll someone. Oh, this gets the most attention. Whatever. Okay. I don't have any food. We're just gonna go to bed
Whose camera's on there's nothing there. When is this convention two more days three more days mess in the new world moonbound?
Parallels retro world space cup you've been seen. Oh, please
Okay, buddy
Yeah, let's see your channel. What's your what's your channel look like? What's that? Where is it? Let me see your channel
What's your channel look like you've been accomplished editor. Let me see some of your work
What is it you don't have there's none
You've never uh edited a video ever you've never uploaded or edited a video before you just watch a lot of movies
Okay, that's good to know. I I would hold on
I want to take a picture of my phone with that on it and say that
Don't I don't think about editing I was editing before you fuck. I was editing while you weren't diapers kid
Retro game nostalgics are asking for content on mess in the new world. Let's go get it
I think I have enough for the console. Where's that retro store? It's like a little stall. Where is it?
Was it down or up at the streaming gear? I need to I think it's this way i'ma play this game tomorrow
Wait, it's play this game tomorrow, please play something else. I don't know how long i've been streaming. I'll be honest
I've been streaming for four and a half hours
I did not think I thought wow. Okay
I have the uh vip card here. I don't know what exactly that means, but let's find out
Is it free close?
That's not
Hey, you're not from around here. Are you new in town?
Nice to meet you. I'm gianni owner of the incredible gianni fashion empire. Okay
Well, you I got a card in the mail
I'm afraid to say i vip area is reverse is you have to be a celebrity to go here
Oh really get in you need the vip card
Okay, you mean one of these good luck with that
Yeah, well you already kind of have uh, like you're already kind of a dick about this whole scenario
Um, I am one of those people I have the youtuber card
and uh, i'm gonna walk in it i'm gonna literally look over my shoulder and just
Walk in while looking at you and i'm gonna walk out
You don't have a vip card. You can't go through. What's this? Where is it? Where's my vip card? Can I get one?
This is embarrassing
I got a vip card, didn't I?
You don't have the exclusive customer card. It's for a different it's for a restaurant
Did I just get a punch card where if you buy like eight smoothies you get the ninth one for free
Is that what I got the equivalent? What do you mean?
burger boy
burger boy used to
So there was places those places that you get like it punches a card for like a sandwich or a drink or something
burger boy
Would ask everybody if they wanted something. Oh, hey, i'm gonna make a run. I'm gonna get i'm gonna go get drinks
anybody want anything
so he could like
Like punch the card like five to six times
And like I got I got everybody's stuff
And he would like get free shit
Those are the strats. Yeah, they are they really are. All right, there's the retro thing right here. How much is the console?
$2,000 for a sega dreamcast. I can't play this unless I have this console though. I don't what can I just own the game?
Mess in the new world. This is for this is a different console. Where do I get the atari?
Is it can I come back a different day?
Oh city hall's trending
I whatever get a picture of me. I have a dream class
Words are impossible
Carry out a procedure. What procedure do you want to perform?
Well, the marriage doesn't seem to be in our records. You could well you can get married
Why would it give me an option to record?
Please remind everyone to call their mothers and tell them I love you. Yeah
Call your mother call your mother. Let's go
All right, uh
I don't I can't afford this and it's not even the right console. So how am I supposed to do this?
I guess we're gonna go
We have to go to this er tech place, which I think is over here. Yeah, we're gonna go here
We're gonna upgrade the drone
What about the disco?
Wake her up at four in the morning. No call you call when you next available when
You don't not like right the second. I mean just next available. Hey, what brings you here?
I want to be able to stream
I see you want to upgrade your drone with the streaming function many youtubers wanted
You have to go to the workshop at the back and buy the streaming function
oof
oh
I was a pussy. I look at that. All right streaming. It's two thousand bucks. God damn it. It's misspelled
What the fuck was that? It's misspelled
I was doing an extreme overreaction to oh my god. I found a typo. That's pretty rich coming from you
That's my point because it's who cares
Everything you do is in it. Where's the restaurant where I have the vip punch card?
It's almost time to go to the convention
Subway, we're going to do the boat thing. I can't afford to buy the streaming thing. It's two thousand
I don't have enough. Do you have a tiktok? No
No, but I guarantee you if I did i'd be huge not this again
No, i'm serious like I would be the biggest thing on I would I would have 500 million subscribers on tiktok
All right, I need to find this boat a boat thing or whatever
Convince somebody let him use his boat
Somebody posted your ass on tiktok and I got 50 000 likes
Okay, but you don't you don't think that I could come up with something
I mean we're talking about me here one of the most coordinated ow my fucking hand
That would be huge that would have gotten like a hundred million views. All right settle down. I bought an nft of your ass
It's not official. How do I get to this fucking thing? I'm trying to put this boat
I have to convince this guy to let him use his boat
A minimum gold league level is required. I can't use a ladder
I have to one of these boats. I have to convince somebody to let
zane
Yeah
Hi
I'm zane
I got you a retro game. I'll give it to my friend joy. No, you're gonna regift it immediately. Hold on. I bet you can't do that
You can't don't do don't tell me you're gonna regift it
It's one of the only copies of that game they had
There are plenty of other people to speak to in the neighborhood, you know, go fire some asparagus
Oh, you suck. Okay house of june
Where I need a who's boat do I need dj?
cerulean
Recently arrived in town. You're a youtuber and a great future awaits you. How do you know that?
I'm good at reading people. My name is cerulean
You know, I can see you're a good person, but I didn't come here to make friends
You guys see this guy's boat
Anywhere that I have to convince?
I don't understand
What is it remind me again? What's going on?
Right rainer needs to repair old captain's veins
old captain vane's boat
Who's captain vane?
Is it listed on one of these?
No, what the fuck?
It's 4 a.m. Wait, am I actually gonna get pass out?
Let me get my head on the bar
What happens?
Last night you fell asleep in the street
Do I always have to go around looking out for you to check that nothing has been stolen from your backpack
I didn't have anything
Now on remember to return home before 4 a.m
Oh, i've been watching your videos and I have to say you have to do something with this place
Room decor and even the clothes you wear influence how your followers react
They'll like your videos more if you decorate your home in your own style
Tried that savior tried that and it became a thing that everybody made fun of
I put a lot of work into the reddit shelf back here and I showed them and they made fun of me for a month straight
So, I don't know where you're getting your information, but it's it's outdated. Okay, there's I have an amazon app on my phone
Where is it? I can buy anything I want on amazon what we got
Oh, wait, I can just order this is so much better. Okay, nice
This is I this is a thousand times better ram cookie. You can build a pc
It's amazing on not amazon. Okay. Um, I still don't understand this captain shit. I'm just gonna go to sleep for two days
Silent the raccoon is huge. What's it for the privilege to have me as a follower?
If you don't upload anything you're going to end up with an unfollow my friend. Appreciate the feedback
Okay, uh
What is silent the raccoon? I don't uh silent the raccoon. Oh, what is it?
Must be a retro game or something, right?
Damn it
Shit retro game. Yeah, but I don't I consoles are hard to get
Go to the fisherman's store. I will let me just see if I can get this console they have silent the raccoon
I can get it here. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on
Where's that little stall? Where's this shit?
Come on silent the raccoon
Ooh
And it's for the the zega max drive
Oh my god, buy it
Oh my goodness. What is this? I'm out. What's trending today besides that dancing challenge easter and gameplay
This could be the biggest video i've ever made. All right dancing challenge. I gotta find that
Is this dancing challenge?
No, it's the mayor dancing challenge
Nope. Nope. It's probably in the I don't know. Is it easy vote for worst dream? I don't know. What are you talking about?
I just burped really hard down in my deep in my body. What are you?
And we already went over this
You can't know worst stream does not mean I don't like the game
Yeah, there I could name you probably three or four streams this year. That were way worse. I'm having fun
I'm having a good time having a blast. Actually, this is actually really fun. I'm having a ton of fun
How dare you by the way, how dare you?
All right. Where am I? Where am I going?
I have the console. I need to find a dancing competition. I would imagine that would be right in the middle of downtown
This is a dancing competition out here. This looks like dancing
It's not it doesn't look like a competition to me
Oh, I don't even care. I'm just gonna make the video
Dollhouse streams are worse than this
All right. I have the console. Let's do it. Take that down
One two, let's go. We're doing a gameplay video of silent the raccoon
See if we can get this trending let out a whoa find a bug make a technical comment about the bug
Why is this not filling up at all? This is literally a zero video one star video. Why is this filling so slowly?
Serious, it's too many cuts. This is gonna be demonetized. I just won't use that one. Whatever just click bait
Who cares if I ever okay 150 dislikes?
That's just that's that was all I thought that was really bad when I was making youtube videos
If a video had more than one to two hundred dislikes because there was always going to be
30 to 50 guaranteed dislikes no matter what it was nothing I could do about it
It was just guaranteed right but if a video had more than 150 dislikes 200 dislikes
That means that there were people that actually really did not like that video and whenever I would see that happen
I would have an internal crisis where I sit there and be like what the fuck did I do wrong?
What do I need? What do I do to fix this? That was was it bad?
Maybe i'll do another video tomorrow and make up for it. Thank god. You can't dislike a stream. Thank goodness
All right, the conventions today at 6k views though. Finally player one
Wait, is the convent like it's the 22nd, right?
I was watching a mouse fight with a piece of cheese on youtube today
And it was more fun than watching you do a gameplay buddy. The same person is just seriously like leave me alone
What did I do to you? Like what the hell it's the buddy
I'm just i'm just trying to do as good as a job as I can with what I have
I'm i'm trying I was watching mice fight each other on youtube. Yeah, what the hell is what are you talking?
What's wrong with you? Can I finally go to the convention? Here we are. We made it
finally
Okay
ordered popcorn
pop mars popcorn
caramel popcorn nice
We're here. We're at the convention. What's this guy? We gotta get a vlog here
I'm who am I interviewing let out a bro
Why am I so mad?
These videos are awful. Why have I not leveled up my interview yet?
Whatever i'm gonna get like 10 videos from this
Here we go. All right. Uh, what do we look at first there to start playcon? We'll get oh wait
This is a keynote start the playcon. All right, let's start it
It's I feel like we're going to get red and hercery rhymes. Is this a gaming convention?
Nobody liked that one
Uh, who's this?
Maya mato. Hello. Welcome to playcon. I'm a genius developer and I know some of this convention secrets
Yeah, i'll i'll I would love some secrets
You have to reply correctly to one question
In which year did I publish my first super strike brothers game 83? Oh 87
I think it's 83
Because uh, wasn't mario in um, what's it called wrecking crew?
Not the way not the character mario. When is the mario was 87?
Yeah
Sorry, your answer was wrong
Wasn't mario 87?
regular nintendo
It wasn't 78. It wasn't 83 the regular nintendo came out in 80 85
Yeah, mario is not 83
Ask me again
I'd love to hear a secret. Okay. Well
Correct
I'll tell you the first secret look for a violet colored plant. It looks like the plants in my game
If you post a photo of it on insta life, i'll give you a present. That's very special to me
Are you looking for a purple plant?
Purple plant there it is
Found it got it. All right. So now what what else can I do here? What's this?
Press to start. Can I play?
Oh, hell yeah
Uh, how about um talk to him again? This is yeah, this is military tech
Take this present from now on you'll have part of my wisdom and you'll be able to make videos from the tutorial script
Wait, you have my present now. Enjoy the convention. All right. How do I put this away?
What's in here?
conferences 23 24 and 25 closed
Who are these people? Who are you? Who are you? Who are these people? Okay, I want to do this one
I'm looking forward to trying out all the games, but I don't know if i'll have time for them all
Real tweet
Stop doing that pose. I can't this is the one thing that looks I like it
I'm sorry. You need the vip pass to get into this private room, of course
You need to be a goal. So these are gold league youtubers
It's supposed to be awful to stand like they're like this the whole time
Can I sneak over there and get a vlog as a place to film?
human zoo
Okay. All right. Let's go make a tutorial. I'm going to talk about my experience at playcon
Wait, no, fuck doing an interview now. We're gonna go do a tutorial on
That trending game and that was 500 coins. It was way too expensive five hours
So the plan is don't let me let me get like the the plan going up here into halloween. So here's what we're gonna do
so tomorrow, uh italics night we're talking about playing that, uh
Manamadan game we were like this a couple things we were thinking about playing but that's one of them on the list
Either that or something else. We'll figure it out
Uh, there is one
Scenario where there might not be a stream tomorrow and i'm gonna give you it's like probably like a five percent chance
I'll tell you what it is. I just started taking an antibiotic
And I I don't know if it's gonna make me feel like shit. We'll find out but we'll see
so um
It hates streaming. It's a 100 chance. No
All right plan on there being no stream tomorrow because when there is I get to say there was one
Okay, do not mix it with avocados. I'm not eating avocados. What are you talking about?
But anyways darkest dungeon 2 comes out like in a couple days. I'm gonna play that on friday and then saturday
We're gonna do public domain movie night 2
Day before halloween. So there's probably gonna be a stream tomorrow me and italics gonna play something. We'll see again
I'm on an antibiotic last time I took an antibiotic. I had diarrhea and i'm just telling you let's be honest
I don't care how many people are here watching. I'm very honest incredibly honest person. How much longer you think I should scream?
I'm
Why am I asking you that why am I asking let me get to top 50 let me get to top 50
I don't know why I thought that was so funny
Nintendo next when I get to top 50 youtuber i'm done checking out insta life and seeing that you posted a new photo
Is the best you're too good 100. Hey, thanks. I got some footage to edit
No, just throw this one away
Just toss this video the smoke coming from your computer. This doesn't look good
You should change that part to continue using the computer what i'm done. See you guys probably tomorrow. See you guys tomorrow. Have a great night
30 90
No, actually, it's been pretty good so far. Yeah, we'll see you tomorrow
Look if there's an event where I have to not stream because i'm stupid antibiotic
And that's what's gonna happen, but it's planned for tomorrow. We're gonna do something tomorrow
Keep an eye on the sus tomorrow. I think that's pretty much all I want out of this game. It was fun. It means you're too weak
No, i'm not too weak. I had a good time. I thought that was actually really funny
Why are your streams not in 1080p? Well, that's a bit rate. Not enough. Yep twitch
Yep, that's why you should eat yogurt or take a probiotic to help with diarrhea
Uh, yeah, actually have a probiotic. That wasn't a sarcastic. Yeah, that was a yeah. I have a probiotic in right here
Not right here. That makes it sound like I made that up. There's a probiotic I have
Available to me that i'm taking are these old people problems?
Well, they're currently me problems right now because I don't know if you guys remember before the dollhouse stream
I want some streamer insight here before we go
um
the day before I had to get on the plane I
Had to get an MRI of my brain. It was incredibly stressful
because I had
this weird
pressure in my head
And I was really dizzy
I'm kind of like uneasy feeling
I talked about it a little bit when I came back
but
It was a really really awful thing to have happen right in the middle of that project
So that was a really really really
TLDR, but I don't want to get into it. Um, I have this problem with my sinuses. I have
cysts in my sinus
Yeah, I think they're in both of them. The max are we already talking about it, you know, so um
It looks like I have a little bit of an infection up there
So we're going to do an antibiotic for the infection and see if anything else has to happen
I am completely fine. By the way, like I'm fine. Don't worry. It's just an annoyance that happened a month or two ago
I'm good. Don't worry. I'm 100 fine and I'm not even sure if that's exactly what's going on
But that is what is being investigated now
So again, I'm completely fine. I'm 100 healthy right now
Don't worry. Thanks for the subs, by the way, that was a good time
youtubers life too
Currently on steam if you care we got to hang out with pewdiepie, which was that was pretty cool
Have a wonderful rest of your night. We'll see you probably tomorrow
Keep an eye on us
Right, it's monkey s didn't I run them. I thought yeah, I ran them. I did the credits
Yeah, I did
All right. This is part where I scream and then hit the end screen button. All right, let's try it
I really want to try to get cut off
If I can get cut off mid sentence or something