How are you? Welcome back to Virtual Reality with Jeremy985. We're going to begin today
with Space Channel 5. Sorry I wasn't here yesterday. I think I severely underestimated how much pain I
was going to be in yesterday. I woke up and I turned till I get out of bed. It was like
that's the best way to describe pain. Especially turning pain. Those of you guys that have like
rotational pain. That's a perfect noise for it. It sucks. But I'm good. I'm here. I'm not. Oh my
God. I just fucking fell over. These cords. I swear to God. I'm not even on camera and I almost
just fell down. I didn't even do anything. I'm not taking the brace off today. Don't let me do that.
It doesn't matter how much of a sweaty bastard I am. Don't let me take this thing off.
It is doing something very important. It's over it's it's I'm wearing I'm doing a Doug
Funny right now. I'm wearing it over my clothes. Doug Funny used to wear his underwear over his
clothes as that superhero uh Quailman. So just think of it like that. Health a healing curse?
If it works then do it. You don't kill it can we collectively? I'm serious. Let's do this. I'm
gonna get on camera. We're gonna collectively fucking have like like a healing session.
Can we do that? If you have to imagine if like five to ten thousand people all collectively
think the same thing at the same time will that work? Like the neurons and like the weird
simulation that we're probably living in like will like the data get processed and like will
my like pain go away tomorrow? Let's try it. Give me the healing. What's the curse part though?
Hold on a second. Let me just get my never ending supply of fucking White Claw.
How's it gonna be? Well yeah I'm doing it today. Just a little. This is how you summon what? No
dude don't call it a healing curse. Call it like a a healing potion and we have to go over some
things too because there are people that think I'm like four feet tall. This is really important.
We have to okay I'm just gonna put the cam on. See I moved the camera a little bit because
can you hear me? I hope you can. All right first of all I got the fucking championship belt on.
Just I didn't texture it yet. I feel like a fucking videographer. This is just giving me
flashbacks. Okay yeah get the big get the groom get the groom. All right so listen to me this is
important. This this is not a window okay. I that I hung it's a blanket I hung on the wall
because it's so echoey in here. I had to put up something to absorb the sound.
Understand that's not a window. Second of all this base station is six three. This is I measured it.
It's six foot three. Do you see that? It's like six fucking four. I don't know why everything looks
so tiny on this camera in this room. Like look ready I I look like fucking minuscule. I don't
know why. You know what it looks like? Have you ever seen those um okay you know those optical
illusions where it's like the huge guy is standing here and there's like a tiny little person in the
corner and it's just like oh wow oh my god this is and they're in a room and the furniture looks
all weird. Like it's because the room is like 50 feet long and it's like slanted. That's what's
going on here because look it no I'm normal person but when I go back here I don't know why.
But I don't understand it looks so bizarre or whatever. That's not a window. I'm five eight. Get
over it. I wanted that to be so loud. You got a short neck? I don't have a short neck. That's such a
fucking insult. I don't know why. You know oh hey you're a fat guy. Oh you're stupid. Your neck is
too short. That fuck that like hurts. I don't know what to say. You got anything to say? You got
anything to say to the camera? Go on say it. All right we're gonna play. We are going to play
face channel five virtual reality edition. I've been waiting for this. It's not a monster zero.
It does kind of look like a monster. All right all right fuck it we're going. I'm going in the
headset now. I can't hear you or I'll be able to in a second. Are we ready? We good? What about
the camera? He's too small and then stop. We love your corset. Are you underage drinking? Yeah yeah
I'm I'm 17 guys. Oh no you caught me. I turned I turned 17 last month. All right let's fucking go.
I'm going. Wait let me get one more sip. Are you underage drinking? I like that one actually.
All right oh Morty. By the way I can use that reference because we're gonna be playing that
game probably today. Where's the audio? All right make sure I'm comfortable. All right let me get in.
Audio is in a good spot. Let's clunk myself in here. Face channel five. Okay oh I just burped
and my nose burned. All right that looks good. Where are the controllers? What a substance that
you don't want to put in your body? Can you imagine like burping like if no controllers are
connected? What are you talking about? Did I take too long? It might be too loud. We'll find out.
Oh there you are. Acid sneeze. Say happy birthday to Catboy. Happy birthday Catboy.
All right I don't think this really matters too much but I want to do the story. How's the audio?
Are we clean? Do we sound clean? 20 subs and he's gonna miss. Who's gonna give the subs?
Thanks for the 20 subs. Thanks for the subs. Oh I got some subs. Got some subs. Oh I got some subs.
All right it's good. Let's do it. Story mode. I'm ready. Story. Tutorial. Oh we're gonna do
another tutorial. By the way I found out why I didn't like Boneworks. I'll explain later.
If we don't put a stop to this all the groove moxie across the entire. What just happened?
That's just like I almost just puked. What happened? What? If we don't put a stop to this
all the groove. I thought I passed out. Why is it doing this? Why is that? Why am I going dark?
Okay. Does it start the next chapter? Why is it doing that? Since you're new here let's start
you off with some orientation. If you want to become an ace dancing reporter you're going to
need to master the basics first. Fortunately we've got veteran reporter Ulala here to.
Oh Ulala. First off we'll need to get you scanned so you can come inside.
Place your hands out in front. Why is this?
Placement confirmed. Okay. High energy stream. You got it. Initializing costume fitting.
Costume fitting complete. Identification verified. Let's head to the studio. Wait am I
um Ulala? I feel like I do have a short neck. Do they know? Where are we? Oh yeah! What what
happened? Change log. No get that off. What did I do? I don't want to see the change log. What happened?
We're good.
Oh my god I'm a huge fan. Memorize your partner's moves and then dance them right back.
She goes like this. Ow. Okay.
You try. You try. Don't put your hand in there. Don't put your hand in there. The legs not moving
look weird. Next let's try dancing to the beat. Okay. Look this is the person in the back row in
the workout video that's not doing it very well. You know they're like. Right. It's like that's why
they get put back there. All right now let's meet the person in the front of the video.
Oh it's gobs. I can't wait.
High energy strength. I didn't really pay that much attention to any of that.
Okay all right all right. Here we go. So chew is this. I gotta remember my left from my right.
This is left. This is right. This is chew. This is down. Holy shit this looks really fun.
Why am I so far. Give me that mic. Hey hey hey hey hey hey.
Baba boy. Baba boy. Let me say it into the mic. Baba boy. 16th what. That's hard to do with
full hands. I'm gonna get a hundred percent of this game. What. I'm unstoppable. Pose pose. Sus.
I can't do all that. I'm just gonna. I'm gonna be back here doing this.
Oh shoot them. Oh shit. What. That's good.
I'm gonna wear myself out in 15 minutes. Why.
I can't even talk to you guys. Holy shit that was intense. You suck. Whoa. All right all right come
on come on. I'm doing it mom. Just shoot him with a gun. Hey who needs a ring fit. I forget.
Oh shit. Did I get him. Oh shit I'm sorry. Am I doing what. Oh shit.
This is fun to play. This is a fun game. We want Rick and Morty VR. No stop.
Uh oh. We're gonna have to lay him out. Stay tuned everyone. That's a B minus. That's a B minus.
Wrong way. You're doing the wrong way. No I'm not. This is left. Is it mirrored on the webcam. Yeah
guys. This is my left. This is left. You're seeing. Whatever. White claw break. Thank you all for the
groove Moxie you've gathered. It was most delicious. In exchange I shall make you among my very own.
Oh fuck. I gotta go from above. Don't forget the water. Don't forget the water. Very important.
I hope nobody saw that. All right. This game's actually pretty fun. It's probably gonna be so hard.
Oh shit. She's doing. She's doing the Mortal Kombat idling fighting animation.
Plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two. What the fuck was that. Hey what's happening.
Why can't I just see myself. That was fucking terrifying. Why are they watching me. What was
that. That was OBS. I'm standing right next to you. You don't have to use a microphone. But let's go.
Do I have to sing this.
Pose. Pose. I got it.
Da da da da da da da. Dancing good pose. Dancing good pose.
And you and you and you and you you you you you.
Pose. Period.
Period. Pose. Power. Power. Go. Right. Down. Power.
Go. Go. Go. Why am I saying it. I'm just probably so loud. It's so confusing.
Why am I like shackled. Can you guys even hear me talking. I get so loud. Stop showing me me.
Uh oh. 94 percent that's an A. I got you.
Deranged man screams into highly sensitive microphone. Sorry is that happening.
Is it happening. It's time to make our move. You girls ready.
Germa V tuber girlfriend. All right you know what time it is. It's time for.
Whoa. I'm doing pretty good. I'm here. Don't worry. I'm here. What do you need me to do.
Kick some ass. It's all right. I can do whatever you need. You want to beat somebody up.
That's why you brought me here. I'm the fucking muscle.
That's what you get for showing off. Go. Go. Hiya. Hiya.
Thank you. Half five.
Give me 100 percent. Next game. Jesus Christ. What.
Two.
Working up a sweat. Who are they. Who are they. I don't know who they are. Who are these people.
Hey. Hey. Jaguars. Be careful. Be careful.
We should probably do this politically democratically.
Hey. Oh shit.
What. What happened. Did I get it. Watch her. I'm good.
Hey the UN just called. We're going to buy him a little more time.
Oh it's not the UN. Oh the giant fidget spinner.
Now I get to be the pop star that everybody loves. Have a nice flight. Oh la la.
I get the microphone. Yes. Betrayal. Point the satellite at earth and begin the liquidation
process. There's evil. Whatever. You were the chosen one. That's sad. Where we at. We good.
What the fuck. Drink the water. He's drunk. It's a fucking one white cloth.
It's like point zero five percent alcohol. We were sucked into the UFO.
Is everyone. Oh great glitter. Can I. I want to hold it in my other hand.
You're not going to be a fuck with me. I have the elder wand. This thing. Minus two. Okay.
It's her.
Glitter.
Period.
Oh I would get sick from that.
I'm going to put it in my mouth and scream.
What was it. Yeah. He's insane. I'm not. I'm normal.
After all. Just one of you.
Don't you know. My name is. Who's that. Hey. I'm done. Well. What about me.
Got it. We got to save. We ready. All right. Rush him.
Oh. 100. When it comes to dancing.
Wait. This is the villain redemption arc here. Have it back. You can have it back. Take it back.
I'm my redemption arc. Take it back. Here. I don't want to go to hell. Just take it. This.
This gets me into heaven. My god redeems. Right. Come on. Take it. I want to go. I want to get to
heaven.
What. Why are we shooting there. This is kind of weird.
What the fuck. All right. Watch out. What's that called. Oh.
Shut up. Why was I not paying attention. What. My arms are too fucked up.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Whatever. Did I get it.
Literally. No. Oh my god. Jesus. Wait. Can I stand here. I think I did a lot of work.
I'm almost missed that one. What the fuck. Don't touch me. Hey. What was that. Well I don't want
to turn. I want to. I don't know what they're doing. You didn't let me choreograph this with
me. I wasn't here at the rehearsal. Oh. Whatever. I'm tired. I'm done. I'm done. I'm going to walk
off the stage. That was fun. It's your moment. That's it. I guess so. That was pretty cool.
How long did that take. Forty minutes. Wait. Wait. Wait. Dance. Putting. Was that a drug
handoff. Thanks for the coke. Put that in here and then we continue to move like we were supposed
to be here. You're an enemy. Oh. Sorry. We just got shocked. It's like. Oh. Sorry. Are you okay.
Yeah. I got me too. Did you see the blue line. Did you see the blue line. Oh my god. I was
fucking crazy. It's like a Marvel post credit scene. And here we are with celebrity death match.
I'm here. It's Tom Green versus Jim Carrey. That's the same guy. Same guy. All right. So
coming up next. We are going to play. Wait. I want to give her a high five. That was cute.
We're going to play Sniper Elite VR next. Well, we will hope for peace in the universe. Thank
you for playing the game. Sega Grounding Incorporate. Oh shit. Hold on. What. That was my big.
That was my big moment and I failed it. How did I suppose. What. I got 175 percent. All right.
Let's move on to Sniper Elite VR. I'm going to get some water. I was looking forward to that.
I played all the other ones. But hold on a second here. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Arcade dressing room. Hold on a minute. Do I get any clothes. I kind of want to be the alien.
All right. I want to be this guy. Arcade. I'm curious. I think this is just the game. Right.
Miku's far out report show. Excuse me. Excuse me. Um. Wait a minute. Hold on a minute. We're not
skipping. Do you guys know that I thought that Miku was a real person. I didn't know that it was a
vocal whatever robot. I thought it was like an actual like singer. I didn't think it was a vocal.
Whatever there. I until like six months ago I thought like Miku was just was like a singer.
This is going to be hard to do. I'm going to try. Hopefully this is not too loud for you.
Do I spill it. I don't think so. No. I don't think so. But I've heard some of Miku's songs.
Who's Miku. How old are you. I don't know. She's real to me. Space drink. Alcohol. There are no laws
where you're drinking. It's not. I can't. I'm drinking a fucking White Claw in a VR environment
in my own space. I'm telling you guys this helps. So two days ago where I almost puked from the
dinosaur game. That's not going to happen today. All right. Should I be key or Rue.
I'm excited for this. Miku's far out report. I thought she was like eight feet tall. What.
I thought she was like seven seven or something. I thought she was huge. Who the fuck is that.
Okay. Did I say that. Okay. Are we ready. Here come the aliens. Time to dance.
Who's this little weird guy. Good. Okay. Let's go. Not the cat. I don't want to be the cat.
Rescue successful. This is where I got to. Excuse me. Miku. Miku. Can I get a selfie real quick Miku.
I'm sorry. I'm just a huge fan. Oops. Hey did the viewers go up because Miku is here now.
Did they literally. Yes. Oops. Shit. It's only halfway through. Holy shit.
Oh that's another successful rescue. Be careful. Oh hard mode.
Rue bought prime. Where are the guns. Where are the guns. Where's the shooting. I know.
Just give me a minute. I can fucking move still even with a pain condition. You'll never take
that from me. You'll never get it from me. Stop making sounds for no reason. Oh I don't want to
do that. No. Whatever. 89. That's all right. This game makes. What. This game makes light of war.
What are you talking about. Oh this game makes light of war. Let's finish this together.
What did you think Miku. Did you like what I did. Did you like me. Did you like what I did.
Oh just do it. Do it normally. Oh yeah. Bye.
See you later. Good wave. I think that's all to see. We got to do this. Do it all.
I'm not going to open this game ever again. I mean like that's actually like not.
I'm never going to open this game ever again. So much. We'll do the stuff that's here.
A hundred stage dance battle. Holy shit. I'm ready for this. You're going to be dead after this game.
I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm a human. My blood is ready pumps. I like to fuck too. What does he say.
Is that me. Oh no.
Stage 11. Let's go.
What. That was right. All right. We're moving on. What the fuck is happening.
I'm winning. That's what's happening.
I keep saying that.
fucking OBS. It's showing me like 10 seconds ago. It's freaking me out.
Woof. That thing. That thing. That thing. I gotta do it. Meow. Woof. Meow. Up. Meow. Left. Meow.
Right. I didn't tell me they're gonna go faster than that.
Genuine Phil. What? Oh, Honda. That was fucking perfect. Honda. Honda. Woof. Honda.
Honda. Honda. That's so fucked up. I'm in a coma. I'm in a coma and I'm trying to
get out of the coma. I feel like I'm lying in a bed right now and my
face is kind of twitching a little bit. Like I'm gonna wake up soon if I do this.
Toyota. Toyota. Toyota. Toyota. Honda. Toyota. Woof. Honda. Woof. Meow. Fuck. I got it.
Oh God. You were in a car accident? No. I can't. Toyota. Honda. Toyota. Honda. Honda. I was like struck by a car.
Oh no. I can't. I can't. I can't. Oh.
Macho.
When does this end? I'm gonna beat this whole thing.
Jaguar. Jaguar.
Oh shit. Jaguar. Macho.
Car thing. I can't.
I'm almost there. I'm seriously almost there.
Meh. Meh. Jaguar. Meh. Hey. Oh, I'm getting a pulse. I can hear him. I hear like the nup, nup, nup. Come on, Jeremy. You can do it.
I'm coming. That's too many. It's the gorilla driving the car. That's just the movies.
Gorilla book. Gorilla reading book.
Pose. Just do it all. Shit. Pose. Pose. Pose. Pose. Pose. Pose. Jaguar. Did I do it? Holy shit, I did it.
I just sat out of the bed. It was the gorilla reading a book. He was driving a Jaguar.
It's like, Mr. Elbertson, you had hernia surgery. Are you okay? You've been here for like a few days.
Alright, I think that's good. That was fun. Wait, did you see how many calories you burned? 180 calories. Wow.
Alright, that was cool. I'm gonna drink some water. We're gonna do Sniper Elite VR. Talking to you.
Only 180 calories? Yeah, that's not that much. Do the roar. Oh, what was wrong with Boneworks? Alright, hold on.
I figured it out. So, Boneworks was a game that came out way before Alyx.
And I remember it was like, wow, a game that's actually utilizing the knuckle controllers.
And it's like, oh, look at the physics and shit. I played Alyx before I played Boneworks.
Isn't that kind of an issue, right? Like, Alyx is one of my favorite games ever.
It was my game of the year last year. It's the best VR game I've ever played.
So, I didn't play Boneworks before Alyx. Therefore, it was kind of a stepping stone to get to Alyx in a way, right?
I think that's why I found it a little underwhelming. At least me personally, right? Fuck you.
Hey, listen. I didn't say that. I don't think Boneworks is a bad game. It just didn't grab me.
That's it. It's probably fucking really good. The physics are fucking awesome.
It was really fun. The gun shooting seemed fun. The stuff having weight, that was cool.
It just didn't grab me. And that's okay. That's okay.
I don't think it's a bad game. I never said that.
I think me playing Alyx first set expectations in a weird way. I don't know why.
It was made to be innovative, not to be a good game. Well, I mean, it was, right?
I remember watching the dev videos. I don't think it's a bad game. Stop putting words in my mouth.
All right, Sniper Elite VR. If one of the mods could change it to Sniper Elite VR, that would be fantastic.
Go ahead and hold on. Can I not select it from here? Come on, dude. What the hell?
Oh, really? I don't have to. Oh, shit. I can't select it. Wait. Oh, my God. I'm using this.
All right, Sniper Elite VR. Where are you? There it is. All right, let's do it.
Pick up that can. You look like a gnome. Your opinion doesn't matter.
Oh, that's interesting. You know, the gnomes are like part of the reason why the Alliance was able to get to the fucking place that they were.
You understand the amount of cookies that you ate from those Keebler elves, those little gnomes?
Fuck the gnomes, right? You understand how important they were?
They protect your fucking garden, bro. Don't ever speak of that again. Alliance.
All right, so this is Sniper Elite VR. I think this is probably fine.
Subtitles probably on. I would assume, right? Calibrate height. Cool. Comfort.
Sprint vignette off. Smooth turn dot off. Belt size, ammo pouch position right.
Kill cam normal. Kill cam follows bullet. I guess it's just default off.
Graphics quality. Get that shit on fucking high, please. I got a 3090. Excuse me.
What a flex. It's not a flex, though. I paid like three times the price for it.
Like, it was a stupid thing to do. I had to get a graphics card. This is back when they didn't fucking exist.
All right, let's go. This seems good. Okay, new game.
Right-handed. Teleport movement. Snap turning. Intense. Free movement. Why is he sick?
Free movement. Smooth turning. All comfort assists are off.
Free movement. Snap turning. What should I put on? Put it on intense?
You will puke if I don't put it on something else. Okay. So should I do...
I don't think I want to do intense. You look like an action figure. Thanks.
Intense, intense, moderate. I'm going to do moderate, okay? I don't want to puke.
Difficulty select. That's fine. I'm going to get a giant VR video play.
Take this opportunity. You know what I'm doing. Oh, you guys can't even see the movie.
I am... This is not...
The height's wrong. I need to recalibrate the height, please. Hold on.
Oh my god. That didn't help. That didn't help. Oh my god.
Revert, revert, revert, revert, revert. Why is it doing this?
I need to fix the floor. I'm way too fucking small. I am as tall as that child.
This is wrong. I can't pick anything up. That's a shitload of bread.
We're going to eat all this bread? This is de-dust.
This is actually de-dust.
I'm sitting? I don't remember sitting.
Movement. Okay, walk here. Rotate. Alright, let's go.
Hold down the grab button. Out of bounds. What the fuck are you talking about, dude?
Hold down the grab button. Oh, get the rifle? How am I supposed to get the rifle?
It's like blocked. What? Oh.
Shit. It's the index. I have to hold it.
Stow the rifle by putting it over your shoulder. Great. Another fucking put it over your shoulder bullshit.
Up full. Okay. Move to the window. Okay. Draw your rifle.
You got it. Pull the bolt back. Retrieve ammo from your belt.
Insert clip into rifle. Where does that go?
Did that work? Push forward to relook. Okay. Hold on the rifle
with your second hand. Raise and look through the scope.
Oh my god. I don't know if you guys can see this. Can you guys see this?
Can you guys see me aiming? You do? Okay. You can see through the
everything? Good. Look through the scope. Who am I shooting? Squeeze the trigger to fire.
Okay. Steady yourself. Hold your breath.
In real life. Hold focus to steady aim.
Focus slowly slows time and shows the hit indicator.
Okay. Hold focus to steady aim. How do I do that?
Oh shit. That's a fucking headshot. Oh this is fucking crazy.
Radio. Where's the radio? Oh there it is.
Rechamber. Use. Did I do it? Did I use
the radio? Use. What do I do? Did I get it?
Use. What do you want me to do? What does it want me to do?
You already did it. Okay. Now what? It's a save point.
Why did I throw the gun? I'll just get it. That guy took the gun.
Get to the gate. Okay.
Oh I have a gun.
Alright. Both. That's Dante. Oh. Can I run faster?
Sorry. Sorry. I'm the drunk guy again.
Oh shit. Dante. Dante.
Let's go. You can fuck with me buddy. Goodbye.
That guy's dead. Oh over there. What? I thought that was
explosive. It was explosive. Why did it take so long to get there?
Did I get him? I got him. Oh sick. Shit.
Got him. Headshot. Alright his brain.
This bullet travel. Oops. Right in the knee. Alright let's go.
Here. Take the weapons. Take them all.
What's this? Let's go. Jump.
Is that a bad guy or is that a good guy? I can't imagine. I feel like this is like a
modded Call of Duty. Alright I got full ammo. Let's go. Oh you
motherfucker. God damn it. Who's left?
Who's left? Come on. Fuck.
I can get him. I'm not out of bounds you stupid game.
Stop shaking. Oh. In the mouth.
Who's left? I'm not even out of bounds. This is stupid.
Where is he? No. I did it.
You're stupid. It was all scripted. Who cares?
You're so sweaty. I know.
Game audio is low?
Interesting.
Better?
Oh hello kids.
Do you look like a dancer?
This game sucks. That's not fair. That's not fair. Don't say that.
This is kind of fun. I'm actually just kidding. It's actually kind of fun.
Boneworks 2? No. I'm just kidding. This is actually fun.
New mission. Let's do it. What am I doing out here?
Wait did he have bread in his hand? Wait I think she has bread in her hands.
God damn it. It's my day off. I don't want. Just leave me alone out here.
Why can't I just read Calvin and Hobbes in peace?
Alright let's do it. Rifle range. Let's go.
No scopes?
Brick and Morty now. No. You look like an Oompa Loompa.
Just rewind an hour and figure out why. I just have these always.
Oh wait no. It's just Mjolnir.
What?
This is way better than that.
What do you got? 10 targets? Where are they? Let's go.
Why do I have to do this? You just taught me how to use the rifle.
That was so loud.
Alright. I'm going to talk shit about VR again.
I'm going to talk shit. Let's do it. This doesn't have to be here.
You just showed me how to play the game.
I don't have to learn how to play. You just showed it to me.
Do I need a tutorial shooting range? You just showed me how to play the game.
Why are you so terrified that I'm going to not know how to shoot the gun?
Just do it. You know what I mean?
It's like, let me tell you about this immersive story.
Are you sure you know how to use the weapon? No. Get him out to a range and make sure he can hit a target.
It is so loud. I know.
Oh come on.
Deadly. Your voice was loud?
You're talking mad smack for reloading with the wrong hand.
So now what do I do? Can I leave?
Use the pistol. Arm. Use grip to pull slide.
And you reload. And then you go like this.
Is it another range?
God. Just let us play.
You're terrified that we don't know what we're doing.
Pick up the grenade.
Hold to aim.
Why did I just shrink? Oh okay. Hold to aim. What did I do?
I pulled it out.
Alright.
I'm literally sitting right in the center of my play area. What are you talking about?
Okay pistol area. Which is over there now. Alright let's go. Is there a teleport?
No. Is there a fast run? Equip a pistol.
This is how you make a lot of people mad.
I need a, I need a bullets.
Not bad. Not bad.
Very good. Not bad. Not bad. Oh yeah.
Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Right yeah. He's not very good.
Is he? You don't think so? Oh look at him. I'm so far behind.
I went beware German snipers. What are you talking about? What's going on quit mission journal?
Why is it do I get out of here? I began to feel at one with the weapon. We good. That's not bad
Okay, now what over here was the pause button? I don't know
Ten rounds five seconds count of the hours. I spent at those ranges my comrades lives might depend on me hitting my tongue
Let's move. All right, let's go
These weapons could be devastating if controlled properly to me. I need both bullets. What the fuck? I just fucking loaded it
I just loaded this what this thing sucks. Why would I ever use this precision matted? All right, let's go
stressed
huge honka
Okay
There's a shotgun make do with what we had doing our best to pick the right. I want the shotgun Joe
I don't care about the I don't care about anything else place it in the box
Then had to gather what weapons and supplies we could from the battlefield
Okay, I'll take a sniper rifle
Okay, I'll take a sniper rifle shotgun alpha bravo Charlie so that I got the shotgun that and the Charlie
Okay, whatever that is. Okay, let's go save the loadout. Okay
Drilling is the shotgun. Oh, I can't all right. I want the pistol. I like the pistol better. I can't have all three
Hey, what the fuck are you talking about place your favorite weapons into these loadout crates and they'll be shipped off to the various
Partisan safe houses for use within the missions each
consignment must have a rifle
Whatever can't read the pistol is the m19. Oh, oh, that's loadout a loadout B loadout C
I thought it was loadout and
weapon slot a B and C
Okay, that looks good. That looks good. That looks good. Let's move. Give me the fuck out of here
You've built like a truck. I know my ass is huge. I know I'm ready to play a mission
I don't like how high I am. Okay, let's do it
I got a P
I'm with this book again. Did I have another kid in the meantime? I'm drinking water. Everybody relax. Oh, that's I hate that
Okay, let's go
Here we go in the moments before his death Dante had made a contact with the Allies and begged them for help
We could only keep fighting. Hope they had heard
Let's go in the moments before his death and they had made contact with the Allies and begged
We could only keep fighting
They heard and pray they would be here in time. So let me untangle this
The artillery protect the partisans stop the attack
All right, stop the attack
You got it where that shit fuck I got it right in his liver I'm fine
Oh shit, can I get it he was no leader damn it I missed wait, he's moving so fast
I knew only I could save my teammates from being over. I didn't get it
Oh
Yeah, oh shit, how am I supposed to what that was right his head oh
My god, how did I miss him?
Fuck come on. Oh
My god, what the fuck are you talking about? Oh
My god, it's a fucking wall
Give me a shit
What the fuck
Well, wait, what is this
insert magazine
Shoot it. Do I don't have bullets?
Insert Meg. Um, give me this fuck. All right. Oh, what else do I have in here? Give me that. Oh shit
They're closing in
Oh
Give me the gun, what are you talking about? I'm in the fucking play area boy area. Oh
My oh my god. What am I hitting?
What kill him already? Oh my god wasn't much destroy the bridges
attempt to radio reinforcements prepare for the next wave Oh
fuck
Okay, okay now
What oh shit, right I've Bolton this
I got a head. I'd show that guy in the head
I saw the guy in the head with a shotgun from like 600 meters away
Holy shit
Give me them. All right sniper rifle father. The area was too overrun and it was up to me to hold off
Let's go. She's got him. Ah
Damn it
I can't
What oh my god
But we would need help from above
I'm not fucking around anymore
Just no fucking ammo in this gun
I'm trying as hard as I can. Let's go
What the fuck are you talking about? Not this time not fucking around this time. I'm not fucking around this time
That's it, right? Nope right in the head. You got to be kidding me. You saw that you you can see through my eye
Where is he? Where is he father had taken charge of the unit? All right, where's the car?
As the enemy closed in on us. I knew only I could save my
Blown up. Oh my god. Why?
What I'm trying to blow the car up
How is that not?
Fuck. Oh shit. They're over here
The Allies had sent a bomber to try to cut off the enemy fuck I
I don't understand
Give me a grenade. Why am I so bad at that? Give me this. There's no what is happening. Okay
Where you at? I have to pee so bad. You have no idea it wasn't much
But if it could destroy the bridges, okay next wave enough, I gotta pee. You have no idea how bad I have to pee right now
It's awful
Piss your pants. No, this is health. It's not health. Why oh, it's right there. Okay, I see him
That's how I feel right now. Oh
That felt good that actually felt really good to play father had to fall back the area was too overrun
Give me that give me give me give me all right over this way, right? Yep over here fucking no scope get the fuck out of here
How did he shoot me I'm literally standing all the way back here what the fuck I'm
Giving us one more tray one more try and I'm out here. It's that way. What the fuck?
Yes, I sure from the tower I could slow the enemy what do you think goes in here help from above to stop them?
I kind of think I'm think it's gonna use this
What a worthless fucking weapon. Seriously, like why would I even use that fucking stupid thing?
I'm angry now. Let's go
Father had taken charge of the unit, but he was no leader as the enemy close yet
I can't I knew right great. Give me give me give me save my comrades from being over. It doesn't do anything
Mom, please I'd be allies had sent. Oh my god to cut off the enemy
Where are you shooting this guy right ahead? Go on. Come on this way right here this motherfucker right in this hallway
Get the fuck out of here
Shatter it. Come on
Come on, Gwen fucker. God. God. I can't see
Hey, okay
You've no idea I gotta be so fucking bad it's hurting god damn it, but I can't aim that way
Okay. All right. All right. All right destroy the bridges
I'm ready. Let's go. No more fucking around take them out. God. Damn it. Where's this center? All right, I'm good
I might actually piss my pants on string in VR
Shit, he's dead. All right, where else this way this way this way this way this way this way this way
Get down get down get down get down get down get got it. Yes
The area was too overrun. That's not it. It was up to me to hold off before the bomber
a
YouTube poop video
They use that same loud fucking noise in every YouTube poop
You fucker. What the fuck be help help. Why where is he?
shit, ah
Got him. Hey. Hey, I see him. Okay. Oh my god. That didn't hit him in the head. Come on. Oh
I'm done with that one. I'm going to the bathroom playing something else. I'm gonna pee the hair. I'm back
That game was really fun. It's just kind of hard
like the scope
Is that one a stamp of approval?
Just fun. Let me untangle this thing. Hold on. We had a party while you were gone
All right. Let me take a look what I have left. There's so many VR games. Let me see what's I need to wipe this down a little
Give me one sec
The volume is gonna have to come down to
He forgot to wipe. I can't believe I did the fart in the microphone joke, by the way
The whole time I was peeing I'm just thinking about the fart in the microphone thing fuck I did do that didn't I
All right. I'm going back in I'm gonna turn the cam back on in
30 seconds or so. Hold on. Let me just get in here
What should we play?
Let's take a look
That was Sniper Elite VR and it was pretty good. We've got
L.A. Noire Case Files, Arbar, Compound
We've got Hellsplit Arena. We've got Rick and Morty, Virtual Rick-Ally, of course we do
Hmm. I wonder what should we do
Compound? L.A. Noire, L.A. Noire. I'll do L.A. Noire
Is L.A. Noire long? How long is L.A. Noire? It's 20 hours in VR. Oh my god
It's the whole game in VR. No, it's not. I thought it was the VR case files. It's like 30 minutes. Okay
All right. I'm gonna load it up and we'll give it 30-40 minutes. We'll see we'll give it an hour
L.A. Noire the VR case files. Let's go. I'm coming back on. Hello there. Hi. How you doing?
I might have to lower the volume here
So there's a lot of people that wanted me to go back to L.A. Noire
After I played it two or three times and got halfway through the game and gave up forever
Here is your stream
This is probably the last time I'm ever gonna play this
I have piss stains. I do not have piss stains. All right, where is it? Computer crash?
Apparently, it's apparently it's coming. Let me make sure it didn't crash. I don't think so. Where is it?
Oh, I have to select an I've to select a language with my mouse
What? Welcome to Rockstar's game launcher. You will need to be connected to the internet to sign in to activate the game
Oh my god, are you kidding me? What?
Choose install location. What the fuck are you talking about? What I have to get the Rockstar games log
Okay, I'm installing Rockstar game launcher. I have no idea what my Rockstar account is. I have absolutely no clue. I play the game
You let me in acting to Rockstar game service
updating Rockstar games launcher
of a god
Please for the love of god use your right hand to bolt the right-sided bolt. This is my last plead. Well, I'm not playing the game
Rockstar Social Club, come on dude, like I'm in VR. You're gonna make me do all this
Down over the Social Club and install Social Club
Here's my activation code. Good thing you can't see that
You are this is an authentic Rockstar code redeem. What the fuck is happening?
cloud saves
Can I just play
I think it's opening
Is it can you guys see it?
We're good
Okay, i'm going
That was dumb
All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm not ready
All right. This is Rockstar presents
vr case
I forgot the name of the game. I don't remember what game we're playing
Rockstar's vr case files is what I thought the game was actually called
It's gonna be a long one. I'll tell you
All right
Are you ready? Are you ready air?
God, let's go
Please select your base station configuration
My base stations face each other my controllers are accurately tracked no matter which way the hell you what rockstar
What are you what are you doing? It's like base station configuration my base. Yeah, they
Where are my hands? Yeah, they're like this select your desired physical play style roaming. Yes
Calibrating height and play space, please stand in the middle of your play area
Look straight ahead and press the right thumb stick
Provided with you some people get sick when they're in vr. This is a fictional video game really trying to take me completely out of this
What is all this? What do I have to sign like a fucking agreement to play the game?
It's like la noir the game came out 10 years ago
It came out 19 years ago
What have a hat?
Look at the wall to make a selection
new
All right new game
At any point in the game, you need to recalibrate your play space press and hold the right thumb stick. Try it
I know anymore. You have to examine clues to open
And close your hands press the trigger and grip buttons. Look at how your hands close
Oh god, was this go back? How do I go back? Hold the grip or trigger to pick things up?
Okay
Cool, you can crouch down to pick up objects by pressing the left thumb stick
Pick up the pen. Okay
Stand back up
Okay interact with the press the trigger
Weapons in la noir use a toggle grip press the grip button again to drop the revolver. Okay, so you go like that
Grip preferences can be changed. So it's just like this and you go like that
like the case
From the case folder using the trigger
City of los angeles start
Okay, i'm excited. Well, it's a shame. You don't like to talk about it. Cole ralph
Friends who want to stay friends don't discuss religion or politics
And in my case you can add the war to that
To rotate felps move the right thumb stick
Okay, let's turn who is that? I know that window bow away before he jumped for all
La noir has three different movement modes press a to continue
Depending on your vr experience some forms of navigation may cause discomfort
You can navigate to any position using your
Recticle double tap left a or right a to bring up your recticle and pressing it and navigate to the position
No, I don't
All right, so it's a
The next mode is highlight movement press right a to continue
Double tap left a or right to bring up your electrical point the fence to make it glow
Okay
Standing near a navigable object will cause it to glow
Navigate over it
Final one is arm swinging. You can change your walking mode in the pause menu. Yeah, I want I want to fucking move
I don't want to like
Okay, hold down left a to initiate walking swing your arms
Okay, like this warning some players might find this mode uncomfortable, okay
Hold down to sprint. Yeah, I want this. This is better. Yeah, I don't want that
apprehend the suspect
Where is he?
Don't make me chase you
I'm coming
I got this
Oh
You didn't even let me check
I'll bolt grip and trigger button to make a fist. Oh my god. Get this off. Okay block by raising your arms
A successful block will reset your screen duck and dodge your opponent to attack. This is like a boxing game
How you doing wendell
Your parole officer's feeling lonely
He's got a hole get him in there for an asshole like you you can make it up to him in 10 years time
Watch your head
This hump will be back in the iron hotel by tomorrow night. Nice work. Cole. Thank you. You run track in high school
No
That's funny
Take the hat off. I can't
armed and dangerous
All right. Yeah, get the hat off. You're right. Can I take his hat off?
We'll take that. All right, let's go blocks from here only a couple blocks
That's
Okay
You and me the steering in la noir uses a toggle grip
Grip the door handle and push to exit. This is not this. How do I get out of here?
Grip and pull to engage the handbrake
This grip the radio to respond to dis dispatch
14 adam calling kgpl. We'll handle the 211. We'll take that
Let's go
Grip the ignition key and turn it
Press the left trigger to break 14 adam on route
This is too much hold on I got it just keep yourself in the seat
Press your hand on the center of the wheel get out of here
Get back here citizen
Take a little drive here
I feel like the cartoon character in the movie that gets control of the car
Right. I'm like the monkey. You know what I mean? That like oh no, he can't monkey can't drive
No, he can't
Oh my god
This is fucking puking doosie
Oh shit are these bad guys
Oh shit
Keep your other hand off the pump pull the trigger to go like this push the trigger to spawn ammo
What keep your other hand off the pump and press the trigger feed the round four rounds
Double tap left a or right a to point your head to the highlight cover press again to move
Oh fuck
What the what what happened with my shotgun? What happened to my shotgun?
Did I get him reached to the chamber with your other hand and press the trigger to release the chamber
Shit with your empty hand press
spawn ammo
Fucking god. Damn it
Where'd it go?
Let's go put your weapons. Why do I keep dropping the gun?
No
All right, i'm going crouch while in cover by pressing left thumb stick
Shit use the cover felt
We don't know how many are in there
Take it slow
Backup will be here soon
LAP
What the fuck that's all right i'm doing this
All right, seriously, I fucking feel like i'm at like a disney ride where i'm not doing it
All right
It's weird the index controls are weird because I don't have to grip it
I grip it and let go but then I have to go like this
You know, okay, I grip it and then I have to let it go and go like this. It's weird
All right, come on come on come on come on
All right. I'm not gripping. I have to literally let go of it
Okay. Now I just have to hold it
Okay, use the trigger to shoot. Let's go
weapons on the ground now
Holy shit, I shot that guy in the fucking head
Your goddamn head down use the cover felt
LAPD put down your weapon put your head put it down is surrounded. I'm offering you a chance to
Take it slow
And here put your weapons down and your head in the air got it shit shit
Got him
Where is he was it as soon as he poked his head? Damn it. Give me the gun
Fuck stay in cover
Oh my god, I can't shoot this guy
What the fuck?
Why?
And it's the electric chair
We got them all I think we got them cold. We did it should be all nice job guys
Holy shit, it's fucking hard hopkin says anytime you reach for the shotguns
You're either gonna end up dead or wearing a citation. So I guess it's okay ralph
You did well in there
On my back like a tick tock video. I couldn't ask for a better partner
Where am I? I don't where am I? I don't know where I am use your words. Hold on. I'll use my white cloth
What's about kgpl
What are we doing
What are we gonna do
What happened? Hello
You and me we going
Oh fuck. Okay
Come on. We gotta high five before a case
No, don't warp
Am I dry?
No
Holding the brake
I'm holding the brake. Why would it not break?
Oh my god
Okay, literally left triggers break, right?
Why is it not working?
Watch this ready
This doesn't do anything. It's so slow
Floyd rose homicide you might back up. Yep. Yes, sir felps and done wilshire division
We had a shooting took place down this alleyway
We have the vic scooter paten a negro male bagged up and on his way to central morgue
Witness as a tall white guy our shooter put two in the vic's head and then threw his piece
I need you guys to try and recover the gas
Thanks
Points of interest will be behind felps turn around 180 degrees. Give it your best shot guys
The dead guy's a low light. I'm not expecting any miracles here. Did we recover the weapon bag it and return it to technical services
I'm out of here
A lot of it. I gotta check and see if he has anything
Hey, excuse me. Do you have anything on you? Do you have any that? What do you got on you a gun?
All right, let's go. You can look at your partner to ask for advice
We've got to be thorough coal check into every corner. All right, let's go
This is a fist hump. Just going through them. I walk you're probably right. Let's just get it over and done
All right, have it your way. We'll search right up to the back wall
If you still don't come up with anything come find me and we'll talk it out
How do I walk heads are always better than one?
I want to walk
How do I move?
I want to walk look at this junk. I don't want to do this. I want to walk
Old a
Oh, okay pick through other people's trash
What's over there?
What have you got felps anything? I found something over here. It looks like it might be some kind of a weapon
I tell you i'm jinxed. I always get landed with this crap
It was just a root beer. I don't see anything over here felps. What's his name? Jesus
Cole come take a look at this. What is it?
blood
There's blood over there
Shooter put him up against the wall and blew his brains out
hell of a way to go
Doesn't really matter how you go I should be taller don't get all deep on me felps. Okay, take that into evidence
Where am I?
Looks like there was a break a break over here of some kind
Whoops looks like there might have been a break over here of some kind
I'm gonna go up. This is just the regular game. Isn't it? This is just the the first game
This is the game. I remember this case
rotate
Rotate your hand to manipulate an object and search for points of interest
Smith and wesson serial s 7 1 8 9 3 game out through the window
It's the game you're playing. Yeah, but I thought the v so this is just la noir, but it's in vr. That's it
Grip settings. I'll be all right. What do we got in here two rounds fired?
And instead of dropping it down a drain our shooter hoists it up here
interesting guy
Interesting we should follow up on this now before the perp tries to leave town
Release how press the grip button to exit inspection. Okay
Information on the case can be reviewed in the notebook
Sure can your notebook is in your left shirt pocket
Okay, I need hold on put that down use the pencil and the trigger to select entry. Okay, we're going to go with clues
Blood stain and there was a smith and weston here each recovered clue is sketched in catalog. There it is
Okay, this there it is
This is what we think he may have looked like
We may we think he may have been wearing a diaper. All right, exit your notebook press b b b b cool now
What what about that now? What go down? Is there anything else up here? Wake up col? We have the gun col
Let's take it back to central. We could get a commendation
I could show some initiative ralph and see if we can come up with an owner. That's a long shot col
It's pretty fancy gun. You know a local gun store. Sure. There's a place a couple of blocks from here
He said he got like really annoyed with that. All right investigate the gun store
Stop in the name of the law
What is this thing?
This is a nice car
What is this 1920 1920 chevy?
pretty nice
You did good nice work
I'm tangled up. All right. Are we ready? Let's go
Show's over keep moving all of you
Gun store, let's go. Let's move to this destination
Let's go
shit
This is so awkward
Can I go down the alley?
Whoa, it sounds like an old ship
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey
Excuse me. What are you?
I can't okay. Let's go
Get in the car
Your insurance. All right, go. Why can I not drive?
It's fucking scary
All right, it's right here
Gun store 10 44 p.m. Let's get in there and investigate that guy. What do you think?
Otherwise, how tall are you? I hear he's 610. I'm not a loss
Have a word with the owner. He ought to have the guy who bought the weapon registered
Don't mind me. I'm just a weirdo officers phelps and done
Can you tell us anything about this gun? Where were you smith and wesson?
Model 27 registered magnum. Uh-huh chambered for 357
Nickel plated with pearl grips. Thank you same gun used by general pat and who bought it from you?
You're not suggesting he's the owner. No, i'm not you seem to know a lot about the weapon. I ought to I sold it
You know, this piece will stop a rhino but that did put it down babies are only available special order
Here's my smith and wesson order book
Do you mind if I take a look who bought it my guest?
This is about something bad, right?
Yep, okay
Who bought it model 27 with pearl grips col?
You see it on there
Model 27 with pearl grips
Model 27. We've got model 27 here with pearl grip this guy right here
There is luck errol schroeder
203 south gless street this one
No, wrong guy. Go back
Go back. I don't want to go. I kind of go back. Okay smith and wesson revolver. He had it on him
And sounds pretty good to me
Uh registered gun owner and murder suspect. It's very good to know good to know clues
within weston
revolver
Uh
Okay, sounds pretty good to me. Thank you for the information. Appreciate it. What does he uh, what does he live?
Thanks. You've been a big help anytime always happy to help out the la pd. Let's get out of here
shoot him like
detective butterfingers
Hey col, let's get moving open the door
You're a human
Hold on a second. I gotta I gotta write down my lotto numbers at home
Only stay right there if you pulled the trigger
Okay, six and for a penny or a pound. Well, i'm sorry. We're gonna be million. I'll give you twenty thousand dollars
Just let me do this
Put it down
You want to pay this schroeder character a visit? Don't you?
We're best friends
Wait, I need to
Let's go
Oh, this is actually makes me kind of want to puke
You want me to keep tabs on the path of destruction you're creating it might come in handy quiet
Where are my headlights? I can't see anything. How do I turn my headlights on?
I can't see shit. I really can
Don't
Yes, keep tabs on the path of destruction. I'm creating keep tabs. I'm doing
All right, we're almost there
Do I have a siren?
There are no headlights
Schroeder's apartment 11.06 pm
How come I can't use the right a to run
That's kind of annoying. So, you know, I can't I can only use left a
What's happening?
Where does he live right here somewhere?
Where does he live?
Do you know where schroeder is? Do you know do you know what schroeder is? Have you ever heard schroeder?
You ever heard of the name schroeder? Do you know what schroeder is?
I am an officer of the law. I'm an officer of the court
Okay, whatever
Where's the apartment here
In here doors of knobs can be turned
All right. Uh, we're looking for schroeder
Sherwood schroeder schroeder apartment two
Looks good
apartment two apartment two, let's go col
Follow my lead that was horrible. That made me actually want to throw up. I don't know what happened
But whatever we're gonna keep going. What are we waiting for?
All right apartment two is uh is the apartment we need to go into let's go ahead
Uh, let's go ahead and knock
What are you? I'm sorry. I'm officer cole phelps. This is officer dunn wilshire division
You're the owner of a smith and wesson model 27 nickel plated with pearl grips. I might be
What of it then you'll be surprised to know that schroeder payton was murdered tonight with your gun
You're out of your mind
Schroeder he works for me. They have that gun here in my drawer. You might have a comment
What the fuck is going on here you're under arrest schroeder cuff and ralph way you're not taking me down for this
What the hell am I
What is the vr fucking kick out?
What happened?
Well, am I still alive? Oh my god, where does it think I am?
Where does it think I am? I don't understand
Where does it think I am?
What's happening to my character?
What's why is it doing this?
Oh my god, come to me come to me. Okay, it's like shaking around. This is horrible
Am I punching someone?
All right. What on earth is going on?
Ralph you all right fine. I hardly felt hold on I
He's lucky. He caught me off guard. What the fuck? I have a shadow that freaks me out so much
I'm gonna take a look around. Oh my god. What is this doing?
Are you guys seeing the same thing? I'm horrible. I'm in the center of my play area. What the fuck does it think i'm doing?
Okay, I gotta take this off like this is fucking horrible. What is this doing?
I didn't like unplug it or anything. Did I?
No
Where does it think I am?
Jesus
Wake up. I'm right in the middle of my play area
What do you want me to do look for clues?
Oh my god, I thought he was gonna shoot himself. What the fuck is happening?
What's the fuck
What?
Why would you hold it there? Ow
Oh my god, what were you doing?
He's like fucking like this is this whole thing is fucked up right now
My my vr is like shaking
All right. I gotta get out of this game. This is something fucking horribly wrong right now
I gotta change games like this is fun. But like holy shit. Where does it think I am?
Is shaky like you guys?
Oh, we got things to do
It's so frame ready. Yeah. No, I gotta go. I okay good fucking goodbye. Goodbye. I'm sorry rockstar
What the fuck is this bullshit?
Base stations of all thought everything's normal. What the fuck?
My god, this whole thing is fucked up
Okay, uh, give me a moment while I figure out what the hell is going on
Um been playing the i've been playing for like the last three hours. Hold on a second. Um
Can I reactivate the camera? Okay, the camera's back
Weird about steam viewer. No steam viewer is fucked up. I think I have to leave the game guys. I'm sorry
This was like really fun, but I i'm gonna try to restart it. Maybe hold on i'm gonna go beer before a second
Ralph you all right. I'm fine. I hardly felt it
He's lucky
Uh, I've reset of the game. Let's see if that fixes it
but first let me get some water and a little bit more, uh,
you know
Oh, I mean is doing it again. I think it is. No, don't do it again. Come on
Keep an eye on him ralph
It really doesn't like when I move out of the play area like at all
I'm gonna take a look around
I think we're good
All right, let's do it. If it fucks up again if it freaks out again, then
I'm gonna uh, we'll play something else
Going in
This is all bullshit. You hear me? I told you everything I know
All right. Oh
Just checking my hair real quick
Stay down
Oh, no. Nope. No, this is fucked
This is really fucked
Yeah, this is fucked up. Yeah, I don't know if um
I don't know if la noir is gonna work out
Somebody said that this came out when the vibe was a thing and they probably haven't updated it a very long time
Damn it
Uh, give me one sec
It crashes a lot
The cord's fine. Yeah, I checked the cords. Everything seems plugged in
There's an old ass game it doesn't support index fuck well that was fun for what I got to see
It's time for rick and morty
All right. I will play rick and morty vr for 30 minutes if you promise that none of you will leave
Promise me you won't leave and i'll do it. All right library. What do we got?
Um, let me see. Let me see. There's something else. I want to play
there's
I want to play compound that looked really fun. All right, we're playing compound
Let me go pee one more time because I know i'm gonna have to in like five minutes i'll be right back
Okay, i'm back
Let's go ahead and open up a compound
And we'll continue
Uh mods change it to compound, please if you could
That's so sad
That seemed like that was really picking up too. Oh, well. Oh, well, I want to see more
thriving
That was kind of terrible to be honest
I really feel like I was gonna be sick
Because when you're moving what you're not moving forward it really does a toll on your brain
It just hammers your like right in the frontal lobe
All right. Let's do it compound time
Damn, dude, you shit out of that fat ass
Listen to me
You have to understand something
I look
I'm wearing a thing that's like compressing my back
So it might look like I have whatever
What do you want me to say?
Why did I read that because it was there and it was for me. I could see it
I could see it. All right, let's go
Wait, you can't even see
Hey, I can
Compound vr. Let's do it. I'm gonna bring you guys back shit
Oh
Aha. All right, let's move
All right currently selected no snap turning like minecraft, uh select your controllers i'm using
the
How I select oh
the index
This is the valve index
Turning option currently selected snap. No snap turning locomotion. That sounds good to me
Uh, I think this is probably pretty good pick up the gun
Pistol and shoot the icons select the desired options. All right, let's move
This feels pretty good
How loud is that can you yeah, why can't I see you guys?
What the fuck is that did it crash?
What the fuck come on
Report this to the developers
Give me another second. Hold on
Is it loud? I'll turn it down a little
Okay report. I was playing la noir. Yeah, so la noir really fucked everything up
Make sure that's fixed
No, there's another like crash tab. What the fuck what let me i'm gonna restart steam vr. Hold on. This whole thing is messed up now
Okay, we're good. Sorry about that
Uh, I have come back from the crash
Go back in. Sorry vr is a very finicky finicky beast. Okay
compound
Thank you for your patience. Appreciate it
And we should be able to go back into this now
Can you see it?
No, there I am
And you should be here. There you are
Fantastic
All right, let's try this again
Fucking vr. All right, get me in all just for the loud noises when I touch this thing
I'm capturing
There you guys are. Thank you
Back to it. Come on
Index this is fucking loud though. It really is
loud for me
Which means it's probably really loud for you
Rebel hq fuck it's itchy
This is really kind of nice looking though
tutorial and shooting range
Very cool. Oh, it actually is like completely index compatible
Nice nice. It is like this is cool. I like it
I really actually really like it a lot so far
All right. Cool. You make hamburgers and shit. That's awesome
Uh currently selected easy as pie medium
Uh, I don't want hard boost. That's probably throw up
Okay, let's do the uh shooting range
Oh
Hot dogs horseshoes and hand grenades. It's by the same people
Dude, this is fucking really actually really fun
That was cool. Do I have to reload it?
Out of a reload, okay fire a few bursts at the target until you completely run out of ammo in the horizontal clip
Those the bullet spread is too high to hit anything distant
Sure
Okay, reloading is a skill and you'll need to practice
How do I get it?
To reload the smg press the spawn ammo button on your offhand controller
Pull a clip out and attach to the top
Oh shit
Okay
Hang off the clip. You'll be ready to fire
How are you doing weapon action button? Oh shit
That's cool. All right. What about the other ones?
What is this?
Oh
This feels really good. Okay. Now I can how do I open this? All right, like you can go like this
That's fun. What about this one? I have to hold it with two hands. I do
Oh shit, it's like a sniper rifle
All right. Well, how do I load this one? Good noise. It's got really good noises. It does
How do I load rail gun is perfect dealing with high damage long range, right?
Four shots take your time
Okay, put a stripper clip on the bolt opening on top of the rail gun
Isn't it going here?
It doesn't do that. It doesn't do that. How do I do that? Am I doing this wrong? How do I do that?
Line it up
One face forward
What are you doing? Orange goes forward
Oh
This thing is okay. That's cool. What about this one?
Oh cool
Nice. What else?
How do I oh shit
So far the gunplay is fucking phenomenal. I will say
Oh
All right. How do I reload this?
This is like this
Oh shit
Okay. What about this one? This is fun
Okay. Now this goes
Where does this go in here?
Cool. Did I know you didn't use this one? What does this one do?
Okay, how does this one reload just like that?
I love it. I I actually oh, there's a bow and arrow you are you kidding me? Oops
Where am I?
Give me that
No way
Grab grab bows with your offhand
This is sick
Wait, hold on. That's fun
Emergency handgun does it have infinite ammo? It does
Store. Oh wait store weapon move weapon action
Fire spawn ammo grab drop. All right, let's do it. I'm ready. This is fucking awesome
Switching to your pistol is always faster than reloading
Now, let me do a stretch
Music by speed black enter the compound
I'm ready
Let me be sure i'm in the right spot
Practice area. All right
You give me that emergency handgun. How do you store like that? Okay. So how do I pull it back out?
Good to know
So I don't have to hold the grip
Actually, maybe I do
Maybe I do
Yeah, that's actually better though. Okay, cool
Uh, there's the options mutation dispenser
I don't know what that is
repair shower
removes mutations
Let's just go
underground sewers
All right. I died. Can I get two handguns?
This is awesome
All right. Good. Good. Good. Where we going? I need a gun. This is actually like the funnest vr game i've ever played
Okay, how do I do I can ammo for it?
ammo map clear
Danger poisonous chemicals electric hazard join the core via corpse
Oh, that's how you cycle. Okay, so I did it. Oh shit. All right
sewers level two
Hold on. We got to spin around a few times
All right. I'm ready
Holy shit. This is fun
This is fun. This is really fun
This is like what the guy that made doom like wanted to make doom
profit before safety, okay
nice
It feels so fluid too. This game is like super fluid. I love it
It's it's fantastic
Drink the game this game actually looks pretty solid demented
Just got her. Is it wearing a corset? Yes
Map clear nice. All right
Anything else I can do can I get like money or something? What should I do?
He's waste training
Jeremy your voice is fucked. It's because i'm coming through a vr headset
Continue. Yeah, let's go
reception and sales
Hey, just double the price to remove the following side effects
Itchiness nausea balding brain damage
What am I doing here?
m staff only
Sell a family member
Uh, is this a store?
sales, huh
There's like bullet movement. Where is he? Oh
Fuck oh my god, he hit me in the head
Ooh new weapon. Oh shit. Oh shit. I can't take both
I can't all right. Well, whatever. I don't need it. Let's go. Oh fuck
It's the rail gun, right?
Oh shit
This is all right. Is there other bosses in this game? Because if it is are they bosses?
Rail gun has a scope
Use the scope. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I see
reception and sales too
Oh shit
Maniac what?
Oh my god
Did they get him?
workers workers
Holy shit. All right. Give me this ammo. Where's my actual health? Oh shit. I had I have a thing here
Oh, that's cool. All right. I'm really into this. This is actually really fun. What happened? Did I die?
That was a colat. Yeah, that was fun. All right, let's keep going. What does it say my ammo does it say my ammo somewhere
32 13, okay
You actually put the game on easy. I did when I put it on the regular difficulty. What's our vaccine?
All right, this uh, this game's an early access still that's
Really surprising actually
Oh
Nothing over there. We're good. It's easy
It's early access and yet it's still better than a lot of triple a games. I mean, this is fun
This is one of the sickest alpha games i've ever seen if this is alpha
I mean, this is really fun
If they're bosses then this is like i'm gonna give it a pretty
That it
I kind of want a different gun
You know what?
I want this that thing's fun, but this one's better where we at. Okay, I gotta go
This way
Hell, yeah. Yes continue. Whoops. Don't leave that
That would have been really bad
It's drop time to stream up only where am I going? Oh, this place is pretty big right through here. Holy shit. Okay
Oh my god, it's the fucking thing from the terminator. Not the terminator fucking the
Um robocop robocop robocop robocop robocop robocop robocop robocop
Give me this eat the hot dogs. We're good suspicious including women children elderly. All right, we're good
Cat puke I want that. Oh shit. It hurt. No, no, no, no, no
Oh fuck
This is a gamer game. I'm telling you
This bullet lead to
Oh that hurt
I missed something over here. What did I miss over here? There's like a hidden thing right here. What is this?
Oh nothing
Gamer game. There's no bosses on easy. Can you do a weld?
Um, I think it'd be hard to move and do a weld actually maybe not because I can move with the right stick too
I'll try it. Oh shit
Oh god, this is gonna be hard i'm gonna i'll give it a try you can only shoot him a couple times though
Not worth it
Uh burger, uh, I haven't gone this way. Let's go straight
Sick. All right. Good the contrast between now and sniper elite
I mean sniper elite is that game is more precise. This is more about like moving around fast. That's it, right?
It is let's go try a harder difficulty
Weapon unlocked laser pistol. I'll up the difficulty if I can after this
I feel like this is gonna be probably a boss
number one priority
Oh my god, wrong way wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong
Who's calling god damn. Sorry. I'm being like silent gamer right now. This is sorry
There's no commentary just weird guy in vr with like a big ass plays compound
Yeah
All right. This is a huge level. Should I go down?
I'm thinking probably go up
Are we clear? I guess I should I investigate
There's nothing else in here really up the elevator. I think that's right go up go down. Oh shit right here
Very very oh new weapon. No, I already had that
Give me something new. I don't want that. I don't like that thing. Somebody said reloading sounds like eating a radish
I guess all right new level. Where's the exit? Oh, it's over here
Profit management too. Does it any idea how much more I have before like a boss or something or is it procedurally generated?
No bosses. There's no bosses in easy. Oh, so should I like back out and put it on higher difficulty?
That looks like a boss
shit
It's easy eric
I'll change it. Oh my god
Easy eric after this level that is the only boss that's on easy
Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever it's all right, okay, let's play on on harder, okay hard
Where do I put this? How do I make the game hard?
Take it with me. So it's now's on hard. All right, let's go. I need a gun. Let's fucking go
Oh
Okay, hard henry. That's right. Ooh new weapon. Yes. All right, cool. Jax is back
For a brief moment. He is
maybe
Warning you are being hunted by what?
Oh my god, what the why am I moving backwards? Stop moving backwards. Why am I moving backwards?
What the fuck? I was trying to move forwards
All right, let's go go go go go go go
Fuck i'm starting to feel it
in my chest
The boomer brace can only do so much. It's almost uh
Oh, hold on. Let me see how this plays
Okay, now we go like this
It goes down like that close it
end of the stream voice
Not quite but almost
Oh fuck what i'll get it
What is that? Oh, it's this thing. All right, fuck that weird rat thing
We're good. Oh, okay. It has direct hit. Oh shit i'm out of ammo
I'm fine
Good nice
Healing potion. Oh, yeah, this looks so fucking fun. It is I want to like keep playing it
But my body's like breaking down
Right in here. I can feel it. Holy shit. How do you kill this thing?
I really don't want to have to do this, but I think i'm gonna have to stop. Ah
Why
Why?
Again get on me. Hold me tight
One more I want to play that's okay. That feels all right. All right, let's go
I mean, this is so much fun
No
Uh, fuck
Sorry. Sorry. Be careful. I'm all right. I'll be fine. Damn it
All right. I gotta I gotta stop. Fuck. This is so fun though
Uh, it's only been like three hours and 30 minutes
No
Sit down. It's not gonna help dying of old age. No
I'm not
But how about like a chill game? What do I have? That's chill. Let me take a look. What do I have?
That's like more relaxing
Oh, you know what you
beautiful beautiful people
I have an idea
Let's go
Tilt brush that game was so much fun dude. Seriously compound that that's like an a plus
Sure, it's
Correctly
I'll play it tomorrow. No, no, no
I'll be okay. This is this is a very relaxing game
This is relaxing
But i'm just gonna chill and i'm gonna put like bubbles everywhere. I'll draw you guys a picture. This is really fun, too
All right. Let's go. Uh, let's see environment night sky or
space
Or let's see
standard
We just just did all right. Let's do let's get a good blue
Is a fire
This fire how is this fire? Oh, I guess it is fire
Okay
Now undo undo
Let's do let's get some light here
How about um
And it's like like this pretty good start. Okay, and then i'm gonna do
Get some snow the snow is gonna be blue
It's a good like entry way
A little more. How does he have an hourglass figure and a beer gut?
God damn it. I don't know
Fucking crazy. Okay
Well, because i've got like a dancer's body and I like to drink beer
How is that so hard to understand?
Oh my god bubbles. Okay
VIP that guy for 10 minutes. Okay
Uh, let's do
I need to build something tuned what color make a big face
Start with this
Okay
um, uh, all right
This is like a crab it's a hermit crab get the fuck out of here we need a shell that looks all right
Maybe a little bit less
That looks good. All right. Come here
Hermit crab i'm going along nicely. All right, we need he needs uh, he needs pupils. Oh, uh, whatever
That looks like a snail that seemed to be hermit crab. Watch
That looks all right. How many legs do they have? Not that many. How about some flowers too?
Well, how about some sunflowers?
Oh
Nobody knows what that is. That's not the teletubbies
No, it's
I can't even do it again
He's coming up from the bushes
All right. What the fuck is it? It's it's the dog with just look up dog. La la la. It's simple
It's like an old meme video from like fucking 12 years ago
It's not trump
Oh la la
La la la that's my favorite dog, you know, what's my favorite animal when it goes la la la la la
This sucks
This is awful
Dr. Wiggles
Oh nickelodeon presents the funny hermit crab. I'm gonna make a cake looks kind of cool
Put on the brace. No, I need to I gotta I gotta cool off
You sound like a dog. What you're already caked. Yeah, okay
All right. Let's um, let's erase everything
There's there's your hermit crab. I'm gonna make a cake
And then i'm gonna stop this is tilt brush is really fun though
if you have even a shred
of artist
Inspiration and artist artistic skill you can do some crazy stuff in here. Uh, let's make a cake. Let's go with
What should the cake be? Okay, let's go with
Okay
Fucking comet coming to earth
No, sorry
Um hyper grid. It's just every technological video game
Well detroit become human
Oh my god, look at all the squares and triangle like techno stuff
I don't what I do. I don't I don't no snapshots get the camera out of here
Okay, let's start over. No, just do a cake like you said you're gonna do. What are you doing?
All right. Here we go. That's not that's not a cake
Oh la la
La la la
This is no this is gonna be like a cake that you left in your car for too long
Don't you just want to take your real life hand and just smush into this? I do so you don't need to make
Like the the diy slime bullshit
You don't have to like pollute the earth with like the slime the plastic glue slime
That's never gonna go away. Just play tilt brush is the same thing like look I can do this in tilt brush
So you mean I can like and like squeeze it move it and I don't need to like pollute the earth
See what I mean? I can just like it's so cool. It's I love it and like I can squeeze it
Slime tuber it even makes the sounds too. Oh, I want to put that on there. All right undo
God it's not
It doesn't what about those comets coming to earth
This is like this is like what I see when I look down in the bathtub. Okay, like you know, it's just like oh there it is
What it looks like
Okay, uh put your eyes on it no that looks bad
How about uh cell vinyl? Ooh
It looks like an invader zim character. Don't forget about the fucking lightning. Um, what is this duct tape?
No, I don't like that. Uh, I need a different color. How about uh, what is this like turd?
What's this like fucking goldfish poop? I didn't do that. Oh, can you imagine what this is saying?
To me, this is kind of saying something along the lines of
La la
La la la, okay
Now are we black right so I can fill it in it's not what I wanted it to look like but it's okay
Whatever. I don't know. Do I care? It's like
It's gotta go right. It's gonna grab somebody over here. Hold on. We're gonna add some fucking finesse
I feel like this is just what kind of burdo looks like
With a lens of we're both on hallucinogenic. It's elusive. I fucked the joke up hallucinogenic drugs
Where am I? Oh, I like that. Okay. How about um, how do I stand back up?
Dude check this out
Oh, dude, it's so sour. It got something. It was like
Okay chat misunderstands the joke yet again. What?
So this is an nft
I'm not done. No, he's like in the shower. Yeah
Okay, cool. Ooh
Wait, how do you do dna dna is like that dna?
No, it's close
I just like playing around with this shit. It doesn't matter if this looks like a children's puke. I don't care. What about um,
Oh stars
Cool. Cool. I like it except for this part. We're gonna get rid of that part
I don't like this either. What is what what's going on up here?
I don't like that. They give him a body. It's I just like doing that. That's fun velvet ink
Somebody comes in the room. This is like that. I feel like i'm it's like a um
A rorschach painting and what do you see here? How did I just do that germa explain germa, please explain the bathtub joke
You have a deformed to what?
What are you saying? Say it again. So what the what's the bathtub joke?
Yes, explain it and what what did I do?
Bathtub. I went I said a bathtub reference
Explain the bathtub joke. He forgot already
He said you look down and see in the bathtub
Okay, is this a dick do I need to spell that out for you?
Like I just looked down just like fucking what are you talking about?
Like if I go like that and i'm in the bathtub i'm going to be looking right down at like a
What do you do? You really know I need to explain that
A deformed penis
That's not a this is like what your dick does when you just are sitting around hanging out in your living room. Okay
This is what it looks like. It's like pushed up against your pants. All right, i'm done. I'm done. I'll see you guys stone sunday
I'll see you guys on sunday
See you later. What do you mean? Not no, you have no this is what it looks like
If you sit in the bathtub if you're lying in the bathtub and you are lying back and you look down
It's gonna look like this. I'm sorry, but I have to do this. It's like
What do you want me to say?
Like what do you I usually give what's what's wrong with you? What's wrong with your body?
That's t. O. S. That is a
Piece of frosting that I can't wait to never mind
Look at we're doing all kinds of colors. Look at my creation
I mean I would
People are way more talented than I am can play with this. It's like
When when like the bomb goes off
You know what I mean? Like what are we even looking at? It's just like destruction. You're the only person playing feels bad man playing what?
I'm getting out of here
I don't have a deformed penis
I'm not gonna do that
That looks like a corndog
Let me let me just visualize what I what it looks like
I mean, it's smaller than it typically would be but i'll see you someday. I'll see you sunday
Sorry, we're doing these like four-hour vr streets, but like I just
I have to take these breaks. I gotta go take a bath. I actually i'm gonna take a bath. I'm gonna look down
You're drawing penises. I was not i'm not that's not what was happening
I
I'm actually going to take a bath. I really do mean that
So we'll take another day in the middle. I'll come back and there's still like a bunch of shit that I really want to play
so sunday will be another like
five vr games or so
and then
Oh and then
Got something to talk to you guys about
on august 1st
There's gonna be there's gonna be quite the announcement. I wouldn't miss that stream
Well, you could because that's the announcement of the thing that's not the thing that's the announcement of the thing
But august is gonna be huge
Got a lot of interesting stuff going on in august
And i'll see you guys on sunday
It's not catboy stream too
And it's also not grotto beasts. They make that very clear
That's also a thing
This is different
Oh, that was a lot of fun though
Thanks for watching
Compound was awesome. I just wish I could move around and play it
No, nobody's nobody's pregnant
All right, let me write the games I played
and
Space channel 5 vr was an
An 8.7 out of 10. It would have been like a 9
It would have been like an 8 point. No, it would have been like a 7 7
But I mean like miko, you know what I mean?
Uh sniper elite vr was probably like an a but I just couldn't handle it. So i'm gonna give it like a c plus
Then compound was an a plus
What was between that?
What else did I do?
What was the third game?
L.A. Noire. All right that that that would have been so much fun
I would have stayed in that
Then obviously tilt brush is like
Five out of five
So on sunday, we'll probably open with um
I have a couple of really big popular
We'll see I got a lot
La la la la la
Uh, thanks for sticking around though
And thanks for the subs. I couldn't really see
There were a lot that came
Stop doing get a hair check. Yes, we would. Yes. Yeah
Not even that bad
It's really not that bad
Could be way worse
Bath time with jeremy
Uh, let's let's do a raid. Why not?
Of you who is the one
Let's go to mr. Sark is streaming
No, I don't ever catch
Let's go raid sark playing alan wake
Um wake dlc i've played it and i'll see you guys on sunday same time around 4 pm
Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves