What about Rumbleverse? I've heard of it, but I haven't played it.
Alright, what's it called? 20 minutes? Is it on Steam?
20 minutes till dawn. Okay. Early access.
This is also $3! Vampire Survivors is $3 too, isn't it? Or $2?
That's interesting. Okay.
Uh, stream might have an issue here, because I'm about to be sick.
I'm downloading a game right now, so the stream might, like, die. Are we good?
Rumbleverse is fun. This game's 100 megabytes. Damn.
Okay, let's see how it is.
20 minutes till dawn. How about? Stop!
Yeah, 100 megabytes.
Dude, I don't even need to change the name of the title.
Trying out this new game, right?
Alright, how are the options? Is this a controller game?
Thank you. I can turn that off.
Should I do controller, or should I do mouse and keyboard?
Controller? Okay.
This is the only character that I have. Standard mode, endless mode.
Standard mode. Ten minutes survival. Alright.
20 minutes? Standard mode. Yeah.
Okay. Flip to shoot. It's a right trigger to shoot.
I actually would probably prefer mouse and keyboard.
Yeah, definitely. Oh yeah, without a doubt. Hold on.
I need to turn the sensitivity down. Can I turn the sensitivity down?
Auto-aim. Oh, okay.
This is fun. Choose an upgrade. Double shot?
Dark arts. Ooh, it's like a crit.
Bullet speed? Max vitality? Ghost friend. Ghost friend.
This is a full-on genre now.
That actually makes me really happy, because Vampire Survivors is so fucking fun.
This type of game is so fun. I hope these guys make millions of dollars
setting this genre. Right?
I hope they make millions of dollars.
And then it's like, okay, a bunch of people are making games that are like this too,
but that's alright. You got a huge bag.
Alright, I hope they make a lot of money.
This game is called Garlic Likes. Really?
I like that. Rapid fire. Let's go.
Oh fuck, I'm gonna die. I'm dead. I'm not.
Alright, hold on.
Energetic friends. Summon attack speed plus 50%. That sounds good.
Oh, I see. And it also unlocks stuff. Dragon egg?
Oh, fuck yeah. This thing hatches into a dragon in three minutes.
Fuck, I'm dead. This game is awesome. Shit.
Okay, this game is cool.
Okay, let's do it again. Let's do it again. This game is fun.
So, it's two hits. Move speed is essential.
It feels like it, yeah, because there's not really any reliable way to get away.
Are there upgrades in this game afterwards? Yes, there is.
Oh my God, I love this game.
The other one was good too, but this one feels...
Okay, here's the thing.
The difference between the last game and this one
is from the very beginning of that last one that we just played,
I felt just powerful. I was so powerful almost already.
I was just destroying everything. I just got my ass kicked.
I didn't even make it five minutes.
I like that better.
I like the game needs to really progress, progress, progress, progress
until you get to that point where it's just crazy.
It almost gives you an opportunity to learn the game better.
Alright, let's see. Reload rate, fire rate, yeah.
Wait, no, let me see everything else.
I think I like this one.
Vampire survivors get a lot more difficult as you progressed.
Yeah, I did. I shoot the tree.
Oh, all right.
Pick up range is always good. That's a good.
Oh, should I just do super reload, Andy?
I do appreciate you can see the ammo on the cursor.
That's huge.
I got to collect some shit here, otherwise I'm going to be in trouble.
All right, double shot sounds good with this.
Oh, move speed, but didn't you guys say this is important?
I probably should do it.
I'm already starting to slow down. Yeah, I'll do it.
That's definitely a huge increase.
Yeah, this is much better.
When are you going to unbox an Xbox One?
No, that's actually really funny.
I do an Xbox One unboxing video like the Halo edition with faster cheap on it.
Right. That would be actually pretty funny.
I'm into that. Wow.
Am I going am I going super fast right now?
Oh shit, I want it to be a lot of help.
Oh, is that I like the setup.
I like the build.
Oh, all right. I got to get some of that.
All right. Time to collect.
It's simple. Yeah, it is simple, but that's a good thing.
I think I'm doing double shot.
Yeah, a little damage, but I think that's fine.
All right. Let's really start to snowball here.
HP. Increase bullet damage and move speed by 10 percent every 10 seconds.
This resets when you get hit.
Oh my God. That's actually huge.
40 percent. I just don't get hit.
There we go. That's what I wanted.
Don't get greedy. I got greedy.
Your dragon gains 8 damage every 60 seconds.
This ability works even if your dragon is still in the egg.
Egg salad. Increase reload rate by 5 percent for every enemy killed.
That's okay. That's kind of cool.
That's kind of cool.
Should I just I think I'm going to go for the dragon.
It's going to stay alive.
Oh shit, I'm going to die.
I got to focus. No more talking.
What the fuck is that?
All right. Holy shield. Health.
I think I need this. I got one health.
Ooh. Enemies within your vision range take 25 damage every two seconds.
I got to stay alive though.
Re-halo pieces can now appear as upgrade choices.
Collect all three to recover Shauna's halo.
Okay. Is something else in there?
Oh my God.
Okay. That was... I died.
Shit. All right. That was fun.
Let's go. Get the upgrades of the main menu.
I'll do one more and then we'll go there.
Fuck. I really like this.
When did this come out?
A couple months ago?
Why did it take me so long to understand that it existed?
I got 20 in the recommended Discord channel.
20 play Freddy fish 3.
Oh no. No play this one?
I think we're going electro.
Let's try it. Every second shot.
That's awesome.
All right. Magic lens.
Quick hands.
Let's go with the health right off the bat.
This is the one. This is the run.
We're going to get to at least 15 minutes or 10 minutes.
I need some rapid fire though so the lightning happens more often.
Dumb ass.
All right. Give me something good.
Max HP plus 2. Character size plus 50%.
I don't know if I like that.
Ooh. Egg. No.
I want lightning.
Okay. When lightning strikes an enemy,
there's a 20% chance to automatically refill three ammo.
Let's do it.
I wonder how often that's going to happen.
Hasn't happened yet.
There we go. It's pretty good.
That's good, but I need reload speed.
Summon an electro bug that calls down lightning to strike two nearby enemies.
Rapid fire or electro bug? Let's do it.
That's good that it just passively does that.
Ooh. Power shot. Nice.
All lightning damage increased by 12.
Increased lightning area effect by 75%.
Yeah. Lightning build.
Let's do it.
Now I need rapid fire and more ammo.
Double shot.
Ooh. Yep.
Does that count as two?
It does, right?
Oh, it doesn't count as two.
I think it's that one.
Yeah. I need the movement speed.
Plus the fire rate.
Thank you.
Three halo pieces can now appear.
Take it.
Dude, what the fuck just happened?
That's got bounced around like crazy.
Bullet speed.
Fire rate. That's what I want.
Oh, yeah.
All right. As long as I don't act like a bonehead,
I should be fine here.
Ooh. Ooh.
Does this count?
It's not fun when Jerma is not being stupid.
Man, we're just sometimes just chilling, dude.
Dude, if you step on the gas and you go 100 miles per hour the whole time,
you're going to run out of gas and the car is going to break down.
You got your car.
You need to refuel sometimes.
Magnet's good.
Yeah. It's a good choice.
Yeah. You don't want the car to run out of gas.
How many times have you said gas today?
At least 10.
All right. I want that.
Or what is the is the vision rain this big circle around me?
Were you ever come to Pittsburgh?
Dude, I was there yesterday.
I was there yesterday.
I got a fucking steak of cheese.
I got a Philly cheesesteak.
You missed me by like four hours.
Wrong city.
Well, you don't think that they have cheap like famous cheese steaks
in any other cities in that state?
Well, you think it's only exclusive to Philly?
They do, but they suck.
What?
Are we this one?
You called it a Philly cheesesteak.
If I order a New York style pizza,
the person behind the counter is not going to go.
Hey, you know, this is Buffalo.
Oh, no, no, no. Sorry.
Hey, you know, you know, you're in Cincinnati, dude.
If it's in New York style pizza,
New York City style pizza.
You're an idiot.
You don't even know what city you're in.
I just fucking lost because of that.
Oh, my eye.
That was such a good run too.
Man that person for seven days.
Philly cheese rant.
Yeah, if you make a Philly cheese, dude,
you can't just be like, oh, hey.
Oh, hey, grandpa.
How are you?
I'm doing very good.
Oh, man.
Hey, are you going to make me your famous Philly cheesesteak?
Yes, I'm going to make you a Philly cheesesteak.
I know how to make it really good.
Did you even grow up in Philadelphia?
No, I didn't.
I just know how to make them really good.
And I have family there.
Did you grow up in Philly?
No, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Is it Otto?
No, it's not.
Cheese steak gatekeeping.
All right, I want to do something cool like this.
I got a famous salmon I'd like to make.
I got a famous egg salad I want to make for you.
What was even your eggs?
I'm sorry.
All right, I'm going to pay attention.
Remember, that's disgusting.
Well, that's kind of something.
Ooh, I like that.
But this synergizes better.
All right, more, more, more.
Should I go for the egg?
All right, I'm actually going to go for the egg
and not be a moron.
We're good?
All right, I think I can comfortably.
Yeah, that one.
Whoa, tree.
Damage 35%.
Yep, we're going straight up.
Just bullet damage.
Bullet bounce?
All right, I got to think about going somewhere else.
So it will bounce off of people.
Hey, I've been performing some rituals on you
and just wanted to know if you still had 10 toes.
Yes, I do.
Please do a ritual where I have a healthy life and shit.
Come on, do some rituals where I learn
how to figure your skate or ice skate or something.
Something interesting.
Let me do something cool.
Stop removing toes and shit.
Stop.
Next time you're at the altar or whatever it is,
just be like, you know what?
Let's make something cool.
Let's do something.
Maybe he eats a really good piece of pizza tomorrow or something.
Come on.
Enough of this bullshit.
Enough of the bullshit.
Don't go over there.
Gun mastery.
Wait, did I just?
All right, yeah.
That sounds pretty amazing.
This is actually the run, so I'm not going to blow it.
Quick learner.
Increase experience gain by 40%.
Yep.
OK, that's where.
All right.
Really?
Oh, the dragon's coming out soon, right?
That experience thing is insane.
Reload rate, 5%.
Bullet damage by 50% for one second after reloading.
Reload rate by 5% for every enemy killed.
This resets after reloading.
No, we'll do this one.
Yeah.
Yep.
OK.
Dragon.
Bullet speed.
Ghost friend.
Dragon bond.
This one.
Dragon does more damage, even when he's in the egg.
Did he actually kill the trees, or is that just a waste of time?
Jesus.
Whoa.
OK, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Damage 45% and huge size.
Yes.
Fuck.
All right, this is getting hard.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Choose an upgrade.
Bullet damage minus 50%.
But burn, lightning, and freeze duration by 30%.
I don't have any of that.
Summon damage by 50%.
Summon attack speed, but my reload rate is awful.
Forward bullet damage, bullet su-
Yeah, it's got to be this one, right?
Max HP.
Is that going to kill me?
This one will kill me?
I think that was the right call.
This is ridiculous.
Is the area getting smaller?
I'm not getting fortnighted, am I?
Definitely this one.
What is causing that?
Can I stop it?
I'm really glad their enemy projectiles are red.
Movement speed.
Uh, I don't know.
Probably this one.
Just more, more piercing with damage.
Oh, that was close.
No.
I think I need to take it.
I do.
I got so much shit over there to go pick up.
Let's run them over here.
All right, pick up.
Enemies explode into three bullets when killed.
Huge.
That's good too, though.
I'm going to do this.
They explode when killed and does 10% damage.
Holy shit, that's unbelievable.
All right, just don't blow it.
There's so many bullets everywhere.
So I got a question.
Does this include...
Way too dank?
Uh, does that count for the little bullets that are coming out from the explosion?
It does?
Okay, that sounds kind of crazy.
Uh, yeah.
Jesus.
When shooting your last ammo, also shoot 10 bullets in a circle.
Oh, hell yeah.
Oh my god.
Okay.
This one's probably good too, now.
Yeah, 25 damage.
All enemies within your vision range take 25 damage every two seconds.
Or take the shield.
That's probably a good idea.
All right.
It's getting kind of crazy here.
Bullet speed plus 30%.
I'm going to do the moving speed.
I feel like I need it.
So many experience gems everywhere.
Pick up range.
Bullet speed.
Increase reload rate and move speed by 25% while Holy Shield is active.
Um, yeah.
Wow.
All right, this is definitely the one.
Feels like I get killed by a boss or something.
On every fifth shot, launch a fireball that deals 40 damage.
Burn as well.
I think I'm going to do maybe speed.
All right, I'll do the fire.
Yeah, this one.
All right, that's a new enemy.
Shit.
Oh, but it's so bad.
I think it's this one.
Why is it happening twice?
That shouldn't be happening twice.
Am I just getting really lucky or something?
Oh, yes.
Let's go.
Walk speed.
Uh, ghost friend.
Pick up range.
Go.
All right, I'll do ghost friend.
All right.
Whatever that is, I got to be careful.
My ears are itching.
Ah, all right.
What is it?
Triple the effect of the next upgrade you take.
Oh my God.
All right.
What is it?
I mean, wait.
That'll, I'll die.
Minus three that I'll, it'll kill me.
300% walk speed though.
That would be crazy.
That's your speed while shooting.
I mean, that's still amazing.
I could reroll it.
Should I try to reroll it?
So this will shoot three bullets behind me.
Wait.
So hold on a minute.
This will shoot three bullets behind me every time I click.
It sucks.
I'm doing it.
How come it's not shooting three?
Didn't say it triples the effect.
Oh, I got scammed.
Oh, well, I got seven minutes.
I'm fine.
It's three stacked together.
Is it?
I think it actually might be.
Yeah, no, it is.
It is.
It definitely is.
See what it's doing.
Yeah, it is three.
No, we didn't get scammed.
We're good.
Yeah, it's definitely three.
Maybe it's time for lightning.
I'm shooting a lot of bullets.
Okay, so but is that really that good?
So max HP, it'll take away one of the empty ones.
So that's just a free plus 10 more damage.
Okay, I'm doing it.
I can already tell the difference.
Worth it.
Five minutes.
We're almost there.
Is that zero?
Reload rate, bullet damage crazy, but max ammo.
Wouldn't that make my max ammo zero?
I would have one ammo.
No, no way.
You will spin so much though.
I go for it.
All right.
I'm going to go for it.
Turns out it was worth it.
Oh shit.
I just got hit by what?
Actually not great for right now because I can't aim.
I would love to aim at these guys.
Shit.
I was so close.
I think that kind of screwed me because I couldn't aim at.
I couldn't aim at the individual people shooting the eyeball.
The bullets.
Damn it.
It's all right.
Wait, is this stuff shotgun?
Oh, this is awesome.
Really?
There's so much to do.
I'm going to turn this down.
Okay.
Um, who should I unlock?
On every third shot throw out a wave of fire that burns enemies.
That's kind of cool.
Starts with more HP.
Right click to summon a shadow clone.
Starts with lightning.
That's pretty good.
Right click to quickly shoot all of your remaining ammo in random directions.
That's kind of cool too.
Is there more?
There's more.
All right.
I'm going to.
We're going to we're going to save our money for a second here.
Let's do the one.
All right.
More HP.
Let's do this one.
And shotgun.
I love shotguns.
I like that crossbow.
That's kind of cool.
Ooh, I like that too.
All right.
I'm going to go with shotgun.
Wait a minute.
Oh sword or shield.
Do I have to go in order?
Oh, okay.
Rank one.
I think I'm going to go with this pickup range is huge.
That's 3 6 9 12.
All right.
That's 15% pickup range.
I think I'm cool with that bullet damage and summon damage.
I mean just do more damage, right?
I think this this is the one to do.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go for it.
I got the shotgun.
I got a diamond.
All right.
This is the one.
You didn't have to stop aiming.
Well, the problem is I only had one shot.
And if I...
What do bullets do I have?
Okay.
A fire rate bullet damage.
I'm going to do damage and knock back with the shotgun.
That seems like a good idea.
Face is itchy.
Stop.
I kind of want this.
Enemies in your vision take 25 damage every two seconds.
Now the vision is what circle?
Oh, it's the little circle.
Okay.
I'm not happy about that, but whatever.
That's okay.
I thought it was the big circle.
I mean, it's a shotgun.
So might as well.
Actually, the vision thing is actually doing pretty good.
This is a little bit more.
It's more damage than the shotgun is doing.
Rapid fire shotgun.
All right.
What should I get for food today?
What do you guys think?
Somebody said Taco Bell.
They were going to get it, but I kind of screwed that up for them.
Oh, yeah.
Double shotgun blast.
Is it actually firing double?
I can't tell.
Is it?
It's just plus one.
Oh, it's the fifth projectile.
Okay.
Movement speed.
Good to get it early.
Vision range plus 15.
The damage from glare also applies the on-hit effects on your bullets.
Oh, okay.
So I have to get burn or freeze or something, right?
Oh, come on, dude.
Stop.
What am I doing?
I'm blowing it.
What do you got?
Raise bullet damage and bullet size by 15% permanently every time you heal.
Whoa.
I'm about to get hit.
So I have to start healing.
How do you heal though?
Reliably.
All I see is max HP.
I haven't seen heal HP yet.
Is it my doing something wrong?
Not healing somehow.
Fire path heals.
Fire and HP.
HP plus.
Okay.
Twice as much glare.
I'll do freeze because I need it.
Because glare will inflict freeze, right?
Very helpful.
This one?
You can get a healing fruit if you kill a tree.
Oh.
Good to know.
Does the eye have to be open for it to take damage?
Jeez.
Only talks to us when he needs us.
Well, I'm focusing.
I have to pay attention.
Probably going to do this.
Or should I do ghost?
Stop.
The freeze made me run into you.
Shit.
All right.
I'm losing it here.
Okay, there we go.
I mean, that's probably the one to do.
Yeah.
Reload rate.
Max ammo is big.
I can shoot three times, right?
Yep.
Oh my god.
I'm absolutely blowing it.
I'm moving so fast.
The movement speed made me run it.
I don't know if I want the movement speed.
It's too fast.
I wasn't prepared for it.
I just ran into that person twice.
All right.
I'll pull it together.
Die.
Have to take a healing thing?
I know.
It's this one.
I got to kill one of these trees.
I thought he was dead.
That was almost death.
This one?
I think so.
Trees have so much health.
Should I not even be trying?
I'm definitely in trouble though.
I'm not doing enough damage.
All right.
Give me a level.
Health?
Shield?
Probably.
I mean, it's got to be.
It has to be the shield because if I take a hit or curse,
that's just crit.
I'll do it.
I'm in so much trouble though.
Oh, glare and curse work together really well.
All right.
I see what you mean.
I have to take it.
I have to.
Because don't I get a bonus for that?
Just try to level up glare the whole way.
It's the only thing that's keeping me alive.
I think I'm going to get overwhelmed when it's all these sucker
things.
That's back.
I don't like any of these.
I don't like any of these but splinter is probably the best one.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
Oh, shit.
This thing.
I need a level.
Come on.
Shoot.
Dead.
There's nothing I could do.
I was so screwed.
I just couldn't kill anything.
Shit.
All right.
I'm going to do that one.
One more.
Character is good.
I'm going to try this.
I'm going to try the crossbow.
All the damage.
That counts as a crossbow, right?
All right.
Let's go again.
I feel like I'm going to like this.
You hold it.
You charge it.
This thing does a lot of damage.
Here's to everybody too.
I like it a lot actually.
We just need a ton of damage.
Why do his eyes look like that?
Like what?
Okay.
So technically it's one shot.
So this would be awesome, right?
Smite everybody after shooting your last shot.
I have one shot.
So yes, exactly precisely what I thought.
This is this is my weapon.
Okay.
That's cool.
I think I'm going with magnetism early.
Make sure I don't have to worry about it later.
You can hold it for a long time.
Wow.
All right.
I didn't know that.
You can probably chew through in a whole line of enemies like that.
All right.
Yes.
Double shot.
Oh fuck.
Yeah, that's disgusting.
That is disgusting.
Okay, a shot behind me too.
I think so.
Who said this sucks?
I don't know if I agree with you.
Dark Arts.
That could be good.
Whoa.
Yep.
This is one shot.
Although it's only doing two damage though.
That's kind of bad.
It doesn't scale with the charge.
Unfortunately, 100% that.
Yeah.
Reload rate is absolutely key here.
Ghost friend.
More reload.
Max ammo.
Wait a minute.
That's probably not a good idea.
Or is it a good idea?
Don't tell him.
Don't tell me what.
Take the lens.
Give all bullets to pass through 30% damage in size.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, I see.
One of these things.
I didn't know he's right next to me.
All right.
What is this one going to be?
Bullet damage and bullet size by permanently every time you heal.
All right.
I got to pick up that other thing then.
Where's that?
Where is it?
Two bounce.
Do the fire.
Pyro Mage.
Not bounce.
Pyro.
Or at least I can kill shit this time.
I was having a lot of trouble killing anything last time.
Bullets that pass through your magic lens will inflict burn.
Pick up range.
Vision range.
I mean, that's probably a good one to take.
Kill a tree.
Tree, tree, tree, tree.
What do you mean tree?
What happened?
Get the freeze so you can kill a tree.
That's three arrows.
Less damage.
But that seems kind of amazing.
It is.
It's plus four projectiles.
Get out of the way.
Dude.
Get out of the fucking way.
Why am I so slow?
This one's big.
This is big.
I got to be very careful.
Please be careful.
This is massive.
That's a massive deal.
Yes.
I need the heals.
Sorry.
I'm quiet Andy right now.
But I got to get to the end.
As much damage as your bullets.
Probably this, right?
Reload rate.
That's fire, right?
Do the dagger.
All right, we'll do the magic dagger.
I have to remember that that's my projectile.
I will confuse it.
I went around the tree.
I'm pissed.
I think it's this one.
Oh, that's huge.
That's monstrous.
That is monstrous.
Monstrous.
I just take the health.
So there's just 20.
Just take the extra health.
I'm taking it.
So I'm going to magic scythe.
Bullet speed.
Shield.
Yeah.
Bullet damage and fire rate when you get hit.
That one's pretty good.
I think this one's good.
10 extra damage.
30 extra damage.
Yep.
Let's go.
Oh my God.
Reload rate and speed.
Reload rate.
Am I at the cap?
Holy shit.
Bullet damage and knockback.
Yep.
How come I haven't healed yet?
Don't I have something that heals every time somebody dies by something?
Curse 2 would be insane.
Summon damage.
That's it's definitely curse.
How come you don't blink?
I haven't.
I like I have.
I'm doing curse.
Holy shit.
I probably I don't think I have blinked.
Oh my God.
You're right.
Hold on.
Give me a second.
Jesus.
I just like made my I just made it worse.
We got fire rate and reload rate by 10% permanently every time you get hit.
Okay, that's okay.
I guess this is such a great build.
I can't lose it now.
You got to play smart.
Oh, I don't like that.
That's I mean doubled though better shield.
I think that's the that's the safe play.
Not the cool play, but it's a safe one.
Burn.
See you later.
What do we got?
Speed.
Fire rate.
Spread.
Max ammo.
Summon damage.
It's just speed.
Be careful speed damage.
So yeah, hell yeah.
I just want to kill it.
I need to know what it is.
My God.
This thing's still alive.
Yes, when diamonds HP is at or below half of Max HP piercing plus to a knockback.
Oh, well, look at all these goodies over here.
Zero point five percent chance.
Okay, two minutes.
I feel like it's going to get crazy here in a second.
When Holy Shield is not active kills with smite lower the regeneration time for Holy
Shield by one second.
Damn.
All right.
That's amazing.
Try to get to level 30, right?
Probably important.
Oh, yeah.
This is this over 40 seconds.
Nice 30 seconds.
Not level 30, but it's all right.
Yeah, great.
10,000 currency.
Nice.
Very cool.
All right.
Let's do one more.
Just joke one, right?
Let's do one more crazy one.
What do I want to unlock?
Maybe the flamethrower.
Okay, I'm going to do flamethrower and the flame character darkness one small survive
the night to unlock greater challenges small enemy spawn more often.
I'll just do regular fun to watch.
It's kind of like Binding of Isaac.
Oh my goodness.
That's fast.
Well, this is a great character.
It's a joke character.
But I mean when I'm in joke character, I meant joke weapons.
This is not a joke character.
Go darkness one to progress.
That's all right.
I restart.
I wasn't looking at the best kind of the whole game.
Oh, you're betting.
Sorry.
Well, we refund it.
Refund it.
You ruin the bets.
It's all right.
I just we can refund.
It'll work.
The SMG is OP too.
Oh wait, I can do another rune.
All right here.
Now you're betting on this one.
Okay, same deal.
And I will do darkness one.
You turned off the rune.
Wait, don't bet yet.
Wait, hold on.
Did I turn off a rune?
Oh shit.
Hold on.
I unequipped the rune.
Oh, okay.
Well, we're going to restart.
You can only pick one for tree.
Oh, okay.
I didn't know that.
I get it.
All right.
So this is 10% damage and summon damage.
Okay, 10% damage.
10% damage.
All right.
Now you're for real betting on this right now.
I mean you guys it doesn't really matter.
You're going to bet anyways.
Do you think I'm going to win or not?
Like it's not like we have to redo it all.
It's not we don't have to redo it.
You guys are going to bet anyways.
Yeah, it's equipped.
Okay.
Here we go.
Darkness one.
Rune is equipped.
20 minutes.
Let's go for it.
This weapon's fun.
Oops.
Oh, I was too busy.
It's all right.
They haven't even bet yet.
All right.
I'm thinking fire rate, spread, and reload rate.
Fire rate right here.
Bingo.
Oh my god.
I'm so sorry everybody that's going to lose.
I'm not used to being this slow.
Everything's fine.
I think it's just fun.
But burn.
It's the burn character.
Fire rate.
I need reload rate.
Bad.
Reload rate.
There it is.
Oh, double.
I need the reload rate.
Bad.
Don't worry believers.
I got your back.
Oh, ah.
Don't worry believers.
I'm not giving in.
Drastic.
It was drastic, but it should work out.
All right, what do we got?
I got three health.
I'm good.
Burn damage plus 67%.
Oh my goodness.
Hey, believers.
I got you back.
I almost walked into somebody, I think.
Why did I narrate that part?
Like, I got you back.
I almost just walked into somebody.
Like, yeah, no shit.
You fucking idiot.
Who are you talking about?
Of course you.
Oh.
I'm sorry believers.
I couldn't help it.
I was just too slow.
This thing's so fast.
I'll win it back.
I'll get it back.
Just bet on me right now.
Bet on me right now.
I'll get it back right now.
You lost.
I know, but bet on me right now.
Bet on me right now.
Bet right now.
I'm telling you right now to bet on me.
I am saying bet on me right fucking now.
I'm going to go all 20 minutes.
Bet on me.
I'm telling you do it.
Do it.
Check this out.
I'm telling you bet on me right now.
I'm not fucking around.
Not anymore.
Double shot.
It just got real right now.
Imagine being a non-believer right now
after seeing what I just picked up.
You're believing?
Good.
You should.
I'm not going to be communicating that much with you.
I'm trying to win you channel points.
Mitigation is going to cease as of right now.
That's burn effect.
Glare puts on burn effect.
Can you imagine spending money against me after what you...
Really?
I mean, if you bet against me at this point,
I mean, you got like a...
Your hands are kind of full of fucking air.
A lot of crunchies over here.
Dude, if I win this, I deserve.
I deserve McDonald's tonight if I win.
I'm just being really, really honest.
I deserve five Happy Meals.
Welcome to McDonald's.
How can I help you?
Yeah, I'd like to get five Happy Meals, please.
I don't have any kids.
Should I say that?
Oh, yeah.
I don't have any kids there for me.
Okay, I don't care, but all around.
It's illegal to buy a Happy Meal if you don't have any kids.
Shut up.
Not you.
If you lose, you have to get one of the gyros from Arby's.
World's grossest fast food item.
That's not part of the deal.
That could be the world's grossest fast food item.
A gyro, gyro.
There's a, I don't know.
You know what I mean?
That's my favorite comment of the whole night.
Okay, if I...
No, that's gross.
I don't want to do that.
Gyro, gyro, gyro.
It's gyro.
Stop.
What do I pick?
Do I just leave?
I don't think any of these work.
Power, but bullets is not, it's not gonna help.
Can the fire bounce?
I feel like that sucks.
I think I'm just gonna leave.
I don't like any of these.
Not for what I have right now.
Bullet bounce plus two, but can the fire even bounce off anything?
This would be the one that I'd pick, but I don't really know if I want this.
Bullets, I mean, maybe this is all right.
Bouncy fire.
I'm just leaving.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no, no, no.
That doesn't count.
That actually doesn't count.
I pressed D instead of S.
That, I would have to do it again because I pressed,
I thought I was pressing S, but I was pressing D instead.
I took too long on that dumbass screen.
So I pressed D.
I was trying to hold S.
Whatever, just bet on me again.
I promise.
All right.
This is the real one.
If I lose, I have to get a fucking gyro from Arby's.
And if I win, then I get my McDonald's Happy Meals.
This is the real one.
This is my bet.
This one's for real.
This one's for me.
You have to eat it live on stream.
No, I will take a picture of it.
I will take a picture of at least two bites out of it.
You know what's crazy?
I don't want to eat fucking Arby's.
I don't want that at all.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
I'm gonna be silent now.
I don't want to eat an Arby's gyro.
I don't want that.
That sounds awful to me right now.
That's the last thing I want.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
I'm actually putting both headphones in for this.
And I'm shutting up.
I'm not going to talk the rest of the time I'm playing.
Pyro does not sound like a good idea, though.
Because why would I get pyro?
My bullets already inflict burn.
Why would I do pyro?
It stacks?
Okay, I didn't know that.
That's not good.
It's dead?
Oh shit, I killed it.
Yes.
Oh my goodness.
Sick super fast rate.
Triple base max ammo.
I get to have McDonald's today.
All right, let's go.
I need burn damage, burn damage, burn damage, burn damage.
I see burn damage up.
I need it.
Shit.
I don't know.
It's probably Galeria.
I need lightning too.
The lightning is going to be...
The lightning is doing so much work here, more than the fire.
I need lightning damage increase.
That's pretty good.
That's pretty good too.
I'll go with ice.
They're closing in.
I'm surrounded.
Shoot someone!
Dark arts.
Arby's, we have the meat.
Frostbite.
Jesus, it's that.
Or it's curse.
It's curse.
Oh, it's that one.
Why are there so many things?
Oh, it's because I did that hard mode.
It's that.
Or I need more reload.
Bad.
That's a dire.
When you inflict freeze, also inflict burn.
Whoa.
Let's go.
The new Arby's disgusting chicken sandwich.
I feel bad.
Okay, I feel kind of bad.
Because like I think Arby's is a fucking awful place.
But I mean, is it all right?
I don't know.
Does that like mean what I'm saying?
Oh shit.
Oh no.
I don't want to go to Arby's.
Why am I reloading?
I have auto reload on.
Every 10 enemies killed by curse will increase your bullet damage by 1% permanently.
This one.
Shit, I bumped somebody.
I didn't even see them.
I'm okay.
Where's the boss?
Where's the boss die?
It's probably this.
Watch out for the tree.
Oh my God, that's so good.
Come on.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I think so.
Glare?
I think it's glare.
Glare.
Let's go.
Oh, holy shit.
10% fire rate every time she inflicts burn.
Oh, knock back.
Knock back.
I don't have to eat at Arby's.
Well, hold on.
Don't get cocky.
I could die really quickly here.
Fire rate, bullet damage, reload rate, ammo, piercing.
Yep.
That's over.
It's literally over.
It's over.
I killed the tree.
This is just absolutely stupid what's going on right now.
Look at how fast this is.
Look at this fire rate.
The game is broken.
This whole bet is so stupid.
Might hit level 40.
I might.
38.
Wait, I'll do this.
Stand still.
Firework.
Holy shit, don't be stupid.
I don't think I'm not going to hit 40, but still cool.
I did it.
Sorry, Arby's fans.
Not tonight.
Eating an Arby's gyro.
That's such a huge punishment.
I like, wouldn't you feel bad if you were Arby's?
No, I don't want to lose a bet and eat an Arby's gyro.
Double or nothing?
What, I have to eat two Arby's gyros or no?
There's no double or nothing.
That's it.
Your eyes are deep fried.
They are?
I think they're okay.
Maybe not.
Maybe they're a little weird.
It was worth it.
And that's where I'm going to end the stream.
I think that's a solid place to go out on.
I will buy some stuff though.
This game is absolutely fantastic.
What a great game this is.
This is really good.
Very good.
I got to say, this is wonderful.
This is a great game.
Dual S.
All right, I just want to test these.
I like this.
Start the game with your HP at half of your max HP.
Bullet damage and fire rate by 5% per rank.
I kind of feel kind of bad.
I'm going to unlock all the weapons.
Bat gun, grenade launcher, magic bow.
All right, I just want to try the SMGs.
That's kind of cool.
All right, I'm going to try spark.
With the dual SMGs.
I just want to try.
I'm just going to try.
I'm going to play for 10 seconds.
Yeah, it's pretty damn good.
This is great.
OK, cool.
What a great game.
Synergies.
Oh, that was helpful.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
I'll see you guys on Wednesday.
Wednesday, we're going to play Sorcery Part 3.
Going back to it should be a nice, chill stream.
Thanks for watching today.
The games were fun.
Had a good time, as always.
And I'll see you guys on Wednesday.
And then again, I'll be on Name Your Price on Austin Show's
Name Your Price this Thursday.
I think I earned a Happy Meal.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks for the support.
Take care of yourselves.
Hopefully we see you soon.
This has to be five Happy Meals.
If I had lost that round, I would have been like,
all right, see you guys later.
Yeah, I'll tweet out the Arby's.
I would have turned the stream off.
I would have went and talked to Holly.
I would have closed the door and been like,
how do we fake me eating Arby's because I really don't want it?
But I would have to prove it.
I would have to have to take a bite on camera and prove it to you, right?
Oh, God.
Somebody got a McDonald's ad.
Really?
Well, you're making it sound so much worse than it is.
I know it's not that bad,
but I actually genuinely don't like Arby's at all.
It is probably one of my least favorite fast food places.
Have you ever eaten it?
Yes, I've had it twice and both times I said,
I do not really like this.
You're making it sound like you're forced to eat prison slop.
The new Arby's prison slop sandwich full of meat,
cheese, and onions.
Authentic to the real thing.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
See you guys Wednesday.
Starting at, let's see, what time should I start on Wednesday?
We're probably going to start early on Wednesday.
Probably like somewhere between 12 and 1.
We'll probably start somewhere around 12 31 on Wednesday.
Pacific.
Good night, though.
We'll see you soon.
Take it easy.
Goodbye.
Yeah.
Yes.
Call your mother, of course.
It's implied.
See you later.