And I'm gonna be showing you guys some of my favorite things.
So, let's get started.
Hello! What's up? How are you? That was pretty cool. That's the first time I've seen that.
Yeah, it was fun, right? Vinnie put that together for us.
I haven't seen any of these. So, I've seen, like, a few.
But, hi guys, welcome.
That was awesome.
My, like, heart is like...
Oh, it's beating out of my chest!
That was unbelievable.
First time I've seen that.
Introduce yourselves. These are two very important people.
Yeah, so, I'm Jake.
I'm the owner of JK Productions.
And Community Jake, as you may know me.
Jeremy's manager.
And, yeah.
I put together this show.
Jeremy's incredible idea.
And I have Alex here, my right-hand man, who was in charge of all the tech.
So, if you want to say hi.
Hi, my name's Alex. Yeah, I was the director for the dollhouse.
So, any of the technology that wasn't from the extension was something that my group was working on.
And that we'll talk about tonight.
Also, these two guys were responsible for more than just this.
Archaeology. Thank these two.
Bugleberry's hot tub. These guys.
Even before that, the Halloween stream. These guys.
So, they've been around for a long time.
And, of course, the carnival.
Oh, yeah, absolutely. The carnival. I can't, how did I forget that?
But, they've been...
These are the people behind the shit that you see.
So, they're in the flesh here.
Yeah, and I'm really excited tonight.
We're segmenting the show into three parts.
So, the first part of the show is about the pre-production of Dollhouse.
Sort of how it came to be.
And then, the second part of the show is about what the Dollhouse production was like.
So, while it was happening.
What was it like sort of behind the scenes.
And then, the third part of the show is with our talent.
Where we talk about the content and how we came up with things.
Like, different segments on the show.
And how a lot of it, most of it, sort of happened on the fly.
Like, as chat made their decisions and that sort of thing.
And how we, you know, developed our beats and all that sort of stuff.
So, I'm pretty excited. We have a ton.
We have way more footage than we could possibly show.
There's a lot of clips.
There's like hundreds.
We've cut down well over 100 hours of footage.
Down to, I don't know, maybe 90 minutes or so.
And we're probably not even going to get to show all of it tonight.
We don't usually get to talk about this side too.
So, this will be for people to see.
Also, on the second channel.
The second channel is going to be like a cut down documentary, essentially, right?
Yeah, so we're doing the...
Even if you don't see it today, you'll see some of it later.
Yeah, we're doing the normal second drama cuts of each episode.
And then we'll be doing a behind the scenes cut too.
That's like the super cut of all of this stuff together.
So, even if there's stuff we don't get to show today, hopefully it'll show up there.
Release the cut. Release the cut.
No, not yet. Not until I get my hands on it.
It'll be six hours.
With us today, in the first part of the show here, we have Nick Lawrence from Andy Mark.
I want that to happen.
We've got Nick Lawrence from Andy Mark. If you want to say hi, Nick.
Hey, everybody. My name is Nick Lawrence.
I usually work for Andy Mark as a mechanical engineering person,
but also in a small group of people that get to do really fun, super special projects like the dollhouse.
And it was a total blast. One of the coolest things I've ever, ever, ever worked on.
Yeah, and also carnival stuff too.
So, all the robots, that's these guys. They did that too.
So, they were responsible for so much stuff.
And I cannot say, I can say it a million times, but you guys are worth going to a million times over.
I would rather use the Andy Mark people over like the highest quality studio in Los Angeles.
A hundred times.
That's really, really kind.
There's no way we'd be able to find.
I just want to say in front of everybody that we super appreciate the opportunity, and we had a blast doing it for sure.
We look forward to more.
Yeah, oh yeah. There will be plenty more. That's for sure.
So, I think to start us off.
There's a cat.
Oh yeah, there's a cat. Cat sliding down.
Simon's planning a place. That's it for the stream.
I think to start off this section, I'm going to show a few renders, photos real quick.
And then we're going to jump into a tour that I gave to our BTS op, Vinny.
And we can kind of skip through that and see what it was like on set there.
But to get us started, this was like a super early render of what the space looked like in the mind of the engineers over at Andy Mark.
And as you can see, we had this idea about we want this dollhouse to be two floors.
We want there to be, it needs to be more than just a bunch of sets.
And we talked about having disconnected sets, where it's like, okay, well, we can pretend that they're upstairs.
We can use some camera magic to superimpose them upstairs or whatever.
And at least I was pretty consistent that it needed to be a house.
It needed to be a two-story house for us to have the effect that we wanted it to have.
And so as much as it annoyed everyone, I think, to be insistent on that, this is sort of what we came up with.
And so looking at it, these are some renders that we had of inside the warehouse, because the roof in the warehouse isn't really that tall.
And so we had some issues with how high the truss can be and where the lights needed to be and all that sort of thing.
You could see, like in overhead here, we have the upper rooms and the forward rooms are actually set back.
The upper rooms are set back, which is why when you see that full house view, the upper rooms look smaller because they're 20 feet back from those lower rooms.
But it really is necessary in order to shoot that way.
And to light the space, right, to be able to light something without having a floor on top of it.
And you're talking about a building where at some points in this building, the roof is only 23 or 24 feet and the set itself is 18 feet.
So there was a lot of kind of camera tricks and light tricks to make the items look correct.
And to have the forced perspective for the walls.
You really need to feel like you can see what's on a wall, right?
You can't build a 90 degree wall or you wouldn't be able to tell what you were placing.
They're like this, right? Like that?
Yeah.
Essentially, they're like right up.
Yeah, that was definitely.
Originally, I was going to go out the top floor window.
That was the first idea was, oh, I want to go out the second floor window, not the bottom floor.
That was the plan.
How the fuck are we going to have you go out of the second floor window?
I was like, I don't know, figure it out.
And then I like walked out of the room.
Yeah, Nick, if you want to say anything about those forced perspective rooms, because that idea was the genius, I think, behind how we were able to shoot this.
And that totally came from your group.
Yeah, definitely.
There's a lot of people.
I mean, I'm just one of the team.
I mean, Liz and Ren and Brett, really the other corporate owner team that all have a lot of artsy theater perspective.
And they really kind of drove the shapes of the rooms from our end.
And they were like, yeah, like every set ever.
They got the rooms open so you can see the stuff on the walls, which makes it so much easier to shoot and see like, you know, grandma spoons on the walls.
You can actually see them instead of having to like bring cameras way around and see the detailing of the doors opening and the window openings all of them.
Yeah, it's funny that like when the project was pitched to us, we were like, you want two stories, right?
OK, so we're going to fake this, right?
And you're like, no, it's got to be two stories.
OK, so it's two stories we got.
Yeah, you can actually see the real life one here.
The walls on the kitchen room and the bathroom room were kind of tapered together here.
Now you can see the walls kind of tapering open, which is pretty neat.
One of the things we had to be super careful of, you can see in this, is the tops of all the alleyways are just fabric.
They just needed to be black and we had to be super careful like to remind people to not step on them because it wasn't like it wasn't a flooring.
So it definitely caught me up a little bit while I was doing painting.
Yeah, I almost fell and died actually once during the setup of the show.
One of the things that we super had to care about was safety, right?
And we way, way, way overbuilt that upper level because, you know, when we were planning the show at one point, we thought that there might be as many as like 15, 20, even 30 people in one room.
Plus, Jack could have placed all the furniture in one room.
So we had to deal with like thousands of pounds of payload and make sure it was safe.
Right. So it's like all the structure underneath is like way, way, way overbuilt for your average house.
Yeah, let's let's get the tour video started. We could pause it along the way to point out some of that stuff, I think.
Yeah, that sounds like a good idea.
Yeah, so this is the set and it's a yard.
We consider the yard to be a room because it's a place where Jack can put things and, you know, it's on camera.
People can interact there and stuff.
But on day one, we just have rooms four and five.
They're number one, two, three, four, five, six.
So rooms four and five are the yellow rooms.
I think this is probably five or six days before air reference time.
The yellow room will be, on day one, the entire living space.
When did you guys finish it?
Like, when was it ready to go? How far before the stream?
What time did the stream start?
Three o'clock on Wednesday.
I mean, when I walked in, I was like, holy shit, this is ready.
And I think that you had just barely finished.
People don't realize that all this was potentially finished not even a week before the stream started.
Yeah, one week before the stream started is the day that we got the delivery of our tech rental.
So all that truss work and lighting and stuff that you see was one week before stream.
And so actually, I think six days before stream.
So all of the tech got built and then all the finishing.
I mean, you'll see in this tour, the state of the rooms, this is still probably three days before air.
And then when we're there, the colors of the doors and all that will be, I guess.
So Chad will have a little bit of a challenge trying to figure out how to make it work.
Room five here is the bathroom.
And the bathroom is smaller than every other room in the house, but it's still quite large for a bathroom,
which Chad seemed to notice on the Sims 3 stream that we did earlier this month.
So yeah, we've got like a shower, a toilet, a little vanity and stuff.
But there's so much room in here that on that first day,
we wouldn't be surprised to see a bed in here or some other furniture in here
because there's not a ton of room in that other room.
And we think that's kind of funny.
Over here, room six, this is probably a bedroom.
I think we're calling it a bedroom in the software.
But again, you know, Chad can kind of do what they want.
Now the yellow room becomes...
I don't know if you go, I haven't seen this video yet.
So I don't know if you go into further detail,
but you can see one of the monitors that's behind the window to make the background there.
Do you show that a little later in this video?
Yeah, I think we see the back of them a little bit later.
But yeah, there were in total, I think we bought over 20 TVs
between the small ones and the big ones to make this set of reality.
So I think that the windows, the TVs in the windows,
was just an amazing effect that it was such a small touch.
I was hoping people caught it.
It brought it all together, yeah.
The rain, the fire, the day, night.
Someone sitting there controlling the weather
to make it correspond with the graphic of the house
and what's going on with the day-night cycle, right?
So it's one of those details that...
I'll skip forward a little bit here.
We're talking about these windows.
And there's also that window in the front.
So if we go and take a look at that window.
And so this is where the burglar is going to come through.
But because all these walls are double walls
in order to create the forced perspective,
it's a little awkward because the burglar is going to have to...
Now you see how hard it was to climb through that.
...step inside here.
And then have to climb out the other, yeah.
Exactly.
But I think it's also kind of funny.
I'm not bothered by it.
I think it's going to be...
That'll work.
And then on day three, we add rooms one and two.
Room one becomes the bedroom,
which is that kind of maroon room up there.
And room six, which was that blue room,
now becomes the living room.
So this is really just the kitchen.
And then the room two is that unfinished room up there
with that closet wall in the back.
And so the storyline goes that at the end of day two,
the house burns down,
and Jeremy collects the insurance money for it,
and he gets to buy a bigger house.
So he buys this bigger house,
but it has this room that was never finished.
And so he wants to finish the room,
to turn it into an office or something like that.
And so he goes up there and cleans all the junk out of it,
and he starts working on it
and accidentally kills his neighbor's power
in the process of doing that.
And the neighbor comes over
and says, what the hell is going on here?
And offers to help him finish the room.
And the other change for day three is in room three here.
What's that?
It said, scripted Saul, somebody said.
Yeah.
Well, the thing is, we had, yeah, you can take this one,
because we had a few things
that were actually absolutely going to happen.
Yeah, so it was important for us to understand
how we were going to get from one day to the next,
because the idea was that we wanted the house to get bigger
from day one to day two,
and then we wanted to blow everybody's minds
by making the house two stories for the third day.
And so we had to come up with a storyline that made sense
to get us from day one to day two to day three.
And we had a few of these technical things
that we wanted to happen
that we needed to know how they were going to happen
in order for them to work.
And the great example of that is the fire
at the end of day two.
We knew we wanted to have a house fire.
We knew that we wanted,
that's like a very Sims thing, have a house fire.
We knew we wanted to have a house fire,
and we also knew that Jeremy wanted to go out a window.
And so coupling those two things together
actually didn't happen until Jeremy was on site.
We knew that Jeremy was going to go out the window,
but we didn't know how or why he was going to go out the window
until it was like pretty much the day before the shoot,
and it was like, okay, why is Jeremy going out the window?
How is he going out the window?
And that's when we talked about the fire
and rehearsed the fire and blocked the fire out
in order to make that happen.
And so the fire was the natural storyline about
you get insurance money, you buy a bigger house,
or you rebuild your house or whatever it is
to get that huge house on day three.
What we didn't know, for example, is we didn't,
the call came from Chap for when he would make the food
that started the sequence for the fire.
So we didn't know where the fire would happen.
We knew it would be related to making food,
but ultimately we had to place it somewhere
when Chap had decided to make food
where it was the right time for it to catch on fire.
So Chap was still involved in that decision, right,
of like the food decision was made
and that started the sequence.
Yeah, and there's so many decisions.
There's so many different pathways
of things that we had thought about
where it's like, well, yeah,
what are the different things that they could choose?
And we kind of planned for all three different options.
And then it's like, well, if they pick this one,
then what are some more things that they could choose?
And so there's like dozens of storylines
that did not play out because of how Chap chose them.
But as you'll see, as we kind of go through this,
the reality of the situation is that you have to,
you have to have some pre-planning
and have some of these more complicated things are executed.
In order for them to work.
And a great example is the window shatter, right?
Which was something that had to happen.
For sure.
People say my mic is fucked up. Does that sound bad?
Sounds good to me.
Sounds weird.
So this is prop storage.
And it's kind of laid out by room.
We're here, couch is over here,
bed is stuck over there,
chair is over here.
So as Chap purchases things,
the people in the morph suit movers will come back here,
pick the item,
and then we'll go through the front door
and install the item inside the house,
wherever Chap said to put it,
or as close to it as possible.
And this is where Nick was talking about
those trusses overhead.
Yeah, those are on like 12 inch spacing,
which is kind of absurd for floor trussing.
You can see it was, I mean,
the rooms are like 16 foot square,
so there's this very long unsupported span
that we had to deal with.
So we ran crap tons of these,
engineered wooden eye beams
to support the weight of that.
But it also created this nice cavity
where we could put prop storage.
And the size of the upstairs
was driven by the building more than anything.
Because of the spans
between the vertical columns
in the building we were shooting in,
we wanted to tie into those to help support the floor.
And did a pretty good job
of hiding the beams,
especially you guys with all the curtains
you hung to hide the beams on set.
But they were baked in
and they were part of actually
holding the set together.
And here's one of your TVs behind the windows.
Yeah, TVs, and you can see the hose manifold
there of the hose coming in
to feed the sink
and the toilet feature.
Oh shit, Andy.
Yeah, we were super enthusiastic
about making sure that little detail
of actual running water was available on set.
Because we already knew we needed running water
for one of the toilet gags,
where the toilets broke in
as one of the potential story lines
we needed the toilet bill to spray water.
We're like, well, we're already going to run water here.
Why don't we just have the sinks be functional?
It actually ended up being useful
because we could use the running sinks on set
to clean between days.
I just had that
realistic touch, right?
And this is the kind of stuff that you guys
would just do.
It'd be like, oh, we can do running water.
How? How can you do running water
that makes no sense?
It's pretty funny.
You can see in the, you go back,
it's actually all garden hoses and adapters.
See if you can see it.
Yeah, so there's the manifold.
So that's actually all residential
garden hose manifold stuff
in two locations. One in the bathroom
and one near the, this is behind
the kitchen area.
And we like went
to Menards and just found all
of the little bits and doodads to go from
garden hose to kitchen sink.
And I don't think you can see it here, but there's a little
black hose to the bottom right
of those two yellow hoses running on the wall. That's actually
running into a five gallon bucket
because drainage is its own
level of difficulty. So we just had
five gallon buckets to
drain the sinks to and we just emptied them whenever they
were needed.
See the oven in this clip too.
I have a clip for the oven.
I think there was a time
I was running the sink
and I think there was a time where I got in my ear
it was like, hey, hey, turn the sink
off. You're going to fill the fucking bucket. It's going to overflow.
Because I was using the sink too much
one of the days. So somebody had to
scramble back there and dump
the bucket quick because he's going to flood it.
This is
the handiwork here.
Was it you that worked on this?
Me and a couple people who worked on
the oven part. I did mostly the
dressing of it whereas another
AniMark person cut the back of it off
and that Brett really
made the hole in the wall work with our contractor.
So yeah, this is really
cool. This is so that behind the
scenes we could have the cookie dough
thing work where you put in the
bowl of cookie
dough and
out comes a whole package of
cookies without ever having to break camera on
that room.
Same with the mac and cheese, right?
Yeah, mac and cheese was done the same way.
I was the one
who was doing the oven management and I had to be
super quiet because I knew the shotgun mics
were on and right over the oven
so I'm super carefully pulling
it out of the oven trying not to make too much noise inside
that oven. I thought somebody was
pissing into that. I was like, oh, that's not
what's that?
Yeah, that's something that
Nick just mentioned there too. Every room had
a microphone in it in addition to
the ones that the characters were wearing
which is kind of a small
thing but it makes a big difference in the end because that's
how you were able to hear things like the moving crew
who are not individually miced. They
don't have microphones on because they don't have lines
but that's how we would get some of that ambient noise of them
running into things or kicking things or
whatever or a scene with a lot of characters
like in the party and what not. We can pick up little
bits of conversation even though not every
single person has a microphone. But it also
the flip side right is that everybody working around that
set or backstage has to be super careful
because there's just like these
ears that are just over every single room
for everything you're doing. Yeah.
I see Jeremy laughing in the chat here.
Yeah, because
I've got my fucking gamer neck.
It actually works.
It does. So water's not on right now. This is the first
time that Jeremy saw the house. This is the first time that Jeremy
saw the house, yeah.
When we were sitting around,
what was going to happen? This is like what I
wanted but it was like, holy shit, this is no way
this is going to happen. Like there's no way this is ever
going to happen. This is unbelievable.
Like unfucking believable.
So this room gets added on
day two. So on day two, this becomes
the bedroom.
Mount Fiji?
What is this? That's just like
the built-in Alexa screen saver thing.
We have custom
like daytime, nighttime. Oh my
god. This shit was so cool. It really
was. There's three fake windows in the house and a TV.
You know in those
sim simulation games you play?
Like when you see something for the first
time, I was actually walking around like clapping
at all this shit.
Like it was just, it was just
insane. Is this a
I guess we could wait to talk about the
glass window. Oh yeah, going up
the stairs. And this is
so much stuff. This is an
insane amount of stuff by the way.
You guys had so many options to
buy things. Everything on that
list, none of that was not there.
How many items were back here were potential?
100? At least.
We lost track. Yeah. 120,
130 at least of the larger
items. So every night
they counted the items to know where they were too.
So it was like they were constantly being checked to make sure that
the list of what was available.
They knew where every item was. They knew
how to get to it because that time is so fast once
they select. Nick and I went to
Goodwill one day
and we basically cleaned them out of furniture and they
said that it was the largest
order that they had ever had.
And then he and I went back
three more days after that
and just cleaned them out every single day. It was
like box trucks of Goodwill
stuff. Yeah, literal
box truck after box truck after box truck.
And the original idea was
potentially that we were just going to bring
it back, right? Like we might just
bring it all back. I don't know
what you guys are doing with that stuff.
It's still there.
It's still figuring it out.
Some of it was claimed by crew, but I
assume that everything that's left over will just get
donated again. I mean, some of it
was pretty clean. Just donated again.
I want to make this a point too.
Pretty much one of the things we wanted to make sure was
happening here was so a lot of
the stuff that we got from some of these
like thrift stores and stuff was to either
get it back there, donate it again,
donate it to where it belonged.
And a lot of this wood too. A lot
of this stuff is going to be reused and
repurposed from the construction manager.
It was all built to code.
It can be used to build houses.
A lot of this is actually going to get potentially repurposed.
So that's really good
because we essentially
put all this stuff here
and essentially built a half a house.
So I definitely wanted it
to go back as much as we could and kind of
repurpose and recycle it if we could.
I see chat asking about the stools.
So the stools,
there was one stool. It was just like
oh, we should probably have a foot stool as a thing that they could buy.
And chat loved
the stools and so that night
we sent somebody out and said buy as many stools
that model stool that you can find
and just cleaned them out. It was like
we went to every store in the area that sold
that sort of stool and just bought them out.
So we then just used them
whatever we could. We used them in the mystery boxes.
We put them back in the store.
They were in the cabinets upstairs.
The mystery cabinets or whatever they were called.
You get mystery boxes with
just stools in them.
This is case storage back here.
Yeah, we had the delivery of all
the stuff that, the technology that loaded
in here was the equivalent of a whole semi-truck
work. It was like
several hours to unload, unload
and set it all up.
That's the very back wall, yeah.
I think we have a picture too of
kind of the layout plan for all the
motors and everything. We had a lot of stuff
suspended in the air to support all the lights
and... I got to clean up
some stuff in there and then...
This is back where everybody was hanging out. There was a monitor
here, back there. It was a screen.
So all the actors,
all the people that were kind of waiting on the
wings, they were all hanging out back here
just watching the screen, just waiting for somebody to pump
in their ear or somebody to run back
here and be like, alright, we need to climb!
And then just, they would get ready and come out.
Yeah, I think I might
have a clip of that. It's called
Green Room Chillin'. There they are.
There's our actors back in that green room.
They're ready.
Based on the
chat decisions, we didn't know how fast
it might be between bicycles or
between different scenes and gags,
right? So everybody kind of had to be armed
all the time. That couch is
so freaking comfortable by the way. You could fall
asleep on that couch. Just people in
Marcy's just hanging out, like, what's up?
You got used to that
for a while. Everyone's just like
sitting there on their phone. Everyone's
watching, just waiting.
So here's some of the documents
that Alex was talking about.
Yeah, like in this case,
we had
16 points where in this building
we had to suspend things like truss
for lights or for cameras.
The camera shots you saw where you could place things
in a room or when you see them flashing
and you're picking a room, all of those shots are cameras
that had to be suspended so that we could cut between
them without getting crew in them and worrying about
where the wireless operators were walking.
So we had 16 points where we
hung things, or curtains, right? Like
we had that whole upper floor curtain with
heavy drapes that you couldn't see that it was
there so it would be a surprise for the last day. So
this kind of, we make these
different drawings that lay out where things go so that
as local crew comes in or hired
crew and whatnot, they all kind of have the same thing to
work off of. And we kind of
write all of our changes on them as we go. There's
lights and video and each one kind of has their
own to keep track of.
I think we have a video too of the
lighting. When we design the lighting for
something like this, it all gets put into a
simulation program
where it actually shows all the different
types of lights that are going to be available
and a little recording
kind of shows it. But you can kind of see
this is the party sequences designed in
this simulator program.
So we can actually, you can see kind of the rough layout of how
the rooms are. It's somewhat representative
and the lights are laid out where they would be
on the different points that are hanging in the air.
And so then we can design
these sequences and get an idea of what they look like.
You can see a human analog in one of the rooms as well
and kind of see what
we'd be working with and know where to lay
things out before you're on site. Because once you're on site
and you put something in place, it's a lot
harder to move it. So we try to simulate a lot
of that as best we can.
I mentioned this to you guys on the
actual set, but I'll say it to you guys here.
When this idea was just kind of floating
around like years ago just for fun,
you know when you close your eyes and you
see, like you see the
thing that you, let's say you're working
on a project or you're writing something or
you're making content or whatever,
when you close your eyes and you see this movie
in your head, right? I
saw this set is
what I saw. And it's crazy to actually
see it happen. Your imagination,
your actual visual of exactly what
you see in your head, it's bizarre
to see it actually play out.
When I play, the people are doing the
question marks to me. You guys don't play movies in your head?
Who doesn't do that? You can't
just see a movie right now, play it right
now? Am I insane? What's happening?
They're saying you hallucinate.
It's not hallucinating.
I'm imagining the set.
Hallucination?
It's a vision.
So when I close my eyes
and I saw this set, this
is like what they built is what I was seeing.
And that's incredibly rare.
That never happens. Where is this?
This is at the airport.
Oh, it's at like the airport. I was like where the fuck
are we? The airlines
aren't very happy with the amount of stuff we move.
Yeah, we'll move 20 or 30 road cases
at a time just like through
the luggage system. Sometimes
it'll show up on a second plane because they couldn't get it
to hit weight on the first plane.
But part of the deal is that works.
This is the rest of the set. Yeah, imagine.
You have the render
from the day one, two, three
color render.
I see if chat noticed one thing about the
day one render. Oh, yeah.
Mm hmm.
The horse in it. The horse is not
in day one. No, but this one. Yeah.
Somebody said chat can't rotate
a cube in their head.
I was going to point out too
in these renderings
a couple things here that are interesting.
So the giant TVs are there.
They were placed in a specific spot so that
no matter where the characters are moving in the house
they could always see chat. So those
giant monitors, one of them was chat and the other
one was what was going out on the feed. So they could always
see no matter which character and where they were.
There was always a view from each room.
But the other thing here that's kind of interesting is
this was supposed to be the model for
day one with just the middle rooms.
And the yard actually wasn't part of it.
And that was added later. That was an on-site change
kind of based on the logistics of
how would things get into the
house and what were we interacting with. So
that's like an example of something that
those kind of things just happen on. It doesn't matter how much
you plan in advance. We needed that logistically
so these pieces moved around
and we had the yard accessible in the first day.
I think that was the night before change.
I think those curtains were already up there
or being tied on at the point that it was like
nope, we want the yard visible.
There was a visual with seeing
that side view with the
cutaway view. And we sat there
we were just staring at it like, if I'm coming in
through the left side of the door
we can't
just have it be, oh look it's just outside
and I just appear in the door
into the kitchen, into the living room.
So it's good that we actually had a solution to it.
I guess one
last little pre-production thing
that we'll talk about before we move into the next segment
are these
Gobos that we had made. These are kind of cool.
They're a little hard to see. You may not have seen them on
the stream but you can see them here. We took
nice photos of them. These are
metal disks that are
hunched and laser cut basically
to show an image. In this case we have the
germ and the logo
here. You can actually see a good amount of detail on it.
And then those moving lights that we have we could position them
to color and
location and all that so we could actually light
Coinbase with their blue and Twitch with their
purple and then Jeremy's logo
with the green and blue. And so at various
points, we didn't show the corner camera
a lot because of the context of the rooms
we were showing but there was a few occasions
or like the monologue when
Jeremy talks about Coinbase and what not where you could kind of
see their logo and their color and
it adds a lot of character to
the house and what you're seeing too. That was awesome.
Nick, is there anything else you want to talk about
in pre-production before we
move on? Maybe the glass
a little bit. That would be about it for the window.
Oh yeah. If you want
to talk about that. Sure.
That's like one of my favorite gags
the whole week. Let me
cue up a video here. So
those of you who watch the stream,
Jeremy going out the glass
is real 100%
and we're going to show you some footage.
We got proof. We have real proof
that it's really real. Not a stunt double
not pre-recorded. That happened
live. Absolutely live.
So first I'm going to show you
we had a sheet of the glass
show up broken
to our set and so we had a piece
to test with because we had this broken piece
and so here's a
short clip of Nick testing
what it's like to punch through this glass. By the way
at least, Nick,
I think you were terrified to do this because none of us
had interacted with the glass at this point.
I had no idea.
This is not real glass. Don't do this at home.
It's not real glass. Don't punch a glass.
This is Hollywood glass made
by a studio in Culver City
that this is all that they do
they're the only manufacturer of this glass
for television. It's very expensive.
Don't do this at home.
I was not certain how it was going to go
but it explodes
with any real
energy put into it. You can break
it and it breaks into large pieces
but with any real energy it
just explodes out but it explodes
safely. All the edges are pretty dull.
The worst thing that happens is you get a
little bit of dust
on your fingers that looks kind of like glitter
but before I punched that I did not
know how it was going to break.
Which was kind of worrisome but we had info
we could actually tell Jeremy like yep, it's safe, it's good.
The fact that
the gloves were picked on
the second day. I remember sitting there thinking
I put on like big rubber.
Yeah, like you guys didn't even know but you
like protected my hands which was like
important, right? Hands, forearms,
wrists, that whole thing.
I was going to say before we show the clip I have some clips
of Jeremy practicing.
This is the very first time that
he practiced. There's no glass in the window. This is just
him flying through the window.
Yeah, let's do it.
There's only one rule, don't jump too far.
Foreshadowing, yeah.
So it actually isn't super fancy.
You can see some of the construction here.
There's actually just some scrap trim pieces
that is used with like some spacer trim
to hold the glass.
The big thing about this is when
we thought about logistics of the show we
didn't want the glass to be broken
before he gets to it, right?
But we also knew that it
takes a period of time to
install this glass and we didn't want it to be
like held in with brackets or anything that would be disturbing
so it just, like the two pieces
slotted in in those wood pieces of trim.
You can actually see a great view here
of kind of the different glass things
but we knew we only
had, we knew it took about 20 minutes to install
it and we didn't want to interrupt the stream whatsoever
so it had to survive the whole stream.
So like the whole time I'm like, is it going to survive?
And I was like, nobody can touch this wall,
nobody can slam that door while the glass is in.
I was kind of a
jerk about it because like it would be kind of
catastrophic to have a piece of glass
like fall out before
it was supposed to, right?
That was the gag of the second day
so if it was, if we went into that room and the
window was already broken it'd be like, oh well
I guess I'm getting thrown out anyways.
Every time someone went in this room
the radio call was like, careful with the door, careful
with the door. Don't touch it, be
careful, be slow. So we
did a lot to make sure
that this was safe so obviously the
glass itself that breaks into
pieces but all of the trim
is actually painted balsa wood
so that when his face inevitably goes
through one of them it just breaks
into like his dust, right? It's not like an actual
piece of lumber that would harm
him as he goes through it.
The top panel is actually not
this Hollywood
glass, it's a piece of very very thin
polycarbonate that would flex and
like blow out if he
ended up, you know, if Jeremy jumped
too high and ended up going through that top
piece it would just leave. But incredibly
he didn't. He completely
cleared, he completely cleared
the second, like his body, the entirety
of his body goes between
yeah, yeah, we'll see, we'll see in a second. Alright.
Let's play the clip.
You're dealing with a professional.
Sorry, I thought I had it. So, well I guess first
we'll show the front ways
how you saw it at home.
Right?
So this guy is in this room.
He is huge.
He's like Jerry in real life.
Yeah, he's an artist. I'll play
back one more time.
He was a
big guy.
Notice the fire in the window.
The fire in the window is
such a great touch.
You hit that perfectly, like super perfectly.
Now here's the proof.
This is it right here. I
took this footage because we started the scene
and I realized that nobody was back there and I was like
we have to have this, so here we go.
Brutal.
You can hear me say, you good? And he
gives me the thumbs up.
Let me see if I can
play the end of it again one more time.
Remember the rule was don't overshoot the mattress.
It makes such a great sound
to, that's not like sound effects
either. That's not foley. Oh wow, what a great sound effect.
Right there.
I did have, I did get
like a few small abrasions
here and like maybe like here and here
like down like on the forearm, but nothing.
Nothing that would, you know,
that wasn't bleeding or anything, I was fine.
Scraped, a little scraped.
It was unbelievable. I remember
when you showed that to me, you were like hey
what do you think about like this concept and like
I was going to put the ball so and I'm just like
I think I just started clapping.
I was like this is the greatest thing ever.
It was perfect. I don't think chat
knows what they started with. Well, so this is
he can't tie his own shoes because he's wearing the gloves
but if you go to this one too, on the day
that I demanded it, on the day that
chat chose the cargo
shorts.
Jeremy, you want to talk about the cargo shorts?
Yeah, the cargo shorts. I don't think people realize what they
did by picking cargo shorts.
Yes, so here's the deal.
So those are not the
cargo shorts that you guys actually
picked. There was cargo pants and
cargo shorts. Now the problem was
the cargo shorts
were like a size 28 waist
and I could not fit in them. It was
inappropriate, like actually inappropriate.
It was not cool.
So the hope was that
there's no way you guys are going to pick cargo shorts
because that's like boring. You're going to pick the flamingo.
You're going to pick the duckies.
It was a boring choice that you were never
going to pick, right? But when you
picked it, it was like what do we do? Because I
can't stream like this. This is
actually not okay. It was like
skin-air tight
to my body.
And we had to,
right when I was told, somebody ran backstage
and was like, hey, it's the cargo shorts.
We're just like, shit. Get the
cargo pants in. Cut the cargo
pants into shorts. Because I'm not
wearing those for like four or five hours. No
way. So if you look at
the bottom of the shorts, they're like all
frayed up and like very
clearly cut with a pair of scissors.
Almost inappropriate.
Almost like TOS inappropriate.
I'm glad we avoided that.
Yeah, so I run backstage. I have a
belt pack that I would put on that has his ears
so he can hear us talking and it has
the microphone that he was using. And
what I see is two production assistants
on the ground with scissors just going
crazy on the cargo pants trying to turn
them into shorts. We might actually
have a picture of that. I think somebody took a picture
of the two next to each other for like fun.
I'll see if I can find that over the break.
So at this point we're going to take
a quick break.
Sorry, Chad.
It's going to be an ad break. And we could
talk a little bit about ads and sponsors
a little bit later because
they were the only reason that we could do this show.
But we're going to go to ad break
and when we come back, we're going to talk production
with
our video director Bobby,
with Criken, our game director,
and with everybody's fan favorite
Art Mark. Art Mark
is joining us tonight. So
look forward to that.
But yeah, we'll see you
in just a few minutes after these
short messages. Thanks, Chad.
So our company Ghost Commander's
role on this production was not only
building and designing the
extension itself and the different interactive
modes like buy mode and placement
mode and the
different poles of live mode that played out
throughout the stream. But
we also ran the thing live. So
on set, we would basically
push each pole via
our computers to everyone
watching. We compile the results
and then display the results
as well and then relay
what won and what should happen at what time
to the rest of the crew. So things
like, you know, how
Jerma should react in a given situation.
We would then turn into different
pole events and different options.
Some of those we build on the fly based on
what viewers liked and wanted. And then we push
that out to everyone and then, you know, gather
the 30,000 replies and then
relay to
the rest of the team what needs to happen
on stage. Wait, a professional
fartographer? Yes.
I am operating all the microphones
so any audio you hear on stream comes from
this console and this laptop.
Wireless microphones are
all set for all the actors and I have
this wonderful soundboard with
a variety of fart selections
to fit the scenario. So I can do
one of those, I can do
one of those. If I want something a little wetter
I can kind of go in
that direction.
So I am making the sound magic out of here.
Take seven.
I'm going to get into the devil and start saying that
because I don't want to have to fart.
So this is our video production trailer
so we're taking all the camera feeds
into this trailer and
distributing them out throughout the
entire set. We're feeding
different TVs, monitors, the live stream.
We've got some graphics computers
doing a bunch of stuff
to create this awesome game and
this is where all the video stuff happens.
Nine, you're working right now.
Can you push it slower to his face?
I don't want to be caught, I don't want to be free.
Keep pushing, keep pushing. Ready, ten. Take ten.
Ready, nine again. Tight as you can on his face.
Ready, nine.
Ready, ten. Take ten.
Ready, three. Take three.
Alright. I think that's a great intro
for our next guests.
How are we?
Hi.
Is this working?
Yeah, it's working. We can hear you cracking.
Cool, cool. Hi everybody.
Bobby, how's it going?
How we doing?
Wait, Bobby, are you still on set?
He's still there.
What the hell?
Let him leave, Jake.
He's been there so long.
Yeah, what the?
He's like slowly pulling up the mic to talk.
And we got Mark. Fart Mark.
Yes, I don't have any farts queued up right now
but I can work on that.
What an opportunity.
Where's the emoji instead?
We got natural fart.
Yeah, I got the emoji. This is something Bobby insisted
I leave set with.
We tried to hide this in his trailer
but he found it before he pulled out.
So he was like, no, this is going to the park.
And thank you immensely for that.
Well deserved, well deserved.
So where do you want to start?
Well, why don't we talk
a little bit about
let's start with you and talk about
Ghost Commander and the extension.
I have some clips
of us kind of ruminating
on that stuff a few months ago
and did the onsite in Indiana if you want to hear some of that
or if you just want to give an intro and then we can
play some of that.
Yeah, I'll start with that.
So we, I'm Kraken.
I'm a streamer. I've been doing so for like
a decade now.
And started out
doing the usual streaming stuff
and then decided over the last three years that I wanted to make
interactive streams
more possible. Not only for
my own content but for other
content creators that I respect.
So I started a company with my co-founder
Lauren, who is pictured in
a lot of these as well, behind the
computers with me.
And we basically built a production
company that builds interactive livestream
experiences and the tools that can run them.
And so I remember talking
with Jeremy back at TwitchCon
whenever that last one happened
in San Diego.
2017, 2016 maybe?
It feels like, yeah,
we talked about
the concept of a show like this
and we both got really excited about it.
And back then it was kind of like, you know, oh, it would be nice
but we need a lot of money and a lot of
other people to make it work.
And then fast forward, you know, however
many years and
you guys bring me back up and you're like,
well, we have the money.
We have the opportunity.
Would you guys like to build an interactive show with us?
And I was like,
you know what? Why not?
And so we flew out all the way to Indiana
to see you guys without
signing anything yet. We're just like,
we're going to trust it's going to work out.
No documents.
No signatures. Just get there.
And that's what happened to me.
The live thing, the live
anything that's happening, that's any of these
options, you know, it's like the
so we talked about potentially
people being able to click on stuff or being able to like
where I'm
thinking is
because we can either have them click on
actual objects and be like,
do this. Or
we can have like a
drop down menu of all the things that are available.
You know what I mean? Like, oh, actions
that are available, right? Let's say you have
getting behind the scenes.
He's getting behind the scenes. Perfect.
What do you mean?
Oh, right, right, right.
So what I think
this is, I mean, this is okay.
But I would probably
consider redoing the whole thing.
It's not funny.
Oh, yeah, we had the bit going
where you're just going to be
awful.
Yeah, I forgot.
I completely forgot. We were going to do a routine
where, no, that didn't make this at all.
I'm realizing, I'm being a dick
here. We
were going to have the behind the scenes show be me
being an asshole to everybody for an entire
like three months. I
didn't even use it. This is the only footage
we took of me doing that. I was watching
your face as you're watching this right now going, why
the fuck? What? That's me?
What's wrong with me?
That's so funny.
So basically, what happened here is a pretty
good example. You can see on the whiteboard
we just had a big brainstorm
where Jeremy would be like, here are the sort
of touch points I want. I want
the moment where the movers come out
and deliver the item that chat picked for.
I want the moment where chat picks for me to go to the bathroom
80 times and I have to
keep doing it and
from there we kind of extrapolated this
show format and the different
stages of like going to sleep and then buy
mode happening, live mode being
whenever he's awake, placement mode
happening after that where they can pick where in the room
and then we also worked backwards from
how many days we wanted to shoot and how we wanted
the set to kind of evolve
over those. So the small
house, the buy upgrade, how much
money we think that should cost,
how we can incentivize chat to then spend
that money to upgrade the house.
All these things were discussed
and thought out ahead of time and we were basically given this
big list of
would be nice, this is what we want and then we went
and built the extension over the
remaining couple months
and then came back and ran the thing live
with everyone.
It's crazy how much
of this original brainstorm made it in
not to think about it. There was so much
we had and I think
it was pretty much all there.
It's actually shocking.
It really is and Chad's actually picking out some
pieces from this image that I put
up that I probably should have looked at before I put it up.
No, we're good.
But I think it's a good time to actually
talk about sort of
sponsorship and how this whole thing
came together
and so Jeremy had this idea like
two years ago. I remember getting a phone call. I actually remember
exactly where I was when he called me
because Jeremy calls me a lot and he
has a lot of ideas and
a lot of those ideas are great and a lot of those ideas
are just like completely insane
but that's what makes it work, right?
And I remember him calling
me with this idea and my immediate reaction was
this is amazing, we have to do this.
And it was
like over a year that we were looking for money
to do this because we knew that we couldn't
do it alone. This is an extraordinarily
expensive production
as you can imagine. You saw there were
well over 30 crew on site plus
all the pre-production, plus all the set,
plus all the gear, plus all the travel.
I mean it adds up really quickly.
And so
finally at the beginning of this year
Twitch became interested in the show
and we started negotiating with them
and we came to a deal which included
a certain number of
hours streamed as well as a certain
number of minutes of ads run at an ad
density which is why we're running ads on today's
show for instance because it's part
of that package deal. But Twitch
really gave us an incredible amount of money
to make this happen.
And we also were then shopping
for additional sponsors because we knew that the amount
that Twitch gave us was not going to be enough to cover
the entire show. It was a
great start. It was enough where
if Jeremy had to do it out of pocket, I don't think
it would bankrupt him, but
it definitely
No, not really.
But it was a
good start but we definitely were looking for more. And so
we were shopping around and
some folks pointed out some potential
sponsors that were there on the board at that time,
none of which panned out.
But it really was
the addition of Ludwig
less than two weeks before the show
and his idea about going to
Coinbase and saying hey
Coinbase, can you
is there anything you can do to help
these guys out? And they were
unbelievable, just completely phenomenal
in the turnaround time and the flexibility
that they gave us. I mean they basically told us
you don't have to do anything. Can you show our logo on screen
and can you shout us out once? And that's
the only content
that we want.
They honestly just wanted to
have the show be good.
That was incredibly surprising because
there's been plenty of opportunities
and Community Jake's been around for quite
a while now, last at least three years.
We've had potential opportunities in the past.
Not just saying that you've been around in the community, man.
I'm older than you, I got
a lot of years on you, don't worry.
But in the past there's been
opportunities to do stuff before,
but not at the level that
they were involved, Coinbase,
and they just wanted us to have a good show.
They wasn't like, well you've got, hold on a minute,
you've got to have like ten tweets,
I need to hear about this, you need to do a full
ad in the middle of the, we need to actually
talk about like seven or eight ads. No.
They just let us do whatever we wanted. And they just
wanted to be part of it. It was awesome.
It was the best experience
with any type of sponsor
I've ever had in ten years. And that's why
you never see sponsors on this channel. Ever.
Because I want
to be able to do cool shows
and not have to
have to do something I don't want to do, or have to be intrusive
in the show, and
I know that's a concern for a lot of people
here too, is, oh you're going to get a sponsor
but are they going to fuck up the whole show
and now all of a sudden it's going to be
a shitty project, now it's like
it's taken over by a sponsor.
I'm never going to let that happen. I never want
that to happen. So, finding
people, finding sponsors that actually will
work with us and care about the projects
that we do, that's how it's going
to be. And if we can't make
something happen, if we can't work something out, then
that's too bad, right? We'll figure something
else out. But I want to like kind of squelch
some of those concerns too, that people
think that, oh here come the sponsors!
It's over! It's like,
no, we're going to be fine. No,
they made it happen. They really
made it happen. At least I'm super grateful.
Alright, now that we've
got that piece out of the way. Also, one quick
little thing too,
something very, very interesting to note is this was
at the very beginning, when this was in the
concept stage, this was going to be one
stream. This was not going to be more than one
stream and we kind of had so much going on
that it was like, maybe this should
be two, maybe this should be three
and then with Twitch being involved we kind
of had to figure out what kind of show we
wanted, but this was only supposed to be one stream
in the initial phase. We're just thinking
about that now, that's impossible.
So much stuff.
Looking at some of these numbers and seeing the
estimation of, oh we'll have two to three
live mode polls a day
and live mode, it'll be like
10 to 30 minutes for each day and it's like
that didn't happen. We ended up doing
12 every day and there was
rapid fire, constantly things
happening and so it's funny, even
our estimations here were really modest
as to what it actually ended up being.
There's a lot of really cool
stuff here, I think, like a time capsule of
the evolution of thinking
through how the show could work.
The other cool one that I have here is about the timeline
about how this came together.
This is when we met
in Indiana on site.
Look at him in the corner.
It's such a great photo.
It looks like the beginning of May maybe.
What's going on?
He's having a stroke.
What am I doing? Am I asleep?
Chad, did I
fix Jeremy's audio?
Are you happy with Jeremy's audio?
I was an issue with people.
They say I'm coming out of both ears.
People that had
cell phones have a single speaker.
We've seen this issue before. I think I solved it.
People are happy now.
We met
at Antimark. This is still
months into the production but at this point now
we're at a place where we've identified Ghost Commander
and Kraken and his team as partners
and identified Antimark as partners
and all that.
We came together for a site meeting
at Antimark in early May and you can see
that the plan here
was week by week, here's the check-ins,
here's what we're looking for on these days
and here's
our stream dates and here's what's going to happen that week.
We pretty much stuck to this
within a week I would say.
Something in the middle there is really
interesting. There's one thing
that I regret didn't happen. I don't know if you want to
talk about it, Jeremy.
I think you're about to say it.
We originally had planned
to test out the live mode
chat voting for different things for him to do
on the Catboy stream
where he would be a cat
and the concept was we would take
the same tools we're already developing for the end
where we would be able to send him
to do different cat things
and it would be all done through chat
and the extension but because
of the timeline it didn't quite line up.
We were going to get a big scratching
post back here and actually this is
great behind the scenes stuff. I wanted
to have a litter box. Remember
I told you this and you were like no we're not doing a litter box.
He was so insistent on the litter box.
Constantly talking about it.
I was going to go like shit in the litter box.
He's like I don't want to do the show if I
can't shit in the litter box and we're like please Jeremy
we have so much other stuff we have to do
please don't get banned this early on the cat thing.
We wound up swapping
that with the hot tub stream.
We wound up doing the hot tub stream which featured
Catboy I think to placate chat a little
bit.
The tools are now built so
the potential for a Catboy stream down the line
using the same dollhouse stuff.
They're there. The tools are there.
I think chat wants it.
I can't shit in the litter box.
If I can't shit in the litter box.
I was going to like you know those
litter boxes with a dome. I wanted
to just like go climb in one and like sit
in it.
Yeah just like stick my
head just stick it out like whatever.
Jake you
guys tell me my ideas are good. Sometimes the ideas
are bad. Maybe I get banned
permanently from Twitch. That would have been bad right
before the show.
We can try it now if you want.
Now the show's over.
Not that the show's over. No.
Alright next up.
I want to
talk about the dream sequence.
And Jeremy
and I had a heated discussion before the show
and we've decided not to show
the original dream sequence
for
the rehearsal one.
For
risk of
some TOS issues.
It was so fucked up. It was just fucked up.
And I'm just like I don't want to do this.
This is fucked up. We're changing this.
This is too fucked up. Alright just to get
I was on the toilet.
Okay so let me just
paint the picture here. I'm just going to describe it.
I don't want to show it. It's weird and creepy
and I don't like it. So originally
we were just going to have me on the toilet.
You can just mute it and play it.
Alright so originally
I was going to be on the toilet
for the whole dream. And it was like
I'm just sitting there and I just hear like
fart noises and like shit sounds.
And by the way there was a shit sound
that
during that segment
where it was a real shit.
It was real shit coming out of somebody's ass.
I swear to god.
It was like so realistic sounding
and I was like I don't want this
to play right now.
It was an extended.
Can we time out here for one second? I have a clip of you
talking about that shit sound.
He's going to play the fart sound.
He's going to play the shitting sound.
You guys
Oh my god.
The audio guy has a folder only for
bodily functions.
And originally he was playing
when I was sitting down
like realistic foley
of somebody shitting into water.
And I was just like
that can't be used.
It was horrible.
It's super real.
I can't picture it.
You know that sound.
That's like the public bathroom washing
your hands.
Just hear that fucking thing.
No way.
He's got like a fucking hundred of them.
You know what's funny to me too is that
some of the bits
like that Jerma would do during the show
would be to yell at the fart guy.
And I had a hard time telling when he was serious
of he was really not wanting as many
farts or that was just part of the bit.
Maybe Jerma you can help
hop in on that.
By the third day I think I walked over
to the audio station
and I was like maybe like one an hour
maybe like two an hour.
I was like maybe like three farts an hour.
And you're like yeah yeah okay.
Rationing farts.
Alright so you call out the fart quarter
numerous times.
When he was in the shower
and you're like don't do it again, don't do it again.
And he kept sneaking out.
I'm done. And you leave the shower.
By the end of the show, I mean I don't want to skip ahead but like
you can see like Jerry was like so
like you were just testing us. You're like
you were throwing random shit at the production team
to see what they would deal with
like a wrench through the plans. I don't know what
got into you during that but we were like
we were like what is he doing?
Let's just see what they can handle.
Every single fart you broke
character laughed.
The worst.
Because I can hear it. What you guys
didn't know is a lot of the sound effects
I hear them like in my ear and like I can hear them
listening to them. So I'm just sitting there
like in the shower and I just hear this loud
just rip ass and I'm just like
I wouldn't do that.
So I just have to listen to it
and react to it. The worst thing that you did
to us Jeremy and
I think this is the appropriate time to talk about this.
This is the production side of things. The worst thing
that you did to us was during the party
when you picked up the phone to call
guests and
you said I'm going to call Edna
and then you turn
to the camera and say see how this fucks
them up and then continue going
because Kit needed
to be the police officer for the
party to work. The only way the party
would work is if Kit was the police officer and so
you knew that you were just going to
fuck us up and so that's why the party is paced
like so weird because Edna
comes with all the guests and
then we have to somehow figure out a way to
get Edna to leave and then he has to go and do
the hardest costume change on the entire
thing that we can do and he'll talk about that
a little bit later but like that
that has a different voice
so you have to prep her voice because it's already
been converted at that point back to being Kit's
voice. Yeah so thanks Jeremy
that was fun. But that also
gave way to like a conspiracy
threat on reddit I saw of like
is Edna dead because the last we see her
she's in the pool and like death
and the clown are talking about Edna
and then suddenly Edna disappears and everyone's like
oh my god they fucking killed her off
off camera and
like hey you know maybe it's a possibility
now in canon. I think another
hard audio piece for Mark was
the doorbell because he where he was positioned
in front of a house you couldn't see the doorbell
so people especially German would sit there
and like poke the doorbell so I could see
it on camera I'd be like doorbell doorbell doorbell doorbelt doorbell
doorbelt kilarti
moment of flush
where the audio booth was positioned I had the
first yard to my left and I had the toilet to my
right but because of the forced perspective I
have line of sight to the doorbell itself or the toilet flusher so like I'm
trying to watch your camera shots to see when I'm gonna hit the doorbell button
or when I'm gonna hit the toilet flusher so yeah so you can see what this looks
like here that was uh that was tough and then Jeremy starts fucking with me and
he's like I didn't press it yeah well cuz I've started to do like these
incredibly animated movements before I flushed so give you like a second or two
to be able to cue it up you know being like oh I'm gonna flush the toilet ah
no and I like reach down and touch it or whatever showers was really nice all
right so but battle station I do I do want to talk with a dream sequence
though I have a cool clip here of the dream sequence being incepted and like
sort of the idea behind it and then I have the the clip of the dream sequence
playing out but with the crew audio in ear and you'll hear Bobby calling calling
that so we just read well I think I think we discovered yeah we got a ray
from what we see right coming up Ludwig is in the building
look like his hair should I find an embarrassing clip of Ludwig to play
before we start here or is there a boy yeah I think I got one here there we go
this is I mean it's it's not a barrister
that was awesome I can only do a lot yeah dude you did it like flawlessly a lot
it literally sounded perfect we were sitting back there going there we go I
can't believe he did that perfectly like everyone's a musician like every single
person that touched that thing knew how to play and we were like on we didn't
know how to deal with as production team really I guess we stay on this for like
the next five minutes we also didn't know that we didn't think it worked
until we got it there all right so let's go ahead and play this is the crew call
clip this is I'm gonna play I'm gonna play not the whole thing but just a few
seconds of the inception and then and then we'll play the bad dream was to me
like gladiator versus like warrior and like I could get up so like they'll
just be doing like something in the road and I'm just very happy about it so
we're talking about safe place to insert right that's a way for the rest of
it's happening so the thought that we have is around the dream scene especially because if the idea is for them not to interact with you, you can't just be one of the various to be someone else so can we if you're either the gladiator or the warrior and you're the cowboy can we just come up with two different scenarios for it?
something I never thought I'd say. I don't know if that makes sense. What color are the morph suits? Black.
I was gonna say what if we had someone with black morphs like moving his arms like do what I say Jerma. That's right, go through the door now. What the fuck, I'm being controlled.
That's actually not a bad idea, it'd be a morph suit.
I want like a visual too, like something that's supposed to be there.
I want Ludwig as a cowboy.
I think that's good because there's no confusion on whether this is just the sexy nurse at night actually coming out.
Sexy nurse.
He kept saying that, he kept saying sexy nurse.
He kept calling us sexy nurse.
So, here's the clip, that goes on and to give chat an idea, the idea of the dream sequence was not something that you chose to happen right the dream sequence is just something that happened, but then you got to choose whether it was a good dream or a bad dream.
So, if we actually, if we let that clip play on a little bit longer, we talk about like well what would a good dream be and what would a bad dream be because we need both of those to work.
Even though we were about 99% sure that you would choose a bad dream, which of course you did.
So, here again we're not gonna play the rehearsal one, but here's how it played out and you can hear Bobby calling this as it plays out.
You want to reset Scott.
Give me another move.
Ready 13.
Kraken is ready.
And take 13.
Are we having a bunch of people in room four for the end of this bit?
Let me know when to send Kraken.
My question is are the multitude of people that we're having in room four for the end of the bit, are they ready?
I can get them ready right now.
Yeah.
Jizz is working.
Are we going to sleep here?
Yep.
Go to sleep in three, two, one.
Go to sleep and kill his mic.
Okay.
Go dream sequence.
The Kraken's coming your way, Jib.
Ready 13.
He's all 13.
Get ready for Kraken's mic.
Open Kraken's mic.
Once Kraken's in the room, we slowly bring in lights.
Ready 12.
Get that shot on 11.
11.
Ready 11.
Take 11.
Can we use the shotgun in the kitchen?
Ready 12.
Take 12.
Ready 8.
Yeah, okay.
Ready 12.
Ready Jib.
Take 12.
Take Jib.
Jib is working.
We're saying NASA audio.
Bad dream.
Ready 8.
Take 8.
Ready 13 to follow him to the next room.
Ready 13.
Take 13.
Can I start putting these people in the kitchen?
Oh yeah.
Kraken.
Have them come between rooms three and four into the kitchen.
Are we showing them right now?
Don't show the kitchen, no.
Okay.
Do not show the kitchen.
They're just loading.
Ready 8.
We need to get that TV thing out of the way.
Get what?
Ask Kraken to move the TV stand.
Ready 8.
Take 8.
Ready 13.
Take 13.
Kraken's mic's a little hot.
Jib is working.
I don't know what needs moved out of the way.
No, that's good.
It's good.
Ready 8.
Go tight on him, mate.
Take 8.
Ready 13.
Take 13.
Okay, is that it for people going into the kitchen?
That's it.
Nobody else goes out of the kitchen.
Ready room 4.
Dissolve room 4.
Ready 10.
I'm staying here on room 4.
Can we get Addy here?
Take 8.
They put him back to sleep when he'd wake up in daytime.
Ready 10.
Take 10.
Ready 9.
Who's supposed to fall asleep here?
Take 9.
Kill the dream sequence.
He's supposed to go back to sleep, right?
I thought I was awake.
Sleep.
Yeah, he should sleep.
And put him to sleep.
In 3, 2, 1.
Put him to sleep.
Ready 7.
Just go to sleep right there.
He's supposed to go to sleep right there.
Pass out.
Just pass out.
Oh.
Ready 7.
Take 7.
He's just walking.
Take 13.
And stand by 7 again.
In 3, 2, 1.
Dissolve 7.
Kill his mic.
And we're going by mode here?
Nope.
Go daytime.
Wake him up.
What are we doing?
We go daytime.
Okay, stand by for daytime and camera 13.
In 3, 2, 1.
Daytime.
And wake him up.
Ready 8.
That little bit at the end there, when he calls for daytime and wake him up, it just feels
like that moment in the Truman Show when Kristoff is like, okay, you know, ready daytime.
Everybody to their initial places or whatever.
It's just like so bizarre.
Originally, because we were trying to figure out, because Kraken was essentially back just
handling a ton of shit during, I'm sorry, a ton of shit during the whole show.
And we were like, how do we get him on camera?
Because we wanted him on camera, obviously.
And one of the ideas was actually to have him be like in a moon, right?
Just like looking down like inside of a moon, like giving some like commands or something.
But we didn't want to, we didn't want to like break the immersion, I guess, of the show.
Because it was like, oh, we're going to both show everybody like backstage and like all
the screens and stuff.
And I think I was like, I don't want that.
But originally you were going to be like in a moon.
Yeah, I'm glad it turned out this way.
I think crossing that like fourth wall into the actual room as this like disgusting Jesus
ripoff character was a nice little like transition.
And that still felt in the world, but also being an absolute fever dream.
Can we talk about how you had to wear that costume all day?
Yeah, no, I didn't have time to paint.
Yeah.
So since my duties had me like there until the final like 30 seconds before I appear on camera,
the entire day I just shoot it in a toga with no like pants or shoes on.
His hair is sitting on the table next to him.
Yeah.
He looks like he's going to the hospital.
Everyone was like, you're out.
He's got a surgery and I'm like, shut up.
I'm supposed to be God.
I like brought this wig around.
I have to look like God.
You were telling us that you had to drive the car a certain way because of your outfit.
Oh, yeah.
No.
So this is like, I mean, I'm a larger than average man.
And when I was in that little car, this toga was like way up to my waist and I had like
no pants on.
So I was like I had to like hunch over and then like I just like curved my back like
an absolute like caveman gremlin on the way in because I didn't want anyone to like upskirt
me as I'm like riding in on this like clown car.
It was a very surreal place to be.
But I pretty much blacked out the entire time I was on stage.
I did not remember what I said or when.
I was just kind of feeling it out.
Yeah.
The audio that you hear in that clip is is not specific to that clip that calls like
that for every camera and the stuff that all the movers that have those headsets on.
All of us that you've seen, like in these photos that have those headsets, we're hearing
that the whole time.
Bobby is very tired by the end of the day.
But that that's how those are called because it helps coordinate everybody like that's
moving.
That's why you very there's very few times we actually see a camera person in another
shot or the gym arm or something where because it's Bobby coordinates that with having to
get the gym out of the way and everything.
But you can talk more about this how it goes the whole time.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm pretty much talking for the entire stream, just kind of directing cameras, helping
mark out on the audio side for what you know, because he's kind of looking down a lot at
his audio console.
So any cues I can give anybody on the crew.
Oh, and this scene here was probably my personal favorite.
What are we doing here?
Push it into his face if you can.
All the way tight.
Thirteen if you can.
Thirteen.
Is that thirteen?
Like as this was going on, I didn't know that Uncle Ted was going to make an appearance
and we kind of ended the day here.
None of us knew.
He just started doing this.
Uncle Ted sits next to me, the person who played Uncle Ted, and he literally takes his
headset off.
He's like, I've got an idea.
He just literally runs away from his desk that he's supposed to be at.
I was like, I don't know where he's going or what we're doing.
Yeah.
So right here I told Mark to kill all the mics.
We go tonight.
And then all of a sudden I see this motion on eight and I'm like, oh God, oh God, we
got to go back to this.
We got to go back.
Which one is it?
I need the light clear, Josh.
Is burglar ready?
I need thirty seconds on burglar.
So we're not going to go to bye mug.
Just let him do this.
The audio in the scene was weird because German's mic was active.
Are we not getting audio with this right now?
Is it all cleared?
Right.
Yeah, because Bobby told me to clear the mic.
So it's all cleared.
Miltan had his mic on and the camera setup was maybe 20 feet away from that blue bedroom.
And it was a direct feed from a camera into that TV.
And the TV audio was on.
So the audio was coming from Miltan's mic and the mic in that camera out of the TV into
German's mic.
So it created this like weird echo effect that kind of worked for the scene.
It was sort of a happy accident how that worked out.
That was, by the way, that segment there.
That was done within like overnight after the second stream.
We were talking about like, oh yeah, we could maybe have the TV there.
That might be funny.
They set up this entire like back studio back where the furniture is.
They did it in like four hours.
It was like, what the fuck?
It's here?
It's already done this like elaborate thing back here.
How did you guys even remotely do that in less than like three, four hours?
That was Bobby.
That's Bobby.
That's old Bobby.
Jerma asked and we delivered.
Do you have any pictures?
Do you have any pictures of like of that?
It was kind of funny to me because I kept going to Jake and I was like, Jake, I'm just
not happy with this setup.
It doesn't look the way I want it to look.
And then Jerma comes in and he's like, this is amazing.
And I was like, all right, I guess I'm done here.
And we went with it.
So it ended up working.
It was.
It was insane.
I don't know if this is going to work.
We're going to try it.
Hang on.
Let me.
What are we?
Yeah.
That's the setup.
See if it'll focus.
Come on.
I need to probably get my face out of it.
Well, you get the idea.
There's like a stage, set up little stage under that deck and a camera.
And so it would look every the video was piped from there onto the TV in that one room.
So it would look like it was a live.
Yeah.
And one of the, one of the things I definitely wanted to put back there was a monitor so
they could see themselves and frame themselves appropriately so that they could see what
they're going to look like on the TV.
And without that, that whole Ted scene would have like, you know, they wouldn't have been
able to see like where they were and whatnot.
So it ended up working out really nicely.
And this picture, you can see Mark's perspective better too.
He was talking about what he can see and not see for the sound effects.
This is the picture from his station.
And I was like, my focus was back and forth between that launch pad with all those buttons
with the sound effects and the faders as people were coming and going.
Because I'd say probably 90 to 95 percent of that entire thing was improv.
So like normally with theater, you have a script you can follow as characters come and
go and sound effects cues.
This was all happening in real time with no script.
So it was a lot of reactivity and doing things as they happened.
Mics were getting passed around.
I didn't know who had what mic.
Josh, the stage manager, did a fantastic job of saying, you know, this mic is coming out
on this character.
Big shout out to Josh.
Trying to keep us in the loop.
Yeah.
Yeah, Josh totally killed it.
And not only were you having to worry about everybody's microphones and we had everybody
mic'd up in different rooms as shotguns, but you're pumping sound effects through.
So you have to worry about that.
You have to worry about the sounds.
You have to worry about when to put a fart in because it's incredibly important.
When to put in the real guy or radio sounds.
That's a lot to do.
Also, he's also he's also got a com headset on.
So he's really mixing in one year with like what was it ended up being like eight, nine,
ten mics.
So plus, you know, six more shotguns.
So it's really impressive what Mark was able to do with the front house situation.
Yeah, I remember that.
And there was a little bit of an audio discrepancy between what I heard in my board and what
actually went out over the air.
Like some of the mics were a little bit louder over the air than they were in my ear.
And I have some gain issues to work out between because the video and audio passed through
like eight different pieces of equipment before it went out to Twitch.
This is kind of crazy.
That's crazy.
Yeah, it was.
It was a lot of fun.
I've got to.
Oh, go ahead.
On the so after we wrapped the second show and we knew the party was coming, I remember
like talking to Mark and we kind of had I think we were like driving home to the hotel
and we were like, so you're ready for that party?
And he's just like, haha, like we were aware of the amount of people that we had to focus
on all with their own mics that you had to like cut between.
I think it turned out amazing with, you know, what sort of information and all the and Bobby
for cutting between all those different shots in the party, like being able to see the cutaways
of like Edna in the pool or the Grim Reaper and the clown talking in the corner and like
have it all feel like a vibrant living, you know, party scene was fantastic to watch.
Well, also trying to keep the story coherent.
And that's where like Bobby and Alex and everybody were fantastic at saying, OK, let's we got
to listen to what Ludwig and Randy are saying right now.
So make sure their mics are hot.
So it was a everybody on the team just kind of came together and having that communication,
having those headsets was key to keeping everything focused and where it needed to be.
Yeah, to jump on what it was a little bit of a logistic hell.
Yeah. Yeah. After the fire scene, I felt like it was kind of chaotic because the fire took
place in pretty much all three rooms plus the front yard.
And then the fire was happening and then the other guys were still playing with their fire,
doing their little gags in the other room and tosses Jerma out.
There's a thumbs up shot that we got that turned out to be great.
And then the next day I was like, OK, there's going to be 20 more people in the house.
Like, this is going to get crazy, but it ended up working out great.
And just the communication for everybody on headsets was just super key to making this show successful.
So I want to show this clip real quick.
This is this is the party scene and tables perspective from the tables perspective.
So you're not going to hear the crew audio over the comms.
You're just going to hear what it sounds like in that room because I think it's a pretty unique perspective.
That's wild to look at from this perspective after it's all over.
Lights look totally different, too.
And I got to give a lot of props to the camera guys that we had.
They were really selling the, you know, the main action as this whole party was going on
between the two wireless operators.
So we really didn't miss any of the little small gags here and there.
I'm sure there's a couple we missed, but there's a lot going on at one time in six different rooms.
Also, don't forget, any time that Edna appears, the other fun part for camera and for audio
is that people can't get near Kit with that microphone because then you hear the Edna voice on.
So when chat would vote for you guys voted at one point to have Jeremy dance with Edna, I believe.
That's really hard to actually pull off for us because they can't talk when they're dancing easily
because you would hear Edna's voice amplified with Jeremy's voice.
Right. So there's all these little pieces where a simple decision causes four other things for us to watch.
I think there was a few times when I actually came through.
I came through Kit's mic a few times and it was just like, it sounded insane.
So I tried to kind of like, like, like, like, like try to react to like just my face was so hard to do.
This was so great. That's an insane picture.
I love that. For that piece, the Edna thing, I think typically when Kit's using that mic,
it's, you know, a streamer mic, a mic that's really, you know, he's the only one in the room also.
So like when you put it onto a lapel and put that effect through it, you never know what you're going to get.
And so as he moved around, his voice level changes.
So you can kind of hear the level of Edna change throughout the scene.
But Mark did a really good job of riding that fader and riding those effects.
So shouts out to Mark on that.
So we're trying to get Ludwig connected right now.
He's having a little issue, but we're getting him sorted.
So in the meantime, I want to play one more crew audio clip because it seems like chat really likes those.
So we'll play another one that says album cover.
Oh, speaking of album covers, I have an exciting announcement.
I don't even think Jeremy knows this.
What is it?
We submitted it today.
And in about seven days time, you should be able to listen to the bi-mode soundtrack on Spotify.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
So, yeah, that's original music.
People may not realize that.
Yeah, people probably don't really address myself to that every day.
The amount of times we heard that on set and while live is staggering.
I have to imagine people are playing it, too.
Yeah, it's like being at a ride at Disney, right?
They play like the same like two minute audio clip of like, it's you.
Oh, welcome. We need to get you into that seat.
You're going to fight the rebels.
Right. It just plays all day.
Yeah, people are asking about DMC.
Yeah, that piece was commissioned for this stream.
All of the rest of the music that was used was royalty free music that is licensed through various regular royalty free sort of sites.
But the main piece that's used during the bi-mode, that's used during the character selector, that's used during the loading screen, that piece was made custom for us.
And I don't think we have a single really good piece in any of the pods because it was all like either custom or otherwise.
So that's why you get to see the whole thing.
That is remarkable.
Considering how many sound effects and little audio files were played, that's remarkable.
Jake gave me a week to find those.
He was like, hey, we have a week. Find a bunch of sound effects and music.
We have like 12 hours of stream to kill. Find some music.
OK, good luck.
Yeah. Was there one other?
Yeah, so we're going to go ahead and play this scene.
I love this scene.
Lawyers. This is this is one of one of Jeremy's birth child scene.
So, yeah, we talked about the scenes that were sort of set up ahead of time.
The DIY room, obviously, was something that we needed all the props in place for it to happen.
In terms of how it happened was totally up to chat how those walls got painted, whether or not he actually discovered the safe was was up to you as well.
But in the end, that wall comes down, he finds a safe and inside the safe is the money.
And we needed an army of lawyers ready to make that happen because his concept was, you know, he calls one lawyer to settle it.
And then that lawyer calls another lawyer and that lawyer doesn't know what to do.
So he calls another lawyer, et cetera, et cetera. So that's how that that wound up.
There was an alternate storyline, too, I think, where it and and Jeremy got married.
And so we would have called the priest to have them get married in the middle of that scene, but that didn't wind up panning out.
So anyway, I'll play back what you saw on stream and along with the crew audio to add to this, too, add to this, too, just this is important.
So when when the call the bear, all the bear, I opened up this this door here that you see of that to the kitchen.
And there's just a guy with a bear head.
He wasn't in the whole costume.
So I'm just like, how the fuck are we going to get him in here?
It's just as he just has his head on.
So he's like he was he was essentially they weren't prepared for that at all.
So I was imagining he might have like come into the house and started like attacking people.
But it's just him with the head. He scared the shit out of me.
He's literally just sitting in the in the in the little little cubby here.
And I was like, what the? Yeah, I want to say that fancy bear.
Yeah, it was just a very old fancy bear.
We so Jeremy didn't know that was going to happen because originally this was meant to play out and the bear thing wasn't an option.
But as we're we're running all the polls and running the stream on our side, on the extension side, we see Chad just blowing up with call bear.
Like they're they're sick of these lawyers.
They need like a stabilizing, violent force to like, you know, return normalcy.
So they just wanted the bear in because we already showed them that you can call bear for the gorilla.
So they know it's an option. They know that they can call bear.
And so we're like, you have to we have to call bear like I can give me five seconds.
OK, it could just be that I'm going to I'm going to back it up.
The beginning call of this is is do we have the bear ready?
And the bear costume change is the hardest costume change of all because it takes almost 15 minutes to get in the costume.
It's ridiculous. And so, of course, the bear is not ready.
So here's the call. And Josh is desperately going, fuck you guys.
We want us to call the bear. Is there any way we can get a bear just to peek in?
I can give me five seconds.
It could even just be the head, right?
Yeah, tell him to go in between the rooms and peek out the window or something.
Yeah, just walk by and be like, you know, the amount of times Bobby says five seconds.
Yeah, we can do that. All right, get him ready.
I need 20 seconds. What window do you want?
We're going to run the pool now.
Into the kitchen.
Not yet. Not yet.
Oh, I got it.
Ready, nine, take nine.
This is going to be tight with the bear.
All right, take your time.
I'll let you know when you're good.
Bear coming into the window, nine, be ready.
Not yet. Do not bring them yet.
We're not going to go in yet. We're just making sure we can fit.
OK, he's going to call now.
Viewers voted for him to call bear. Let him know.
OK, I can't see.
Yeah, by the way, there was a huge concern.
That bear head is so big, we didn't think it would fit between the walls.
Like for him to stick his head through the window.
So that's what that call was.
Which would have been hilarious.
If he had gotten stuck in there,
it would have been worth turning the camera and just showing it.
Like if he actually got stuck there.
You're here to monitor, so I just...
Bring Jed. Go on the bear.
No, do not go on the bear.
Do not go on the bear. He's the parter.
Take ten, take ten.
All right, send bear now.
Take ten. Ten's up, ready eight.
Ready eleven, take eleven.
He just paid seven grand.
Ready ten, take ten.
Where's the bear coming to again?
He's through the window in four.
All right, ready thirteen, take thirteen.
Bear noises.
Ready eight, take eight.
I don't think so.
I think it's just his head.
It's not his head, it's his head only.
It's his head only, Blair.
He can't come inside.
Ready eight, take eight.
Can we get the bear to poke through one more time?
Ready ten, take ten.
Yeah, I need fifteen seconds.
Yep.
So much for Josh.
We really wanted the fist bump.
Give him a fist bump, camera guy.
Give him a fist bump.
He couldn't be, it was his bare hands.
Give him the fist bump.
Ready ten, take ten.
Yeah, but we're just gonna get the camera guy
to stick his hand through.
Do we put the fist in the window now?
Stick the fist, yeah, do it, do it.
It's gone, it's gone, it's gone, it's gone.
Ready three, take three.
We were trying to get you a fist somewhere.
The bear go, ready ten, take ten.
All right, I think that's gonna...
If it was a human hand, that would've been funny.
I was trying to tell him, I was like, go now,
it doesn't matter, send someone, but it's too late.
Well, also, wasn't he dressed...
Yeah, I was trying to tell our camera operator just...
Yeah, a little camera operator.
He had, didn't he have the gladiator costume on?
Yes.
Because he was ready to be the gladiator, right?
So it was this bear head with a gladiator,
it looked like a Fortnite skin.
Honestly, I think they should've sent him in anyway.
I think just a bear in a gladiator outfit
to defend you against the lawyers
still would've been a very worthwhile scene,
but you know, let's just say.
The real path would've been if the bear was a lawyer.
Yeah, bear comes in as a lawyer.
If we needed the standing bear or the scary bear,
because he claimed it took like 30 seconds longer
for one or the other, so he just,
we want standing bear or fancy bear,
standing bear or fancy bear.
It was some great calls on com.
Yeah.
It's so hard to see out of that suit
that the first time when the guy that plays that,
the bear came out to rummage through the trash,
he left, but he was crawling and he couldn't see,
and we had to go get him out of the drapes
because he was crawling through the...
He was like stuck in the drapes that surround the set
because he can't see where he is,
so we had to go get him out
because he's just in the drapes like lost.
Do you have any shots from when the bear mauls Kit
as the car salesman and then tries to leave
and like trips over and like his head starts falling off?
I think so.
Yeah, so what we're gonna do now is we're gonna,
we're gonna take another ad break,
and when we come back, we have both Ludwig and Kit
standing by for the third segment of our show.
Huge shout out to Bobby and Mark.
Thank you so much for joining us.
Thank you guys for this opportunity,
super unique and super fun, I appreciate it.
Awesome.
So after this break, we'll be back with Kit Boga,
Ludwig and Kraikin.
So thanks everybody.
It's me, Fred!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
What the fuck was that?
Didn't like that.
What?
We were looking for something.
You did a Fred reference?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I don't know, we had the leftover helium tank,
I needed something.
It was fucked.
Is my audio good?
Can you guys hear me?
Your audio's fantastic.
You sound great.
Yes. I love that.
I downloaded VMAX.
What's going on?
I have an entire operation in front of me.
I see, I have like seven different overlays.
But how much?
I'm doing good.
This is, this is, this is dope.
I didn't realize that you producers, you talked.
Ha ha ha ha!
Like that I have lips?
The entire time.
Yeah.
They were like talking and like directing.
They were like, they were working.
I don't know.
Like a lot.
It just happened.
Yeah.
We had to talk the whole time.
I thought it just kind of happened.
I didn't know.
Crikey.
My apologies.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Yeah.
Well, I'll accept it.
What are we looking at here?
What is this?
Oh, you know, I don't know.
Good driveway.
Let's play it.
Let's see.
I think this is a load of furniture coming in.
I don't know why this is what's queued up, but.
It's a random furniture.
Oh, this is fucking amazing.
Isn't that great?
Piece.
Oh, what a beauty.
There's Ted's couch.
There's the bar.
This looks like somebody's moving.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
We basically did several times.
Yeah, there's the bar.
They put the bar in.
So, yeah.
Why don't we start with,
I want to hear from Kit and from Ludwig
and from Kraken about what your favorite scenes
of the show were and why.
So, let's start with you, Kit.
Favorite scenes, specifically.
I loved, although I don't think Jerma did,
so I feel bad saying this.
I loved your love scene with death,
partially because if I remember correctly,
you specifically said that you didn't really want it
to go very long and it did go very long.
I have that clip.
Let me see if I can find it.
I just like awkward moments.
Well, the thing about that scene is they were never supposed,
they were supposed to cut away.
Yeah.
Am I echoing?
Is that me echoing?
No, you're good.
I hear you once.
You might hear yourself in V-Mix.
I hear myself twice.
I hear you four times a second time.
Everybody has headphones on.
Ever had a stream open somewhere?
Wait, it might be me.
Hold on, is it resolved?
Hello?
Hello, yes.
Yes.
It was me!
Yay!
I was like, do I have a stream open?
I like to throw in tech issues.
I like to throw in some tech issues so I can solve them
and then I can be a hero.
Yeah.
So here's the moment, Kit, when we discuss that.
You want to be under the sheets
or already up and adjusting your clothes?
Nice.
I was imagining being already up
and in the room, not adjusting your covers.
Wow, that was exciting.
Wow, I've never experienced that before.
I almost died like six times.
That was weird.
Did you start smoking it?
I'm still tired of you shooting at me.
I'm still smoking after I got back from the bathroom.
What if they put a blur on the,
kind of pulling around a little?
That makes it too real.
Yeah, that might be too much.
That's too much.
Yeah, I think the idea was to shoot away from it
and then just play the music, which I think is fine.
And Amelia showing up is a great reason to cut away.
Yeah.
Yeah, so.
Yeah, we cut away to ending the house.
What are you doing?
What is this?
What's going on here?
First you stand me up, then you get a new house,
and now?
I'd be like, wouldn't you?
Like, what, you got a chance here?
I'd be like, this guy, death?
You would take it.
I'll just walk out and be like, don't call me,
I'll call you.
So they didn't cut away.
Yeah, I stayed under the covers.
In fact, it was like, I was in my ear, I'm hearing,
hey, we didn't cut away, you gotta stay under the covers.
And I'm just like, you cut away, you play the music.
You cut away and you play the music.
Like that, and they're like,
just don't use it, we don't have it ready.
So I think you got up a few times too,
cause you didn't wanna be in there.
They're like, go back to the bed, go back to the bed.
Or you have to go back, cause you're staying at the door.
There wasn't a good moment to cut away
cause you guys were just laying on top of like,
you're standing like, laying like this,
looking at the ceiling without interacting at all.
There was no covers involved.
It's just the most awkward, like sitting,
like lying side by side.
And then we're like, when are we supposed to cut away?
Well, cause it was a small bed too, wasn't it?
It was like a full, right?
Or like a twin?
It was a queen.
It was like a little bed.
Was it a queen?
It didn't feel like it.
It was a queen.
It was just like, it felt like a full, I will say.
I have a confession to make.
I'm making this confession live on air.
I have not told anybody this.
Milton and I conspired to not cut away.
We talked about it beforehand.
He was like, so do you, like,
do you want me to like get under the covers and move around
or like, are you just going to cut right away?
And I'm like, no, no, no.
I'm like, get down there.
Like, like pull them down there if you have to.
Like, you know, make it, you know, make it.
I don't think I want that.
The original idea was like, I'm under there with them.
And like, oh, this is great.
This is fantastic.
Oh yeah, me and death sharing a woo-hoo, right?
But I, I was under the impression that like,
I would hear like love, fun, like music, right?
And they would cut away.
So I'm just sitting there going like, this is great.
This is awesome.
I love lying here with death.
And it's like, cut the fucking camera.
Like, why is it still in the room?
Because I had a program monitor.
I'm sitting there looking over.
I'm like, why, why are we, why, why are we still here?
I want you to cut away.
I mean, the problem is-
I just got up and I was like, all right, fuck this.
I'm out of here.
We had to watch Amelia walk through the whole house,
which I mean, that takes like 35, 40 seconds, you know?
We're just going to watch.
We're just going to-
Well, because we can't show me woo-hooing somebody on stream.
That was my main problem was like, I can't like, we can't like,
we can't like roll around in the bed together
and like S word on stream.
We can't do that.
That was the whole point of the cut.
By the way, your usage of the S word the next day
when streaming, I think was just, none of us expected it.
That was up there in my favorite moments.
Cause we were, all the production team was listening
and we're all cutting normally.
And then you started doing that bit.
And I forget who it was.
One of us was like, did you just say sex?
And we're like, oh, and then we're like, all right,
lean into it, lean into it, play into it.
So we like did like alerts, like, like you did what with death?
And your face went like beat red instantly
and you like realized what you did and tried to backtrack.
I was surprised constantly, Jerma,
that I've been on Twitch a much shorter amount of time,
but I have lost all sense of pride and shame
and love for self-respect and I had learned
that you still have many of those important qualities
that humans have that hadn't been stripped away yet.
Well, I was just for terms of service.
I didn't want to like, fuck death on camera.
You know what I mean?
Like, oh yeah, let's like, yeah, this is great.
We're going to have sex on camera.
I was, that's why I was afraid of it.
All right, Ludwig, full story.
Why don't you tell us about your favorite moment on stream?
On stream or specifically?
No, just of the show, I guess.
Okay, because I think the best moments
were like sitting in the room
and then just vamping on funny things that could happen,
half of which never came to fruition.
But it felt like being in class with none of the work
where you could just say shit out loud
and then, you know, everyone will laugh.
And it was great.
Everyone just, everyone kept flinging jokes.
There's so much laughter.
But the one, I mean, I'm a sucker for Amelia.
I'm an Amelia fan favorite.
Yeah, I'm a sucker for Amelia as well.
Cause all of it was, I mean, none of it was intended.
In my mind, like when we first talked about
the maid character on rehearsal day,
it was like, oh, you know, like maybe you'll come in
and clean and like, I'll go to work.
Like I might even be there.
And then it devolved quickly, rapidly.
And they became, you know, their own special character.
It's one of them.
Yeah, in fact, the, let's see.
I've got, I'll take this here.
One of the things that I love most
about the Amelia character was that we went into that
that day too, your first day on screen.
And it was just like totally supposed
to be a throwaway character
that maybe would show up a couple of times.
And because of chat's decisions
and what they were saying in chat,
it totally devolved into this kind of like,
like romantic sort of thing.
Self-opera.
Well, Jeremy invited her on a date
and then that became a whole thing.
Cause then when the date was a standup,
then that had to become a storyline for the next day.
And the date was a standup
because of chat's decision, right?
It was like they chose to make them do something
that made them late for the date and it didn't work.
And so when we all got in the room at the end of the day,
cause we were going live again in like whatever, 16 hours,
we were like, what's gonna happen with this storyline?
This idea of like, no,
like Amelia is now part of this soap opera
and also Amelia is Ludwig
and the only difference between them two is the choker.
Right?
That choker.
Yeah.
I think it's funny,
one time you walk into the bathroom
and I call you Ludwig, cause I just hear your voice.
So I'm just like, oh, Ludwig.
And you're just like, no, that's not who this is.
What I actually did, I went, yeah, I mean, no,
this is Amelia.
Cause I had forgotten too
that I was Amelia in that moment.
I was like, oh yeah, I'm Ludwig.
And I was, I failed to answer.
Yeah.
It is funny how little responsibility chat would also take
cause they are the reason that you bailed on the date,
but they were furious that they had caused that to happen.
They turn on each other, not themselves.
Yeah. It's like, as soon as,
if anyone decided on something
that someone personally had not picked,
they just yell like rigged
and like attack the other sub faction of chat
that wanted the other thing.
And it was, it was pretty like surreal
to like set up those dominoes
and then sit like, let them go
and just see how immediate it was like dogs,
like fighting over a bone.
Like everyone would just go at each other and read.
Any wrong move.
When I took off the choker,
they went from loving Amelia to hating Ludwig.
It was that, it was the, if I, if I never revealed that,
it would have been fan favorite.
I left the villain, I left the heel.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, that's when we developed this thing.
Let me see if I can run it.
The Ludwig dollhouse and this concept behind like,
how does the stream end?
How does, how do we, how do we get out of this thing?
Was not predetermined prior to the night
before the last show, right?
It was like.
Shout out to the graphics department.
Yeah. Shout out to graphics
for coming up with that stuff real quick.
And actually for you Ludwig too,
for doing the recording of your little head thing, right?
Like that was, that was so clutch,
but the way that it all came together in that,
the save file and, and like,
Ludwig's takeover of the stream and then,
and then resetting the save file.
I actually have a clip.
That was funny.
I have a clip of that coming together.
Let me see.
Yeah. I thought about this last night
and it just like got out of the line there.
It like might not, if it was even,
it's probably too late at this point,
but if they could even cycle to like something else,
like if it was like they could cycle to Ludwig
and like he had his own needs bar, right?
Like that might be kind of fun to like have us
be given two different directions,
but at this point, that's probably way too difficult.
It's like 14 hours there.
Is there a difference you see?
Yeah, like 14 hours there.
We'd have to reset the needs bar for the person,
but then we get like if you had an animated face thing
on the bottom left, then it's no different.
Yeah.
And like I could be like pissed.
You're not controlling it.
What? No, no, no, no, no.
You're controlling, you're controlling, you're controlling.
No, no, no, no, you control me.
You can just vote for who they want to control.
I could pump like one of your IFVs
and be like, give me that fucking mic.
I mean, this is my show.
We're roommates now.
No, no, no, no, we're not roommates.
We're not roommates.
We like the title of the story.
Yeah.
You have like a graphic pop-up that now shows a house
and it says like, German plus Ludwig.
You're like, whoa, this isn't plus him.
We have the needs bar in the corner.
We have like the little like, yeah,
that face of Jeremy there that's there.
We took it down probably through and put the logo up
just because it was like, it was a lot down there.
But I think if you clearly then show it,
if we just recorded like your heads so that we had it.
And then I can make the same sort of overlay
we did for that.
Yeah, exactly.
I would say like after they take control of him,
it should probably be another maybe 10 to 20 minutes
of like total time for them to do a few actions
to buy one or two things maybe.
So he does so they get actions as him
still during the party.
Oh, it'd be funny to spend all your money
and that's where we go.
And you make a big point where you like,
they buy the most expensive shit and like,
but people are just like, oh man,
let's go get the most expensive stuff for the party.
I find like your cash reserves,
we buy something else right after.
Yeah, he's like, it's not my money.
Put it up again.
That was the inception of the idea right there.
Yeah, it came together way more naturally
than I would have expected too.
Yeah, and it was all done like a day before.
14 hours before the show.
Yeah, yeah.
Because I remember going into like the shooting of this
and we like didn't know how it was gonna end
on the final day.
It was just kind of a, you know,
because the day two had the fire
and that's like such a great moment.
But day three, it's like, you know,
it kind of came down to whatever chat decided,
whatever they, you know, like they glomped onto
and we're like, we wanna see this plot line play through.
And it just happened to be Amelia, I think,
which felt really natural.
I'm looking for a clip I have of Kit backstage
before the reset of the game,
where.
I love Kit.
I have to say, I love Kit.
Kit is like the sweetest human.
And then in any interaction,
will always be so considerate to a fault
on how you might've interpreted it in some negative fashion.
And I would always remember he'd like, you know,
you'd like come back or something.
You'd be like, was that, was that like good?
Was that okay with the police officer?
Like that was good, right?
And I'd be like, yeah, man, that was fire.
We were dope together.
It's always good.
Yeah.
You're the sweetest life force I could have imagined.
That's very kind of you to say.
And funny to boot, funny to boot.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're not allowed to be funny and nice by the way.
Okay. I already picked one.
Are very clearly kind of struggling at that one.
You're not allowed to be both.
All right. And better at both.
That's not allowed. Okay.
That should be banned.
Oh, geez.
I'm having a real tough time.
What video are you doing?
I still have your,
I still have all the cash you gave me, by the way.
You got the money?
I don't know where I put the,
did I give you the signed bill?
No, no.
I think I lost just the signed bill.
The signed stuff.
It's play money, by the way.
Just to be clear.
I stole all the cash from set.
I found out it was play money.
What an L.
But I stole all the cash from set
and I had people sign one
and I lost just the signed bill.
I thought you had had it,
but now it turns out you don't.
So it's gone.
Could you not?
If you want, I can sign one of these, but.
Did you just ship it to me?
The saddest signed bill of the mail.
Yeah, I signed it for you, kid.
Yay.
On the topic of the.
You guys were an amazing addition to the show.
One of the things that I wanted to make sure,
is bringing on people that,
you know, it's the German 985 dollhouse.
How do we make this happen for three days, right?
How do you possibly,
how could I be up there for three days doing,
oh, look at me?
There's only so many times I can do that
for like 12 straight hours.
So bringing on,
I'm just trying to,
we were trying to think of early on
who we could even like mesh with,
who would be fun,
who would be interesting,
who would be funny.
And we had some late additions, too,
that came in and just knocked it out of the park,
like Milton, Micah, Randy.
Milton was unbelievable.
Milton was a rock star.
He just showed up and he was,
he was like literally the last second possible.
It was like four days before the show,
five days before the show, right?
And it's just like, you want to fucking do this?
He killed it.
He was amazing.
Loved it.
I loved every contribution.
And we've got technical problems.
I can't, no, I'm looking for a clip
and I just, I can't find the clip.
There's a clip of Kit and Milton and Micah backstage
as we're about to start the reset sequence
and Kit goes like,
so I'm going to go out there and plead with chat to do this.
But I think he actually prefaces it.
He's like on the off chance that they pick not to do it,
like I'm going to go out and do this
and then they're going to come out after me, right?
It was like just the perfect setup for it.
I unfortunately get it.
Oh, at the end?
At the very end.
Yeah.
Well, cause you had said,
I don't remember who thought of it,
but we're talking about resetting the game.
And I think we all assumed that chat
was going to reset the game.
And I remember thinking, what if they don't?
Like they're, they might not do that.
And they did not do that for a very long time.
No, it was like five or six polls, I think.
Yeah.
I'm so glad that it happened
because you could have that opportunity
of more and more people coming and begging.
And like, it felt like this climax of building.
And it was like, I don't know if you guys saw the percentages,
but it was a matter of 1% to 3% difference every time.
Like it was down to the wire.
Chat was just ravenously like battling each other
to try to push it one way or another.
And it felt like a real climax.
It was really cool.
And just to be clear, Craig,
and you can talk about this a little bit too.
We had no way to rig the poll.
It's not like,
because at some point during that sequence,
I was like, can we just like push it over the edge?
And Craig, it's like,
we physically don't have a mechanism to change.
Like the data comes in and it goes into it and that's it.
Yeah.
The only bug that people saw that I'm aware of
was the sorting issue in like the first day,
where like it would show a winner,
even though another thing had a bigger percentage.
And that was purely like our UI pushing the wrong winner
out of a sorting issue.
But all the numbers were calculated.
And you can see that like the majority votes
went to the right thing.
So none of that was padded in any way.
It was all literally what Chat picked.
And we just had to like preempt
kind of what we expected Chat to go for.
But even then we had contingency plans
for like literally everything,
which I think is the awesome part about the show is like,
there's a, and so just to segue,
I guess it's like my favorite thing of the show
was the whole Uncle Ted segment where,
you know, Chat voted for him to check the mail.
That led to him getting a letter and we're like,
we need him to get more money.
So I guess we'll do inheritance.
And so I pushed the notification of his uncle died,
which then went to,
he made up the name Uncle Ted when talking to his mom,
which then went to Chat,
like lamenting the death of Uncle Ted
and how he was like weirdly happy about it,
which then went into like day two,
we're like, well, we needed him to get more furniture,
but he has 20 bucks in the bank.
And I was like, what if we made, you know,
a set of furniture that was free
because it was Uncle Ted's inheritance set.
And so Chat of course goes and buys that because it's free.
And so we were like, kind of setting all these pieces.
And then, you know, once they get that set,
that enables our character Blair
to play Uncle Ted and come on set.
And then we even had the decision of whether or not
to kill him.
And like, we thought Chat was going to kill him because,
you know, you guys are psychopaths, but you know,
there was an option of this where you don't kill Uncle Ted
and he's a character for the rest of the show.
Like that, we were prepared for that.
And he could have been around for the party.
He could have been like a consistent guy,
but they're like, oh, he's a ghost.
Call the Grim Reaper.
And yeah, that whole bit was my favorite.
Yeah, because if you had called like the priest,
priest would have probably showed up
and been like, this person's alive.
Like maybe like do an exorcism on them,
but this person's alive.
I don't need to.
This is actually a clip of them waiting backstage
to see which way Chat goes.
That's awesome.
Yeah, I don't know if you've shown too many moments
like that yet where we sometimes had these trees
where we knew every possible thing that Chat could vote on.
And so we would, all of us would be suiting up
or like getting ready for whatever character.
And then if it didn't get called, we'd just walk back.
Yeah, I actually, I have a, go ahead.
That was the worst for Kit
because Kit, he would be like Edna, the policeman.
He'd have to like swap the most insane costumes.
Mia would be like, all right.
Not the bear though, but.
Yeah, that's true.
The bear actually was brutal.
Yeah.
I'm gonna show my crib sheet.
So this is how the entire show was run
off this piece of paper here.
And.
A lot of lines.
Yeah, so this was not made months in advance.
In fact, this was made after the first stream
before the second stream of here are all the events.
Here's who's involved with them.
Here are the Chat options for them.
And then we had other notes about like
what all those different Chat options entailed.
But then as we were going, I'd be making notes about,
okay, how is this changing?
How is what transpired gonna affect
what's happening in the future?
Who's involved with what?
Who needs to be in what costume, what and where?
And so this was kind of like the master sheet
of what we had done already and what was left to do
and what options we had left.
And you can see there's some things on here
that we never did.
We never had the sleepover.
The lures by it.
Yeah.
The sleepover.
Yeah, the sleepover.
And the other one was the check.
You missed out.
The check.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Oh yeah, the giant, the giant like,
Jack, I forgot about that.
What was it called?
Publishers Clearinghouse.
Yeah, it was called like,
I think we called it Editors.
Sweepstakes.
Editors Sweepstakes.
Oh, you guys made it.
You made the whole check and everything too.
I'm looking for the photo of it.
It was a beautiful check.
Yeah, there it is.
Yeah, and even when people showed up,
because anytime that somebody knocked on the door,
it was up to essentially you guys to send people,
like you chat, right?
But once they were in the house,
it was pretty much fair game
to make up a random storyline with Improv
and just see where it went from there.
And doing the weird stuff with,
needing you guys adding like a variable,
but like, oh, you're gonna call the bear now.
Oh, go to the bathroom.
Oh, go in the shower.
I just kind of created a bunch more dynamic
and it gave for different storylines
to just be made up on the fly,
even stuff that wasn't even written down.
So it was really cool.
I really liked how inspired by Scooby-Doo you were, Ludwig.
All those Scooby-Doo.
Oh yeah, you were really into the Scooby-Doo stuff.
Obsessed, I don't know.
I think it's so funny,
like the just happened to have missed him,
walked into a different door.
They walk out another door.
I don't like that physical comedy.
I could be 75 and also think it's funny.
Or the cabinet in the kitchen.
I also battered my knee.
You still have bruised that?
Oh my God.
You see that?
That's from a-
Looks like you got hit by a softball.
It was from exiting the house
as a robber through the window.
Yeah, I didn't even recognize until like the next day.
Dang.
That's bad.
That was quite the stunt.
We all signed waivers, right?
We signed waivers, didn't we?
Look, if I complain after you jumped out of a window
in a glass, I think.
But I guess I would say who won the house.
I can't complain.
I have here the things we had at the door, the disclaimer.
Was there a disclaimer?
Oh yeah.
I'll go with one of my favorite things
of the whole entire week.
Oh yeah, nobody asked you, huh?
I was gonna-
I don't think he asked.
He didn't even ask me.
Kitten, when you and I were in the DIY room,
and the amount of times that I'm swinging the hammer around,
how you are actually not acting visibly scared of me.
It's pretty funny.
People are like, hey dude, you know you came pretty close
like three or four times to hitting me in the back?
And I'm like, no, I didn't, not even talking about.
I didn't know that you hadn't done some of that stuff.
So yeah, I was just a little bit afraid a few times.
I heard you on your channel the other day
and you were like, yeah, I didn't realize
that Jeremy had never done anything before.
He didn't know how to use a paint,
he didn't know how to use a hammer.
I'm not trying to like shame you, I just didn't know.
Like soft, unused hands.
I just didn't know.
There's the signs.
That's so funny.
There's a part where you pick up the sledgehammer
and you just like kind of slowly got golf swing
into the wall, just making little holes.
And then when you pull the painting down
and it's just like, you didn't get the painting.
And then the safe opens.
The safe actually opens,
like before we even get to see it.
Did Chad see that?
I think they did.
Oh, they didn't.
Oh.
We hit the safe open.
I didn't know about this.
So I left the safe not latched
because in rehearsal, Ludwig, you got it open,
but you, it was like, I was like worried about it.
And I was like, what if you can't get it open, right?
So then I was like, okay, I'm gonna leave it,
but not completely latched.
But then I should have thought
that they were gonna try the handle on stream.
Just open.
That's my bad, yeah.
It opens.
Yeah, the fact that that's,
because that kind of thing was supposed to come down,
but part of me was like kind of scared
just to hit those poles.
I feel like I was like,
I'm scared I'm gonna take the whole second floor down.
That would be so bad.
Like I take a giant swing, hit one of those podiums.
And then all of a sudden, like me and Kit
just dropped through the floor,
like home alone two.
But you went during the party back up there
with the sledgehammer to hit those actual
like connecting frames.
You were on some shit at that party, man.
You were like, this is the final scene.
I'm gonna do whatever I want.
Well, it was like the end of the stream.
It was like, it was the end of the whole week.
I was like, fuck it, let's just swing it.
We talked a few minutes ago about
how things sort of came to happen as the show went on.
And we had like, we had a finite number of costumes
and a finite number of props,
but like exactly what was gonna happen with them
wasn't like predefined.
So I have a cool little clip here of Kit coming with Milton,
who's the prisoner, out onto stage.
And what I think is cool about this clip,
nothing particularly exciting happens in it,
but it kind of gives you the perspective of
they leave the green room to come to the stage.
What is that process like?
Was it raining?
It was raining.
So we could barely hear each other talking.
Yeah, it was leaking too, right?
You guys talk about it yet?
No.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, I would pause it and talk about that for one second.
So during this portion here, when it was actually,
it was pouring like monsoon type rain.
And when they were inside, Kit and Milton,
we could barely even hear,
it was like talking over a vacuum cleaner.
And one of the things that was happening backstage was,
and there's a part of the stream where I look up
and I'm getting hit in the face by water.
And I don't know if you got it or not.
I think it was right here.
Yeah, it's like right at this point here.
I'm getting hit directly in the face by water.
And it was just real water coming from the ceiling.
And Jake, maybe you can logistically talk about where it was,
but it was like a transformer.
Yeah, right behind this wall.
Well, Kit is the one that saw it, right?
Oh, Kit, it was you, Kit.
It's like right next to us.
Milton and I, yeah, it's right behind where we were.
We just heard water pouring.
What is that?
And so he tells Josh who's standing back,
and I wonder if it's even in this clip actually,
where he tells him, I'll lower the audio here
so it's not rounding us out.
But yeah, so I get a call on the radio.
Josh is like, hey, Jake, we got some leakage.
And like a few people had mentioned,
cause like we knew there were a couple spots on the set
where water would come down.
We knew it wasn't gonna be a problem or whatever.
And Josh is like, no, no, no, this is down
by the transformer.
And I'm like, oh God, hang on one second.
So I come back there and I don't know
if we actually have any photos of the transformer set up,
but the-
Imagine electrical stuff.
There's two, yeah, there's these two transformers
that are the size of a car, like a small car,
like a beetle and then maybe like a large motorcycle
like next to each other.
And they take, we hit 480 volt service
and they step it down to what we need
for the lights and the motors and stuff.
And sure as shit, there's water coming down
like a foot away from one of these transformers.
And so I run to get a bucket and Josh runs
to get like some towels or something and clean it up.
And like we were fine, everything was cool.
And thankfully the rain only lasted
for like 20 or 25 minutes.
So it just kind of came and then it went
and it was over with.
But it was just like, it was just our luck.
And so while it was happening,
we didn't know how much it was picking up on the mics.
Fortunately, it wasn't that much.
Mark did a good job with some noise suppression and stuff.
But if you notice closely in those scenes,
we set the TV monitors inside the rooms
and the outside graphic to be raining.
So it looked like it's raining.
So if you did hear any rain noise,
you would at least think, oh, they're adding rain noise.
And then the person that talks to Jeremy in his ear
also made sure to have him say multiple times
about how it's raining and look out the window and stuff.
So we tried to cover that stuff.
And we did have the power outage thing too.
So that was like, oh, rain and storms can happen.
When you told me it was raining and you held your hand out,
I think it's around the scene.
I just ignored it and pretended you were crazy.
But yeah, it was real rain.
Oh yeah, there's a part where I'm just like
going like this in front of you and it's hitting my hand.
I think it's like right around here where you,
this scene, but yeah.
This also gives you an idea
of what they can see backstage, right?
You could see basically a security camera view
of every room to get an idea of where people are
for if you're planning improv ideas and whatnot.
And they could see chat, they could see you guys going by
and they could see what you see.
Yeah, Josh was a huge-
You had like a beautiful moment with the rain.
What was that?
I was just saying that he had a beautiful moment
with the rain where it was hitting his head.
But you were saying about Josh?
Oh yeah.
Just gonna say Josh was a huge asset for us
because in terms of like coming out and queuing us up
for what was gonna happen,
that was me saying, can I go to the bathroom?
Oh yeah.
So he would figure us for going to the bathroom.
I remember that because then someone on call was like,
all right, queue kit and mill in
and Josh is like, he's in the bathroom.
All right, Jeremy, you need to be up for 30 more seconds.
There was a point where I ran to the bathroom too.
Oh, he was a rock star.
Yeah, there was a point where I ran away
and peed in like the urinal.
And I think I said over the mic, I was like,
I hope I'm not on,
I hope you have my mics at zero
because you can probably just hear me pissing.
Yeah, there was only one moment I can remember
where we cut to like the wide shot of the house
when they're picking a room
and you were not in bed
because you were going to the bathroom
and we're like, someone just finally said in the mics like,
could you hear it?
Not there, is he?
No, no, we couldn't hear you.
We couldn't hear you.
We had the mics up.
It was joking.
He just vanished overnight and chat slowly was like,
wait, where is he?
Oh no, what happened to our streamer?
And then like, we cut back and we're back.
This is a moment I have of when God enters the scene
and this is actual behind the scenes footage
as it happens as it plays out.
We should do a version of this with crew audio too.
That'd be good.
Yeah.
I need you this way.
Quick, quick.
Here, go.
Gotta get his car ready.
Quick.
Go!
That's like pretty much what it was like,
but it was great.
Grossly car.
Oh yeah, those shoes, by the way,
are about a half the size of my feet.
Like, I was.
But it's the real thing, you know?
There's like multiple moments that hit me
while we were running this thing, just like.
And this thing goes so slow.
Like, was this, was this low on battery?
Cause this thing goes so slow.
There was a faster option,
but I was terrified of just running to the side of the set.
So I was like, I'll just go slowly towards him.
This scene has to be sacrilegious.
Yeah.
I might be going to hell for this.
Oh, I'm sure it is.
I'm in a clown car.
Yeah, pearly gates is going to look at you, Greg,
and he's going to be like, really?
The clown car?
Yeah.
There he goes.
It's so slow.
Well, I thought they were going to just have
a little juice back there.
It really is slow.
Oh my gosh.
I thought it was running out of batteries.
I was like, oh shit,
it doesn't like run out of the batteries.
It has to go like 80 feet.
That's like the size of most kids' yards.
I almost ate shit there, by the way.
I almost tripped on the door.
He pooped his pants.
Did you guys talk about the rehearsal version of this scene?
Oh, the realistic diarrhea going into a toilet
real fully of a human shitting.
Yeah, we have.
I thought that I couldn't hear the effects.
But watching you guys spur the moment improv,
what it could have been was pretty wild.
It was pretty nuts.
Jeremy won't let us play the original clip.
Yeah.
He won't let you release the cut.
That's funny.
I don't release the cut.
You don't release the cut.
I remember hearing the sounds where I was.
I don't know if I could hear the sounds.
Maybe it's worse with all of the effects.
It'll be on the DVD extras.
The DVD extra.
Maybe after Jeremy retires, we'll leak it.
That's what sat you to limitation just goes away.
It was just fucked up.
It was just like a fucked up sequence.
I've sat in the toilet for four straight minutes
because we didn't have all the other stuff.
It was a nightmare.
You said, guys, what are we going to do if they pick nightmare?
And then you guys sort of improv'd
this terrifying nightmare scene.
Right after this, you're like, I did not like that.
And we're like, that's the point.
That's the point.
No, we didn't like that.
We're like, we can't do that.
I was like, I really didn't like that.
I don't want that in the show.
I didn't like it.
It was crazy.
What's your favorite moment?
My favorite moment?
I loved the dream sequence.
It was scary.
It was really scary, especially the rehearsal.
But then after watching back the one that aired,
it definitely was scarier than I realized in real time.
And so I think that was probably my favorite moment.
I think my second favorite moment was at the end,
after they decide to reset.
And we have one character after another after another
come into the scene.
And it's this callback to all these different characters
throughout the show.
And they're pleading with chat.
It's like, come on, guys.
It's time.
We got to do this.
You got to reset the game.
Stop it now.
We got to end it.
Yeah, exactly.
And the fact that chat really is the one that made it happen
and to complete the loop is just a really neat moment for me.
I 100% agree.
I also really loved, because originally, Edna.
We weren't sure who it was going to be,
because could we get that actual audio to work
and actually having you be able to be Edna with the voice
changer and actually have it work?
That was one of my favorite things of the week, too.
I love the cookies coming out.
I'm glad it worked, because when I do her voice,
normally I hear it in my headphones.
And I didn't there.
And so I didn't know if it was sounding correctly
the whole time.
And I was afraid, what if this sounds terrible?
Yeah, Kit, one of the things that Lauren and I
were talking about behind the scenes
and when we were planning all the different who should show up
and when, was your Edna character is so different
from every other character we had on the show.
Just energy and the comedy and just the way
the dynamic between Jerma and you in those scenes
was so different.
It felt like an awesome breath of fresh air.
I really enjoyed it.
It was so funny.
Yeah.
Oh, that's great.
It was perfect.
That's awesome.
I love when you went to the bathroom.
I was waiting for that.
Yeah, I was hoping.
I don't know what happened with the audio,
but I was hoping that you guys would do some goofy effects
with the audio there.
Yeah, they got their chance.
I think everybody got their sound effect
in the bathroom there.
OK, good.
Got at least one fart in.
Everybody got at least one bathroom gag.
So everyone got to fart or poop in the toilet,
which is kind of gross, but whatever.
That's how it goes.
I don't know if anyone talked about it yet,
but I don't think I'm the only one.
But there was something, sorry if this sounds cliche
or whatever, but there were a lot of moments
where Jerma walked around like a giddy little school
girl, really excited about particularly jumping
through the window.
But it was pretty cool to see, I don't know,
just the way you were watching it all come together
and just living it out.
It was pretty wild.
I actually, I have this clip of Jeremy
seeing the house for the first time
inside the trailer where we had the graphic.
Oh, the cut up from the cut away.
With the graphic overlay, yeah.
She's like walking around in there.
It looks like a sign film.
You disappear between the rooms.
I'm just imagining like, oh, Jeremy.
It's like Kramer Dunford.
Yeah, like this is ridiculous.
That's insane.
Well, I want to like do the stream now.
You know what I mean?
I just want to like start it.
God, this is awesome.
I really did.
Yeah, you were so excited.
Just so many props back there and just like.
Well, it's just awesome to see something
like this come together.
It just, never in my wildest dreams that I think that,
and I was making TF2 YouTube videos like 10 years ago
and it's like, we were able to put this together
and do this now.
It's just, I never would have thought this was ever possible.
So watching, being able to actually like go and play
with the giant toy that was made
with 30, 40 plus people that had involvement in it.
It was just, it was surreal.
It was a surreal experience
and I will never forget it until the day I die.
Yeah, I think it carried over for us too.
Like you had definitely an infectious energy
and just, you know, the kids had excitement
like seeing you just kind of dive into every scene
and just live it, made it a lot easier for all of us
to like wrap around how your dynamic was
and I think it definitely showed,
especially like, you know, the second and third day,
I think like, first day being the test,
I think by second and third day,
we really hit our stride and it really turned out great.
Yeah, I could, I literally couldn't be happier.
You're just super positive.
You're so, I asked you maybe 17 times after it ended
what you thought about the ending
because I felt a lot of pressure
because it, you know, it involved a lot of me and Amelia.
So I was like, man, I hope he liked that
because you had planned day two ending so precisely,
day three ending was like, I don't know what's gonna happen.
We're just, we're gonna figure it out
and so I asked him like, I think like 17 times,
like, what do you think?
Like, how was it?
He's like, oh, it was great.
Oh, it was perfect.
Oh, it couldn't have been better
and I was like, oh, great
and I kept asking because I just felt so self-conscious
at all times.
Yeah.
You guys were unbelievable.
You guys were hilarious.
You were funny.
You could just implant yourself anywhere
and that's why you were on the show to begin with.
That was part of it, right?
Is I've watched your streams, all of you guys here
and you can do it.
I couldn't have asked for like a better,
like cast and crew and it was unbelievable.
I don't wanna get emotional.
I promised I wouldn't get emotional
on the behind the scenes stream.
I promised I wouldn't.
This is the kind of shit that I wanna do more of.
I wanna see more of this stuff
and I think that over the coming years,
let's keep doing them.
I think that there's a lot of potential
to keep kind of trying to just do fun stuff
and just try, right?
Because look, this could have been a fucking disaster.
This could have been the shittiest stream on Twitch.
Yeah, but it happened, right?
That's what I was thinking
when I was hyperventilating in my car an hour
before we started the stream on Wednesday.
This could have been just an absolute fucking train wreck
but you try.
You try to do something that you think is fun.
That's it.
Yeah.
Thanks to everybody who participated,
to Kit, to Ludwig, to Kraikin, to Milton,
to Micah, to Randy, obviously to Ray
for bearing that costume.
I feel so bad for him.
Bearing the costume.
There were so many just superheroes of the week
that it'd be impossible to kind of,
it was everybody.
Everybody had this thing that they were doing.
This is like the thing that's really to know
and why at the end of the stream it was like,
get everybody on here
because if you were on set as,
oh, I'm a, you know, I'm a fuck, I'm the audio guy.
Like you did like three or four other things
that were not just I'm the audio guy.
If you were, oh, I was putting the Tress up.
Did I say that right, Tress?
Yeah.
Like some of these people were actors.
Some of the people were like the shadow people.
People had like three or four different roles
that weren't just the thing that they came to show up.
Vinny, the editor, he was supposed to just come
and take video for the behind the scenes shit
and he did like seven people's jobs.
It was ridiculous.
So it's impossible without all the people
that got to do, hopefully had a lot of fun
and got to do multiple things
that they thought were interesting.
I think this is probably a good place to end it
unless, Jeremy, did you want to take one or two questions
from chat for our guests?
I think we should take a couple if we can.
Yeah, that'd be great.
So if you've got questions from the chat-
Especially with Kit and Ludwig here.
Yeah, you should add Kit, add Ludwig, add Kraikin, add-
Jeremy, if you have a specific question for one of them
and we-
How hot was it on set?
It was a perfect temperature.
It was fine.
Unless you wore like the bear costume,
Ludwig says it's hot.
He doesn't think so.
It got a bit toasty, like, well, I got to like get off.
I got to like relax in the green room.
But when I had to take over for a bit
and like lie down there,
especially when you're doing something physical
and you start sweating, I don't know.
You were a trooper, that was hot.
Oh, physically on in the dollhouse was hot, yeah.
Yeah.
But like being able to like get out of that room.
And I did a few times too.
A lot of the times when it went to the,
kind of the transition sequence
where it was buying something and here's like an ad.
I got up and I was able to get out of there
and just kind of get some water, walk around.
So I wasn't just like stuck in there permanently,
but yeah, it was pretty warm in there.
It was an air conditioned facility,
which makes a big difference too.
Like even though it was hot in the set,
it was that much cooler than it would have been
because we were fortunate
that the facility was somewhat air conditioned.
We then put hundreds and hundreds of pounds of curtains
in front of the air conditioner,
but it was still air conditioned.
I've got a question here for Kit and Jeremy.
Talk about the pink paint, pink, pink, paint.
Pink?
I think he hadn't, he was using an accent, right?
And I'm saying pink.
I think I was doing something like that.
I guess I must've said pink.
I must've said pink or something.
And then I heard that back in production
and I was like, did you say pink?
And so I was like, I just made a notification
of like minus 20 bucks for pink, pink.
And then that was the notification at the top.
Oh, I don't know if I was saying it for paint or pink.
Yeah, who knows?
I think you said pink, pink.
Yeah, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink.
And then I called it pink, pink.
And then we're like,
we're telling Blair to tell Jeremy
to bring up the pink thing.
And you must've been so confused
why you were being told to call it pink.
I had no idea what was going on.
I was like, hey, bring up pink.
And I'm like, what?
I was like, what is pink?
What are you talking about?
I didn't know what to say.
I thought it was like a bit that Jeb had.
Like, oh, he's gonna do this pink thing.
Not really.
I tried to, some of the voices and characters I did
had a little bit of like lore from some of the scam calls,
but I tried to just mostly focus on the dollhouse,
so I didn't really bring anything over.
Excuse me, Jeb.
I missed that.
I missed so many references.
You love saying Jeb.
Not a single time.
He did Jeb.
I just kept doing it.
I just kept going, oh, Jeb.
Yeah, excuse me, Jeb.
Jeb is a mess.
I think, honestly, I really think I said that probably 30 to 40 times,
at least.
In hindsight, yeah.
I saw someone ask about, oh, go ahead.
No, go ahead.
Someone asked about the Jerma inviting Edna to the party,
which you had mentioned previously in a different segment,
which, I mean, yeah, the quick statement was just,
I was suited up as the police officer
because I think Ludwig was going to talk to me or something.
There was some storyline progression,
and then Jerma said, I want to invite Edna to the party,
and so I just had to switch.
I ran all the way back,
and at one point was like taking my clothes off in the green room.
I think you still had the lipstick on as the police officer.
Yeah, the cop had lipstick on when he came back out, it was amazing.
You still had the lipstick.
Everyone told me to do that.
I was going to take it off.
I was like, no, it's funny.
OK.
Is there a video on the second floor?
Ludwig and Kraken, someone in chat wants to know about the good dream.
What would have happened with the good dream?
We brainstormed a couple of things.
I don't think we like...
I think it was like I was a cowboy,
so some sort of like cool cowboy maybe fights like a gladiator
because we had a gladiator costume.
Yeah, just something like random, but like, you know, maybe cooler
or badass.
We also played around with like kind of like a sexy dream,
where like, you know, it was kind of like he was being puppeted around.
And like, there's also a version of it, I think, where we had the same kitchen
thing where everyone was like laughing at him, but there's instead like cheering
for him. So it's like a version of that dream.
But like, everyone's, you know, happy to see him.
You're the greatest, you're so wonderful.
Weren't they congratulating you on a good poop?
Yeah, it was like the end of the Evangelion scene,
but you just pooped and everyone was there and like, congratulations.
You're like, we're so proud of you.
Yeah, yeah, I think that's because they told us when we were going in the kitchen
that, yeah, whether it was good or bad, we would find out
and that we were either to cheer and say good job or make fun of them. Yeah. Yeah.
Another question for Ludwig,
but I guess probably also very applicable to Kit is when did
when did you get involved with the project?
Like, how did that happen?
And are you open to further collaborations?
Um, Kate, you run it first.
I would never want to work with it.
No, I, I don't prefer.
Yeah, after this, I will never speak to you.
Yeah, I would be delighted to do anything with any of you.
It was a blast. I will never forget it.
Tons of great,
improv moments and like Ludwig, you had mentioned
just being able to vibe his vibe, a word that kids use vibe off of each other
and come up younger by the day.
Yeah. Come up with ideas.
Seeing Ludwig's hair in real life.
There was lots of good moments.
But the I think it was a couple.
You gave me a couple of months notice.
I think Jerma and Jake, you guys, like,
DMed me on Discord and said, hey, we're thinking about a dollhouse thing.
Would you be interested?
And you didn't give me a ton of detail.
I just said, yeah, I think I gave you a call in like maybe March or April
because I saw your name on the whiteboard there from the meeting that we had in May.
Oh, yeah. And you were you were you were pretty well
like it was a known you were a known quantity at that point.
So then you did give me quite a bit of notice.
We didn't maybe we didn't really hash out
or didn't know exactly what it was, but you had mentioned.
Yeah. What do you want to tell the story of your involvement?
I don't know. I forget exactly what I weaseled my way into Jerma's life
and force him out of his twitch cavern that he hides in.
But I think it was some time because like the battleship thing we did
and then the tournament, I think it was right around then that you asked.
And it was like it was like twofold.
It was like one, you're like, hey, that was great.
Like that was that was that was fun.
Hey, totally random. I have this thing going on.
And then I was like, yeah, it sounds great.
And then like a day later later, you're like, by the way, for like
you happen to have a sponsor, too.
And I'm like, this is all right.
Let him show why I call it.
I was just curious. I was just curious. I was just curious.
Yeah. Yeah. And we were so I was I was like, yeah,
I was instantly down because and I think you're surprised.
Were you surprised?
Well, because I think it's because it was yeah, it was it was such short notice
because it was like I think two or three weeks out from the show.
And I'm like, he's probably got a lot of shit going on.
You probably look, I understand you have to treat this travel involved.
If you don't, I understand.
And you're just like, no, I'm game.
I'm like, you're game.
All right. This is perfect.
Cool. Yeah. Come on.
You mentioned Ludwig.
I at first assumed it was like a different Ludwig
that I didn't know of.
No, that's a different one.
We got like a celebrity impersonator.
Celebrity impersonator.
Oh, that's really pretty funny, though.
Yeah, like an impersonator of just like a different streamer.
Oh, but like a doctor.
I think I'm actually the doc.
Just the hair and the mustache.
Terrible. Yeah.
But honestly, it was after we did the battleship stuff
when you and I did the battleship thing back and forth with, you know, the shirt
that, you know, maybe one day I'll do that.
I'm probably not, though.
Hopefully not. You just don't know.
I'll buy it. We had a blast.
Like the thing with like kind of collabing with people and stuff.
And I have to like mesh with somebody.
You know what I mean?
And during those streams, I was like, this is fun.
These are bouncing back and forth.
He's a funny motherfucker.
I like this dude a lot.
So it was really, really simple to like reach out to you
because it was just like, oh, that was great.
Because you never want to have a scenario, right?
Will you? It's tricky to.
Oh, let's let's ask this person if they want to be involved.
Never speaking to. I've never talked to them.
Don't know what their what their deal is.
I have no idea how they how they are, how they are off camera.
Are they somebody I would mesh with?
And then you get in the same room we get on camera.
It's like, are you ready?
You're going to do like the show that, you know, a guy that I don't know
that I never talked to, do I have any chemistry with?
I don't like doing that. Yeah.
So, yeah.
Craig, do you want to talk? It's very simple.
Do you want to talk for a quick second about Ghost Commander
and your involvement, how that kind of went down?
Maybe plug your stuff.
I mean, as I mentioned earlier, we like I've known Jeremy for a few years now
since we did like role play stuff in games almost in a while.
And then at one of the Twitch cons, we started talking about,
you know, ambitious projects we had at that point.
I had started Ghost Commander with Lauren.
It's basically our interactive
Twitch production company.
So we build both technology and shows that are like, you know, viewer integrated.
And so I was telling him about some of the stuff that we were working on.
And he was like, oh, I had this idea for, you know, a dollhouse show or like,
you know, I play like basically a sim in a house.
And so we started shooting the shit and like, oh, this sounds really fun.
We'd love to collaborate on this should it ever happen.
But then, like, you know, two years later,
you guys managed to secure the money and you called me back up
and you're like, all right, I think we want to we want to actually explore
how we could do this.
And so we, you know, hopped on a plane and went out to see what we could do.
And that's kind of how the whole brainstorm happened
and then built the whole thing over the next couple of months.
And here we are. So and make no mistake about it.
The without the Ghost Commander team and without the extension,
we can't do the stream. The stream doesn't even work.
We like can't even physically go live without having that.
So it was the catalyst to even be able to do it in the first place.
So forever grateful. Thank you.
Yeah. I mean, if you want any other time, like the cool thing
that what we're building is every one of these shows we do, we're like
our code base gets like stronger and we have more learned knowledge.
So now that we've done this, like we know how to like balance an economy
for like a hundred thousand people, which, by the way,
I don't know if you've shared any of I mean, we we've been looking at
some of the records of the extension usage and we broke Twitch records.
We there were more people using the extension than chatting.
And holy shit. Whoa.
Yeah. It was north of like 65 percent of the viewership was
was using the extension to click on stuff, which is not a thing.
Yeah. So we're we're overjoyed that it went so well.
And it's also put us in a cool position to be able to work on
more stuff like this, you know, both with you and with other streamers
and whoever really wants to.
So yeah, it was the scariest thing.
I think like a week before the show,
we were in a call and you guys were showing the extension.
And you're just kind of like it was like a it was done,
but there was still a couple more things you had left to do.
I think I asked a hundred times.
I was like, so is this going to work?
Is this is this what if what if what if this happens?
Is it going to break? What if it breaks?
What if we do this? What happens if it breaks?
And you're like, no, it's it's going to be good, man.
It's not going to break.
And I was like, what if it breaks?
It's going to break like I was having these panic attacks
like a week before the stream.
But then after that first day, it was just like, holy shit,
this thing like worked pretty much without a hitch at all.
There was like a minor like that small problem with like the sorting thing.
But how in the name of God, you guys were able to handle
30,000, 40,000 inputs like a second.
I can't believe it. I can't.
I actually showed some.
I don't I'm actually traveling right now, so I don't have the pictures on me.
But I showed some of the heat maps of the placements
because people thought the placements might have been rigged
because we didn't show exactly where they placed it.
But that's because we had 30,000 inputs to sort and visualize.
And so what we got was this like disgusting
like rash of like different clips on screen.
And we had to like interpret that as, oh, they want to block the door. Right.
And then we would like try to position.
We tell the production team to put the spotlight at the door to put the item there.
But yeah, it was insane.
And we have I can share those pictures with you later, Jake, if you want it.
But yeah, that'd be great.
We're going to do we're doing we're doing a BTS
reel for YouTube.
And so I'd love to get some of that stuff in there, too.
Sure thing. Thanks.
I was asking about the stairs.
If you wanted to show that real quick, too. Oh, sure. Yeah.
So yeah, I was asking about the access, the access in the back
because you can't see that from the camera side.
The original plan was actually to put these stairs in that space
between the bathroom and the bedroom between the pink and the blue room there.
But we realized if you put stairs or you couldn't get furniture up the stairs.
So we had to put the stairs in the back here to have access for the furniture up.
But this is what it looks like without the drain.
It's the kind of thing, too, where the stairs had to be built
oversized in order to accommodate wide furniture is the kind of thing
you don't think about without having to like build a set.
So they had to be built oversized staircase.
So with extra wide, they could get a couch up if that was picked.
And then every stair also gets marked with a tape that glows in the dark.
Interacting in the dark back there.
So everything would get marked with stuff to help me.
It's actually pretty funny because this this up the stairs, Jake,
I don't remember like two or three years ago when we first even floated the idea.
I was like the only reason why I the only reason why I want to start
process on the stream is because I just I keep seeing this image in my head
of two or three people in spandex suits just trying to carry a couch upstairs,
like into a bedroom, like being controlled by chat.
And I was like, that's that was the reason to do it.
That was the only reason why I wanted to do it.
And you guys know we made it happen.
There's this and there they are.
This is going up the stairs, like watching guys with like, yeah.
And you saw earlier the stream that Nick right there, he was here earlier.
They were unbelievable.
They were so these guys are so funny.
They're so talented.
They're like seven hundred
IQ engineer brains and they're funny and they're talented.
It's like they're like perfectly rounded humans.
It's why we keep working with them.
They're unbelievable.
Well, I think this is probably a good point for us to wrap our show.
A huge big thank you to.
Oh, yeah. Kit, what's up?
I don't want to totally interrupt, but do you happen to have a shot of
at the very end after we ended stream?
And for like 15 minutes, everyone just stood there and chat was saying
thanks and clapping for like, yes, forever.
That shot does exist.
That was a very surreal moment for me.
We just all like the whole crew is just sitting there.
And that was going crazy.
Yeah, I think he told us that there was something like,
I don't know how many tens of thousands of people there after it was over to.
I got a text from from someone at Twitch that was like,
you know, you've had a good show when you're you've you finished
and you're on your your end credits and you still have 90,000 people in chat.
Like it's just it's it was such a cool feeling to be
have been off screen for 10 minutes and still have 90,000 people there.
That was that was just going back and looking at the screen
and chat was still like, thanks, Clem. It was nuts.
Yeah. A lot of the production team like ran for the on stage
fridge and just grabbed beers out of there like we did it.
And then we just look and it's time that's all clapping.
Yeah, it was it was very surreal and euphoric kind of experience.
I think there's a clip of that in the outro that we had this idea.
We had this original idea where it was like, you
how like, oh, yeah, how many people do we get on the on the archaeology stream?
Oh, that was like forty seven thousand people, fifty thousand people.
Holy shit. Imagine if we got like forty thousand people again.
And then we looked over at some point
at the last moment of the last 45 minutes of the stream.
It was over 100,000 people there.
And I remember I think that look, I think you were backstage at one point.
You were like, yeah, just broke 100k.
And I was like, wait, what happened?
And I looked over and I'm like, holy shit.
So, yeah, that was that was more than we ever thought.
We're ever going to get on the stream.
I remember keeping an eye on it because everybody was really excited
about hitting that number, you know, and I was like, yeah, that'd be dope.
And so I did it. It was.
It was dope. It was a cool number.
That's what the kids say.
Dope. That is busting.
If you want to use that one, too. OK.
I'm going to pull next all house.
Oh, yeah. The next.
Yeah. The dollhouse stream, too, when we have like eight bedrooms.
Don't say that. Stop.
I'm going to give you a heart attack.
It's a month long stream. It doesn't end.
And there's a roof pool.
Oh, my God. Roof pool.
And now we're talking with water in it.
Yeah. Did you talk about the almost water pool that happened?
No, we didn't.
So, yeah, that that pool was going to be full with water
until the day before, like until I think you talked about it
while the stream was happening, right? Yeah. Yeah.
Live, I remember you talking about like, hey, this was have water in it.
But we thought that against that.
Yeah, it was all going to happen.
I remember. Yeah.
Jeremy, you were like, yeah, it's going to be like 100 pounds of water, right?
And Jacob, you're like, no, that's thousands of pounds of water.
Yeah, it's nine thousand pounds of water.
It's a 1200 gallon pool and a gallon of water.
I'm just like, do we like we don't really need it to be full of water.
I mean, we're using it for like it's one day.
Do we really? We don't need that much.
We don't need a pool in here because that was like logistically
when the stream was done, somebody has to get rid of that.
Like somebody has to take that somewhere.
What do you do? What do you do with it?
So I was like, just don't even put water in it.
There's no reason to.
Oh, no, my cam froze.
This is oh, boy. Oh, you're still here.
We can hear you. Yeah.
You look good.
I want to take a I want to take a moment to plug
our merch site, a little bit of backstory on the merch because
we've we've seen it on Reddit and stuff.
So the the plan for the merch came together before
Ludwig's involvement and Coinbase's involvement because we were flat broke.
I mean, we were in the hole a lot of money
and we were like, oh, my God, how are we going to
how are we going to pay for this?
Like, we're going to have bills due and we're not going to be able to pay them.
And so we decided to launch a merch line.
And that's what we did.
And so we did some kind of generic merch, the t-shirts and the
and the sweatshirts, which are pretty cool.
We did the special edition, the green one and commissioned that poster.
But obviously, we didn't have any content yet from the show.
But we were like, we just have to we have to put something out there.
And then we kind of came up with this idea of, OK, after the show airs,
we can sell a bunch of the stuff that was that were props on the show.
So if you go over to the site, German 95 dot com,
there's a link out to our eBay store where we have a whole bunch of props
for sale that were that were used on the show.
And we also have worked with some community artists.
And we are now selling some fan art posters and stickers.
So you can go and check those out and order those,
support the community, support the artists in the community
and help support the show.
So that's my plug.
I'm sorry I had to do it, but it's part of my job.
So German 95 dot com, go check it out.
Do it only if you want to do it now.
But you could. And the auctions, when do the auctions end?
The auctions end tomorrow night, basically.
Tomorrow night, like Pacific time.
Like, is there a certain time?
Yeah, Alex, what's the I think they end at one a.m.
Eastern on the second.
So I would say by yeah, that's 10 p.m. Pacific.
They say, oh, they say out of stock,
but they're not actually out of the click through.
You got to go to the eBay click.
Yeah, it is.
It is anyway.
There's too many layers of friction, I will tell you.
I think the eBay should just bring you to the the seller.
If you link it directly to the cell.
Well, we when we built the store, we had a problem
because it was a new eBay account.
And when you list things on a new eBay account, the seller page
won't display the eBay auction items.
Now that we have hundreds of bids, that does work.
But we would have to go back and change the infrastructure on.
Day battleships going for a penny, bro.
I was just going for it's at four twenty six or four twenty five sixty nine.
Why are you so why are you currently bidding on it right now?
Why is this on screen?
These were the options for your bed.
Remember, I I sent you a text.
I sent you a text.
Which sheet set do you want?
And you picked the gamer ones.
I like that there's the glass on sale because that is going to be
the most fun thing to ship is.
Well, it's Hollywood glass.
It just shows up as like a bunch of pieces.
I think we have a disclaimer.
We don't we don't insure it.
Oh, man. That's a sick item.
Site is dead.
Well, it's probably 20,000 people clicking on it at the same time.
Yeah, it's been serviced, whatever it is.
The eBay seller name eBay seller.
Yeah, the eBay seller is Elberton and Sons.
And we get the highest priced item is the signed costume package,
which includes the taped watch and the drinking hat.
And your signature looks great on that one.
I think I have a clip of him signing that maybe I'll add some value if I play that.
Just so you know, we didn't like it once and we just printed it.
How the fuck you how are you going to OK, whoever gets the mailbox?
It's a real huge mailbox.
You put it in front of your house.
That's definitely an interesting item.
This is real.
I mean, I would just like all the posters.
It's kind of fun.
Work your way through.
Yeah, I know I have a clip of him.
If you win, if you win the helmet, message me and I'll get you the clip of him
signing the helmet, because I know I have that one somewhere.
Oh, that's cool. Not fake. Not fake.
Yeah, but where do you put the mailbox?
You can put that in front of your house or like where do you do it?
It's a real mailbox.
You like petition the town to change your house number to 985
so that you can use the mailbox.
One, two, three, nine, eight, five, the plaque.
One, two, three. Yeah, just put it right here.
Didn't someone find like a dollhouse lane in like one of the videos?
Wait, is there actually a dollhouse lane?
Is there really? I think so.
I didn't want to say like a real place.
I'm like, nine, eight, five, nine, eight, five dollhouse way.
And I'm just like, that can't be a real fucking place.
I don't know if people saw to on Jeremy on your plaque.
I don't know if people saw the there's a little detail kind of hidden on that plaque.
Oh, there is. There is.
Yeah, my look, I was doing waist up today.
So like I didn't think I was going to have to.
I was like, look, I look I look like like I have a good shirt on.
I have like a nice like V neck on.
Just stay low. I don't care. I'm weird.
I'm not looking.
And I think you can see me from the from the waist down.
I was staring. I couldn't see it.
The folks at Andy Mark built a little piece into that for you.
I see it on the top there.
Yeah, that's cool.
That's a little hard to see, but the logo is engraved on the top.
So the logo is engraved.
You can see it when it shines.
Now I try to.
Oh, here, wait, I'll bring it back.
I'll bring it back.
It's weird because my camera's delayed.
Yeah, you can see it. There it goes.
Yeah. Yeah, you got it.
That's it right there. Yeah.
Yeah, it's awesome.
Very, very lovely stuff.
It was a nice touch.
I remember I felt like Nick, like, showed me this and like handed it.
It was like, yeah, we look at that.
And I was like, I was so touched.
I was just like, hold it together.
Hold it together. Hold it together.
I can't like, you know, at times I like tried to not like cry.
Like, it's like the last day, especially, I was like, thanks for coming.
It was like so difficult to like, just tear the water.
And then the day after when we were tearing down and you came by the set,
you like came by the set for like a minute.
And then you just like went to the office
because I think you were just so upset about the whole thing coming down.
It was just it was it was sad.
Yeah, I just think everybody was taking cords down, was dropping stuff.
And I was just like, oh, it's sad.
But it was fun. Now on to the next one, right?
Absolutely.
I think if we're cool, we'll leave it here.
This has been it for the Dollhouse and the Dollhouse crew.
Thank you so much to our wonderful talent that's here with us, our fantastic crew.
At least he's smiling.
I'm doing what I can.
For a second, I thought, whoa, it just moved.
He's shaking it when he talks.
I'm moving it when I talk.
What? Oh, I thought like, OK, that was freaking me out.
I was like, why isn't it moving?
Everybody's talking about it.
I appreciate you a little bit.
I got you. Hold on.
Although I'm out of focus.
There we go. There we go.
Yeah. Yeah.
We're going to go to that corner.
Yeah, can we? Is there a way we can do that?
I think we can do that.
Sure. He's going to get on his knees.
I can't. I have to shake my camera by actually shaking my desk.
Oh, no, the immersion.
We're in these squares. Well.
This is adorable. Thank you.
I can't move this.
We're stuck in the chairs.
All right, Chad, vote and BTS stream.
Vote BTS, please, we need to go home.
Well, I have to wait before we end the stream.
I got to say this, too.
Yeah, I I'm going to be live tomorrow.
Like, we're going back to kind of normal.
So I'll be live tomorrow.
I'm going to play Hard Time, that like prison game where you're like in prison.
It's M.
Dickie, the wrestling wrestling game guy.
I know that game. Yeah.
Yeah, it looks like fucking it looks insane.
So I'll be back tomorrow.
Well, I'll just check the sauce.
I want to make sure I got that out so people knew that I was coming back tomorrow.
And we're back this weekend on probably Friday or Saturday.
Probably starting No More Heroes 3.
Going to be a fun one. Been waiting for that one.
Can we plug everybody?
I mean, everybody knows who these guys are.
They're fucking they're absolute lads.
I'm going to do some plug.
Hey, you know, we can't be doing our thing going on.
We can't be doing our thing.
Twitch.TV4 slash get buggy.
You know, you know where to find us at.
Oh, thanks for involving us.
Thanks for inviting me.
It was a blast.
It was great working with all you guys.
You, too, Ludwig.
Hey, and when you invited me to that sleepover the first night
and you had that like that little milk carton, the warm milk for me.
Yeah, you know, I do what I can, man.
I do what I can.
I was a little hurt when you said you wouldn't stay the night,
but it is what it is.
Lost on that one.
I'm joking.
I do have to say thank you
for getting me a way nicer room than Jerma for no reason.
People don't know about that, but they hooked me up.
They hooked me up with the room, the ride and the flight.
I was making a joke the whole time.
I was like, oh, hey, by the way, I'm in the presidential suite.
I've got three bedrooms under the presidential.
And I wasn't at all. I was just in a regular room.
And then he was like, wait, that's the room I'm in.
I'm like, no, what are you talking about?
He's like, yeah, I'm in like I'm in the fucking suite, dude.
And I'm like, you got a suite.
I didn't like I actually thought you're making the joke.
We made the joke every night.
I thought you knew because we both that you didn't have a suite at all.
I went into your room. I was like, I don't think this.
I didn't think anybody had a suite.
So I was like making the joke that like, oh, I get the suite. Right.
But I just didn't. But you did.
I mean, Jerma called me.
Jerma called me and said, like, like, it's coming.
He's good. He's coming.
Like, like, you know, make arrangements.
And I'm like, fuck, I don't know what that means.
Like, what do I have to do?
And so he's like, yeah, it's the first class limousine.
We'll get him the presidential suite, like whatever.
Yeah, I don't live all the way.
And I'm pretty sure Jerma had to ask, like three wise men,
which direction the hotel was at.
It was beautiful.
I didn't say presidential suite.
I just said, oh, it's like, take care of him.
You know, it's like, I don't know.
It's like he's a fucking big guy.
He's like an important guy.
If it's not presidential, I don't show up.
Make notes.
Oh, make arrangements for him.
God. Make arrangements.
But long story short, yeah, I did not have that suite and he did.
And I was very surprised to hear about it.
It was like the last night, too, at the last possible minute.
Yeah.
Kraikin, you got a plug?
Yeah, you can catch me on Twitch at twitch.tv slash Kraikin.
I'm actually currently on vacation after dollhouse.
I need a little bit of time off.
So I'm I'm deserved, I think.
Yeah, I'm not going to be streaming that frequently for the next two weeks.
But then when I get back, we're doing more interactive streams like dollhouse.
If you like stuff like that, we do that all all the time on my show
as well as some other stuff.
So, yeah, I'm going to plug Jerma985.com
go buy some merch so I can pay my mortgage.
You just tore down a perfectly good house.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I'll be live tomorrow.
Thanks, everybody.
Thank you.
Thanks, guys. Thanks.
It was an unbelievable experience.
Yeah, I'll cherish it forever.
Thanks for your support, chat.
It means a lot. Bye.