I know, I know. I've seen it spamming chat. Listen, I know. I had to take a few important
phone calls and they happened at exactly 12 o'clock and then at 1230. So I'm sorry.
I'm very nervous because I've heard the voice crack. It's not four, it's not three, it's one.
That's pretty good. That's pretty good. That means I can stream for at least five to six
hours without running into 730 PM internet turn off issue. That's pretty good. I did say that like
between 12 and one, I did say one. I'm even late to being one, but whoa. What's going on?
Why is my Twitch dashboard saying that the stream is like dead? Is everything okay?
My Twitch dashboard, it has a bright red thing that is telling me that this is not good.
That's weird. Why is it showing me that? Okay. Well, whatever. We're going to play some Sims 4
again today. Same character, same world that we're in. The only difference today is I did install,
I want to say about maybe seven or eight mods. Some of them were wacky, but I don't, I'm going
to use them sparingly. I'm just going to make this really clear that everybody that thinks that I'm
going to be hanging out in the house and the person in the house is going to tell a bad joke
and I'm going to literally run them over with a car. I'm not going to do that. We're going to use
these very sparingly. All like the cartoon Tom and Jerry hit somebody in the head with a mallet
kind of shit. We're not doing that unless it's going to be very sparingly because I can't start
late. I have to start on time. I did. Just do it your way. All right. No, I didn't get any of those
mods. Why do you, what do you think for all the people that have been kind of bringing it up over
the last 12 to 15 hours or so you can, you can't, I can't do those mods. They're not allowed. They
are not allowed on Twitch. They're not allowed. Yeah. If you're a coward, no, if I'd like to keep
my channel active, well, I'm going to get banned from Twitch and indefinite ban from Twitch and
then write a tweet being like, yeah, at least I wasn't a coward. What, what? No. Oh, people ask.
Yeah. I want to mention this too. People asking about the VIP changes. So I, I completely removed
VIP as a role. I just, I just dropped it. There's only one VIP on this whole channel anymore.
And it's my girlfriend. So VIP is gone. I just got rid of it. I thought maybe, oh, would I give it
to like other streamers or game devs? No, just the whole thing is gone. Just get rid of the whole
thing. Get rid of it. Nepotism. Good afternoon, Mr. 985. Hey, good afternoon. No, I'm honestly,
the whole, the whole role is just going away. VIP, I didn't want it to turn into this, but it kind
of turned into sort of a commodity over the years. It started to get some pretty real value behind
it, which I really don't like. So I just decided to remove it. It's just gone. Will you be quiet
today? No, let me be quiet. Those of you that don't know, I thought about adding new VIPs
a while back and it can get a little awkward when people can essentially kind of bring up, hey,
why, why did I not get VIP? Why did they get VIP? What, who deserves VIP? What did they do?
And it's almost like you have to start to like prove that somebody deserves VIP for some reason.
And I just, I just don't want to do that. I'm just not going to do that. So nobody gets VIP
anymore. Oh, there's one person that gets to be, whatever that word. It's me. I'm just like passed
out after saying it loud. I'm kidding. I'm relaxed. You know, I thought about VIPing Ball Fondler.
I thought about it. I thought about him being the only one and then just mute everybody and just let
him talk for five minutes and then permanently ban him forever. Paulie just said, you don't have
to give me VIP. Well, I did it on my, for my own reason. It's pretty fair. That's really powerful.
Don't do that. Do it. I'm not going to do that, but yeah, as we continue to go here, I don't,
I don't think VIP kind of is just not something I really want on the channel anymore. Call me a
weirdo if you want, but that's just the way it is. I don't like having to pick and choose people
and then have people potentially, I'm not saying this has happened, but potentially get angry or
annoyed. And then I have to come up with a bunch of reasons why somebody did or didn't get it.
Isn't Ball Fondler banned? Oh, well, nevermind. Change your pinned tweet. I will eventually.
Oh no, no, no, he's unbanned. He got unbanned during baseball. Hasn't been rebanned yet. Okay.
Well, be careful then. What are your thoughts on chemistry? I don't think it's important.
It's a, and it helps us kind of understand our world better. Helps us kind of understand
how the, you know, things react. It helps us understand our world. Okay. Are you guys ready
to play The Sims 4? And again, I'm not just going, people are not, I'm telling you right
now, people are just going to be spamming it and I'm telling you mods, take care of this.
I don't want to see, you know, like kill them, attack him, attack him, punch him. No,
we're playing The Sims 4 and I'm going to be a, one of the mods is actually kind of funny.
I don't want to spoil it. Sparingly. All right. You guys ready? You guys even see it? No, I haven't.
Okay. I, I don't, I don't know how much, what is it? Autonomy, right? I don't know how much
autonomy these mods have. So I'm going to make sure I have a save point in case somebody just
gets hit by a car, like in the first five minutes. Also, I did some exercises. I did,
I did some very light stretching and breathing exercises for the last,
it's why I was late for another 10 minutes because if I laugh really hard, I'm going to get hurt.
So I need to be ready. I have to be aware of this. Okay. Are you, are you ready? We're still in,
we're in, oh, I think we're in Batuu still, I think. Can you guys hear it? How do I get out of
here? This is a weird angle. This is a normal angle. This is an, this, look, this is a normal
angle. I'm just chest up in frame on a webcam. I want you to explain how this is weird. I need
to know why this is weird. It's chest up angled webcam. This is a scripted angle. You're inside
out. YouTuber Andy. I am a YouTuber. I was a YouTuber for six years. The door should be on
the other side. What? We've got architects in here now? This is an iPad zoom angle. All right,
let's go. Okay. So there is autonomy because this is a Fortnite dance. Okay. We need to,
let's leave. We should get out of here. Is it, why am I getting a skill? All that's missing is like
a bone on a tripod facing this way. Where's Santa? There are no game sounds. It should be.
Can you not hear anything? Oh, I had him off. It's really weird with that, without any music here.
This is what I've been hearing. Guys in his own world. My acquaintance was telling me how much
they dislike you. Try being a little nicer, becoming disliked as a slippery slope. Okay.
You have a suede green screen background. All right. It's, I'm done with, with this area. Can
I go home now? Oh, I hope I didn't break anything with the mods. Dance skill acquired. Blorg is
busting some moves. He has unlocked some new dance moves and can show off the arm
charm dance move on the dance floor. What? What's the, what's the orange T-shirt kid?
There is, what do you mean there's no sound? What? This, there is definitely sound.
There, I can see it right here. He thinks we can't see the green screen. Oh my God. All right.
How do I leave? I don't want to, I want to get out of this vacation. It's already all
fucked up. I knew this was going to happen. I just was about to hit this guy with the car.
I knew this was going to happen. I'm, I told you this is why I can't,
we have to go home right now. It's quiet. The second that I see somebody start doing a Fortnite
dance, it's like, it's over. Like I can't just play the Sims now. I knew this was going to happen.
How do I get out of here? I want to get out of the vacation. Does anyone know how to leave?
By the way, you can't do this for this long. He's probably exhausted. Use the phone. Okay. End
vacation. End the vacation, please. Yes. Okay. That was fun. We had a lot of time.
We had a lot of fun at the, at, at who? It was cool. Do that until he passes out. All right.
Here we are. So welcome back. The Petsitter took good care of Yodel. All right. Cool.
I love how twerk for money is there. Sing?
Oh, no, this is, this is not a mod. Okay. No, I don't. Oh, hold on. I got to take it.
I'm not even using these. These are going to be used very sparingly. You're already in the extreme
violence sub menu. No, I was, I, I didn't even look at it. I don't even know what's there.
Let me change career paths. I need to change career paths. It's very important. Uh, find a job.
I didn't tweet the stream out. God damn it. I'll do it in a minute. Okay. Is it here? Where is it?
Did I inst- there it is. I can be a Warcraft War Chief for the Horde. Of course I'm quitting
that job. All right. So achieve level one fitness, level two logic. I get to be like a War Chief.
All right. Cooking charisma. I thought we were going to start Fortnite dancing.
That's the dream job. Okay. So I need logic. How do I get logic again? I only have 400 bucks.
Cooking though. We can maybe practice cooking. I guys, I forgot everything that I installed here.
Um, I know that I installed wear objects as hats. That's one, I guess. There's also like the,
you can punch people. You can attack people. That one's on. Um, utensil preferences? Bruin herbal
remedy. Insect repellent. Is this a mod? It's in game. All right. Let me, uh, what time do I have
to go? I love how it's, uh, okay. I gotta show up Monday morning. Gotta show up for, you know,
I'm a scout for, uh, for the Horde. All right. So I need charisma. I already have enough. Logic
level two. Wellness level one. This interior design's awful. It's all right. It's gonna be
fine. So I need to do cooking. Can you practice cooking or do you just have to cook? Like just
cook, right? Let's make, um, oh, I learned how to make this. All right. Let's make a single serving
of this. That sounds good. Why are you coming over? What? And he's got worms? What's happening?
Oh, it's cause this stupid cube is up here. Okay. All right. That's better.
Resume. Turn the volume up. How did it turn down? That's what I have to ask.
How did the volume go get turned down so much? All right. So I need three cooking skill. I can
do that. A little too much powder. A little too much. How many gallons of milk do you think you
could chug? I wouldn't do that. That's like kind of awful for you. It's really bad for you.
This counter. Oh, okay. All right. Very good. Looks good. Looks pretty tasty. Uh,
I'm not clicking that. It's too early. It's been 10 minutes. I'm up poisoning. Why would I poison
the food I'm about to eat? I need to save this before something happens. Twerk. What's the crabby?
Okay. I'm going to honest that he now he's really confident. All right. Uh, I'm going to accidentally
poison this because it's right above put away. I'm going to click put away, but my brain's going to
click poison and it's going to, it's going to be bad. Okay. I need to cook again. Should I bake?
No, that's a different thing, right? All right. How about a, uh, hamburger cake? That's stupid.
What was that? I didn't click. What are you doing? What is he doing? What is he doing? Free style?
That was fun. Okay. I don't understand that. I don't know why they even program that. Why do
they program that into the game? I want you to ask yourself the question. What was the last time
stop fucking make the food? What was the last time you guys went an inch? Did you put it in a pan?
When did you, I last time you guys went a half inch away from food you were cooking and went
no, this is, it happens way too often. It happens way, way too often. And you know what's really
funny about this? He's going to get to level 10 dancing. Warchief. But do you, when do you stop
doing that? I think I'm just going to let him go. Warchief material. God. Okay. I kind of do this
shit though. I've already talked about this. There's been so many times that I've been about
to eat food or eating food. I'll take a bite and come over and just do one of these. Okay. Same,
right? Yeah. When was the last time you just, sometimes I don't like sitting and eating.
Sitting and eating kind of is annoying to me sometimes. I like standing and eating. Is that
weird? Kind of walking around and taking a bite out of something and just kind of putting it down,
like doing a couple, a couple of weird like steps like this. Putting my back against the wall,
being like forward and then take another bite. I don't, I kind of do that. I don't do it that
often. Okay. Look, people that are like, what the fuck are you talking about? I don't do this every
single time I eat food. I do this like once every like month. I do it like once a month.
You're wicked annoying. Okay. If I, if, if I invite friends over and we're going to have dinner,
I'm not going to be like doing this stuff. But what do you know? That's the only one I'm just
like, I'm happy because the food's good. Depends on the food. Yeah. I don't say if I eat like a,
like a gross spaghetti or something and it's like, oh, this is like kind of under cooked
and tastes awful. I'm not going to be like, oh, why would I do that? It has to be very good.
How long am I going to wait? Is the food done? Did I even turn the oven on? I don't think the
oven's on. All right. That's enough. Is it still in there? Oh, it's perfect. Wow. It's excellent
quality. Who the fuck is this? Who is, who, who is this? Why is this person here?
You mad that you're, why are you here?
You're stepping it again.
What's this? Hey, get out of here. That's just, this person's a fucking vampire or something.
This person's a werewolf. Oh shit. They're going to turn. Are they turning? I don't know.
Is this person turning? Why did they growl at me? They knocked on my. Oh my God. Oh my God. Get
out. I gotta get the weapon. Get out of here. Get out. Get out. Get out. Oh no, no, no, no. I have to.
Get out of here. This person was going to kill me. This person was going to attack me. How do I get
this? What do I do? Oh, okay. I got to relax, man. I have to relax. What was the point? Honestly,
what the fuck was that? This person knocks on my door, steps in shit outside on my porch,
growls at me, starts to turn into a specter and then starts yelling at my dog. I'm sorry. You're
going to get fucking Metal Gear Solid. I'm sorry. You're not going to turn into like a vampire and
start screaming at me in my house. I'm going to bring out the Metal Gear Solid technique.
I'm sorry. That was fucking scary. Wait, I can demand 47. Yeah, that was scary. It took 27 minutes
for you to kill somebody. I am sorry. I did. I don't know what these mods activate. For all I know,
that person could have been here to kill me. I don't know. These mods are out of control. I
don't know what's going to happen here. What are you doing? Oh, you like the dog. Okay.
Yeah, also Grump Clump was helped find all these mods. So some of them are really funny. This
War Chief mod, I can't wait. Excellent. How do I get rid of this? Laugh? I don't know if I want
to do that. Why is the Grim Reaper still here? Discuss dance techniques. Murderer.
What are you doing? I am on alert right now because I don't know if he's going to just attack me with
that side. I need to give my dog- I need to relax after what just happened after being-
Hey, you want some burger cake? I'm kind of hungry.
I get rejected? I'm flattered, but I'm not interested in that type of relationship with
you, but I would be happy if you would like to be friends. Okay. Well, I'm sure we'll be hearing
from you very soon regardless because the nature of me being attacked. That was weird. Does anyone-
What was that actually? Was that person a monster with a wizard? What was going on there? Why were
they growling at me? Did I invite them into the house? And that was a vampire. Okay. So did me
inviting that person into the house cause me danger? They were just doing vampire stuff.
Growling at a new neighbor coming into the house. What are you doing? What are you doing?
Okay. Let's get back to normal here. I didn't even- Stop! What are you doing?
I am not telling him to do that. Don't you dare. I don't want this to be on the floor.
It's- You've corrupted- No! I thought I was- I'm gonna get fucking bit by a vampire.
Wait, I can cook a food for the dog? Cook homestyle pet recipe. What? That's kind of cute.
How about beef and chicken fish cake? Oh, I don't have any fish. Do I? I don't. Huh?
What? I knew I shouldn't have fucking installed these goddamn mods. I knew it's been 30 minutes
and I can't stop. I have to- I can't play The Sims. I can't. I don't- I don't have any fish.
So just- Don't throw it away. Can I just repurpose this? It's not even out of the package yet.
And I do- Am I really gonna do this? Are you serious? That was 20 bucks. I have to tweet
the stream. Give me one second. I'm gonna- I have to tweet the stream. Two seconds. Okay. Tweeting
it. How does- I always forget to do this. Sims 4 with mods. Come chill. That's all right. It's
still in my head. It's still getting me. Okay. We are officially tweeted. Oh, by the way,
I have some good news. I tested negative for COVID this afternoon. So I'm gonna test again
later tonight. And I hope I'm good to go. There is one problem that I have to go to the doctor about.
I- My like stomach is kind of messed up, but we'll see. But I'm pretty good to go. Negative.
That's good at least. I got my sense of taste and smell back. So I'm happy about that. And let's go.
Okay. So I- What do I need for the Warchief? I need wellness level one. What's wrong? Let's play.
Let's get a bath and let's play. I have to work today? I have to work in three hours. Oh, shit.
Put ice where I am going to delete this character if you do that again. Give the dog a bath. What
are you doing? No. Like, what are you doing? Like, seriously? I don't like the way you were just
sitting there. Give bath. Let's go. All right. Here we go. Bath time. I kind of smell. I wash my hands.
What are you doing in the top left corner? Trying to not be in the way of information
that's important for you to enjoy watching a Sims playthrough. The water is too hot.
I- I can't adjust the temperature. No, I think he's all right. Is the audio desynced?
I don't get it. Are people just gaslighting me?
Okay, cool. All right. So now let's, um, I would do this too after giving Otto a bath. You know
what I mean? Like, why not? That's an achievement, right? That's like a let's- this is celebratory.
Where's the dog? I just gave you a bath. Don't come out here and get all dirty.
You just got a bath and you're all wet. All right. Stop doing the Fortnite thing.
All right. So let's, uh, work for Blarg starts in an hour. All right. Let's, um,
here. Come here. Give me a hug. What did I just do? There we go.
Okay. I do need to take a shower though. Take a quick shower. Yep. I didn't quite get all the
things I need. When is the work? When do I have to leave for work now? Or in like 30 minutes?
Just shit my pants. Right when I got new clothes on. I took a shower, put my clothes on, and then
shit my pants. Am I going to bed? You think you- it's right there. It's literally right here.
Okay. I gotta go to work. Get up. Time to go to work. When does work start? What? Did I miss work?
Did I miss- how did I miss work? It said one hour. Oh no, I missed my first day of being a scout for
the horde. I slept through it. Does that actually mess with hygiene? Or is it just weird and gross?
Okay. Well, I'm gonna- then I'm spending today working on skills then. I need- oh, I have to
change this aspiration because I don't want to do this. Whatever. It's fine. He can be a
war chief Jedi. That's fine. All right. I need logic level two and wellness. What is wellness?
Wellness? How do I do work? Is it exercise? If I do stretches, does that count? What is this bar
filling? Over and over it'll tell you. Reading books on wellness, yoga, meditating, and giving
massages. I didn't flush the toilet when I used it? Ex- what? I need to buy a yoga mat. Okay.
How much is this? $125? Excuse me? Instructor's yoga mat? How much is this one? What, I can have
like yoga classes on the beach? Let's go. I need chess for logic. I don't think I have enough money
for it. Oh, fuck. How much is a yoga instructor? Just let me know what routine interests you and
we can get started. All right. Um, ask to start yoga class. Brain boosting? What should I do?
Energy centering? Family? How about brain booster? I'm gonna do a brain boosting yoga routine.
This dog. Wait, phone. Oh shit, I gotta go to work. Uh oh. Thral is calling me. Where are you?
You're supposed to be here. 40 minutes ago. Hmm. We're gonna start? Are you gonna start the routine
or what? Oh, here we go. How much was this? $110? Am I gonna even get one skill point for this?
Like a mail? I have 78 bucks and I owe $650? Fuck, I can't. God damn it. I need to cut this
short. It was a hundred. Ah, I'll be right back. I'll be right back. I'll be right back.
She went to sleep. What? Okay. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. Brain boosted.
I need, I just need a regular yoga mat. Can we do any, can we like do any more
yoga routines or are you just gonna stand here? By the way, I ghosted Thral. Oh wait,
I can go to work still. I can go to work. I can go to work. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Go to work.
Go. Go. Go. Go to work. Go to work. I can still go. Go. I can't go to work.
I'm gonna take a bubble bath. Bottom right button. I can't. Yeah, it's too late. I can't.
Am I gonna get fired? I'm not gonna get fired, right? Oh, I did get it. Okay. I got level one
wellness. So now I need level two logic, which I'm gonna sell a yoga mat. Thanks for coming.
And I need to buy a, where are you going? Okay. I need to buy a logic chest table.
I just searched. Okay. Here we go. $450. What can I sell? What can I just get rid of?
I can do it on a computer. I can? What? I don't know you could do that. Play game. Career.
Oh no. Right. Is it play game? Play game. Play lick block. It's probably lick block, right?
Is this doing it? Is this logic? I hate Tetris. I'm just so bad at it.
So what am I leveling up the gamer skill? It's just video gamer skill. That's probably important
for being for war chief, right? I need to be pretty good. Wow. I need to research a lot. Wait,
can I just get a bookshelf? How much is a bookcase? I can do all, I can do cooking. I
can do logic. Like a bookcase, right? That's how you do it. Here we go. Right? Vintage books.
This counts, right? There. I don't care. Let's put this here. Read. Which one of these is
Lord of the Rings? Purchase books. Read something. You have to buy the logic books. What?
Okay. So I need to show logic. Purchase books and get logic volume one. Is that in here?
Oh, acting. Okay. I see. It's alphabetical. Logic volume one. $75. God damn it. All right.
Enough. No more video games. Do your homework. All right. Let's go. When does it work? Okay. I
got a skill in logic. I need another point. Did I just wait? Did I, do I have like a mod that's
giving me like hyper skill points? That was immediate. I don't think I do. Do I? You just
start at level one. Oh, okay. What's wrong? All right. Work is in, oh, I'm supposed to be there
right now. No, I'm like sitting there. Wait, when do I have to go to work? Okay. So I got,
I got all day and I have all night and into tomorrow. Okay. I got it. You want to play?
Here, let me play. Let's play fetch. Go get it. Get it. I just like a flash of memory was that
when the vampire stepped outside the house. So I can train the dog more. I think I'm doing
like a training skill. That's cool. Oh, you're having fun. All right. What level, what level is
this now? All right. Completed already. I got pretty good at this. The urn is still in your
inventory. It's always a lot of weird shit by the way. Why is there poop in my pants?
What is going on? What is this stuff? Oh shit. I can sell all the Star Wars memorabilia.
I can sell all the Star Wars memorabilia. Wow. I'm going to be just fine. Can I not? What is this
suit? What is this chair? What is this chair? And why am I not using it instead of this piece of crap?
You have to place them first. Oh, I'm going to sell all my Star Wars memorabilia. I don't care.
This is perfect. Okay. What do we got here? Hamburger cake. That's pretty cool. An old coffee,
two apples. Shit. What is that? Okay. Stop. No more, no more fetch. I know you're getting tired,
but we have, we got to sell some of our memorabilia. Oh, fine. Just go to bed. We'll do
this tomorrow morning. Drag and drop the items. What is this? Oh, the Holocron. This is good. I'm
going to be able to sell this for like a thousand bucks. Look at all this stuff. I'm going to make
so much money. Kyber crystals. Are you serious? I don't want to sell the ones I like though.
This BB-8 replica. What is this? Scrap metal? Sell it. All of it. Read. What? Okay. How much is
this like high fighter replica? A hundred bucks. I want to keep it. Okay. The Holocron is $325.
Fuck this thing. I, but that's a Luke. Missing out on dreams. It's all right. I don't want to
get rid of the purple one. I want the red. I want, but this is, um, no, I'm, I'm keeping these.
Was that a pie? Did my guy get bigger? You have the worst trade in the whole game,
which is what the, I want to be a Star Wars fan. Okay. So Sith Holocron. Cool. I'm going to,
I got to, don't put that there. I'm trying to do this. Where did that just go? You idiot. Get
rid of this. I'll sell a bunch of this shit and then I got to pay my bills. This is not important,
right? Reddit gold mine. Now I can buy the chess table. They are very important. Oh,
what about my poster? Only a hundred bucks. Oh, I don't want this anyways. Actually, what is this
one? I'll keep that one here because does that mean, wait, I'm going to probably going to get
like a for the horde pose. Wait, I'm going to pretend that's a for the horde. What is this?
Pile of presents? Or dollars? Comm link? What is this? Can I use it? No, what's the point of
this? Who's the dog barking at? Oh, uh, I'm going to keep selling shit. What am I ever going to use
this for? Okay. We got, I'm going to keep the Kyber crystals. Who's buying the shit for $1.
I'm going to keep the apples because it's, I don't know. It's kind of cool. I'm going to put the Sith
Holocron out here because it's cool. First order uniform. I'm not selling that. A blaster right.
Oh, a cool plaque. All right. I got enough money.
Okay. So now I got to pay my bills. Where's my mailbox? Okay. Here, right here.
655 bucks. And then I got to make a, uh, logic table. Am I texting?
Oh, this is what we all were waiting for. It's finally here.
And I'm not even happy about it. I got all this stuff, but I've got like this $2,000 lightsaber,
this $5,000 AR training unit, an authentic signed first order costume. And I don't care.
Isn't this what I want? I thought I wanted this.
You can now discuss workout techniques. What? Oh, this is not me training to be a Jedi. It's
just me exercising. I thought I was training to be a Jedi master. That's not what this was.
Okay. Well, I got money. Jedi aren't real. What's, how do I fix this? Oh yeah. I made it.
He like hates like scoop and stuff. All right. Empty the trash, fill up the bowl and clean this
up. Clean up. Cause I got to get to work tomorrow. One more law. I got to read the book, right? What
time is it? 37 minutes. I have to start working. Why was I out here swinging a lightsaber on like
a fucking dickhead? Why? Oh my God. Okay. 37 minutes. God damn it. Don't go to bed.
What are you doing? That was so weird. It's time to go to work. That was weird. He went
under the cover. I need to be in my work outfit. All right. Go to work. Work starts right now.
Go to work. What? How do I go to work? How do I go to work? What's happening? It's not there.
Go to, no, don't eat anymore. Okay. Go to work. It's time for work. I have to go to work. I don't
want to get fired. How do I, how do I go to work? The mods broken. Oh, the mod seems to be broken.
Oh, that's unfortunate. So I got to change jobs? Oh no. We can't be a war chief. Yeah. This mod
hasn't been updated. I don't think in like three years or four years or something. That's funny.
Although let's try one more day. I'm going to try going one more time. All right. But what if
calls me? Do I answer? Are we communicating? All right. I need to be ready. What's the issue
with it right now? I can't go to work. What are you doing? You have to clean this up. The geek con
isn't, oh, I'm dressed for the occasion right now. I'm going to bring my lightsaber. I'm going to
bring my holocron. I'm going to, it's good. I'm ready. I've been waiting for this. I am ready to
go to geek con. I am going to just stand in the middle of this place and just do lightsaber
practice. And people are going to be like, holy shit, that guy is the man. What are you doing?
He's supposed to be in your outfit. Are you, what? Put it on. Okay. So this is geek con.
What was that? They just launched a rocket. Explore space. Uh, yeah, I think so. Where am I?
He's very angry. Hold on. I got to do this. Yes. No, come on. You're in front of a lot of people.
You have blown it so bad. So bad. What is this? Like VR stations? Why am I so angry? This is like,
I've, I want to be here so bad. The geek con challenges have begun. Head to the computers
to test your programming skills in hackathon or use the motion gaming to test. I don't have any
gaming skills. Where are they going? Oh, I got to, I got to test my gaming skills. Ultimate gaming
test. Let's go. Wait, wait, I'll do that later. I can upgrade the ship.
$500 on this. What, what just happened? That was 500 bucks. That was a shitty ride at a theme park.
No, I, this is taking role playing to a whole new level here. I'm actually installing better
rockets on this landing stabilizers. I canceled it. Okay. I'm going to upgrade this thing.
This guy, this guy shouldn't be here. They, they, they need to put like tape here. You know what I
mean? Like, otherwise I'm not supposed to be doing this rocket science. I'm leveling up a rocket
science skill. I'm not leaving. I'm doing this for like the next five minutes. How am I aware?
Am I going to level up rocket science? Santa, Santa's here. He's joining the hackathon.
This is so stupid. What's wrong? Stop, dude. Okay. Wait, is Santa going on a trip?
By the way, I don't think anybody can get on this. If I'm doing this,
people wait. I, they can't get in here. I'm currently working on it. He is waiting in line
to do this. I don't work here. Why are people letting me do this? Oh, this is,
this is celebrity. Santa just got an autograph. I know you want to get on the ship really badly,
but that's not happening. Okay. How long can I do this for level three rocket science? I'm not
leaving until I get to level five rocket science. Hackathon has come to an end. First place received
the, oh, you get a computer. 75% done. I'm doing, I'll install something else. Oh no, no, I'm getting
on this. I'm going to make sure I'm in the line first. Oh, okay. I did it. I can't. No, no, no.
I want to go now. It's my turn. I had to explore space. I upgraded this thing.
What?
Lorg doesn't remember much, but thinks he may have been abducted. He now stands in a small sterile
arena. A modely assemblage of hideous beings sits furtively in the bleachers. Slowly a pedestal
rises from the floor. It contains two items, a ball and a container with two holes, one round
and one triangular. The room is tense with excitement. I mean, I'm going to, I'm going to
put it into, I'm going to put it into the round hole. That's what, that's what I would do.
The festival is going to end before I come back to earth. The round ball definitely slides into
the round hole and the room erupts into ferocious applause. Lorg instinctively bows graciously as
the puzzle recedes back to the floor, replaced by a new one. This next rising pedestal has a hat.
Yes, it's a very fine hat, perhaps a derby. What should Lorg do? Wear the hat. It's over in like
20 minutes. Am I going to get stuck in outer space? Eureka! The hat goes on the head. More
cheer is spewed forth from the crowd as Lorg rifles the hat into the stands with a flourish.
To be caught by one lucky fan, the hatless pedestal sinks and disappears into the ground
and is shortly replaced again. This latest test pedestal appears to hold a chair, a simple metal
chair. All right, I think we're going to go, we're going to sit next to the chair because they're
definitely doing this thing where it's like, oh, put the hat on, put the circle into the circle,
sit in the, dead, right? I'm going to sit next to the chair. No, you ruined it. What? Lorg is too
smart for them. That chair is one of those moving platforms. As the crowd applauds Lorg's wisdom
and foresight, thank you everybody. Please have a seat. The chair sinks down into the dark recesses
in the floor, replaced by the next challenge. This pedestal is made of solid gold and contains
valuable looking jewels. I don't think I touched these, but wait, what if it's a shitload of money?
I could actually just take it. I might, I need the money, but it could be a trick.
Thrall would want you to take it. Don't be greedy. Greed is good. Don't do it.
Okay. On one end, this is morality, right? No, I know that you're tempting me with riches. I don't
want them. It's going to be, this is morality, right? But on the other hand, I could make like
10 grand. Are they testing morality? Another trick, Lorg thinks as the gems glitter and sparkle.
Then the alien beings look at each other in confusion. Does he not know the value of what
is presented? A buzzer unmistakably indicates failure. Bring me back. I want to take the jewels.
I want to go back. I'm going back to space. Bring it back. I'm going back in.
I'm going back to space. I'm going back. See you later. It was nice to see everybody. I'm going
back up there and I'm going to take the jewels this time. I'm going back up. What? Passing the
planet Yang, Lorg sees a weary looking alien standing amid a huge pile of trash bags and rusty
futon parts. He's moving to a new pad on the planet Rompeter and his friend who was supposed
to help just bailed. Lorg's got some extra time. Should he pitch in? There's no no. Sure. You can't,
no. Is there enough time to get one of these funny hot dogs? What's wrong? Good thing Lorg
has an expanded cargo bay from being a Jedi. It's a lot of stuff to move. Old concert tees,
milk tray furniture, but it all fits in pretty easily and they blast off for Rompeter. The alien
is so grateful he gives Lorg his least dirty futon mattress as thanks. Lorg incinerates it.
I want a- lost in a nebula. Lorg instruments go haywire and his rocket ship is bathed in purple
light. Purple and gold dust coats the sky as far as the eye can see which isn't that far. He must
have drifted into a giant nebula. Lorg can send out a call for help or forge ahead and hope the
instruments can sort it out. Forge forward. I just got rocket science. Lorg wanders through the cloud
the dance of gold and purple is almost hypnotic. An exquisite dream or luxurious grave. What?
He is at peace with the beauty of his lugubrious fate when suddenly the ship breaks through into
the clear. He's free. He just needs a little more luck. He's got to get home on fumes. Am I going to
die up here? Oh shit! I made it! Okay, we're good. Okay, I- is the convention's over?
The convention ended already. I gotta go home. Do you have a bathroom? Where's the dog? I hear a dog.
This dude- this dude comes back from a bunch of alien travel. He's so exhausted.
Comes home, sits down in a chair, and just shits his pants. Oh my god.
This guy is exhausted. He is so tired. Oh, I feel so bad.
On an adventure. He's asleep.
Dude, the guy in the first order costume shits his pants. I don't know who we call about this.
Who do we talk to about this? Yeah, I mean, I don't know. I think the guy in the Sith outfit,
he's in there sitting down. I think he shits his pants. Oh, do we call security? I'm just in- I'm
in REM sleep right now. Oh my goodness. What? It's karaoke night? Oh my goodness.
I'm starting to lose control, I think. What? Honestly, what was that?
I'm curious how this plays out. Let's just see what happens. I have to be careful taking a sip
of this. I'm gonna choke on this. Oh, he knows he's in it. He's sitting in it. Use the bathroom.
Yeah, it's called- dude, you gotta throw- you gotta throw all your clothes in the trash,
you know what I mean? I hope you brought a backpack with a change of clothes.
Oh my goodness. What is this? It's really decorated in here. That was nice and comfortable,
and I did a really cool adventure. I explored space. I'm going back to sleep, though.
I woke up to change my fucking pants.
Where am I gonna go back to bed? This guy's- this guy's fucking- why don't I just go home?
No, you know what? It's time to get up. It's time to get up. It's time to sing karaoke.
This is so loud. I have to turn it down before it gives me a headache.
I think I'm- I think it's safe for me to save here.
What are they all saying? Oh, there's a celebrity behind me.
Celebrity. That's a- that's an absolute proper celebrity.
Okay. You have to step back. Can I sing?
I need to go home. Sing? But should I just sing? Oh, dude, hold on.
Did you just cut the music? Or is she looking at me? She stopped because I'm doing this.
I don't know what happened. She's stuck. I think she's just confused what I'm doing.
I'm incredibly distracting. I want to sing. Why can I not sing? Too uncomfortable.
No, don't go to bed. I want to talk. I want to hang out.
No. Look, just eat the apples that are in your mouth. Who cares? Eat. Plant.
Who, Apple, Andy? What am I doing? What is this? Oh my god.
Let's go wash this in the sink. No, I want to do that. Can I like wash my hands?
This is a very strange- this is a strange person. I can talk to the toilet. Special effects?
Oh, I can turn it off and on. That's kind of- whoa. Okay, I gotta go home. It's over. Time to leave.
That was a fun geek con. It's time to go to bed. I think- I think somebody else shit their pants.
I don't think it was me. See you later, everybody. Upgrade their toilet. No, I'm gonna pass out.
I'm gonna fall asleep on the ground. Send him back to space. I don't think I can do that anymore.
Look, I got rocket science 4 from that. I can make my own rocket.
That was an adventure. I was out of control. Oh, I got an achievement. Like the sims 4 for 5 hours.
Okay, that was an eventful day. I have to go to work in 7 hours, so let's make sure I get some
sleep and take a shower. That's important, number one. And then we're gonna go to bed.
How do you upgrade a bed? How does that mean? How could I upgrade the bed with a wrench? Oh.
There we go. All right, I'll get rid of these. Too many sims. We're good. You got food, right?
How are you doing? Are you good? You want a treat before I go to bed? Here, have a treat before I
go to bed. You also need this- this dog needs a bath every day. Every single day. Sleep. Feed him.
All right, it's time to see if I can go to work. What's wrong, you okay? What's the matter? Oh,
we're good. Two hours. All right, I need to be up. So get up, have some food. What do you got?
Leftovers. And let's see if I can go to work. What's this so dirty? It's the same dirty,
spoiled cake I was eating at that restaurant. Okay, it's 8 a.m. Go to work. Oh, I think it's
broken. It's broken. You can't go to work. Well, looks like I'm going to be a rocket scientist.
Sorry, Thrall. It was funny. It was fun. Okay. I can do it on the computer, right?
Career. Find a job. All right. Astronaut. That seems pretty good, right? Is it astronaut or is
it rocket scientist? Okay. Oh, wait. Scientist. Which one? Which one is it building rockets?
Scientist or astronaut? Wait, there's a rocket scientist? So I could do- so do scientist because
rocket scientist is a scientist. Okay. Oh, I could have just read the tag line here. Okay.
Scientists who proves they've got a gray- the gray matter to change the world as we know it
can unlock no emphasis. Like the UFO hunter with a chemistry lab. Okay. An astronaut is
space ranger and interstellar smuggler. This is important. I think we're going to need to
have to do this with a poll. Astronaut or rocket scientist? You actually get to go to work as a
scientist. Interesting. Either scientist or astronaut. Which one? Science. Science. Astronaut.
Okay. Astronaut or scientist? Astro- how do you spell astronaut? I don't know. Scientist.
Uh, just one minute. Doesn't matter. Oh, two minutes. It's fine. How do you spell astronaut?
Yeah, I got it right. Okay. Oh, poll's already active. Oops. Hey, don't influence the vote.
Don't influence. It's just- just ask the question. Well, you guys are being influenced. Sorry about
that. Okay. So sims in the scientist career are more likely to be abducted. Okay. Satellite dish
allows you to contact aliens. Okay. I mean, that's cool. I probably would have- I'm- why am I so
sweaty? I think I was laughing too hard. All right. I mean, that's the way it is. We're doing- we're
doing scientist. Scientist. All right. I need to have two breakthroughs. I don't know what that
means. Two breakthroughs? While gardening, reading, or performing experiments. Read? All right. First
of all, clean up. This is a mess. And I got to work in lifestyle. That was previously hidden.
View the lifestyle menu. Wait, what? I got single and loving it. All right. So I start work in two
days. So I have a lot of time. I just got to get my mood up. I got to get focused and I need to have
a couple of breakthroughs. So how am I doing right now? I'm pretty good. Let's start to read. Read a
puzzle book or something, right? I should probably do logic again. Where is it? Where's the logic
book? Should I purchase like- is there a science book? Wait, rocket science volume one. There it is.
Bingo. All right. Have a couple- have a couple of breakthroughs. You good? Eureka!
Lord McDulty had his first breakthrough and wrote down an idea for a momentum conserver.
Click on the notebook button at the top of the phone to learn more about it. Where? Change phone
background. Silence phone. Change phone cover. Where is it? What's it above the phone? Wait,
no ingredients required. Can I just make it? No ingredients required. How do I do this?
Do I need like a science thing? A science table? It's a perpetual motion machine?
Wait, are perpetual motion machines impossible? They can't exist, right? They don't exist. But
don't they make these- I feel like I've seen a perpetual motion machine where it's like a ball
can just keep moving like over and over again. They can work. It's not perfect. Isn't the dog
at the mall the thing that goes- a perpetual motion machine? Oh no, it needs power. How do
you make one? All right, I can't keep fucking talking like that. I just asked you guys how to
make a perpetual motion machine. Something that like science has never figured out over fucking
a hundred years of scientific research. How do you guys make one? Only a hundred years? More like
hundreds? Well, you know what I mean. They're inherently not possible. This dog is- this dog is
fucking filthy all day. Every day. The dog is filthy. I don't know what to do about this. It's
every single day. Well, because everything needs power to operate, right? So you don't- you can't.
Because if you have like a battery-operated perpetual motion machine, the bat- you need to
replace the batteries. Oh, hold on. I'm focused right now. Um, why can't I read that? Is it in my-
All right, read it. Battery-operated perpetual motion. COVID messed up his head. Here it is.
Oh, my voice. Okay, so I got what I needed. Two breakthroughs and I need to be focused. I am
focused. I have to go to work focused. All right, and that is in a while. I know how to make one,
but I won't tell you. Why not? That's- yeah, that's rude. Okay, so I'm focused. I've done
some rocket science. I am going to make sure I am fully fulfilled for tomorrow. What's wrong?
We got- okay, I'm a little sad and amateur hour. You're bored from this book. Oh, all right,
let me have a little bit of fun. Just like, look, information on vampires or whatever. This is the
kind of shit that I would just have auto play at YouTube and just, I don't know, just watch like
fucking 10 videos about it. Dude, I watched- um, Lord realized that fucking golic and plasma can
be found in Forgotten Hollow. Oh, all right, there's fucking golic in there. Uh, so.
This dude has a problem. I couldn't even continue what I was going to say. You can
purchase the vampire book. Okay, well, you had some fun. Cool. I need to eat. Dude, a flavor enhancer?
I want to do this stuff. How do I get- I want to read a book about being handy because having- this
is perfect. Wait, repair. That'll help, right? For the dog's sake, dog deserves to be happy. What?
No cheating. I'm going to give the dog a bath and then play with the dog. Yes, you like being,
you like being a handy worker. Okay, cool. All right, come over here. Let's have a bath.
Come with me. You're going to get a big treat and then we're going to play fetch. What happened?
What are my dreams? You want to be a debate captain? I want to have a nerdy conversation.
I want to listen to lullabies. I want to get some sleep and be funny in a crowded place.
Okay, well, I can get this done. How much is just like a little radio? I need a- okay,
I need a little end table with a radio. Okay, now I need a radio. Just like a little one. Just a
little one right like this one. This thing's way too big. A cafe wall speaker? Okay, listen to
lullabies radio. All right, you doing better? Happy? Look happy? Okay, let's fulfill one of your
dreams. Why does this guy want to listen to the first 15 seconds of every horror movie trailer?
It's kind of weird. Are you fulfilled? Not quite. Now you want to listen to retro music. Okay,
next song on this album. Why would you have this album? What happened? Oh my god. All right,
where's retro? Retro. Go on, listen. If I keep that, is it bad? This is like, I don't know,
I tell you guys about like when I used to fall asleep. If a DVD was in the DVD player and it
would just be on the the 25 second song that was at the menu screen for the DVD and falling asleep
to that was unbearable. You would hear it cycle over and over again and it would wake you up and
it would piss you off but you wouldn't get up and turn it off. Don't even mention Shrek. Yeah,
like you would all of a sudden just hear like, oh the years start coming in, they don't stop coming,
you're stuck and it's like, shut the fuck up. Shut up. But you're just so tired. You just don't
care. You don't want to get out of bed. You don't want to, where's the remote, right? I remember
Punisher DVD. The menu of that DVD is, there's a song and it's like, it's a guy with a with an
acoustic guitar and it's like, they may come back someday to live once more.
And it would just go, it would happen. Oh, it was 20 seconds of that song. It would play over and
over and over and over again. And I would just wake up over and over to like the, they may come
back someday. I'd be like, please God, please. Please, there's a power outage. Please, I'm praying
for power outage right now because I don't want to do this. Oh shit. Stop it. Stop it. Stop that.
$378. Where, where am I? I can repair this. This dog is fucking filthy every day.
This dog needs a bath every six hours. What? Oh, you need to go. Wait, no, stop, stop.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Who is this? Who is this? Why is there,
where did this, where did this trash come from? I can't believe he pissed on this person.
I can't believe he pissed on him. You, I can't believe that dog just did this.
You just might, this person walks through the wall. This person might be a scary person.
Want some coffee? Did I even fix the toilet? I did. Okay. Don't go in the bathroom.
This is bad if you go in the bathroom.
Imagine, my eye is freaking out. Imagine going up to your neighbor's house and introducing yourself
and when you knock on the door, the dog runs out, greets you and just pisses all over you.
We need to make some friends. What are you doing? Um, let's like gossip. No, I'm about to go.
What am I up to here?
Do you have a question?
You want to listen to music?
Goof around. Okay.
I mean, is that what she asked? Did she ask to slow dance?
Why was that a selection? Why? I, why was that a selection? Laid back shuffle. I'm this,
he is going through a lot of different emotions right now. I can't get up because she's in the
way. I can't stand up from the chair. Yes, I can. Okay. Oh, you want to, let's go. Let's go. Let's
go. This is what you wanted to do. Okay. You want to dance again? Um, I'm doing it. Are you doing it
too? Was that me? What are you doing on my computer? Do you want me to? No, come dance.
She's like, I want to dance. I want to dance to music. I want music. Well, come on over here.
What do you got? Show me what you got. All right. All right. What about that? Stop doing that one.
Stop doing that. Stop doing that. That was bad. That was that. That's going to, you're going to
leave. I don't, I didn't, that's, you don't do that one. How about this one?
Do you not like this one? I feel like both of my arms are being controlled by two different
people in Gmod. Oh, she's leaving. Well, that was nice to meet you. I maybe we'll see you again.
What's your name? Minerva? What's your name? Minerva Charm. Okay. All right. I got to clean up.
It's kind of disgusting. All right. That was fun. That was fun. Bye. Goodbye. Goodbye. All right.
All right. All right. I got to get to bed. I got to work. I got to work in 10 hours. Turn this off.
Why would you get out of bed to do that? I was lying in bed with the remote in my hand.
This is YouTuber music. Wait, I can't get up. Holy shit. Okay. Go to bed. You got food, right? You got
food. Clean up. Clean up all this, please. Scavenge for parts and then pee like a champion and then
get in bed. Go on. Hurry up. I got two upgrade parts. Oh, whatever. I got to get up anyway soon.
What's wrong? Oh my God. This algae growing in the sink. Turn the music off. He changes his mind every
two seconds. Stop. Just get in the bed. You stop shitting your pants. Oh my God. Okay.
You shit the bed. This person shit the bed. I got to get up and go to work.
I don't have time. I just got to get up. Trusty notepad in hand. It's time for
Blorg to go work at the lab. Maybe today is the day for a major breakthrough.
Here to join them. Yeah. Let's go. Welcome to future sim labs. You'll be quite busy conducting
essential experiments, researching new technology, and maybe even interacting with alien life.
It's your job to leverage potent scientific equipment for the purposes of good.
We hope. Well, welcome. Okay.
Hold on. I got to turn it up. A little up. Wait, I'm crying in the bathroom? What?
What?
I'm sorry, dude, but you can't just listen to kids music.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? I got to like meet my coworker.
Okay. Let's meet our first coworker.
I'm new. Good to see you.
Bruce.
Complain about work. It's my first day.
Pretend to fire? Why do I have this authority?
Why would I have this authority?
Cleave, Tannif, Pazoo, Plyver, Pneve, Clevite, Banu, Fidoy, Bafala.
So I walked in my first day. Wait, did I just get fired?
Ask them to wait. Pursue your dream job. What? Like don't work here anymore?
Sorry, I don't think I know you this well to have this conversation.
Okay. So how do I clock into work?
No, no, no, I am not going to joke about coworkers. I'm not going to tell joke.
What are you doing? All right.
You're fucking this whole thing up. You're fucking this whole thing up.
Is there anybody else that works here? Oh, okay. Another coworker. Mix synthetic food serum.
I don't think I should be using this. No, don't get out from the seat.
Just talk. Turn your head around. Oh, you're making the food serum. Okay.
Can I do that? Okay. I need to get to know a coworker.
Okay. Get to know. Just friendly, just normal conversations. Hey, how's your day?
Okay. I think I'm being mocked. I can't tell, but it's all right. Let's talk about work.
Yeah. Is it a roulette table? Okay. All right. Let's talk about
mock outfit is the same outfit I am wearing. Wait, where am I? Where am I going?
I'm about to build a rocket. Build it. Where are you? What are you doing?
This cool music just played and you walked away from it.
It doesn't get it. It doesn't know how to do it. Okay. So I'm going to do
synthesize serum. Okay. I need plants. Where do I get plants? Okay. Brainstorm and invention.
Brainstorm on invention constructor. Okay. I'm too angry to do anything.
Oh, you guys can't see that. My camera's blocking it. Try move the cam to the top right.
But I think that blocks in that there's a lot of information that gets blocked.
I think a lot of information gets blocked no matter where it goes.
Put it middle left like here. Is that good right there? No. Middle right like here.
You'll miss info like right here. Maybe right here is good. What do you think? Right there.
I think that looks all right. There's not important information that's there.
Let me the brightness is really high on this right now too. Hold on. That's what's making me red.
I figured it out. It's I had this weird color corrector on. That's why it's doing that.
Okay. Well, let's fix this. That's better. We're still in 60 fps. All right. We're good.
All right. I'll save the game. Now, how? What am I supposed to do about this?
You have a bug. Please fix it. You got to restart to fix it after you apply the fix.
What? I have the angry bug. The sim is always mean. It's a bug. I'll do it after work.
Do I have to just restart the game or how do I fix it? Is there a delay on your camera?
No, there isn't. I don't know. I got to figure out why people are saying that.
Here we go. I'm doing work. Go to computer. Put on the command center. Okay. There is a tiny delay.
I'm going to try something here. Just bear with me for one second while I do this.
Did that fix it? Ready? Like so right now I should be really delayed. I should be very delayed right
now. That's correct. Now it shouldn't be. It should be fine now. But is it? That's the question.
Wrong way. Yeah, I don't understand. It's very weird. I wonder if it's something with the camera.
Let me try one more thing. Did that fix it? Can you guys hear me? Are we good? Is it better?
There's no delay. You know, I'm going to watch some clips when this is done and see if I can
recreate what's going on here. Okay. But anyways, yeah, so I have to fix this. I have to go to
the MC command center and then go to MC tuner and go to interactions and disable mean interactions.
Really? I'll fix it after this today. Scary. Mean is fun. Oh, okay. Hold on. Here we go.
Okay. I can brainstorm now. I'm nervous calling me. Hey vlog, I think
Britanny Cho is pretty cute. Should I ask her out? I don't know who that is. Sure. Go for it. I
guess. I don't know who that is. Why do people call? Why do people call you to ask you if they
should go? I don't get that. I've never met that person before. I don't know who that is. I can't
give you good advice. Oh, hold on. Brainstorming. Okay. Get to know. Experiment on the chemistry
lab. You done with that? It's almost, I'm almost done with work and I haven't done anything. I
don't even have half a bar bubble filled. Oh God. Can I even get one filled? What happened? What
happened? I broke something. What's going, what's it doing? Oh, he's dancing. All right. Stop that.
Stop, stop, stop, stop. There's an explosion. Oh my God. Stop. He's taste. Nice work. What'd you
make? This guy's on drugs. Somebody shit their pants over here. I heard it. Somebody shit over
here. I heard that. Okay. Stop groove jam. You already had one queued up called vibing.
Could you please vibe your way into finishing your job? Practice analysis. What do I do that?
Hurry up. Do it. I can't. I got, hold on. Why is everybody minus twoing? What'd I do? What happened?
Minus two. Oh, I'm hungry. All right. I need to practice analysis. I would have touched in the
CEO in a meeting because it said like vibe your way over here. I was at, I would have touched CEO.
All right. You're done with this. Go over this way. I'm never going to work with this guy again.
Like he can just go. It's too much. It's too much stress. Okay. Almost done with that. Got it.
All right. I need to get to know a coworker. Can I, can we, I just need to say hello and
okay. Let's theorize about aliens. Okay. Work ends soon, but I can get one more of these.
There's no such thing as aliens. I've seen them.
Yeah. Okay.
Right. I'm starting your element collection is really show them off.
Okay. Let's talk about the aliens.
Aliens don't exist.
Selium, this is painful. What I, I have to do these. Otherwise I didn't fulfill my tasks at work.
What am I doing? There is a cafeteria here and I didn't even know it. Whose food is this?
Why was there food? I only heard $40. I'm not going. I'm not going to work anymore.
I'm sending him to work. I'm not doing that anymore. Somebody said that dude. That's what
a babysitter makes. Come on. Babysitter salary. I'm never going to work and get this Star Wars
shit out of here. Can I change this? Cause it's stupid. A Star Wars isn't stupid. I like Star Wars
some of it, but I mean, I don't want it to be my complete aspiration of my life to go to the Disney
world Star Wars park every day. You know what I mean? Like I don't, I need to change this to be
like build a rocket. I currently just need to go. All right. I just need to go to Batuu and just
fulfill this. Unless you change it. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Right. Right. Um,
okay. Knowledge. Computer whiz. Nerd brain. What's like aliens or space craft? No, not vampire. It's
probably just here. Knowledge. Computer whiz. I think nerd brain. Yeah. Rocket scientist. There
it is. Let's go. All right. Good. Werewolf? No, no, no, no werewolf. We're good. Okay. So now
the house is clean, right? I only have $558. What is this? Today is, uh, love day. I mean, that's,
yeah, I, I, I got, I'm not, I know. Some smells in the fridge. Clean, clean, clean. All right.
Ladder. Bathroom. That's what I need to do. Eat something. Is there more spoiled food in the fridge?
I'm going to cook because I need cooking, right? Steak tartare. Oh, I don't know. I just made me
hungry. I'm gonna make like beef ramen. Clean up. This is a mess. Hence for what? Missing out on
dreams. Become disliked by Santa. All right. Put the retro music on. Where is it? Retro, retro,
retro right there. What mods do you have? I, there's also a mod where you can put objects
as hats and stuff. I kind of don't know how to do it, but I'm, I think I'm satisfied with what we
got right now. Declare him an enemy. Didn't we go on vacation together though? I feel like, why would
I want to be, I feel like we're friends, right? Okay. So the dog, dog. Wow. Oh no. He beat the
shit out of me. That's right. At the end of the vacation, we had a big argument and he, and he
like punched me, beat the, he beat me up. He literally, he dropped me. He knocked me out
at the end of the vacation. Why though? Does anyone know why? I don't, I wasn't really paying
attention. Don't eat. Oh my God. Well, it's just him eating it. Sneeze directly into the food.
It's just, I'm gonna put it in the microwave, right? All right. That's beef ramen. That's
gonna be good. It's a quality. Excellent. Okay. All right. I fulfilled that. What's this? Find a
collectible. Ooh, I can do that. All right. So you're going to eat that and then come out here
and dig in the sand for something. I keep forgetting this is the default outfit he has. All
right. Let's see. I'm going to fulfill another dream here and then I got to go to the lounge and
be funny on the microphone. I can tell jokes. Message in a bottle. There it is. Do it for
everything. Let's see. Oh, it's love day. Okay. Message in the, uh, message in the sand. Oh,
just a bunch of bottles. Bottle. Bottle. All right. What do I do with these? Read this message.
When I was young, I lived in the shadow of a legend, but I decided to tell my own story.
I explored the world from historic Al Samara to tiny oasis springs. I sailed over a waterfall.
I kissed a llama. I climbed Mount Komoribi, been madly in love and raised my greatest pride. My
son, my life is full of memories and it's in its twilight. I sent a wish into the ocean and I fear
the shadow is surrounding you, but rather step out and shine brightly. Can I sell it or just play it?
That's an easy 12 grand. All right. It's love day. Social networking. Tech social media timeline.
Serve ramen to who? Practice program. I'm probably going to need programming.
Oh, let me guess. Dogs filthy. Slow dance with the dog. I don't think you can.
I have a fever. I'm sick. Please. You need to get hold on. I don't even know anybody.
Okay. Now take a shower. All right. We're good now. Two hours. You got to go to work and I've done
two breakthroughs. I need to be focused. How do I go focus quick? Read a book, right? I have to read
a book. Read this thing. Get off the computer. Get focused. Am I focused? Am I smelling the book?
Leave me alone. Am I focused? Come on. Be focused. No. He's a book smeller.
The bird feeder. There we go. Fill it. Trusty notepad in hand. It's time to...
No, go. I'm not doing that again. Go alone. I should wait. No, I'm sick. How do I call in sick?
All right. Calling sick. Call in sick to work. You're sick. No, don't call in fake sick.
Monsivzadeh. That... whatever. Arsifefroben. Lemino. Quar. Gorbaneh. Oh, Zaphis.
It's not fake sick. And I don't know why he still wants to serve ramen. What was that?
Oh, what was that? Did you see that? What was that?
Made a resolution, but it's the last day. What? Oh, I made a New Year's resolution. What was it?
How do I see it? Get a significant other. I have 20 hours to complete this. Okay. All right.
Okay. Wait, is there an event going on? Wait, wait, wait. Don't do that. Put this away.
Is there... there's an event, right? Is it some kind of thing going on in town?
Okay. Give flowers. Go on a date. Romantic spirit. Okay. I don't know. I have to, like,
maybe I should have to see who is available and see if there anyone's... I don't know. Interested?
I don't know. Am I sleeping in my chair again? All right. Travel. Um, travel. I think I'm just
gonna... I think I'm just gonna go somewhere. We'll do online dating. Okay. So, there's a
wedding venue. There's a lounge. A wedding? There's a wedding venue. There's not actually,
like, a wedding going on, right? No, it's just a venue. There's nobody even here. What? Freestyle
what? Are you fucking weirdo? There's nobody here. I'm pretending to...
Is there a wedding today? I'll just wait for it to start. I'm taking... I'm taking the fucking,
like, the seat of the parents. Will there be a wedding today? There are people here?
It's... okay. So, I... maybe these people are just checking out the venue? Oh, I thought I was gonna
use an extinguisher. It's not my wedding. Wait, is this the thing here? Hold on.
No. Should I plan an event here? What if I just invite a bunch of people here? Can I do that?
Invite to hang out at current lot. Imagine somebody gets married.
Okay. Not everyone could make it over. That's Santa. Santa doesn't want to come. And it's like,
no thanks, man. I don't think so. I got hung up on... This is weird. I'm just... send down the aisle?
Wha... wait. What's going on? Wait. Send down one sim. I have to greet people. Oh shit. Okay. Hey.
I already have to apologize. I think I have to apologize for inviting them here.
This guy hates my guts. Does anybody like me here? Can I call everybody over?
No. Flaunt wealth.
That was... they did not like... Oh, they... nobody likes that. Oh, I hate this. Oh my god. All right.
So set... What? What? So I am going... What did you take a picture of me for?
Don't take a picture of me. Don't put your finger in my face. Don't put your finger in my face.
This guy is very odd. What? If I... Hold on. I'm curious. If I send up the aisle,
send down... So, okay. I am going to escort you down the aisle. For what reason exactly?
She's Fortnite dancing. Yes. Somebody else is doing it. Somebody else is Fortnite dancing.
Finally. It took like two... It took like four hours. Somebody's finally Fortnite dancing
without me telling them to. Why did I get that excited about that? That's weird.
Did she die?
What? Who put the music on? Who put the music on? Turn the music off. That's fucking messed up.
Turn the music off. Turn the music off. Don't put the... Excuse me.
Oh, no. This is a tragedy. This is a tragedy. What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. We're all just crying.
I can't press the button. I can't press the button. Somebody else has to press it for me.
Somebody else has to press this button for me. I can't press it.
I didn't do it. I didn't do it. Somebody else is doing it. You're going to take the mic?
Can't believe he's died. There's too many people in the way. He hates acting. The festival of light
has started. What happened? Acting sad. Everyone's taking a picture of death right now. This is
strange.
I'm gonna give you my lightsaber.
I hope you like it.
You like it?
You just took a lightsaber and left. That's going to show up on eBay in exactly two hours.
Authentic Sith lightsaber. Usually sells for $500, but I'm going to sell it for $220.
Last updated. Six minutes ago. I hear you love a bargain. If you want, I can... I can't believe
my nerve is dead. If you want, I can show you where to buy cheap ingredients. All right, sure.
That's... I... You and me gonna go hang out somewhere? Yeah, let's go. Oh, where are you?
At home. Really? Sounds like there's a lot of people there. Ah, it's a TV. I'm watching something
on TV. Do I say... Okay, so... I would not open with this. Guys, don't open with this. Ever.
Where am I going? Give yourself a pep talk.
I gotta freshen up a little. No, no, no. We're good. We're good. All right. So,
wait. No, no, no. No, I didn't leave. I didn't leave. I didn't leave. Let's do... How are you?
How's your day?
Barsp. Grenoy. Flippin' heavenly.
Okay. Wait, were you there? Did you... Did she call me at the wedding hall?
Okay. Good to know.
No. What? No. Go down. Oh, God. I don't know. I was just like... I didn't... We didn't even
know... We didn't even see it. Did I just save the game? Your notification wall is full.
Where am I? Wait, I did it? Wait, I... How did I do that? Who else? I don't know. I don't know. I
told you I wanted to use this shit sparingly. Get up. Get up.
I gave you my lightsaber. I did this. I'm not doing that ever again. I'm not doing it ever again.
It was the... It was the fact she just didn't... Look at my eye. She didn't come into the place.
She was just flossing. Everybody get... We get to do it once and now I'm not doing it ever again.
I'm not doing it ever again. I'm gonna... I still... I have to get up and I'm gonna go
talk... We're gonna talk things over with Santa. I just... I didn't know what I was gonna do.
I need to go take a shower. Why am I eating this with my hands? What did I just do?
Okay. We're good. I hate your Sim. I do too. Okay. I need to take a shower.
Hitting the leddy. Why am I still holding this bowl? Get up. How do I clean... How do I clean
myself? Outfits. Outfits. Okay. Change outfit. No. They're all gonna... Oh, I don't... I hate it.
Can I like go... Like go into the fountain or something? I need to get over here and talk to
people. I need to... I need to go over here. I... What time is it? Okay. It's... No, it's midnight.
Shit. It's over. Am I gonna... All the hot dogs in the grate? I need... Why are you still making
food? Why? I can't... My energy is fine. Get up. Stop going to sleep in this chair.
Will you talk to me? No, dude. I need to talk to somebody. We'd have to just chat.
Okay.
I'm not poisoning the food. I'm telling you. We are... We've already hurt someone. I'm not doing...
No. You don't... Oh my god. You don't need to make any more food. That's not necessary. You don't
need to... This is... You've got like 15 people who have food here. What are you... Why are you
making this? Oh, I'm clean. You want to go stargazing?
Oh, hey. How are you? Hey. What's happening?
Overheating? Why am I overheating? Okay. I'm having a little bit of... I thought this was
blood. I was like, what? Blood from the car. Okay, we're making a new friend.
This game is ridiculous. What an unbelievable... It's just... It's just who?
How did you get in a call at 4 30 in the morning to come do a basketball competition?
You answered. You're here. Wait, it was you on the bench. Holy shit.
Is it ever going to not be funny? I don't know.
You're middle-aged? No, I'm a young adult. Look. What are you doing here?
Oh, yips. It's five o'clock in the morning.
All right. Hey, we're having fun. Whoa. Whoa. Settle down.
We're having a good time? This was a fun little outing.
See what's happening. All right. That's almost my turn. No one's missed a basket
the whole time we've been doing this. I've owned businesses. I don't have any money. I need to talk
to... Poor Jimmy Phipps. Poor Jimmy Phipps. You're making room. Oh, no. Wait. We need to...
We need to talk. We gotta talk. How's it going?
Hey, what about my galactic conquest?
Pretty cool, right?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Okay. Share photos. I've got some photos, right? Okay. I got some
cool pictures of the galactic... of the Millennium Falcon ride.
Can you guys see our cars?
Let's talk about aliens.
You think aliens are real?
I think we've got a new best friend.
Oh, hey. There's a celebrity right there. Hey, dude. I don't know if you know this celebrity.
You can't shoot at the same time. Let's talk about the rain.
Oh, no. Pleasant conversation.
You're making fun of me? Oh, no, no, no. He was doing like a funny impression.
What about favorite singers? Oh, goodbye. All right. Well, we know Jimmy now.
Where am I? Oh, no. I gotta go to bed. I gotta go to bed. Yeah, it's time to go to bed.
The same spot. I can't. It has to be sparingly. We have to play the game or else it's going to be
nonstop. I was going to click on random people and like punch them and hit them with cars and
slap them. No, we have to be sparingly. It has to be sparingly. Go home, your dog. I'm trying.
I've clicked it like three times. You killed someone 27 minutes into the stream. That was
different because that was a defense. That was a defense maneuver. A vampire came in my house,
snarled in my face, yelled at my dog, and then started doing magical powers in my house.
Went like this, like and then yelled at my dog and then went, did a bunch of magical moves.
And then I decided I was like, I have to fight. What are you doing here? What are you doing here?
What are you? What are you looking at my mailbox for while I'm not here?
What are you looking at? Why are you looking in my mailbox?
So
we're getting friends. That's an important thing. You don't hate us.
Right.
I got to go.
I got to go. It's nice talking to you, but I got to go. I gotta go.
What's going on with this? This bathtub is so gross. Take a mud bath. Okay, I'll do it.
I've never done this before. Is this cool? Does this like feel good? Or I feel like it would be
weird, right? I don't. I feel like it'd be slimy and strange. I think it's time to just invite
Santa over and just just hash this out. I've been wanting to. What's wrong? The pet is afraid of
the bath because of the mud or because of what I the what what what you don't like the mud bath.
What just happened? Did I just pass? Get out of the bath. Get out of the bath right now.
Get out of the bath. Out. Out of the bath now. I fell asleep and I went under the mud.
Okay. Hey, you're good. Well, when I get up, you're taking a bath tomorrow.
And I have to go to work again in two days. All right. I got some time.
We're going to get your bath and then we're going to play fetch outside.
I think I'm still employed. I hope so. Oh, no. I'm delighted you recommended I spend some time with
Kazooia. I was amused. I'm hallucinating. What's the matter? All right. Come here. Come here.
We're going to take care of you right now. Give you a bath. Give you some attention and then we'll
play some fetch. Actually, no, let's do. I haven't even done this with you. It's raining. Never mind.
I'm not actually going to eat this like six month old hamburger cake, right? Come over here. Yeah,
we're good. What are you doing? I almost just took a picture of you. Okay. What's with my frame rate?
Stop eating old cake. This guy died. It's cake. He eats cake and hot dog buns. Okay. We're going to
go pet the dog. Oh, having fun with your ball. That's good. Come over there. Let's go. Okay.
Brush. Yeah. Brush. Brush. Get out of the bathroom. Brush. Been a while. Will you go over here?
Brush. How do you feel? Much better. All right. Let's do this for a minute here.
Let's play. Yeah. He eats cake. The only thing I eat. Part of a well-balanced diet.
Okay. Very nice. Three points in dancing. Four points in rocket science.
All right. Well, then let's put on kids music.
Let's just get this out of the way.
It's 3.30 in the morning. When does Santa get up?
Come on over Santa. Let's figure this out. Get up. How many servings are in this hamburger cake?
I don't understand. This is what I've been eating for. It feels like a month listening to retro
music. It's summer now. Does Santa even exist in the summer? 7 a.m. When does Santa get up?
Santa's in the North Pole, which is what time zone? What time is it? 8 a.m. Okay. It's 8 a.m.
Let's go. I want to hash this out. They'd rather not come over. Okay. Dude.
Dude. What if I find him through FaceTime?
Oh, that's what you wanted. Okay.
Okay. So what if I traveled just to this location? Wait, does Santa have to be there?
This is a rental? Can we just go here? What do you mean rental? Host a party. He didn't show up.
Holy shit. Where am I? Hurry up. What? Festival of Youth? Wait, Santa might be there. All right. I
got to get. Okay. What's the like a sorry like an apology flower? What's a sorry flower? Get the
Christmas rose? Okay. Actually, that's a good idea. I'm going to buy snapdrakens because I think
they're cool. Okay. What is this? Oh, a painting.
For free. Who's painted this? I'm not. I'm not actually going to do this. I'm going to replace
it with a different painting. They're going to come back and be like, what the fuck did I take?
Why was I like on crack? Can I even paint? Dude, stop. God, this guy's such a weirdo.
Did you paint? Oh, no. You just want to chat. Okay. Let's talk. Okay. That's fine.
Okay. Wait, what are we talking about here?
Okay.
Oh, what is this painting? Let's chat. Discuss. What did I just say?
It's induced about a new show. Uh, Steve Friendly. Um, likes and dislikes. Uh, get to know.
Oh, sure.
30. Okay.
What's going on here?
Don't talk about aliens.
How about, um, what about dance techniques and stuff? What am I doing? Don't take a nap.
What's cloud gaze? Cloud gaze.
Bombaday. Let's go.
What exactly am I gaining a skill in here?
Okay. Um, why am I so tired? Oh, that's my house right there. What's this place?
Well, I'll get some food. How about some egg rolls? That sounds good.
Okay. Why is this? Why is my torso so wide?
Okay. Are you going to sit down? Hey, what's up? Don't do that.
How are you doing? Did you get something? You learned how to make egg rolls.
How are you? How's it? How are you guys doing?
We're all enjoying ourselves.
I'm telling a gross joke.
So what a new life.
You don't like fitness.
How about, um, it has to be sim of honor.
Wait, you get, can I come to the wedding? There's a wedding. Can I go to the wedding?
Yes. All right. I'm actually going to get to go. I'm going to get to go to a wedding.
This is awesome. Perfect. When is the wedding? When's the wedding?
Congratulations. All right. All right. Perfect.
When's the wedding? My birthday. When's the wedding? It's not real. It's next year. What?
Really? Don't forget about, don't forget about me.
So excited for your engagement. I can't wait for the wedding.
Do I actually get an invitation? I gotta make sure I'm invited.
I'm so enthusiastic about this. All right. We got invited. We got invited to the wedding.
You know, I'm going to, I'm going in there. I feel like I don't even go swimming in my own
private swimming pool. Wait, this is my house. Where's my house? Oh, it's not even here.
Where is my house? Where am I? Isn't my house right here somewhere? Oh well. All right. This
is nice and relaxing. It's trying to, okay. I gotta get out of here. I gotta go home. I can't
believe I have to wait a year to go to that wedding. Why am I? Oh, here's my house. It's not a real
wedding. The wedding doesn't exist. What do you mean? There is no wedding. Invite Santa as your
plus one. All right. Uh, bathroom and then sleep. You got food, right? Yeah. All right. You're going
to bed too. Let's go. I should wait before I go to bed. Turn that off. Did I miss? Okay. I gotta
go to work tomorrow. Let's get a full night's sleep. All night sleep. Peaceful. What career?
I am doing rocket scientist. I need more logic and I need to read three books. It's rebate day.
All objects purchased in build mode are in a 10% rebate. Buy an object worth at least 500
to complete this tradition. Why do I care about that? That's what I hear like sprinkly sounds.
What was that? What is going on? Hey man, over here. Grab yourself a piece of a hamburger cake.
Still fresh. I'm about to get points in something. What is it? Yep. All right. I gotta just wash
my teeth and use the bathroom and then I gotta go. I gotta. Yep. All right. Go to work. Just go.
I don't think I'm ready to get a promotion here. I'm not. I mean, I did the two breakthroughs.
We'll see. Dog's really happy. That's good. What is he doing? Check the dog's stats. How do I do
that? You can check its stats. What do I do? What do I do? Do you love with the microwave?
What's happening? Oh my God. Relax. I don't even. I'm not going to that. Take your dog to the vet.
Yes. Okay. All right. We're going to go to the humor and high drinks festival and we're going
to go. We're going to bring a few friends along with us. I'm in my work clothes. Don't do that.
Don't do that. Don't do that. Furious with someone nearby. Oh, didn't I come here with somebody?
We gotta figure this out right now. What's your problem? What's your problem? Tell me.
What's your problem? You punched me in the face at the end of our vacation. Hey,
this drama isn't my fault. It's not completely. I'm allowed to feel bitter about what's happened
between us. But why? Look, I'm going to apologize. I don't know what I did. I didn't do anything. I
attacked me at the end of our vacation. We good? I guess we're vibing. I think we figured it out.
I think we settled our differences. It seems. Hey, all it takes is an apology and a Fortnite dance
and you can rebuild some of those bridges. I'm not going to do it. I just want to see what's
available. Choke on a grilled cheese? What does that mean? Rip his heart out. What?
I don't care. I have to do it. Wait, he's still alive. I'm just kidding. It was a joke.
How do I apologize? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where's apologize? What's apologize?
You can't kill Christmas. Quick. Apologize.
Here's the thing. No one's going to believe him. Oh, you don't understand. He attacked me
with a lightsaber. He's a Sith Lord and he slashed me with a lightsaber. What? He has a lightsaber?
What do you mean? I keep trying to apologize. No, it's not working.
No, it's okay. I'm just trying to. I gotta find common ground.
Are we going to find common ground?
I'll give you a thousand dollars if you just stop. I'll give you a thousand dollars.
Here, take some money. Here's a thousand bucks. A thousand dollars. Pretty cool. That's a good
gift. Everyone's like, wow, I can't believe it. Here we go. Okay. Now let's just chill.
What's he calling? Are you calling? Put that phone down.
What am I bringing the chips over? What did I just try to bite him?
I think I just tried to bite him. Did I burp in his face?
Wait, hold on. What's happening right now? Is somebody getting arrested? Who's getting
arrested? Did he call the police? I don't understand what happened. What, because I
took a lightsaber out? Where did I go? I need to read this.
He can throw his very own lampoon party.
Did he just, what did he just do?
You did attack Santa with a lightsaber. Those are like just the things I don't,
I don't think whatever sentence I've never said. I mean, yes, I did attack Santa with a lightsaber.
But then I gave him a thousand bucks and we hashed it out and then he called the police.
Wait, what? Is the person supposed to punch me and steal my money? Who?
Hey, did you know it was a rebate day?
All right, time for bed. Wait, I'm almost, how old am I? Okay, I'm almost an adult.
Who was punching people? They said this person's been punching me and tried to take my money.
Am I ordering drinks? You slapped Santa. No, but I didn't slap anybody else.
I said, hey, this sim is slapping me and trying to take my money. That's not Santa didn't say that.
All right, go home. Somebody was dancing. Your sim was saying that about the other clerk that
left. She wanted to take your money. Really? All right, we got, we're going to the vet tomorrow
because I don't know what this means. Do I have to work? Oh, I got to work tomorrow.
I think this is dirty ass bathtub. I have to put a fire out. Order a pizza. Bitter about Santa.
Hey, come over here. Let's, I'm going to take you to the vet when I get back from work tomorrow.
I'm going to take a bath. So I think, honestly, I think the funniest thing that happened today
was the getting off of the spaceship, shitting my pants and falling asleep in the chair at the
geek convention. I don't think anything will compare to that. I keep thinking about it.
It keeps popping up here. Just sitting down, nodding this way and shitting my pants after
getting off. I have like three, like what would probably amount to like 10 light years worth of
time traveling. Okay. I can't believe you can tap me. This game is unbelievable. How do I keep
sleeping on this game? I only have any money. Imagine shitting yourself at Comic-Con. I have
$58. I gave Santa a thousand dollars for forgiveness and it worked for 10 seconds.
And then he called the police. All right. Get to bed. There's too much to do. All right. Get up.
I've got a lucrative opportunity for someone who doesn't ask too many questions. I need you to hold
onto a stack of money. What? I need you to hold onto a stack of simoleons. I'm planning to launder
until the trail turns cold. Sure. It may not be legal or moral, but it'll help. That's all I got
to do. Anybody want a piece of cake? It's the only food I eat. Spend all the money to get a
huge plasma screen TV. And when she shows up, I don't know what happened. Somebody attacked me for
it. Time for work. Six minutes. Just go. Okay. Actually it might get promoted. It's possible.
Although I'm uncomfortable. This has to be a little bit higher, right? Not quite. What's up?
Just stop calling me for this shit. Hey, Blork. I wanted to know. I'm trying to get to know this
other sim. Do you think I should? It's like, why? What does this even do for me? All right. We are
going to go to the vet. How do I go about doing this? I think it's travel, right? Travel? He's
in a lightsaber mood. Ow. That hurt. The vet's in a different world. Where's the vet? Newcrest?
This is empty. Uh, where's the vet? Brindleton? Okay. So we need to go to here. Okay. The clinic.
And let's just go for a checkup. Okay. Hello. It's my pleasure to meet you. How's everybody
doing? Um, I'd like for someone to check out the dog. Oh, look at this little cat. Hey, hey.
Oh, um, we'll just do a checkup.
Drain all blood?
Where am I going? All right. Let's, where's the, let's go. Let's get the pet examined.
Come on. Let's check. Let's see how you're doing.
Get pet examined. Okay. Here we go. How are you doing? Let's check. Let's get a checkup.
Oh. Okay.
Okay. We can do this too. This is, this person kind of work. No babies. What? Oh yeah. But I mean.
Hey. Oh, look. How you doing? You okay?
Is this a dog or a cat?
That's a dog. Okay. I thought it was like, wait, is that, is that a cat?
Cat. Okay. I'm going to go on their computer. I can buy a vet clinic.
I don't have any money. This is not going to happen.
All right. So we're done. We're going to head back. Cool. Where's my dog? Hey, come on. We're
going to go. Let's go. We're going home. Oh, you did such a good job. Whereas come here. You did.
You had, you did such a good job. I'm going to give you a big treat. Change outfit. I know. I
know that thing's annoying, but come on inside. Let's go. I don't want any strenuous activity.
I'm going to clean this bath. How do I clean them? How do I clean this? It's fucking gross.
Oh, there we go. Okay. Okay. Go to the, no, you don't have to use the bathroom. All right.
So now I need to eat. Drop it. Oh, no, no, no. I don't have to drop it. You're fine. What's first
person mode? Tea, right? All right. Let's go. Holy shit. You maniac. Why did you do that?
Why would you do that? How do I look at the, it's kind of scary. How do I get access to the mouse
to look at stuff? Escape. Oh, okay. That was weird. Troll forum. You only have work in minutes.
I'm going to let him do it. Are you having a good time at least? Wait, it's summertime. I'm going
for a swim. Wait, it's getting dip with who? Hey, hold on. Carpool will be at work here soon. Hold
just wait a minute. I have to, I have to swim naked in the ocean for five minutes. Get into your
house. What are you doing? I'm not going to go to work naked. No, you change into work clothes.
Yeah, you do. All right. Seems pretty happy. I said, dude, no offense, but your house looks
like a hotel room. Do I still have this angry, anger bug that I never fixed? That's actually
kind of funny. Yell at coworkers. All right. I haven't been promoted. Okay. Retro music.
It wants me to put a fire out. How do I start a fire? How do I start a fire? I need to put a fire
out. All right. What do I want to listen to? Retro music. Right. All right. But Phil, there you go.
Aren't you happy? And I'm going to order a pizza. I'm going to get a pepperoni. That sounds so good,
actually. Pepperoni pizza sounds amazing right now. Thin crust. Yep. Thin crust. You can hold it up
and it goes like this. Like that. Not like this. Like that. And you fold it a little bit at the end
and you... I... People go, will you fold? I fold sometimes. Not every time, but enough sometimes
when I do it. And you get that sting, that tang, that umami. When did I say that? I was talking
about it. I was eating food and I said, there's too much umami in this and I couldn't eat it
anymore. And I was high. Ollie, are you here? I was eating something and it was too umami and I
couldn't eat it anymore. I was like, this is like umami overload. And I just, I couldn't eat it
anymore. It was like too delicious. It was like overload. I forget what it was. It was... Wait,
really? It was blue cheese sauce that you put all over a garlic pizza. I think that's right.
And it was just... I couldn't take it. It was fucking delicious. It was a no red sauce pizza.
What was it? It was... Okay. It was a buffalo chicken pizza that I put a bunch of blue cheese
sauce on and it was overloading me. It was a buffalo chicken pizza covered in blue cheese.
And the type of sauce on the pizza and they had the way that it was hitting me right here to a
point where I couldn't eat it anymore. It was actually sensory overload. You were also really
high. Yeah. I mean, I was little. Again, like, you know, recreational marijuana is legal in Las Vegas.
Don't overdo it. You know, if you're of age and you, you know, something that you feel like doing,
just be safe about it and don't do it all the time. Do it, you know, sometimes. If you don't,
don't be pressured to fucking do anything like that. Same thing with alcohol. Do it the same way.
Where's my pizza? What? You didn't show up to... Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Where's
my pizza? Why would I be enemies with this person? I ordered a pizza and made... What are you doing?
I microwaved a pastry and I ordered... That's what you ate instead. That's the person that
wanted to take your money. Really? Interesting. I don't have this person on my social list.
What happened with Santa? Well, I'll give you a quick TLDR in case you don't want to watch the
VOD or watch these streams. Santa and I, we had a big Christmas party. Yes, this is yesterday's
stream. Had a big Christmas party. A bunch of people came over. We had a bunch of fun. We sang
a bunch of Christmas songs. Santa showed up and I thought Santa was trying to shoot me with a gun
and I freaked out about it. Then I got mad at him. We ended up having a... We hashed it out
and we went on vacation to Star Wars Land. Everything was perfectly fine. Everything was
very normal. This was not a problem. It was like we're at Star Wars Land. We're having a good time.
We split up. I became part of the First Order, which is like PogChamp. Santa did some... Dressed
up as a stormtrooper and was just kind of eating the restaurants and stuff. It was cool. It was
fine. At the very end of the trip before leaving, Santa attacked me. I don't know why. I actually
don't have any idea why. I don't... Can somebody... Actually, this is like not a joke or we're not
fucking around. Why did Santa attack me at the end of the vacation? Then we became enemies.
You checked his ID and it was fake, so he fought you. You tried to turn him into the First Order.
All right, but we're at Star Wars Land, dude. Really? They give us badges to what do you want
to do. Oh, I want to pretend to be in the First Order. I want to be in the Rebel Alliance. You
don't take it that seriously. It's like, dude, we like played a game of Among Us and I caught
you as the imposter and you stopped talking to me on Discord. Like, come on. So, eventually,
it got to the point where, you know, I wanted to hash it out at this party that we went to
and just said, kind of, fuck it. He was pissing me off and he said a bunch of mean shit about me,
so I took out my lightsaber and I fucking slashed him. Why am I microwaving food?
Oh no. Okay, so I'm eating too many pieces of cake and microwaved food. This is what I get
for eating all that cake every day. What do you want me to do? Okay, watch TV. Yep, turn on TV.
Watch, um, I don't know, whatever. Watch the kids network. You want to hear the kids music.
And now I'm flirt with Bako. Okay, how do I get a hold of Bako? Okay, that was fulfilled. Listen to
kids music. You want to watch kids TV and kids music. Go dance to it. The games are on now.
I'm doing it. That actually scared the shit out of me. How many hours do I have to listen to this
before he's happy about it? Who's outside? Is there somebody outside? Somebody said this looks
like a hotel room. What's your favorite stoner? Well, let's not use the term stoner. Partake
sparingly. Uh, I have a really, really embarrassing confession to tell everybody here. Even when I
talked a ton of shit about Takis and I was like, this, these things are disgusting. They just taste
like acid and all the music sped up. I heard like, I was like, why am I getting stabbed? Um,
but anyways, yeah. So Takis, I, I feel like there's this weird thing where I ate one one time
and I had never really eaten them before. I said, these are gross. I don't like these. I'm never
going to buy these again. I said that for real. I don't like these. I'm never buying these again.
Maybe six months later, I just saw them in the grocery store and did this weird, like ironic,
I'm going to buy them because it's ironic and funny. So I bought a bag of them and I eat them
all the time now. What happened? So I don't know why. Your pizza is in the mailbox? Elderly dog.
Why? This is ridiculous. I would be pissed about it too. You put my pizza in the mailbox.
You like prankster. That's some prankster shit. You know what I mean? Is it still good? It's still
good. He's going to leave it there. Oh shit. Hey bills, make sure you turn on the kids music.
Wait, he's going back? What? Hold on. You went back to get another slice. This is like a puppet
combo game. What's wrong? Just go to work. You strange, strange man. Does my breath stink?
Look at all the puke faces. That's a lot of vomit faces. Okay. I don't think I'm ever going to get
promoted. Let's just get into that. Discuss fears. Listen to lullabies. You got it. Volume's on
really high. I feel like this is a Mr. Beast video. Playing this music really loud and you
have to try to sleep the whole night through it or something. Sorry. Sorry. You left the circle
where the bed was. You don't get the $100,000. NPR music? What? How is this NPR music? He fell
asleep in the chair. All right. Did I listen to the lullabies? Enough. In case he eats it.
I'm just going to poison this piece and leave. It already is poisoned. I just...
Oh, I can't eat it. Oh, grab a poisoned serving. Throw it away. Oh, wait. The dog won't eat it,
right? Get rid of it. Turn this off. What time does it work? I actually have excellent performance
right now. I actually might get promoted one more day to see if I can do this. I'm hungry,
though. There's so many things that smell in here. The house is filling with gas.
How are you doing? Need to go out? This is still full, right? Yep. Clean the hell up.
Ira made... Dude, I have 1500 bucks to my name. I'm going to lose all that money.
Brush and then give a big treat. And then I'm going to make a big treat, too,
by microwaving a microwave dinner. Where are you going? Oh, she's so slow. She's perfect.
A big treat. Coming to a weird realization. The dog eats better than I do.
Not enthusiastic about it anymore. He's just doing it because I told him to.
He doesn't even want to do this. Oh, that hurt. Somebody said this is really depressing.
Microwaving a dinner and flossing is actually kind of sad. That's sad. This is actually depressing.
He won't even eat it. The nonchalant, not caring loss. I got my microwave dinner. That was so sad.
It's like he was so enthusiastic months and months ago about doing the floss when he has a delicious
meal. It's almost like he's doing it because he feels like he has to now. Because he wants to.
It's just like, I feel like I have to. This is what I do, man. I make my dinner and I do floss,
I guess. That was so fucking funny. It was so awful. He's clearly had enough. Yeah. I could
probably eat the dog food and be healthier. I already was single and loving it. That already
was unlocked. All right. It's time to go to work in excellent condition. Need to go to the bathroom,
brush my teeth, and we'll go. What the hell is this? Trash fruit? Harvest trash fruit.
Where did that come from? Let's take care of it. I mean, it's here. It exudes a constant stream
of smelly odors. Where did this, did somebody plant this? All right. I'm in good. I need to,
let me read a book. I'm going to read the, ah, nevermind. All right. I'm confident. I'm
doing pretty well right now. No. Oh, my dream of waking up and listening to Twinkle Twinkle Little
Star every single day. Sorry. That dream's fucking weird. It's my dream to listen to Twinkle Twinkle
Little Star every single day of my life. That's weird. That's a weird dream. Every day of his
life. Every single day. I'm never going to get promoted. Doesn't like being around other Sims.
How am I ever going to be, get promoted? Okay. Level up the hand. I can do that. Can we upgrade
the, can I upgrade anything? I can't. I am going to do, what should I do? So I just try to just
go completely focused on making sure he's healthy and get it. You need to get a table. Buy a business.
I have $1,700. I didn't, he's still eating microwaved food and just desserts every day.
No wonder he's so fucked up. No wonder he's so, he's got something wrong. I need to get,
clean out the fridge. It's time. It's time. Get rid of everything. Get rid of all this food in here.
Dump out all the leftovers. Get them out. Good. Get the microwave pastry. You put 10 in there.
You microwave 10 pastries and put all 10 in. Get it out and don't eat it and throw it away.
That's enough. Put that, put it down. No, put it down. You know, just eat it. Just eat it.
Just eat it. Eat it. That's the last of it. It's not, you're not getting any more of that.
Passionless job.
Job. I think he hates his job, but his aspirations are to be a nerd.
His aspirations are to be a nerd, yet he doesn't like his job, but he's, that's, he's in the,
one of the biggest nerd jobs ever. Isn't this his aspirations? Right? You're in the biggest nerd job
ever. True. But, uh, mine does not require you to be intelligent. So there's a big difference.
In fact, it's the complete opposite, I would say. Whoa. Where did that come from? Go swimming?
All right. Stop, stop, stop that. Enough, enough, enough. No more eating,
lick, drinking, drinking. Stop drinking out of the toilet. Get out of the toilet. Enough. Stop that.
I didn't mean to say that. Oh my God. Oh my God. This is so stupid.
I just don't give a fuck. Oh my God. This is so dumb. Swimming, uh, front to inside.
Hold on. Just do the, do the back float, man. Back float, back float, back float, back float,
back float, back float, back float, back float. What the hell? He's not dead. He's fine.
He's not dead. This is fucked. It's almost my birthday. Building some confidence here.
I'm good. This is something like, like Wolf of Wall Street shit. Do this before you just buy a
bunch of options, man. And then yeah, you go lie naked in the fucking water and earn a thunderstorm.
He looks like a lost whale. I'm good. I am showing off my moves. What? Lork has felt the cool night sea
against his skin as he pushed through the luminous waves, revitalizing and refreshing.
Don't look revitalized or refreshed. That's my favorite one. All right. I'm telling you,
I kind of, I kind of get this. I feel like I would be, I would get so dirt. I would want to go right
into the shower, right? Like cleaning something really gross. I would want to be just in underwear
and just, just only underwear and then get right in the shower. I feel like I would get
all of my clothes and stuff. They just right now go into the shower right now,
turn, have the shower running, like getting, getting in there. I'm going to go to lifestyle
coaching. You're like, we probably could use it. You didn't put any clothes on. Oh, I can
remove this. Should I get rid of this or should I keep it?
Come on, sing it, sing it. Okay. This rock. I found a rock outside my house. How much do you think
it's worth? No, he's not calling the rock. He's calling the council of
Barani. No, I called the geo council. How long is this conversation? Cool. Go pick it up.
Pick it up. Wait, I can play and I can shower in the rain. Go here. Wait, what's, why is that
the contextual thing to do? No, you go inside. You go inside. You go inside. Go inside. I don't
know what you're out here. Go inside. Do I have to work? When do I have to go to work?
Oh, I got all the time in the world. All right. So what do I, what do I, it's 10 AM.
Oh my God. I was just literally standing over there. There's another rock out there. Call the
council.
All right, we're good. So now what? Try to calm down. Oh, playing in the rain.
All right. Okay. Okay. All right. All right. That's enough of that. Check your buy mode.
See if there's anything fun. Oh, good idea. Outdoor stuff. What's like, where are the fun
things to do? Maybe I invite people over. Outdoor activities. Ooh. Old Timmy's wash tub. Oh,
there's a fireplace. Okay. I need to put that out. Bees. Whoa. I'm curious. Oh, I'm out of money.
All right. Let's try this. What do I do? I don't think that was a good idea. I can be a beekeeper.
I'm quitting my job and being a beekeeper. I can't light this because I'm afraid of fire.
This was, this would give me like science points. I think this is logic or science, right? Using a
telescope during the day. Yeah, that's kind of dumb. Oh, I'm still wet. There it is. Logic level
two. I need level three and I'm focused. I'll get it right here. I'm going to get a snack and come
back and do it again. Festival of snow. Ooh. Wait, I'll do that in a minute because I need to eat
first. Actually, there'll be food there. I'm going to sleep for like an hour or two. Go sleep for an
hour. Quick question. Bob Pancakes and I were planning to spend some casual, you, you just made
that person's name up. Bob Pancakes? That's a spam phone call. Ah, I want to, there's so much going
on. I want to do the snow festival. All right. I'll go. I'll go. Is it still under storming?
Wait, I can get married? Is this my chance? Meet people. I gotta keep my eye on this person.
Why do you have a knife? Why do you have a knife? Why do you have knives? I have to investigate.
Why do they all have knives? I need to order something and get some food to me.
And I need to, we gotta talk. Do they all have knives? What happened to me? You just took my,
I paid for that. I just paid for that. I just paid for this. This was $50.
I want 50 bucks. I got $250 from this person. He didn't even know.
Wait, hold on. Can I, how many times can I do that? How am I hacking him? Hack him?
Is this Watch Dogs? What am I, how?
Okay. Give me, I want that. I'm going to throw away in front of you. No, I just cleaned up. It
was, he finished it. I just, I just look like a fucking, oh my God. I just cleaned up that
person. I was trying to throw it away in front of him. All right. I'm sick of this guy. No,
no, we're going to let it slide. We're going to let it slide. I have to make some relationships
here. I'm just going to friendly introduction. They're all carrying knives.
I'm just trying to meet people. Okay.
Let's just, I'm just going to talk here. Mention flirty festival vibe.
Describe flirty dream. Joke about getting together. Throw petals. I'm just going to
throw petals in here. It's just going to be like, oh, it's the festival, right?
Okay. I would like to order a puffer fish, please. And hopefully somebody doesn't take
it from me. If they do, they get slapped. Thank you. Wait a minute.
I'm thinking about it.
This guy right here.
So I have, so, okay. More choices. Animalistic murders. Okay. So enable disabled non-deadly.
So they already can do the non-deadly stuff if they feel like it, but not just killing people.
Yeah. What the fuck?
Nice.
All right. Nancy land grab. Let's talk. Activate murder for one of them. It all goes to hell. If
you do that though, it all goes to hell. Enable it. It's all going to go to hell. Just enable it.
Don't come near me. You scum. What are you talking to? What? This guy has a gun.
Attention everyone. This man will attack you. He's talking to me. What? He needs to relax.
If I were you, I would go to a different town because everybody hates you here.
Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. Everybody relax. Everybody relax. Why do they all have guns? Everybody just
chill. Shut up. Leave me alone. Don't come near me. You scum. God damn it. I know I should hit him
with a bottle. Is that a snake? Like a vampire hunter?
All right. I got an idea. What is that guy? All right. Here we go.
I'm going to put it in my inventory. Let's see if I can do it. I'm poisoning the puffer fish
and I'm going to try to give it to that guy. Okay. So not this guy. Not this guy. Wrong guy.
Wrong guy. Wrong guy. I want to feed it to him. Are you all right? Why do people just steal food?
Enjoy him a lot.
What are you doing? What?
What's going on? Why is this guy so? He's feeling fantastic. This guy is immune to poison.
I am so confused right now.
It sure should. What is this move?
What happened? What? Why are they all running? That was fucking crazy.
Oh, I need to relax. I was gonna Mario like butt pound his head and he just kicked me
right in the in my ass and my balls. What happened? I tried to that guy. He's
fucking that guy's immune to everything. I tried to poison that guy and he was completely immune
and then I tried to crush his head with my butt cheeks and it didn't work and he read what he
said. This man right here tried to sexually harass me. This is not even the same guy.
This is a different guy. What did I do to this guy? What? I don't know what happened there.
That was fucking crazy. He witnessed it. Dude, that full kick. I almost need to like watch that
whole scene back because how did the cops get here so fast? Where am I? I'm sleeping. Oh my
God. Hold on. Somebody's got it right here. I'm trying to figure out what exactly happened here.
Let's find out. I don't get it. That's the guy I bought the food from. So what happened?
Okay. Where's this guy? Where's the other guy? I can't do it anymore.
He's in the he's to the right. He's in the front. He's the guy right there. He's the guy with the
points. He's the guy with the points. Oh Jesus. I don't even know what I was doing there. I was
trying to kill the guy. There should be an emote. We'll work on it. Whatever. I'm still here.
Do the ass stomp on somebody. I need to almost see what it does, right?
I'm just curious. I need to know. Wait.
Wait. He's saved scumming.
I just need to know. Oh, he's gone. It's saved. Is anybody even here? It's 5 30 in the morning.
We need to know and I'm going to reload it.
Oh boy. That's enough of that. That's enough of that one. That's it. We're not doing that one
again. We're not doing that one ever again. We're not going to do that one again and I'm going to
just quickly. I'm going to reload the game because that was very strange and I was imagining I was
going to jump and just do like a Mario ground pound on his head. That is not what just happened.
So we're going to go ahead and we're going to go back and I'm just going to go manage the world.
We saved it. Just go back and leave this space here. Somebody said what the fuck dude. I thought
it was a Mario ground pound. I thought it was like a butt pound. I didn't think it was like a squisher
ahead with my butt cheeks to over. I'm sorry about that. We're going to keep on moving. We're going
to keep. This is what happens when I save. I'm not saving anymore. It was a ground. It was a ground
pound. It was a yeah just like a you know what I mean like that. That's what I thought. I thought
it was a and that's not what it was. So we're going to just reload that game that we were just in.
That was pretty good Yoshi. It says booty face pound. Yeah but I don't know. I don't know what
it was going to do that. Wait where am I going? Where do I even live? Oh here. The spa is now
available. Um okay. Where where where am I putting the spa? Am I buying this or am I putting this
here? Oh okay. I yeah I guess I can go there. Why am I getting this right now? How come it's telling
me to do this now? Are we good? All right I am going to take a spa day. I think it's it needs to
happen right now. We're going to go do a spa day and relax. The sauna. Wait why is it saved? Yoga.
All right yoga time. Yoga class. I'm a little tired but it's okay. Let's let's wind down with
some yoga. I would like to join the class. 110 bucks. Get what? I thought I already paid for it.
Wait no it's not like roller coaster tycoon. Okay so let's go ahead and just let's go ahead and get
a aromatherapy. Uh we're gonna get a yeah let's do it now. Let's do a deep tissue. Where am I?
Yeah deep tissue massage. Relax. All right everybody chill. Everybody chill out.
There we go. Hey look at that. Mindful.
Very good. Is there somebody complaining?
All right let's go for it. I'm feeling a little relaxed.
That was a lot of money. I didn't realize how much that was. 180 bucks.
This is the guy that I couldn't poison.
Do a hitman level. Strangle him in the sauna. No I stop giving me ideas.
What if he chokes on a grilled cheese? That would be kind of no no I'm not doing that.
Nope not happening. Run him over in here.
Wouldn't that be gaining energy? Wouldn't this be relaxing?
Who is screaming? Your sim has gained a lot of weight. I think I did that. All right so now I
feel pretty good right? Okay can I just do yoga in the room? I'm just gonna do yoga in the room.
I'm not gonna pay for this. I'm just gonna do it in the room.
Why not? Well get this guy out of the way. Why is this guy blocking the way?
This is a door? Here it is.
I'm taking a bubble bath. Lee market is in town. Oh all right wait I was gonna do the winter
getaway. They have beds here. Can I sleep in a bed? Can I sleep? Do they have beds that I can just
kind of lie on? Just sleep on the couch. Wait that's the person that was in the costume.
I hear you're not too good at haggling. Why don't you let me take you to the flea market and show
you how a pro gets a great price. Let's go. Yeah this is what the the guy with the what was it a
like a raccoon or something? What was it? All right I'm going. Well I have three dollars. Yeah
so it better be good prices otherwise I'm not going to be able to afford it.
Okay what's up?
Where is this? Oh it's over here. Um ask to see outfit. Can I see that outfit?
Party outfit?
No. I want to see outfit.
So many options.
Oh
All right so we need to haggle with the vendor. I'm ready. Let's go.
Okay what do we got for sale over here? What do you got? You've got you don't have anything.
You don't have items in your store. I'm confused. We're you inventory. You have no money. That
doesn't matter. Why do there's nothing I can there's no inventory. I haggle I haggle with
nothing. Can you sell me the nothing please?
Are you crazy? I'm already losing money. All right. Oh
Oh
Brought a street sale?
All right
Hey how you doing? I got some stuff for you. Yes would you like to buy something?
Stop talking to me. Okay so what would you like to buy?
Oh what can I do for you?
I put some rare rocks over here and you're not just going to take them.
You're so tired. All right are you back to talk about prices or what?
No it's too tired. Um I want my stuff back. Did you sell it? To who? Where's the other stuff?
This is mine. I put it here. All right go to bed. Go ahead. Get some go go to bed. Go to bed.
Go a lot. You know go I can't sleep on this stuff. Oh I can buy this stuff.
Dude come on. This is his favorite chair. He sleeps here every time. This is this green chair. He
comes to this place and just sleeps here. Steal this chair. Oh who is it? I don't care. We died
here? Oh right okay okay okay yeah that's the right I forgot. All right let's go home. Go home.
Shit what was that? What was their name? Sell the fire pit? Yeah that's never gonna use it. I'm not
I'm afraid to light it. 76 bucks that's really not very much. Okay go use the bathroom and go
eat something. The name was Christopher Bulcob. Okay do you not have a job? I do have a job.
I have not been promoted this job because I keep getting distracted and then I end up
selling a piece of furniture to pay for something. All right are we gonna get a
Fortnite dance? That's the real question.
Actually looks kind of good. That okay I want people to tell me if I'm a weirdo
but that Salisbury steak frozen dinner is what that reminds me of and I actually genuinely like
those. They're one of the only frozen meals I like besides maybe pizza.
They're just I don't know it just it just hits differently.
What? Get out of that toilet. Just stop. How do I stop? How do I say stop? Stop stop stop stop
stop sit sit. I don't understand. I don't understand me.
Look at look at how smart she is. Look I did it. I'm smart.
Okay do I get a delicious treat?
What is this? Did I get like the ultimate bonding with uh with my pet? My animal?
Toy bar. Toy bar.
All right so what I get a hundred bucks for this or something?
Azarab will be. No stop talking about your insecurities. We're about to level up our
our bond together. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat.
Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Well it's been a while but I fucking nailed it.
What did I get for that? So we leveled up our our bond. That's cool. An open shower. Oh what
because the dog was there? I don't get it. I forgot about the bees. Oh I get maybe I should
have brought this to the flea market. Go to the werewolf neighborhood and knock on some doors.
Oh wait can I become a werewolf? I have a question. This is important. Um you guys want to see me
play more sims? Do you guys like it? You guys want to see more? Yeah? Okay. I think there's
still a lot more to see. I'm not ending the stream yet but I just I'm just curious. I think
it's been a lot of fun. All right yeah we'll definitely play more. Okay I'm gonna uh when
do I have to go to work next? Oh never mind. Hey look at that. Oh it's my birthday today. I'm
calling in sick. I'm gonna have a birthday party at the werewolf place. Yeah calling sick. It's
my birthday. I'm taking a vacation day and I'm gonna go to the werewolf neighborhood. And if
I don't have a birthday party. Should I throw a birthday party first? Okay birthday. Here it is.
So add an event. Uh a costume party. A dance party. Dinner party. A birthday party.
A weenie roast. A mountain climb. I need I don't have enough money. I can always
give her to some more Star Wars memorabilia. Oh why am I holding this? Okay I got money now.
All right I'm gonna throw a birthday party but I want to I want it to be somewhere interesting.
Birthday party. And I want to have it at um at 5 p.m. and I want to have it at where?
The hair and hedgehog. That sounds pretty I think I'm doing it the hair and hedgehog. The Von Haunt
estate. The ancient ruins. Is it the is the hair and hedgehog the place to do it? Go to the ancient
ruins. All right let's go for it. All right I am gonna invite me. It's my birthday and okay who does
not uh want to kill us? Not very many people to pick from. Uh all right you. I remember you.
We're gonna invite Santa just because. Right thing to do. Where's the guy I tried to poison?
Why is he not on here? Okay we need a caterer. Uh we can hire this role. I want to I want you
to enjoy the party. Mixologist. We're gonna hire this. The entertainer. We're gonna hire the
entertainer. And we're doing this at the ancient ruins. Does that sound stupid? I feel like this
is gonna suck. It's just a bunch of grass and a tree. This this is not cool. I mean I mean it's
cool maybe like historically or something but it's what like this is fun. It is. It's gonna be lit.
Don't. It's not. It's gonna be stupid. Is it haunted? It's five o'clock today. I have to be
ready for my birthday. Go to bed. I need to be fully refreshed and fully ready. I'll um it's
my birthday. I don't care. Oh I'm gonna put on kids music. Just relax. Here um you're so angry.
Don't worry. Here's your favorite children's music. Here it is. Go ahead put it on. Everything's fine.
Here's the birthday dance. We're gonna let him do this because it's his birthday.
Somebody said man child simulator. This is psychotic but I mean be honest though. Is it really
that strange? He's just kind of doing this. All right it is a little weird. How many key changes
are there? Yeah key change. Okay. Yay. Happy birthday. Happy birthday. That was so much fun.
What station do you want now? You want retro music? You got it. Who's with that?
And a pizza. We'll order that. We'll order that. All right you are ready for the day. Oh my god
this place is a dump. How are you doing? You doing good? We are going to not have a microwaved meal
today. We're going to cook a grand meal. A grand breakfast. A huge turkey dinner. Oh I can't I can't
make any of this. We are going to make a we're gonna make vegetable dumplings. No we're gonna what
do I want? What for birthday? Not chips and fish tacos. Oh I don't know. I can't. Hamburger cake.
Now how about pancakes? A taco casserole. Yep. All right taco casserole. And I'm gonna eat the
whole thing by myself. This is enough for like 15 people. I'm gonna eat it all. Yipsy. Fiddish.
Somebody told me he said stop. I'm not telling him to do that.
This is gonna be so good.
And and there it is. An entire taco dip just for me. I'm not even gonna use chips. It's excellent
quality. Oh I forgot the food. That still looks good. Oh it's my birthday party. Okay no no I'm
not ready. Okay I'm gonna go to the bathroom and I'm gonna take a quick shower. Why are you angry?
No it's you're about to go to your birthday party. Shower cold shower. All right let's go. It starts
at 5 p.m. All right let's go. How do I get there? I didn't miss it. It was 5 p.m. Not 4 p.m. Party's
about to begin. All right let's go. What did you bring me? We're here at my birthday party.
Here we are. Birthday celebrants need a cake. Caterers need a refrigerator. A counter and an
oven. Entertainers need a piano. Huh? Wait I need a cake? How do I get a cake? All right I need a
What do I need? A fridge? A table? No not table lamp. I just need a table. Okay poison the cake.
Okay what else do I need? What did it say? I need a day. I need a cake. I need a refrigerator. A
counter and an oven. Don't they bring this stuff? Don't they bring it already made? They're gonna
come and cook the food here. I need an oven. Bring your stove. What about a grill? Am I paying for
this? Am I paying for this? Okay I need a cake. Birthday hot tub. I know I shouldn't have done
it at this place. I'm not paying for this. Um roller rink. I can't. We're gonna build a rocket
together. No. Um all right I need a counter. A counter. A counter. A counter. I need a cake.
Do I have to make the cake? Get a bar. Public bathroom. Wait what am I doing? That doesn't
matter. I need a cake. Holiday fruit cake. Classic cake. Cake with style. Or dance floor.
You're destroying these ancient historical ruins. I just I just realized what was going on. I need
music. I need speakers. I feel like a DJ table. DJ. DJ booth. What else? A microphone. Like a band.
I need chairs. Chairs. It's gonna be the most comfortable party you've ever been to. It's all
gamer chairs. Okay what else? I need a birthday cake. Do I have to make a birthday cake? Fireworks. A
mini golf course. Okay where's it? How can I how do I spin this? That's too long. I have to move a
bunch of stuff. I'll fix it. I have too much stuff. Why is there a big why? I don't want this walled
in. I just want this thing. You know I just I just want this. There we go. All right this is gonna be
the most lit party you've ever been to. Let's just be real. What about a bowling bowling alley? Yeah
I think so. I think I'm good. Getting there. I just pulling up to this party. All right how
big does this need to be? Welcome to the party everybody. Are we ready to get this thing rolling?
I just need a cake. Check it out. Everybody come in. Check out what I got. Everybody head to the
party. Where are you going? Okay let's go. Already somebody already having a ton of fun. Hey uh
somebody thought this is a shitty party. I just went to one of those party rental websites and
just added every single thing to cart. Shipped it. You're the. How much would I pay for this?
How much was? Don't give him any money. You already paid. You already. He's.
There's a fire already? How? Anybody want to take care of that?
Both making cakes. Oh there's no room. There's no counter space.
I can't believe how shitty this guy really is. All right who's making my cake?
Ah can you make my cake? Do I? I'll do it. Santa are you just eating sugar butter and eggs?
You people are moron. You're stupid. This is not worth a thousand dollars.
Can I finish the cake? Why are we? How many cakes are we making?
Oh all right. Cake is here. We've got a cake. All right. Add birthday cake candles
and add a wedding cake topper because it's my birthday. I can do whatever I want.
I need to save this. Where am I? What was that? I'm going to try going to the gym.
All right everybody. It's time for the birthday cake. No it's not. No it's not. No it's not. No
it's not. No it's not. No it's not. No it's not. No it's not. No it's not. Put it away. No it's not.
No it's not. Put it away. Put it away. Put it away. Put it away. Not yet. My birthday's not over yet.
Put it away. Put it away. Put the cake away. Oh no he's gonna get a slice. This is the immune guy.
This is the immune guy. Put the cake away. That's the immune guy. I didn't even invite this guy.
Oh no he doesn't have a good look.
That shit has skulls coming out of it. There were skulls coming out of it.
This guy's superhuman. He's superhuman.
He's superhuman. He just kind of. He's fine.
This party sucks. Oh no is he dead? What happened to him? Nobody's looking.
Is the DJ here? Is the DJ here? Is the DJ? I hired a DJ.
Santa's hungry.
He's like he didn't even die.
Look at all these bonuses. Oh a pinch of salt and laughter. Cooking memories.
It made a new good friend. Ah new friends. Shades of short and fried.
This guy. I'm kicking this guy out.
No we haven't. You can't leave. We haven't even started our bowling.
No no. Wait the only. The DJ is the only person that's gonna bowl with me.
Nobody even danced. Good thing I didn't pay for this.
We're supposed to be bowling already.
Do it. Do it. Holy shit dude. Wow. That's it. And it's your turn. It's your turn.
Thanks for coming to the party. I appreciate the um all the effort.
Appreciate that. The tunes you play are pretty uh pretty hype.
Oh man. You know what? Nobody. Nobody can know that I did that fucking poorly.
You can't tell anybody. Nobody can know how bad that was. I'm sorry.
Nobody can know. Nobody can know how bad that was.
This is a force choke. Get out of the tub. Get out of the. Get out of the tub.
Oh my god. Get. I'm gonna delete this thing. That was a nice bowl.
What's going on?
RKO. Why all the rain is causing. She.
She got burnt by the electronic equipment in the rain. Get up. Get out of. Stop.
All right. Let me try. All right. It's over. I saved it right before this. Right before I poisoned
that guy at the party. And I just wanted to see what we get. We get a test for things. Right.
I need to see what this does. Where is it? Bro. You're baking a cake. Oh I have my birthday cake.
Wait it's poisoned. Don't eat it. Adulthood. Fulfilling dreams. Planning for retirement.
Perfect time to start wrapping up those lifelong goals. Oh happy birthday.
I'll see you later. I'll see you in a couple days.
I saved it before that. When we come back I'll just do the party. Suffocate what? For money?
Wait. I have taken it as a hostage.
Clear up reputation on social media. Suffocate with a diaper. I'm not.
Hold on to that one. What am I making? Please we need the diaper. You're gonna have to wait
for that one. I think it's ready. I think you can put it in the oven. What is he doing?
It's a weed man.
Is he being electrocuted by this? This is so dangerous.
Make a wish. What? Why did I age up again? Why did I age up twice? What just happened?
Oh it's because I'm eating the cake. All right well I got it saved.
All right. That's a perfect ending. So we're gonna rewind the clock a little bit next time.
Complete the party. We're not gonna poison anybody. I mean that was pretty wild.
Next time you'll see me I will be live on Friday. I'll see you guys on Friday. We'll play a couple
things on Friday. Maybe. I don't know. I think I'm gonna play multi-versus. I think Warner Brothers
isn't going to sponsor it which is just sick. They've added a ton of shit so we'll probably
play that for a couple of hours and we'll do something else too. I tell you I definitely
cannot play the Sims mods during that stream. I don't think so but we'll stream for like five
or six hours on Friday. We'll start with something and then move to it at the end of the stream.
In fact there's like four new characters. So I'll see you Friday starting at early early
right because I have to because wait what time is it it is exactly 7 30 and I just I just dropped
I just dropped frames right now. I just saw it. So perfect timing. So I'll be starting somewhere
probably around like same area from 1 o'clock 1 o'clock Pacific. Thanks for watching. That's
kind of that was a crazy one. Playing this game with mods is always an adventure. I'm glad we got
to do I'm glad I was alive for more than six hours. I'm happy the internet was fine but we're
gonna have to stick to the schedule because otherwise I will not be able to do it. I won't
be able to stream otherwise. So here's your new semi-permanent schedule like starting at 1 p.m.
and stopping whenever within within six hours. So see you Friday. Thanks for watching and here are
the credits. See you guys later. Take care of yourselves. What should we do on Friday? I'm
trying to think. Frog Detective? Actually that's that might not be a that might not be a bad idea.
I feel like Frog Detective can be done in two three hours right? Maybe. Or Breath of the Wild.
Breath of the Wild is easy just to jump into. Thanks a lot for the subs. There was a lot of subs
that came in. I really appreciate it. Thank you. Again I want to make sure I make it clear again. I
don't shout subs out anymore. I stopped doing that a couple years ago and I've given the reasons a
few times but I really do appreciate it nonetheless. Thank you so much. It means a lot. Play NeonWay?
What's the reason? I'll go over it in in 30 seconds. So I wanted to remove I wanted to remove
any incentive to giving money to the stream essentially. And shouting out and thanking subs
especially ones where it's a lot. I just don't want to incentivize people to just
dump tons and tons of subs and money into the stream and kind of almost this is not what people
are doing right? But effectively I'm gonna say something about it right? People have been
insanely generous to the stream over the years. I wish I could say more than thank you. But I
stopped reading donation messages. I stopped doing notifications. If you want to sub to the stream
I appreciate it. If you don't, you don't have to. I'd rather it be that way and we just kind of hang out
than do it otherwise. Time's up. Okay there you go. And people do still give a lot of subs and
I wish there was more I could say than just thank you. That's an insane amount of money to
give anybody. But I have such attention problems you guys already know it. Another reason too which
is not as big of a reason but reading sub names and taking my eyes off. Look at how much I can't
pay attention already. It adds another layer of me losing kind of focus on what I'm looking at.
And I already have those problems. I said you had the biggest nerd job but I meant it in a loving
way. No I know I know. We fuck around a lot here don't worry. I get it. But yeah I'll see you guys
on Friday. Have a great night. Take care of yourselves and have a wonderful rest of your
evening. See you guys on Friday. Take care. Call your mother. See you soon.