Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some Magica Wizard Wars.
Now, if you're confused by this, that's perfectly fine. This game isn't out. It's not gonna be up for a long time.
This is a pre-alpha of this game. It's the game that I got to play when I went to San Francisco.
I brought a thumb drive, they allowed us to record it, and they said if you want to make a video, then go for it.
You can talk about whatever you want, just don't talk about like the game's development because it's sacred.
No, they didn't say that. But this game's really cool. It's kind of the sequel, well not really the sequel to Magica, but it's an offshoot from Magica.
And something you're very, very easily gonna notice with this footage is this is not a single-player game.
This has nothing to do with single-player. There's no campaign, there's no storyline.
All there is is just competitive multiplayer arena PvP. That's the whole point of this game.
Everything that you know about Magica is kind of still here. The spell combinations are still here.
The messing around trying to find cool little spells to do those, that's still there.
But the guys at Paradox wanted to really flesh out a true multiplayer experience because a lot of us know the multiplayer in the original Magica was kind of technically broken.
There was a lot of problems with it. There was disconnecting, there was all kinds of issues with it.
It was still fun. Once you got people into a game and you got through the technical issues, it was a lot of fun.
This game is from the ground up a multiplayer game and that's something they're very, very highly stressing.
They want nothing to do with single-player. They just want you to go into game with a bunch of your friends and murder each other as wizards.
Now that's awesome. How is that not cool? Because from personal experience, when I played in the multiplayer in Magica 1, killing your friends was one of the funnest things you could do.
Just trolling your buddy and hitting him with a lightning strike and having him explode. That was the best part of that game.
And they took it and made this offshoot game with that. It's all about just killing each other.
And Friendly Fire is still here. You can kill your teammates so you have to be pretty careful and you have to be very coordinated with what you're doing.
Which kind of leads me to how this game is played. I'm not going to go into the basics of Magica because I'm assuming if you've seen this video and you're interested in this video,
then you kind of already know what Magica is. But for very, very briefly, I'll explain it.
On the bottom of the screen, there are eight spells. They correspond to Q, W, E, R, A, S, D, F on the keyboard.
This game is not going to be up for any consoles. It's kind of impossible for it to be on consoles because of this item combination.
Well, spell combinations. And you can combine any spell and they do different things. If you combine water and beam, you're going to shoot a water beam.
If you combine electricity and fire, you're going to shoot like electro fire. You can combine up to three spells for various different effects.
That's all I'm going to say about the basics of Magica and this game because that's how you play the game.
But I'm going to go into the team coordination here and how this is actually working.
A lot of people at first glance and me included thought this game was a MOBA with lanes. I thought they were going to be creep lanes.
I thought it was going to be just like something like League of Legends or Dota 2 or I thought it was going to be another one of those games.
It is not that. If that's your predisposition, if you think that that's what this game is, get that out of your head right now because it's it's completely different.
This game can really be described as just a death match, just an arena death match where you capture points to win the game.
And that's really what this is. That's all they're going for. They don't really have any plans as of yet.
I don't think to turn this into like League of Legends. That's not what this is going to be.
The way that Paradox described this game when we were in San Francisco is sort of like a team fighting game along the lines of stuff even like Street Fighter and like Marvel versus Capcom.
But a very team based. You all control one character.
And the reason why they brought that up is because if you look at the bar in the bottom of the screen, there is a spell bar down there.
Now, I can only use one, two, three or four if that bar is filled up and you fill up that bar by doing certain things by attacking people, by capturing points.
But that bar will fill the more stuff that you do, just like in a game like Street Fighter.
And if I use my one ability, it's going to take one quadrant of that four quadrant bar.
If I use my number four, which is a meteor storm, it's going to take the whole damn bar.
So they're trying to do this. They're trying to balance this in a way where you have to be very selective on how you use those abilities.
And those abilities can be swapped out. They plan on having a ton of different abilities you can put down on that hot bar.
So I'm very excited about that. I can't wait to see how many different combinations there'll be.
How many what what the meta is going to be? Will there will there even be a meta with that? I don't know.
I'm sure there will, but it'll be fun to watch it happen.
And to sort of stay on that same type of topic, there is going to be a fully fleshed out item system in this game.
There's going to be different robes. There's going to be different staffs. There's going to be different melee weapons.
There's going to be a lot of things you can unlock and equip that will change the properties of some of your spells.
So you can build different characters. Let's say you want to build. I want to do like a shitload of lightning damage.
I can build the staff. I can put on this melee weapon and it'll increase my lightning damage.
But it might decrease your shield capacity. It might make your frost damage be terrible.
That's how they're going to balance the game. And I'm very interested to see this.
Like I said previously, I want to see the crazy combinations that people will come up with when this game is released.
And speaking of releases, the game does not have a release date yet because it's a very early build in the alpha.
But you can sign up for the alpha. There's going to be a link in the description.
If you are interested in Magic of Wizard Wars, you can click that link and sign up for the alpha.
Maybe you'll get in. Maybe you won't, but you can still sign up there and hopefully you get picked.
And the game is going to be completely free to play when it is released.
You're not going to have to spend one cent in this game if you don't want to.
There will be microtransactions. None of us are really entirely sure what those are going to be yet.
But Paradox explicitly stated they do not want this game to be pay to win.
So expect something fair. I'm not sure what it is because we really don't know.
But that's going to wrap up the video, guys. Again, if you like what you see, go ahead and sign up for the alpha.
Hopefully you get in. I'm rooting for you, baby. And that's going to end the video, guys.
So I'll see you guys all next time and take care, everybody.