How you doing? What's happening? How you been? Good?
Please play with Steven Universe. I'm sorry, no.
I don't have anything against Steven Universe. It just...
Tasmanian Devil is a selectable character, so
that's who I'm going to play with.
And by the way, where's Daffy? I just want to get that out of the way. Where
is he? I think there's probably a bug in my game.
Some kind of a... probably a data that I had verify integrity of game cache. I
don't see Daffy Duck as a selectable character.
I'm not sure what's going on in my game, but... So what are we doing?
We're going to play multi-versus. I got access to the Alpha,
or whatever this is, the early access of it. It ends
in about two hours, so I want to check it out for a couple hours and
see how it is. Daffy Duck got fired from WB.
You don't fire a cartoon character? What? Nice milk voice?
Why do I know what you're talking about? I hate that I know what you're talking
about. Nice milk voice. Is it though? Is it... I mean,
maybe a little bit milky, but... What did this person say?
I got immediately used to the new mic. It sounds neat now.
Oh cool, thanks. Just to let you know, I haven't...
I haven't fixed anything with this mic. Anything, since the first time you heard
me use it during the horror games. I kind of sat down and opened up the
compressor and just got... I was just like, I don't care.
And then I said, I'll fix it later. It's not laziness.
It's not laziness. It's almost like a disdain for having to do it,
because there's so many little knobs I have to
twist and stuff, and move, and drag, and sliders, and
the attack, and the release time, and I'm just like, I don't fucking, I don't care
right now. I think it's okay. So it's laziness.
No, it's a disdain for needing to have to do it in the first place. It's not
laziness. Tweaking audio is the worst. Okay, you know
what it is? I set the whole thing up, and it took me like an hour or two to
get this where I want it, and what I want it to be like.
And then I got to mess with a bunch of knobs after messing with the knobs, and
then the knobs weren't in the right place. I'm just like, you know what?
I'll do it eventually. I'll figure it out. So don't worry.
He's lazy. Next person. We're playing multiverses, and you need to stop.
It's disdained laziness. But how you doing? Hope everyone's
all right. Hope you're having a good day. My day is going pretty well. I think it's
time that we moved over. By the way, after this, because I gotta
get going. We gotta go, because I only have until 5 p.m. Pacific.
Did I watch Obi-Wan Kenobi? No, I didn't. I own almost every Star Wars shirt that
they've released in the last four or five years, but I've only seen
the goddamn milk voice. That's the only one I've seen. I've seen the only
the new one. The new movie. I haven't seen any of the new shows really.
He's in Fortnite now. I know, right? Yeah. Do a watch party? I'm not going to do a
watch party. All right, so anyways, after this, there's a few games that I want to
play. It's going to be a mystery game, so hope you're ready.
So let's go. You guys ready? What's up? And because we're playing, it's
Warner Brothers. Hold on, let me make sure. Do I have a fly down?
Did you shave? Yeah, I did. But because it's a Warner Brothers game, I decided I
was gonna wear Aquaman. The shirt is so tight now. I don't think this shirt ever
fit me. This is a classic shirt, but I don't think it ever fit me for real.
And now I've gained probably like another 10 pounds or so, and it's
it definitely doesn't fit at all. It's very, very tight. You outgrew your kids'
clothes. And I gotta get a haircut too. I don't like what my hair looks like
today. Okay, you guys ready? Look at it. It's all
fucked up. It's all bunched up over here. I got to slick it back.
That looks okay. Not really, but whatever. You look like a vampire. Whatever.
All right, so here we go. We're gonna play... Who should I play with
first? I did the basic tutorial. It just plays just like Smash Brothers, except
it's pretty much 2v2, right? So let's go. Let me just do 1v1. This is
the teams. Let me just do 1v1. Let me just try it for now.
Should I play online already? What if I don't know what the fuck I'm doing?
Can you guys hear it? I should be able to hear it now. All right, 1v1.
Choose one. Okay, let's go. Cross play. That's fine. All right, should I be
Shaggy? Shaggy's a bruiser. Rain Dog. Who is Rain Dog? There's no
background music. Oh, it's because I turned on the streamer mode, so it
removes, I think, everything. Bugs Bunny. I was looking at
Tasmanian Devil. I'm gonna do Taz. Experimental. All right,
Summertime Taz. I don't... I can't... I don't have that yet. Is the game good?
What is all this for? Oh, what's this? Oh, dude, Hustle Town game!
I looked like a fucking... I was made out of taffy for a second. When I
leaned into the mic, I looked over here and I looked like I was made out of
fucking clay. It was weird. Alanna's to always...
All right, let's go. My mic cut that off. What did you hear?
The mic cut you off. You didn't hear me say, oh my god, Chalky Arian!
Oh, Aria Stark! What are perks? I don't care.
It's called... Do I have to pick a perk? I don't have any perks.
Onion... Onion Stark.
Taz, Onion Stark! This is fucking loud.
All right, let's go. No perks, no perks. I don't even know what's going on.
It's the first time I've ever played this. First to get two ringouts wins.
I have no intention of letting someone else be the victor. I was like, that's not
Taz. Why are we playing on this stage? All right, so you got the bite.
All right, what's that? Attack down. Oh, burp!
Oh, you got... I got Salt and Pepper too. Oh, shit! All right, that's what I can do.
Oh! Oh! Oh my god!
Why am I a turkey? Oh, no, that's not me. That's her.
Oops.
This is fun. This is fun. This is actually pretty fun. This is fun.
There's no music. Why is there no music?
No, I... Let me go to the music section. Good fight. That was actually pretty fun.
Let me... Let me... Hold on a second here. Oh, let's give a toast.
I toasted. Okay. Oh, all right. All right, let me tell you something right now.
Let's put the OST. Put on Looney Tunes music. It's on streamer mode. Oh, I'll fix it.
Excuse me, though. This runs fucking unbelievable. The problem that I always have, and I'm not
fucking around. I'm not making this up. Input delay and lag in an online match is unbearable
in every fighting game I've ever played. I just can't do it. I literally can't play them.
I didn't even feel like I was playing online. This is not an ad. No, it's not. This is not
a sponsored stream. I just got access to the game. Trust me when I say there is almost no
input lag, at least in that match. I'm going to give it a little bit more time. What is that?
Does this use rollback netcode? I don't know. But holy shit, that felt phenomenal. That actually
felt fantastic. You know what I'm talking about when you play a game online, a fighting game,
especially, and you press A to do a move and it's like, hey, hey, jump, jump. It's like,
I'm not playing. I'm literally, I'm literally not going to play. I can't do it. I physically
can't play. That felt really good. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. What do I have to do? Turn
off? What do I have to turn off? Streamer mode? Should I try something on the character?
This is fun. I'm excited. Audio, streamer mode. We're, we're in line at the Superman ride.
Why did I turn this off? Oh dude, it's so sick. I can't believe it. We can just walk through the
whole queue and not experience any of the queue experience and just get like half of whatever that
was, that movie, that like four minute movie they're playing. I guess I'm seeing 10 seconds of it.
Say goodbye to the VOD, whatever. Let's try bugs. Batman's locked? I really like this. I think it's
because I won. Every time I play Smash Brothers Online or a fighting game online, I get fucking,
what's the term, beat up? It's bad. I can't even like play. I can't even have fun.
It's called rolled, obliterated, decimated. All right, I got a match. Uh oh. All right,
versus Wonder Woman. I mean, unlock your first perk bar. I get mastery level two. All right.
All right, let's go. Is Seinfeld going to be in the game? Are you serious?
All right, I don't, I don't know how to play with any of these characters. All I know is they have
cartoon moves. If you have a cartoon move, I'm going to be, you're going to be fine.
Let's two ring out. I like this. Oh, what stage is this? Oh, that's a, okay, that's a stun.
I don't know what his fucking moves is. I just hit myself with my own rocket.
He, okay, that's, what the fuck was that? Oh, oh, there comes a comeback.
Oh shit. What the fuck just happened? I got a pie.
What the hell's that? Sorry. All right. My hands are so greasy. My hands are greasy.
You have no idea how greasy I am right now. It's bad. Oh, that's it.
I'm so greasy. You have no idea. I'm covered in fucking oil.
To do it to him. He's actually cracked. Not really. I just itched my ass on camera.
What? Why? I'm tired. I just like woke up. What the fuck am I doing? I'm fine. I'm fine.
I got a new unlock. I got a new utility perk. Copyzilla. We don't care. That's fine. I don't
care either. Fucking self report, self-made problem. Try play as Shaggy. This game's fucking
fun. I was so concerned going into this because I saw all the advertisements. I'm like, okay,
I'm not so sure. Maybe this is just first time playing. I haven't played a game like this in
a while, but this feels clean. This feels really clean and really good. I have emotes too. No,
I swear to God, this isn't even an ad. I promise you, this is not an ad. I just got access to the
game. I promise. I promise this is not sponsored. What? Oh, all right. So I can practice.
So everybody has a combo, right? He doesn't. Okay. Who am I fighting? Uh oh. I'm fighting.
It's uh oh. I'm fighting Chad Shaggy. This person's a level 10 Shaggy. I'm going to get fucking
destroyed. I'm scared. Weak Shaggy. What are all these? Uh oh. Let's go. Oh my God. I forgot
how to play. How's he doing that move? Where'd he get a sandwich? Oh, whatever. He had a perk. I
didn't have any perks. Whatever. I had perks. I don't have perks. That was fun. You know what?
I like, I think I like bugs. No, I got to play with every character at least once. How many,
how much time is left on this alpha? Oh my God. I can only play for like 40 minutes. Why didn't I
play this two days ago? Why didn't I do this like a week ago? I was so concerned. I was going to hate
it. Okay. I want to, who should I play with now? Do Tom and Jerry? All right. Hold on. Let me,
let me go into practice with Tom and Jerry. It's time to try teams. No.
How do I do just like a practice? Oh, here we go. Like advanced tutorials. No, I already know. I
kind of know that. Is there no practice? Oh no, there is practice. Yeah, there is. Okay. So let's
do Tom and Jerry. Dude, I can do pirate Tom and Jerry. Okay. So they run together. Everybody has
a double jump. Everybody has a charge. All right. That's like a three hit combo. One, two, three,
four. Pretty nice. Pretty nice. Up. Ooh. You get a pretty good combo there. Ooh. What? So all right,
regular special is you launch out Jerry. You can, excuse me? This seems advanced. This seems like
advanced techniques. That's a mouse trap. How do I get Jerry to come back? This is the hardest
character to play in the game. Okay. Well, I could probably see that. Dude, even that combo is insane.
How would you fight against this? This seems crazy. Oh, what if he dies? What's the fishing
line do? Is it a grab? Can't tell. Holy. Oh my God. If you can actually land that, that's crazy.
All right. Okay. That's cool. They're all right. They're kind of hard to play with. What about
Batman? Well, that's okay. Cool. All right. Batman. That's not ready. It's not ready.
Wait, I'm getting a, that spells not ready yet. That spells not ready yet.
This can't use that yet. All right. Batman's kind of cool. What is Batman's default spells?
All right. That's I don't, I don't know. Oh, that's the battery. Okay. Does it blows up too?
Doesn't it? Uppercut. Okay. What about down special? Ooh. Okay. Cool. What about Superman?
No, what about Velma? What does Velma do? Does that mean Scooby-Doo is going to be in the game too?
It has to be, right? Oh, I see. Okay. All right. All right. All right. I think I actually like,
I think I like Velma. That's the side. What about the charge? Okay. Up special is this weird potion.
Oh, it's a freeze. Why do I have a big head mode? What happened? All right. So side B is this like
run and you grab and then you, can you throw them off? You take them to the edge and then they bounce
backwards. Okay. All right. I like Velma. I'm going to try Velma. I think the next game. What is this?
Who's this Pokemon? Rain dog? Who's rain dog? What show is this from? All right. What's standard?
Actually kind of good. This is an OC character. Oh, really? All right. Seems kind of cool.
Be Jake. He's pretty, pretty, pretty good. All right. How about Jake? I like that three hit combo.
Two, three. What about, what about down attack? Nice. That's really good. Oh, he's super stretchy
too. All right. So what about standard special? It's a bite. Oh, okay. That's a cool down.
All right. That was pretty cool. Or what about down special? You turn into a house.
I'm imagining, right. Okay. It's like Pac-Man. All right. What about side? Turn into a horse.
That's up special. That's pretty cool. All right. So could I, so let's, let's do a little bit of a
combo here. So check this out. Ready? Oops. No. Oh, all right. Cool. Nice combo. Whatever. Oh,
what about Steven Universe? Standard punch. Okay. That's a three hit combo. Why is it a bubble?
That's pretty cool. Side smash, up smash, uppercut. All right. What about specials?
What the hell is that? So that's a projectile defense. Okay. What about up? What the fuck?
What can I jump? Can I jump on them? Oh my God. I can jump on them. Holy shit. You can knock them
into the, um, all right. That's advanced techniques. Pretty cool though. All right. What about garnet?
All right. I like that multiple hit combo. What about down? That's very far reaching.
Seems incredibly powerful. All right. Wow. What a fun game. Jesus, man. What am I doing?
I'm so unaware of the weird gross things I'm doing today. All right. What about, uh, up?
Do you put these stars out? All right. Pretty sick. What about Superman? Oh, Ari Stark. All
right. Very quick. I feel like this is going to be a, a meta character. Lots of fast movement
slashes, tons of fucking movement speed. All right. Sick. Let's go. I'm ready. I'm going to
play around as Belma. Oh, I still want to do 1v1. Oh my God. I forgot what Jake and Finn are,
Finn's in this. I didn't even see them. All right. What do you got for stuff?
What about your perks? I don't, I don't have any perks. All right. Belma versus Steven universe.
See, I don't have any perks. Equip all. Let's go. I don't have any perks. See? All right. We're both
level one. It's fine. Not one of these matches has felt laggy. Not one. And that gosh darn it.
I mean it. I feel like I'm connected with a ethernet cable to this other person's computer.
What's that? You went through the stage. Get away from me. Oh my God. Don't fall off the
waves. All right. Sorry. I got 60%. I got 60%. What was that sound? I feel like I'm not playing
her correctly. You look like the annoying orange. What are you talking about? Am I level two yet?
Oh, I got some boxes. Oh, I got a perk. Cool. Collection. Oh, okay. Gold times a hundred. Okay.
So I have this. Your team receives 10% reduced ability cooldown. How do I put that on? This taunts
too. All right. I'm going to play bugs and I'm going to do team fight. Let's try it. Team fight.
Choose your character. This is a rare. Whoa. All right. Cool. I don't, I can't do anything,
sort of. Definitely going to put this on. All right. So it's 2v2. I love this. These kids
game Tuber reactions. I'm actually excited. These kids game. Double fucking Batman. What the hell is
this? Is this allowed? At least we have perks. Prepare yourself. All right. I actually would
probably bet on this team. If this were real. I think you're the toughest I've gone up against.
Let's go. Watch out. Oh, got him. Slowed him. He slowed. He slowed. Got him. Good interrupt.
Shit. Oh, got him. Sorry. Sorry. Don't let him get away. Don't let him get away.
Nice job. I got carried. No, I didn't. I got carried. That was a good team effort.
That was a team effort, man. Equal effort. Yeah. Although I am in the, okay, so all the level ones,
this is why I love playing a new fighting game right when it comes out. Because all of us,
every single person besides a small percentage of people, we're all just kind of pressing buttons.
It's great. I love it. We're all just kind of still, I don't even, I don't even know what
Bugs's downbeat even really does. I know it goes underground,
but I mean, everybody else thinks that too. It's great. Prepare for my dectifying exploits.
Say hi to my uncle. Hey, you know what? I don't even care. Just fuck the whole thing up.
What is going on? I do look like a big kid. What's happening right now? I look like a big kid.
What's going on? That's better. Put it to a middle part. I don't think I can even do
a middle part. I don't, I actually don't think I can do a middle part. That was just wet.
Please put glasses on. All right. I got to pay attention to this. I'm like, I'm like seven in
one right now. Shit. What's wrong with me? Oh, how did he fucking miss that? I'm gonna
fall off of this motherfucker's 143 Fahrenheit. That guy's at 143 degrees Fahrenheit. Fucking
get rid of him. Finally. Shit. Look at this. 420 damage. I'm starting to understand, but I
didn't throw it. What are you talking about? I didn't jump out of bounds. I'm starting to
understand Bugs Bunny's moves. You got to pick somebody and just play. That's the only way.
You got to just play. I'm going Bugs. What about the chapstick? Thank God for reminding me.
Of course. Just play the game. Oh, they're both level one. I think we're fine. Is this the same
person that I was with last time? More games for your wax face. What did I just witness? I don't
know. Whatever. Let's do it. Oh, no. Oh, Jake, no. Stupid reactions. Oh, missed it out. Oh,
my pie. Fuck you. I got to get a stun. Goodbye. What happened? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
we got it right there. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Don't worry.
I got it. I got it. We win. I feel like I went pretty cracked out right there.
Nice job. That was a nice game. That was a nice fight. Good job. Your lips are way too pink. I
don't know what you want me to say, man. Your lips are too pink. Oh, all right. Cool. I'm enjoying
my multiverse game. What time is it? I have one hour to enjoy this. All right. One more match of
bugs. I mean, I'm going to go back to wait, money. Cool. I accept a rematch and teams are one v one.
What's the next game after this? I have I don't know. I downloaded like four things. I have
Sniper Elite five, the Miku game project, um, mega mix or something. And then I also have
Pac-Man museum, which I feel like I hold on a minute. Let me see. I know the kick kick into the
bat. I like bugs is hold on a minute. His side air is really, really good. It's really powerful.
Use your character. I gotta stop spamming the mallet though. That sounds good to me.
What is this? Your team deals one additional damage when knocked back.
Enemies collide. Okay, cool. Oh, we got a mirror. Oh, what is that? That's fucking crazy.
That's crazy. That's, that's really powerful. I got it. What stage is this?
Oh, I almost got it. Left trigger. How do I use this? Get out of here. Easy on the edge here.
Shit, that was close. I could, I got caught up. I got caught up. Yeah, let's go. Let's go again.
I feel like that was good teams. I threw. Let's go. No, I didn't. Let's do rematch.
Choose your character. All right. I'm going to change it up a little bit here. Lord stock.
You must be thirsty. Snacks. Yeah, let's go. Snacks. Did you turn the swear filter off?
I don't know. Maybe. Can I get a birthday wish? Happy birthday. It's your birthday today.
Happy birthday. It's a kid's game. You need to stop sweating. I sweat all day, man. I could be
reading a book in bed and I'll just be like sweaty. Even if the book is, it could be a cookbook. It
doesn't matter what it is. Honestly, it does not matter. All right. Right off the bat. Go in.
And I forgot how to press the button. This guy fucking fly up already. Holy shit. Do we have any
fucking power? Dude, fucking can we knock somebody off the fucking edge? I just spit a tooth out.
That's what it felt like.
At least he didn't eat me.
What's happening? I don't know what happened. I'm so fucking sweaty. Oh, what happened?
I didn't know you could hold on to the edge like that. I was like stuck to the edge. What was that?
Fuck. I was stuck to the edge. You're peeking your mic. I'm going to fucking break it in half.
Nice mic. All right. Taz is fun, but like I just, the up, his recovery move is not that great.
You can hold on to walls and climb back. Yeah, that freaked me out. I was just stuck on the wall.
I was just started mashing buttons. I was freaking out. All right. We're going back.
Oh, I was already in a party. Sorry. Can I buy some stuff versus the AI? Free for all?
Foreplay of mayhem. Let's do some 1v1s. Let's go back to bugs.
I have a black eye? No, it's the shadow from like, uh oh, Tom and Jerry. That's good. All right. Let
me, like the 1v1 scenario, I think I'd be fine. Prepare yourself. Oh, the reacting YouTuber to
the fun new kids game. That's not, it's not even a kid's game. Batman's in this. That's T for teen.
I'll beat you. All right. Leave me alone. I got to win a match. Oh, the bounce. Damn it.
Use this.
Huh? Damn it. I want to end up with that. This is really funny. What? Piece of cake. I'm not a
victory in the continue. You know what? I got to get used to. So with the analog, when you press
up to do up smash or up air, whatever, sometimes I do left or right because the analog is still
thinking I'm pressing left and right when I'm trying to press up skill issue, skill issue.
It looks like a black eye. I think I'm just very red today. I shaved and I'm playing an intense
fighting game and I'm trying to do and I'm trying to get as much. Look,
I'm trying to just go, go, go, go, go, because I only have like 40 minutes left in the fucking
alpha. It's a smudge on the camera. I don't think so. It looks like you're wearing rogue,
rouge, rogue blush. I'm just super excitable right now. I'm just super excitable. I'm playing a game
that I'm intensely paying attention. You know, I get shit on this channel all the time for dude,
fucking read the tutorial. Why are you walking into walls? Dude, you went in a circle five times.
I'm getting victories here and I'm getting red.
Red. Oh, you caught me. Nice job. Nice job. Shit. What was that? How are you still alive?
That was crazy. Good fight. How are you still alive? You had 200%. Yeah, I know I did. You're
right. Look at this beautiful blushy boy. I need a haircut. I'm just sweating. It's not even blush
people. Oh my God. He's blushing. No, I'm sweaty and in pain. That's it. Oh, he's blushy. Bugs again.
Let's go. This is actually really fun. Let me see something. So the air specials are different.
Choose your character. Okay. I got to drop that safe more often.
It reminds me of the Pac-Man fire hydrant from Smash. Prepare yourself. Oh my God. I haven't
blinked in an hour and 15 minutes. Clean the camera. There's nothing wrong with the camera.
Get your eyes checked.
All right. You morphed on him? Let's go again. That was a good one. That was intense.
You didn't speak at all? Yeah. I'm trying to win. I'm trying to play. Guys, I have to prove at
least once a year that I understand the concept of a video game. At least once every six months.
I have to at least prove to you guys that I can still drive the video game car sometimes.
This is fun as fuck too. God, I'm so happy. A fighting game. Finally, for the love of God,
I can actually play the game online. It's not I press a button and a half a second later,
the action happens. So explain to me while I play because I won't read it, but I'll
somebody will spam it to me later. Why is this so clean? Why is this so good?
Oh, nice hit. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job.
I got to get in there. I got to get in. He's getting too much range. Oh, I missed it.
Anyone taunt? Good job. That was insane. All right. One more. One more. This is a rematch.
Yeah, we got the best two out of three. Let's go. You look like a skin walker.
I'm sorry. What do you want me to do? How's this? Is this better?
All right. This is this is for all the marbles. This is for all the marbles.
That was intense. God, it's I feel like that super villain that is so happy that finally there's a
challenge for him. You know what I mean? Like finally, finally I can play against somebody
that's intense and that feeling of fighting and strength. Finally. You look like Mega Mind.
All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's go. This is this is it. Now I know why people play these.
I get it because my whole body is like kind of nervous. Is that weird? All right, let's go.
Oh, my God. Do it. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. What's happening? All right. All right. Let's go.
Match point. Red team. You lost your friend.
Good fight. Good match. God damn. Damn. That was fun. Nice fight. I was really afraid that
you're going to come back there. Oh, my goodness. I look 14. I have to stop shaving my face. I feel
like people look at me when I shave my face. They go, what's wrong? Why does he look so weird?
I understand what people are saying now. Holy shit. Oh, my God, dude. That looks crazy.
All right, we got only got like 21 minutes till the alpha is over.
All right, we're going experimental here because I know I can play with bugs. Bugs is my main,
but I kind of want to just jump around as another character in the 20 minutes I have left.
What does Wonder Woman do? Let me go back. Okay. The thing about... Okay, but what about bugs is...
Oh, that's what that does. Okay. There's so many more combos I could have been doing.
If you're in the air, he paints it. I get it. Okay. Interesting. All right, let me see Wonder
Woman. What's the combo for Wonder Woman? Cool. One, two, three. The one thing I don't like about
bugs is bugs has kind of a weird combo. He just goes like this and you can miss it really easily.
Okay. What is that? Oh, okay. Is that a pull? Oh, it's on a cooldown. That's like a little dash.
All right. Down special seems to be a shield, I think. Up special is this float and you can...
Okay. All right. I think it seems pretty self-explanatory.
It's a sword character. I'm wondering about that whip. All right. Let's go for it.
It seems cool. Sword Andy. I only got like 15 minutes to play this game.
We'll go back to teams. That's just fun to jump around.
And I am genuinely not fucking around. I know that we fuck around a lot on this channel and
I mean, and we tell a lot of jokes. This is very good. I mean, go ahead and say
add if you want. It really is. This is like the most fun I've played in a fighting game
since I was like fucking like 16 or something because it works. It looks really fun. I'm telling
you it is. All right. So while there's a few minutes here, why can this game play so well on
the internet? What is this thing people were saying? This like netcode thing. And why doesn't
every video game that's a fighting game use it? It's called rollback netcode. Prepare yourself.
For no reason. Is there a downside or something? Why wouldn't anybody use it?
It's really difficult to implement. It's pretty much arcane magic. It predicts what you were just
going to do. The infants of our tribe are stronger than you. Let's go. Shit.
Don't fall off the edge like an idiot. Oh wait, I just jumped. I'm giving my teammate that. What?
In the future. There it is. One more, right? Blue team.
Oh, you fly to your teammate. All right. Red team.
Oh, get that last hit. Oh my God. Kill. Kill before I die. I blew it. I blew it for us.
I blew it for us. Way too bad. I just didn't. I didn't know how high her thing went. It's the
first time I played with her. I blew it. I just like didn't know how high the thing.
It's the first time I played with that character. Sorry. I'm sorry. It was fun. All right. New
character. I threw and now I did. So it's really hard to implement this netcode. Who made this
game? What? What developer made this game? Because and what else did they do? Me. Let me spend some
currency first. It's really hard to implement. Well, they did a phenomenal fucking job.
Batman is locked. I want to play a game with Superman. How much does he cost?
How do I unlock him? 2000 gold. All right. Yeah, sure. I want to try and match with Superman.
Stop swearing. My mom's getting mad at me. That's a mature audit. You had to click the
mature audience thing. All right. Let's play before the servers turn off. Let me just see how he is.
Wonder Woman seems pretty solid. Just a solid pick. All right. Let's see Superman. Superman has
this punch. Big charge. That combo seems insane. And you finish it off with one of these.
One, two, one, two. Jesus. All right. Superman is very much a punch character.
I actually really like characters like this. I like just bouncing. Okay. So what about your
specials? This is ice breath, right? Okay. What about side special? Holy shit. I can aim that too.
Okay. Superman seems pretty ridiculous. Is Superman insane? What's the tier list look like?
All right. Down special. What's the application here? Oh, you just, okay. It's kind of like a
defense. Up special is big fly. Can you fly as Superman? No. You can fly as Superman.
So you have to be in the air. Wow. Holy shit. All right. Superman seems pretty fucking cracked,
if I'm honest. Let's go. Is he not? They nerfed him? Do they even have time to nerf any of these
characters? The game has been in early closed alpha for like five days. Choose your character.
There was already a closed network test. Oh, okay. I'll do my best. I'll try it. How can
be staring into our souls? I'm reading the chat room. He looks off. Maybe you think it's because
of this? Do you think it has anything to do with whatever this is right now? Do you think it has
anything to do with how off I look today? I wonder if you think it has anything to do with this.
They mean Superman, right? That's what I was saying too. That's what I was saying too.
All right. Superman time. I feel like with a little practice, I would really like Superman.
He kind of lumbers around, but he's really powerful. Oh shit. I keep getting caught.
That's probably it. Whoa. What the fuck was that? Get him. Jesus. He's a little slow,
but I like the power. I like the move set. It's pretty good. This is a man-sized character. I
only got 10 minutes. Okay. Well, should I play it? All right. Viewer's choice. Who do you want me
to play with? Superman has a triple jump? Viewer's choice. What do you think? Shaggy?
I haven't played with Shaggy. You're right. Okay. Shaggy. I played a lot with bugs already.
I did one. I played the first two matches with Shaggy, but I had kind of no idea what the hell
was going on. All right. He's got a combo. What are his moves are doing here? He has this super
Saiyan mode. Interesting. Okay. He goes ultra instinct. I have to move this light. Oh, that's
our Harley Quinn's in the game. Does that mean the Joker will be in the game eventually? I feel like
all the Batman characters will be eventually. They have quite a roster they can fill out if
they really want to. I would love to see Daffy Duck. I don't know where he is. Oh, I got it.
Can I eat this? What can I do with this? What do I do with this sandwich? Oh, I got it. Oh shit.
Oh my God. I keep trying to just flatten them. What? He went through the fucking thing.
Oh my fucking God. Knock him off. I don't like Shaggy. What the fuck? Why can he go through that?
That's so weird. This motherfucker can go through the whole stage.
Holy shit. Shaggy. You're the fucking worst character in the game.
Okay. He's fucking terrible. Shaggy fucking. Oh, Shaggy. Look at Shaggy.
Holy. Shaggy is the worst character in the game. Actual skill issue. Shaggy's S tier. Not for me.
Not for me. Quick. I got to do one more with bugs. Before Craftman blames his tools,
Shaggy just like smokes weed and fucking sits in a chair and screams at ghosts.
He doesn't have any superpowers. Superpower. Superpower. Superpower. Superpower. Superpower.
Superpower. Superpower. Superpower. Superpower. Superpower. Superpower. Superpower. Superpower.
Superpower, guy that eats food. He's terrible. Never playing with him ever again.
What about Velma? Velma has like 180 IQ. Super powered intellect. Oh, I like that.
Batman. Batman is the superpower of money. What about Harley Quinn? Harley Quinn is the superpower
of new york accent what the fuck is that thing all right that's a good one to go out on it's
literally 459 right now i think the servers are turning off literally right now one more do you
think i can get in one more i wonder if it actually is like strictly at 5 p.m let's see what happens
let's do one more fun one of a character i didn't really play with even if i lose i want to play oh
oh shit damn it oh well that was a lot of fun right hey they said five o'clock they meant five
o'clock when does this come out what's the actual release date on this july is the beta i went in
i i was pretty pessimistic going into this i saw the trailer i said oh that's kind of interesting
because people have done this before other companies and other studios with a bunch of
characters have done this before i'm gonna i want to play this this is good this is really good i
would not tell you i would not bullshit you on that this is good that was even like i don't know
about the how balanced it could be eventually whatever right but that was a lot of fucking fun
open beta is in july i will absolutely be playing this again without a doubt what are we going to
do next uh let's do a poll i don't want to keep playing that sucks i should have started my
stream three hours ago okay so uh can we get a poll in the chat we have sniper elite five
the new miku game or pac-man museum universe or pac-man universe pac-man museum or something
pac-man museum okay but is am i gonna even like the miku game am i even gonna actually
want to play this it's a rhythm game all right i'll give it a try i'm gonna take quick break
i'm gonna pee refill my water and i'll be right back and i'll be back with whatever you guys
decide see you in two minutes or maybe three or four i'm trying to leave the i'm trying to exit
the i can't exit the game i'm like i have to alt f4 i'm stuck here okay there we go
all right i'll be right back let's see what the people say