Hi, I know, I'm sorry, I know it's like 351 pacific time. I fucking fell asleep, I took a nap,
I got up, I went back to bed, and you know when you just sometimes you just take a nap
and then not everything turns off. Your brain, your eyes, your nose, your mouth, it all just
shuts off. I rolled around and it's like oh it's like it's like three ten. It's like oh
what oh okay. Gotta get the fuck out of this bed. Can't stay awake for more than an hour?
God. 4 p.m time to go to bed. But anyways, there are some very very fun things.
Reason why my sleep schedule is so screwed up is because I was in the discord a couple days
ago or yesterday morning because I had stayed up and I was getting all kinds of cool shit ready.
Got like the sometimes I just get the itch like once every couple weeks or so to just
I want to have like a notepad and I want to find out like some fun things to do on stream
and that's what I did. I was in the discord at like six or seven o'clock in the morning
pacific talking just like oh hey so here's like some fun things. People are just like
what the fuck are you doing? I'm just like oh yeah I'm good. I fell asleep. But we're
gonna play Dragon's Dogma. It's one of the things. Also expect a Dreamcast conversation
here in about two seconds. Just about two seconds. Unless we get into the menu of
Dragon's Dogma. And I think a lot of people are not gonna like the Dreamcast conversation
because I didn't realize a handful of things about this system.
Two very important things. Important thing number one. A majority of the popular
releases for the Dreamcast have been ported to PC and upgraded. We're talking about Shenmue,
Space Channel 5, Knights, Crazy Taxi. They're all on PC. So oh and they look better.
They have a higher graphic fidelity. Uh oh. Problem number two. Actual Dreamcast video
games that you would buy on Amazon or eBay. Um some of them are over $150 each because
apparently the Dreamcast collectors it's a pretty big deal because they're pretty rare.
So most of the good good Dreamcast games that you can't get on PC that you can only
get on Dreamcast. A majority of them are over $50 to $75. Emulation is an option but here's
why I don't like emulating anything past PlayStation 1. Every time I always have some
kind of problem. Either it doesn't capture well, frame rate problems, crashes. I every time.
The post of PlayStation 1 era of emulators I always have an issue with them. So what I did
is I went ahead and I bought them. I bought a bunch of Dreamcast games. I had in the closet
back there already. I didn't buy look I didn't buy any like the $150 ones. Like the ones
that are like $125 each. No. But the Dreamcast is going to be one of those scenarios where we
don't just oh hey remember PlayStation 3? It has like 60 fucking games. That's not going
to happen. There will be like 10 fun Dreamcast games and I'm not just going to burn through
them. I'm going to play them. There are a couple of survival horror games that are only on the
Dreamcast that I think would be really fun to see. There are a couple of fighting games.
There are Power Stone is on the Dreamcast and it's a ton of fun. I'm not just going
to play it for five minutes like we did some of the other PlayStation 2, PlayStation 1 games.
Seaman. Yes. The microphone. And by the way the you want to talk about expensive.
The Seaman microphone is almost $100. The Dreamcast microphone it's like a piece of plastic
with like a bird shit on the top of it and you stick it into the the VMU thing and it's like
70 fucking dollars. Why? Well I think we're really collecting that and there's no other way
to get it to work. You have to use it. And speaking of which one of the there's a highly
requested game that I've been seeing in the recommendation channel. People have said it to me
over the course of the last couple of years. I'm finally going to play it. I bought it. I bought
all the necessary stuff to make sure it actually works. I'm going to play Lifeline
for PlayStation 2 and we're going to try to beat that whole game. That's also coming up
here. If you don't know what that is that is a it's a game where you control the whole
thing with your voice. Good luck with a Boston accent. Well as you can see I can get
rid of my accent very quickly and very easily and the tone of my voice I can do a standard
speaking voice so it should be able to pick up all of the it should be able to pick up
all of the things I am saying. Hey take a look at that there's uh there's Dragon's Dogma.
Oops why is it not there? Okay now it is. Dragon's Dogma uh this was another one of
those that was on the list for a long time. I figured it's it's time to start to play some
of the games on the list. Also also he's been he's been doing research for like two days.
Dark Souls 3. I'm gonna play Dark Souls 3 again at some point over the next week or so.
Well who who cares? Dark Souls 3 what you beat that game like twice on stream. I know
I beat the game on stream twice on stream. Uh we're gonna do mods. First person mod comes
to mind. I really want to see how that game is in first person so that's what we're gonna do.
We also got all the Dreamcast. We got Shenmue. Shenmue is I I got it on PC. We've got crazy
taxi. This is I got like a bunch of shit ready to go now. All the Dreamcast games. I've got
like 10 of them. Let's see if we can get that started maybe tomorrow like I guaranteed.
Wait what are we doing? What what even is this game? Okay quest log.
Using a lantern will hold darkness at bay. Press back to open your inventory.
Okay so there's uh items that restore health and stim and I'll go with my lantern.
Is that the lantern right there? There it is. It's 0.60 cents a small light source.
Let me go ahead and use it. Change the game I did. Why does it still say I'm playing Celeste?
Wait wait what is it? Because it says Dragon's Doggo for me. Yeah what? It says right
it's Dragon's Dogma. Dragon's Dogma Darkerism. Okay what if I yeah it's it's there.
You can refresh your page. You gotta refresh. Oh oh we got a one guy scenario. Okay
all right all right all right I get it. Yeah sorry. All right so what did I do? But it
just said hit press start. Press start. Who is calling me? I forgot I did the am I on the
Truman show? Because every time I it's like I start streaming and then hey you got a phone
call. It's like I've been I was sleeping. I've been sleeping for like six hours.
Call me when I'm sleeping and I'll answer it. All right so this is uh status. Got options.
Saving quick. Is it quick saving I'm assuming? A six hour nap. Oh check your attributes. Okay
general offenses defenses skills condition profile height 179 weight 77.
That's centimeters and kilometers. So that's that's very tall. How tall is that?
Thank you Kazzy for the five community subs. Five community subs. Thank you. Strength, magic,
stagger power, knock down power. How do I just oh I got two people here. I got seven
and Saldy. How do I drop the menu? Details. Okay here we go. Elements. I'm sure I'll
figure this out some other point later. So draw. Oh that felt kind of good. Light attack.
Oh this feels good. This feels good. Is it jump? Is this a good game? This game actually feels
good. Holy shit. JabbaDab gave five community subs. The final station of our long struggle.
Thank you JabbaDab. Thank you Juno. Juno, Upsetto. Both of you five community subs.
Thank you guys. Five five five back to back to back five community subs. That's the dragon.
Hey you're not even flinching. Doesn't even matter.
Uh shouldn't we be a little more scared of this? I'm so confused.
This guy has some balls. He just a fire breathing dragon just landed. Screamed at him.
Breathe fire. Blew up a building in front of him and he was still doing the default walk.
Some ledges may be scaled but long fall will end in injury or death.
All right well I'm fine. Invoking this stone can gain you new allies known as pawns
whose lord that was very fast. Okay
examine. This is a rift stone. A stone etched with a strange marking and maybe used to summon
pawns from beyond. This is like a game show. Do I have to pick one of these two?
As you progress in your adventures pawns will provide you with useful information and hints.
All right he's like let's go come on hurry up dude. This is just a tutorial like basic orders.
Take the offensive is our valent against the worms.
That was my voice. Is that me talking? Because we got a healer, we have a bone arrow
and we have shield and sword. We cannot suffer the worm to work any further atrocities.
Careful a goblin. All right a goblin.
Do I even have to do anything? Can I just watch them play? Wait okay hold on I need to
pay attention. Press right trigger to pick up items people or enemies.
You can restrain or throw targets. Press right trigger again.
I got some kind of full Nelson. Oh I see okay.
So okay this is gonna be a lot of fun. What was the last thing that it just said?
The survivors come master. So what's it down? Okay down is come to me. I'll go at once.
Wait give me that coin pouch. Oh it's B. I gotta pay attention to that. Oh man why
did I have to be asleep? Holy fuck why does he have 40,000 gold and dash by
clicking LS both during and outside of combat? Okay I think I'm gonna change that.
I want to grab him. All right let's like let's steal upon it. Do it.
Pardon. Kill this guy. Kill this one. Kill this guy. Please will you kill this guy?
I don't even know who you are. Oh he's already dead. All right come let's go hither.
What fucking witch was that?
Oh left bumper or right bumper is a weapon skill. Where's it going? Where'd you go? All right come here.
So uh hindsight slash. Okay shield summons. Oh there's so many. Link strike. Skyward flash.
Okay this is this is a hold on hold on.
This is fucking cool. Is there a lock-on that I'm gonna miss here?
Oh wait he and now you're doing the thing I was just doing. I get you. Thank you. Anything
else? What's this? All right I've come to realize I'm the useless party member.
I'm the NPC that's just grabbing random things. I still have money though. Don't come we're useless
anymore. Do I get to pick my class? This is probably the very beginning right? This is
like the joke beginning. By joke. That was fucking terrible. I feel bad. Good guys, bad guys.
All right I got it. Don't worry I'll hold them. What? Shit. Sorry.
I'm the little brother that got invited to play with the older brother and a couple of his friends.
Let's hasten to the dragon's roost. All right hold on. Wait wait wait. Are there any secrets?
That's a pretty good secret.
Arisen this way sir. The worm awaits beyond sir. I should be proud to have you feel it
close by and hidden away here for fear of beasts all around. But with you we cannot suffer
a worm to work any further atrocities. Our army is routed. This plain truth. Beyond that grand
door the dragon makes its roost. Okay I know it's gonna happen. We're all gonna die.
Oh shit it's a Chimera. No sir Pilate. God is he alive? Here we go. I'll grab him. What am I doing?
I've got him on a tail. I've got him. All right so I get to cut the tail off.
Is there like an actual dog bowl? Is this just shadow of the closet?
Get back over to the snake. No don't get on the goat head. Oh my god. Tamed it. Super gimmick.
Poisoned whinies. Everyone's dying. Icons.
I'm getting on top and I'm hitting them in the head again. Right in the goat head.
What? You're not gonna hold him still. I just look let's all hold him. Not even a half health.
All right be rid of the tail. You must kill the tail. All right right in the belly.
Right in the head. A symbol. Well I'm the party tank.
Goat's head's almost dead. I'm gonna climb up.
Goat's head has been killed. Get up there. Oh get up.
This is actually monster hunter. It kind of is.
This is just monster hunter but you don't have friends.
There are no. Wait is there online? All right. All right. All right. John. John. I think you got
him. Jesus. Somebody grab him and shake him. Here we go. I feel like I'm at the end of the
game. There's an MMO version of this game in Japan only. I told you that was gonna happen.
And countless lifetimes come to pass. This is where I get to make my character. I'm gonna
be a wizard. That was by Andre De Regio. Uh-oh. The hell portal has opened.
Didn't even get to meet the dragon. Quick get the tail.
Oh the bird's gonna be yelling random lines at each other.
His skin is like armor. Go for the tail. What? What's it doing? Is that what a meteor looks
like? Oh it's a dragon meteor. I get it. I was just trying to do a cannonball and you
fucking birds got in the way. I was gonna get a ten at a tenth. New smash character. Yeah.
Benedict Cumber Smug. Yeah I don't know why that's so quiet because it's pre-rendered.
Here we go. All right. Here we go. Character edit. Height. Weight. View poses. All right.
Not bad. Not bad. Okay I'm gonna make the most default standard wizard you could ever make.
I'm talking I want like a cartoon Disney like big tablecloth on me with like a bunch of
patterns on it. Name. Please enter a name and valid characters will be changed to an asterisk.
Okay. Name. No what happened to John again? How about uh Air. Airthor. Airthor. Airthor.
Airthor. Airthor. Airthor. Airthor. No that's Radagast. I can't use that. That's illegal.
Air. Air. Airthor. No get off of that. It's not even fucking good.
Blandalf. No I'm not gonna do a Lord of the Rings thing.
Carthor. Garthor. Garth. How do I get out of here? No Garthor. There you go.
Garthor. The noble wizard Garthor. That's fucking perfect. All right well how do I do I can't how
do I get out of here? I yes I accept. I accept it. Oh my god. Your monocle will display for
players with parental controls enabled. What? Is there a Garthor already?
Jeffrey. Godwin. All right. I'm just gonna go with like Greg. Gene. Okay Garthor. Select
a base body. There's too many. There's too many base bodies. Garthor. But you can call me Gene.
Yeah that's a pretty good Garthor I would say. Yeah all right that's the base. That's just the
Boomer emote. It is not. Select a voice.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Maybe. Possible. No. Good.
Good. That's this one I think.
No I'm not gonna do the goofy chipmunk baby voice.
That one's much better. No. I'm not doing the streamer voice. I'm not doing the
youtuber streamer voice. You understand? Let's go through this. Ready?
So let's take a look at the voices here. Okay. Sounds pretty gruffy. That's pretty good man.
Not bad. Deep and low. I'm not like that much of a uh. This is the one.
Oh my god. Yep. Every video you've ever watched has that. Every single one. Every single
video has that in that. Uh proceed. Wait wait wait wait wait. Hold on. Wait wait wait.
Back back back back. More detailed edits. New preset face will overwrite the current
face selection. There we go. Like the beard and the hair.
It's not literally Gandalf. Okay. This is. I don't even remember his name. Barth?
What's this guy's name? I like this one. Hold on I gotta see more of him.
Let's go into details here. Size. No. View expressions.
Well. Oh my goodness. All right. Should I make him uh like a. Should he be like a
green? Frog? No no more frogs. Like undead? No no no. He has to stay. No no no. I'm just
gonna make him. What a Gandalf. Gandalf looks like this right? Gandalf was not green.
All right. Face shape. Can I do anything else besides the. Okay eyes. I gotta pick the right
ones. Oh my god. That's fucking terrifying. I feel like this is the next John Wick movie.
They're gonna. You think they're gonna stop at three? No. They're gonna make a John
Wick 4 and it's gonna be when he's like fucking 75. Yeah they better have a blue star
wizard robe option or I'm leaving. Me too. I will exit the game. Hmm this is tough.
Uh I like. I like these ones. No these ones are way better. Those are my actual eyes.
That's what my visor actually looks like. That's kind of scary. Okay vertical spacing.
All right. No I'm not gonna make. What's the. What's that movie? Uh Attila? No that's not.
No not Attila. I'll. I'm not making an Alita character okay. That's gonna be a weird movie
to watch. This is just a bird. Yeah Alita battle angel. Fine. What does Alita's eyes.
What color does Alita have for eyes? Is it red? Okay here we go. Looks good. Okay brows.
That does not fit. This this is a head transplant. Okay can I do details? Yeah
vertical spacing. This is gonna be a very very odd reference but maybe somebody will.
Is this Dr. Parnassus? Does anybody know who that is from that movie? That's a movie that
nobody saw but that this is just Dr. Parnassus. That looks good. Look at all these pictures.
These are all so fucked up looking. No no I'm not. No he's not. He's not getting a.
He's not getting a cute nose. Sorry. He has to get like a dwarf nose.
Actually I kind of liked it the way it was. Maybe one. Yeah right there.
Like right in the middle. All right looks good. Mouth is important. This is uh what you're looking
at here is a great crazy grandpa got your iPhone and was taking a selfie but accidentally because
he's so old took the shutter take a hundred photos button. Do details on this one. Boy
that's not bad. I think that's fine. Ears. You can't even see the ears.
What? No it's not gonna. It should be maybe an elf. No Gandalf wasn't an elf. All right.
Hairstyle. Let me look at this one more time. Details. Okay 24 is the right one. Or is it?
Okay can you give can you give them can you give characters in this game to see a haircut?
Is it possible? I don't think it is.
You can change the hair later. See ya. See a haircut. No I don't. No no no.
All right just keep going. Preset bodies.
Give him a huge jacked body. No that doesn't work like that. He can he can this character
can stay in Ren and Stimpy where he belongs. My character is gonna be no that's too easy.
It's too easy to just make like a fat guy or I'm huge you know. I mean I have to keep him
normal but out of shape normal. Wait I can make it what? Oh I thought you could change
just the color of his like chest. Okay that's fine. Statue. Height.
No we're gonna make him normal okay. No we're not gonna make him huge. We're gonna make him
normal. 141 centimeters is how tall? That's what? That's four foot nine. Is this inches?
No that's we're gonna keep him normal. Not small. We're gonna keep him in the normal range.
This is fine. This is normal. Weight. Okay. Musculature. Pretty good. Torso. Now fucking
with the torso fucks with the way you've made his face. Although I do really like the coat
hanger though. Not realistic. We'll have to go for two. Two's fine. So all right should I just
make jacked dad? This is jacked dad body. You know the guy that's like in his late 40s
and can't wait to go to the resort pool to take the shirt off because he has like really defined
shoulders. A fat stomach. And like a big chest. Yeah I think I'm gonna make resort casino dad.
Yeah I gotta go back to the stomach. Where is it? Torso?
No where was it? It was back. Statue? Okay here it is. No it needs to be less defined.
That's that's better. There we go. Huge fucking arms. Although this is this is pretty good resort
casino dad too because some they don't even work out your arms. You just do you just do like
curls and and then you do like the chest. No this is perfect. No that's much better. Not
another frog. Is he just he is turning into a frog isn't he? Wicked skinny legs. No I'm not
gonna do one of the fat ones. We've been doing Kenshi body again. No these are good. All right
I'm gonna fix this. I'm not doing Kenshi body. I promise. See? I told you I wasn't gonna do
Kenshi. Stance. No nobody has posture that good. It hurts to have posture like this.
That's fine. Stance. Ladylike or macho? All I'm doing is just lifting my arms up a little
and giving myself duck feet. How's that do? You want to learn how to be macho? Just raise your
hands up a couple of degrees above your waist and then pivot your toes. Okay and it features
scars, wrinkles, facial hair. This is actually pretty detailed. Oh no scars. That that implies
that I that implies that I may have lost a battle. Oh I haven't even been touched.
I'm untouchable. Nobody can hit me. Boy that's all right. 23. Oh my goodness. Oh my goodness. I
don't I no get the beard back. It's the hair. It's the hair that's doing that. This hair just
is so terrible. All right that's fine. The beard we had before was perfect. I think that's
just enough beard. I think. What else we got? I don't like this character. I think this is
perfect. Wait hold on. Details? All right so we can do the reverse youtuber if you want.
No no no no. Look if you can't dye your hair when you're 75 years old you can dye your
beard. Okay I think we're good. Makeup. Okay I can't really see anything. Adjustment.
Give him a cool scar. No he didn't. That implies that I was injured ever in a fight. Okay we got
Garthord. Jean Garthord or Jean. Male. Type 10. This is perfect. This is going to be the best
wizard you've ever seen. No scars means you didn't fight at all. No no scars means that I
have never been hit. I'm unhittable. You take a gigantic swing. You you pull back with
all of your might and you swing straight down and nope you're not going to hit me.
I've never been hit by a blade or an arrow or a magical spell. Pretty good. I'm ready.
I'm ready to play. Yes I'm ready to play. Make him fat. No no we can't. That's the
trope we can't go down on this channel. If there was like a germa trope it would be
character has to be very fat, very small, and very old. We have to at least try a different
character for once. No like old fat guy. I'm okay with old small guy. We can't do the three
strikes. Three strikes. Make him two. He's two. He's way too small. Is he? Then how small did
I make him? No I had him like today like every day. Waves gently lapped at the bike.
Didn't even let me read it. This is me. I can't wait till they do the camera pan. Yep.
Oh what a beautiful day in my village. Look at that pool over there. Nice resort that we're at.
I can't wait to take my shirt off and go swimming. But what I do is a dad on vacation
and smoke a bunch of cigarettes too even though I don't even smoke cigarettes.
I love the voice. You guys said I was small. I'm not even small. Look at all these people
around me. I am as tall as almost everybody here. See? I towered over that guy. I want you to pause
that and I want you to look at put a ruler up on your screen and see how tall I am.
Again untouchable. He was aiming for me. Who's that uh Marvel character that has so much luck
that you can never they can't even get hurt? Lucky. What is it? Domino. Yeah that's my
superpower. Unable to get hurt. Here we go. Where is he? Where is the human?
Unhittable. I can do whatever I want. Nobody fucking hits. Carport. Almost hit. Nope. He almost
hit me. God damn it. My first scar. Got me right in the shoulder. What the heck.
Does he know? He knows. I'm gonna get a whole lot more of these scars.
I don't know what you're saying. I'm sorry. I've got I don't know if this is what your
ancient prophecy is.
No don't eat it. Oh no. So I get it.
The dragon ate my heart. I have to get my heart back from the dragon.
So I need a band of adventurers and a band of merry merry merry. I get it. Pretty good Kingdom
Hearts opening theme song. Where the fuck is Goofy? Is Donald gonna show up? Scar.
God damn it. That's a big one. Take up arms. Fight. Fight.
You're in the chef's house. It's time for you to begin your journey as Artisan.
Arisen. But before you can win your heart back from the dragon you'll need to prepare.
Take a weapon. Oh this is where I'm gonna choose my Mickey Mouse path.
Do you like friends? Are you strong? Are you smart? Here we go. Your vocation determines
your basic attributes, wieldable equipment, and skills. Fighter. Strider. Mage. Primary weapon.
He's gonna be a two-handed wielding double-bladed axe. All right. Basic vocation to conjure of
magics to heal wounds and target elemental weaknesses. Looses a ball of fire that explodes
upon contact. Invokes a magical sigil which recovers the health of those who enter.
This is Doomage. Take on mage as a vocation. Well that's the character I made.
You can equip yourself with a primary and secondary weapon. Primary weapons such as
swords and daggers are combat essentials. Secondary weapons like bows and shields offer
support. Did I just air zooka? Oh wow. Okay I'm so happy I got the air zooka.
How do I what do I do? How long does it take to cast?
Oh okay that okay that's how long it takes to cast.
You can hold it and then you can target it. I get it. Okay oh you bet you target an area
and you just stand at it. I get it. Okay so air zooka. Fireball. You just release to shoot.
Okay let's go.
They're already talking about it. Fuck.
The one thing that he was good at, the one thing that he told everybody.
Not anymore. He's a loser now.
The only reason why we thought he was cool was because he was never hit.
He didn't even have any powers. We can't sell that. The tourism will drop.
Give me some dialogue. Quest successful. Defeating foes and completing quests earns
you experience and each level gained raises all of your attributes. Press start to bring
up the pause menu where you can check your attributes, a full map, quest information, and
more. Oh my god. Well hopefully that didn't mess anything up later. Kneecaptor. Look at
all these berries and apples and oranges. Let's sheet this so I don't get any more trouble.
Is it broom? Can I pick up the broom? Come on. What the hell is this even for? Okay what can
I do with a broom? Why did I pick up a broom? This is probably heals. Who made this Capcom?
Okay so those are those are those are resident evil herbs. They have to be.
All right let's go. Cassardist. Progress through the game by completing quests.
Always talk with the people you meet. They'll surely... people who bear an icon above their
head possess special information. Those bearing green icons have new quests to offer.
Look at this beautiful world. Beautiful game. This is why they put this here. You come
down you see the fantastic landscape. This is awful. Worse than I feared. Present. My thanks.
This is awful. You can't pick people up. He didn't like the pie. Well it was a free pie.
Well you can't get mad at a free pie. Would you get mad if somebody gave you a free pie
no matter what the quality was? It could be absolute awful quality, but if it was free
then who cares? There's talk of monsters emerging from the shadows all along the shore.
Nasty things too. The brine they call. They say there are many and yet one. Seems this brine
can be bested what's more. Not to do but avoid the water's edge. What does somebody
give you a pile of shit? Performing actions that people dislike will decrease their
affinity for you. This is the guy that wanted the pie, huh? This was the pie tutorial.
All right, look at the height difference here. This guy's like 6'4". This is not that small,
right? This is like, that's not that small. If this guy's like 6'1", this was, this is like
6 feet versus 5'11". I don't know what it is to some of you guys in this chat. Anything
under like 6'5", is tiny apparently to a lot of people here. If you're not over like 6'2",
apparently you're like a puny tiny person. Where do you guys live?
America. Purchasing equipment and useful items from shops or wandering merchants you encounter
on your travels. You can do that. Didn't somebody say I had too much money? Let's burn it.
You can restore health and stamina and advance the passage of time at any inn or
resting place. This game looks, I feel like this game is going to be a lot of fun.
I'm sorry. Wait, come here! Come here! Oh, that was a full baseball swing in the face.
Can I use this inn ever again? It's a false swing. That would kill someone.
Is this stealing? Some items can be combined with others to produce surprising results.
Experiment and see what you can come up with. A game where you can steal and there's no
consequences. I already like it. I don't know why I'm burning this guy's bed. There's no reason
for it. Tiny pillow. All right. I will agree with you. That pillow is very small. Okay.
Do the math though. This is a standard bed. If I were to lie down in this bed right now.
So let me line it up so my head would die. My head's not going to touch it.
Okay. My head would touch that pillow right here. Maybe like right here. If I lie down
straight. This bed is huge. Look at how big this bed is. Nothing to do with how tall the
character is. Rock. Well, they have resident evil crates too. It's an inn. All right.
There's a stone over here. Isn't that one of those wishing stones where I can wish
for a friend? Wish for like an ally? Empty flask. Okay. Let's put this away.
I just kind of like looking around. Your character is five two. The character's not
five two. It's five like eight. Barn. Where's this uh wish? There it is. Examine.
There ought there. There's ought there. As wrought there. Was that like a very strong
English accent? There is the first combat mission. What? Am I supposed to know who this is?
He's got a scar too. Wait a minute. We were both scarless at one point? That's not him.
He's of the pawn legion. They come from some unknown place. Just appear without a warning.
They're a strange lot. Not human. Quite. They look the part sure enough but they lack the will.
The spark what drives us. They have no capacity to feel nor act alone. So they live as
sellswords. That's gonna be the middle name of my first child.
Brandon sellsword elbertson. So you know I'm a fan of game of thrones, you know?
Second germa sellsword elbertson. I already hate your kid.
Why don't you take him? Might be you learn out of why he came to you in the first place.
Available quest change as you progress through the game. Additionally you can always consult
the quests section of the pause menu for your current objectives. People with red
icons appearing over their head have information relevant to your priority quest. If you have
several quests ongoing at the same time you can set one as priority in the quest section
of the pause menu. What's going on with the throat today? I don't know.
Doing so will make all people, places, and things relevant to the priority quest appear
prominently on your minimap. That's good. Pawns in your party will also offer advice
for the priority quest more often than for other quests in your log. Okay. To truly know
what arisen are meant to do it is likely best to follow the pawns lead. But you've
got information for me. That pawn will be looking to head west with the attempt.
Why don't you see? Oh fuck. He'll not make the trip his kindle rot where they stand.
Okay he's following me. Why not see that pawn to the encampment?
Might be you'll find art there as well. I thanks. You have a knife. All right this
guy didn't even introduce himself. Purchasing equipment here in Cassadis will make for a
safer trip to the encampment. Sell or is it where's the what do you buy? You look well.
Is there like a general store? Wait hold on. Hold on. Can I put him in the well?
This is not possible right? Oh it's boarded up. God damn it. Why do they give you this kind
of power? He's slapping your butt. Why am I doing this? There's no point in what I'm doing.
This is not gonna even do anything.
He comes back right? That guy comes back. He doesn't respawn. There's no oh you're
companion respawn. Actually gone forever. The game has permadeath so that guy actually is gone
forever. Fuck him. I don't need him. Oh my god. Can I just get a new one? Is this the
purchased a guy vending machine? Come on. I need another person. Well I'm gonna listen
to his advice and I'm gonna buy some supplies. Who gives a shit about that guy? That guy
wasn't gonna do anything anyways. This this game's fucking cool. Why did it take me so
long to play this game? This game is fucking interesting. Wait lantern. No get the lantern
not the empty flask. What am I even picking up? You already have one. Is it this is not a
lethal fall right? Is it? I'm just I don't know. I'm just gonna climb. No that's not
lethal though. All right let's take a look at the map. After accepting a quest first
note the quest marker in your map then continue by searching for the quest. That guy's actually
gone. Is this like a joke that people are doing by the way? Or is this he's actually
gone forever. There's permanent death. Quest markers will be buried. If you've
got one and want to progress through another you may find a solution in your initial
problem. Okay so where's the where's the shop? Pablo's Inn, Riftstone. What about this is?
Barn. Is it the inn? Did I permadeath that guy too? All right now that I know that there's
okay grocery store. Thanks for the groceries. There's nobody here. Steal from register
wherever the register is. Okay I got it. Okay I'm just taking all this guy's money.
Let's fuck the whole place up. You know what I mean? Never mind. Is he he sleeps oh
fisherman's house. What did I just did I just put a fairy in there?
Well this is not Legend of Zelda. Flask of oil. Okay I'm telling you guys I'm feeling it. I'm
feeling the bug from this game. Yeah sometimes you can just tell. I can just tell. I like this
game a lot and I haven't even played it for like five minutes. Actually I played for what?
How long has it been? An hour and 20 minutes? No it has not been an hour and 21 minutes.
That's how you can tell that I think the game is fun. I thought it's been I thought it
was like seven minutes ago is when I turned the stream on. Why not see that pawn to the encampment?
He's dead. Can you come with me instead? I need a like a shot. Here we go. Oh hello. Hello. It's
a mercy so much to the village was spared. I only wish I had more to offer. Okay curatives,
tools. How much is this stuff? It's overwhelming. Okay do I need an axe?
No I'm not gonna baseball swing her in the face with my fucking walking stick.
What do we got for armor? Leather cap traveler's hood. Well how much is it? What is it? What does
this do? What does this do for a feathered leather cap thick enough to protect the head
from mishaps? Location, magic, defense, defense. What does it even look like? Oh it's on there
now. Okay I thought that was my hair. This thing is so stupid. This is made out of like
newspaper. Wait do I add it to cart like it's amazon? I do. Why don't more games do that?
How long when did this fucking game come up? The add this item to cart and then check your
cart out. You gotta be kidding me. Why do is this not in other games? All right let's see
traveler's shirt. Let's take a look at the defense hemp shirt. Defense four, defense five.
This one's not bad. This one's expensive though. I don't have enough money. Maybe just
get a shirt and a hat. I think that's what I'm gonna do. Let's take a look at the
checkout. Cap and hat. I got plenty of money. Okay keep that in the checkout. Wait tunic.
No that's fine. Gloves. Got defense 70, 88. Funny bone guards. Minus one percent striking
resistance. Just wear the beads. Pants 70, 85. I don't want to get too crazy here
because I'm gonna need to make sure I can 68 to 69. 70, 85. These are fine traveler's tights.
And then a cloak. Too expensive. Jewelry. Too expensive. Okay what about uh no no no no no
don't cancel the transaction. Weapons. Wooden staff. What do I have on right now?
This thing is way better than what I have right now. I have like a piece of shit on.
This is look at how much better this is. 132 magic? Yeah it's only a thousand bucks.
Add it to the cart. This is gonna turn out like every single amazon order I've ever had.
I'm gonna go in to buy one thing and I'm gonna have a cart with like
145 dollars in it. Okay tools. Tool employed to mine or just get one.
Preserve materials. Place an item inside to prevent it. Get one of these.
Blask of water. Yeah you gotta take water with you on a trip. Poison arrow. Oil arrow.
Dragon spit. Okay all right all right all right that um that's it. No it's not hold on what are
these? Consume it to recover a bit of health. I have seven of them. Let's get to buy three more.
Get it to 10. Consume it to purge the body of poison. What's my what's my cart look like
right now? Let the cap chart staff pickaxe. All right buy it. Weapons. We've got rusted
staff. So I can let me see what it looks like. Cool all right it's a nice dinosaur bone.
Put it on. Equip. Put the dumb hat on. I've got what is this? Set of fisherman's tatters.
Traveler's shirt. A pleb shirt really. There's tights and I'm gonna sell the rest.
So let's sell. I just didn't I what about a rock? Well you can throw the rocks never mind.
Didn't I steal a bunch of shit from somebody's house? Yeah just I don't just take that.
Herb bucket. Yeah see look. I want this stuff. I just took it to sell it.
Rusted staff. Get rid of it. I wonder if this this is shit matter. This doesn't like improve
your fishing by like five percent right? You know some games have that kind of shit. You have
to wear this. Wear the full set of fisherman's outfit. Your lore is better. All right let's go.
Uh yep. Didn't I have something else too? Item storage. Whose is this? Item storage.
This is my stuff? How is this my stuff? Why is it $2,600 to take my stuff out of storage?
Wait wait wait. This is selling. 312,000 gold. Wait why is this like this? Why does this stuff
exist? This is the DLC stuff. That's kind of unfair. I could get myself like more than a
quarter of a million dollars right now. More than that. Well how do I pull it out? Bye.
This shit ain't even in here. What the fuck is all this stuff? I need to go to the end to get
it out. No I don't want to do that. That's cheating. I'm just gonna pretend those don't
exist. I'm ready to go on my adventure, but I need to go to my equipment. All right how do I?
Is there like a certain way I can make it? I can heal. Can I touch the stone?
No. It's gotta go. I'm going and I'm gonna be ready and I'm gonna fucking attack herbs and
spells. Assign items to buttons. Where do I do that? Status? Map? Options? Status? Skills.
Okay here we go. Hold on. So I have to heal. Condition. Oh okay here we go. So this is a common
herb used in preparing and consuming. Okay it's uh sort or how do I put this? Use combine.
I can't combine with it. How do I hotkey it? Is there a way I can make this on the hotkey?
Because I just have use. You can't set shortcuts for items. Okay. You can only hotkey
it on the keyboard. Finally you set up permanently dead huh? Oh permanently dead. He's back.
Game saves automatically. You can also save manually. Uh all right I will heal you. Come
here. I just tried to heal you. Will you let me do this please? Right there. All right just
hang out in there for a second. This is a very slow heal. Throw them off the cliff.
I'm not gonna throw this guy off the cliff. Uh oh goblins.
Save the peddler. Attack while holding. You have weapon skills. You can dash. Yes I know how to
dash. You gotta pawn because this is the right knowledge and skills. They're able to assist
in tandem attacks. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Oh wait a minute. Hold on.
Why am I? Why are my things on fire? My air is on fire. We have triumphed. When foes seem to be
too much to handle try gaining levels or obtaining better equipment. Can this guy gonna
give us money? That was far through. I'm called Reynard. A traveling salesman. Though
those damnable beasts ruined my wares. Oh I'm sorry for that. But thanks to you it was only
wares I lost. He just like you just gnomed that guy and he ran away. I can't even attack that
guy now. They often come across rare items not found at stationary shops. If you see a peddler
make sure to check what they have to offer. Um well I can't do that anymore. Thanks. Thanks
guy. Gob. Gob. All right let's check this place out. Empty flask.
All right so we can go. What about down here? No yeah that's it. That's just fall off.
Right. Are we gonna fall off if we go down here? What was that? This stretch of road is
called the Menomia trail. No give me that. Why are you picking the rocks up? This looks
interesting. Stop. That's my stuff. A wealth of useful items can be found by vanquishing monsters.
Get the fuck out of here. That's mine. Just fighting over fucking mines again in veins
like in Warcraft. What's this? You can use materials. Let's just keep going. Time for
them to throw them off the cliff. No I'm not gonna throw them off the cliff. He's too useful
for me right now. Not yet. Search the log. Cedar branch.
Small nut. Did you just skin the tree? I guess I could just sprint. I want to change that to
something else. A different button. What could I make that? I'm not sure I can make it anything.
I don't like pushing left stick in. What are you? Why did you do that?
What the fuck did you do that for? What is he doing? What the fuck is wrong with you?
This is definitely, this is like a player right? No I'm not gonna throw them up. What are you
doing? We both keep having the same idea. Chests are full of articles and treasures of great value.
Yeah the Vandal brothers. Silencer arrows. Cool. Many a life was ended by falling from two
greater heights. We gotta convince them to let us in. All right we got front door. We got back
door. Are we allowed in here? If memory serves. What the hell? All right so somebody's speaking
out of the Riftstone. Follow me. That was the Wendy's girl.
That was a good one. Have all you need. We are in first and foremost but we offer more than
simple logic. We can safeguard your belongings and your big any you like. So they can learn,
this is where you can learn new skills. Rest for 300 gold. What will it be today? Learn skills.
All right I need 200 discipline. Fire boon. Thunder boon. I think I want to be electricity.
What was Gandalf? Nothing. I don't think, did Gandalf ever do a spell? He did like a light,
big thing of bright lights for like one second. He didn't have any ice moves.
Didn't have any fucking fireballs. Wasn't even a good wizard. Yeah he did the you shall not
pass. It makes like a big bright light. He was a light wizard. Well I can't do anything.
He made fireworks. All right let's get it.
There's the funny joke where Jerma says dumb things about things he doesn't know.
Well I'm like dead serious. What did Gandalf have for spells? He did like bright lights and
like a kind of crash through sides right. He did do fire at one point.
He could do like a big push yeah like a wind right.
What does Goku did besides bright lights? That's a good point.
Is that gonna make another character?
It was a theory that he only used as much magic as level two wizard in dungeons and dragons.
Well a tireless spirit of self-improvement grants the strength to lead the legion.
Gandalf was much more powerful than he let on. His job was to guide the people of middle
earth and not do everything for them. You uncultured swine. All right search the area.
My kind grows better able to serve the more we learn.
So what did one of these. Sorry I was having a Lord of the Rings argument in chat. What was
it? Alas you have yet to prove that if you would prove yourself the arisen show no fear.
Okay so I mean call the arisen. Check the area around the encampment until you find a
threat that so I just have to fight a monster. Okay a rift stone. Strange power emanates from
within. Is he gonna follow me? The beast comes. Hurry. When foes are too much to handle.
Oh they're not gonna be too much to handle. So he was a light fire wizard.
Yeah that's what I was partially correct. Like he has like light and like force like waves and
I was correct. He does have fire.
This is actually this thing's pretty huge. All right get in there.
Shit. Climb on a larger monster. What is heavy attack like this? Okay just fire.
Okay so as you take damage the amount of health you can recover through magic in the
field also decreases indicated by a white bar with the rest of an in.
Or use a curative item to fully restore your health. Giving pawns curatives to whole will
allow them to use it at their own discretion. There's no reason for me to do that.
So if you burn them they'll just they light on fire. I gotta climb up on top. Should
I even climb up on top? Should I just stand back and just cast fireballs?
Let's get a heal over there.
All right I gotta stop. Somebody just said mage gameplay and then they said resident sleeper.
I'm a fucking Gandalf all right. So I'm gonna play Gandalf.
What? Get away from me. Why did I just leave? What the hell was that?
Um all right can I climb and do like a fire bomb in his head?
Oh I can like shoot him in the head. Oh fuck. This is a lot of moving around.
How do I hit support? All right I gotta hit him right in the other leg.
All right now enchant me. Somebody do something.
I shall strike the head.
God damn it.
He can't use his arms. Light all of his whole body on fire.
Magic users. Laughing my ass off. Look I'm just I'm gonna be just fine.
Mage gameplay. Don't worry it's gonna be fun. Right in the face. That's what you've got to do.
I gotta just mage him in the face. Just wait till I get the lightning move.
Oh shit I'm tired. What a true mage.
I'm a little sleepy right now. I'm gonna cast a fireball at him.
Mage is always terrible. It's not gonna get better. Don't tell me that.
Gandalf is like my favorite character in Lord of the Rings.
Mage gets really cool later. Yeah so we're gonna be just fine.
Nothing else. Mage at endgame becomes literal jedi god.
So see everything's gonna be just fine.
All right I've proved my worthiness. Early mage gameplay. Resident sleep mode. That's how it
always is. Remember Gandalf was level two in Lord of the Rings. He could have done so much
more but he didn't because he wanted to make sure that they they had the trial not him.
A bunch of uncultured swine.
Ekba located in the command headquarters of the encampment provides many different support
functions to adventurers. Speak with them to rest and heal your wounds. Learn and enable
useful weapon skills. Restore excess items. Okay well where's my discipline point?
275. All right I can do one. I can get another move. Let's see what they got here.
A frazzle. Concentrated field of cold around the user that deals ice damage to whatever foe it
touches. It's like a battle mage. Thunder boon. Launches a bolt of magic that enchants an ally's
weapon with thunder so I can enchant his weapon and my own right. Levin. Smites the enemy from
above with tongues of lightning especially effective at driving foes out of hiding.
Okay it does do my weapon. I kind of think that's cool
so I can shoot lightning bolts. This does sound really cool too.
Yeah I'll try this. Tongues of lightning from above.
Mage is a good base for a magic archer. That sounds pretty fun. Levin. Okay I have to change
my skills. I don't have any augments. No so I can do that's fireball. We'll just do
Levin up here on primary. I can do it's like switching that's like freaking me out here.
Stop doing that. All right Levin is gonna be Y.
What will it be today? Now I'm gonna test it on this guy's skull and see what happens.
Have your pick idiot. Come again soon. Let's see.
Levin. I'm just kidding I'm not gonna do that. This game looks fucking awesome.
Yeah I mean early game this seems just like there's a lot to do a lot going on.
I'm very interested. It's very fun.
This is going to the switch? No it's not. It is?
The stream's over. I want to play this in bed on the switch.
So thanks for watching everybody. Just kidding.
They tell some you and you to share your heart.
So this is I'm gonna make another character. Oh god set the look of your constant companion
throughout your journey has arisen your main pawn. This is important. This is kenshi. Another
hour incoming. No no no no no. We're gonna get this done very quickly. Okay uh another
wizard. Well I'm doing Star Wars A Link to the Past every single I'm gonna have four wizards
and we're each gonna be a different element like in that Zelda game. I'm gonna have fire wizard.
I'm gonna have lightning wizard. I'm gonna have ice wizard. I'm gonna have fucking uh
jester like joke wizard. Not a wizard. I can't do like all red robe, blue robe, green robe,
white robe. That would be so interesting. Oh we only get to we only get one. Oh shit one of
this has to be a huge guy. I gotta make a huge tank. You can do that but it would be awful.
Be smart about this. Oh but I want I want to do like the four links.
You can do it but that only if you're stupid and I hate you. Come on.
All right okay here we go. I don't know what the hell that name was
that's why I instantly deleted it. Bob shell. Uh you do jacks. Jinx. Can't make Ronald McDonald.
Mickey D. Oh I hate making characters because I sit here for too long.
Shito? I can't make Shito. Shito would have to be a bard for Shito. Is there like song?
Sean. Seth. Sharp. Shelly. Shito. Come on. She. Sean. Smudge. No. Sora. God. I'm gonna turn my mouse
upside down because I think it's it's pulling from yeah I have my mouse has to be upside down.
It's gonna be like a musical instrument or something. Siren. That's a musical instrument.
Sprinkles. That's fine. All right this is important.
Tiny. Very tiny. Yeah but it needs to be skinny. No no no no no no no go back.
Go back go back go back go back back back back back. That's not correct.
Yeah I mean it really could be any of them. Fine I'll do the joke one. Build. All right I
can do okay now I can do actual editing. Okay detailed edits. Uh let's get body is
most important to happen first. I need small but stretched. Stature. All right height.
Can I do like a custom color? Make it taller? You're gonna make a stick bug.
Can I have like a mask on or something? I don't know if there's an option to do
um here. Skinny. Bulky. No. Tiny. That doesn't look right. That's the same person I just
made. No it's gonna be long and skinny. Little tiny arms. Legs long and skinny.
Stance. Straight up. Not just like that. Make Kylo Ren. I'm not gonna make Kylo Ren.
Okay facial here. Let's get this off. I'm just clean shaving. This does I know this doesn't look
anything. Just wait we gotta give it a second. Hold on. This doesn't.
Okay hold on. Faces.
I can't do that. It's gotta be this one. Completely bald.
Face shape. Gotta have a big wide mouth and just a circle for a head. That's not bad.
That one's not bad. I can make it. That one's okay. Yeah this one. This is like a nice
round face. Eyes have to be just the two dots. I'm gonna just do that. You're making Bobby
Hill. I'm not making Bobby Hill. I can make the eyes really small. Okay hold on. This
character is gonna be fucking terrible. I'm gonna live with this fucking character forever.
Vertical position down. Spacing. Pretty wide. Size. Small. Eye color. Black.
Okay. Face shape. Is there a way I can add the details? Okay here we go.
The head. It is a little bigger. The eyes. We're gonna get the shape. Brows. No brows.
Can I just delete them? Hold on. I think I can. You can't really see them there.
Just make them lighter. Nose. We need to try to get rid of the nose.
Is that even possible? Have to get a little one. Vertical position.
It's not possible. This is where we're gonna get. We're gonna get. It's gonna get sold here.
Ready? We need a long skinny wide mouth. This is wide as it can get. That is the
widest I can get it. No ears. This didn't work at all. What about like makeup? Can I
add anything? It just has to be. I mean this actually helps a little because
Shito's eyes are just black. No that doesn't. This is not bad. It really isn't. Because
that's the line for the mouth. That's the the darker eyes. I'm not gonna want to listen to
that. I can't believe I'm doing like the YouTuber joke. How tall is he? He's huge!
All the way tall but he's. He fits in my hand. You know tall and lanky. I mean he is very
lanky but he's very tall. He's seven feet tall. All right this is a weird universe.
Fine. Change the voice. Can I change this voice later? That's. You're talking like
four hours from now. You really gonna hear that shit anymore?
That's good. I'm not. I can't handle the baby voice the whole time.
Nobody can take that.
I like eight. Eight is just enough annoyance without being annoying.
All right I'm good. Shito. I think that's good to go.
Ooh hold on. Hold on. I gotta answer as if I am Shito. So this is important.
Your answers will shape your pawn's inclination. When faced with danger which trait would you
most value in a follower? The charisma to lead others. Charisma. Shito sings. While in battle
which strategy would you prefer your follower employ? Kill all enemies. Strike at the
strongest foe. Rescue comrades in danger. Call for reinforcements. Call. Call or rescue.
Shito would never kill anybody. Your follower rescues your party and turns the tide of the
entire battle. What would you have them say? This way master. Leave them to me. Now master.
Strike the final blow. Quickly. After them. Master strike the final blow. As a ruler which
gift would you how would you how happy would you be about one of these options?
A magic potion that preserves youth. A brave and just hero to succeed you. The perfect spouse.
A majestic white steed. It's not spouse. The perfect spouse. You see the spouse of course.
Spouse means a little bit more utility. Spouse is more guardian.
Gandalf has a white horse. This is not Gandalf though. I think I like the utility. White steed.
Vocation. Fighter. Strider. Mage. Hmm probably something that can...
one of these two. We're gonna get our asses kicked if I do Mage. Bow and arrow. I mean
the bow is shaped like his body so the bow it's a bit sad that's what his body looks like.
Don't worry the next character we get is gonna be Danny DeVito and he'll be a tank.
Her fealty is sworn to you Arisen. From this day the Legion's men called pawns live and die
by your command. Nothing about this is correct. Am I okay I was gonna say what am I supposed to
be doing here? Quest successful. Having been reorganized having been recognized as Arisen you've
been granted a loyal pawn to be your constant companion in your journey. In addition to this
main pawn you may hire up to two other pawns to support you in your adventures.
Different pawns have different strengths so you support pawns to tailor your party to
fit your current needs. In addition to minding level and available skills a pawn's knowledge
is another important part of creating an effective party. Pawns with appropriate
knowledge of quests or foes can provide helpful advice and battle strategies.
What am I doing? This is a rift a space between realms from which there any and
all manner of pawns may be found. Should one catch your eye speak with the pawn to enlist
it to your party. The god of war guy. You may hire only two pawns onto your party at one time
they can then be discharged. You may hire only two pawns onto your party at one time they can
then be discharged by speaking with them again. Hmm I wonder if I should pick poop butt.
I wonder this that's well what a great character that probably is. Level 61 what level
am i i'm level four why would i bring a level 61 all right i want to like how do i see more
get out of here all of you get out of here we're gonna do process of elimination
you you get the fuck out of here too i can't uh did you just give me just five of the same
default character all right that's like that's a bird box sandra bullock dab only poop butt
remains oh man gamora gamora icky toasted bear goodbye duke no no no fucking poop butt why
do you have to be the best character right now he's just waiting he's looking at me just waiting
no i don't want elizabeth mickey mouse get out of here you get out of here all right this
one's at least there's some detail here level four he's the best qualified why do you have to
be the best qualified get out of here give me somebody else no stop looking at me like that
use the stone and search pawns by level friends a pawns wait that's what that is one of my
friends somehow star made that character no i'm not using that top ranked rank one
oh let me search for level level four download germa i don't even know how to do that search
conditions search by name i don't think i can narrow by vocation weapon skills both gender
name search search pawns pass someone's favorite list pawns your main pawn knows pawns by level
go back go back name i don't think i can my friends change search conditions
because i can i don't think i can why are you doing this poop butt is right there
why are you doing that poop butt is right here it's the easy but that's the that's the
ah one more time get rid of rug i don't think i can is everything in order master
don't get the fuck out of here may our paths crossing yes there isn't okay what do you got for
stats fighter no no yes there isn't no no no get away from me all right this is the last time
i'm gonna refresh you got like a swear in your name get out of here take tiny tim tiny tim is
like level 60 i can't take tiny tim is there no one worthy of this party search by level
no no okay search he's the 30 he's level nine samwise what if i search by level then poop
butt goes away yeah plus look see it's like i can't even see what they look like i have
to summon them to see what they look like okay i'm not picking one of the ones with the
asterisks all right i'm gonna try one i'm gonna go for one we're gonna see what they look like
here we go we're gonna go with um it's a mage we need a fighter tiny let's take a look tim
tiny tim tiny tank tim uh i thought that said this is getting delf i don't know we need to
look at we need a game rhythm okay bring them out right they should be bring coming out here
that's that's supposed to be fucking gave newel isn't it no i don't want to do gave newel that's
the ultimate look at this look at me joke no everybody go away what's worse i don't i'm not
sure gave newel or poop but i don't know they're both bad oh no i can't ah all right that's it
i'm out of here i'll just get over here now i can't use tiny tim don't you guys realize
tiny tim is way over leveled he's just gonna kill everything in one hit ah a master in his
pawn is it you'll be quite the force come the day you learn to test one i didn't do it right
mind you that is a skill better i can help in that rigo what the fuck are you talking
about hold on all right i need to go back where's the rift set a waypoint
right just go get me can i not go back no i don't want to do the no i'm not doing that yet
i'll talk to you in a minute well it just teleported me to the to the front of that door
i was standing in front of the stone and then it was like no you're over here
oh my god this i already hate that voice
redstone okay come back who the fuck are you okay there yes or isn't i am honored to travel with
you i'm not bringing the level 31 do you understand yes or isn't no i'm not bringing them
this is gonna ruin the game isn't it if you should ever i'll use them later what happened to
the game they leveled down the fuck is he come on let's do this and get out of here gave where are
you i have to keep gave no they don't one guy said that no why don't i bring in donald trump
i think we lost gave forever gave delete that guy deleted his character that guy is that guy
currently playing the game and did he level the character up once ball sack wait i didn't
see if he leveled up his character once he's currently playing the game right now where is he
guys there's no fucking way then i'm gonna do poop butt and ball sack i'm 33 i'm a 33 year old
man do you understand how like that i my mother would be so disappointed where is
gabe newell by level level six where the fuck is this guy get out of the way out out out
all of you tiny tim you go gabe we want ball sack you're not gonna get it yes or isn't
i am honored to travel with you i'm not gonna do fucking ball sack out at least see if ball sack
no who's talking oh i hate this crew it'll be easier going no it's this is like the joke
i wanted to i am mercedes i lead the men of the enlistment core
we play they say you hold dominion we have to play
to take up swords and fight myself but they are a clumsy lot oh this is just like a meme
a meme team gabe had new poopoo butt i cannot call them into this world as you do though
what manner of magic lets you command them so i'm pretty sure a ball sack is mine you're here
watching well it matters all right let's go make use of the encampment as you please
you don't need any rest come again whenever you tire if we want to walk about we best bring
them on of course what about
oh yeah i can't wait i can't wait to play
the call will remain here a while onto them let's rest why not this voice shit is gonna
get so irritating hydra where are my friends
oh
i hate this this is gonna get so old very quickly
you can't even hear what they're saying
this is the low voice is when i went into that closet
into the monster politics thing it's coming back to me full circle
all right i'm just gonna i'm gonna fireball
save poop but he's he'll be fine oh he's getting eaten
save him how do i save him he's getting digested oh fuck how do i get out
oh i can't do this it's too many distractions
how do i get him out
my fucking stomach i hate this i don't i want to restart the game
oh i gotta heal you come here
oh we're okay everyone's fine
is this a character just to suck i don't think i'm supposed to win
oh my god it's
like the hydra's neck okay i'll try
i've never seen this fight take this long it's because i'm in like a fit right now
now once once poop butt got eaten and all the sounds and the noises and the fucking terrible
voices and just slowly going all the way down and being digested i'm sorry guys i couldn't handle
that
my fucking head hurts the judgment swift footwork impressive now i have to go get ball sack
it was inevitable i think in any case the jupiter i'd hoped to gather a larger force before leaving
for the capital but the hydra's head and the origin who claimed it may i cannot say what the
past may hold it will be slow going with the card i dare say you'll have no trouble catching
up not hold on not now i want to go get ball sack what you have some time is
i can't use it i can oh that's the waypoint okay right it's got a big x on it all right
let's go get ball sack i can't fucking believe i'm back here already there it is no
where's ball sack he's already there five
five was it not a fighter was he different class the one level nine ball sack was level four
level four didn't i just look at level four you have to rng his name oh there's no way
that's gonna happen again is there hamburger feet i don't think i want that one oh nope
let's see what hamburger feet looks like all right let's go yes arisen i am honored to travel
with you he's the most normal character with the most abnormal name all right let's go
what do you know i cannot say what the past may hold it will be slow going with a card
i dare say you'll have no trouble catching holy shit he's still in the camp but then i'll be
yeah i'm just i'm just a long road ahead i like just looking around and look doing stuff and
this is a lot of fun all right regroup with sir mercedes head for the mountain way castle
and help her escort it escort mission what the hell are you doing here oh can i help you
then i bid you farewell he's coming with us four party members my ass
oh nice catch can we not bring him terrible creature i saw it from my spot in the post
what was it it's been dispatched then uh hold a moment is kina not with you she was said to leave
the village in search of art for your wounds i thought you accompanied her these are dark times
for a girl alone in the wilds let's ask at the village where do we go from here all right let's
see we got up here uh manami a trail or we can go to down here which is the sea breeze trail
this is the main storyline here so we're gonna go to this one let's go you just made my
grandmother cry i'm sorry i just need to see if it was possible
the road splits here let's be doubly sure of which will see us to our destination
who are we killing quite the view eh this too this this is like grant f.o don't put
pedestrians in front of me
who oh these guys
holy shit oh my god i didn't have to do anything shido what the hell was that
what is it chasing after this person what this is it's too much random shit going on
we have triumphed okay boost your prowess on a vocation all right so i gotta like be
moving i gotta be doing moves slay them one by one dogs up ahead lightning bolt attack i've got
it queued up
i just hit that guy in the back mage is not really great ain't it not not an early game
no fireballs early game that's targeting them completely right that's not doing any damage
damage chest oil no do you guys have any room apparently not all right let's go whoa that's a
lot of wolves it does a lot of damage but get out of the way out of the way out of the way
i'm gonna put a heal down no i'm not thank you game thank you for being an actual character
please our beast small fang
i can make food and shit probably right what are you guys doing
vocation rank shito they're so useless all right can we please go so i have to buy
experience stuff right let me see status for shito okay skills now i gotta go to one of those vendors
buff them with fire and lightning oh so i get wait i can cast it and i can
enchant it with those two why don't i enchant myself can i enchant myself
why even attack i can just grab them with the program that was impressive
i was really impressive actually
strike
10 out of 10 mage i know right he means zero out of 10
i'm just the guy that gave me fire enchantments
i'm so useless that was they just they're showing me up so bad on my own stream
it's not good i'm just gonna put heels down
this is efficient
all right watch out watch out watch out watch out watch out
shito is streaming right now yeah what like a book what a better stream
the road is not far off i'm the little dickhead that's getting carried by his two friends
save save and continue yes the road splits here be doubly sure which we'll see is to our
destination so the road splits should i go this way let's check out the left side no that's no
no no no this is like a tutorial this is the please learn to play a game do we go straight
down the road did somebody actually make the name shido right now how the hell could you be
that fast don't you need like to verify an email here we go you made it good good we make for the
capital men like is not the cart will draw beasts along the way stay vigilant keep close
our reason animals will have no use for you it's been three hours well i mean to be fair i
did spend about 30 to 40 minutes making the character that was me having i've learned what
to do in this quest let us go escort to the capital structure a wake castle perhaps protect
the cart this is gonna be hell isn't it everybody stop stop get healed even goblins
some small phone locks ahead oh my god take no chances men no get out of the way
oh they're kicking the shit out of this thing here eat air motherfucker can i heal the goat
bowl thing stay at the card side this path is a nest for every manner of our beasts
no man can save from where they will strike
pray be careful okay if i press b it sprints i can get this is going to be good for the
lightning watch this ready bingo it's terrible by the way
move out of the way i don't clear i need a clear shot
stop making fun of my damage grab the cow actually uh engel is actually not bad
that knocks them down and then they can deal with them all right watch out watch out watch
out how's the cow i can can i ride the cow we have triumphed there's no surprise of
course that many a bandit lurks here as well moon shit pass wait that was really dumb is
there any i can't none of this matters i can't loot this i guess i can make it can i make
you go faster just by lightly that's how you know how weak this character truly is
i can't even make him run faster i'm such a wuss i just hurt myself 11 not bad that's not bad
and the damage i'm getting made fun of just don't throw that over here what are you stupid
we have triumph strength in numbers all right i got vocation rank i'm gonna learn new skills
how are we doing on health down here walk right into it all right let's go faster hurry up
slow down how do i slow it down slow it down how do i slow it down how do i slow it down
done
i'm so smart
the pawns talk a lot yeah they do
half the time it's just fucking gibberish so now i gotta ground him that's my job
i figured out the job we have triumphant i knock them down from the air and everyone
else finishes them off i'm an integral part of this mission i'll draw its attention what are you
doing
that's literally just one rock that wasn't even a real rock that was a fake rock all right go
faster behind us stand clear do not get trapped what's behind us oh
oh god go faster fast fast don't stop we're exposed here how do i go fast fast fast fast fast
oh no oh no oh no we're fine come here ready group up thank god all right we should be safe
not yet there's a bunch of wolves and shit over here come on go
hop oh this is bad i need to just heal just be useful put a heal down right here
do you have to cut over there i didn't even get to see what i did
you didn't really end it although you tried
you can turn off the cinematic so okay i'm gonna put it in the way of the cow
that was not even in the way of the cow come here heal cow you progress through the game
by completing quests always talk with people you meet they'll surely have ought for you to do
oh my god
yeah air shot no i was gonna do that what are you doing
oh god damn it we have triumphed come here i can't even heal but to go to an end behind us
lightning there's no end to them who's left
will not hold them long goblin where there must be a mechanism to open the gate
is there not nearby watch for a goblin oh i love this game it's just so much going on
lots of goblins all right i gotta be prepared for this heal in the middle lightning
right inside
no the dog the cow i can't even do any just heal who cares about anything else oh my god
keep marching this place must have seen a ferocious battle this is not good
no we're just wedged in what's with this camera all right we're good almost there
between the encampment and the capital light good we've come this far
see shit stay vigilant till we're in glance or in face men see i'm useful
i just have to be very far away and without anyone knowing i'm here
i've learned the beast i've learned new techniques against that foe
the canyon floor is an apt spot to find ourselves surrounded we best be careful
sneak mage actually hit me
you're just so more much more impressive than i am it's embarrassing
that's not even that bad of a move it really isn't i just it looks like such a
joke that i feel like it doesn't hurt anybody but it does
oh they're picking these up right they have to be they're so close who's left
oh jesus what the fuck was that help me somebody help me get me hamburger feet lift me up
retry from which one of these is the best like this one right or
you're not gonna debate me just hold him somebody come here get him in the air oh that was
awesome nice work excellent job
all right we're gonna save one more all right just forget about them can we
oh whatever fuck it let's go
we have triumphed i'm just gonna get one ready and put it right here in the middle
we are near between the encampment and the captain all right let's go good we've come this
far as there isn't let yourself stay vigilant till we're in grand soren's gates they're
learning they are learning they're doing they're pretty good job learning too
i'm so glad they picked it up it would be so horrible if they didn't sorry
right strength in numbers this is where we lost last save it right here because i died last year
last year what the fuck am i talking about i died when i was last here i'm almost there
now strike
so
all right here it comes this time i'm gonna stay back i'm gonna put a heel down get one cued
from right here right over there all right here they come
it's an ambush right here no where is it the guy does like two front flips and backstabs you
where is he grand soren stands beyond this way castle i never upgraded from rust weapons oh
yeah i did i bought the um the weapon that was in the store this is not the rusty stab
where are you all right this is making me nervous why they're not here yet
you never upgraded from rusty streamer
we're here didn't i get ambushed way is there like a random generator here for enemies
interesting okay so it can be different every time that's pretty cool
just keep going depends on the time of the day oh i see okay
talking with others let's begin with that are you all right master oh shit you're almost dead
we share these roads with traveling peddlers guardsmen and other folk or if we get out of
the way because i'm gonna get out of the way move i don't want to have you run over come on
just made it here we go we've arrived well done men well done a hydra's head
is a fine prize his grace will be pleased with the cause work walk proud through these streets
men we are heroes to the people of grand soren yeah pressing down makes them group up on you
right good rest up men this this is what i'll make all the castle directly to offer my
report to his grace i'll have words sent for you friends praise sojourn in the capital of wine
tutorial complete
that guy has the same haircut as me we were the same person kind of
fortune smiles upon me i am called mason mason now you'll come to the capital a conquering
you'll be needing ought to do hey jerma why the fuck did you do that my word to you
what did i do with the pawns inquire about them here in grand soren their kinds woven
tight into the fate of their reason if you know your destiny if you mistakenly the items
you received have been distributed to you your main pawn and item storage i feel more
familiar with this question game with the pawns what could he mean by that item information
of the dragon take some quests and explore the city okay very cool so um i need to find
somebody to level up i've learned of this area he's not the last i have no idea what he's saying
who among you has seen the dragon who i can tell you little at the moment i'm afraid no doubt
you were filled with fear at all all right let's take a look at the map i need fun square i guess
i have i need to find it right trepidation with despair the road is closed so i can't go that way
an ill net respawn at times we abandon all thought and settle into the cowards refuge of
desperation let's take a look at map doesn't show locations unless you discover them yeah
so let's discover the inn what does that say i don't know grand soren union inn
the service is a guild for local adventurers speak with the in-keep uh assalam to recover
health earn skills and manage your stored items once you've grown enough as an arisen
you'll be able to change locations here is a city new to us and vast are you there isn't
the men of the course speak of forgive me i spoke poorly pray and i am asa and this is my
in though we deal in i hope this is the first of many visits first of many minutes oh you
wish to learn at the pond legion then the shortest path to the answers you seek leads west
there you'll find grand soren's pond it is a gathering place do they have to have uh one
sentence and then you press a couldn't you got plenty of real estate here to fill like at least
another one or two sentences just tell the sentries you have business with the guild
they'll let you pass at your pick any you like all right uh rest everyone's got like
50 hp so i'm gonna have to do that let's learn or set this day learn skills what we got
high angle core skills augments secret augments well let me just take a look
an advanced form of angle that loses a number of fire projectiles an advanced form of levin
that spites those in multiple lightning bolts halodom invokes a magical sigil which
clears the following from those who enter so clear status effects holy boon dark boon
so this is dark enchantment light enchantment what will it be today at your pick a new life
change location mage warrior ranger sorcerer mystic knight assassin magic archer well here
we go hold on wait a minute it's gonna take me a second here so mage conjurer of magics to
heal wounds and target elemental weakness a mage adept at all forms of magic including
punishing offensive spells mystic knight a versatile warrior who can also assist with
enchantments and support skills can't do that magic archer a skilled explorer and well balanced
adventurer able to wield a magic bow so really it's magic archer mystic knight sorcerer or mage
so this is magic and spells and heals this is super offense this is kind of like a cleric's
like battle mage type guy right and then this is the magic archer concentrates a flurry of
slashes on a single point easily shredding foes with meager endurance so this is a angle
threefold bolt fires three magical arrows at a single point okay so here is some skills here
scarlet kisses let's take a little mystic knight blink strike i already had that before
lightning and fire again fire counter this is a block perfect block blasts those of the fireball
yeah that's like battle mage i don't think i really give a shit about that miasma someone's
a putrid fog that poisons foes who tread into it okay putrid fog including punishing offensive
spells i think that sounds like fun this sounds like fun too though but should i just
go straight up explosive mage a thousand discipline points to do this yeah i'm doing it
sorcerer change your equipment what we got look at all this shit this is this is like the dlc
stuff right new new new look at all this look at this cheating stuff 87 to 239
this is cheating i wonder i wonder where you got that piece of clothing he was level 31
so this is leather cape i believe this is i picked this up so imagine i put it on
cloth greaves so wait this is clothing and then armor so i can put these both on okay nice
uh whiff whiff psi 10 community subs and whiff whiff psi thank you for the 10 subs
whiff whiff whiff master thank you it's a lot of money that's a fucking lot of money actually
10 i always i always forget that's five dollars per sub whiff whiff master x barbecue
i can't put on the free shit look at how good this stuff is i mean there's my wizard robe
why is this off shouldn't be equipped and then there is the wooden staff what do you have
for weapons do you have any weapons here what will it be today okay let's see here we got
arch so we got core skills all right here we go wait what where's do i have any other abilities
i need a two-handed staff oh it's because of the i get it okay okay i see i see the rank
is at one i see all right so what do i have for abilities right now set skills i've got
that already what about we got 11 might as well put it on that's all i got what will it be today
also everybody else so we got shito has some new shit biting wind what do you have right now
what will it be today scarlet kisses you don't have anything else what will it be today
so what's good we got fighting wind toss and trigger button presses thrown did any store powder
dives through the air while spinning blades extended especially effective when performed
from high places cast out cords to ensnare lightweight foes pulling them to the ground
that's pretty good dashes past the target with blades extended delivering slashes that
can be followed with further slashes now let's get you some like combo shit and a snare
it's expensive but i think it's worth it okay who else do i really give it i don't really give
shit about nobody else can even be used all right so that's good i had shot fires three
arrows in a wedge pattern full bend draws the bow with all the users might then loses a
single shot yeah do it don't get crazy here biting wind and then ensnare threefold arrow
full blend hmm i guess i could get another secondary move what will it be today cloud
burst that's an area of effect let's get it aoe all right you're decked out now
no augments but that's okay probably have to get find them to buy them be today
uh never mind have your pick any you like learn or set skills rest i need to do this
because everybody morning everybody's health is all fucked up by a staff yeah i'll go by a staff
across the river where we're this accessing server for what exactly i feel more familiar
with this question now where is this guild for ponds when you're connected online your main
pawns attributes will be uploaded every time you rest at an inn the main pawn you created
can travel to other worlds online so there's my pun these adventures can result in new
knowledge items and equipment they bring back when they return you made pommel gain boons
earned in other worlds at the inn as well visit often to keep current on any developments
well that would have been really funny when this game came out really interesting
oh there you are all right everyone's healed we need to get some new clothes and armor and
shit whatever hold on we are we can safeguard your belongings it is our pleasure and our
have your pick any you like come again all right that looks good all right let's go
we need to find like a armor and weapon store uh the three jugs
why what don't hand me so i want to buy something are you tell you're the arisen
make a habit of coming by sir and i should take all the time you like
what do you got this is like a little healing store i don't even i didn't even need to buy
these now my character doesn't have a heal anymore got 12 i'm gonna give you a shit
load of these buy a better hat buy a better hat okay what about like nuts
tiny amount of health fair amount of stamina a bit of health great deal of stamina whoa this
is 1500 gold fuck it just sell it pumpkin this is just a bunch of money moldy carrot
why is that one so expensive flask of oil lanterns no i don't want to sell those
rugged bone misshapen i-3200 this is a lot of money all right i'm gonna check out
i guess just selling nuts and shooting fish dude not to sell those i'm not gonna i'm not
going all the time you like do come again have you equipment to enhance you look like these
weapons and need no different than food or their master works or trusty sword okay who can use this
you can buy a new sword for what we got shito i think you currently have this on do you okay
stilettos ironclad staff crimson glare common archie staff that looks correct but why is it
grayed out it's eighteen thousand dollars for this why is this so expensive i can't afford the only
weapon i can use uh master works can i just sell one of the dlc things i mean it was just
free money that's cheating they're only useful for selling yeah all right i'm selling one of
those items all right we've got lifestone okay we got tiara of enlightenment monocle jester's cab
there's so much shit that i don't even want new set of non-investments can i see how much
they're worth sell the monocle it's worth 300 000 but that's cheating is that okay you guys
gonna be mad if i do this no yes yes yes no yes yes don't do it 300k isn't much i'm gonna
unsubscribe fuck it i don't even care or will it be to have your pick come again soon
i'll confess them ask the world so this is ridiculous why is it i'm doing it i don't care
all right all right all right everyone i did i just already did it i did it it's over you can't now
there's no going back now i'm gonna buy the thing that i wanted to get common art staff
get it and you know we're gonna some money let's call it a little bit of a shopping spree here
how about feather hood wizard's hat 8700 i got the means cheating in an easy game that's not
but would you rather be just put it all on and be unkillable for the first like six hours
of the game oh that's cool scholars coat yeah i want that too i'm gonna buy stuff for shito as
well there you go art staff put it on all right uh what do you got you need throat cutters
stilettos stilettos yeah i think so what about uh bow bow leather hood uh skulker mask
i'm just gonna buy like four of these just buy three of these buy like three of these
oh i want one of those leather gloves buy three of them uh boots scholar boots
buy four of them mahogany cape uh buy three of them what do you mean what you don't equip
pawns what i don't equip sub pawns oh god damn it okay hold on i only got one of those
only your pawn and you so what do they have all right okay all right we're good we're good we're
good one stiletto one bow one mask one outfit one bangle two boots one wrap one glove
strider yeah this is much better very nice okay and your helmet put it on 44 really not
much of an increase but it's fine uh this is from me and a cloak back to me i need
enhance what does this mean the plain wooden arch staff at simple design and ready availability
have made it a common sight across the it's 1300 bucks just to upgrade it once
that's not bad is that that's just do it level one sure all right nice what about you 70 gold
840 gold do it and then the bow denied is 65 he's gonna upgrade stuff and think regular
items are bad calling it no i'm not that's not gonna happen all right i'm gonna put on my
last thing and then we can keep going where are those uh they kind of can i give this
how do i take that from us she does holding the equipment give it here now boots to give
a pair of boots we're so close so this is 143 these ones and then where are those
plus ones to magic what the fuck are those things what the hell was it did i not give it
there they are no no no stupid all right almost done plus one to magic good grand perfect all
right now i look like a real sorcerer what is the what's the basic attack okay it's just
this stupid thing now let's go on a quest uh-huh consult the guards and visit the pawn guild on
the western side of the capital okay did i do that well this is uh west so guards on the west
hi guys was that a hydras head went by before if you're traveling around with pawns
pay the pawn guild to visit please save i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got
it i got it i got it i got it that was a huge jump holy shit all right hey how are you
take your business pawn guild is it all right through here and to the left just don't make a
nuisance of yourself i can't fuck around all right all right so yeah i got all the
moves that i can learn right now i'm at level i'm at level one sorcerer so quiet
might be i can run really fast wait what is it so this is the pawn guild where's my other
wisdom where's shit where's poopa no who am i looking for who's missing does somebody die
oh it's uh just feet hamburger feet where's hamburger feet
you can summon pawns as necessity demands the rift represents the bond between pawn and arisen
don't remember her name welcome arisen we have awaited your coming this pawn is called barnaby
the guild serves as a place of rest for pawns and as the gate to the everfall the everfall
grand soren it is a place of great importance to our kind okay but for now let us rejoice in
the coming of the arisen the light that guides the legion
have you so what is it what do we need to do let's talk good we found it good we found it
good we found it good we found it good we found it good so i don't i'm not replacing should i
replace somebody no no no i don't want the level 60 no we're out of here i need to actually i do
no i do need a healer you're right uh hamburger feet of gave has to go because i don't have any
any heels is everything in order master wait what give select an item to gift well who am i
give what am i give you what although okay so i'm giving them a review okay review appearance
battle and helpfulness that's toxic it buddy i was he helpful i don't remember doing anything
all right but it's it's gabe newell okay appearance rating although hold on a minute
though this character may have been made in 2011 so this actually could be pretty relevant
for that period that he was made okay battle rating you have like a circle shield and a
knife it's pretty helpful that's fine okay comments there you go shows fine taste
it was well worth the effort may our paths cross again all right bye gabe hamburger feed
lives another day all right now we need a healer 10 what are we level seven she's level four well
she's got plenty of room to grow we like level five level six it was up to six why is she
only level four okay we need a mage right yeah bring them all in let's get a good name
abel clarice alan hilda nun felice aida jack goblin uh uh fanny let's pull fanny in
uh mila let's get another i want to get another list i didn't like that list very much
uh bb four five six bb barbara uh i need to check and see if they have healing spells
and um barbara bring him in what are you still doing here this fanny there's four five six
there's bb why four five did you just get lazy yes all right what do you got
general permission offensive statuses defense skills okay here's it there's a heal
hold on er i need like another lit everybody's so basic it's just person it's just person person
person where are the frogs okay let's dude i'm gonna have to see who dude is christina
just see it and uh boo wait wait wait what are you doing
what wait wait wait wait wait what i gotta send you people away hold on all right this
there's dude dude do you have let me hold on yes sir ism you do and you have a bunch of
other spells too all right yes sir isn't you stick around for a second that's a person's
first and last fucking name i don't want to let's see there's absolutely no fucking way
i'm going to click on any of those not even remotely you stay here though stay
all right we're gonna find it here loki all right i need to see what loki looks like
slayer head what a slayer head hi guys and elaine have to pick one from here this is
this is just a guy oh that's just a guy like a nun outfit all right well there's slayer head
no loki hi guys
let's just yes all right you have a healing spell yes sir ism
sarah what are you doing here get out of here loki dude or hi guys yes sir ism
it's supposed to be loki from super marvel 64 all right hi i think it's gonna have to be loki
loki has so much better moves his moves are amazing yes sir ism yes sir ism take them both
that means i have to get rid of hamburger feet all right you're coming with me i am honored to
travel with you he doesn't have a funny hat oh god i forgot how important that was you're
right she's level four and can't grow is everything in order master is that for real
i mean you saw at least four or five times where she did something fucking crazy
friend request this pawn stands proud of what we accomplished may our paths cross again all right
bye bye jana proud moore's voice actor all right we got dude and then we're also gonna get
uh gonna dude and loki both of them no now we need a fucking tank yes sir ism i am
honored to travel with you let's go what is your voice a grand cathedral fit for a grand city
it's no i'm gonna be able to understand what that person is saying we got mage better mage
tank no we got yeah healer better sorcerer range we're good let's go he's got a normie voice
well it's it's actually refreshing that's not even normie voice when everything is
nose and fire and ice pulse like that's that's abnormal to hear that when all you hear is this
the whole entire stream the guy that has a normal voice is different yes who the hell are
you send friend request who the fuck is this all right can we go it grieves me i would beg
your assistance in this matter arisen if it please you you have my thanks random pawns that
walk around that's really actually pretty cool why didn't they make a sequel to this game
were they too busy making monster hunter world probably beyond lies the everfall an ancient
place that sleeps beneath grand soren's stone they did make an online one capcom just hates
us oh we pawns have long served as keepers of the entrance to this place but since the
dragons coming a strange aura has filled the everfall uh presence this game has a 33 on
metacritic no it does not that's not even possible what are you talking about hold on
metacritic dragons dogma metacritic it's kind of like an 80 what are you talking 33 percent
that means the game doesn't even function that's like the game crashes to desktop when you
open it that's how you get a 33 if it be some omen of evil to come we cannot allow it to go
unchecked i ask that you seek out the cause of the change the everfall is a place unique
unto itself this is not a simple task which is why i ask you you got it explore the everfall
you guys ready miasma i'm on my way very well no fuck look at these corridors this
be sure we carry an ample store of oil to keep the lantern burning thanks poop butt thank you
appreciate that uh i need my equipment how do i uh not select all right i only have one
i got a lantern use it let's go got a search down here logs
that's a long way down they all walk off no they won't very well okay i just just
make i was just checking if they they were like lemmings jump for the item on my way
oh fuck there is an item i cannot take much more did he just say so hungry so hungry
i got the sauce okay how do i load game you don't you have to live with it i need that guy
really badly
all right last game this is the first 30 minutes of the game not when you
not when you spend like two hours making characters what i didn't get the
none would believe grandson and held such a place beneath it oh fuck okay i got it i got
the sauce let's go first mission of the game it's only taken four hours bugs let us make for the
bottom all right we got it this is so much better you cast so much faster
my time grows better able to serve the more we learn you guys are right it was definitely
worth picking this got what the hell was that that's a different move anytime like a pushback
force push that's really cool all right cool watch out watch out don't fall what are you
doing what the fuck is wrong with you watch out i'm just trying to do something i want to
see if it's so strong i don't even do a damn thing nice heal thank god that guy exists all
right we got zombies yeah i don't even hurt them i'll support you
oh i got enchantment
detroit
i hate this guy this guy has a fucking hat on that's the only reason why this guy is
interesting to all of you is because he's wearing a funny hat and that's just the dlc hat
i'll take that we'll go no further until we find the switch that opens the screen
will be easier going searching this area now okay just throw one off again i don't think
i'm going i'm not going to throw somebody off controlled by some kind of device which is
back to this one controls this door master are there like illusory walls and why would
they i don't even know why i'm asking that question throw somebody off and then try to
catch them
lightning's not doing so much fire who is dead everyone's getting the ass kicked
what the fuck is happening right now yeah the lightning does not work at all
so about fire
there
that's never going to get all strength in numbers arisen
we have triumph we have triumph we have trium is hearing the same line three different times
oh
i got fiery chip and now that's good thank you for learning about that
holy shit doesn't matter if you're holding them no one's there before striking
skeleton
come on man will you heal him we need to heal he's so passionate yeah he is
he's really good at holding enemies still leather circle it
is dark and unsettling this place all right now that i've opened this door yep
i wonder what the normie character is thinking
not probably not very much considering he does have that hat on
i feel like i'm not doing much damage even with the regular fireball
melee is gonna take this on here
he is a normie though that's that that's like the normie hat i don't believe that
and why am i saying normie okay we got that i can pull that i closed this that's locked now
that's fine
location for she does increase good a fire on these zombies very very
very very
what a gaff
they're so annoying they really are they rub it back they're the fire they they're weak to
fire they rub it back quickly it's locked oh shit oh no wait wait wait no no don't just go
after it did you just blow me a kiss what the hell was that oh okay get ready get him get him get him
oh holy shit did he knock him off the oh wait healer healer here get the healer up
where's poop button there he is oh my god this is bad this is really bad
do it simple sir how long is this gonna take think well before striking
oh come on
what do you propose not much apparently let's continue gamer alert accidental gamer alert
oh this looks interesting healing powers that's definitely a save scenario watch out bugs
bats i'll take that must have been another troll right here
what's that how much further down would you go good shot really good aim i got there
advance slowly where visibility is poor will give us time to react somebody please somebody
swap this bat please what doors were closed stand open and those once open are now closed
this place hides something shall we take a look some doors are open when others close
others open while others are closed i thought that just said please save the game over there
here give me a fire there you go nice work dude
i gotta give more courage to them so they can take care of themselves
rusted what is it rusted what large not
i've learned a new way to fight there is just picking up rocks so fucking useful huh
we have tried to lose your way you need but consult your map
there's really only one way to go guys it's around the circle and down what was that ladder
i can't even replicate that voice it's too hard to do that
why are you going the long way you went all the way around nice try
something to save me you jumped over the railing all right cool get some money
you questioning my strategic placement here of characters
is that getting leadership advice from poop butt i believe i was
odd light be causing this light flame servant's throne are we ready all right just check the
area a little bit it's probably a boss yep i knew it large coin advance slowly where visibility
is poor will give us time to react poop but the wise what could that odd light be
not down there yet skull those are expensive what's that take
uh i've gained quest knowledge report back i have a port crystal's work in tandem with
fairy stones invent this port crystal in the ground any place save a dungeon
and you can use a fairy stone to return there in an instant
all right we got a fight here how are you going upstairs why are you retreating what are you okay
we must run now and when did you become my quarterback
all right let's go go go go run then that's what somebody dead oh no get up
stop fighting come on let's go let's go i'm out of breath
we have to leave him who cares it's just a normie with a hat on oh come on let's go
stop fighting what oh god let's go grab it holy shit i have one h
let's go well then go where's this other where's dude no fuck him who cares
don't make it i keep i need to eat the stamina thing where is it stamina use it
let's go they're trying to sacrifice themselves for you
they're good i think they're all alive no wait eat eat ah no come on poop butt hurry up
my god what are you people doing over there let's speak with barnaby leave it to me
this game is out of control sit at the special chair to mentor your main pawn you can give
direction on how you would like them to act in battle and while out in the field similarly
you can also advise your main pawn how you would like them to speak to you in the knowledge
chair am ever aware of the enemy's weakness in battle be they alone or in numbers does this
please sure understood my first concern will be aiding my allies in whatever way i can
i try to speak or remain silent as the situation demands would you have me continue in this way
master um but but what does that even mean that could mean every single scenario i try
to speak or remain silent as the situation demands that's every single possible scenario
i speak sometimes but sometimes i'm silent do you want me to do that still sure as you wish
i will attempt to be more talkative from now on oh no that's not what i wanted all is yours to
shape master should i suffer a deadly blow how shall i voice my anguish me arrogant ordinary
as you are if it pleases you speak with confidence how would you have me respond to
your orders ordinary as you wish how should i how should i voice my anguish if my left arm
is ripped off should i scream with confidence anguish what would please you if a group of ogres
smear shit all over me and then burn me alive how should i respond to them so this is the
pawn guild a light in the furthest depths you say i see in truth even we pawns know precious
little of the everfall i can say with utmost certainty though the light you speak of is
newly come my character runs like a toddler we cannot know if this small aberration will
give rise to great calamity hence he is pretty small but the chance enough is called
to take action we shall redouble our efforts here and keep vigilant for further signs of change
that's a that's a fifty dollar that's five thousand bits just came in right now fifty bucks
big bits from a wild meryl thank you for the five thousand bits and they say i've been
watching your streams for a while now just wanted to say thanks for what you do
you never fail to make me laugh even when i'm feeling at my worst keep doing what you do
thanks again thank you for watching i really appreciate it thank you for the huge amount
of fucking money thank you for the massive amount of money i'm glad you can have fun here
dude is still here all right new spells you have to imagine that
i'm gonna throw dude off eventually yes what is it are you the arisen
i bring a message from the duke himself his grace has judged your feet in slaying the hydra
most laudable to honor your noble works you are hereby welcome to the worm hunt
the worm may now accept orders from sir maximilian captain of the hunt bring this
was laughable outside the castle gates he will instruct you first the document confers the
status of hunter upon you carry it on your person always okay that's a really great
default npc pathing run excellent work guy you may now take on worm hunt quests head to the
castle gates in grand soren's noble quarter and speak with sir maximilian beyond those
gates lies the duke's castle i won't who the fuck is this yes arisen yes arisen duke edmund
dragon's bane is a hero he slew the worm a generation past no no i got a great team here
he said he was named duke before his cavalcade reached grand soren's gates worship him as
their savior a smithy i should think he tried no wrong person
under his guidance they're just taking things from this guy's outs this looks interesting
yeah it's also not yours the enlistment course scours the land for soldiers to man the
frontier remember it's because you're on i talk more frequently now mercy this looks
interesting please please no sir i know it is not a matter fit to thrust upon a passing stranger
but yeah there's like a mourning family in here and you just went and took a bunch of
shit from their house please i ask only that you listen a while thank you sir this child is
he's my son was my son his heart stopped not a few hours past always weak his sweetheart
since he was but a babe i had long known he would not live long what the fuck is this
person doing with the crate but to see it to watch him slip from my grasp i am left with
not but rage at my impotence that guy part of the house raid here he saw us do it and he
came and just grabbed like a bunch of clothes pain to try any means that i might to bring
him back to magic curses anything to bring him back to me i know it for madness but still i
hear pray accept these sir the first of those stones i bought from a merchant my son and i
passed in our travels he spoke of a powerful magic within it gather rocks such as this
together he said and even the dead shall wake so we got make an undead son this is gonna be crazy
big marsh 10 community subs not that i thank you big marsh
50 dollars in a different way thank you thank you guys so much for real dropping fucking big
money laundering i had a change of heart he's bringing it back his mother yelled at him outside
and so i searched but by the time i found a second they hold pursuit rain hollow it is a
vain hope to seek immortality in such drinkings i know he's refilling the box
he's not sorry bringing it back and filling it up again wake stones are miraculous items
that can bring your character pawn allies or others back to life treasure each wake stone for
the fragments required to form them are quite rare and each stone can only be used once gather
enough wake stone shards and they will automatically assemble to form a complete stone deliver a
wake stone to austin seems no one knows just how he managed to defeat the beast
i was there was water i was trying to wake him up with water maybe he was like just
asleep what if he just whipped his head up like what the hell all right let's go
where shall we head uh let's take a look so i guess i don't that's not necessarily a quest
as much as it is just bring one back no i know i guess it is like um no just pointing to me
i'm going the mage route yeah i am at least initially here so where what am i doing ah i
want to go i want to go to the inn because i have new stuff to do new spells i can put on
yeah rank three turn the lantern off okay this is the armory with the inn right there
are you gonna do a full playthrough oh i'm not sure i'm still very interested
we can take on curatives if i'm still having fun and it's still interesting to me then of
course i'll probably just keep going until i don't necessarily care anymore which i still care now
why not take the day to walk its streets find your bearings have your pick any you like
so learn or set new skills learn skills there we go lastitude a magical fog at a desired
location that afflicts torpor upon foes who enter torpor fire boon ice boon thunder boon
holy boon high miasma spans the size of the poisonous fog and endures for a longer period
of time high levin high engel i got how much way up so why not it's just a better version
of it and lastitude i don't even know what the hell that does that's right ice these boons
i really should probably put one on holy boon holy light maybe yeah let's get it and then maybe
ice boon now i'll get ice boon frazzle that's not bad i'm just i'm gonna have the points
might as well just get it okay we got biting wind cutting wind an advanced form of biting
wind let's get that dazzle hold stun sprint helm splitter reset oh shit i have another one
core skills oh no i don't know i i guess i just unlocked these mitigates gravity's pull
enabling a gentle landing even from great heights augments the power of magic attacks
designed to knock down foes negotiate higher prices for items that you sell greatly reduces
damage sustained in magic attacks well let's change these skills high engel high levin and
i mean like holy boon just so i can make sure i have it what what's secondary i'll put the
boons on secondary let's try last two yeah because these are like little buffs now you
cutting wind is this oh cutting wind is already on so dazzle hold or scarlet kiss dazzle hold
probably that one a little bit of utility what will it be today core skills are new
combos and improvements you and your pawn can use them all after learning them no need to
equip those oh okay that's cool a broad range flurry of dagger blows deadly double strike
forward engrave quick loose that's cool and i'll get this one too so dazzle hold i need
augments wait what i don't have to put those they just on they're just passives
what will it be today understood is there a amount of core skills you're allowed to have
or can i just all of them are just passive and they can all stay on your follower has
returned from assisting another arisen in another realm what what is what is 3500 rc
a weapon bearing no maker's mark cursed with blackest magic did somebody just give me like
one of the rarest things in the game did i just get a stream snipe gift yeah that's somebody's
is this a stream snipe gift wait wait wait wait no no no no i don't it's not gonna like
level shito up like 500 times i don't think i want to do this you're fine so i can say
yes it's not gonna be a problem it's fine it's fine okay okay
five stars what's the message no message i hope i was able to please you arisen
you progress through the game by completing quests always talk to the people you meet the
show they have i might have to i don't think i'm gonna turn online off i'm just
gonna get free 3000 rc points every five minutes now free shit these last years
grants have your pick any you like what will it be today what will it be today rc is used for
nothing until the end game oh okay doesn't matter at all oh okay what we got here notice
board we got the peddler's petition and scouting mission you've one chance to boost
a companion's affinity by escorting them safely to their destination escort request
reynard great wall and camp and 10 golden talismans okay all right i'm ready to go
maybe take a look at some more items no you got the same shit come again okay so i need to
west i don't have anything right now i have this but i just have to do it the map i think
i just have to talk to people let's go on a talking mission even at its worst the world is
ever home to home any green question marks are they stealing more money we're like to have
dealings with the armorer here for some time to come where shall we head green green green
when there a guy in here that had a green is this guy that's red a stone to recall the dead
to living you stones red as blood and sourced with arcane magic strange you should mention it
i heard tell a traveling traveling merchant in a cave a few days past
it may come to naught but you might seek the stone on the shelves of grand soren's shops
really you can summon pawns as necessity demands here at the pawn field so somebody's
selling it somebody's selling this thing what's it called wake stone
wake stone you got nothing all right well let's i don't know if i'm supposed to be able to do
that right now barber barber shop welcome devin what will it be today
no this is just to change your hair is the x on the map no i that's my x
i put it on there i've not even gone down here as expected of a residential area he's much more
merchant's house wait a minute wake stone where up again let me zoom it out okay
pawn guild is the in craftman quarter i feel like i have to go somewhere i haven't been
i think i've been up here go up to the castle okay well let's mark it is this a back seating
stream or is he going to figure it out for himself uh it's kind of a it's all right
it's a little both i mean if i if i'm just looking around for the next place to go then
this is a cheating well i mean i did already take the free money so
can you kill something all right here we are now i need to go in here maybe how's the day
find you no i'm not killing anybody here i'm knowing in here hey look ah arisen my men
have told me much of you throw somebody your visit no no no no i'm sir maximilian eisenstein
captain of the hunt so named by his grace duke edmund dragonsbane i beg your forbearance whilst
i detail what is expected of you in the hunt the worm hunt license you carry permits the
bearer to undertake the most vital of tasks those missions given by duke edmund himself
of late all our will is focused on learning of and defending against the wicked dragon a
weighty task to be sure but one which the fate of the realm and its people rests upon
i am under orders to lend arisen all reasonable aid as they might require i would pray you return
this assistance in kind it will be my honor to show you the ready charges for the wormhunt
the choice is yours okay decipher a text and wrote a monster infestation investigate a cult
aid a research team i feel like this is the most boring one cult is interesting
how about that cult certainly then here are the details i fear this task is no simple call to
action sir it will no doubt take time and a more subtle approach than your other work
you can do them all well that's perhaps you've heard of the society they call salvation
in truth most of what we know is the product such hearsay they are a band of heretics who
worship the dragon welcome the petition it brings in the chaos come with the worms arrival
their influence has grown pray keep watch for signs of salvation as you go about your business
if you find all tell me okay good i'll rest easy after accepting quest first note the
quest marker on your map then continue by searching for the required items or information
it will be my honor to show you the ready the choice is yours okay and decipher a text
certainly i have important work for you the task at hand is just such a case will you
take it on as i was setting about to find work for you i came upon this slate i know
not his origin nor its age but the writing it bears is old so old our men could only
read a few words dragon scar a rhythm heart okay what little we know all points to you
sir best you should have it if there's order of import written there all right so i have
two things to do now let's go take a look we've got set one as the primary yeah pawns
and your party will also offer advice for the priority quest so we got the cipher and
we got seeking salvation speak with grandsaur and citizenry to glean knowledge of the cult
activities uh seek so i'm gonna set this so now i'm going to talk to people in town
must know something about this matter but first uh i haven't taken a break in five hours so i'm
gonna go pee i'm gonna grab some more water i'm back in like two three minutes i will be right
back see you very soon okay hello yeah i want to grab a water ask around let's continue you
what do you know it will be my honor to show you the ready charges oh never mind it's you
go away weirdo we're making jupiters hey don't call me a weirdo got two uh get the hell out of
here i guess this way i appreciate the infinite stamina when you're in a town though i really
do you got more shit for me to do you you seem the type unlike to judge a man but i would
ask you a favor sir a wise choice i would you'll be eager to hear what i i have long searched
for a certain toll salomet's grimoire he said its pages hold the power to grant the book
itself is ensorcelled you see even a novice is as a grand wizard with that grimoire in hand
i would ask you to seek it out recompense okay you gotta learn we this is an education
stream we have to learn learn learn learn ask ask ask what do you know about the
cult after salvation are you he'll be one of mason's friends no doubt all too eager that one
he's been questioning everyone with ears to listen i've gained talk with mason mason makes
his home here in the slums here we can rest manage inventory and skills it's like they're
playing a different game we're on a mission we got stuff to do and they just they're
doing their own world where's this mason where's this marker what was that guy
his name he was actually mason down here wrong way i know i mean how do i get over there
this is a left i can't go right here can i the fucking huge jump unwanted possessions and other
refuse ultimately find their way here i had hoped perhaps to find the book here whatever you say
all right where's this dude mason that name is so familiar hello no yes sir ism
not you mason i'm trying to keep focused no mason where the hell are you
no you're albert you're not the right guy
this shop does hello yes this is not this is not somebody's house
look on the map there's nothing on the map i mean that's i put that way point there
there's nothing here how far out is that that little circle is there but it's not on
the actual map oh it's right here why do they gray it out oh jesus oh man all right well
is it is it here it's on a different elevation well shit okay down in the sewers
is how do i get in there like in here oh god am i alive seems this way leads outside as well
mason is said to frequent this area hey thanks poop button you've been very helpful
there you are looking for me friend bearing good tidings i hope they're said to put me
in chains i'll wager that goes to ask the good folk of gran soren about salvation myself
oh i'm gonna choke me seems i'm cursed with a villain's mean door one look at my face
stores a man's stone dead oh what the fuck man can you get it out of your system already
had i your gentle manner they have them singing long and loud seems to me we share a common
perhaps you'd take on my investigate that's grand take this with you renew your inquiry into
salvation that token i gave is a counter side it will mark you as friend to agents of salvation
may have loosened their tongues as well i hope you'll return to share your findings good
all right so now i've got to talk to more people okay let's go this leads outside though
is it just open yeah i don't want to do that yet
so now i look like a friend do people that are part of the cult
and then once they become very close friends that's when we do a backstab
first person is here lady with the pot oh i see we are kindred spirits sir throw off
building will you be at the gathering then where it is needs to be a high officiant presiding
not that us lot will be permitted to speak with one in such an office directly mind
okay there's a meeting going on i just broke her vase i'm not gonna do anything else but i'm
gonna stick with the same the main quest here they're doing a meeting of the vias
i guess i do have to go over here can i make it this way by this area feels completely
seems the castle walls are reached by a flight of stairs ahead the ones that i just took thank you
for telling me okay there we go say no more friend i must confess i'd not expected the
arisen to shan salvation's creed though truth be told i'm far from a devout myself
that's all you got no other information just why is there a chipmunk sub sometimes
yeah i i mean it's very the game has a character creator and you can make them have very very high
to very very low voice that's probably very off-putting if you're just joining us
and trust me it's off-putting to me and i've been here for five hours playing it
the gatherings to take place down in the catacombs i hear he sounds upset talking about
me there just far too dangerous a place to brave for a night's diversion
by the way i didn't make this character i did not make poop but or dude these are
characters that were given to me that's not a lie that is for real you didn't have to pick
them oh yes i did whoa don't do that oh seeker's token it's not gonna hurt that bad is it
can i run and jump and grab the ladder no definitely not that's such a germa joke it's
not my character though i swear to god i would hurt a lot all right let's go if only you could
levitate what's this doing here the hell did this put me why did it bring me out here uh do we
swim
must have washed up here what how convenient water too deep or idle too long in the water
you'll fall unconscious so why the hell did it want me to come up this way oh what it's all
the way over here it so i have to go the other way because it was an exit it will point you to
any exit okay so that's not where i need to go though like i gotta go up here like up
there and out so we need to go out that way not out here to the ocean ride a horse
horse no don't do that not the horse part that part what i don't even know half the time
what the fuck they're saying he said the catacomb entrance stands to the north way
is there a way you can get through here no i'm gonna go up and around turn on subtitles
folder that's not a bad idea but that would be so irritating in its own right
hello among you has seen the dragon who saw it raise a village at the southern shore
no doubt you were filled with fear at all with trepidation with despair all right let's go
finally get me out of here the city has amenities to suit every need
armorers and interreter we can finally get this going let us check the map
why would you jump off there okay we need to go this way on that road heading that way
all right open world let's go we're everybody with us right yeah i'm gonna get ambushed
no horse is just printed your pockets and be quick about it
can somebody help me here can somebody do something
what the fuck i need to heal help he's coming after me what the fuck is this guy why is he
unkillable don't let him get me don't let him get me oh my god please get away from me get
away from me get away from me get away from me frazzled frazzled is he dead what the fuck
you say that now are you sure about that what the hell is this so it's a leather
circlet what are these great deal of health and stamina rotten berries a bit of health let's give
one give this cloth to dude pork crystal this thing's heavy a bit of shido a bunch of water
oh i have that's so heavy okay this is the heaviest should i have arrows well i don't need
these so just take them it's the rubble that is so heavy ran soren rubble wolf pelts that's
heavy i mean it's already sorted by weight isn't it i probably should have stored this shit
yeah you poop butt take like some of this dumb shit he's just carrying around rocks
but i don't i don't know maybe i need them okay i'm alright maybe the wolf pelts give it to
poop butt throw away the rotten food all right let's go this is painful to watch when you
finish the game four times well uh you have finished the game four times this is the first
time i've ever opened it war has not been kind to this place i need to heal poop on is such a
casual word now okay wait a great deal of health and stamina just eat the nuts
all right uh i want should i get like meat from these guys or something
let's get some food
he's died there's meat okay good let's get some meat
holy boon can i do it to myself
how do i do it to myself click on the stick to do it yourself
and an army of scholars pour over old texts all to fight the world so i can charge this twice
okay one two three i see i got it what's this beast steak fair bit of stamina
stamina health and stamina one two okay get him that works what's that are you guys gonna
pick up the meat on my way i'll well search the area he's power leveling
killing boars in warcraft all right there's a bad guy over there i think
all right no more fucking around kill a couple more cows and let's go that's it
there's certainly no worry of ambush out here rusted daggers didn't somebody say rusted
the daggers can actually be used like the rusty shit can be upgraded and actually works pretty
well seems fairly shallow it seems i'm not jumping in there you see i've fucking destroyed
myself last time we're going the right way rusty weapons are extremely overpowered when
they're upgraded fully that's kind of cool so there's a reason to use them there's a
chest right here throw somebody in to test it so much money no here's the entrance
i was trying to shoot this guy wolves fall quickly to planes
that's good to know thanks for the tip you look like you're
larping i mean part of me is larping oh what are those wizard men
electricity pretty good
the lizard wizard almost at the sewer portion oh i didn't even know that i thought that was
a rock
so how are we doing
where is this entrance i'm not even the right spot get out of here out
will my grandkids be able to see this on second journal maybe it's very possible if
youtube is still available in like another 30 or 40 years you might see it all right slow down
oh wolves are come on help where are you two oh fuck i'm tired
hold on am i gonna name my firstborn shito i don't think so my firstborn is gonna be
dave david including the stutter that i just did what what are you looking at no i'm gonna do
that too did i just fucking burn somebody's tent why the wolves in a camp
oh
where else do you think wolves live in a tent they don't put up tents
what's this dude does not talk that often i've noticed that and when he does it seems very
strange he's so out of place instead of sleeping mushrooms little 15 they grow up so fast is there
a reliable place i can kind of cross this river what's that just gonna have to cross
it's right there uh is that actually safe it's so far to run many a life was ended by falling
from two greater heights it's a good point all right here we are very well two take care you
water
fire into the water that's not gonna go very well is it lightning into the water oh fuck i haven't
saved it in a long time get out of the water get out of the water guys very well what the
fuck was that what happened he's stealthed oh my goodness everybody's dead
oh my fucking god this is very bad this is extraordinarily bad
holy fucking shit this is this i just got absolutely fucking destroyed i don't even
know where the last time i saved it was oh this is fucking fantastic let us check them out the
mild weather year-round makes grants is well suited for human life that's that so that was
an unwinnable fight i had to just run or do these guys just suck now what level what hold
on what level are these guys level 14 level 9 level 10 is it time to just throw these guys
in the river it was time a long time ago uh god damn it i mean i have she does one that levels up
fire this kk slider motherfucker
that was fucking perfect
sacrifice them to the river all right are you all right master yeah i am i will be very soon
fucking go off no that's not the person i want i cannot move my consciousness
fades are you all right master i'm sorry the beating heart of all grances all right i need
to do a couple i need better companions and i need better items he said the catacomb entrance
stands to the northwest this way leads on to the encampment i need a stone god damn it is
there even a stone here yeah it's in here right pawn guild my consciousness fades
all right let's go i need some level 14s 15s somebody better than
poop butt who's been nothing but just go to zero
business with the guild level 14 let's see what we get no what are you still doing here
go home go go bear elizabeth all right elizabeth has a huge bow but i already have a bow
let's take a look let's do a search bonds by level level 14 and we need a we need a fighter
somewhere they can tank because that's what that's what poop butt was but poop butt was dying
over and over again you got to put dane cook on there take your pick hagrid okay we got hagrid
get out of here why is hodor so small hagrid poop master with dane cook what do you get for
moves dane first strike shield summon symbol all in slot looks like aquaman yes sir isn't
all right well you have terrible moves so sorry hagrid time for you to leave what about poop
master yes sir ism blitz strike shield drum yes sir ism what are you doing here oh then
the terminator yes sir ism yes sir is the terminator or what about hodor yes sir ism
yes good bye yes sir ism i am honored to travel with you and i need another mage
i hate how he was actually the best one there all right uh hot cheeto zelda
candy s uh cheeto and cheeto we're gonna have to see
berry this one is just called heels so that's exactly what i'm looking for hot cheeto is
just that's zelda bingo berry and heels okay i yes sir ism
oh okay yes sir ism i am honored to travel with you it's just a hamburger feed with a
costume on just trying to get back in the party well we're good we got we have like the chat
joke poop person and then yes sir ism yes sir ism is everything in order master
i'd hope to serve you adequately may i yes sir ism i am honored to travel with you
let's go this is a place quite restful to my kind does poop master have a normal voice
the capital even holds a barbershop pawns who have expended the last of the same boys
will have little trouble the capital even holds a barbershop
they're all just huge all right are we ready time to go get some heels
let's go get some healing potions i got i need way more than this don't let the
party distract you from this compact stream how am i enjoying the game so far i think it's great
it's just weird enough and has enough interesting things going on that i think it's i like it a
lot it's fun uh but apparently i'm having trouble traversing the game because i need to go in
here and i didn't go the right way he said the catacomb entrance stands to the northwest
save at the end yeah i'll rest at the end i don't care about that guy all right let's take a look
i got to like storage shit congratulations have your pick managed stored items deposit what do
we got i have a bunch of trash marker to be placed anywhere one my wish to return
so i can just use that right okay silk fucking hemp insignias shrouds rubble iron bones
okay okay i know i need this ancient slate license i think i need these two on
i have two shards these things don't weigh very much today this thing is fucking heavy
what will it be today okay come on do i have anything i can combine oh wait a minute
oh i can use i can make wine return the slab return this lab i've seen that episode of
courage the cowardly dog what will it be today so what did do i did i actually i need that item
somebody says what the hell is it how is the text deciphering thing all right this thing
is staying in here what will it be today have your pick in your life what will it be today
understood i'm gonna get healing items who the hell is this why are they dressed like this
player name rift crystals didn't i already do this what why can they dress my character up
what yes i don't want this i brought this back for you i've learned new techniques
what the fuck did you just give me where is it what the fuck did you give
it's in storage all right let's go i'm so confused i fear have your pick in you that
what will it be today an almighty divine blade received along with your returned heart
how do i throw this away now what if i give this to poop master and then throw them off a bridge
only i can use it no i'm not i'm not what will it be today i don't even know what will it be
today no i'm not even going to open it no thanks what will it be today i'm just going to
keep it in the box and you come again soon okay let's go i just need to buy some healing
items armory an armorer i believe armor is traded away all right so this is a bit of health fair
amount of health a couple stamina the jester outfit was funny i don't like how they can dress
up my own character where's the body of poisons drive up the urge to slam i'm just
gonna get a bunch of these just to bring one speed eyedropper throat drops okay i got like
30 30 of these five of these let's get like 10 more of these lantern empty flask flask of oil i
got five that should be enough all right i got a ton of heels i'm ready i feel more familiar
with this question now he said at the very beginning of the game he knew he was gonna have
to get his heart back i mean yeah but i didn't uh i didn't really want to get the last item
in the game let us check them out nobody said you have the wrong thing to say well let me take a
look connectivity on online main pawn online access no one set the fast travel stone just
put the fast travel stone out here like right in front of the door no why not no okay all right
let's go get our asses kicked by the same guy it's already went there okay to feel more
when the capital is in sight okay here he comes
or the ruins of such here does you take like holy boom you take like an ice spoon who are
you aiming at he's gonna come out and he's gonna scream at us turn out your pockets and
be quick about it like for an opening counter after they strike i'll support you
in numbers we couldn't even hurt this guy 15 minutes ago or has not been kind to this place
oh no
well that's not good
now come on are you serious
he's just jumping around what are you doing you can't do anything you have no moves
why are you picking them up oh this guy's fucking stupid man what's his name you gotta be
kidding me
all right stop it oh my god we're getting destroyed this is particular i spent all that
time getting ready nice job poop master you did very good
oh my god i died like three yes okay heal heal i didn't even give
items to anybody fucking god come on oh my fucking goodness
why are they so hard
i'm on my way no they hold the advantage go run come on come on come on out run away
mannendorf is dead i don't what do you mean you don't understand how i let this happen
we got ambushed by like 30 people in the clock tower and we got destroyed oh i didn't
make it
don't give it to gannondorf
kill him dead
don't worry i am here please don't overdo it okay
i'll heal your wounds she don't needs they all need it this really is just kenshi on the ground
didn't i buy a shitload of these did a curative will serve this will restore a bit of health
all right no that was fun what's that what's this keep picking up rocks
this can strike day or night even in the shadow of france soren's walls so i need to go down this road
felonops i will have ample store of meat for an emergency i'm on my way i'll go at once
that was so funny he was actually just jumping around don't worry i am here what are you
all saying maybe one of those stamina things i need to get the meat from the cows again
what's that all right so now i should be able to let's be doubly sure which we'll see is to our
walk down this road who's this guy straight from the roads and we'll soon find monsters
arisen can you guys use your health things you're making me nervous they're not going to
use them are they what's with the voice changer for the characters
they use them when they need to okay the voice changer is just their voice
there's a character creator that was a fair amount of stamina
switch to their inventories okay it will serve as a fine landmark hand over anything
worth you've got where oh not this shit again guys guys pay attention guys guys deal stay in it
nice
no we did you guys are strong check the map make sure we're going the right way i am okay
just stay on this road to the left how are we doing everybody good all right let me see
oh i holy boot right so i have holy boot selected press the stick in and that does it to me
which then gives me holy bolts all right is that a bandit or no
are these bandits they just look like regular people
are they
they attack in quick succession
i guess so they're homing that's kind of cool come on
that's it
what's the water pike thing called i mean the water
they attack in quick succession
i'll support you we have triumph we're not getting that much experience
if you don't hydrate you're gonna miss your p i got a water writer i'm good
this will restore a bit of health thanks for the reminder all right i'm almost at the spot
let's save it shito is yellow well shito is not a human bad guy okay
it aims to hide itself then attack i'll support you
oh fuck
um oh no okay i need to ice people
i'll take this
okay everyone's ice enchanted
oh
road is up here i still hear music though
can i get a heal i shall restore your health
hold on thank you the path diverges did i cut it too quickly i think i might have
i think i gotta be up there i cut it too quickly i gotta go around let us check them out maybe not
monsters never want a character server still working for the game yeah
seems like it at least
isn't ready yourself i'm on my way i'll go at once all right going
oh
there it is there's a line he said the line everyone was waiting for that
but i really should try to play this game again it's quite good yeah it's just kind of fun to play
i mean we the first two or three hours of the stream we went over the kind of the jokey
shit that's in the game but as just a video game it's it's actually very fun it's a
straight-up video game i don't think that's safe i'm on my way there's like a stone over
here should i change people
i'll take that what level are these people 15 14 oh good that's just in case you're going
to change out a party member or something all right save it let's go pay the cult a visit
easy this looks interesting do you come to offer prayers for those who put down the crystal
here very well i'll go at once what's that do i only get to place that one time i'll take that
i need a lantern it is too dark to navigate without a torch i'll well search the area
the crypt was fashioned ages before the fate came to grancest oh rats light cure
this looks interesting you need to open this gate to use the lift long ago when the people
worshiped the old gods the gods of nature we cannot pass through i suspect it's why they
return their dead to the soil to the earth god what's this that their souls might be
cleansed and born anew and they never stop talking it's very very funny they don't ever
stop speaking
go the other way go this way that's interesting this place crawls with the undead i've learned
of this area what's this yes you have
a joke voice you heard it
well fire is really good here
this looks interesting what is that
so it would be awkward if nobody talked in a party of four people
yeah it would all right strength in numbers i believe some of the coffins are booby trapped
that's good to know check closely before opening the coffins no booby trap in there
this is the person here
we all have a curse now maybe i shouldn't have jumped inside of the casket this second you
fucking opened it
opening up all these fucked up sarcophagus i'm gonna stand in them just poop master things
nice move that was a knee right to the face
oh
all these uh fragments are dropping they're pretty good
we have triumphs if they hate fire they'll know this does not seem
back up
i'm on my way yeah it was really embarrassing
whack them all you ain't gonna get up
oh
whoops level 16 nice very cool leave it to me what's that
i'm dead oh and he said undead what is it showing me here area oh no nothing okay
so i'm about to wrap around there is the lever back here
i'm gonna assume i have to go down a little bit further or okay look another lever
no i'm dead no i am the structure is built from a natural cavern it is half a labyrinth
i'll take that chest and crumbled here and there with age what's more it is a lost place
this the game really is so cool the fact that these are all people that i didn't make
is really really funny really interesting so am i gonna step on the spiders or you guys
gonna do anything
coins good now we got a crossroads up here
oh i'm sure they are
is
fire is the best
swords up only while they inhabit a host
oh i get it
okay you gotta wait till they go
oh
dude i'm just so relaxed right now
is the holy boon that's a good idea give it to you
snooze day yeah sometimes you have snooze day see what we have here i'm playing a bunch of
intense games lately interesting as sometimes it's nice just to just to open my mouth and
play a game where's the letter like animal crossing oh you're right master nice to relax
and fucking murder my pawns to make room for new ones
you missed some new leaf isn't the new one coming on there's a new animal crossing coming up with a
switch this year right sometime in 2019
that doesn't matter trust me you're gonna be fine
holy boom let's give to you
i'm feeling a ghost coming this isn't dragon quest well no it's big
oh i didn't know what to title it i could have titled it like welcome to the freak show or
something let's have a look change title no it's too like we've got the screen's been going
for over six months six and a half hours can't change the title now
thanks for throwing that in the back of my head all right all right all right easy
okay all right we got a problem here holy holy holy this skeleton has to work
so
okay everybody good we have triumphed make up all the shit that we need dark
i ain't going down there without save no way
that was a south park character
oh let's go uh this way i guess back around doesn't it whoa what's over here
holy shit no i'm dead
yeah the fucking mage is the mage charges in first
that's all right i guess i have to go that way
uh give everybody holy boon let's go where could this path lead
yeah i shouldn't be sprinting around corners
it really should be
okay i thought that was he was wearing something on his back he is but you know never mind
frame plate is open so now where from here all right go on my way
you just rip all the way around
everybody beefed up let's go see what we have man i i got so tired
i went into relaxation mode you know when that happened
it was after the the big snake hydra fight thing oh fuck oh no
holy what should we use against fire
ice
this has been a cyclops lightning
hoop master that's having trouble
keep your distance that works what do you propose latitude works pretty well
oh
latitude works oh i freeze it hit him in the head
trolls are weak to the mobs oh i see
right in the head freeze him freeze him freeze what's going on
watch out i feel like i'm playing the world of warcraft
oh shit i'm tired holy shit he just rock kicked me i just took a picture of him drop kicking me
in the fucking face cheeto somebody save cheeto i'll do it yeah the fucking mage will do it
oh thank god he's frozen excuse me goodbye get him we did it that's it who else is down here
well easy don't don't just run forward we just took on the abominable snowman we just killed
bigfoot and you want to run and sprint and kill everything right now and attack stuff
this looks interesting can't save it here now we can go
now we'll gain the upper hand
iron greaves there's more shit over here liquid vim and milk
i feel like we're getting close it was a somebody made a lennox joke
leave it to me what's the lennox reference don't fall down what's that hair i'm on my way
the joke is lennox oh i see lennox i also missed some community subs from big marsh
i'm not sure what i must have been not paying attention i must have been focusing on
something or i might not have been here but thank you big marsh if you're still here
for a shitload of community subs thank you you guys not gonna pick all this up
you named it poop master i did not i didn't name this i know people are gonna coming to the stream
and they're thinking that i did that i swear to god i'm gonna get rid of him that character
has to get thrown in the trash because people are gonna come and think that i actually made
that character i didn't make any of these people i made it shito that's the only one
haha you named him master oh my god i know i didn't though i had to use
this looks interesting what's this had to use two years ago
it's the map this is the way to go but let me just see what's down here first probably an exit
shortcut something way back up maybe uh-huh we draw further from their meeting place
there is the shortcut perfect didn't want to make youtuber jokes but chose poop master
yeah but wasn't that more chats doing than it was mine and i've got to be fair to myself a
little bit here this pretty much like a 30 chance that the character's name is going to
be named like poo poo dickhead or something we've seen at least three or four of them
the voice from beyond the door it's the meeting
the cult meeting we're about to break it up
is this on pc it is on pc
it's a graphic mod
do i should i have a graphic should i open the front door
what are they
this
don't don't don't blow cover here no stay with me very well
best we brought cures for various ailments they may save our lives
duty bound to seed our souls unto it
what i didn't do anything
no i wanted to watch that what what did i do wrong
this is the answer dear
there comes a boss he's going to sacrifice everybody in there they're going to turn to a
giant monster don't look behind you don't look behind you oh we never see the full front of
face okay defeat the undead oh really i was about to have help me poop master
the guy that i didn't make every time i say his name i have to assume maybe one or two people
came to the screen i didn't make that character we obviously haven't so keep at it
die hey i just joined the screen did he make poop master no no i suppose it's the stuff of
every day to you arisen i'd thank you to join me for a moment we have triumphed strength in
numbers arisen what's that why didn't you make poop master does that somebody didn't even
realize listen the person that made poop master didn't know that his character was
going to be able to be seen or used anywhere that was a dumb just easy shitty name to make
your character he has no idea that it's being used online how many times you guys made a
character name and it was like dog shit because you don't you know if you're playing a game
you don't have to worry about it to be sure but at least he's talkative no honor you say
it was just a lark all in good fun never gave over to that raw about destruction and salvation
never just the same it'd be trouble if we let him go free now that he's seen the two of us
together why you you promise no five two by the way right guys nope more like six one or like
five eleven i feel more familiar with this question the arisen ran counter to the tides
the heretic he said but i i see what reasonable sort the sword like to hear reason i get off
of them come sir what's to be gained from bloody in your hands your choice to make arisen
i'm on my way away from him there's not to stay the dragon's fire what say we await
tradition together there's many a pleasure to indulge in air salvation comes gladly furnish
the coin that we shall follow whatever you decide spare me arisen that i may live to see
very well you'll be well don't be a fool sir surely my gold is worth more to you than my head
empty stomach to do for an unarmed man i force push them was wrong to doubt it
that kills people glad to know you're someone i can trust in times to come
go i didn't know you could die from an erizuka
we'll bring this skull of foxes to bed you and i oh maybe i shouldn't have done that i
shouldn't have thrown a firecracker in the air sound judgment this was the only way it's okay
he was a bad guy hey thanks even had you spared doubtless mason would not have shown such
mercy cheeto is getting jaded uh-oh uh-oh i wonder what's inside you gotta let the leader open that
don't you say master looter is on all right now you fucked it all up the guild leader
loots the bodies and then we roll and then it goes out to who wins let us return to the
capital what's that what's this doing here well uh new mission is over so that means we can
sacrifice one of these guys probably poop master nice throat model top well favorite flower
many a life was ended by falling from two all right we need to go back this way
well i guess we're just to go here
here we're giving it this other one get up what happened to hamburger feet well
we went through a lot of people actually so there's been at least five or six new recruits
that's a new staff what's going on up here don't worry i am here
is this oil
absolutely direct no attack
you just misquit
we have triumphed all right poop master thanks for playing your tire rest give me the shit
you have on you give it here i can't take this away from him i can't swordsman's ring
take care you are soaked in water that's the least of his problems
well i guess he's staying for a minute just land on your neck from like a 75 foot drop
100 foot drop seem just got a little wet you all right be careful careful you're wet
oh my goodness this game is so fucking funny but just like a remarkably stupid game
but but hey hold on hear me out the the the game is great what's that
i don't mean that in a negative way at all there's new spells and shit yeah that's true
all right i need to go back this way climb on a buffalo okay i'll try it and what's this
oh my goodness don't kill it why are you killing this there's no reason to do what you're doing
right now what are you doing here why would you come over here there's no reason for you to
attack us right now there's no reason is he gone i don't want to do this can i go can i bring
this into the city where's the how close are we now if you don't attack help help i'm on
my way no no no help as in just is there like everybody just calm the fuck down passive
what the fuck was that this way towards the city come on you just get out of the fucking way
shido that's like a second time you've done that no no stop stop don't don't don't don't do
that you need to get out of the way though all right that's it i'm done i'm gonna be
fucking the town leave it to us their brains are so small take them into the ocean
i mean it's a possibility but you can't steer them i would love to ride them into the city
can i climb this i can't be like a cat holes like this one are crucial in warding the
capital for monsters kill them all no no just follow me follow me back in the goddamn town
i have to go that way i guess i gotta go straight let's kill them
let's do it ain't nothing
just two archers they're easy nothing
nice work all right let's get out of here
okay straight on the road and then take a ride he's playing a mage yeah it seems like fun
the capital is not without its dangers as we remain cautious why you're not using
auto travel be ready for anything you madman grab the eternal fairy stone from your storage
all right so what do we need to do in here we need to go this way noble quarter complete it
he doesn't know don't break his gamer immersion can't climb this i think i have to go all the
way around get a new skill or two yeah i think what we'll probably do is i'll probably get
a new skill or two yeah i think i'll probably get a new skill or two yeah i think i'll probably
get a new skill or two yeah i think what we'll probably do is i'm probably gonna call it up here
it's been just about seven hours after the bits probably about eight hours
end of the stream voice yeah there's so much shit to do
think you play more of this game i think so i think so i did the cult then the gatherings
of salvation did have sinister purpose it is a grave shame the elysian slipped our snare
we shall redouble our vigilance here to keep the city safe i fear you are as like a target
as grand soren though for now i leave you with my thanks that's a lot of experience
cool level 19 all right so here is the deal over the next few days i got a lot of shit so
there's a bunch of stuff that i'm gonna have there's dreamcast there's some playstation 2
stuff that i wanted to do there's the dark souls 3 first person mod there's so much stuff that
i want to do 170 dollars of amazon purchases but there's i have a lot of things to stream
so expect to see this game again in the next few days but we might change gears tomorrow
depending on what i have because i a lot of stuff is ordered and it's shipping
so depending on what i end up with tomorrow we might change gears a little
but definitely expect this game within the next couple of days and then of course the january
23rd stream is just going to be irl i'm not going to play a game so let me take a look
actually let me see a like a calendar why am i going to stop streaming like tonight
um just because it's probably going to be about an eight hour stream and
i can always feel my energy levels dropping and getting a little tired getting hungry
when it's less viewers than kenshi you know it's not good that's all right though that
doesn't bother me it's also like yeah it's also like very late there were a lot of
people here earlier it was like almost 4 000 people here in the first couple two or
three hours of the stream i also started late too so i started like an hour plus late so
no i don't i don't ever expect people to you know if you if you're not interested
that no that's fine there's still a lot of fucking people here more than like two
2 500 2000 that's a lot of fucking people i had a had a great time but let me look at the
calendar because so today is technically friday tomorrow i don't know i kind of can't this is
the weird kind of spot that i'm in with all the games that i have to play so a dreamcast stream
is really going to have to be that's going to be over at least a couple of streams
a game like this needs to be streamed more than once starting like dark souls 3 insane mod
night that's that's can't just do that one day right i have to think of how i want to
block this out and do this i got shen mu i have all those classic dreamcast games
i'll figure it out so expect tomorrow and i don't know maybe we'll just do this again tomorrow
maybe it's very possible but if you don't see this tomorrow then expect either the
dark souls 3 insane night or uh some dreamcast stuff or i also have lifeline for playstation
2 which is the voice activated like i don't even know what it is i know it's like a
voice activated adventure game and then the 23rd yeah we got there's a lot going on so
regardless you'll see me tomorrow we'll figure it out thanks for sticking around if you're
leaving we're gonna do the bits and the subs see ya thanks for watching see y'all tomorrow
what's the usual time to stream i you okay i think that i no thank god i just clicked
i think i just shot that guy but i didn't all right we're gonna save it i usually start
around 3 p.m pacific which is 6 p.m eastern let me just exit the game because it's kind
of i can't really alt tab out of it there we go quit the game 7 a.m for aussies i can't
that's so strange to think about that think about where that is it's a 14 hour difference
isn't it no more than that 17 hour difference that's wild but let's go through the bits
see y'all tomorrow hopefully this time starting at three not like four pacific hey jess thanks
for the one dollar give shito the autotune voice modulator and actually that's not a bad idea
i gotta set that up though i have to change what my input is and everything it's gonna take a
few minutes so we'll do that another time because uh i don't have access to that changer right
now i have i probably have to like restart some stuff but it's a good idea like you
alex for the one dollar germa when are your shirts coming out i'm dying well let me i'll
explain the t-shirt thing so while back uh ashley and i were like hey let's do another shirt
and the shirt is if you don't know it is the solar system it's a beautiful picture of the of
the actual solar system there's some really nice nuanced stuff there's a a boy and a
man and his son you know looking through a telescope at the actual night sky it's a beautiful
shirt a couple months went by and another emote was added which was a different planet
i probably should put that on too another month went by oh wait hold on
we got like two more planet emotes so eventually it got to a point where
this shirt kept on getting pushed because we just i kept adding planet emotes so
to save the space on the shirt there are a couple of planet omissions just because it all
wouldn't fit on the shirt well for instance germa saturn doesn't exist it's not there
the planet doesn't that planet's gonna get like deleted in the next germa rumble anyways
germa mercury is also not on there cluedo is on there the only ones that aren't on there
are saturn mercury and i think that's the only two that are on there jupiter is on there oh of
course it is yeah you gotta have jupiter on there but it'll be it's a nice shirt it's really
really interesting it's really fun and it is going to be on sale very soon because i
literally just talked to her again and we're gonna go from there so expect it within i would
at some point before the end of january so either the last week of january or the first
week of february is probably when it'll be on sale and the glue man shirts coming back too
so they'll both be on sale because there's really no other reason why that would be held
back at all because there the shirt is pretty much done and the glue man shirt already is
done it's the same artwork it's just going back on sale but hopefully that answers your
question thank you for the one dollar thank you bake me home for the $1 thank you divas
for the $2 thank you mr. dask for the five dollars their masterworks all you can't go wrong
oh oh the masterwords all you can't go wrong where i where have i i keep hearing
that where have i heard that before the master works all you can't go wrong master works all
you can't go wrong no wait no and i think did i forget already forget it's from the game no i
know but what is a star sub sound okay that's probably why that's definitely where i know it
from then why that has a sub sound but then again what the fuck is my sub sound mine's worse
mine's way worse i gotta change those i gotta you know i might just drop the sub sound like
sound off completely or do it something else i never know what the hell to do place it with
something else don't do that we'll see superintendent chalmers thanks for the one dollar i can't believe
they made a game about the dogma from monster hunter the dodo the dogma i played monster hunter
what what's the dogma hey c4g thanks for the dollar 25 here you go sonny use this dollar in
a shiny quarter to buy yourself a brand new dreamcast new dream caster the dreamcast was
not expensive it's all these rare dreamcast games that are like a hundred plus dollars each
i severely underestimated just how rare some of this stuff actually was
uh thank you sad vega for the one dollar hey germa i know you won't see this till after the
stream but there are some great mods for this game that improve the graphics and look at the
game without changing its mechanics unless you want to change mechanics go check out nexus mods
and don't get the blind me mod and i'll get the don't blind me mod really helpful with
lightning effects i was actually going to say that i was thinking that but i didn't say it
that every time the lightning struck it was kind of unnerving to my brain i will at least
go get that one uh and also the resident enb grandsis texture improvement there's also a handy
dandy mod pack that i think is most popular that improves most things i'll probably just
go get it especially the lightning stuff and some of the other maybe graphic updates but
i thank you i appreciate that because i the lightning thing is something i was thinking
but wasn't saying hey dan with wings thanks for the 10 dollars dan hey germa i haven't been
able to resub for the last couple of months since i wasn't working due to school
figured out give back by giving some community subs and bits from my favorite streamer
also you introduced me to celeste with which i am enjoying a lot that's not surprising celeste
was a really really really great fun challenging platformer no surprise that you're enjoying it
but thank you for your community subs and thank you for the 10 dollars no one is ever
under any obligation to pay me please keep that in mind but thank you so much regardless
online influencer i have one guy bought it how many people bought celeste after the two celeste
streams that's not a great return on investment if i was a game company what are like 11 people
buy it okay imagine if like imagine if even 100 people downloaded celeste celeste is how much
money 20 bucks so if it's 20 dollars so that would be like what 100 copies would be a
two grand right so imagine if i had been like paid i'm not saying i'm not just that i'm not
saying i was well this is the exact amount of money i would get but imagine if i was paid to
like promote that game and only like 80 people bought it well they would have made money but
would they have though because they would have had to pay me right true but at least you
still get paid but those 80 people convinced two other people to buy it so then you got
80 people telling two people then two people telling 80 and then 80 more people than all the
sudden that's that's 200 000 sales over the course of like six months how much do you charge
per stream i've never done it so i don't know i have no idea probably like 30 probably 30
bucks no no it would have to be it'd have to be like you know what it would be like
it would be a uh it'd be a thousand dollars per person watching well that would be way too
much maybe what would it be about per viewer 100 bucks per viewer because you know that's how
valuable these viewers are these aren't just some simple run-of-the-mill fucking viewers
okay i could sell you guys so hard you know i know i could talk about how you guys are some
of the most valuable viewers on twitch and it would be i'll be telling the truth but that
marketing person would hear that i'm only worth 100 bucks that's pretty cheap well 100 times
1600 is that's a lot that would mean 1600 that's oh my god that's too that's way too much money
that's 160 000 okay you know what i'll stream i will stream fallout 5 but i want 160 000
dollars and that's that 1600 people there were 35 3800 people here earlier that's almost a
half million dollars to stream it no i don't do sponsored streams so i never have and
i don't think i ever will you mean you you mean your audience is the easiest to manipulate
what fairway solitaire doesn't count because that was like on youtube like six years ago
it's the only time i've ever done it i've never done it ever since and that was i
already made a video listen to me hold on a minute let me defend myself i made a fairway
solitaire video because i liked the game a lot the company then contacted me and said hey you
want to give the game away to a bunch of people and i was like sure i think the game's fun it
was later it was after that and it was just you could just download the game for free if you
used a code i think you know if i had to pay for anything i was like hold on it was just
it's just gonna be free like no questions asked the game's free they're like yes if
they use your code okay that's it the game is just for free it was like a two dollar
game at the time and now the game is just free years later you sounded defensive no i don't i
don't do sponsored streams because i don't like the dynamic i don't i don't it doesn't sit well
with me for a few reasons because of nothing against it if people want to make some extra
money you know that's fine if it's relevant to what they're doing that's fine but i just i
just don't like it like why in the name of god would i ever play like some free to play card
game for like an hour and a half like why would that ever happen you know i would never
do that what if it's a game you enjoy yeah that's fine but that's not typically how it
works from my uh last five plus years doing things on the internet it's always like the
game that nobody actually really wants to play will give you a shitload of money if you play it
i don't want to do that it's not like i mean sure there are people that have you know sponsored
streams from companies they know like ubisoft and i mean i've that might not even be real
but i know that there are large companies that do them but a lot of them are games that
people might not even really necessarily care about in the first place at least that's how it
was like on youtube if the makers of 700,000 games offered you 10 grand to play volume 3 would
you take the money no i'd be like i'll pay for it but the game well actually you know what how
about this sure i'll do that every single one of those games has to open though and if the
games if one game on that list doesn't open i get triple the money for each one that doesn't
open that'll light the fire under the a** to make sure that they work sounds like a good
deal we've got some shito fan art oh that's really cute it's like everybody loves shito
if a game developer sent you a game copy or review copy would you take it no and here's the
reason why here are the reasons why i don't do sponsored streams i don't like to take
free games or press games press copies because i think about it differently if i get a copy of
a game for free or if i get a sponsored game it will change the way that i talk it'll change
the way that i do things because i know that this was given to me or this was sponsored and
i have it just is in the back of my mind me paying for a game or me just buying it and
doing whatever i want with it i am at my own free will to do whatever i want if i were
to take a game for free and then say a bunch of shit about it it'd be like okay well
like hey wait wait why are you doing that i would rather not hinder anything that i ever
wanted to say or do because i know a lot of sponsored streams they say hey you can kind
of say what you want but don't do anything don't be so bad oh you know i don't know i would be
afraid that somebody would rip my fucking contract in half because i'd come across like
a bug that i didn't like and i'd be like fuck this game and all of a sudden it was like
the piano fucking falls from the ceiling it's like if you get a christmas present you have
to pretend to like it yeah but i'm not even sure the the answer is pretending to like it it's just
knowing that it was given to you for a reason there's pretending to like it and then there's
knowing that you were given this thing for a very specific reason it's also difficult to
judge something fairly if you didn't yeah but i mean for journalistic journalistic approach
right like if you were like a journalistic outlet if you're like a game reviewer
or it i don't think there's that this maybe there's not something actually wrong with it
if your company is based around doing full-on like breakdowns of games maybe it is maybe that
goes against it completely feel free to say whatever you want as long as it's not negative
or discourages people from buying the product i just can't have that living over my head even
if i like it some people are better with that dealing with promotions you're just not one of
them yeah and i don't have it look there's i don't have anything wrong with it there's nothing in
my brain that says that's wrong what you're doing but also keep this in mind too at the
end of the day you guys are watching a stream and what you see on the stream is what you
in your in your mind it's something that i have decided that i wanted to show you right
and if i tell you with this three or four thousand people here hey check this out isn't
that really cool check it out i don't want to be disingenuous of the things that i'm showing you
because there's a lot of people that come to streams and they oh i want to what what are you
doing today oh it's something that you necessarily didn't decide to do you decided to do it but
for a different reason not because you wanted to show your audience something because maybe
you were offered money to from a company to show it not necessarily you wanting to do it
and it's nothing to do with honesty it really did i it i did say i used the word disingenuous
but if i let's just put this way if i got fucking 10 grand to play a shitty mobile game
on stream and pretend i was having fun some of you guys would download it and you'd be
like this game sucked this was stupid why did he do that oh he did he took a bunch of money
okay i guess right like they would that's the reason i think it's nice that you want to show
us something that you'd really enjoy or at least try to enjoy i mean that's from my view that's
what i want to do here and the money coming in people talking about money and making money and
there's a shitload of money comes in already a lot so i mean could i make more money could
i make way more money i don't maybe if i took a bunch of sponsored streams and deals but i
don't like i don't have to do that i don't like need to do that and if i can just kind of do my
thing and not have to worry about taking it like sponsor deals or but that lies down obviously
the reason why i'm able to do that is because so many people do sub to the stream and do
give money so i don't like i don't have to go get like oh i'm gonna get i want to get
like a ten thousand dollar sponsorship it's not it's not really that necessary because
like you guys already you guys already do that you already give a shitload of money
there's maybe a weird question but how do you handle such a large amount of donations tax wise
uh it's i mean it's just it's classified as you know like income like tips it's just money
goes through twitch even with paypal it's still classified as tips right and you have to
pay taxes on tips stop having integrity but i but i don't want to come off as like the
i'm the last bastion of integrity on the platform no there are plenty of ways to
run a live stream and there are plenty of other people that don't do like sponsors
there are a lot of them i'm not the only one and like i've said 10 minutes ago i don't i don't
have a negative attitude towards somebody that does classified actually means he doesn't do his
taxes wait what i have i have i i'm about to do them in like i'm about to file my return
probably in a week or two so and i got a actually have i have a very very good cpa
very trustworthy evading you know just jerma ignore this message i can't you have the one
guy emailed there teach us how to do taxes it's uh all right you want to know how to do
your taxes dip yourself in fucking like just get just buy like a giant fryer later
and then dip yourself in it on max heat that's what it's like buy the tune liquid from
who framed roger rabbit and just slowly sit in it sounds about right just eat the paper
but it won't work we aren't tunes um what what you're on a tune stream right now
hey how do you feel about urinals let me tell you something all right let's move on now spend a
lot of time talking about that but it's nice to discuss it every now and again because there
there are pros and cons to all these things you know like think about that to put one
last point into that conversation imagine if i did a couple of sponsor streams and then all
the sudden that pays for jerma rumble too you know what i mean like there there are
pros and cons but the cons for me have always out kind of grown i mean the cons the cons have
outgrown the pros for me pretty much every time i think about it i've thought about it a lot
this ain't something that i've just kind of hey let's talk about this now
i internalize this all the time but thank you dan with wings that was where we left off
uh drum age thank you drum edge for the one dollar hey you probably don't even remember
the cheer about lisa uh and begging for it but still want to apologize for it it was wasted
as fuck like right now no don't worry about it don't worry about that it's all right you've
recommended a game to me oh no i think i know what you're talking about when i brought up
moving to another game and i just used the word lisa i think that's because you were the
last message that i saw about a game recommendation and that was just the last
game recommendation that i saw there's nothing to do with what you said or how you said it or
something no you you you you were the one guy and that's how that happened people have been
asking for lisa a trillion times i suggested a year ago yeah but okay every time somebody
suggests lisa they are sandwiched by two people saying don't play lisa you know there's like
a i just like burped really loud and then hopefully the music covered it if anyone
doesn't want lisa play it now it's a good ass game series but i feel like it's not for you
maybe i don't know you should not play lisa it's too sad to make it a fun stream that's kind of
what i hear that it's a great game but streaming it is like it's a sad game
and it wouldn't be like a fun stream it would be like a sad stream is that accurate
you'd have to take it seriously we'll see i'll put it on the list i don't know
that's tough because i want to be like sad on stream i don't want to be sad in general either
but thank you uh drummage for the one dollar two dollars here could you check out age of empires
too for lulls sometime if not could you at least give your thoughts on it if i even know
what it is it's one of the original real time strategy games that predated everything else
i know what it is i watched a guy play that on a plane when i was like 14 i was sitting
in the aisle seat and he was one row above and in the aisle seat to the right so he was
diagonal to me and he had a laptop on the plane i had to have been like 14 or 15 at the time
he was older he was probably in his like mid to late 30s and i was just sitting there
watching him play and eventually he like noticed i was watching because i was just
staring at a screen and i said what is that and he said this is uh age of uh age of kings
it's age of age of empires too is age of kings right age of kings yeah i got it
age of empires too age of kings and i remember going oh this is great watch he was the game's
lead developer i just caught this right here in the chat here uh roshimi uh swift recently
diagnosed with severe ulcerative colitis any good recipes or any lifestyle changes i should try
i understand you've had issues and i just wanted your input yeah i i don't know what your uh
plan is for your doctor i don't know what your what they're going to try first because
there are a couple of different options for treatment but lifestyle wise at least initially
you have to kind of start ruling out stuff that you can't really eat for a while i
couldn't drink even i don't know i'm not sure how old you are but i couldn't drink a sip of alcohol
if i even drank like one beer or like one cocktail it would be living hell the next like
three or four days so for some people have their own internal uh issues and some foods
affect people differently especially if you have colitis i've since got into a pretty good
run here where i haven't had any really major problems i still do have problems but you know
i won't really discuss them on stream because they're kind of uh very disgusting and very
not i don't i don't i don't think i'd want to share the that stuff on stream but uh wait hold
on i'll touch on that in a second somebody just said about me being a kid in 1999
you would have been a teenager i was like i said 14 or 15 right 2009 2019 that was 20 years ago
so i'm 33 23 30 i was like that's 13 and i said 14 what are you talking about your math is off
my math is correct but uh you really need to just kind of look at your diet you start to rule
out fried stuff fatty stuff and some people can eat whatever they want and make sure you
get a good doctor that's going to give you a good treatment plan ask about it's a very
expensive drug unfortunately for some dumb fucking reason but one of the things because
i had mine started to localize itself i don't know where yours is but the drug is
is kanasa is the drug and it helped me a lot because mine was a little bit lower
i'm not going to give you any recommendations for what you should take for drugs
but i had a lot of issues that eventually after a couple of endoscopies the doctors were like
you know it's localized a little bit lower so we're going to put you on this it's a
met meslamine meslamine it's like an aspirin kind of uh derivative
scheduled for a colonoscopy in a couple weeks but i was hospitalized for a good week due to
pain that's why i started seeing a gi specialist will definitely continue to see that specialist
because you might get a little discouraged and not care and not want to do it oh i
got to go in and get it scoped i got to get scoped i got what do i try this
it's really easy to like kind of just fall down into like a depression and not give a fuck anymore
but keep going make sure that you get that doctor you on the right page then try to take
care of yourself and get yourself into remission it's a huge pain but i feel pretty good right
now and i did not 10 years ago not at all so i can relate for real i wish you the best i
wish you the best of luck hopefully you and your doctor can figure out a good plan i thought
i was lactose intolerant at first yeah when i first started having problems it was i went
through i mean i'm not going to be disgusting or anything but there was a bunch of weird
shit that i did that the doctor was checking for it took it took it was after i got
scoped for the first time that really it was okay i think this is what you have
and from there i got put on a couple of drugs that i really didn't like
and it's kind of sucks that i was on them for a while i don't even know if they still prescribe
it which is kind of terrifying in its own right i mean i wonder if this medicine even still
exists yeah it does yeah i was on imuran for a long time and i really didn't like it
but it may have been one of the reasons why i went into remission i don't know
but i fucking hated that drug i hated being on that drug because there's a lot of weird
issues with it imagine jerma as a celebrity i don't think i want to imagine that they
definitely still prescribe imuran i was on it until last year so that yes they do i don't know
if they still did it because there's a there's a lot of literature that i can really help it's
an immunomodulator they prescribe it to people that do like kidney transplant it's like a
transplant acceptor drug but it does have some weird effects on crones and colitis
and ibd symptoms so it just weird that just freaked me out taking it like an immunomodulator
like if it's fucking with my dna but anyways i wish you the best of luck take care of yourself
listen to your doctor and get a good plan but anyways uh age of empire age of kings
i'm aware of it and i think it was cool dub ski dude thanks for the one dollar dragons dog
is a special game to me the most legendary gaming fail of my entire life happened in this game
i was soloing the ur dragon it's a secret boss with like 20 health bars and it literally took
six hours for me to beat when i finally killed it it hit me with petrified i desperately tried
to loot the corpse but turned to stone and died before i could grab anything and i lost
the loot forever i literally wanted to eat my own head that sucks six hours that is rough
that's very rough and that's the kind of stuff i can look forward to then bring it on sounds
fun thank you dork cube for the one dollar this game looks beautiful and ugly at the same time
it's because i don't have the mods to make it look better that was my fault mind my halo
thank you for the ten dollars smelly boy thank you for the one dollar
where is shito show me proof that he's alive he's saying i am alive he's alive all right
you ready to go back to bed good night pre-recorded shito uh thank you
for the three bucks they say it had to be done i can't tell is did you what is
this an image of my eyes on that character is this the willem defoe face i don't know it's
freaking me out i can't look at that for more than five seconds don't look at that picture
before you sleep it'll that that monster will come out of your mirror or something
hey smelly boy thanks for the one dollar who's your favorite animator on new grounds
blow it out really hey mostly lost thanks for the one dollar your resistance and
hesitation to use any stupid jokey characters is even funnier than the characters themselves
especially since we all know you'll give in eventually well i did i played with two
characters that had poop in their name there was poop but and then like poop master so it
happened i told you 30 percent of the characters have that word or a variant of that in their
name you're not going to be able to do a full playthrough of this game and not have
one character in your party whose name is like poopoo dick it's not going to happen it's
going to happen because you're going to have the right spells and abilities that you're going
to need and you're going to want to bring them in just for like a couple minutes to do one mission
i can't believe somebody gave me all the end game items like what the hell that i'm actually
like kind of sad i just realized that i did that just image just popped up in my brain
right now thank you carrot seven for the one dollar i fell asleep during your character
creation woke up to a brave soul named poop butt being eaten by a hydra i like this game
that was so fucking funny and the fact that a bunch of people said that they've never seen
that cut scene before because i took too long to fight the tutorial boss but that was because
i was laughing and couldn't do anything i was watching a guy named poop but get fucking
digested by a snake what was i supposed to do how are you supposed to react to that
there's no way you can react to that any differently oh god that was fucking funny that
took so much energy out of me though i was laughing so hard it took it so long to go through
he started in the top of the mouth and i didn't i never got him out you just slowly see
this like sleeping bag slowly just go down into the thing's stomach this is called this is
save poop butt is this it save poop butt he's he'll be fine
all right somebody tell me i don't care about spoilers or backseating are there more big crazy
fucking hysterical bosses like that in this game or is that just kind of like one every
yes yes okay well then i'm absolutely going to play this again if there is a shitload of dumb
encounters where poop butt can get eaten yeah where you will absolutely be playing it again
but anyways thank you to uh carrot glad you rejoined us after sleeping bread avi thanks for
the five dollars oh shit germ was playing my favorite game can't stay and watch because i still
have to catch up on my vod homework but here's my first bits to celebrate been watching since tf2
still as good as ever keep up the good work earnold definitely looking forward to this vod
and more to come i gotta go thank you bread uh you're not here but maybe if you watch the
vod and you get to this point thank you bread avi for the five dollars and thanks for
sticking around as long as you have fuck yeah thank you dot shaft for the ten dollars
hey germa love the stream i was thinking about donating a lot more but decided to take off a
dollar for every shortcut you didn't take during the simpsons hit and run stream so you're going
to give 15 dollars okay thanks though appreciate it thank you for the ten dollars dot shaft
appreciate that thank you hey frodean weapon thanks for the ten dollars frodean i had a
bit of a rough week with you streams always helped lift my spirits thanks germa hart ps
tell shito that i said hi i will hey shito yeah now frodean weapon wants to say
hello to you do you say hi back no why i don't think they said that did you
no i don't think he did did you did you just frody did you hold on i'll talk to him you
want to talk to him okay did you say he was the worst character behind grill master
because that's what he just that's what he said he said i'm talking to him right now don't worry
ban ban no i just i think he might be mistaken i don't i don't think that was the person you're
talking about are you sure i don't i don't think you're right i don't think you're right it
wasn't frodean weapon i'm telling you i've been watching the chat all right yeah will you
if i give you a little treat later will you will you cut this out i can't make you
spaghetti spaghetti takes like 40 minutes to make all right fine i'll give you spaghetti
i'll wake you up when it's done fucking spaghetti i have to make spaghetti for this
little wonderful boy but thank you frody and weapon i've got one of three related information
that you did not say those things thank you for the ten dollars thank you p337r for the
three dollars hey j e r m a nine eight five remember when we used to not spell out each
other's names i do remember i try to remember remembers a really hard word for me i don't know
why remember sometimes i just go remember remember thank you so much peter for the three bucks
thank you apex apex you were for the one dollar i'm gonna borrow your pond real quick
and send them back holding a hoe for such a lame unoriginal fetish pond what i don't
understand who is that who's the cheetos in the chat right now what is that what emote is that
but thank you apex thank you mandum for the two dollars mandum requiem we had a fifty dollars
five zero zero zero five thousand bits from a wild meryl thank you so much for your 50 bucks
i'll put that to good use thank you timmy tim tan thanks for the one dollar
they just say h that's it dork cube thanks for the one dollar all praise poop but the true
arisen thank you for giving us this great character jeremy i can't wait to see him duke
it out with all your other great creations in the next jerma rumble well and then right after
that for ten dollars is poop but true arisen is the name of the that's the name of the
person in the chat have i done something to anger you that you would lie to these people
about my inception no you may not have created me in the traditional sense but rather you willed me
into existence i am the embodiment of the type of arisen you wish you could be and for bringing
me into this world i say thanks dad capo thank you poop but true arisen for the ten dollars
it was an honor not making you but putting you in my party because i got peer pressured
into pressing the button thank you hey grill master thanks for the one dollar grill master pro tip
of the day grilling meatloaf can be tricky due to its consistency try adding a coating of fondant
to the loaf before placing it on the grill it'll toughen up the meat and make it much
easier to grill thank you grill grill master bbqx grill master bbqx hey have gun thanks you
for the one dollar hey germ i'm really enjoying the stream since everyone is making anime
recommendations i suggest guns x sword a sci-fi spaghetti western with a good english dub here's
the opening in its least spoilery version i think you would enjoy it who's making
recommendations well this person right now god i fucking hate grill master x bbq i look
all right that's nothing to do with this latest bit uh but thank you for the ref
thank you for the reference uh hopefully when i you know when the application will maybe give
you a call and just tell them what i've done and things that you did that you did you did
i really appreciate the reference thank you uh lentils thanks for the one dollar
when are you going to play more games like katamari i really enjoyed that stream
joined the stream late today but it looked fun there are a lot of katamari games maybe one day
we could go and play the next one in suggestion or succession it's letters with a c multiple
c's and s's or multiple r's and e's and m's that's when i have the most problems succession
succession just my brain is going too fast slow down are there any games that are like
katamari katamari there's four or five of them oh yeah it's a great game hey tingy thanks
the one dollar no thank you snow soup for you for the one dollar thank you tingy for the one dollar
thank you jules for the one dollar germa i see you wear some superhero shirts so i got to ask
who's your favorite super person nightwing aquaman green goblin ah favorite superhero
that is a very hard question uh general grievous no no no no no no no no no no
not ben 10 he doesn't ben 10 doesn't count i really hate to be like a bandwagon shithead here
i hate it but i hate to say this everyone's gonna be like of course you're gonna say that
because the last move thanos i know i know it's like okay yeah bro you like that because
of the last movie that came out probably thanos is a villain well they said they said who is
your favorite super person nightwing aquaman green goblin they put a villain in the question
i think i think thanos is a great character now we talk about on the good side not just a
villain thanos is actually pretty good in infinity war movie thanos or comic thanos i
mean yeah there are differences and i know the whole story i know thanos's entire story
but for every time i bring up something that somebody hasn't seen yet i get screamed after
spoilers you have no idea what comic thanos is oh well i'll block your ears for a second everybody
if you don't want to hear anything the whole uh three two one i don't know what i think i think
about thanos except the fact that his entire life is about trying to please and uh fall
in love with the actual embodiment of death and that's why he does the things that he does
because he's trying to impress death pretty interesting take on the comic book version of
the thanos he read the wikipedia i read the comic book i have it i own it okay you can listen now
show it on stream you want to show it on stream fine let no way actually that didn't
i got lost in the mail during the move i gave it to my uh my nephew yeah you didn't even
know that it got lost and then you gave it to your nephew huh no no no he's trying to
make the embodiment of death and that's why he does the things that he does
he travels from planet to planet and look guy that has one talking point repeat the same
talking point but change the sentence a little bit good job you read his tldr wiki all right
what do you know about him huh what do you know about him if you're such an expert let's
hear it oh yeah you remember hey block your ears everybody block your ears if you don't want
to hear any thanos spoilers three two one the fact that the fight with wolverine the fight with
deadpool the fact that deadpool is the only one that could even hurt him in the first place
because he didn't really lose the fight against deadpool deadpool just was annoying because he
wouldn't die so thanos just got bored and it turned out to be a victory for deadpool
you remember that you read that one i just made that up that means that i have more
knowledge of the superhero universe than gondor lane does i will take the victory thank you very
much leveled up to a level one million you have the wiki i don't have the wiki open
frantically browsing on his phone am i really i'm browsing on my phone i don't even know what
my phone is anyways let's let's finish the bits i just know i do thanos it's thanos favorite
superhero i don't know doctor fucking strange or spider-man or venom no i let's go back sorry
it's not thanos no what the fuck am i talking about it's not venom either it's carnage carnage
is my favorite super hero or villain i love carnage is a great character it's carnage what
do you know about carnage separation anxiety storyline the it's one of my favorite actual like
no jokes aside not kidding or anything the separation anxiety story arc with spider-man
venom and carnage is one is my favorite marvel storyline and i would love if they would actually
do it eventually what about ant-man though no fuck ant-man they took honey i shrunk the kids
and made paul rudd say some jokes it's like they tell honey i shrunk the kids but they
give the kids superpowers i've already seen that movie i'm i'm kidding i'm kidding that's
a joke that was an expert ant-man analysis i'm just i'm just pushing buttons right now
don't you understand i almost just pushed the camera on button as a joke like i'm pressing
buttons and i don't have clothes on so that would have been bad he likes to start shit i'm
just kidding around but venom is one of my favorite carnages i just like the symbiotes
they're interesting something about them are cool is the spider-man symbiote was really
interesting the fact that he could have used it and he did but he didn't want to i like
that whole arc the whole arc with venom and carnage is really interesting to me
because they're not just two there are a shitload of symbiotes there are like at least four or five
suits because there's a whole race of aliens didn't need the wikipedia open for that one did i
how did this even start oh yeah that's my favorite villain thank you tingy for the
one dollar thank you divas p for the one dollar thank you bet three for the two dollars
hi jerma hi bet three i have not seen into the spider-verse i've heard it is unbelievable
so can't wait they're not a race of aliens the earth suits all split from venom there's a whole
alien race of those symbiotes just because they were children of venom because he ate after
midnight doesn't mean there's not a whole planet full of them thank you tingy for the
two dollars thank you give us p for another two dollars why are you doing this i don't know
why are you doing this thank you kill code for the one dollar hey germa old clip time
hope you enjoy don't dodge here that's the one thing i remember about blight town
do not dodge ever don't ever do it you will regret it i know a lot of people think
that some of this shit is on purpose like i'm trying to bait reactions or something or i'm
doing it to try to play up something no that i i don't i don't mean to that didn't happen
sometimes of course i do some of these things on purpose but you all know when that is because we
talk about them in real time or there's a joke that's being made but stuff like that i that
that that happens what was the last time that that happened and i went on like an actual
meltdown about how people were going to think this was a joke and a lie and i was like
pretending it was pretty recent it was like a couple of streams ago what was it the slap
yep the slap that's exactly that's yep but how could i i read a thread and somebody wrote he
literally did the most impossible physically mechanically impossible way to slap yourself
it has to been fake it was something along those lines i read it and i'm just like
uh i almost wish it was on purpose because then at least internally it wouldn't be that
embarrassing i've never seen anyone do that yeah i just got too amped up but i got too into like
the joke and i overestimated how far i had to go and i had to preview of all the things
to turn the webcam on and do hitting yourself in the fucking face i still can't believe it
fake slap it's fake oh and spilling and running into the uh uh buckets of water
in viscera cleanup detail none of those were fucking fake they were all real all of them
jerma i refuse to believe it's real i tried to replicate what you did and every time my hand
refused to slap my face but i i don't i was trying look here's the thought process here
i'm gonna try to explain this as best as i can i did it twice what three times right
the first time i was moving very slow and it wasn't that funny because it wasn't fast
so oh look i'm trying to pretend oh i missed you and i three stooges but in my mind it wasn't
as funny because my hand wasn't moving that fast so future me decided i'm gonna move my hand
really fucking fast so when i have the slap noise play it'll be it'll be perfect and it'll
actually look funny i'm trying really hard to replicate it and i can't don't don't try to
replicate don't try to slap yourself in the face no don't do that don't try this at home
hey sweat night thanks for the ten dollar sweat night hey jerma glad to see you're enjoying
dragon's dogma so much as is one of my favorite rpg games despite all of its flaws
if you want another great game by the same director i would strongly recommend devil may
cry three like dark souls it often gets a bad rap for being extremely hard but once you
get into it you'll see that it's a great game with some of the funnest combat and cut scenes
in video game history not that difficult not that difficulty should be a problem for you
you god gamer and then the new devil may cry is coming out there's so many video games
eventually there's going to be video game libraries because that's what happened with
books think about that too many books were written so they had to start to make giant
buildings to put them in places back when they were like 40 books that were written
that didn't matter now we got entire gigantic structures to hold the shit load of books that
have been written that's going to happen they're going to be video game libraries
it's called the internet yeah but it'll be you can there'll be a card catalog you go
through g g god of god of war goddess god of war one god of war two god of war three god of
war five god of war attack of the clones god of war and then in brackets 2018 god like there's
gonna be 30 god of wars there gears of war gears of war two gears of war three gears of real
mobile gears of war four gears of war five gears of four six you think they're gonna stop
making call of duties they'll be in an entire military section of this library
that in that catalog will be 250 call of duty slots it's so weird to think about that
because it's a joke now right that's a joke now oh they make a call of duty every fucking year
they're not gonna stop doing that for a very long time think of how many there are now and
think of how many there will be in a hundred years what the hell is gonna happen there this
is like your olympics prediction right see you all in five years yeah i got a lot of shit for
that don't make me bring up the olympics video the video games at olympics video
i was laughed out of town when i made that video i was all the top comments it was just like this
is the dumbest thing i think you've ever said why the hell would this ever happen like okay
you're really reaching for content here and it's just like oh well what do you know
lickety split here we are you're a smug i will be smug on that one because i remember
being really sad and being like what but that's it could happen this will never happen you
idiot but i'll be smug as i want but that one the video has five and a half thousand upvotes
and only 100 downvotes yeah because i already talked about it on stream and a bunch of people
went and made sure that they you know changed their history there and then you know i said
that comment about how he was like a dumb asshole i gotta go back and like upvote the
video and really like edit that comment hey man like that's kind of yeah i thought about
this too i thought that that was like a good idea too when i thought about it like uh like
a few years ago german 95 you're boring activate smart click map so we have something to do
all right we'll see hey we'll see in about five years when you think about that what you just
wrote right there and then you're gonna go back and be like oh i probably shouldn't have
said that anyways thank you sweat night devil may cry seems like a really awesome series i've
never played one second of any of the games i'm sure you'll see it on stream eventually
mostly lost thanks for the one dollar our character without facial here is just trevor
lawrence i don't i mean that i that i don't think so i oh that's a very very very
it's not no i come on they have like similar hair
i don't i don't see it that way it is i don't see that maybe trevor lawrence's
weird fucked up grandfather or something hey thank you demonic cucumber for the one dollar
thanos short comment comic thanos annual happy birthday from thanos it's just an older version
of him no it's not no it's not no it's not thank you for the comic book i'll add that to
the wikipedia page that was open the whole time it was open the whole time it was open
the whole time but i got you guys good we already knew well one of you did but thanos
is actually no joke at probably one of my favorite current villains or superheroes for all that that
matter uh thank you granco for the five dollars i missed the stream but there here are some bits
anyways if i watch the vod later and it's bad you will hear from my lawyer's sir don't get
any lawyers it ain't worth it hey graveyard ghoul thanks for the five dollars hey germa
you're very cool thank you graveyard ghoul appreciate the five dollars and that's a very
nice thing to say to somebody thank you clueless sniper thanks for the one dollar please give these
bits to shito i will thank you clueless sniper for the one dollar shito will enjoy them hey
tingy thanks for the two dollars here i wanted to see how long it would take you to notice
me doing that right went from one dollar per stream to this today because it was taking
too long by the way it took six dollars for you to catch it but what was it for me to
i was just reading your message i knew what you were doing but i just i just was i knew what
you were doing i have stream labs it has a who sent the bits it's not like i could couldn't
tell who sent them what fingers are your favorite least favorite uh index and thumb no middle
finger and thumb are my favorite fingers i hate ring finger it sucks it's stupid they're
always in a weird spot it's hard to move them around it's hard to maneuver them they
hurt sometimes trying to do certain tasks hey demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar
i've always wondered do you actually read comics if so what's your poll list if you
don't i'd recommend the current venom and carnage runs also venom which is venom but
set in the vietnam war that's really interesting uh i mean i i have in the past but all the
jokes aside i don't currently read any i think the last actual comic book that i opened
was probably civil war that's probably the last one that i opened and looked at and was like i'm
gonna read this see his clicks i hear them but my hands are on my desk folded like a fucking villain
do i use old school obs i do i use uh obs studio i don't use the stream labs one you
complained a lot about wwe 2k 17 18 19 why not the next rumble go back to 2k 14 uh i've
talked about a couple of the reasons why the number one reason is because it just takes
too long to load once you have 20 30 40 characters made in 2k 14 and once you have
10 20 plus layers on one character it can take 30 to 40 seconds to load hair on somebody
it's just it doesn't hold up if they was a 2k 14 for pc they decided in 2k 15 forward
to put them on pc but that's the last one that's the last really good creator it just
doesn't hold up old playstation 3 hardware late generation playstation 3 game trying to just
dump as much shit as they can so it just takes too long to make one character especially if you
want to do a lot of stuff to them the creativity was nice i know and they got rid
of the whole cinematic stuff where you could make your own little stories and have weird
shit happen with characters it really is too bad but they it's too bad they made that a
sports simulation game oh well you should be able to emulate it emulating playstation 3 games is
just so finicky half of them don't even work it's really hard to do some of the emulators
are better than others but i've had so many problems trying to get past the playstation
1 era emulators to work even remotely correctly we're not far enough into technology i think to
be able to truly emulate like last gen games it's just i don't think it's there yet and it
might not ever be because it's really easy to emulate the data that was on a cartridge
stuff like super nintendo genesis n64 they're all very emulatable even playstation 1 and into
playstation 2 somewhat shanesaw five community subs thank you shanesaw thank you so much
five community subs rpcs3 has a lot of stuff working well at the moment give it another year
and i bet it's amazing i hope so because if i could use my you know powerful computer to render
shit that's in a playstation 3 emulated version of 2k14 i would do it in a heartbeat
but it just doesn't work right now but thank you so much shanes uh shanesaw
getting close to almost at the end of the bits only a few more left
thank you to uh demonic cucumber for the one dollar spill joke
shanesaw is still going is that was that delayed from earlier no
shanesaw is gifting five no that's okay there they just showed up just got delayed for some
reason weird but thank you so much uh demonic cucumber says spill joke and then they link a
link is a bucket dear god there's more no that was a great short hey george maca thanks
for the one dollar four days left germa can i have your intellectual shares of clown in the
town when you're gone just joshan loved you since the gta4 vids was stir you're the best
thank you so much george and thank you kairatobi oh and great great canadian just kind of comes
out of nowhere with five more kairatobi five great canadian fuck club five community subs each
thank you guys am i going to stream resident evil 2 absolutely i'll probably do it within
a day or so of it launching thanks to the both of you and finally here we got fitty for two dollars
fitty thanks for the dollar hey fitty thanks for the 100 bits thank you fitty for the one dollar
thank you fitty for the one dollar and then one dollar again two dollars thank you yeah
thank you fitty for the one dollar yeah i'll just order a pizza wait what the hell germa's
reading through my live thoughts on stream oh god please stop those two hurt my brain to read
what is this delay i don't know maybe it's uh i don't know that's really weird i jumped with
the message up because yeah because i read them both kind of at the same time hey talking about
subs a shitload of community subs are coming tonight why don't we take a look and see the
people that subscribed or were given a sub germa's gonna keep saying your name as fuck
club the great canadian fk club well what is it it's frick club great canadian frick club
what that is not what it is my mom is listening germa what the frick what if i just say great
canadian club but dragon's dog was a lot of fun i'm not sure the plan tomorrow because there
are so many options that it's i almost don't know what i'm gonna do it really depends on
what because there are some things that are planned on coming in for delivery tomorrow
you can also just play this too dark souls 3 the mods look like a lot of fun one of them in
particular i thought was really funny is there's a mod for dark souls 3 that randomizes the speed
of the game so it can go in slow motion up to like fast forward speed that sounds like actual
help yeah sounds like fun though there's one where you can play as the enemies too that's
probably good i i have to check them out that's going to be at least a couple streams it has to
be so basically you got multiple options yeah please do that tomorrow if i can get it to
work that's going to take a little bit of work though because with any mod or total
complete scripting or game changing mods there's a tendency for them to take a
lot of troubleshooting so i'm gonna have to spend some time tomorrow hopefully doing that
what's gonna be the january 23rd stream january 23rd stream is gonna be an irl hangout stream
where i wear a full goalie outfit and like duct tape my door closed that stream is only
gonna be like an hour no not because no no not because i'm gonna no no no no no no no
i will stream january 23rd until 1201 but i don't think i'm gonna start that stream
at like 4 pm that's gonna be like a late night stream so i'm gonna start that stream
at some point in like the late afternoon and then we're gonna just kind of hang out in
final destination my room it said that it said it oh shit bro okay all right never
mind so it's 7 23 pm eastern or pacific was that what time zone was that it was eastern
okay so that means that at 323 pm okay so i will start that stream at three o'clock
or 230 and we're gonna hang out i was gonna get like bug spray and like spray it around
but i don't know if i want to make my room smell like that but anyways that's gonna be
it thank you everybody for your insane amount of support as always see you tomorrow he's
gonna inhale the bug spray and that no all right i'm gonna just duct tape my door
seven six five yeah actually it would be four it'd be 4 23 so i'll start that stream at like
334 with my like goalie outfit on being naked it'll be safer no i need like pads
what if like the roof falls down i'll be in like full hockey gear and i will not be affected
all right i'll see you guys tomorrow have a great night thanks for watching
hopefully we see you soon take care ta ta for now