Hey, what's going on guys? Jerma here. Mmm, with some SCP 087b. Kind of a mouthful, I know.
But this is kind of an offshoot or a spin-off of the first SCP game I played a couple weeks ago.
And it was heavily heavily requested. A lot of you guys, when you saw that I did 087, you said,
Do 087b. It's much more scary, much more ridiculous. So I said okay. I also did Containment Breach.
So I think this wraps up all the SCP games. Maybe I'll play them again, but I think this should wrap it up in regards to SCP games.
I might be totally wrong. If there are more, let me know. I will absolutely play them.
But let's get this going here. SCP 087b. Sort of along the lines of the first one where it was a staircase simulator.
But this one has hallways too, I guess. And brick hallways that were created by the Romans. That's not true.
But this is trying to find ways to make myself happier right now because I'm about to be very scared.
Floor 2. What the hell was that? Already? Are you serious? No way. Already there's going to be something like that?
There were eyes just peering at me. I don't even want to go down here. There were two eyes just looking right at me.
I don't want to go down this hallway. Whatever. He's not there anymore. He went to go eat breakfast. Floor 3.
Oh, they're already going to throw stuff like that at me. What? Oh, okay. Wait, hold on. Is this like a maze or something? I can't even see.
No? Okay. I know. Stop doing that. Every time I see that, like, pair of eyes. Five.
Roger that. Six. Goddamn.
I wonder how many octaves I can make. What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? I'm blocked off?
What is that? Why is it like a peephole right here? I don't understand. Maybe the guy was like peeping on me or something. That's weird.
It's very weird. Very weird. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
That was a fail. Should I turn around? I don't know if I should turn around. He's going to come get me.
Maybe this is what this is for. To, like, see him coming to get you. I can't even turn around. You have to face your fears, right?
Is he, like, coming? I wish I could, like, peer through and see. I just want to be your friend. I just want to be your friend.
I think he's gone. I think I escaped that dude. He, like, spit on me or something. I got, like, an acid brain.
I was like, eeeh. That's going to happen again, and I'm not going to escape next time. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Hello. Hi.
There's another one. Okay. Last time there was one of these, like, peeping little holes, that dude showed up.
Let's see if it happens again. There he is. There he is. Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Oh, my God.
Still alive. I don't know how much longer I can do this for. Okay. What's that? What's going on? What is going on? What is going on? What is going on? What is going on? What is going on?
What's going on? What is making that noise? What is making that noise? What is that? What is that thing? Is that, like, a- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. The question is, do I run? I don't know where to go. Should I turn around and just run? Screw it. Come at me, bro! Come at me, bro!