I just get so tired on these long road trips. Man, I need a coffee or something.
What's with all these people with their lights? Learn how to fucking drive. I mean, seriously.
Look, downtown cab company. Will you leave me alone? Like, can I just like block downtown cab company?
Because they just, well, we got a random event. Robbery. Robbery in progress.
Can I seriously just say, I kill the person getting robbed in these random events more often than not.
Like, this happens all the time.
To clarify, that was a joke about a bus driver installing off-road capabilities to his school bus.
And delivering some unruly children to their school in a very unorthodox fashion.
Back to the show.
See, I don't know why mummy doesn't want me to play in the street. It's fun. Look.
So here's a challenge for you guys that have GTA V and are looking for something difficult to do.
Hop on a dirt bike like this, get on the highest mountain, and drive down in cinematic mode.
If you can make it to the bottom, you won. Because it's like impossible.
Oh, is that like two seconds?
This reminds me of those commercials. Like, everybody knows those commercials.
But like the truck that's sitting on the mountain for no reason.
How do they get the truck up there? Like, well, how did I get the truck up here is the real question.
I drove it. But they don't drive it up the mountain.
They bring a crane and they drop the truck on the mountain with the crane and like a helicopter or something.
I don't know how they do it. OK, I have no idea.
And they might drive it up the fucking mountain, but I really don't know that.
So let's test my hypothesis right now. Let's drive down the mountain.
Let's take our new Ford Tundra 2013 and take it down the goddamn mountain like they would expect you to do if you had one of these cars.
And another thing, let's talk about advertising in general.
I'm getting sick and tired of these advertisers. Holy shit.
OK, so we made it. Sorry, Ford.
I apologize because you can see this like works. Sorry.
Honey, this is just an absolutely breathtaking view of San Andreas.
Oh, it's so beautiful. I can't wait to send this to my cat.