Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with the new scout weapon the backscatter or the spy scout backstab gun
Also going to be using in this video the cloak device for the scout and the jumpy jump melee
So if you put all these together you kind of just turn into a spy and here you go
If there is ever a place where this
Should shine it's probably right here
Once they push the card up a little bit to like right about here
Is when I could be able to come in and get at least a couple of backstabs just like a spy
Well, you know what? We'll get this guy too because we can you know, why not but i'm gonna burn here
Where do I know so i'm not worth it. I'm committed to this
I'm not going anywhere and I don't want to drink the bonk. I will take the burn damage
Because it's important that they get on this card right now like right now. Okay, here we go. Here we go
This no, you know, you don't don't kill him leave him alone
This is this is where we slowly just go like this and just kill this guy
Okay, good good good good backstab good job i'll get out no don't get out bring this guy no
You ruined my plan. My plan was to
All right, everybody we're getting up on this guy. Nice job. Okay, we're back to square one. I'm not spotted yet
This pyro is looking for spies. So he's looking for me
Not turning your back now, are you?
Oh
I probably would have got that kill anyways if I had just shot him with the regular scatter gun
Hey
You're under arrest for backstabbing my friend. Okay, I need the health and
Back to square one use the jumpy jump. Make sure nobody sees you good good
Now we
We wait
Oh, i've been spotted. Oh, i've been spotted but he can't get up here unless he goes all the way around
He's gonna go all the way around and he's gonna die
Hey
Get out of here. This guy's trying to come up. I've gone gone. See he doesn't even know i'm there. I made it out alive
Here's my new spot. Here's my new spot waiting for this heavy. There he is. Got him. Got him. All right. Watch out soldier
Watch out. Watch out
Uh boy
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Where is he? I'm trying to up
Oh
That's the rule. That's the rule
And he died
No
No, don't ruin this
Me and the scout. No shit
No
Dude, he can't hit me over here. I got it my charge. Come on. Come on my drink
God damn it. The drink needs to charge right now charge it up. Come on
God damn it
You are not me and you are gonna get back stabbed and so is this guy?
Okay, that's two the one thing I will say when you use the bonk nobody ever like pays attention to you
Nobody ever like wants to know if you're still around
It's crazy, right? Like I feel like I am a spy scout
Because of the bonk
Check this out. See he knows I exist
He's gonna forget I ever existed. All I have to do is come back here. I'm using my dead ringer right now
I just use the dead ringer. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What is why a pyro is just appearing in front of me
Seriously, like what the hell was that?
Two pyros just oh jeez louise
Oh, jeez
Come on. Let me get this guy. Come on
Well, I made it behind everybody can I
Be sneaky enough where I can get somebody from behind, you know the best place
You know what screw your teleporter you guys are gonna have to walk now
You're gonna have to walk and once you start walking and that's when you're gonna get back stabbed by the spy scouts. Bye
Oh, fuck push it push it
God, come on. Let me get that one hit on them. Let me
All right
Hey for those of you that remember who remembers those old soldier paratrooper toys the things with like the crappy parachutes on their backs
If you threw them in the air half the time they would do what he just did
The soldier just turned into one of those right there. That was insane. All right. Well anyways
Am I gonna be able to do anything up here or is this guy coming for me? You're gonna come for me?
Oh, yeah, nice try
I'll backstab your pyro friend
And then guess what i'm gonna backstab your soldier friend, too
But I won't get the kill
But I won't get the killer. Oh will I no i'm getting this kill i'll fly behind you
Anybody else up here? What the hell did you just kill? What did that guy just shoot?
Dude, the new the new demo night terrifies the absolute shit out of me. It really does
Can we be frank for a second? This new demo night is is fucking terrifying
Everything about this demo night is is awfully hard. I'm just like talking now and not even paying attention to the fucking game
Hey pal, you're dead
Oh, there's multiple multiple ones of you
There are more than one of you
They're everywhere. They're fucking everywhere
dude
All right. Can we just can we just go over how far I just flew right there?
I'm okay with that one
You want to talk about a stair stab? That was like a mountain stab. That was a mountain jump stab
Watch out for the demo nights got our demo nights versus their demo nights
It's just a demo night party. That's what it is. We're gonna go this way
Don't need to drink yet
Now I do
I'll see you later
I don't want anything to do with you
I just want to get behind your entire team. Is that so much to ask?
I can see the shadows. I can see where you are. Holy shit. Are you kidding me?
Where's this guy waiting for me? What's this guy doing? Well in that case
Okay
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude
Well, how long is this gonna last that's the question
Okay. Bye bye medic friend. You're blocking me you block
Two three four five. We got a lot of people here. Let's just go back around. I know you see me
I know you see me now. You see me now. You don't I told you I told you
Invisible and confirmed invisible
If that doesn't prove it, I don't know what does