Alright, big goofy submarine. The beetle. I don't really like the beetle. Probably gonna go with frogman.
Stand ball for turtle fall. Pilot, stand ball for turtle fall. Stand ball. Got ya. Stand ball.
Hey yo, what's up bro? Stand ball. Ooh, we got a titan fall. Stand ball. What was that, two kills? Free kills? I don't even know.
Alright, so Slippy, shut the fuck up and keep the line clear please. What the hell is this guy? He doesn't have anything over his head, he's just like a guy.
Okay. I guess he was an enemy. What? Stop doing that. You killed me.
Man, they spent a lot of time on this game. Trying to make everybody look like they're busy. And I'm a little busy taking out some grunts.
Too busy taking out. Ooh. Watch out. Stand ball. Ooh. That's how you stand tall for titan fall. Get on top of this building.
Where are my grenades? There they are. Get granaded. Watch this guys. Boom. Nope. Watch this guys. Boom. Boom.
We're now in the titan. Whoa. Today is such a tough day at work. We're up. Get the fuck out of here. I'm trying to make a joke.
Oh shit. My work has... You dare mess with my workabees? Yeah, now you're... I gotta eject. Eject. I don't even know what I did.
What the hell just happened? I just got thrown? Let's go. Come on Spectres, you gotta move this way. Just follow this guy.
Four of you just go. You brainless fucks. There we go. It's a titan fall. Let's go. Everybody stand ball. Come on. Get out of here.
Let's get our Spectres away. Come on Spectres. Yeah. Go. Get covered. Good job. Nice thinking.
Gang, I need two Spectres to make the front of the... You just shot one of our workers. Nice job.
Oh, I hate the blue team. I hate you all. I've never liked anybody on blue team. Especially you.
Hey, you know, I really like your hair color. Did you dye your hair? You look really nice today. Oh, you know, I hate red team. Red team sucks.
Right now we're gonna go on a streak. I am not happy right now. I am not fucking happy. I don't even want my titan. I want my titan to follow me around like that movie.
Little Big Planet. Whatever it was. What was that movie when the kid had a giant? My iron giant? Iron giant. Yeah, that's what it was.
This is me. I'm Timmy, the little Tim guy, and this is the iron giant. So let's go.
Kevin Garnett on the Boston Celtics. Going for a slam dunk. Don't even know if Kevin Garnett's on the Celtics anymore, but we're gonna get a slam dunk.
Yes. Slam dunk. He even broke the backboard with that. Did you see the backboard shatter when Shaq did the slam? Who did I say Kevin Garnett? I didn't say Shaq.
Oh, whatever. Whoever basketball player did that. That was really awesome.
What's your favorite thing? Star? Special guest, special guest star in the video. What is your favorite aspect of Teen Titanfall?
Beast Boy and Raven. Yeah, those are two good characters. You know what my favorite part about Scream, Scry, and Scrawl is? What?
It's gotta be the maps. They are, whew, you know what I mean? Like, whew, whew. That's like sweat coming down off the brow, you know?
How did you get up there? Get down here this instant. You're in big trouble. You're not supposed to play on the giant skull. Wait till your father hears about this.
What is he shooting at? There's nothing even down there. He's just being a shit bum auto titan. Like, get down here, please.
Actually, he did just get somebody. Walk backwards into this. Walk into it. Stand tall. Let's do this. Get away from him. Get away. He's gonna blow up. He's gonna blow up.
Another titan. Take the missile barrage. Oh, that's not a good idea. Oh, that's not a good idea for you. Let's get, get, oh, there's a fucking guy on me. There's a guy on me.
Get off me. Let's get back to work. Is this thing doomed? Oh shit, it is doomed. Get out. Get out. Get out. You're gonna land on top of him.
Come here, you fucker. Now you are doomed. I see you. You think you can stay invisible? Come here.
Shit in my face. And that, ladies and gentlemen, is how you stand tall for Turtle Crawl.