Hello everybody, welcome to the Christmas Eve stream.
I am ready to rock and roll.
Oh, what's up? What's up? What's up?
Good to see everybody again.
Uh, I don't... Alright, I turned on the stream I think already.
Now I'm Ken Haido. Welcome, welcome. How are you? Welcome to the stream. Good to see you.
Merry Christmas. It actually might be Christmas.
In some parts of the world right now. Very possible.
What time is it? 4.30?
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11. It is almost Christmas.
In EU?
Hey man, keep it down. I'm trying to sleep.
Wake up! It is! Oh, it's Christmas right now. Alright.
Yeah!
How was your peppermint mocha? Okay, let me... I have to explain.
And I'm still suffering right now, by the way.
So...
Uh...
I was in the Christmas spirit.
I was very, very excited for the holiday.
So, I... You know, you get flavor for a coffee. You get like one of those creamers.
And I got peppermint mocha flavored creamer.
Like, oh, this is fucking Christmas time. Let's go.
So, I mean...
I drank like three of them. Three coffees with it, in it.
And, uh... It was delicious, by the way.
Then I had to go to the bathroom.
And I'll be very, very honest with you.
I had to go to the bathroom again.
What?
We hold it for the stream because it's Christmas Eve.
And I... I'm holding it for Santa.
It's one of those things that comes in waves.
For those of you that understand and can get my drift.
I'm fine. I'm kidding. Oh, my God.
By the way, I have no idea what I look like.
Um...
This is gonna be a surprise to all of us, I think.
This is gonna be a shocker to all of us.
I'm just gonna look at the preview and see what I look like.
Ah, it's a blistery day here.
Father Christmas?
Look at how fucking much older I look.
And look at how wet my hair is still.
I haven't shaved.
Look at how, like, I look like it... Okay.
You'd probably think I got hacked if you saw the thumbnail, right?
If you saw this thumbnail,
it's like, who's this guy on Jerma's channel?
And why is the channel hacked?
It's my secret identity.
Yeah, this is like this bullshit disguise that...
Oh, yeah. I'm Superman, by the way.
I just put on glasses, put my hair back, and have a mustache.
God, I should just fucking leave halfway through the stream
and play a video of, like, a bus getting rescued or something.
Hold on to that one.
Imagine I'm just sitting here just playing normally.
I'm just like, oh, wow, look out.
Oh, nice, headshot.
And then be like, headshot.
Hey, guys, I gotta take a quick shit.
It's diarrhea, so it's gonna be, like, probably half an hour.
And I gotta fucking get up.
And then I come back, and people link me a video that,
oh, my God, did you see what happened?
And it's like me without the glasses and a superhero outfit,
like, saving a bus full of children,
dressed up like a therapist.
I'm not gonna... This is loud, by the way.
I'm not gonna wear this.
This is just for you to take a screenshot,
because I can't put these on.
It just seems weird.
I feel like I have a VR headset on without the VR in front of me,
because there's no lenses in these.
You know how some people look, like, much better with glasses?
What's the reverse?
Please wear it? I don't think I can.
I've got that light back up here, too,
which is not gonna do me any favors.
It's a fucking wine mom.
And I've got two kinds of chapstick!
I really am fucking 40.
So, here's what we're gonna do.
I've almost got my cross-eyed.
Yeah, these are coming off. I'm not fucking wearing these.
Those are coming off.
So, I have a bunch of Itch.io games that I want to play.
Some of them are Christmas themes,
some of them are horror, some of them are fun,
some of them are weird,
and we're just gonna do a bunch of them.
I don't know how long I'm gonna be here.
I don't know how long this is gonna take.
No idea. All I know is that I've got my wine here.
I've got my...oh, I'm gonna turn this on.
Gonna get toasty in here, I guarantee it.
Oh, let me move this.
Ah, turn on. Turn on!
Turn on! There we go.
Okay. Hold on, let me move this.
Let me move that.
Move this. Let me move that.
Move this.
I've got, like, an empty coffee mug here I want to get rid of as well.
All right.
I think I'm ready.
You just turned off the PC.
Hey, you know, hold on. I think I have to...
I think I have to be right back for a minute.
Yeah. Yeah, I think I got...
Yeah, I gotta BRB for just a second, guys.
Yeah, BRB.
Just one second. Just a minute or two.
Hahahaha! Merry Christmas!
Did you get one? Did you get your present?
I'm trying to make it around the clock.
I'm trying to get there.
There it is. I told you we were going to get one for winter
and one for Christmas.
Just in time for the holiday.
Got one of our new BRB screens
and I love it.
We're going to use this for, like, at least a week or two.
I don't even care if it's Christmas is over.
Do you see the characters in the background?
Can you count? Is that Grandpa? That is Grandpa down there.
Yeah, Blordow made this.
Got it done.
And out and ready.
We're just in time here.
So that's going to be the BRB screen
that you will see from now on
for the next week or two.
And now, we can actually start the stream.
I wanted to show that, though. I thought it was really cool.
Now, don't mind, like, the scary music
that's here now.
We're playing a scary game. It's called Santa's Cookies.
It's the first of the Ichio Night.
And I think we can begin.
I think we can begin.
That's a pretty good...
What year is it? What year is this?
Uh, last week.
2022.
Whatever it is.
It's a vintage!
I got it a week ago!
Evil hair. I look evil today. Are you ready?
Oh, but we want you to play horror games.
All right, well, the only time I'm going to play horror games right now
is if a lot of community subs are coming in, too.
Holy shit, thank you, everybody.
That's way too much.
Don't give me... Stop giving me money.
I demand it. That's 100 community subs from Zixia.
Merry Christmas. Stop giving me money.
Don't give me any more. I'm going to be very upset with you.
I'm going to be very upset with you.
Don't give me any more money. I'll be very upset with you.
Is this thing in the right spot?
What's it look like without this? I don't know.
All right, here we go.
Are you guys ready to rock and roll for the Christmas Eve extravaganza Ichio extravaganza Wine Mom Night?
Let me drop this.
Should I do two headphones for this?
I think my face cam's too big.
Yeah, I was right.
Uh, Zixia, that's insane. 100 community subs.
So many community subs are coming in.
Don't give me any more money. Thank you.
But that's a huge amount. 20 from Animos.
40 from Animos.
Let's fucking go. Santa's Cookies.
Ready to rock and roll.
Turn it up. The game crashed.
Shit. That's my fault.
That's my fault. I fucked it up.
I'm ready for this one, though. I fucked it up. Hold on.
Try it again.
Okay. Santa's Cookies.
Here we go. Merry Christmas, everybody.
Oh!
That's right. Voting for New Year's Eve.
Die!
Wait, what was he?
Get me! I didn't do anything.
What happened?
Um, voting for New Year's Eve.
I was...
Dude, the OBS preview is over here
and I got jumpscared from it.
Um, okay.
New Year's Eve stuff.
The poll, the vote,
is almost ready.
It's gonna take a little bit longer.
I'm hoping
that after this stream is over,
later tonight, you will see on my Twitter,
boom, Survey Monkey. There it is.
If it's not there tonight,
and that'll be an early Christmas present
for you tomorrow morning.
So, it's going to be there within the next
12 hours. Guaranteed.
People still giving a ton of money?
Alright.
Stop giving me money. I'm serious.
Stop giving me money. Please stop giving me money.
Don't give me any more money.
I'm addressing you directly now.
Don't give me any more money. I don't want it.
Stop it. Alright. No, no, no.
I haven't drank this yet. Alright, let's go.
So, what happened?
So, I don't want to meet Santa.
Why do you open doors? What?
Who am I? Why am I this small?
Is he right outside?
What am I supposed to goal?
Okay. I don't see him.
What am I supposed to be doing?
Oh, I got milk.
Oh no, I don't have a glass. I think I have to fill this with milk.
Can I just put it in the sink?
It's your fucking mom and dad anyways. Who cares?
I'll just put it in the sink.
Can I hide in here?
Why did I get jumped on so quickly last time?
Where's our house?
Oh shit, there he is.
Where's his hat? Oh shit, close the door.
Where do I go? What should I do?
This is not even Santa. This is just dad walking around.
Where's his hat?
I'd wear.
Can I go under the bed? There's a sprint.
I don't see him down here. Oh, milk.
Residents, hold on. There's milk, milk, milk, milk.
Put it down.
Alright, I got the milk on the table. Oh my fucking god, there he is.
Where do I go? Where do I go?
He's going back up the stairs. I think I'm okay.
So I have to put the cookies up there too?
Oh, there's a cookie. Oh shit, I think I missed.
I hope Santa didn't have any
pep and mocha coffees this morning like me.
I think I'm alright.
I think I probably leave now.
It plays the music when he's there.
Where are the other cookies?
Relax, holy shit, dude. Are you kidding me?
This is not even scary.
Did I just fake that? No, I really didn't. I swear to god.
But that was way over- I haven't played scary games in a long time.
It's been a very long time.
That was way over-acting.
I gotta go back to acting school.
You guys think it's gonna be funny that in 10 years
when actors
don't even want to be actors anymore, they just want to be streamers?
There will be workshops
on how to react to
a jump scare.
I could teach that class. Alright, that was Santa's cookies.
It was pretty good.
We're gonna stay in this same realm
I think. We might as well
get them out of the way.
This one's called The Christmas Incident.
Find out.
Return of Scare Saturdays? Well, I mean, I just
feel like it'd be fun.
Christmas Incident. This one looks weird.
All these games were got on
ICHIO, by the way.
I think I'm gonna have to capture my monitor.
Alright, this is called The Christmas Incident.
I'm gonna turn this way fucking down.
Alright, 20 should be alright. Play.
Turn it up. Have you met Santa?
Okay, we gotta-
Can I get the sensitivity menu back?
This is way too low.
Every game has
wicked shit sensitivity, though.
Hold on, I gotta fix this. This is not gonna happen
the way that it is right now. Looking for a game
to capture. Well, there isn't one, so just wait.
Fucking didn't even
do the sensitivity, goddammit!
Every game that's ever released
ever, always
have the mouse sensitivity
you have to do 0
to 10 or nothing at all.
Like, anything over 10 is
unusable. I'll get it this time.
Call it. I'm gonna keep it at
50. Christmas- The Christmas
Miracle. That's better. Alright.
Can we give like an actual clap to this
dev, whoever you are?
You are better than every single AAA
studio that makes mouse
sensitivity awful. Alright, so let's go.
This is kinda creepy. Both
headphones in, I know I'm cheating. Have you
met Santa? Yeah, I've met him.
Maybe once or twice.
Pick up the flashlight. Okay.
There's no FOV slider.
What the hell is going on? You hear that?
It's creepy. Okay, I got a
game coming up that I'm really not looking forward to playing.
There's a game that I'm gonna play
in a little bit that is
considered one of the scariest, most
unbearable Itch.io experiences.
It's by that Puppet, um
Puppet combo?
It looks so
ugh. I'm not
fucking ready. It looks so horrible.
I don't know if I wanna do it.
But this low poly shit is way
scarier than like a hundred
zombies running at you in Resident Evil.
They gotta go back to this stuff. They really do.
It's just so unsettling. Enter house,
press E. Hold on.
It like looks like 3D movie maker, which makes it
worse. What am I looking for?
Just investigate? There are people talking.
Can you hear them? There are people eating
dinner. Where are the people?
What radio station just plays the
inside of a restaurant on a Thursday night?
I don't know. Okay.
BP. Can I turn the flashlight off?
Nothing in here. Oh, there is something in here.
There's a bloody knife. Now over here?
Wait. Yeah. This is where I came in.
Do I need to pick up any candy? Is this an elevator?
Why would you have it? Why is there an elevator?
Are you painting on the toilet? Oh, I thought that was
an easel. I was like
doing like a fucking piece of artwork while he
was taking a shit. Why is there
a mirror in here?
That's so weird. Can you
imagine just like squatting down here and
just like on your phone and just going
like this? That would be so
weird looking. What do you mean squatting?
How do you go to the bathroom?
What are you talking about? You squat down to take
a shit. How do you go to the bathroom? What are you talking about?
You stand on the toilet seat?
Sit. Yeah, squat, sit.
Like, you'd be
like, you know what I mean? Squat.
Take half a squat. What happened to my pop
stand? What the fuck is going on? You squat.
That looks fucking weird.
I'm not going to drink that way. Do I have
any backstory here? It's a horror
game, guys. Where's the notes that are
everywhere with like three pages of exposition?
Where's the open diary
with like fucking four pages of what happened
yesterday? This is what? You think this is a horror
game? Ooh, a big key.
I like this. I
love, I don't know. I think it's so cool
that over the last like ten years or so
that we've been able to have indie devs have been able
to just make whatever the fuck they want. It's really cool.
Is there a sprint? There is not a sprint.
I got a key though. Was there a locked door?
Oh shit. Oh,
there is a present waiting for you
under the Christmas tree. Is that Iron
Maiden? Why are they just like the
Olympic fucking rings? What?
What are these? There's a present waiting for you
under the tree. Alright, there's a person lying here.
Okay. I'm like unsettled right
now. Go get the present.
That's the wrong way. Oh shit. Okay, I thought
that was a hallway that went this way. It'd be so
funny to the killer. Like to the killer though.
Like you run that way
and you stop and you go, oops, sorry, nevermind.
What am I supposed to do?
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me,
me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
Mokaish! Tree's downstairs.
Isn't the tree over here?
Alright, he's not just hiding back there, right?
Go get your present under the tree.
He's gonna just grab me and scream in my face.
I know it. Where's my present?
You forgot to put your eyelashes on.
Oh, I forgot something.
Is he running? Stop making
the fucking noise. Where is he?
The front door? Is he upstairs?
This is different. Oh, no.
I'm gonna get lost. I'm gonna get lost in here. Does that sound startle the witch?
Oh, I don't like- I hate this shit so much.
Why do I- like, you know, can I tell you something?
I need to talk about this for a sec before I get scared.
What the fuck is wrong with humans?
The lengths we go to to entertain ourselves and like stimulate our brains.
What the hell am I doing here? Why are we doing this?
Humanity goes so far to desperately try to stimulate our brains to a point where we like pretend
we're locked in a murderer's house and there's blood everywhere and we're gonna get fucking killed.
Guys, even just the notion of the firework is enough to be like, what are we doing?
Oh, yeah, I mean, I got an idea. Let's just make explode stuff.
Like, just make huge explosions in front of everybody. Like, why? Why are we doing this? You're high already.
What happened? What the fuck was that? I didn't do that. Why did my light just do that?
Why did the lights just go out? I'm not- am I- look at my hands.
Why did the lights just turn off? Why did the lights just turn off?
That was scarier than the game. Is the house haunted?
Did somebody hack my computer and like hack my house and turn my lights off in my house?
I feel like that was somebody here. 32-bit holiday jam 2021. Good work. That was fun.
Special thanks to the Unity Asset Store. Good shit. That was fun. It's quick. It was fun. It was weird.
I like it. It was good. Christmas incident. I love the low poly. I think it's fantastic.
You look genuinely concerned. Bro, the lights just turned off in my room and I didn't fucking
click switch. That wasn't a routine. I didn't- that wasn't a bit I did.
Alright, let's keep going. Moving on. I think there's one more like this that I want to do.
We've got- okay, I gotta make sure I remember which ones we did. That was the Christmas incident.
We did Santa's cookies. The next one coming up is sleigh bells. Sleigh bells.
Hopefully it's not loud. Careful. Stop breaking my immersion OBS.
Another low poly one we got here. Sleigh bells. Why is everyone saying yes? Why am I wearing- what
did you say? Why are you wearing a 2013 turkey evil eye bath towel? That's so weirdly specific.
I have no idea what you're even talking about. It's a nice sweater. I think it looks good.
It's not an ugly Christmas sweater. This is a beautiful Christmas sweater.
And I've got the game. I've got the game on. Yes, sleigh. You did this. Merry Christmas everybody.
You know, it's been kind of a fucked up year or two. It's been kind of stressful for everybody,
I think. But, uh, let's hope we- we keep going. All we can do is move forward. And that's it. Okay.
I'm ready. Press any key. You got it. Click here to watch the making of this game. Sleigh bells.
Who made this game? By Blake McKinnon. Additional sound effects by Brianna McKinnon.
Move WASD, sprint to shift, attack. There's an attack. Left click, zoom, right click,
F, E, and Q. All right, let's go. Christmas Eve and I'm still taking my clothes off in this
horrible town for money. Sigh, I better deliver Billy's Christmas present before it gets too late.
I wonder if he even remembers what I look like. He hasn't seen me for months. Not since he went
to live with his father. Why'd they have to take him from me? I miss my little Billy. Okay. Toggle
your flashlight. I like the music. I'm gonna go this way. There's a stamina meter. You know when
you put lip balm on and then your skin starts peeling off on your lips? What's up with that?
Our objective. Deliver Billy's present. This is zoom. Okay. I thought they were just gonna
fucking crash. Oh, I was gonna get, I didn't get it because it was, the file was so huge
for like a two second joke. I was gonna hit gone home, but you're a car. It was making me laugh.
I like this. But imagine if I played that. Okay. Are you Billy? Where's Billy? Where's my house?
Who are these people? Oh, snowman. That's a pretty damn good snowman. I gotta tell you.
The hair in my wine. Okay. I almost drank it. I don't care. It doesn't matter. You guys know
you eat over an inch of dirt every single meal. You know that? You eat over an inch of dirt every
single meal. Weird. Every time you've ever eaten, you're always eating over an inch of dirt because
you're at least about a foot off the ground at the dinner table, aren't you? Use that joke at
Christmas. Your family will laugh. I guarantee it. You're always eating at least an inch over
of dirt, at least. You know what I mean? At least you eat over an inch of dirt means you at least
eat over the inch of dirt. Get it? You guys don't get it. Or bet somebody to bar a hundred dollars
at. You'll win. Oh, deliver. I think this is it. Okay. I'll just leave the present here. I doubt
they'll want to see me right now. I better get home or it gets too late. I don't want to be out
after midnight. You minus twoing that? I just made everybody here a hundred dollars. You're not gonna
minus two when somebody has to pay you a hundred dollars because you proved to them that you eat
over an inch of dirt every meal. People fucking money. Whatever. Fine. All right. Merry Christmas,
Billy. I better get home. Chat is pissed. They'll get over it. I've made worse jokes. If you're new
here, don't worry. In fact, eventually here over the next 12 hours or so, you'll be able to vote
for what your favorite worst joke was last year. You've been on my Twitter. Worst joke of the year
is a category. Do I have an objective on the map? Make your way home. Okay. Where do I live? Where
do I live? What if I don't know where I live? Subway. This is blocked off for some reason.
I wonder what's going on up here. I won't be getting home this way. I'll have to go through
the subway tunnel. It's not that much further. I'm going to get fucked up today, by the way.
Just want to make sure everyone knows. All right. Go through the subway. Easy. All right. Here we go.
I got to go home through the subway. I got to walk the whole subway train line thing. It's allowed
to, is it all right? Aunt Sausage. Cat and the Mouse Experiment. Blake McKinnon film. Is this
guy, is this guy made like a horror movie? All right, Blake, let's see what you got. Let's see
what you got. Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas to you too. I just licked my lips because I'm a lip
licker. I just can't stop. And I just tasted soap because I've been putting, I'm trying to do this,
man. I just, I gotta stop doing it. I'm such a, I'm a lizard. I swear to God. I, I'm so aware of it
too. It sucks. He's been disemboweled. What sort of maniac would do such a thing? I better get out
of here before whoever did this comes back. Get out of the subway? Oh, there's a lot of ads for
this guy's movie. There are more ads for this guy's YouTube horror movie than Spider-Man No Way Home.
Advertiser budget is probably pretty high for this one. It's loud as fuck. Is it all right?
Where should I go? Wait. I don't think I should go that way. Why is that even scary? Like, I mean,
it's weird that there's a, but like if I saw Santa, I'd be like, oh, safe. Santa will protect me from
the fucking scary monster that's here. I wouldn't be scared of Santa. All right. Do I have to run?
Why the fuck did you get over there? What happened? What are you talking about?
What? I wouldn't be scared of Santa. I would hope Santa would be the one protecting us.
If Santa's the one with the axe, we've got a lot of problems. We've got way more problems than we
think. Okay. So what am I supposed to do? Just run away? So what the fuck, man? Do I go buy him?
Oh shit. It's always a bathroom punch. What if I just punch him in the face?
I'm tell- I honestly think this. If like an old man was coming at me with a big axe,
I would just snap his neck and win. They have to swing the- an axe is not a great weapon.
All right. I'm dead. I don't think I wouldn't be afraid of an axe. I really wouldn't. An axe has
this like one point. It's heavy. You have to swing it. I would be able to dodge it and I would just
go dodge underneath them and grab him by his chin here and his top of his head here. And I would
snap his neck. It would be easy. Axes are not good weapons. Seriously. So, okay. I got to follow the
arrow somebody said. What the fuck? Ah, see what I'm talking about? This guy can't even hit me.
Don't turn around. Don't turn around. Don't turn around. Get out of the subway. Get out of the
subway. Get out of the subway. Whoa. Holy shit. Look at that. Whoa. What the fuck? That's so cool.
I didn't know you could do that. I need a crowbar to get out of the subway. Where the fuck is the
crowbar? I need a crowbar to get out of the subway. Bathroom? I knew you were gonna go right.
Where is the crowbar? It has to be the bathroom. Oh, down here? What the fuck? He's killing
policemen. Crowbar? I don't see a crowbar. Oh, fuck it. Out of here, dude. Where is the crowbar?
Can I hide? I have no idea where I am right now. I'm just going in circles. He's on the map. No,
he's not. What the hell is going on? Crowbar? Crowbar? Crowbar? You! How do I get the fuck out
of here? Oh my god, dude. Give me a break. Come on. I don't even know where I- I don't even know
where that was. Is there a crouch? I gotta hop. Okay, I gotta go right? I don't want him to see me.
Don't- okay. He'll walk by and I can go around. I'm high as fuck right now. As long as that's
legal in your jurisdiction and you're responsible about it and I'm okay with it. This is too loud.
I'm turning it down. Fuck it. If I can go around and hide. You- oh, yeah. Pre-fire.
Ban this person from the lobby, seriously. Oh, you piece of shit. Give me a break.
I remember it's down here. I gotta- okay. Lock this in long-term memory, please, Jeremy.
Here, I see blood. It's literally right. No, it's left. You stupid motherfucker.
I'm gonna get through this. It's the stamina that's killing me. It's right. So you go right,
straight. Alright, I'll get it. And then I gotta get to the exit, too.
The flashlight? I'm gonna flash that off. Okay, down, right. He doesn't know where I am. Right?
I don't know where I am. Where am I? Ah! Okay, I don't- I forget everything.
Fuck you! Give me a break. What? Right here? Where am I supposed to go?
And then I gotta go down here and leave the subway. Don't turn- I'm not gonna turn around.
No way. This looks like a Roblox mod. It's low poly. Just give me a checkpoint, please.
Oh shit, my light. My light- hold on a second. Whoa! I can't- if the game's paused,
he can't hurt me, right? My light's fucked up. I'm trying to be professional for once in my god
damn life. Alright, now what? Find your way home. It's very quiet all of a sudden. I wonder where
everyone has gone. A gulp. The weather outside is bright. I got fire and solar light. Since we-
since we no place- hold on. Since we no place- I'll get it. Since we no place to go. Let it snow,
let it snow, let it snow. Use that part. Like, three people just got banned. I don't know what
you did, but what the fuck are you doing? Oh, why do they have to keep locking this gate? Oh,
that's not Santa talking. I thought it said Santa. Looks like damage- can I break it?
How would you not be able to break it with a crowbar? Why could you not break it with a crowbar?
I don't even have a crowbar anymore. Why the game take- the game took the crowbar from me.
Are you kidding me? The flashlight. It coughs. There's a crazy guy running around with an axe.
He's- but he's- I think he's literally 15 feet behind me. He's gonna kill me.
Oh, I should go file a police report. He's- he's literally fucking 30 feet behind me. He's even
an axe. He's gonna kill me. Go- go to the station tomorrow morning. Okay. Just to tomorrow morning?
Okay. Okay, thank- all right, thank you. So, I need to find a weapon.
Politic Landy. I'm well lit for that one. Fuck you. I need to find something that breaks this.
Can I just punch it with my hands? How am I supposed to find something that breaks through
a wall? I had a crowbar in my freaking hand. Go home. What do you think I'm trying to do?
And how dare you talk like that to the streamer? Number one rule is respect the streamer always.
How dare you? I- I don't want to activate this yet. There's gotta be like a weapon or something
I can find. Something to break the door. I don't want to turn that cutscene on because then he
starts chasing after me. Hold on. Uh, it might show up on the minimap. Can I write your obituary in
advance? Ban that person for an hour. I think I have to do this first. Okay, now it's like,
oh, I can't get through here. Where is he? Where is he then? All right, does it- is it gonna show
up in the minimap? Something I can break? He just fucking hit me in the back. Oh, I'm so dead.
All right, I gotta find this, whatever this is first. Find something to break the door down,
but I wait, I don't know where to look. Blue dot on the map? It was only a yellow dot on the map,
though. I looked. Sneak around if- okay, turn the flashlight off. What can I find here? Go through
the window? Yeah, I'm not activating his spawn point here. Not yet. What about can I jump up on
stuff? Go through the window. You saw a window? It was a blue one just as you died. Really, was
there? All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, I'm going, I'm going. So I gotta run
this way. All right, go. Blue dot on the minimap. Oh shit, I see it. Oh bro, I got an axe now too.
You're fucked. I know what that is now. All right, I got it, I got it, I got it. You suck.
I don't. This game's hard. Blanker. All right, there it is, right there. I see the blue dot.
So get the axe first and then I'm going for it. Do two hits and you're out? Yeah, well, I, it's,
it's kind of tricky. So let me go get that first. That was what, down here? Yeah, right here.
So I got the axe. Now I shouldn't spawn him. I don't think he's gonna spawn unless I get over
there. I mean, you just hurt my feelings. I'm just kidding him. I'm just messing around. All right,
let's go. Find your way home. Oh shit, I live here. What? An eviction notice? They must have
changed the lock too. What? I need to get out of here before Santa finds me. The only way out of
here is along the train tracks. I turn the flashlight off. Get myself killed here. Can I
break this? Where is this motherfucker? I know he's here somewhere. Stairs onto the, wait,
the stairs. Go upstairs. I go. Where are the stairs? Stairs? Where are they? Where are they?
Where are the stairs? Where are the stairs? I don't see them. I got here late. What was
your Christmas gift? Is there a staircase up here that I didn't see? Where is it? Huh? Oh,
there I go. I just needed my glasses. I just needed my glasses. He's gonna be on the road here.
Wait, you know what I mean. That was one of my eye. My eye is burning. Two headphones going in.
Fuck it. I'm going real mode. For all the new viewers, I don't wear headphones. I only wear
one earbud because I'm like a baby and like I get sensory overload and I can't think and I can't
talk when there's sound going into both ears. So I have to do it like this. Otherwise I can't talk.
I swear to God that's not made up bullshit. It's real. See right now I'm like, I'm hitting a wall
of talking. I can't do it. I hate it. I need to be aware of my surroundings and I need to
hear my surroundings. I would rather there be mono audio coming through here and stereo coming
through here and I don't get to hear the left side. It sucks. All right. I got to pay attention.
This is important. What's all the stuff on the mini map? What's the green? There's a green thing
on the mini map. Oh, crowbar. Why would I get a, it's a gun. Gun. I have a gun. This guy's fucked.
Eight shots. All right. There's a crowbar. I think this is the final battle. This seems pretty final
battle-ish to me if I'm serious. What if I shoot him in the head? Does he just die?
Escape via the train tracks. Okay. See the gun. Why would I take an axe when I gotta get a gun?
16 shots. This guy is dead. What does he want me to go out here? Objective. Kill Santa. It is.
He's dead. Just give me a whatever. I'm just going to run around. I didn't, I didn't know
I had to shoot him that many times. Just a guy with an axe. If you shoot somebody in the head
with an axe, this is going to drop ammo. Let's go. Oh, your AI is fucking stupid. I win. Oh,
I don't have any bullets left. Fuck you. I need stamina. I can't run from him. I need stamina.
He's an idiot. He's an idiot. He's an idiot. Okay. I got time. Green dot is ammo. No, it's not. Shut
up. Is it really? Where's the gun? Where's the gun? Where's the gun? Where is he? What do I do
with the gun? What do I do with the gun? All right. He's dead. All right. He's dead. I'm going to,
I win. Poop face. That would be a really bad poop face. I feel like you'd want to go to the
doctor immediately. Give me the gun. All right. I got it. It's easy. I don't, I feel like the game
will fuck up if I pick that up. It's ammo. All right. So because the green, I thought the green
was the plant. 16. Let's get it all. You probably have to hit him every single time though. It's
probably like 30 shots. I thought it was something in the plant. I don't know. All right. I have 24
bullets. Garbage day. That's an old meme. All right. Let's do it. 24 shots. I'm not going to
shoot him yet. I'm going to get them onto the tracks and walk them backwards. Here we go.
Get the stamina up. Ready boys and girls. Oh, he's dead. He's dead. Oops. I thought he was,
I'm an idiot. I fucking missed. Oh my God. I'm going to blow the whole thing. Eat shit, Santa.
You killed Santa. Merry Christmas. I like that one. That was fun. That was fun. That was good.
That was good. That was good. That was fun. Do it again? Why would I do it again? All right.
Moving on. Coming up next. I need to make sure I got to keep track of these. Any more Christmas
ones? I think that's all the Christmas ones. I got to pee. Anybody else have to pee? Go pee.
We'll be right back. Pee break. Quick. And I kind of want to just put the BRB on. You know what I
mean? I just like the BRB. All right. Two minutes. Be right back. Okay. God, I love this. It's so
cute. Go support Blordow. For the love of God, please. He's got a band camp. I'm not even here
right now. Right? Like the thing you're hearing and the thing you are seeing is literally all
Blordow. It's his music and it's his art and animations. So go support Blordow. All right.
We're going to stay in the... I've actually seen this game played. So I can't tell you it's going
to be like a completely... Oh, I've never seen it before. But I feel like it looked like fun. I
didn't watch very much of it. We're going to play Knight of the Consumers. It's a game where you
have to like stock shelves or something. It's kind of scary. I don't know. I've seen it for like maybe
15 minutes of it so far. Looks like fun. And here we go. Coming back. Let me get this over here.
Open it up. Should see it very momentarily here. I put it on ultra graphics. Does that even matter?
I'm not sure that even matters. Warning. This game contains... Hold on. Warning. This game contains a
real retail experience. Knight of the Consumers. You don't stream in 1080. What's the point? Bit
rate. 1080. Not worth it. 60 FPS. Awful. Looks awful. You need at least 10 to 20,000 bit rate
to make 1080 look okay at 60. How many times do I have to tell you this? All right. What are the
controls? How do I play? I have no idea how to play. I have no clue. How do you do that?
Lots of lonely nights in the mirror. All right. Here we go. Hey, you're late. I just fell down.
You're late. But hey, since you're new around here, I'll cut you some slack.
My name is the manager. We're not too busy on days like these so you can have a nice easy shift to
help you get settled in. Remember, I got a reputation to uphold here. You won't have me
looking like a fool in front of the other manager, would you? The store is the best in town and I
would like to keep it that way. If any of my local customers aren't satisfied with your service,
I will be hearing about it. Now, go find Jimmy. He's been working here for a while now. Very loyal
employee. He'll show you the ropes. Put your stuff in the locker and get to it. Stuff in the locker.
All right. Where is... I don't remember that. You all right, Jimmy? I can't take this anymore.
I don't get paid enough for this. The rude customers. The endless amounts of sick
shit stains. I've reached my breaking point. Listen up. It's up to you now. There's still a
lot of empty shelves out there. They need to be stacked before we close. You don't want to upset
manager. Here, take this. It's all the notes I've made while working here. Those tips saved me time
and time again. All right. All right. I got notes. Hold shift is run. Left mouse is throw box. It
stuns them. Right mouse is drop box. When you're stacking a shelf, AD to look around. Hide in the
staff room. Don't get caught. Okay. The sprint kitchen. All right. Okay. You got to... All right.
What I've seen of this game is you got to make sure that you know where the places are. That's
all I remember. So we got kitchen furniture. All right. Kitchen's over here. So where is it? Right
here. So you hit space. Okay. You all got any of those P.T. clone games? I can't get enough of
them. Oh, I have to bring them to the right place. Toys. Video games. Right. Okay. I got to bring
them to the section, but don't get caught. Fucking same person. What are you doing? You got anything
with sugar in it? Magazines. Home cleaning. Pharmacy. Health and beauty. Pets. Alcohol. Drinks.
Sweets. There it is. What is this one? Video games. I can hide too, right? I can run away.
Where's video games? Where the hell is the coffee? Don't get between me and my caffeine.
Home cleaning. Pharmacy. Health and beauty. Alcohol. Drink. It's drink. Drink. Drink. Drink.
Unsettling shit. Okay. I have video games. I fucking just talked to you. Leave me alone, you dick.
Get away from me. Your most expensive bottle of champagne and none of the cheap stuff.
Where's alcohol? Drinks. Alcohol. All right. All right. All right. All right. Leave me alone.
Where's the canned bread? I don't fucking know. Food. Furniture. Kitchen. Kitchen. Where's the
bread? Food? Pharmacy. Food. Staff room. Staff. Staff. Staff. Staff. Staff. Staff. Staff. Staff. Staff.
I can run away. I need to use that way more often. All right. Pharmacy is right there.
Do I have to act? Do I have to stack? Throw the box? Oh shit. Okay. It hurts him. What the
fuck just happened? Put it up there, you fucking idiot. Okay. I'm hiding. Rude. I'm talking about
me. That's me. And it's an extension of me. It's me as the character. All right. How many
of these do I have to do? What is this? Cleaning. Cleaning's over here.
I need a skull mask. I'm going to drive around and scare. Trick or treat. What?
Magazines. Toys? Video games. DIY. Halloween. Halloween. Halloween. I got it. I got it. What's
this one? All right. Cleaning. Cleaning. Cleaning. Cleaning. Cleaning. Cleaning. Cleaning. Cleaning.
What? Oh. Okay. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Oh my god. Okay. It works. You can actually do that.
Where's cleaning? Home cleaning. Right here. Where? Home cleaning. Cleaning. Where the fuck
is the cleaning? What? Where is it? Where's cleaning? You guys really don't make it easy
to find things in your toys. Over. I think it's over. I get it. I get it. But where the
other side of the shelf? I lost my baby. Find him. What are you talking about? Find my baby?
Like, I want to speak to a manager. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Put your other earbud in. The crying. The crying. The crying. You suck. I started fucking playing
the game five minutes ago. I don't want to scream at you, but I'm gonna. Don't fuck up my Christmas.
Don't fuck up my Christmas. By the way, you showed up at 1130. I said lunch was at 1115.
We had to wait for you, Sean. And the quiche got a little bit cold, didn't it?
And that's on me now. And it was hot and ready. All right. I'm going for it. Let's go. Toys and
games. What if we'll eat quiche one day a year on Christmas? Shit's gross. Where's toys? All right.
Magazines. Furniture. Wait. Let me get up. Furniture. Magazines. Kitchen. Clothing. Toys.
Video games. Halloween. Electrical. So what's on the other? Okay. So that's. Okay. Okay. This is
consumables over here. Food. Sweets. Drinks. Alcohol. Pets. Okay. So this is like consumables.
And over on the other side is like furniture. Okay. Makes sense to me. Cleaning. Okay. This is
drugs and consumables. Did you just almost puke? Okay. Here we go. Toys and games. Which was over
here. Toys. And yeah, you have to be quick. Okay. I almost did puke. The fuck is a box?
Oh my God. I need a box. Itchy nose. Drinks. Drinks is on the other side. Consumables is on
the left. Consumables is on the left. No. Shit. I got that. Where's consumables? Um.
What the fuck? I got in my staff room. Rope. What's rope? Clothing. Halloween. Electrical. DIY.
This coffee is messing me up. Got any diarrhea pills? Pharmacy. Pharmacy is on the other side.
Come on, Gwen. Let's go. Drinks. Wrong fucking side again. Food. Drinks. There it is.
You fucking dumb motherfucker. I swear to God. What's wrong with you? Video games.
I can't read the latest game reviews. Magazines. Magazines. Magazines. Magazines.
Pharmacy. This game is making me feel sick. You all right? I had to kill that guy. Pharmacy. Video
games. How many do I have to do? This is a genocide run. We watch you to get away from this stuff,
man. I just fucking knocked you in the teeth. Are they singing happy birthday? Video games.
Other side. Whoa. Right here. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. This game is fun.
What's going on? What's going on? What's going on? What's going on? What's going on? Why is the music
slowing down? DIY. You swear to make you look like a dead grandma. That was weird and obscene.
I think DIY is right here. Food right here. DIY is right here. Happy birthday.
Okay. Sugar. sweets. Sweets, sweets, sweets, sweets. Sweets, wheel, weed, weed, weed,
weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, weed, d-i-y.
d-i-y is down here. Pharmacy. Get out of my way. DIY. What the fuck are you people doing?
Screws? DIY. Follow me. Follow me. Follow, follow, follow, follow, follow.
EXPLOSION!
Shit, okay. I got a headache. FIRE RIZZING!
I need another box.
Yeah, I don't like it's the same people can attack you.
What happened? WHAT THE F- WHAT?
FIRE!
Why did I get fired?
What? I took too long?
What are you- what?
How do I- what do I have to do?
I rented a time.
Video games.
Oh, the bottom right, it actually is a timer.
My mom thinks you're hot.
Hello, Mr. Stevenson.
My name's Drew, I'm a 985.
I'm an E-Clown. And I'm takin'.
Alright, video games. Pharmacy.
Alright, I'll get this. This game's fun. Holy shit, I like this.
EXCUSE ME!
Alcohol.
Other side. Sweets.
Alcohol's all the way at the end. Remember that, please.
Pharmacy. Get out of my way.
EXCUSE ME!
If I'm on- I gotta go fast-
I'm on a timer.
I have to go really fast if I'm on a timer.
Where's pharmacy, you piece of shit?
Other side.
Hey! Drinks.
EXCUSE ME!
Yay!
The rodent?
I need a replacement sofa- oh, furniture, furniture, furniture.
Drinks.
Come on, come on, come on, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Hurry up!
EXCUSE ME!
Baby, baby, baby, baby!
Who the fuck is this baby?
Baby!
FIRE!
You're fired!
Vince McMahon.
Okay, one more.
Can I just put them down? Hold on, wait a minute.
The day hasn't started yet.
This is the tutorial.
Can you hit the manager with a box?
Alright, what if I get them in the right spot?
Can I do that? I can.
Yes, you can.
Alright, let me try that. That's what you're supposed to do.
How am I supposed to know that?
I've literally watched somebody play this game for five minutes.
Okay, pet food is right here.
Drop the box in the aisle before the day- okay.
Are you actually taking?
Alright, let's go.
Video games are over here.
He's cheating on us.
He's got two damn kids for crying out loud.
Alright, video games. It's there.
I think somebody said I can't breathe.
No! No!
That bitch!
How dare she! He was mine!
Alright, DIY is right here.
They grow up so fast.
I feel like this is cheating. Is this cheating?
How are the two kids grown up?
There's drinks? This seems like cheating.
You weren't supposed to tell them about us.
Kitchen.
Other side. If you're 36, your kids must be grown up by now.
Okay, mom.
Why are you going to have kids, Jeremy?
Mom, I don't know if I'm ready for that.
Oh, okay.
You're older though, aren't you?
Yeah, yeah. You know, 40 is-
I would say before 40,
it's probably when you should do-
Yeah, ma, I know, ma.
Alright, ma. So let me tell you.
Let's be real.
Those of you that are trying to rush through your life,
slow down.
I'm 36, guys. Slow down.
Trust me. Slow down.
It's not a race.
It's not a race. Slow down.
Halloween over here. My dad was 42 when he had me.
Exactly, not a race. Slow down.
I think we're good to go.
It took me until I was fucking like 33.
Comfortable. So, you got time.
Relax. Trust me.
Food. Food is over here.
Not over here? Where? Oh, no, no, no, no.
Okay. I'm cheating. This is cheating.
Where are your kids? I have fucking grandma's house.
Alright.
I think that's all the boxes.
I just have to run around and not get caught.
Let's start it. Here we go. Three.
Two.
I'm 32? You got fucking time.
You got time, man. Seriously.
Guys, I couldn't even write
like cursive until I was like fucking 31.
So, don't worry.
I couldn't sign papers correctly
until I was like fucking 30.
Slow down. Not a race.
Excuse me.
Fucking baby, I hate this one.
I forget where she was.
Oh, thank
Jesus on Christmas.
Guys, I didn't even know what...
Okay, I always knew I wanted to be like an actor.
Right? And over the years.
I don't...
Excuse me.
I want to be an actor. I want to be like a film person.
I want to be like a director. Right?
But man, I really didn't...
I had no idea.
Now, I know a lot of people... Let's be real.
So, I know a lot of people on Twitch
and YouTube, whatever. People that you might watch right now.
They're a lot younger than I am.
I started really late.
There's a timer.
Fuck that existential bullshit.
I got shit to do. I got to like do this.
Pretty much TLDR. Who gives a shit?
Like nevermind.
Frontier, frontier, frontier. What the fuck?
Excuse me. I need beer, alcohol.
Come with me. At the end.
No! You didn't even see me. Get out of my face!
Excuse me.
Alright, kitchen.
I lose. I lose.
I lose. I lose. I lose. I lose. I lose.
Fuck it. I lose. I lose. I lose. I lose. I lose.
I lost. I lost! I lost. I lost.
I lost. I lose. I lost.
Cleaning. Where is cleaning?
What the fuck? Where is this?
This is bullshit. What's going on here?
What do you want protein shake I need to clean cleaning
All that's clothing
Clothing not cleaning. All right last try this game's hard last try i'm just saying fuck it. Let's go last try
Is it final last try? I'm not pre-firing anything. No, no, we're just going
You old bag happy birthday
You come on man, yeah pets we're the pets happy birthday
Why because they're singing happy birthday I furniture other side kitchen
I'm trying to turn around and throw it sugar in it. Oh fuck off. What's this one? Toys other side. Nope right here
Jesus christ, I need clothing clothes clothes clothes clothes clothes clothes
Pharmacy other side
Oh, please sugar sweets
That was fun that game's hard that was fun though. I liked it. That was a night of the consumers
Yeah, we got a long way to go. The next one
What about the existential? Uh remark you're gonna say. Oh, right. Yeah. Okay. What was it? Listen to me. What was it?
Name what existential bullshit? What was it? I wasn't important. Uh, no, uh for real though
I was like in my late 20s dude when I even fucking knew what I wanted to do
I made like tf2 youtube videos and got like lucky
Trust me. I I lucked out a lot. So I was like 27 or 28. That's when I started
So trust me. You got plenty of time to figure it out. All right, we're gonna play slide in the woods
This is a scary one. Yes. Yeah people saying yes. Yes. Yes. Okay. Uh point is
This is something called late bloomer
and
That's okay
And you don't even need to bloom who cares right? Like just just try to live your life as best you can
I think a lot of people are too concerned about
Trying to make it trying to do this trying to make sure you do this certain thing
Just do your best, you know
You don't have to bloom. You don't have to it's all right. You don't have to do that shit
Just try to live the best life you can with what you got
All right, this is called slide in the woods
22 20. Yeah, a lot of you guys are younger like trust me dude. I think about this
I am like
12 to 15 years older than a lot of you guys. I've been there before I I trust me. I know
In a long time
You'll figure it out. You'll find your place in the fucking world
But it doesn't have to be like extravagant. It doesn't have to be like I think a lot of people
There's a lot of pressure I think on people now
To have to do something extravagant like you have to
No, you don't
You really don't like
Just do you that's it man. Seriously
Too much pressure nowadays way too much
Let's go down the slide
And trust me the way you feel at like 17 18 19
Will change into your mid to late 20s. Trust me
Ah scary monsters, right? All right. Sorry. Oh, no, never mind. I just went down the slide
Shut up dad
I get to talk like this today because I got the fucking sweater on you're 23 and you feel like shit
I remember being 23 and feeling like shit
I trust me. I remember
I remember
I go up this way
Don't put yourself under too much pressure. It's not worth it. It's not
as I thought
But I was like 20
I thought I was like I have to be a famous film director and famous actor
No, that's too much pressure. Just just do what you can
If it fucking works out it works out if not, you'll find something to do
How many times have to go down the slide?
No one likes you when you're 23
I got chronic pain. So do I
It fucking sucks. You know what i'm here now hanging out with all of you
We're all here something changed. They all have the same flashlight. Thanks for the tip dad
You get it. I know a lot you you get it. Trust me. I know you do
Luckily, it still has battery. Okay, just slow down. You're not gonna rush
Do I just keep going down the slide and it gets weirder?
Where are my parents and the holidays I know can be rough on a lot of people as much as it's like
Oh, Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas everybody. Oh, woohoo. Woohoo. Why didn't him friends?
It can be rough. I know
Uh, so let's just enjoy ourselves here right now together
All right, no more puking. Okay. I promise it is like ruined like a really nice moment
I promise i'll never do the I pretend to puke ever again small town in morning is mass missing person's case
The local park continues to go unsolved reports say both children and adults missing
Uh detective working on the case sheds light on its peculiarity
Here's the notepad
It's as if they disappeared into thin air
He asks anyone if they've seen any information to come to the station. Can you read my english homework for me, please?
You got a minus
B minus you're a victim. You're a bunch of victims
I don't know. I don't know what you mean by that. What do you mean? What does that mean? It's a joke
You can't tell it's a meme. Oh, okay. I was like, what's he talking about? Go up the slide
I already tried to go up the slide in the game
I thought that person was like talking shit
I was like, what the fuck?
Oh, I thought the first was like shit talking. He was ready. No, I'm a defense mode
What's the wine? It's uh, it's a cabinier. I don't know how to say that word
I just pretend to so people think i'm sophisticated
All right double earbuds, let's do it. Yeah, I I just pretend to know how to say that word
So when I go to a dinner party people think i'm intelligent
Still going I can see my dead pixel and it pisses me off crawl meter
Hold then release space while moving to crawl hold then release space to crawl like a little jump
Colonoscopy hold down space. What do you want me to do? Should I just bunny hop through the whole thing? Uh, fuck am I stairs?
I saw green. I was like, what is that? Hey, hey, hey, hey do I have to dodge all this?
All right remove should I do this? I feel like this is a mistake
It's like big bag of trash is gonna explode
Feed them feed them I hear shit and okay
Okay, this is like a face
What do I what do I do? What do I don't get it? What do I do?
What the fuck are you doing over here, man? Relax. I'm fine
Hey relax relax relax. I'm 27. I when I started I was 27 years old
By the time i'm 36
I it everything was okay. Just don't worry man. Relax
Do I have to run away to go back up the hole? I think I have to go back up this way feed them
All right, then we go we get out of here. We leave we go back up the tunnel
Just run there is no run. I think I have to go back up. Yeah, he's gonna go in. All right, go go go go
Hurry up. Let me in
Open the hole open open open open the hole up
He's here
Open the hole open it open the hole up open it. How do I open it?
Open the hole up go what's going? Why is it not doing it?
open
Fuck out of here
Oh, it's behind me
Oh my god, get up the slide kid. Come on kid
Get up the slide kid
Go
Oh god, he's
fucking close
Now in game fortnight boba fet just a simple man making his way through the galaxy like his father before him available in the item shop
Okay
Why is that here? Why did that pop up?
I got a fortnight ad
Oh
Go
Go go go go
I know it's just sound effects, but holy shit. It sucks
By the way fort uh boba fet's available in fortnight. Are you uh people that play that game?
That was slide in the woods
All right. I think it's time to take a break from the crazy shit
We're gonna play a little chill fun little game called freeways seems kind of fun. You have to make traffic patterns
By the way, all these are on itch.io freeways. It's kind of cool. We're freeways. There it is. Okay, does it show up?
Draw a road
Uh, hold on
this okay draw a road from the factory to highway six
Like that easy you must connect all the roads to all other roads
All right, so we're gonna go like this
Like that look highway signs to see which roads still need to be connected
Oh fuck. I'm not gonna be able to do this like that six needs to go to oh
oops
This needs to go over here. It does this needs to go that way. It does
Did I do it?
This person was shit faced
This bit of a shit face that made this make sense. Did I work? Did it work?
Look at the arrows. I got it. It works. I don't get it clear. Okay
Highway six needs to connect to 101 and one. Okay, so here we go
This needs to go here and here
Okay, you can go that way or that way
You can also go
Here I don't get it. I do it
I don't get it the directional arrows
I don't get it
By the way Boba Fett's in fortnight
Wait, all right traffic flow 71 complexity
Okay
New intersection. Let's go put over here
Everyone
Drive your fucking cars over here, dude the arrow what the hell drive let's go
Roundabout. Yeah, that's what i'm doing. I don't get it. Why is it not working drive your cars? It's fucking easy
It's kind of a mess
The direction you draw matters, okay 102 that's better than an a plus that's an s
So this is residential so green road. So this is a 17 north this goes down and this uh goes over here
This connects here. You can go to green road from here
splits
You can't go that way
That's the wrong way. So if this is a highway and this can go through here
And this can go through here
And then they'll just figure it out because they're fucking god damn animals who cares this is they put lights here. It's easy
We're all ants on the highway. Who cares?
We're all animals on the highway from space when they look down we're ants. We're all bugs. We're all animals. It doesn't matter
So what all right? What do I do? This is residential. You have like one road that comes out
One road that goes in play that
No idiot
And there's okay you get to get on the highway the highway's gonna go like here
I don't know highways do like a weird circle of shit. I don't know
I don't i'm not a city planner guys. We're all bugs. Who cares use ramps
Oh, wait a minute
All right, so that's above okay
I got it. What's the problem? What's going on? What's the problem people can come to and from wait a minute. Hold on
Mr. This dude's on coke. I don't get it. I don't I just can't I can't see things
Mathematically, give me the glasses. We're all bugs. God damn it. Who cares?
We're all animals from up above in space. You need a ramp. I don't guys I just drive on the road
I don't know how it works. I just go like this whenever I get to the port part where you guys are describing
I go like this
Big circle big circle big circle big circle big circle big circle big circle big circle big circle big circle straight line
Oh, okay. Somebody planned this that's smarter than me. Uh, what's the game called freeways on itchy? EO freeways
It's like three bucks. I don't get it. I'm moving on. I don't get it highways go like
They keep going
Highway it like take you get off the highway, but the highway the road keeps going
How this way?
And then this way
I don't I don't I I don't understand. I can't do this. I I can't do it. I I don't have the fucking mathematics to reconnect everything
Now take your goddamn turns
Oh shit
That was freeways it's fun if you're smarter than I am go ahead and play it it's a cool game
I i'm gonna get this one out of the way. I'm getting this one out of the way. This one's terrifying
Uh, this one is called puppet combo scary tales volume one. I'm not fucking prepared for this shit
This one's like one looking at the worst in the night
I'm not looking forward to this. It's gonna be horrible
Lower your volume
this uh
Okay
It's just your tracking. All right lower your volume. It's lowered. I got it
All right puppet combo this game. This is gonna be scary. I guess this would join me on christmas eve
Uh, what should I do? Why is this like feed me billy
spiders
Night shift or the riverside incident, which one do you want to be doing?
Why is this uh, it looks like it's fucked up shit. It is fucked up. I gotta run this in a window
I was doing that. I mean i'll do i'm gonna do them all. All right night shift night shift. Why is it?
That's cut off. Why is it cut off? Okay night shift
Uh, you take a job at a desolate convenience store and get put on the graveyard shift as you try to work
You feel somebody's watching from a distance. It's loud. I now turn your speakers down now playing night shift turn off the vhx vhx effects
It opened like it opened another game a blue screen. Uh, what is happening? I gotta capture the right window
It opened up another game
That was weird. What time are you getting out amber? I want me to pick you up. Yeah, it's too far to walk
No, i'll get a ride. Oh
Uh, yeah, sure pick me up. Why not as if i'll be conked out by then
I'll have a beer for you later. Have fun. Okay. Yeah, that's got it
God damn it. I regret this stupid fucking goddamn light it falls
Give me two minutes
You know a ring light is like twelve dollars on amazon. What am I doing putting up this light?
Teetering on my other monitor. What the fuck am I doing?
Why am I doing it like this?
Okay, so here's what happened it fell down knock the wine glass over the wine went over the floor and all over the uh table
So give me one second. I'm still cleaning it up
I'll be right back
This shit is everywhere
Exploded
the wine glass
exploded
this wine
Everywhere. Oh, it's just such a disaster
I'm, all right, though. I'm having a good time
It's okay
You know you win some you lose some you don't buy a fucking twelve dollar ring light on amazon and you yeah
Fuck your whole room up. All right. Sounds good. See you in a minute
All right, let's go. I'm back ready to go
Uh, yeah, I just had to clean an entire wine spill
Nice desk and floor in uh in four and a half minutes
I fucking knew this was gonna happen too
This stupid light I swear to god
I knew it. I was like, you know, that's probably dangerous
Hi karumba, of course
How you doing? Yeah, it's it's not good. It's all right
The thing is it's so annoying because that wasn't even like oh, he's drunk and he spilled. No, no, no. It's uh
Would you like to see where you are? I want to see what's right next to you
There's a light that's right next to the camera and I moved the desk too much
and it just like
fucking I think oh
Yo, we're good. This is expensive. This is like at least a 70 to 80 sweater
Empty now, I think i'm good though. I'm gonna have to repaint that wall. I'm not kidding
That wall has to get repainted
80 000. No, I said if I said 70 is not 80 000. What are you talking about? What a fucking disaster. All right, let's go
What a waste of wine too. This is I like this. This is going unbelievable that I i'm not even like drunk like I mean
It just happened. That was annoying. It's because the stupid light
Remind me before the stream ends. I gotta buy a ring light on amazon for 12. Remind me tonight before I leave
All right, let's go
My hands are like sticky
What is this?
What is this? What are you doing here? Get out of here. Leave me alone. All right
Controls wsd is move q and e is peak shift run space jump. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah drop item inventory, whatever
Two headphones for this one. What do you think? This isn't freaking me out. This hurts my head. Okay, this is a run. Okay
I open it open the fucking door, man
Open the door stay open. Why is it what's going on best in time? Hurry up and punch in
I've got a hot day tonight. Oh shit. Come on. I've got to go. Did you sweep the floor at least? It's the phone fixed
the soup floor
Sorry, dude. I was too busy
Hey rick left a list of side work to do on your shift. Now. I gotta get out of here
Yeah, one more thing. I can't find the keys anywhere. The bathrooms are locked up
So go behind the dumpster, I guess
Have a good day
If my calculations are correct, i'll be rounding third base in one hour and 16 seconds
Whatever you say
All right, so go to the dumpster
Hello
The bathroom's locked
Dumpster
Where's the key?
So loud
Try better. All right keys in the dumpster. Where's the where is it cats must be working tonight?
CRT v off
I that's what I did. It means go behind the dumpster
What did I get top left?
What do you mean CRT?
Thank you. So where's this key thing? Wood door products
Extra stock that hasn't made it to the shelf. All right old room
I need a time card. All right, i'm punched in what do I do? I can't leave the store right now our drill massacre
Blue door red door
That was a drunk delayed reaction. What are you what are you talking about? That was scary
All right exit get the keys. All right green
All right, I don't play this stupid fucking game. All right, where are we going? What do I do?
If I sell anything I put the money in here gas pump. You can turn the gas pump on chips beer and oil
Okay, and drink this donuts. There's a list near the register. Is there?
Hey guys, sorry, the phone line isn't fixed. You'll have to bear with me until the repair guy comes. Don't worry
I'm not expecting any emergencies. I need you guys to do a little better
job on
Sidewalk during your shift. I'm expecting this to be finished when I come by in the afternoon
sweep the floors
Place items that weren't purchased
Fade where they belong clean the bathrooms. Okay, this is a beer put the beer back
beer back
cat food
handy
ethos
Candy, what does this go?
Where do the ethos go gas? What?
soda fridge
What happened? Hi, can you give me ten dollars on pump five?
Thanks. Ah
Did I get it? Okay. Thanks for coming
What is the ethos? I have to put this back. I have to sweep the floor
Where's the uh, where's the broom? Okay. How long how long do I do this for?
I gotta go longer than that
You shit are kidding me the whole bar. You gotta be patient. I'm being very patient
Rome wasn't swept in a day. Did you break your nose?
Like five or six times when I was younger
Who's here?
Me gas what do you want?
What do you want? All right, that was weird. That's so scary. All right sweeping done
Finish sweeping. Okay. Thank god. What else?
Do a little side sidewalk work
Sweep floors in the bathrooms. Where where do I put this shit? It's gonna freak me out
Gas, what is this thing called? Okay
What else do I have? I have something else ethos
Is it not candy? How do I put this away?
Whoa, whoa, whoa easy. There's a customer coming. Hi. Can I help you?
Yeah, I just need some cigarettes. All right, what brand?
Uh banshee red with uh filters
Here you go. I get the fuck out of here. Oh, hey
Can I use the bathroom god? Well fine. Have a nice life
Where do I put the ethos? I can't put them anywhere. Where do they where do they go? Where do these things go shelf?
What the fuck dude?
donuts
Where the fuck do these go? All right clean a bathroom clean the bathroom. Where is the bathroom?
Not in here is it outside I get the fuck out of here
How do I get the fuck out of here? What's going on? Okay. This is van again. This van's freaking me out
Okay, so where's the bathroom? Where's this bathroom?
It's outside. I can't leave though
It says you can't leave during your shift. I can't leave the store. It's in the back keys to the bathroom
You gotta get the key to the bathroom clock. Oh, I got a clock out. I got a clock out. All right, hold on
I'm already punched in
I have to wait for the customer
I'm locked. What do you mean locked? What are you talking about? You're on shift. There's no customer. What do you mean? Check the note again
I'm stuck. What's what the fuck is happening?
The van is back again. What do they want from me?
Don't worry. I'm not okay
Side work during your shift sweep the floors
Place the items that weren't purchased
Back where they belong. I did that already
Clean the bathrooms. I can't get to the bathroom. I can't leave the store
There's this door. There's this door is the security cameras
Can't get in this one and you put the broom back
I don't think I can put the broom back
I have to beat the arcade game
Okay, fuck
Uh, what's the exit right here?
Somebody's here. Somebody's this person here. Hello. Hi. Welcome. There's a customer. How are you? Good to see you. Hi
Hi
You here alone
No, I got a co-worker in the back. Can I help you? What do you want? Can I help you? Where'd he go?
What where are you? Where'd you go? All right, dude, what do you want? Get out of here?
Okay. Thank you. Did you have a white van by any chance? This game's fucking weird. All right bathroom
I need key to bathroom. Whatever my nose
What are you talking? What's going? What do you mean? What's what are you talking about?
Why people talk about my broken nose what you talking about doors open what door can't leave this door
Why is that open? Okay. Are you afraid of the grinch?
No, the grinch is a big green fucking puffball that I could punch in the face and kill instantly
Not scared of the grinch
All right. Let me let me beat this
No, i'm i'm very I could punch the grinch in the face in one hit and kill him instantly
Instantly, I would just go back and I would just haymaker the fuck right here
He would be dead
instantly
in a tenth of a second
Attic, but why would you because that guy's stealing all the fucking meat at the goddamn get-together that I planned with all my
3000 who's
All right, leave leave leave leave
factory room three
Okay
Yeah, he's stealing the meat. We have our roast beast
Oh, I don't know what's happening, bro
That game sucks. It smells like wine in here and it's going to for like three months
God damn it
Where what do I do?
I spill. Yeah
I have a light up here
Here it is. This is the light
This is my like fucking canister my grenade my light grenade
And i'm teetering it up right on top of the monitor and it's so stupid
and I moved the
I moved the desk too much and it fell into the wine glass and it was a fucking disaster
Do I have anything left to put away? I don't it said clean the bathroom, but I don't have
I don't have anything
And I can't leave
What do I do?
The bathroom's out back, but I can't leave the store
Why can't I leave?
Here the computer
Extra stock that's made of the shelf. Okay
extra stock
Can't touch this or anything
I can't clock out
This is storage
This is
This is open now. This wasn't open before
Oh
Bunk it
Bunk it clean the bathroom. How do I clean the bathroom? Hey with your tongue
Is there a cleaning like it?
Explore
What's that sound? I hear a car. Why don't I hear a car? Why don't I hear a car?
Where is the car inside the restaurant? What's that?
I can't even clean the bathrooms. It says clean the bathrooms. How I don't have any cleaning solution
Okay, so what put the broom down?
Sink toilet
Okay
How do I clean the toilet go back inside?
He's blind. There's something lick the toilet
That's the problem you
What
What the fuck are you talking about? That's the end of the game. That's the end of the game. Okay
R2D2 scream
I don't I need to see it. I want to see it. That was this what where did that even come from?
I was like I was like mom
Is like mom opens up the door while you're in the shower
You know what I mean? Like oh nobody's in here
I'm in here mom. What do you what even was this monster?
That looks oh my god, that's so embarrassing
I thought I didn't look like a person. I look like a fucking ape
This is fucking embarrassing here on
This is really embarrassing. Look at my face here. This is actually fucking embarrassing
I've never been this embarrassed before in my life. Like I saw I saw a rat. Look at this
Are you kidding me man?
That's the I think that's might be the worst thing worst one i've ever done
There are bugs in your food
Oh, here you go, madam. Here's the soup to shore. Oh, well, thank you
You lean down you take a spoonful and it's like four bugs in that spoon. Okay, let's do the next one
Give me a fucking break. Okay, uh, we're gonna play what's the next one?
Not night shift. There's not there's like three more
Mom reaction. Yeah
Uh, let's do this
A new meme face just dropped. Yeah. Yeah, I know
Oh, I know trust me. I know
Oh, no, there are mice in here. I like I like lifted up my dress. You know what I mean? I was like
What's the next one there? All right. Yeah, let's take a vote. What should I do?
I got feed me billy
spiders
Or the riverside incident, which one fighters spiders it is
Spiders something is coming your town is not safe. Your family is not safe from the spiders nature's perfect predator
Has had enough and now they're taking revenge. They're at the top of the food chain now
Merry christmas everyone can't see I know it's because it's gonna it's gonna open up another game
Now playing spiders here comes
Spiders
Format turn that off
What the fuck?
I can't see anything
Wait, why can you not see this?
Whoa, this is freaking me out
All right 20 what what is 1440p?
Desync whatever screen full. All right. Why can you not see this? This is wait. What's going on spiders? Come on
Spiders. Oh, there you go
This is the wrong resolution for you though. All right, bro. This is fucking loud bro. Hey, bro
All right, play intro
Start a new game. Yes
Why can't you see this?
Oh, there are fucking naked women on the screen
There are naked ladies
There are naked women on screen
literally naked women
Full naked full nude and it I uh, what's happening?
Why is this not showing?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait
What's going on? It's not capping. There's like four windows open. Why are there two of these?
I have no idea what's going on. I swear to god
They were they were literally naked women on screen
Just next it
Download download a virus
Um, I think the game crashed. Hold on
What is it trying to show?
What the fuck?
Hold on
Let's see it. Let's go. What the fuck?
What the fuck? There it is. Finally fucking what the fuck
I fucking never play in a video game ever again
psx fov
quality
Resolution get that up
Ugh
All right right there
All right, go go play daddy. No, i'm your son
help
Daddy don't what is going on right now wave one. What what am I doing?
40% health already. Come on kids fight back. The next one i'm gonna play is um, we're gonna play another one
Coming up next is
All right, this one's called act normal act normal
It's just fucking zinged by start how to play mouse move left mouse up and down
Spaces grab q and e or mouses rotate have a nice meal. I have to eat who's throwing shit at me
Face. Oh I have to eat. Okay, that's easy
You're right, yeah, i'm fine
What's the goal?
Act normal
That was good tasty
How do I eat?
Eat it
That was act normal. That's fun. Uh, all right coming up next. Oh, this is gonna be this is gonna be a big one
This one's called nun massacre
By the same puppet combo guy. I wonder if you can see it. Oh god. No, what do you mean?
Oh god, no volume down volume down, please germa volume down
Laughing my ass off. Okay
our
mouse right mouse zoom control
How do I get rid of the
CRT tv thing
Seriously, lower the volume. It's low. It's low. I swear volume higher. What's going on? Get out. Yeah that has
That has to drop now
Holy shit, bro. Get out of the fucking way. I don't need to go in here letter. Dear mrs
Mcdonald, I hope this letter finds you well your child is sick and needs your immediate attention
We would normally handle this matter but the situation is I couldn't even read that what happened spiders is still running
Yeah, it is. All right flashlight. Let's go letter. All right, the road is closed. So where do I go, dude?
Where do I go? All right, i'll go double
What's this one called fucked up nun nun massacre, let's go kind of scary so far
I don't know if I can do this one. It's a little scary
Am I even going the right way
Where am I going dude? Just alt f4 this sucks. I I can't just alt f4. I just I just opened it
I thought that somebody's in the room
the nun massacre
like m m
14 vague scenario llc
music by m
kc
3000 written by lila amitari and edward w
With musical guest
blink 182
And now here's your host
brad pitt
I saw a flash. Okay
Your skyrim speedrunning
How long all right i'm walking on the rocky path for like 10 minutes something else besides the rocky path
What did you just do?
Don't worry about it. You're fine
When I was 26, you know, I didn't know what I was gonna do either
But you got it
What the fuck am I doing? Was that a bird?
Like i'm done. I'm done with this fucking light. I'm throwing this light in the trash
Merry christmas everybody have a merry christmas and a happy new year
Skip the intro. Okay, geez
Skip ahead you show shiny not anymore. What happened? I can't go back. I don't think I have a light the walls are moving
This is weird. All right, this one opens
open
A lighter can I hide? Oh hide. Do I have a limited fuel? It's a tv
Nothing, nothing. Nothing. Uh, can I go in there? Hey, what's going on? Go in the toilet? Go in the toilet?
Close the toilet. Hello. What's going on? I can't move. Hey
Hey
I'm gonna lost trouble over here, man. You had a toilet paper over there
Plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two plus two
Does that mean that she was near?
Hey, I fucking i'm returning this to fucking best buy
Hey, we're safe up here
You can't get us on the stall. You can't get us. It's so loud. Oh no, where's that crazy nun?
She's killer. She's a killer. She'll kill us if she sees us
Oh, oh, oh get up. I get safe safe safe safe. Where do I go? Where do I go? Where do I go? Yeah
Yeah, yeah
Where's my lighter? Where's the lighter? Oh, what's this?
Dear diary mommy dropped me off at my new school. I'm going to miss my old friends. I brought bongo with me though
We have a teacher named sister
euphy
Mia she has an assistant named sister odelia
They're teaching us about the saints and what wonderful lives they lived
Today we learned about saint lucy her eyes were put on a plate and she became a martyr
That's a weird word sister euphymia
Said that her love for god saved her from the evil romans
That tried to hurt her sister rose said that mother of polonia
Is gonna
Is gonna take care of us all okay, fuck up a little shit
Where's where's the lighter?
You know when your ear is itchy and also the back of your tongue is itchy
Come on gwen like and you sit there and you go
You're trying to itch the spot that's inside your ear and all the way back in your tongue
God, you fucked up. We should have we should have been fucking steam engines. Where's the lighter? I hate it. It's christmas
You like go to
the happening too
And the main character just kind of walks down a hall and I guess things scares him
Oh, there's the nun credits roll over. Thanks for the 15 dollars. Goodbye. That was good
Okay, i'm not playing that one again
Uh coming up next we have what is scary tales? Oh, no, no, no, we're not doing that. All right
This this one looks weird. Let's play this one
Uh, this one's called
Ocitoetic bypass
It's a game where you play as a skeleton. You have to like go through the hole in the wall. I don't know
We'll give you 10 minutes. That was oh, so testic bypass
Um, thanks for watching. We're gonna move on
Oh, I get it. Okay
All right, pull pull the shoulders in put the head down
That should do it
What?
Oh, I get it. Okay. I got I got I got it got it. All right, come down. How do I go down?
I got it got it
Get in I got it. Yep. My god, how am I gonna do this? What how am I supposed to do this?
I think I got it. No, I got it. I got it. I'm good. I'm good. What the heck is this game?
It's called also testic. How am I how do I get through the hole, dude?
I haven't I don't know how to do this one bend the knees back this way. How do I hop what?
No, no, no, wait, wait stands stand up set up straight and then like lean forward right there it is got it
How do I go? How do I show this lean this way and like crumple up to the left? Oh
I think that's enough. I think that's enough 70 percent. What on earth is this dude? How do you do this one? What?
What?
No human can no human can fit through here plank spread the legs out. You think it'll help make the legs into an n
Dude, he's gonna fall down. That was also testing bypass. It's pretty fun. All right, we're gonna play juice galaxy now
This one looks fun. Uh warning this game has bright flashing lights by the way for those at home. Beware
All right. Well difficulty. I don't know room fucking stinks. I swear to god red
Oh, all right. Let's wait
What color texture plywood? Ooh
Pizza I want a pizza right now. How do I get one? What do I do? What do I do?
God, I want a big greasy pepperoni pizza. Holy shit. It's christmas eve though
Uh, I don't know about that. All right pizza. I like blue. I'm not a red guy. It's okay
Okay body tiny head big chest huge ass little arms big arms small hands big legs
Long legs small feet. It's a huge ass
little arms big arms
Small hands little feet big somebody said it's you that looks good to me boys and girls
Floppy too. Um, anyways, welcome to juice school
I am mrs. Kill kill today. We are going to talk about juice
But first a pop quiz
starting now
first question
What is juice?
Squeeze squeeze for fruit juice is everything it is all around us
Why are you here?
Because I I uh to process and refine juice process and refine juice
Juice must flow. This is strange any greater honor than lifelong servitude to the juice queen
Ah, this is way more shit that you can do you can fucking like raise a fucking family
You can have a farm you can like milk your own cows and shit
You could do your own taxes. You could fucking make a business. You could create a
Uh, you could do like a theater you could like have a your own theater
You can make your own fucking like wood crafted tables and shit. There's a lot more to life
What do you know fucking idiot?
No, is there anything out there in the fog? Yeah
wrong answer
Prepare to die
It sucks, uh, I should never have downloaded this what a terrible fucking game literally uninstall it immediately
Wow just wow you are really weird and gross and floppy too
um anyways
Welcome to juice school. I'm mrs. Slithers. Hello mrs. Slithers. How are you going to talk about juice?
but first a pop quiz
starting now
first question
What is juice?
Uh, it's everything. Oh, okay
Just leave then that's fine
Who's this?
Let's die
Uh, hey, let me tell you a secret
There's a really neat toy on top of the building
You can fly can't you?
Hold jump while in the air
Okay. What are you doing up there? You got a morning star feet?
Attention student. I said to stay away from that thing. Oh, let's go kill this person
Recess is over. Please report to class for your punishment
I'm gonna
Oh my god, you got it
Now swing it at me. It's okay. I do it all the time
That's the mouse button for a swing
Watch out my turn. Holy shit. That's a crit. I'm dying. I'm laying here. I'm dying
Good thing is the damn fire doesn't exist. I think I've had too much wine. What on earth did I just say?
I don't feel so good. Oh, no too bad. Should we go kill the teacher? So you've returned
prepare to die
Just wow
You are really weird and broke wrong answer
Prepare to die get out get out get out get out get out get out. Okay. Just leave then. That's fine
What is this?
Oh bouncy ball
cool
These arms are too small. I can't swing going in here student. I said to stay away from that thing
Be juiced to door
Please report to class for your punishment
Oh shit, okay. I need more juice
All right. How do I get juice shovel?
Get the juice. Oh shit, it's gonna open
student
Do not cross the flesh hole
All right, give me the fuck out of here that big thing at the far end it's a door it can be open
Oh, I don't feel so good
Okay, dude
Shut up
worst
student
ever
Whoa health regen max energy
Don't flight mood arm power
Yeah, definitely arm power
damage. Yep
gravestone
Yo, what the fuck happened? What I touched it what?
There's e to get up. I need to wait baseball bat. What I need a weapon. I can't just do nothing
Inventory I got a fucking shovel now. Oh sword. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait sword sword sword. Oh fuck. Yeah, let's go. You're all dead
Fuck out of here shit bag
Uh, what where should I go fine should
If you check the cabin you take the road left
Go to the evil cabin
Sorry about that, by the way
It was just a prank
Let's go. Should I cut the tree down talk to the other npc? All right. All right. Hey, what's up? I'm signe
I have act a forbidden knowledge. What is juice?
Uh juices everything juices what makes the universe i'm juice your juice
Uh that rock over there. It's also juice
Thanks for the info now die
suffer
Never mind. All right, let's go your mother's watching. No, my mother's not my mother's got a lot of work to do
She's like putting on a christmas
Yeah, merry christmas. Merry christmas to you all hope you had a good christmas eve
Christmas eve say it right so people don't think you're fucking drunk
idiot
Okay, christmas. Hi. Merry christmas eve everybody. I'll be happy to go christmas
level three
This is just dark souls. You're right
Should I i'll get some exp. All right, sort out. Oh what who killed who what happened? All right, he said
I don't know. I don't have to swing my arms around. I don't know what the hell i'm doing. Let's be easy plunger
What?
Oh my god eat shit. Seriously. What hands out sword out kill. Thank you
All right, give me the morning star 2.9 2.8. So that's better sword is way better
Next very soon folks very soon. Very soon. Just give it a minute. This is kind of cool though. I like this
I'm good. You can slurp them. Oh, I got I did it. It's just ragdoll dark souls. It kind of is
Are these little things?
Seems level seven
All right, dude. I all right. Come on. That's a good one. This one's good. Well, that was a good one
Nice pick. All right coming up next we have
I don't know if i'm gonna be able to do this one
Uh with the amount of wine i've consumed over the last few hours. I'm gonna try nonetheless
Uh, we're gonna play everwood everhood here comes everhood one of the biggest requested games
Should I play this with a controller? Yes
Okay, there's wine all over this
Plug where's my plug so playing this after like five glasses of wine. This is a bad idea
We'll find out uh flashing lights again, by the way, just be aware of that
Everhood drunk wine mom. I think i'm gonna i'm gonna be pretty good at this
I think I think i'm gonna do pretty well
An inferrable tale of the inexpressible divine moments of truth. Let's go
All right settings
Yeah
Whatever. Yeah, whatever which one art normal art
Expert no fucking way, dude normal normal normal. No, no, no, no, no, no heart heart heart
Go
Hello
We are delighted to see you enter this realm. You must leave your humanity
Abandon your idea of time and accept your mortality
You can leave and return as you will compared to your current life where there is only one way out you agree
Abandon humanity time and accept your mortality
Eh, I don't want to be I would I would want to live like 400 years tops total excellent
Like the human world we have blurred the lines of purpose, but the road is clear
It's after all for your amusement
I think like three or four hundred years is enough to you like you can see everything
I would live in every country for like five years
After it's like dude, uh, what what I don't want to do it anymore
What would you do for 400 years? I'd be able to fucking raise my great great great great grandkids
That's kind of cool
Someone said this game is hard. I'm a rhythm game andy though. I'm a rhythm game andy
I think I can handle it if there's one thing I can do on this stream. It's play rhythm games. Trust me
I should be fine
Seems like the wooden doll has started walking didn't think you'd wake up
Hmm, you're missing an arm. Can't let you back. Can you do it? Don't move
If I can hit one time i'm gonna give 100 community subs
Is it the beat to the beat or am I jumping over the is it the beat like to the beat
All right
I get it. I get it. I actually don't
I is so it's not to the beat
Stop moving in random directions
This is a point. All right
Delayed to the melody right the higher the pitch the further to the right the bar is going to be. Oh
Okay, that's kind of cool. It's fucked up
2400 subs. Wait, what? What are you talking about right now?
No, it just freaked me the fuck out. Holy shit, man. I was like who is giving that much money. What are you doing?
You owe us 20. Wait, what?
I said a hundred
Not
2400 I didn't I said
100 not 2400
Oh
You must have schmuckles to enter 20 schmuckles to get to the atm machine
Okay, I give 100 yeah
I must insert my soul. I said if I got hit I would give 100 not that was not every single time I got hit
All right, shut up
Quiet. I got it. Everybody relax
two one two
Fuck you. This guy sucks. Shut up. No, I don't i'm very good
What do you say now?
Talk now talk talk talk talk talk talk talk now talk now
No schmuckle is available. What?
Okay, we're good save at the light post. Yep. Thanks for the help give the subs. I at the end of this
I'll give them in a minute. Give me a minute. Give me two minutes
Do mouse and keyboard really?
You think so?
Don't okay
I do not have a vip card. No, I do not very cool
Uh, i'm not really a great dancer, but I like seeing people enjoy themselves someday. I might try dancing. All right. Well, good luck
Hey that doll face. How'd you lose your arm?
My condolences, okay
Uh, sure. I'll have a drink
Why not?
Ew
I love dancing the best thing I know how to do but I do like drinking blood too. I'm getting kind of thirsty
We mushroom people usually play in the woods that you should come visit someday
We love to play hide and seek but nobody wants to be the seeker
Maybe someday. Oh, sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Ludwig Ludwig. Well, what do you mean? Ludwig? Ludwig? Where's Ludwig? What what happened? Ludwig?
Where where's where's Ludwig? What what happened? It was the vampire. Oh shit. I'm like Ludwig
What did he raid? Where is he? Oh my god. Ludwig. I love Ludwig
You desecrated a 2000 schmuck drink. That's not what he said
I have a vip and hoodlums like you are not gonna get away with it first try
Guaranteed or another fucking two community subs guaranteed
See you later. What the fuck with my lights? What he's doing this to me?
Stop it. Why?
What the fuck?
I I have not what?
They're a shit the way what happened did Ludwig actually come here? There's like 22 000 people here
There's a lot of people here right now. What happened Connor raided I got raided
I had to have we went up like three four thousand people corner eats pants. What's going on, dude?
Thanks for the raid. I telling you I knew it. Uh, welcome everybody. Thanks for joining us. I am a uh
I would say a full bottle of wine deep right now
Uh, it's been fun. We're gonna keep going you're scrunked. No, not yet. Maybe a little uh, all right
Let's go. I don't know what my light just turned off, but that's weird. Hold on. Let me let me fix this
Let me fix it. Give me a second brb two seconds i'm back and would you believe it got light again light again
No, thanks for the raid. Uh, merry christmas to you connor. We're looking forward to when we uh play super smash brothers brawl
Next week. That's not happening. I'm just making shit up. All right, let's go three two one action
No one has survived much finish the fucking song you dingus
Now thanks for the raid though. It's a they're ready. I'm so burnt out. Oh, we got the vip ticket
I'll take it. It's an undertale. Please take this. Okay, so I have a vip ticket now. What is that? What do I do that?
I got vip card and heard him
Looks good tastes bad. Good luck. Nice save your progress here. Let's go
Why would I ever play super smash brothers brawl? It's literally the fucking worst game ever made that's underneath et
Nice reference. Yeah, not bad
ooh
Hold on a second
That's not it
What do you want me to do?
Gotta copy the metal it that whatever you know the word
Merry christmas fuck heads
Just copying somebody from chat. All right, i'm pretty much I think i'm at the end of the game
So i'm good to go. We're at the end of the game. Ooh boss fight. Let's go
It's the doll I stole from the arm
Well, well, well, uh, did you come here with your arm back?
Yeah, you won't you should have caught your thief when you have the chance
You will only be an annoyance if I keep you around
No goop better to get rid of you
What the heck that was pac-man, holy crap
All right, if I get hit in the next 10 seconds
I will give
Jesus
Nice, dude. All right. All right, run it back run it back. Let's go. Was I supposed to lose?
Oh, you married you married into it
Married into it
What's going on? This game's actually really cool. I like it
Stop making references that 10 people max will understand
I feel like that's 60 percent of every stream you're talking about most of the things I see
What the fuck? All right headphones going in volume going up. Let's go, bro
Here we go. I'm doing it to the beat of the song and it's just fucking me over
This is fucking tight. This song is sick. Merry christmas. Yeah. Oh, it's yeah, it's 12 o'clock eastern. You're right
Merry christmas to all our eastern time friends. Merry christmas. This game's good. I like this a lot
It's actually really fun. Oh shit song coming up. Let's go damn
Jesus
So many colors mother effer mother effer leave me alone leave me alone
Oh
We're going upside down. Oh my god
Dude, what the fuck are you doing to me?
Oh
Dude, you got don't do that shit to me right now. I can't see anything
Jesus
You don't drink a whole bottle of wine and play this game like this right now. You kidding me?
When does it end? I feel like i've been here for like three years. How long have I been here for?
It's backwards. The game is backwards right now left is right right is left you shitting me, dude
Don't even god that was crazy. That was crazy
You're not supposed to be here. It seems you've returned early
This shouldn't be possible
Something is amiss
I cannot allow you to learn too much would interfere with your purpose
I will restore your body to before you started to um drift away
Okay, do what you were doing, but be careful. That was awesome
That was awesome
Wow
Okay
You want I can give you an absolute truth
This is certainly not the right way to do it
But it might help you
Or it might twist you
Do you want to hear the truth? Yeah
Tell me
Nothing is lost
Once life is death, there will be a part of transfer. You cannot be a part of
Departed oh the fucking departed fucking up
Don't watch the movie. I just saved you three hours
Our choices will be justified in the end. There'll be a reconciliation no matter how ugly
Take this truth that is now in your hands to interpret its meaning. Okay
Now you must continue it. I will restore your body
Okay, is wine mom drunk yet?
This is empty. Well, no, no, this does more
It's christmas eve, man
sending out my
signals to all of you
Have a good christmas
Enjoy yourselves. Have a good hopefully you got something for your friends and family
Hopefully your friends and family maybe thought of you even if it's just a card doesn't have to be material bullshit
Don't worry about that nonsense
Oh, hey
So, uh gold pig stole my legs. Yeah, they're detachable just like your limbs
I can't believe you survived the incinerator
No one survives. Please take this video
Okay
Yeah, let's go get up
Get up
All right. Hey, i'm just a door. I don't have a lot of responsibilities besides standing here
You really want to go after a big guy like that?
I was impressed that they even got through me. Of course, uh gold pig is magic to make it easier
You did survive the incinerator somehow. No one else has done that. Okay, the corpse is around you. Okay
Okay, okay
Okay, this really does remind me of undertale. Where am I going?
Ah, let's give me the creeps. I know it's empty but someone feels like please let us leave red
No, i'm doing a fucking song man
I want to leave this place someday. Maybe one day
I was not prepared for that
Save save save save save save. I don't have what I didn't save. I'll get a first try guaranteed. Where do we go over confidence?
Yeah, no, you're right. You're right. You're right. You're right. That's smart. How do I get out of here?
What do I do stop right there red hood
I've been sent by the gold pig to stop you from reaching the cursed castle
Stop your quest at once go back to where you came from and I won't hurt you. You called my bluff, huh?
There's no I won't bother you wait. I know I won't beat you anyway. I won't fuck off in a nice way in a nice way
Fuck off respectfully
Oh
Oh, I have to move the train
I love this game. It's actually really really really fucking good shit
Oh
We got it right now you idiots my nose is itchy and I can't do anything about it. Oh my god. What do I do?
Yeah, I feel weird. That was weird. That was weird
I got cut off. What was that bs? I can feel you running through my veins. That's if I do you want
Oh, it's you again
What the hell do you want?
I'll be annoying somewhere else. I'm busy. Can't you tell this game's addicting? It actually it actually is really I
I gotta move on i'm kind of addicted to the game. Oh, I need to do I gotta play more stuff
We had a lot of stuff to play
saved
You look like george bush. No, I look like john carrey get it right jesus
The wrong affiliation
I didn't save what?
All right, one more song and we're gonna move on. All right, freddy good to see you. Goodbye slime. Oh, this sounds good
Welcome to slime brother's plank service. My name is flan and my brother's name is muck. That's me
Plank renting service looking for a very long plank
Yes
What do you need to rent a very long plank I mean the diploma of certification for handling very long planks
Okay, do I need to get certified? Yes, i'm certified
I'm not certified. Okay, whatever
It's on the house
All right, bros
Oh that hurt my fucking eyes somehow. I don't know how that hurt my eyes. Let's go last one
Oh, they're holding the planks. That's cute
shit
Bad really bad bad
Good
Here is your very long plank. Thank you picked it up. Where do I use it over here? I came in this way
Wait, wait, wait, what's down here? What about the other plank? Oh shit. Sorry
Can I go this way?
No
Crap no, I don't want to go but no
Kill me kill me kill me shoot me shoot me shoot me in the head. Shoot me kill me
Kill me shoot me
What's happening what's going on I don't know what I just did fuck me you can't see this
I'm so confused at what's going on right now
I
This is saw i'm playing
What's happening? Why can't you see this?
That was really weird. No, there's another another game opened. I swear to god another game opened up. Hold on. Let me try this
Okay, what?
I don't know what this is
It opened on its own
How long is this song
What?
Oh my god, jeremy stop it. The song is traveling from ear to ear and it's freaking me out
What how do I get out of here?
How do I get out of this song? How do I get out here?
It won't stop
What do you mean keep going? How do I stop this nonsense? I want to get out of here
Where's the camera? What happened to my camera? What guys?
How long is this song
What is happening
What's happening?
Why am I still here?
Okay that loops
Okay, that was everhood. Thanks for watching. We're gonna move on
I'm gonna pee we'll come back. I'm gonna I really want to show the brb screen again because it's uh, it's awesome
I'll be right back. Go pee. See you in a minute. Hello eating a cliff bar right now
Wait one second get pizza. I don't think I can't do that right now
Are you going is that going to be a yakuza or will you revisit that game?
I thought that was awesome
But I do want to play art school
Before this stream turns off this game looks really fun. What about saint throw 2?
Ah, probably not. Please keep at it that anime level you were almost at the end
No streams are over. No what I have at least another 40 to 5 minutes to an hour to play at least
All right, let's go move this
I gotta clean my desk too. Oh my god. What a disaster
Yeah, merry christmas east coast
What was that? That game was called everhood
E-v-e-r everhood. It was great. Okay time for chewing andy. Let's get back over here. Let's open art school
This is like a classic itch.io game from my understanding. Let me get this thing bright
Looks good. All right art school new game loading
Oh froshman
I just spit I hope it didn't come up on the camera. Welcome to art school. Okay
Okay, hopefully neverhood neverhood is one of my favorite games ever made analyze your work against my database and give you constructive feedback
I was made by scientists, so i'm really good at this
Don't worry. It sounds technical
But art school is really simple once you get the hang of it use your drawing pad to complete the assignments that I give you
Okay, get inspired sick loading assignment think of a number between one and 50 draw that many birds
When you have completed the assignment return to my office for critique i'm just gonna do one fucking why would I do 50?
No one
for gex, okay
Art school
Think of a number between one and 50 draw that many birds
Well, i'll do one
This sounds I've did it. Where's my prize? Where's my prize? What I can move. I got a color swatch
What oh god damn it. Okay
Why yeah, i'm hydrating I just drank a bunch of water so don't worry i'm good
They're like, all right. How do I turn it in? How do I turn this in? Whoa?
Oh, okay. I'm here. All right. Look I gotta see I got brushes swatches. Let's go
What did you dream about last night two nights ago? Um last night
I don't think I had a dream last night. What was my last dream? What about the night before that?
Um, I don't know the last dream. I remember just drinking Gatorade out of somebody else's fridge
And it was like all the gatorades were mixed together it was weird
It was like all yellow purple green and red gatorade were all mixed together
Like they got the gatorades down to like here and they poured the last third of it into the same gatorade
And they did that they did that with like six of them
So they didn't want to drink the last like gross part of the gatorade
So they combined them all and put them back in the fridge and I drank it. All right, I got it
So I wait I gotta explore what's down here, okay, now what draw ingredients I need more colors
This has been open the whole time. Why didn't anybody tell me that who's open the whole time the entire fucking time
Where did the game go dude? What the fuck? What are you doing?
OBS, what are you drinking crack beer? It won't fucking close
It won't close. I just closed it. I get it. Oh my god
There's an there's an explanation for it get the fucking spider game out of my goddamn inventory
Get out of here. Oh my god. Why?
Here's what happened. I accidentally pinned the spider exe file to the taskbar and I kept thinking it was open
So I kept right clicking it to close it, but I kept opening new instances of the exe
So let's unpin that from the taskbar
and
Keep going
Jesus christ, uh
Okay, draw ingredients
I need more brushes or something, right? Can I go in here? All right, draw. Okay. Uh ketchup
Ostered mayonnaise hot sauce. All right. Got it. What those aren't ingredients. Yes, they are
What how are they not ingredients? I need to get back over. All right. You're right. That's those are condiments
Invent a new country design a flag for it. Sure thing thermal light nation. I need more paints
So there are spiders in your router. Are we okay stream crashed? Are we okay? Are we here? What's going on?
We are I've lagged
Oh, well, I don't know. That's weird. I need more condiments. I need more paints the stream crashed
That doesn't it didn't really weird. All right. I actually need more colors than blue and black
I need to make the german ni5 flag, which is pink green
Blue and like hints of magenta back to normal. That's weird. I'm sorry about that. You get points for exploring
Okay. No, this is not cooking wine. Where is any new stuff?
Oh, fuck you. How did that get the best rating out of everything draw what's happening in the outside world?
Okay snow snow snowing snow snowing christmas snow slays. I need what do I get stuff?
I didn't what the fuck I I went in somebody's house
I went in so I didn't go back. I went in somebody's house my god draw a single line
Oh
I got text tool but I move it
I want to move that how do I move again?
Bring the spiders back. Yeah way too many. How do I erase? Okay. I gotta at least communicate with the teacher again
What's going on? How am I dropping frames? What what's going on here? Fuck. I shouldn't be dropping frames. What's going on?
What's this like two years ago? It's twitch
Oh
Uh-oh, it's a twitch problem. Uh-oh
Uh-oh
Apparently, it's a twitch problem. I guess merry christmas. Yeah, merry christmas to all of you
This drawing is going to end up in a big gold frame
Does that change how you approach it? Maybe a little so apparently apparently it's it's it's a twitch problem
I guess I have no idea. I guess twitch is having problems. It's not a twitch problem
It's a spider problem. The real question is is he gonna draw boogers down both the nostrils?
Of course he is he's in the fucking first grade. Where do I go? Oh new brush. Let's get it white
What's that over there fly?
Can you do your best tim allen grunt?
Fucking idiot. I stood myself for that one. I'm really am not happy about it. I'm not happy about it at all
Very mad. All right. Where what was the point of coming to this little island?
Oh basketball this game's cute. Stop minus twoing. It's been five and a half hours of quality fucking funny content
And just because I said one bad joke doesn't mean the whole stream was bad
scoff
Eye roll scoff and I turn this in so it gets off the screen
All right, give me out of here. It was five and a half hours of uh, ye clown cringe. That's your opinion. It's bad
Oh, I failed this one
I want you to do this drawing is going to end with a big gold frame. I show up around to her
All right past I was gonna draw the mona lisa, but I was like this that's not gonna happen
Not gonna happen at all draw as much as the unit. I i'm not doing this anymore. This game's cool
This game's cute. These are galaxies if you're curious. All right. All right next game this one approach. I gotta be all right
So my portfolio I just clicked it and it's just like fucking they just give me the images. They're just here
It's literally like the shit. I just drew it. It just opens up a file
That has all the things I just drew
In like a windows explorer
menu
All right, maybe maybe like one or two more then i'm gonna get going
Hmm
All right. Here's your chance. Here's your choice
eight bit horror like
1632 bit horror or
Eight bit. All right. We're gonna play faith faith is like a
Old old kind of style which we're gonna play faith. We'll try it for like a half hour or so
All right, guys, let's do it
I've had a lot of fun. Hopefully you guys have to let's keep going. Sorry the stream like shut off a few times
It's weird. It's very odd. That's very stretched. It shouldn't be
Faith is great. Okay, can I make this window bigger 20 community subs? Thanks for the 20 subs. That was by snaps cube
Thanks snaps cube
I want to make this bigger
WSD, okay
Left analog stick pad
Okay, get it face demons and cast them out with a space key. All right penny. Hey penny
Hi penny. What's penny?
All right, new game new game. All right, i'm gonna go up
Blocking the text. Oh shit. Sorry
So I only have two moves is it
Like oregon trail. What was the game with the clerk stuff?
Oh the power of christ
Fine
Uh, that was puppet combos scary tales
volume one
You're invited come celebrate nate and jason's sixth birthday
We're right at 1338 snake meadow hill road
straight past the well
shit, all right
I'm not afraid of a bunch of fucking squiggly pixels
That's scary a bunch of fucking squigglies
I need a key
I can go right
Where's that birthday party?
I mean, that's weird
Don't go into the screen's edges
I think I just got lost
I think i'm lost actually
I probably shouldn't have oh wait. What's this?
Get out of here
What's this? Oh shit. Okay
Can I get some historical connections to witchcraft?
Satanism and the beast system wednesday at 8 p.m.
All the deer
That's right
Holy shit, he got close
What's that pick it up
Okay, this is undertale clone not quite but
All right, yeah, merry christmas have a happy new year merry well, we'll see on new years
I should be live by then
All right. I just want there in a complete circle
Follow the deer. I'll follow deer. It's not christmas here for another couple hours
But uh, I do appreciate unless thank you
All right, follow deer deer is gonna go up
Year is gone
Where did deer go?
Wait, no
Somebody had a birthday party and somebody died
Uh, I hate those little things
You gotta read
Where do I get the key?
All right deer deer deer deer deer deer deer deer. We're going
Get the fuck out of here
Oh shut up really
Ah
I'm going right what?
All right deer
Uh, is it christmas? Uh, it's christmas in the east coast
and also in uh central time
right
Just hit midnight
5 p.m. Christmas day. Oh my god, Australia, New Zealand
All right. This is locked
30 minutes of this this game. Uh, I don't know maybe
Was that a lie or is it do you actually follow deer? Should I follow the deer or is it a lie?
Taking a while a long time destroy the historical thing
Is it one guy? Okay
Deer just mess with the house and read the notes. Okay
Here's something
Oh shit my face
I'm sitting there like
What happened to the server?
Oh my god, I looked like a fucking psycho
Uh, my speed test is perfect
I don't understand. Well, i'm sorry buddy
I have a gigabit connection and i'm a thousand thousand up and down
Well, we'll probably i'm ending soon. Anyways, so whatever
dark twitch kind of uh
expedited that process maybe
You have rich rich streamer has gigabit connection
Do you have any idea how long it took me to get this connection?
I suffered
Those of the old viewers of this channel
Holy smokes. Do you remember?
Being on that old comcast old cock connect we would lose
I that's back when I was tripping like three or four times a week at least
We would drop 20 000 frames a day
This connection has been perfect
Without a single issue, which is awesome
What's the provider?
Oh
What's the key?
Okay, let's figure this out
Found it just gotta put the glasses on i'm fine
The martin's house lies about 100 yards off snake meadow hill road. There's almost no driveway
Trees jut out of the middle is a gravel path. That's mostly covered in grass. Holy smokes
Okay
I found it
That's the key to the house
Get away demons
That's the house key
Up left and then I think left one more time. Why was this itchy when most of these games are on steam?
You distracted me now. We have to do the whole thing again
Um, no, most these aren't on steam. What are you talking about?
I got all these on itch.io only like a few of them were on steam
I got all these on itch.io because I heard that itch.io gives a higher cut to people right?
then steam does
From my understanding
It's yours drm free
All right. I got the key
All right boys and girls, let's go
Amy was in the very back of the attic in a chair perfectly calm staring at us
Okay in the attic
That's a huge bed. That's a bed for like eight people
Can I open stuff?
It's an orgy bed. I don't know why I read that
What a pain that was such a pain in the ass
No, i'm not into that. No, thank you
I would just yeah, I was sitting there just like what the fuck am I doing here? This sucks
What if you're the odd man out of the orgy, right? You have to have an even number would be an odd number
Somebody just kind of like okay. Yeah, it looks good. Um anybody
What's uh?
Wait, you oh, no, you're busy. What you have to have even number of people. How would you do an odd numbered orgy?
What do you mean? What?
Wait
No, fuck that. Fuck that
f u c k that shit
No
I'm sorry. No, I didn't read that
Don't think so. I'm not saying anything
I'm gonna get myself in trouble if i'm not careful here
It's christmas eve god darn it. Okay, i'm not gonna get myself in trouble on christmas eve
I'm not gonna say anything on christmas. No way
I'm just saying
You brought it up you did you said what's with the orgy bro? And I was like, I don't know man
I don't know what to talk about. All right, we got a picture
Okay father mother child. I didn't bring this up. I did not somebody said the word orgy and I read it
I did not bring it up. I did not
You know how long I was holding that for?
Oh, my face hurts
I was sitting there for like at least two straight minutes
Waiting for the stream to reconnect what the fuck? All right. Um, I guess i'm just gonna I guess i'm just gonna go
Wait, wait with life. I thought I was disconnected
Goodbye, it's been swell good to see you again. Merry christmas everybody. I'll see you later. Have a great day
Are we am I gone again?
Wait, wait, if I come back, hold on. It's important. You're on the air. Well, what the I I thought I was gonna catch people
When they came back you're live
Finish the game like my stream key's turning off. I'm what I'm trying. All right, i'm just gonna go
I I don't know what's going on twitch's servers fucked up. I guess green teeth. No, they're white as snow like christmas
Bye, that's it. See you later. Merry christmas to all and to all a good night. Have a wonderful rest of your day
Thanks for coming out. Appreciate it. Merry christmas everybody
Uh, I I mean I can't I don't think I can do this shit
It's like I keep losing connection every like 15 seconds. Good night. See you 13 year old mustache
You're in trouble. I don't know if they can hear me. Good night. Have a great
Christmas
I'll see you all on new year's eve
I think i'm my mic is gone. That stream's over. Anyways, like I can't I don't think they can even hear me
God, I fucking hate streaming
Fucking just I quit like I just I quit I quit I quit I wish I could say that to them live
I'm sure it's fucking say that to them. How can I tell them my god? I fucking quit like I fucking hate streaming
All right, goodbye
Merry christmas. Happy new year. See you on new year's eve. The poll will be up tonight or tomorrow
Check the twitter go to my twitter. Look at my twitter find my twitter. I'll see you not tomorrow new year's eve
No, i'll see you on 27th
It's got me all fucked up. I don't know what's going on. Good night. Goodbye. See you on the 27th check my twitter
Later on tomorrow. Good night. Goodbye. Good luck. I'll see you later. Good night