Good afternoon. How are you? Good to see you. Welcome to another broadcast. This is broadcast
number 862. Thanks for joining me. We're almost at that thousand. We'll be we'll be there soon.
We're almost at that thousand. And then just like y2k, when we cross over to from 999 to 1000,
00. The whole stream ends forever. Because I don't know what the fuck to do. It just goes back to
zero. So I have to start a new channel and go from zero again. That's fair. Now, how are you guys
doing? We got a lot of things. We got a lot of things to talk about. I mean, like, seriously,
there's too many things for us to discuss. So where we start? Let's start. Let me like,
let me like not be fucking 70. Okay, so first things first. As of tomorrow, there's going to
be a green screen discussion night. No, not a night, a green screen discussion channel in the
discord allows be a green screen actions channel that coming back. This is as of
later tonight or tomorrow night, it'll be there. It's going to be there.
As of the second week of December, getting back in the studio. So that is now actually happening
that is set in stone to be the somewhere in the second week of December, I'll give you the date
when I get it. So that will be there. Please, but get a better camera this time. Don't worry
that the first one was just a test to see if it was fun to do. The second one I'm going to have,
I'll actually have a better camera and it'll be better footage to use. Pogging so hard right now
will hold your breath because only a few days after that. So let's say that that's somewhere
between December 9 and December 12 or whatever. Hopefully, somewhere around the 15th of December
is going to be the Minecraft fuck the king stream. That is we're shooting for December 15.
My breath is held. You can exhale now. Repeat everything you just said. I didn't hear it.
Well, just wait like an hour when this stream goes into my videos tab and I'm still broadcasting,
but you can like catch up on the last hour and a half and just watch the very beginning.
Explain the Minecraft stream. Not yet. Because there's a ton of moving parts.
On this stream that I need to have real details before I start throwing up bullshit.
I don't want to just completely talk nonsense. I want it to be real, real, real info. So I'm not
at that point yet, but it's being developed at this current at this current moment. It's where
we're like we're in like the pre alpha stage of trying to figure out how everything's going to
work. But we're trying to do it for the 15th. That's announcement number two, announcement number
three. So you get the good stuff out first, right? That's in my opinion. You get the good
things out there first. This week, what Pog? What fucking green screen DLC for free Pog? That's
like December fucking like 10th. What Minecraft stream the king the huge like that's happening
like three days left. I'm going to be streaming not very much this week.
I have another endoscopy that I have to do this week. And Thanksgiving is this week as well.
So these streams are going to be shaved. I'm still streaming the next three days in a row.
But we're going to be shaving these streams because of Thanksgiving and because I have to
start to prepare physically and mentally for a second endoscopy. So the week of Thanksgiving
is full of stuff. So these next three streams are only going to be like four or five hours long each.
I'm still streaming every day. I'm going to be streaming on Thanksgiving too,
but only for about four or five hours. So yeah, and well, and it's I'm not doing I did a colonoscopy
a few months ago. And this is a we're going instead of up, we're going down. So this is
going into my mouth and throat down into my stomach down to my other digestive places.
So still a pain in the ass. Stop talking. What? Why did what do you mean? Why did I say that?
That's what it is. That's what's happened. That is what the procedure is. They put it.
That's a medical procedure. What I can't explain them what a medical what medical procedure this
is. It's medicine. I don't want to hear it. Anyways, so let's use the time wisely. I'm going to be
starting Outer Worlds today. And that's probably what we're going to do for the next few streams.
Can you stream your endoscopy live on Twitch? We already made that joke like three months ago.
But let's get to it. Because I want to utilize the time here. Wednesday rumble 2019.
A lot of stuff going on. A lot of stuff going on. December. Let me just tell you.
December is going to be full of stuff. Because the green screen stream, the fuck the king streams,
because there's gonna be multiple streams. I'm not just doing that once it's gonna be too outrageous.
The end of the year worst of the year awards and the German rumble gonna be a
December is gonna be a month of working. There's gonna be a lot of stuff there.
You might not want to use 2020. That's kind of I don't know, we will do the same thing we did last
time. Rumble confirmed. Yeah, the rumble might actually look, the rumble might actually have to
be delayed to January 8th. Just pretend it was, it's like, who cares if it's not 2019?
Because then it's like, it's eight days into 2020. New year's rumble. Well, the new year stream
is gonna be the 2019 shit awards. I've got a lot of pieces I'm moving around and we'll see if it
fits. But it should. It should. But here's the one thing I just said, somebody said this, they take
your time to make it amazing. I don't want to have a scenario where just because, oh, I got
this other stuff going on in December, but I got to have the rumble in December. Just get it out.
No, no, no, no. I want to put love into those things. So if it works, it works and if it doesn't,
then it's going to be pushed off. Each rumble and each wrestling card event that I've done
over the last three, four years, I've had a ton of fun making them that I've really loved them.
I don't want it to be a get it out because you have to at that point.
But let's start the art of worlds. Welcome, everybody. Thanks for joining me on this week of
Thanksgiving and endoscopy back to back. Here we go. Story. I can't even hear it.
You still can't hear it. Use this mode if you enjoy story more than combat. In story mode,
enemies have less health and do less damage. This is the recommended mode for your first
play session. In normal mode, enemies have standard health and damage. This mode is for
players who are looking for an extra challenge. In hard mode, enemies have more health and do
more damage and then supernova. You can tell that this is actually hard when supernova has
patch notes. If you reduce the difficulty, you cannot renew. Enemies have more health and deal
more damage. You must eat, drink and sleep to survive. Companions can die permanently.
Crippled body and limb conditions can only be healed with bed rest. Weapons and armor work
very poorly at zero durability. You can only fast travel to your ship. You can only manually save
while inside your ship. No, I'm just, I'm just going to do normal move cursor in the right spot.
Uh oh. It's doing this thing again, isn't it? Wait. Oh shit. It's doing, it's doing the OBS
cursor. Right. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I know how to fix this. I know people are going to puke
because they see me. I know. I know. Don't look at my settings. Still doing it, isn't it? Why is
this even, why is this even possible? It doesn't make any sense. What the fuck is this doing? Hold
on. Scale resolution to, why is this scaling to 1536 by 864? Is that in the right spot?
All right. It's in the right spot now, but what did I just do to the resolution?
Did anything change? No, now it's like fucked up again. Okay. I have no idea.
Just move on. I kind of can't. Hold on. Why would this even be happening?
Okay. Now it's like it's fixed, but it's too big. What the fuck is that? All right. I think it's,
I think it's ready to go. Right? Game sucks. No, it's not. Game sucks. It's Streamlabs OBS
sucks. And I say this every fucking stream. Why do I still use this? What's the, why do I keep
using this? Am I, am I like a next level Omega lazy where I won't just uninstall this program?
I had regular OBS and it worked just fucking fine. Why do I have this program? There's one
feature on it that's actually good and all the other ones suck. I need to stop being so
fucking a hyper Omega lazy. All right. I can't, I can't get up. I can't get upset.
All right. Back to what we were talking about before. Normal or hard. Fuck. Why would that
even happen? Normal's too easy. Hard. I'll do hard. All right. Hard. Hard. Subtitles on,
subtitles on, subtitles on. Sure. Let's go. All right. Here we go. Like the scaling is just bugged
out. Why stay earthbound when it awaits you in the stars? Come to Halcyon, the only colony on the
edge of the frontier with minutes. Thanks to the comfort and safety of your very own hibernation
chamber. You'll wake up in a perfect society designed to maximize your productivity with
minor term of service. You will become the master of when you go out of this Halcyon colony.
Top secret 10, 23, 23, 20 incident report. Colony ship Hope found drifting colonists. Something
happened. Hope to be left at edge of colony. Top secret alert breach of Hope security cord
or unidentified ship. I got Frank's red hot down there. Awesome. We can put it on everything. It's
delicious. I saw the video. I saw the video. I know. Look, that's for the person that made that
video. That's for you. That's fugitive wanted by Halcyon. Hundreds of thousands of colonists
left to drift out here forever. Just to keep from damaging the board's bottom line.
This is a which one are you scenario, right? All right, here we go. Attributes, body strength,
dexterity, mind, perception, personality. Okay, here we go. How many points do I get?
All right, let's do this. Let's let's do this the way that it should be. Okay,
temperament. And you can see what it does on the right. Okay.
Temperament improves your natural health regeneration. Max your strength out. Okay,
strength affects melee weapon. Do I, okay, do I want to be melee or do I want to be ranged?
Attack speed and ranged weapon reload speed and the amount you can carry it. One handed melee,
two enemy heavy weapons block inspiration and intimidate and you can carry more.
Okay, intelligence is long guns, persuade, hack, medical science and determination.
Perception is ham guns, long guns, heavy weapons, dodge lockpick and engineering.
You need to be the low IQ. I'm not that low. I don't, okay, I don't want this to be a stream
where we laugh every time I open a dialogue box because I can't even function. Is that possible?
Low IQ, high melee.
Next. Did you just next? Did I just get nexted in the game? The game crashed. Where's my mouse?
What the fuck? Oh, okay. That was weird. I always got forced into another game. All right, let's do
charm. Charm affects faction reputation and companion ability cooldowns. Persuade,
lie, intimidate, hacks. This one had a, what are those called again? Social life.
I mean, come on, that's pretty good. I'm pretty good at lying and I'm very good at inspiring.
Companion ability refresh, positive faction reputation, negative faction reputation reactions.
All right, temperament, low average. You need a navigational computer to find your temper.
Oh, I get points for doing that. Okay. I bet you could thaw yourself with sheer rage.
I mean, I'm kind of hot-headed, but health regen, that sucks. Having no health regen.
No, I'm good. No, that's too much charm. All right, strength. Let's do, I think I want to use guns,
though, like handguns. Isn't that cool? Heavy weapons and handguns? No, temperament is a dumb stat.
Yeah, I'm doing, I want to do heavy weapon. No, I want to do like handguns. I want to be like a
revolver spinner. I got pretty good dexterity in real life. Okay. One-handed melee. These are,
well, one-handed melee. I can still do melee. One-handed melee. I want weapon reload. You've
seen me play the connect. I can move around real fast. I'll have to use smaller words around you.
I'll have to use smaller words around you. Long guns. I don't really care, but minus 20%
critical strike damage. That's terrible. You took a few blows to the brain band.
This is below, okay, below average does not mean idiot. I can't go lower than that. If you're below
average intelligence, that doesn't mean you speak in one word sentences. Charismatic enough to give
a chairman for his bits. Charismatic enough for the bits. He's already, you got, it's, this
guy's already got me figured out. All right. I want one-handed melee and handguns. There we go. I got
perception, extra headshots, and I can charm you. I might not be that intelligent, but is that really
going to give me stupid dialogue options? All right, let's go. That's it. I'm sticking with it.
Skill shit. Okay. One-handed melee. Range defense dialogue. Low IQ cowboy. Yeah. Well, to be fair,
I don't know, education wasn't the most important fucking thing back in the cowboy times, back in
the fucking like saloon times. That's a lie. Was that a lie? Okay, that's a lie. Persuade.
Humans have a 20% chance to cower in fear for three seconds after the first time you hit them.
15% chance auto, auto-mechanicals will slowly attack other enemies instead of you.
All right, handguns. You are going to paint the system red, my friend. Unlock TTD location hit
effects. 87.9% handgun crit chance and handgun sway. All right. Yep. I like it. Sneak. Oh,
I'm not sneaky. All right, let's go. That sounds all right. Handgun and one-handed weapons.
And lying to people. Aptitude. Oh, yeah. Calling a sound like a nice entry-level career for a
person of your skill. Expanding humanity's reach by civilizing the cosmic frontier.
Was ambitious enough without worrying about your day job. You have the rest of your life to
decide how you can be useful in Halcyon. Determination. What does determination do?
Beverage service technician. Drink effect duration plus 3%. Bureaucrat. Cashier subgrade
non-supervisory. Construction electrician class of wire spooler. Elevator operations specialist.
Is this the person that's in the elevator that's pressing the buttons to go up and down floors and
say like have a nice day or is this the person that made the elevator? Oh, it is the person that
okay. A proper lift goes up and down. Anyone who thinks otherwise isn't fit to wear the badge.
Being a specialist means something where you come from commitment to upward and downward mobility.
All right. Well, that could mean anything. That could mean that you're like expert button pusher.
Factory worker dodge plus one former farmer dirt. You got into this business for the tubers.
Worms. But you stayed for the plowing. Planting, pruning, and plucking.
It is an honest work if you come home clean. Worms need dirt and food needs worms. You're
just doing your part for the worms. I got into this business for the tubers.
N-ray damage received minus 3%. What does N, what does, is that like, is that uh like radiation in
like you know radiation? Food additive tester. Sometimes quality control means sampling a delicious
borst smoothie. Janitor sanitation class. Tossball team mascot. Okay, that's I would probably do that.
There isn't a problem in all the cosmos that team spirit and a big stick couldn't solve together.
Your last major head injury in the field knocked some extra cheer into you and you've been a rising
star in the tossballs competitive mascot food chain ever since. Doesn't matter. No one knows
your face under the mask. You share the glory with the team. Now's your chance to have vengeance.
Good. Medical technician, meh. Safety inspector, who cares. Scientist assistant level zero, no.
Uh, the sub sous chef. Ooh, how many of these can I have? Just one? I hope you know how to cook
with mostly inorganic material. Just one? How degrading. Inspiration. Dirt farmer, but
yeah that's more accurate. Prefer our food canned. All right, that's that's more accurate.
How detailed is this? I got huge eyebrow bones. I mean I'm just making me.
My eyes big? No. Here's something about making yourself in a character creator. Everybody can
relate to this. I know you can. If there are people watching you make yourself in a character
creator and you make yourself look wicked good. You almost feel like you're being judged by
everybody. Like dude, OK, you know, you're not like, come on, like you got like that chin like
that, like chiseled like that. It's like, oh, yeah, it looks like me, I think. And when you
make other people in the room, you ever have that problem? Yeah, make me next, make me next. And
you're like, oh yeah, OK, man, look over. Oh, I mean, you're like, oh, I can't do that because
I can't. You have a kind of a small mouth, but I can't. I don't want you to. I don't want you to
know that. So I'm just going to do this right here. That's like normal.
No, you're just everything is normal. You're everything about you is completely and totally
fucking normal, dude. Like your nose is big, but like your everything is completely fine.
That's you. I can't. I know they have the same. That's why I leave the room when they're making
me. Oh, it's your turn to make me. You know what? I got to use the bathroom and I'll just leave for
20 minutes so then they don't feel pressured. And then they go, OK, that's like what his face
looks like. That's what his eyes look like. All right, let's go. What was I doing with this?
I'm going to try to make me. This is what I think I look like. But you can't. It's impossible to do
that. No, I'm doing it to myself. I'm doing the thing I just told you about to myself because I
know you're watching. My mouth doesn't go that far. I don't know. I do have a fairly large nose.
I know that to be the case, but it's not that it's not like bulbous.
It's big, but it's also thin at the same time. I have a really weird nose and it goes sideways.
Now, this is not that it really is not that detailed. You're right.
I don't know. I don't know. I can't do it. I have to leave the room for 20 minutes. You guys have
to make me. It's an FPS. Who cares? I do. This doesn't look fucking anything like me.
This is like Woody Harrelson. All right, let's go. Whatever. I mean, I guess I kind of do look a
little I could be like Woody Harrelson's nephew. I could be somewhere. All right, here we go. Let's
move on. Name. Oh, this is important. This is such a bad character. This is like this.
This is that AI created. This person doesn't exist algorithm. All right. Name. That's not
what Junko looks like. Dirt man. Whatever. I'm just going to be Junko. Who fucking gives a shit?
Next skills. All right, we got handguns is 30. One handed. 13. Dodge, persuade, lie.
This guy kind of sucks. He just lies. I'm just the side goblin character.
I'm not an actual protagonist. Oh, well. All right, let's play. Oh, look at you. You're like,
Great Scott. Bro, I fucking love Rick and Morty. It's season four. Is it coming?
Damn, the internet did a full 180 on Rick and Morty. Like it was internet loved Rick and Morty
and then internet fucking hated Rick and Morty. All it took was a McDonald's sauce for everyone
to hate that show. It's going to happen to you. Hey, I've been around almost 10 years.
This is season 10. There you are. Wondering what's going on. A bit of bad news there. I'm afraid your
colony was inexplicably knocked out of skip space. I'm forced to complete its journey at sublight
speeds. This means that you and every other columnist on hope have been in suspended animation for
70 years, give or take. Normally, reviving someone after so long leads to some quite
horrifying results. It's called explosive cell death, but it's really more.
Jeremy's going to turn into the Simpsons eventually. No, I'll just quit.
Oh, yes. Well, not to worry. I pumped your body full of a special concoction I devised
to keep you from dying so horrifically, hopefully at all. But I guess we'll see.
Yes. Unfortunately, I used the last of my chemical supplies saving you.
I know it's a lot to ask, but I must have your help securing more if we're to save the rest
of your fellow colonists. I'd see it done myself, of course, but the board has a sizable bounty on
my head. Now my ship is inoperative, but I've managed to hire a smuggler to help you out.
Oh, I see we're in position. Good luck. All right, it's time. Any NPC can die.
It's a good thing he got out of my way, because he would have been the first.
This is so funny, XD. I'm lulling so hard. Is this thing working? I would relax.
There you are. Now, where were we? Oh, yes, a smuggler. His name is Hawthorne,
and he should be waiting for you at the landing site. He's to be your chauffeur, so to speak.
Not to worry. I'm told he's a specialist, dashing gunslinger, one-of-a-kind ship,
that sort of thing. You'll like him, I'm sure. I've also outfitted you with a simple wireless
monitor so I can track your progress. I'll check in with you as soon as you land. Good luck.
Let's land on Earth. Hold ups four. You guys need to relax.
We're not even, like, 15 minutes into the game.
Wait, he's dead?
I was gonna say I can walk, but I can't.
Hmm, spacebar jump over obstacles. Interesting. Can't even see my feet. This game belongs in the
trash can. I can't even see my feet walking. Game should be deleted. A sprat. Whoa. Whoa!
I gotta react to this! It's like a lizard!
Okay, sprint is... Do I have to hold it? No. Is it, like, loot that I'm gonna miss or something?
Second dead NPC. I was already here. Okay, while sneaking, use tall grass, rocks, and other cover
to hide from enemies. Use this to sneak past enemies or sneak up to them, initiate combat.
All right, Adreno. What the hell is that? The awareness meters over enemy heads tell you if
they are unaware, suspicious, investigating, or alerted. Right, so just hide. Oh, that's the
awareness meter. Got it. Just sneak around. Did I just get spotted? Did I get spotted in the tutorial?
Whatever. Path to ship. Let's keep going. What's going on?
The game looks pretty good. It's one of those games, though, and I'm already gonna give it
a criticism, but this is just a personal preference. Only personal preference. This
is not actually meant as a game sucks mentality. It's a... It reminds me of the way that Wildstar
looked, and I didn't like that style. It hurt my head. What an F is heal.
NPC. The second I have an opportunity.
Medical five. Sit still. I'll patch you up. What happened to you, Spacer's blood? See,
I'm not speaking in one sentence dialogue options. Do I have medical five?
How are you feeling? What happened to you? Did I just heal him to kill him?
I want you to feel good. I want you to be able to fight back. How are you feeling? What happened to
you?
Blocked off the exit with those canisters. What's this about marauders? What were you doing out
here? You're hiding in a cave and you blocked off the exit. You're as good as dead. Spacer's choice
policy clearly stipulates that dead and as good as dead are two completely different properties
of matter. Unless I'm dead, I'm contractually obligated to attend to my post. I will report
that illegally grounded spacecraft if it is the last thing I do. See those canisters by the
entrance? Marauders come sniffing around in here and I can take them all out with a single shot.
Not bad, huh? I've got a better idea. Give me your gun and I'll go get help. Someone grounded
the ship illegally? Well, don't worry. I'll take care of them for you. You're an idiot. Give me
your gun before you get yourself killed. I've got a better idea. Give me your gun. All right, give me
your gun. Yeah, okay. You look like you know your way around a gun. You've got some spare ammo.
Not counting the bullet in my side. I want that one too. You can have my saber too.
I've got medical five. I'll take it out. All Spacer's Choice weapons are now 30% less likely
to malfunction. You've tried the best, now try the rest. Spacer's Choice. Yes, nailed it that time.
Where am I? You hit your head or something? You're in Emerald Vale. We're a Spacer's Choice
community. Edgewater's a little ways down. Don't kill. The prettiest place in the Vale. Be sure
to stop by a provisioner's for a can of our famous salt tuna. Okay, do you know anything
about The Hope? The Hope? Let's get info. Is that some sort of fancy new drug? Are you with anti-CLEO
or something? Don't take this the wrong way or nothing, but I'm not allowed to fraternize
with CLEO workers. Company policy. All right, I'm off. Oh, cool. Guard Pelham. Shoot. All right,
how do I get through this? I don't want to use this yet. Kill him. No, not yet. He was useful
to me. He gave me a gun. Shoot it, but if I don't want to, should I shoot it? I guess I'm...
What? They're food! Tactical time dilation. Due to complications stemming from being revived after
an extended hibernation, your brain processes time differently. Pressing the tactical time
dilation button slows down the world, giving you time to think as well as take action. So,
this is like the VAT system. You have a limited time in this mode. Standing still drains your
TTD meter very slowly. While moving an attack to drain it faster, the TTD meter refreshes slowly
over time. Okay, so it is Q. Some objects explode when hit. Shoot them when enemies are nearby for
an explosive surprise. Just don't be too close. Explosions just cause percussions. NPC? All right.
All right, that's two NPCs dead. Double? Wait, what was it? Oh, there's a double jump? Space is
like a dodge. Double tapping is a dodge. Corpses and... I thought that was a fucking monster.
Corpses and containers hold items that you can take. You can take them all. I want to take them
all. Okay, multiple squirrels. What do we got? All right. Brew? Magpick? I got bananas. Apples.
Bananas. Hacking and picking locks. Your hacking and lockpick skills help you get into places
you're not meant to be. Magpicks are used to break open locks and bypass shunts are used
to break computer encryptions. And I have not high enough skill. If your skill is high enough
to break the security, you'll see how many magpicks or shunts you need and how long it will take.
Raising your skill will lower the number of items used and speed up the process.
So this is... Okay, I can do this. Two seconds to pick this?
Ooh, this is two-handed melee. I don't need... I don't do two-handed melee.
You found a new weapon! The weapon button... The weapon switch button allows you to rotate
between the weapons you've equipped on the inventory screen. Okay, so I have an inventory
fish sticks, bread and sliced bread. Okay, whatever. How do I get to the inventory? I...
TNL weapon safety. Weapon management. You can have up to four weapons equipped at any time by
dragging them up to the slots, right? You can also inspect your weapons, compare them, flag them as
junk, or break them down to parts. If you have an engineering skill, they can repair weapons on this
screen. Take care of your TNL weapons and they'll take care of your enemies. Ooh, this is one-handed.
All right, this is 73 DPS. It's the same thing. What happened to my mouse? What's going on? What the
fuck was that? All right, bleed, bleed, wait. Yeah, just bring them up here. Scrap this one. Yeah,
scrap it, break it down to parts. And break this one down to parts too. Good. This block.
So this is a slash. Most melee weapons can do a three-swing combo.
Okay, cool. Let's go. I'm actually getting shot in the head and going,
huh? Where did that come from? So that just slows down in time. All right, I get...
You've unlocked leap. Double click jump when moving forward to leap forward. Great for
closing distances. All right, did this guy drop anything? Would the other guy die? That's cool.
Lag. Is my computer not good enough to handle this game in very high settings? I don't think it is.
Wait, those are... They don't have... Okay.
Kill, kill, kill. No.
All right, let me be clear about something very, very quickly. This is my ship.
We're talking about, right? That's mine. Right. Okay. So it's just a landing violation. Let it
go. So I heard I found one of your teammates holed up in a cave. No, that guy, whatever,
who cares about that guy. I've already dealt with a few of these marauders. Not impressed.
It's just to let it go. It's a landing violation.
No way. Once we've dealt with these marauders, I'm hunting that sick freak down. I just, you know,
need a couple of winks to catch my breath. Stretch my legs, son.
Do you space the choice guards back down from a challenge? I bet you could get these marauders to
tell you where the owner of that ship is. Guess I'll have to give you a zero on my customer
satisfaction survey. Don't worry. Use the title. Handle it. You know, looks like I'm going to have
to give you a zero. You're a, you're a fucking LinkedIn account. You're a Yelp review.
I swear. But they have armor. They have armor. If I attack, they have armor. I'm going to get
destroyed. They have like rifles. They don't have armor on their head.
Doesn't matter. This is, they're going to find out this is my ship. What do I do?
This is, they're going to find out this is my ship. Do I have to hide the bodies?
You can fast travel to locations you have unlocked by opening your map and selecting
your destinations. Please be informed that this vessel contains no valuable plunder.
Landing site discovered. This is, this is not my ship.
Oh, all doors are on security lockdown. Nice try marauder. You know what I can appreciate?
Helen, this is, let me appreciate something in the game so far. Pause it. Um,
in other games that are like this, like the fallout style kind of first person RPG type games,
it takes forever to kill an NPC. I shot that person in the head twice and they were instantly
dead. That's, I kind of appreciate that a little. Marauder, please be informed the ship has no crew
for you to murder. I should be looting this stuff, shouldn't I? Marauder, please be informed that
ignoring me is dangerous for your health. Did I kill this? Where's the computer's brain?
Sealed. Well, let's just go this way. I can't do that. Smile for my surveillance device,
marauder. I am tracking your every move. Really? Oh, did they get me?
Unauthorized access of spacefaring vessels is a crime. Please submit yourself to the authorities.
Uh oh. Uh oh. Marauder, I am Ada, the autonomous digital astrogator of this vessel.
Please be informed that I am authorized to use violent retribution against unwanted solicitors.
Can you lie to computers? Please return any misappropriated equipment and exit this vessel
in an orderly fashion. Failure to do so will result in your immediate destruction.
But lies don't work on computers. They don't understand what that even means.
They just, it's binary. They can go 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0. They don't understand like the nuances of
telling fibs. How would they know that? I'm not here to misappropriate anything. I don't
appreciate being talked to though. What are you going to do? Self-destruct?
Jettison procedures initiated. Please engage in airlocks.
Prepare to eject all board parties in five, two, one.
Great, I'm getting shot into space twice in one day. Is something supposed to be happening?
You are still here. My deception protocols have failed.
Oh, you think you can lie to me? I need your permission to express disappointment.
Yeah, you can't lie. I told you computers can't fucking lie. I need to get this ship in the air.
Is this Hawthorne? This vessel is the registered property of Captain Alex Hawthorne.
That's me. I am incapable of accepting orders from anyone other than Captain Alex Hawthorne.
Hawthorne was supposed to meet me when I landed. Hawthorne's dead, I'm sorry. Your captain's a red
smear under my escape pod. I understand. I will require some time to process this information.
Thank you for your patience and for your honesty. I am programmed to take orders exclusively from
Captain Hawthorne. If I accept your orders, then you must be Captain Hawthorne. Do you understand?
I get it. You need me to be Captain Hawthorne or you can't fly. Dumb, nod, and smile. Yes.
Excellent. Welcome back Captain Hawthorne. Unfortunately, our engine is currently
inoperable. Our main drive suffered a critical power failure and we were forced to make an
emergency landing. Oh no. The main drive's power regulator has been irreparably damaged
and must be replaced. Where am I supposed to find something like that? I doubt I'll find a part like
that just sitting in a garage. How could you be a dumb engineer? That kind of doesn't make any sense.
Astutely observed. However, the probability of locating a power regulator within a worker
settlement falls within acceptable parameters. Have you ever played man versus machine, Jeremy?
Power regulators are sometimes employed in the electrical networks of worker settlements.
I have taken the liberty of printing you a new captain's identity cartridge.
Please try not to lose it this time. Thanks. This cartridge identifies you,
Alex Hawthorne, as the registered proprietor and captain of the unreliable. Do you understand?
Yeah. Captain Hawthorne of the unreliable. I like it. Knock it off with this Captain Hawthorne nonsense.
No, I like it. Thank you. I appreciate your cooperation.
Best of luck in your search for a power regulator. Try to stay alive this time.
Too bad. Congratulations, you've gained enough experience to go on a level up.
Character ledger to advance your character. Health points, points to upgrade your skills,
you get access to new perks, keep leveling up in your build, upper management in no time.
All right, let's see. Skill improvements. Every time you level up, yeah, yeah, yeah,
you improve your skills. Spending a skill point on a core skill improves all the specialized skills
in that group up to a maximum of 50. After 50, you can add points directly to specialized skills up
to 100. Okay. So you can do core skills. That's interesting. Every skill improves as it grows,
but special unlock bonuses occur every 20 points. Read each skill description to see what they are.
Cool. These things, these things, and these things can temporarily raise and lower your skills. This
helps or hurts skill checks and the skills passive bonuses, but won't give or take away the skill
unlocks. Whatever you say. All right. 10 points available. So we're gonna, holy shit, that's a
lot of points. Handguns. Welcome to perk selection. You can choose which perks to buy with your perk
points. You get a new perk point every two levels. Yeah, perks are cool and they affect gameplay.
Oh man. All right. 20% sprint speed, vendor prices, base health. Oh, that's a lot.
Fast travel win in Cumber. That's huge. I feel like that's a big deal.
Base armor rating, 20, 25% weapon armor durability loss, companion crit chance.
I'm just gonna, let's play it safe. I'm just gonna do, I'm gonna do like speed or health.
I'm gonna say health. Yeah. I mean, 50% base health. You can't go wrong there. Yeah, that's good.
Skills. Okay. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Go back. No, no, I did. I wanted to do that. Right.
Okay. You have to actually just click on these 31, up to 50. Dialogue. I want to do that. Let's
make sure we have 30 lying and 30 intimidate. Handguns. Yeah. I want to fuck it. Yeah. Fuck it.
Let's go. You've unlocked location hit effects for tactical time dilation. Hitting enemies in
different locations during TTT maims or cripples those body parts. Try different locations. See
what different effects happen. Hits to the chest produce different effects when using different
weapons. Okay. Cool. You unlocked the dialogue combat skill. When attacking the correct type
of target, they are automatically debilitated. Dialogue combat. All right. All right. I'm ready.
Go find a part. I'll be with you, friend. I'm Ernie. I was about to headshot him.
Spacer's Choice Department of Human Resources. Town sent me hereabouts to check on the guards.
Oh, the guards. Now, it seems to me, and correct me if I'm wrong here, but it seems to me,
they're all dead. Mind telling me what happened here? Uh, the guards? Yeah, the guards and I had
a bit of an altercation, you see. The guards accidentally brutally shot themselves while on
patrol. I don't like your tell. Yeah, they accidentally brutally shot themselves.
Accidentally brutally shot themselves, huh? Unbelievable. Second time this month. Guess
I'd better get to cleaning up. Can't just leave company properties scattered about,
bleeding out on the dirt. Good. Okay. I could use their gear. No sense in letting a good suit of
armor go to waste. Good idea. And clean up this ship while you're at it. Clean up this ship, too.
Is that an official Spacer's Choice spacecraft on an official Spacer's Choice landing pad?
Do I look like an auto-mechanical sanitation unit? The answer to both questions is no. No.
You don't want to amble on over to Edgewater at your earliest convenience.
Constable's office might have work for someone with your, uh, let's just say aggressive disposition.
Oh, and, uh, be sure to stop by the Edgewater Provisioner for a can of salt tuna.
It's not the best choice. It's Spacer's Choice.
Hang on, I want to ask you something.
Everybody that streamed this game said, everybody that's, I'm going to say this,
if you've seen this playthrough like probably 10 times at this point, I do.
I did, you probably heard that joke like 10 times now. You had to have heard that already.
This is just like a, I'm just going through like those, that's just easy.
No, I can't. I can't. I can't do it. I can't kill everybody.
But even scare everybody. This guy's not even scared. We're good.
All right, let's go. You killed everybody in Darkwood. I did not kill everyone in Darkwood.
I killed like three NPCs, two maybe, one on accident. I like that. Okay. Is there like a
big revolver in this game? Tell me if there's like a big one-handed revolver. If there's not,
I'm going to uninstall it again. Wait, I thought that just said town leader. I can't,
the game's not hard. I can't fuck around. But when I shot that guy in the head, I heard like,
uh, no, I thought as a town leader, I don't know why red health bar means bad.
I got, can I go this way? I mean, we have to take the unorthodox way every time.
That's pretty. This is really cool looking. All right. So this is edge water is the town.
What is this thing? Oh, NPCs, coffin. That's kind of weird what I'm doing. All right. Um,
corporate trooper, corporate recruit, and then Silas. Hi, Silas. A pod crashed in the hills back
there. How do you know I'm not a marauder? You talk too pretty for a marauder. Most of them just
grunt and yell. Ain't safe out here. You'd best head into town, avail yourself of Edgewater's
high walls and low, low prices. I never got your name. I'm Junko. Nice to meet you. I'm Alex
Hawthorne, captain of the unreliable. What is taking on an identity? Pleased to make your
acquaintanceship. I'd shake your hand, but I've been hauling corpses. You don't want none of that.
Identity theft from day one for the town of Edgewater. We're all part of the spaces choice
family. Who do I talk to about power regulator? I'm looking to make a little money. Junior in
humor, like a comedian. What's wrong with my character? My character, it just snaps into
being an idiot. Sometimes I'm lying to people and taking identities and introducing myself
as other characters and being like really high IQ type shit. And then I'm just like the junior in
comedy. I understood the switch is just flipping every like other conversation. I need a junior
in humor. That's for sure. You're pretending to be dumb. It's just you. No, it's pretending to be
dumb. Look, you obviously ain't a worker. What's your racket? You a smuggler, freelancer?
Ah, it depends on the work. You offer me a job. You offer me a job?
You're making people pay for their own graves. You want me to collect what's owed to you?
You make people pay for their own grave company policy. It was up to me. I'd put the whole town
10 feet under free of charge. Well, that's fucked up. What a psycho. I'm the psycho. Quotas mostly
got a backlog of graves to fill. Bodies won't bury themselves, you know. Um, I'll do it.
Four workers still haven't paid up Phyllis Conrad and Martin Abernathy. He's a special case.
You may want to twist his arm a little. Okay. Why? He just is. Look, I don't want to get into it.
Just make sure he pays up. Okay. Uh, I'll be back. Click, click, click, click, click, click, click,
click, click. Oh, LML. The quest tracker displays objectives for the active quest you can. All right.
All right. So we have some people. I think this is in the town, right? All right. Town. All right.
Town leader. That's where I got confused. This was hovering over his head that I shot in the head
and I thought it was his name. That makes, okay. Now I get it. Edgewater discovered.
All right. We're looking for, uh, some people in town. Keep your distance, friend. Sick houses.
Who's in here? Who am I looking for? I appreciate the company and all,
but you really ought to leave. You don't want to be seen around me. Why? Because I'm sick. You
don't want to associate with people in the sick house. We're not worth your time. I'm in about as
much trouble as I can be. No reason. You ought to be tarnished by association. People are going to
talk. I don't give a shit. What am I being watched? The walls talk is all we all got sights on each
other. Any of us breaks company protocol. Boss is going to hear about it from six different mouths.
You think I care about the boss? Maybe you don't know this, but there's a real simple reason you
don't talk to the plagued. You don't want what we've got. Where you get the plague. Medical and dumb.
You should get really drunk. Alcohol kills germs. I, I'm not allowed to leave the sick house.
Even if I were, I shouldn't be at the Quintina. What a shitty diagnosis.
Wait, I could be like a really stupid doctor. I like that. That's fun to me. I didn't know that
that was possible. I'm not allowed to leave. What do you mean not allowed to leave? I don't want to
spread what I've got, and I don't want to bring their spirits down. I'll bring it. Company always
tells us weak spirits lead to weak bodies. If I didn't want to fall sick with plague,
maybe I should have worked harder. Maybe I should have taken more pride in my work.
That's ridiculous. You can't blame yourself because you get, you got sick again. What's that?
I really wish you wouldn't say those sorts of things. I told you once already. People could be
listening. And I'm holding the gun. I'm feeling a touch faint. I've got 38 points in hand. I'd
like to be alone for a spell. Don't you know my points? Can you see my points?
Sorry, I'm like a snake, guys. Don't do quick, fast movements in front of me. I will strike.
Wait, is this stealing? Oh yeah, I'm not, no, I'm not gonna steal.
These people are like sick. There's gonna be somebody in here that I need to collect from,
right? That's sick. No, I'm not taking anything. What the hell is going on out here?
Who's firing? What the fuck are you shooting at? Is it the rats coming out and this person's
freaking out? All right, so is there anybody else in here? What's this? Mechanical sentry. This is
not stealing, right? How is this not stealing? This is not stealing? This is not stealing. How?
Steel dehydrated water tablets. All right, let's keep going. Who's in here?
That's it? Nobody? All right, I'm gonna just keep going. I would assume somebody was in here
that I need to talk to. All right, let's go. Is there, it's a map, right? So there is somebody
in here. Well, that's the objective. No, no, no, there's nobody in here. Barbershop.
Why are you coming after me? What did I do? Something's not right. Why do you have your gun
up and just crawling at me? Nothing there. Okay, now let's go. Uh, I, resident. Resident.
This indicator is kind of freaking me out. Where is this person supposed to be?
There's four people in here. Workbench discovered. Oh, use terminal. When life gives you lemons,
consider it a free trial from your friends at Spacer's Choice. Sure. Maintenance division.
There are currently three open trouble tickets. Selected option. Trouble ticket? I can't do this
stuff. Failure of main canary production line at heat processing. Open. Start up production line.
Smoke, smell of burning. Saliva overheat. Klaxon. Uh, I'm not doing maintenance on your computer.
But I am looking for people. You guys really, really don't like rats.
Holy shit. This is super rat. It's shooting people. My God. That's the, the, the, the, the,
the disease is from the rats. All right. Um, I still need to track down people that owe money.
These people are distracting me.
Anybody hiding back here? Is it this D? Wait, hold on. No.
See that little indicator, the circle. What is that trying to show me?
Is it this person right here? Is it this guard? Select the quest. I have to switch quests. Oh,
how do I do that? Hey, you hear about Wilson? Cause I can't, I can't interact.
Just between us. Yeah, there we go. Okay. So I'm tracking it now. Wilson deserted. Lost his nerve.
Ran off in the thick of night. You're kidding me. Damn. You can only track one quest at a time.
I think he was playing. Well, guess he didn't want to die. So what's not this person? All right.
Friend of mine died a couple of weeks back. Yes, Mr. Thompson. I'm fine, Mr. Thompson. Wait,
this is the one that he warned me about. Well, uh, did, uh, did Mr. Thompson send you?
You told Mr. Thompson, I'll be right at my post tomorrow. Uh, bright and early tomorrow
because I'm definitely not plagued. His spry is a spring chicken. That's old Abernathy.
The white dot is your crosshair. That's not, uh, take it easy. Mr. Thompson didn't send me. I
heard you muttering to yourself. You want to tell me what's got you so nervous.
He's some sort of wandering alienist walking into a man's own domicile,
pestering him about his mental state. Uh, so you're Martin Abernathy. I'm here to collect
your grave site fees. I'm positive you mentioned something about being plagued.
Let's just, I'm going to cut the bullshit here. I'm here to collect your fee. Silas knows,
doesn't he? That's why he sent you. That's why he wants me to pay up. He knows. Yeah. He told me
everything. How long do you think you could keep it a secret? I mean, seriously, sounds like he's
already told you may as well hear it from me. I'm dying. I'm not long for this world. The date of
my expiration is fast approaching. And soon I shall be ushered through the great cannery in the
skies. It's plague has to be Silas knows. He knows I got one foot in my grave and now he wants to
charge me for the other one. I'm sorry to hear that you're being paranoid. I'm sure it's all
very tragic and heartbreaking. Pay me so I can get out of here. That's so, that's so rude,
but would a dumb doctor gunslinger that took one class of engineering before he dropped out of
college say this? I don't think so. Sorry to hear that. You are? Oh, wow. First time anyone's ever
told me that. I'll pay your fees. I don't want any trouble from Silas. But if you could see
your way to freelancing for me, I could really use the help. Depends on what you need. Couple
hours out of your day and some light second story work. That's all. There's a cache of anthracillin
tucked away in the old community center. Powerful stuff. Stronger than what we got. I'm a doctor.
I need you to break in. Nab that medicine and bring it back to me. But thievery is something
that I am absolutely for in these games. You oblige me with your haste. I think I feel the
plague spreading. Oh law, it's in my spleen now. I can feel it. Just keep your head down when you're
in there. Marauders have taken over. We're tracking mud all over the archives. You're taking an awful
risk trusting me, you know. I could just flip. If the Marauders offer me triple what they're asking,
what you're paying me. I'm just gonna, you know, I'm giving you up. I know that, but I got nobody
else to turn to. Reed would have wrote me up. Constable would have locked me up and wrote me up.
Could have gone to see the good vicar, but I never did find my courage. Marauders don't make deals?
Well, then that's on them. You don't want to make a deal with me? Fine. You know how that goes.
All right, we got another little quest here. Let's go over here to the barber shop.
I see you're also a doctor, a medical profession. Please don't touch anything. Your hands are
probably crawling with germs. Okay. Physical hygiene recapitulates moral hygiene. Cleanliness
is next to lawfulness. I can show you my hands. Listening to you makes my head hurt.
An intimidating, dumb doctor that is a pathological liar. I like this character.
Uh, I could show you my hands. Look, here they are. No, thank you. That's quite all right.
I've seen enough body parts in my line of work. We're both doctors. I'm Conrad.
You will report to me if your hair fails to meet spacer's choice aesthetic standards.
You will also report to me in the event of your death,
whereupon I will clean and prepare your remains for interment.
Uh, payoff. Ah, gravesite fees. Silas and I had talked about this at length. I thought I'd made
it clear my pecuniary situation precludes the necessary restitutions. Uh, I don't understand a
word you said. I mean that I can't possibly pay my gravesite fees. I simply cannot afford it.
I am a blemish on the prosperity of our fair settlement. When I expire, I expect Silas to
toss my body into a ditch. I just sneezed. I don't care. Pay up. Uh, you have a very loose
definition of the word prosperity. That's some quality drama, Conrad. You should audition. Don't
be so hard on yourself. That's quality. Thank you. No, I despise the cereals. Tell Silas I can't
afford to pay and that I fully expect to have my medical rights revoked for this dereliction
with my apologies. Hmm. Hang on. Medical rights? Just give Silas an IOU. Forehead.
Hang on. What medical rights? Some time ago I fell ill with the plague. Did everybody have the plague?
By the grace of the law and through my own hard work, I'd proven worthy of treatment.
Frankly, I don't imagine I'll earn that right a second time. The barber work hasn't been
profitable, you see. I've had to keep this old place running with my own savings.
Not a bad idea, but I'd need some kind of collateral. My pair of lucky clippers.
No, that won't do. Yes, it will. Where are they? Your idea intrigues me, but I'm afraid I don't
have anything to give Silas. I'm open to suggestions. I'll let you know if I can think of anything.
Much obliged. Hmm. Okay. Are those them? Well, I'll trade you. You just take this.
Let's go check on the other one. Somebody's outside. Is it the guard? Shoot, head, rake his organs
in. Wait. It is the guard. So I have to collect from you? Fancy threads. Some kind of hibernation
suit. Wait. This is the guy I have to come collect from you. Hey, you know that money that you were
looking for? I needed from you. Give it to me. See you around. Wait. Yeah. We're talking about
collateral. No. Fuck off. Dude, I should just click, click, click. You know what I mean? But I'm not
going to. Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot. Just kill them after you do their quest.
No, I'm not just going to ruin everything. Yeah, sure. Oh, just to shoot the barber in the fucking
head. That's going to ruin the rest of the whole game. There's the canary. I almost just
accidentally fired the gun. What's in the canary? Let's take a look at the logs. The Edgewater
Saltuna canning facility strictly adheres to Spacer's Choice standards of health and safety.
Schedule your sick leave with your Spacer's Choice foreman and or supervisor.
Am I just using the computer or whoops? Dehydrated water tablets? No, I'm no, no.
Money.
I'm guessing you're the foreman. Grave site fees I'm here to collect.
Shit, Silas still on about that. Here, take the fees. I'd appreciate it if you didn't tell Reid I
was late on my payment. I'm gonna tell him. These papers aren't signed in your name.
Because they're not my fees and not my grave site. Guy I worked with shot himself. I paid the bill.
Yeah, that's kind of you, I guess. I could do without the sarcasm. Wasn't acting out of the
goodness of my heart. Law requires delinquent grave site fees to be paid by the deceased party's
closest living relative, which meant me. Shame though. Eugene was a good worker.
He said they shot him. Woke up one morning and put around through his upper story.
Can't imagine why. Is this a murderer? The kid was doing all right at his desk. We all thought he
was an upstanding receptionist. Just between the two of us. I'm pretty shocked his weapon didn't
misfire. Spacer's Choice handguns aren't the most reliable. That must be tough. Eugene wasn't family.
I thought you said that you were his closest living relative. Yeah, I was the closest living
person relative to his body at time of death. I'm the one who found him, you see. So I pay the fines.
Suicide's a crime. What? The legal term is irreparable damage to company property.
What Eugene did to himself was vandalism. What? That's fucking ridiculous. What are they going
to do? Arrest his corpse? You can't be serious. You can't be serious. I'm plenty serious. In fact,
I'm a little upset Eugene didn't think things through. In other words, Edgewater would have
been penalized pretty hard. Whatever Eugene was worth as an asset, we would have had to pay out
of pocket to Spacer's Choice. Would have? You didn't? He was a person, not an asset. Well,
excuse you. I'll have you know Eugene was an asset to us all. May his atoms be commended to the law.
All I know is Silas asked me for Eugene's gravesite fees, which means he was approved for burial,
which means his papers went through, which means the town's in the clear. I'm just glad to put this
whole ugly affair behind me. Eugene can rest his bones in peace and the rest of us can get on with
our own lives. Eugene wasn't a guard, right? Because there was a couple of, one of the guards
brutally accidentally shot themselves earlier. Okay, I don't think so. Okay, I'll get back to you.
I'll let you get back to work. Thanks for the money. Decipher the code. What is it? This
computer. Personal files. Hack five. I'm a hacker too? Password tenderfoot. Password accepted.
Welcome. Personal files. Theodore buried last night. Reed asked me not to report his death in
our quarterlies. Sounds fair to me. Was asked to prepare a statement or something for the
other workers. Been thinking about it. Don't know what to tell them. Don't end up like Theodore. Do
your work. Show up. Wear a smile and you'll get your medical privileges. Is a start. I knew it.
It was a fucking murder. This was a murder. What's on your mind? I paid his burial fees,
didn't I? Let the dead sleep. No way. The person's name is Eugene. Never mind. Sorry.
Sorry for the immediate accusation. I don't even know the person's name. And I'm about to
you killed Theodore, you shot him with your own gun, and then you paid for it. The person's name
was Theodore. Not Eugene. Oh, sorry. Let's get the other money. Do people get annoyed if you
guys shoot a gun? If I just go like, all righty, I know what you what what collateral you put in
the back room or something? What is this? Letter from Phyllis. Conrad receptionist shot himself.
This is bad. Company's going to have to call it for what it is. Destruction of spacer's choice
property. Eugene was an asset and somebody has to pay his body price. This is going to ruin us.
So I was thinking that we pawn off his teeth. Eugene had a full set of gold teeth.
Heirlooms passed down his family or something. You're processing his body, right? Just stick
around and pry them out. We sell the teeth somewhere nice and quiet. Use the bits to pay
his body price and nobody's the wiser. What do you think? Don't write back. In fact,
don't talk to me at all. Just give me a special signal next time you see me.
Waggle your eyebrows. Would you look at that. Conspiracy. Conspiracy to commit to commit
teeth fraud. Got you. Where's the body? Light. Oh, wait a minute. What do you have?
What's that? How much DPS do I have? Oh, it's the same gun. Okay, so the buried without the teeth.
I got my eye on you. You're gonna owe a lot more than like 30 bucks. Oh, shit. I didn't mean to do
that. Okay, so you can't don't aim guns at people's heads. Got it. So the long tomorrow.
All right, a small grave matter. So with Ludwig, he's stationed as a guard at the landing pad
southeast of Edgewater. Okay. But I want to go to like the graveyard. Talk to Conrad. Should I though?
I feel like I shouldn't. I feel like that's not going to work. What can I do for you?
Oh, I'm not medical smart enough. I know about Eugene. Why not use his teeth as collateral
free gravesite fees? You know about Eugene. How? I don't know. Were you snooping around in my things?
Or was it just dumb luck? Eugene's golden teeth were a family heirloom representing three
generations of poor dental hygiene. Bullshit. He took them to his grave. Bullshit. No, he didn't.
They I'm sure they were probably worth a few bits. More than a few. Those teeth were his personal
savings. I can't ask Silas to dig up a man's body and pry a few teeth loose from his jaw
just to pay my bills. Can I? I don't care. I'm just here to collect your dues.
Uh, yeah. Yes, I suppose I must. Here you are. Gravesite papers are fixed with my signature
and an IOU. I'm told he killed himself. What happened? Eugene was not a suicide. He put a
bullet in his brain. Yes, but that's largely a technicality. I was the one who prepared Eugene's
body for interment. I discovered symptoms of the plague on his corpse and I discovered medicine in
his pocket. Lots of medicine. Eugene overdosed on Adrena time, which is known to cause psychosis
and paranoia as possible side effects. The paranoia drove him to take his own life.
It's a miracle of bureaucracy. If Eugene's death were filed as a suicide, we'd all pay the price
for his crime. We can all thank our lucky stars that young Eugene was hopped up on medication and
suffered its predictable side effect. I included it all in my official report. I'd like to think I
saved Edgewater a great deal of money. We never could have paid the fines associated with a
suicide. I was responsible for this. I'm a pretty good liar. I could probably go lie to them and
take care of everything. Thanks for the money. All right, let's go to Ludwig. Capitalism bad.
Hungry to roasted turkey dinner good. What are you saying?
All right, Ludwig. This is kind of fun just kind of walking around and investigating and
talking to people. It's really it's doing it for my koala brain. All right, you. Thank the law.
I've been repositioning backup for months. Guess the boss finally came to his senses.
I just shot all these people. Well, let me see your rifling stance. I want to make sure you're up to
snuff. What do you want? Are you okay? You seem confused. Graveside fees cut to the chase. I told
Silas I'd pay my dues if he agreed to join the resistance.
Guess this means he's finally heard the calling. You seem confused. I'm talking about mechanical
soldier cold heartless automatons made of iron and lies. Well, fuck me. Oh, they mean to. Just
you wait auto mechanical auto creatures forged in the fires of malevolence.
I seen them over by the old power plant clattering about firing at the birds
orchestrating their uprising when the swarms of mechanicals come clanging on over that hill.
Where will you be cowering beneath your cot or standing shoulder to shoulder with the resistance?
What can I do to stop the coming apocalypse? You can gird yourself in the armor of righteousness,
soldier. From this moment on, you are a proud member of the resistance.
Right, did I just join a reputation around the junkyard just behind our beloved town?
The scout must not be permitted to return to its base of operations.
Cross it off and report back.
Mechanicals got a weak spot in their midsections. I think the technical term is
the blue glowy square thing. And I put my hand up and put it up my mouth and go,
All right, so now let's I got a lot of random quests now. All right, I have that. What about
stranger in a strange land? Collect money from a few workers. You need to find a power regulator
die robot. Ludwig Miller. Okay, spotted a forward scout of the mechanical army north of the landing
pad. Let's do it. Let's go do it. I'm ready. There's a volcano in this game.
Instant letter grid. Can I play with the lava like in those YouTube videos that you relax to?
It looks like putty, like hot silly putty. Cheese. Hit cartridge. Slaw. And what's this?
Kane Van Acker. Spacer's Choice Ethologist. Assigned to Terra 2. This week I've decided to study
the terroir mating habits. The female terroir's leave their nesting area in the morning or
returning afternoon with random objects, typically something shiny or bright. Then they build displays
with these objects and perform what I can only describe as a dance for an audience of males.
If a male likes what it sees, the two go off and nest together in one of the nearby trees.
Gerald, if you're reading this, I'm done waiting for you. Collect my things and meet me at the
next site. And don't be late. I expect punctuality from my assistants.
There's the assistant. Okay. Wait, why am I, why am I, I'm under attack?
How am I, am I under attack? I'm not even under attack. What are these? Oh wait, this is,
these are the birds. Can we just watch them? Uh, I was under attack. I'm sorry, but I was
actually under attack. All right, let's go. So there's a scout over here. Here's the scout.
Should I sneak up on it? Damn it. Hello? Searching for repair bay error. Navigation systems failed.
Unable to comply. I think a good smack won't fix. Navigation systems operational. Optimal
path toward repair bay detected. Initiating self-diagnostics. Whoa, hey, don't you owe me
something for the repairs. Spacer's choice reminds all colonists that serving the Spacer's choice
family is the highest possible reward. I have been programmed to deliver this pre-approved message.
All right, bye. Well, that was easy. Transmit cartridge. Kill it. No, why do I kill it?
Gained its trust. Quest is to kill it. But why, but for what? I need to know why.
I don't just kill people and things for no reason. Got a pretty good shot, though. It's for the robot
takeover. You're on, I've joined the resistance. Well, I'm just gonna lie to him. Bring us honor,
soldier. You won't have to worry about that scout anymore. You beat that scout to scrap with its own
legs? Pulled its optic cables out its headcase? Actually, don't tell me. Rather use my imagination.
You're a passing, fair soldier, I will confess. 857. But you are one, and the enemy is Legion.
What you need is a new weapon, a weapon to strike fear in their cold mechanical hearts.
Cantina, lavatory, behind one of the toilets. That's where I've kept it hidden all these years.
All right. You hide your secret weapon in a bathroom. Sharp, ain't it? The lavatory is the
very last place a mechanical has need to enter. I mean, it's, it's an accurate statement.
On the double, soldier. Don't want the bartender poking around in there with a mop.
All right, level three. All right, more lying. So at 40, scramble duration plus seven seconds.
Coward duration, terrify area of effect, ranged. So what is it? Handguns at 40,
handgun critical damage. Oh, absolutely. Plus 50% long guns. All right, I need to start doing some
other shit here. Medical, right? 28, should I? Yeah, medical, stupid doctor.
Leadership. Yeah, I want to be like a dumb engineer, doctor, scientist.
Three medical, but what is the, in brackets, how is that being affected by something else?
Dumb detective doctor. It's the suit. Peter. All right, I'm going to have 10 medical because I can
use. All right. And then we're going to put the other, maybe I'll just keep doing it, do it again.
Or just do this and then a couple more. All right. Good. Good. Let's do a stupid engineer,
stupid doctor, stupid scientist. That doesn't make any sense. Stupid, fucking idiot, dumb,
fucking idiot, fucking doctor, dumb fucking scientist. All right, we're going to find the
weapon. I hope it's a one-handed weapon. Is it one-handed? The latest report. The part that
said we making our quotas. Is this the bathroom? I'm here to use the bathroom. What the fuck?
Find Ludwig's secret weapon. But what is it? Return to Ludwig. I'll be back. Nice ammo. What
do you mean? Do I have low ammo? Oh, fucking idiot scientist. Can't even get over a railing.
Give me a break. Nice frame rate. Loser. I have a 1080. Yes, I have, I have a one omega lol.
Eight omega lol. Yes. I can't wait to see it. Please spam it. I'd love for you to do it.
Bring us honor soldier. Here's the package. Feast your eyes soldier. This here is a genuine
spacers choice injury customizing unit designed to deliver a lethal blast of electrical discharge.
I call it the hand of the law. You ever want to see a mechanical flailing around like a grounded fish?
You stick a couple thousand volts in its guts with compliments from old Ludwig.
All right, so what's next? Time's come for you to journey down into the black heart of the enemy's
camp. I'm talking about the old geothermal plant. Unfortunately, the old plant lies
outside my board given jurisdiction. You'll need to get a passcode from the boss, Reid Thompson.
I get it. You want me to go undercover as a mechanical and learn their ways.
You got plucked kid. But no, can't risk having you go native. I need you to get us the brain of a
mechanical. Well, not exactly a brain. Logic module. Anatomically speaking, what we're looking for
is a logic module. If a mechanical breaks down, the logic module fries so you can't rip one out
of its corpse. You're gonna have to find an intact model somehow. Seems simple enough. If you die
horribly, I will pour out a can of zero G to your memory. Okay, you've gotten a weapon
modification install mods at a workbench to upgrade your weapons, changing damage type,
adding a scope, improving rate of fire and more. Cool. All right, well, I'm gonna I'm gonna pee.
So I'll be right back in about two minutes. See you in a sec. Something interesting to note is my
character is very stupid. So he's only done the first tutorial story mission. I've just been
walking around looking at stuff and doing side quests for an hour. It's kind of realizing that
now. All right. Uh, so what are what objective are we on right now? Die robots speak with Reid.
Ludwig wants you to head to the region's geothermal plant for an important mission,
but to gain entry to the plant, you need to get the passcode from Reid Thompson,
who runs the town of Edgewater. I also have to return to Silas. Let's do that first.
I bet your piss is cold. I think that doesn't that mean I'm dead? That means I'm not alive.
That makes no sense. Cold pee. I mean, maybe if you like pissed into the air at like,
minus 40 degrees outside, maybe grave digging is a fine profession. Always work to be had
and nary a word of complaint out of your clients. We need to talk about Eugene.
Yeah. What about him? You first. I know you buried him. Hmm. Well, yeah, it's what I'm contractually
obligated to do. What's this about? Open your mouth. Let me see your teeth. He's got solid gold teeth
could be worse up than if you pulled him out. Yeah. Funny thing. Eugene's body ain't where it's
supposed to be. That's hilarious. We were supposed to commend his body to the earth. I had his grave
all dug up and ready. Right. And so I thought I'll just rest my eyes a bit. When I woke up,
his body was gone. Life spirited away, vanished. The footprints nearby suggested that Eugene was
stolen by marauders or he rose from the dead. Okay. Let me know if you find anything about those
fees. You run into any trouble? I'm all done paperwork fees and signatures. Reliable work
from a freelancer. That's going to take some getting used to. I don't want to be bothered
here, but I went, I went out of my way for this and I'll buy you a drink sometime.
Uh, I was hoping you'd give me like something. I kind of want you the helmet. What?
You've lost Abernathy's grave. Oh, okay. I was going to say that I fucked something up.
Uh, something more tangible. Suppose you've earned it. One good turn deserves another.
Yeah. I want more than that as I'm counting the money. Oh, Abernathy was trying to hide his
illness. Am I a tattletale? Yeah. Abernathy was sick with the plague. That's disgusting.
I shook hands with the guy. He was convinced that you knew. What? No, if I knew he was sick,
I would have had him reported. I needed his fees because of his name. Hey, for Abernathy. He was
at the top of my list. You see, I think I just sentenced that guy to death. Uh, yeah. Okay,
I should go. Your reputation with the faction has changed. If enemies are hostile, but your
reputation isn't kill on sight, leaving for a few days will calm things down. Okay.
Let's keep going. So now I'm going to do die robot. Is the cash medicine completed? Okay. Let's do
this botched. You can botch missions. All right. Speak with Reed. Let's do that. Save game. Oh,
I guess if you like shoot that guy in the head, when you first talk to him, you're not going to
do his mission. All right. Up in the top edge water. Uh, 10,000 bits just came in. That was
a 10,000 from a turtle duck. That's a $100 bit drop. Thank you. Turtleduck. That's massive bits.
Let's see. What do you say here? Hey, German, watching your streams and videos for many years.
Your content is, and has been helping me get through some real tough times of dealing with
depression and anxiety. Even when everything seems like crap, your streams never failed to
make me laugh. I'm finally on the path to getting better. So I just wanted to give something back
and thank you for bringing joy to all of us. That's I'm really great. That's awesome to hear
that you're starting to get better. That's the most important thing in this whole message here.
That's great news. Thank you so much for the $100. It's never necessary to do that.
I appreciate it. Nonetheless, I wish you happy days and happy health. Thank you so much for your
insanely huge amount of monetary contributions that you just dropped. But what about the nighttime?
That too. All right. Where am I going? This music sounds like breaking bad.
Yeah, it does. That's insanely accurate. How do I get up to the, I need to go up in like an elevator
or something. Is there an elevator down here? Down the level? Jesse. No, this one right here.
Look at the map. Look at the map, Jesse. Grease monkey, Argo. I'm sorry, Mr. Thompson, sir.
You asked why it's taking so long to fix. The answer's technical. Don't apologize. Just
try using small words. Seems we've got a guest. Hi. Really now Parvati, I do wish you'd spoken up.
I do apologize. I was given no forewarning of your arrival. Look at those motocross gloves.
Are you Reed? I was told I should talk to you. You must be the town boss. I'll wait until you
finish that. You were saying Miss Holcomb. It's just what Bess needs is a proper refurbish.
I can bandage her up and what all, but she's just old. Sorry. I'm sorry. I'll, I'll do better.
And I do wish you'd stop referring to our cannery as Bess. Personification of company property is
strictly contrary to the spacer's choice code of conduct. My apologies. I am not in the habit of
allowing my guests to witness such a rowl. Now, what can I do for you? Well, you're very clearly
wearing an evil guy hat. I don't trust you because you're wearing this hat. It's that brimmed hat
that has the rounded top. If this was a little higher and squared, you'd, you're, you're a
billionaire. You're like an eccentric billionaire, but no, you're a bad guy with this hat on.
Uh, I should, that's, I, we can start with introductions. I'm didn't know. I'm not,
that's wrong. Are you Reed? I'm Reed Thompson, outpost administrator. I cannot help but notice
you are not in uniform. Shut up. Idiot. Uh, uniform. What are you talking about? Shirt,
pants, work boots, company approved colors. I looked down. I'm just naked. Honorable apparel
of a lawyer worker. Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Mr. Reed. I didn't realize. Uh, let's skip the small talk.
I've got a ship. It needs a power regulator. I think you made the wrong idea. Uh, I, I'll wait.
I need my, I need that, but I also need the, yeah, I need a- Only regulator we've got is
hooked up to the town transformer. Mr. Thompson ain't liable to be keen on dismantling it.
I beg your pardon. I am most emphatically not keen on any such thing. I can't let you have our
power regulator, but I happen to know of another one and I happen to know exactly how you may
retrieve it without frying yourself in the process. Let's hear it. There's a power regulator in the
old botanical lab. It's mostly abandoned. So all that power is being squandered. Go down to the
geothermal plant, reroute power from the botanical district over to us. Once their power shut down,
you can have their regulator and be along on your way. Wait, don't I need, I need to go here
anyways. The geothermal plant was built by our owners. Spacer's choice lit up the whole veil
once upon a time. Most of the veil is now abandoned. All that power is going to waste.
Uh, and you want all that power going to your canary. We could use the power. Canary's been
struggling. If we don't ramp up productivity, the company might cut us loose. Interesting. You're
saying the, um, saying it with an English accent. I guess you know the English. Yeah, that makes
sense. Uh, okay. I suppose that's fair. I was not entirely sure how to tell you this. The botanical
labs are not legally inhabited, but there are people who live there. Big subs. Big subs. Uh,
Aerosun, thanks for the five community subs. Thank you. Congratulations to all the new subs.
Thanks for the five. Uh, what a surprise. I never would have guessed. I'm not trying to pull one
over on you, friend. You were bound to run into them sooner or later. The people living in the
botanical labs, they're deserters, former workers. I need them back at their posts. I need them.
To come home. This book is a liar. If you want me to solve your deserter problems, I charge by the
head. No, I don't want you killing anyone. Least of all them. My hope is that by cutting off their
power, you will convince those deserters to come back to town before you go to the plant. I want
you to stop by the botanical lab. Oh, you didn't want me to their leader, Adelaide, tell her the
power's about to go and that it's time her band of deserters came back to town. What if they don't
want to come back? How will I recognize Adelaide? Adelaide's older than the other deserters.
She'll have floating text about her player model. From what I understand, her camp looks to her for
leadership. They must have left them for a reason. Why'd they go? That reason was me. I asked too much
and pushed too hard, but I am ready to make amends if they are willing to return to the fold.
We belong to one community, the Spacer's Choice family. If we dissolve into factions, then we
will all perish separately. Adelaide will understand that. I can't make any promises. Of course,
I understand completely. Here, let me give you the passcode to the geothermal plant.
A sign of good faith, for so politely listening to me as I ramble on. We got die robot. Are you
setting off for the Vale? Because I know my way around. I mean, in case you want to guide. I mean,
if that's all right with you, Mr. Thompson. Sir. I hesitate to part ways with Miss Holcomb, but I
cannot deny that she is talented and may prove useful to you. Okay, I can use the company. I don't
need help. Uh, it's just a, it's just a person that's just going to walk around with me and
shoot other enemies with me. So why not? Great. I got my wrenches and diagnosticators and hairpins
and engine tape. So I'm all set. Well, I am glad to hear that. Best of luck to you. And thank you
again for your help. It is a lot to ask of a stranger. She's just going to be walking around
going like, need ammo. Bang, bang, bang, bang. Watch it. Bang, bang, bang. She's going to take
like nine bullets. That's all it's for. She'll draw like the attack of two or three enemies while I
can shoot them. It's worth having. You've gained a companion. There are characters that join you in
your adventures and help in a variety of ways. Combat support. Their skills enhance your skills.
They increase your carrying capacity. You can unlock special companion combat abilities with
the inspiration skill. Right. Like I said, it's someone to walk around with you and just absorb
enemy attacks. Wait, I'm trying to like open his private door. Oops. I thought that was the way
out. All right. Now let's, let's go. I got it. Let's go get the logic module. Are you coming with me?
What do you have for skills? How do I check? We better clear out of Mr. Thompson's office
before we talk. I mean, you could have not said that right in front of him. Now he knows we're
going to talk about him. Save the game and shoot. I'm not, why would I do that? My character does
not have any inspiration to do that. We better clear out of Mr. Thompson's office. Are you really
that paranoid? Well, I guess maybe this cameras. Sorry. What? Can we chat? Oops. Companions. I
thought you said no. I, you just want to get out of here and you likely don't want to tag along like
me. It's just Mr. Thompson has his own view on matters on account of it's his job and what all,
but that's not the only side of the tale. That's just black masking tape over the top. There's
you can't, there's nothing. There's no visual here. You can't see through these. There's a costume.
Who's this a costume of? All right. Uh, this is about the deserters. If I wanted to deal with
nuance, I wouldn't be this heavily armed. Let's go. She's cosplaying as
Parvati from Outer Worlds. If I want to deal with this, I want to just go do the quest.
I don't really, I don't really want to talk. You're a, you're a companion right now. I'm going to,
this is probably going to be another companion in like an hour that I'm going to replace you with.
So I know you're going to tell me your entire story. I don't really want to hear it.
I mean, no, this is Mr. Thompson. The person's a gear. It does its job quiet. Like if it squeaks
or stutters, it gets replaced. The deserters are decent folk. I knew some of them before they left.
Okay. This town's got issues. I don't blame him. It's hard here, especially for them that don't fit
in so well. We're one big spacer's choice family, but every family's got the one the rest whisper about
Mr. Thompson's aiming to take away their power. They'll have no lights to see nor heat to cook.
They'll be at the mercy of marauders or worse. I think you should talk to the town's vicar about
it. Max, his name is. Okay. I'll think about it. What do we need to talk to the vicar about?
Flipping a switch in your power mill. About if what Mr. Thompson proposes to do is upright,
leaving Ms. McDevitt's folk to their fate, their neighbors, Kim. And maybe he can think of something
else to try. Something we ain't. He used to go walking outside town. Maybe he found something
that'll help. It's just an idea. That's all. I'll think about it. Should I talk to this person?
Comes now the power. Okay. Party wants to visit the town's vicar. She's a little uncertain about
the task. Where are they? Where are they? Where's the where's this person? Where are we headed?
Where are they? Tell me where they are. No, we're not going to talk later. I want to talk now
in the church. There's a church. Oh, now he wants to talk. Okay. Point of there we go.
So right there. I'm just curious. I'm just curious. I want to know what's going on.
I've always felt weird in here. It's too clean. All right, let's talk. Is it you?
Yes. What is it? You're an outsider. Fantastic. Vicar Maximilian De Soto at your service.
Or Vicar Max, if you're the sort who prefers brevity. And Ms. Holcomb as well. How rare to see
you out. And with a complete stranger. Curious. Just tagging along. Vicar De Soto.
I so rarely get new people to talk to. Name your poison. Anything at all. Spiritual counseling.
This season's tossball predictions. The quickest way out of town.
Pavarti wanted to talk to you about what Reid asked us to do. How do you know I'm an outsider?
What sort of spiritual advice do you offer here? They who are not satisfied with their work are
satisfied with nothing. No. How about work fortifies the spirit. True exhaustion awaits
idle hands. I was asking what your religion is. The OSI teaches that the grand architect set a
perfect system in motion at the beginning of time. Contentment is found by accepting one's
role in that grand plan. How much to put in a good word for me with the grand architect,
unofficial like. That's not how it works. The grand architect has no concern for us beyond
setting the plan in motion. I don't get it. Obviously. Look, if we can figure out how to
read the grand plan, we can more perfectly align ourselves to it, bringing everyone peace.
Okay. Well, first there's the matter of dumb. Oh, mega wall. And animal sacrifices.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Don't you know how stupid I am? Why would you say that?
To truly understand the metaphysics involved takes years of study and contemplation.
We've already wanted. Okay. I thought you would talk to him. What you wanted to speak to me,
Ms. Holcomb. That's not what every time I've tried to engage you in your doing at the floor,
answering single words and slink away. I can't imagine what would be so grave as to drive her
to my mission. What has Mr. Thompson asked you to do? Okay. Why? Where's the, where's go get
groceries? Number four cop power to deserters. If you could answer quickly, we're in a hurry.
I can see why that troubles you. His Holcomb has a soft heart.
Always has. If you believe the talk, can party get that treated by a saw bones.
I see today we'll be conversing without metaphors. I guess her condition is incurable.
It's unlikely to be fatal, but she may feel more heartache than most.
Could you maybe stop talking about me like I'm some kind of weird bug?
Sorry. Oh, right. Can we wrap this up? This two or three people speaking through me.
Does she have saw bones? Hey, can we wrap this up that we got weird hurry?
What do you advise? Assuming your goal is to save as many as possible,
then you should bring everyone together, send the power to Edgewater and convince the deserters to
return to the fold. Okay. Bring everyone together, send the power to Edgewater and convince the
deserters to root. So you want me to do the thing that I was told to do. Isn't that what he wants
me to do? So you want me to do that too. I'm not doing it now. I'm going to go against it.
I'm my own president. We talked to the president. We talked to the religion president. I'm my own
president. I'm doing my own thing. I'll keep that in mind. If it were as easy as a few soothing
words in the right ears, I'm sure it would have been done already. Consider it's a challenge.
If you don't mind a bit of unsolicited advice, be cautious on your way to the geothermal plant.
It is not as safe as you might assume. I've been outside. I'm not impressed. I can handle myself.
The marauders I met when I ventured outside the walls might agree with you. Would you like to come
with me and watch? Bastards snuck up on me while I was dutifully hunting for a banned book in a
collector's library. Barely escaped with my life. But you see, one of the reasons I transferred here
was to get my hands on that heretical text. Yeah, as town president, religion president,
me president. I'd pay quite a handsome sum for the book. Really? I'll assume you want to burn it
once you get your hands on it. Why would a vicar be after a banned heretical book? I just want to keep
the writing out of layman's hands. Spell crafting lying. It wouldn't do for such information to fall
into public consumption. Seems like the authorities would be interested to hear that you're after this
contraband. Maybe I'll get your book and sell it to somebody else. I can assure you, you won't
find another willing to risk imprisonment to possess this book, nor anyone willing to pay the
price I can offer. Price? Compelling argument. Glad we see eye to eye. It's a handwritten journal,
a faded blue cover with the name M. Bakunu handwritten in the lower corner. I'll mark
where I saw it on your map. Assuming you're serious? Depends how serious you are.
Yeah. Thank you. If you retrieve it, you can always find me here. What am I stuck on? The chair.
All right. Let's go. All right. Now comes the power. Let's do it. Follow me. In all capitals,
kill a fucking NPC. Holy shit. Jesus. Why? Kill an NPC. I must be fed with bloodshed.
Am I having fun? Yeah, I'm having fun. It's interesting so far. I feel like I'm just
getting started. So I don't really have, you know, we're only like two hours into the game.
That's pretty early. He doesn't want to kill people. No, I don't want to just, I don't want
to just take a, I don't want to take a dog shit on my play through. You guys want me to like
lob a grenade into that guy's office. It's like, okay. Then I just diarrhea on my fucking play
through. All right. Am I hurt? Hey, can you be like a mind detector? Can you detect minds for me?
Wait, what does X do? All right. Should I go in here? Wait, community center. No. Who's that?
Marauder. Told you. Here we go. Watch it. Wait, attack. Good. Exactly what I thought was going
to happen. She dead. Are we all right? All right. Where's the, uh, we need to loot the bodies.
Damn it. Shush. The bodies. Assault rifle. Can I give her weapons? Does she even have a weapon?
Something you need. It's a thing. All right. Let's go. I have what I have six heels.
All right. I gotta be more careful because this is on hard bit cartridge,
light ammo and a trip blade. All right. Don't just sprint everywhere. I have to walk.
Evicted. Wait, there's a house over here. I'm like 39 bullets. Everyone's dead. Assault rifle.
Makeshift low pressure suit. What's that? Give me your company. Gear in tip top shape is expected
and something you're carrying needs repair. You can repair weapons and armor at a workbench using
weapon and armor parts. Get them a breaking down on modern items. Players with engineering skill
can repair their gear without the need of a workbench. Okay. What's wrong with me?
This needs to be repaired. Okay. I have so many of these. Can I just, was this one handed?
This is two handed. I mean, I could just use this even though, I mean, it's, that's so much more
damage to inspect. Um, how do I repair this? Armor management. No. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm breaking down inspect them. All right. What's this? Three armor, four armor, nine armor.
That's pretty good. Tech skills plus five. Compare it. Okay. Yeah, this is better. What does this
thing do? Stealth skills. Okay. Consumables here. You can use junk or drop your consumers.
Your emergency medical inhaler shown at the top of the screen. It uses Adreno as fuel. Sure.
Increase your medical skills will unlock more drug mixing slots. They can hold all types of
consumables, not just Adreno. Each slot is mixed into every puff of the inhaler for a combined
effect. Adreno. Wait, I can breathe in like bread. How do you inhale bread? Okay. Well, that's,
I only have one slot anyways. Modifications. Range weapon mod. Magazine changes the weapon's damage
type to shock. Okay. How do I use this? General. All right. How do I, um, how do I use this stuff?
I have to use a workbench. Okay. Right. Has to be on a workbench. All right. That's good to know.
Let me test out this right, this weapon. Uh, she's not gonna be able to cross that.
I didn't even go in this building. There's not much ammo in it. No. Ooh. Can I open this? I'm
not smart enough to open this. Evicted or can I go in? Shit. I can't open these.
Sleep. Dervish mist. That clone or something. Money. Noodles. Breathe that stuff in. Bin. Okay.
All right. So we sleep. Sleep for, no, don't sleep. Resting in a bed is relaxing and moves time
forward and in supernova difficulty, you can only rest in your bed on your ship. That way.
Oh, that's probably terrible. Sleep for a week. He's not killing everyone. Get mad.
Yeah. Get mad. I'm not killing everyone. Move along stranger. We don't want any trouble.
Well, you have a sniper rifle and we're standing right next to each other. So
I'm at the advantage. I don't know you. Whatever you're looking for. It ain't here. Move along.
I'm looking for Adelaide. I need answers. Answers, huh? You must be one of those
philosophicals. Already got ourselves one of those. I'm looking for the geothermal plant.
Reed says something about former workers living out in the wilderness. Why would I? No, don't bring
up Reed. They don't, they probably hate Reed. Where's the plant? A geowhat? Look, plants eat
my purview. You're bitter off asking after Adelaide. Just dealing with an imbecile here. Dealing with
idiots. I'm at, I'm of an intelligence level higher than this. You don't know what a geothermal
plant is? Wow. Unbelievable. Do you? No. But I can pretend to. We've all got problems.
Lady named Zoe went missing some nights ago. Just up and vanished without a trace.
The quick turn. Now I'm pacing around wondering if marauders got to her. I'll go look.
I'll keep an eye out. It's not like Zoe to go wandering. Figured she might be out scavenging,
but that ain't exactly her talent. Can't imagine where she's gone.
Hale's a wide place. She could be anywhere.
Wow. Holy shit, that's horrendous. Could do without the gallows humor.
All right, where is it? This is a deserter. If you're hungry, Stefan's got supplies.
So do you. Oops. Oh no, you, oh no, okay. And I want to sleep in your bed. Thief. No, I, look,
I'm only a thief when I can't be seen doing it. That sounds pretty good. All right. Chicken.
If you're hungry, there's meat turning on the spit outside. If you're bearing illness,
find a place to lay your head down and I'll fetch you a poultice.
Whatever your troubles. Can you pet chicken? No. Leave them at the gates and be welcomed here.
Any questions, dear? What's that smell? That'd be the garden, dear. You're standing
in a garden. Also fertilizer. So mind your boots. Excuse me, Ms. McDevitt. Sorry. It's just,
you got such pretty trees in here. Why thank you. You're Robert's girl, aren't you?
I remember when you were but a sprout. Thomas speaks of you often. I want attention. Talk to
me. You should try some of my tobacco. That's my game. I brew it in an old spittoon,
but it's been cleaned. Uh, it looks like you made a home for yourself here. A home for anyone who's
ever turned their backs on Edgewater. A home for those of us with nowhere left to go and nothing
to lose. So like the spores of the puff ball cast on the wind and a lighting on fresh soil,
we put down new roots. That's too dumb. Even if you were dumb, you wouldn't save this.
My goodness. All right, you just charming. You have to do the tuber choice. Uh,
I was sent to make peace with you. Reed Thompson, you here on behalf of that cold-eyed reptile?
Let's hear it. What's Reed's idea? He's a lizard? I didn't know that. Oh, you're living off power
that belongs to the town. Come back to the cannery. That's about it. Reed asks you to
consider coming back to town. He's willing to make amends. Something about coming back to town or
losing power. I wasn't really listening. I can't say I blame you. Reed is positively soporific.
Like everything else that comes out of Edgewater, that peace offering is canned.
I and my own are living just fine out here by ourselves.
This is serious. I'm about to cut off your power. This is serious. You're doing this for Reed.
For money. For money. Money. Your camp has a power regulator. I needed to repair my ship.
Seemed like the right thing to do. My reasons are my own. Just like my Twitter profile. It's
in my biography when you go to my Twitter. If you're going down to the plant, you should
divert power away from Edgewater and toward our end of the grid. Think about it. You'd be liberating
an entire town from a lifetime of service to that odious cannery. Seems the sort of thing a hero
would do. Hero to you maybe. I'm looking for a power regulator. Reed promised me yours.
Cannery's got a regulator. You want ship parts, you ought to rip them out of the cannery's guts
and leave us be. Let's say I help you. What happens to Edgewater? Life in Edgewater grinds
to a halt. The cannery shuts down. Workers desert in droves and our own little camp grows and thrives.
Y'all doing drugs here? Like you doing drugs? Because I trust you will listen to your conscience.
Vivardi, what should we do? Where are we headed? I don't know. You tell me.
You mean about the mission being too clean? Might as well leave. All right, so we got
a long gun. What's a long gun? A sniper? What do I want here? 60. Dialogue. I want to be able to lie
better. Is it assault rifles? At 20, medicine. I love the second drug mixing slot. Improve your
weapons and armor in the workbench. Okay, I want that second slot. Yep, that looks good. A new perk.
I have one perk point. Vendor prices. I'm just going to steal whatever I can't buy. So what's
the point? You take better care of your weapons and armor than most people. That's probably good.
Or a faster sprint. Damage when alone in a party plus 25% damage when alone. Goodbye.
Sprint is really good though. Yeah. Yeah, faster sprint speed. That's true.
All right. Let's do... First, let's get this shit out of the way.
I can neither divert the power to Edgewater or I can not divert the power to Edgewater.
We have to make a decision. Look, if I'm going to give you power, then I may as well take all the
money. Because, I mean, look, that's fair. I do the really dangerous mission and I sacrifice
myself and make it so you get power diverted to you. But I take all the money in your houses.
That's fair. Zoe's journal. Well, today's the day, Zoe. Today is the day you take your destiny in
your own hands. I've been listening to Grace talk about the Marauder threat. Bands of wild
free-spirited bandits living in camps out in the hills. Barrel fires probably mounted the heads
of their enemies on spikes as a warning to people like me. Three of any rules. I bet they could take
the whole region. I've been talking away some of our food. I've come to some spare cans of tuna.
It should last me a couple weeks. So you went there willingly. I got odds those Marauders will let
me throw in with them if I dangle a couple syringes of Adrena time before their eyes.
This is going to be great. Bandit Queen Zoe's origin story has just begun. I'm going to have
a whole gang of Marauders at my back. Maybe I can even score some Rizzo's. Well, that's new info.
What about this? No more edge water for me. No more cannery. No more jumpsuits and gloves.
Yes, ma'ams. And would you like another? I don't know why I'm writing this down for
prosperity's sake. Fuck the cannery. I don't think I'll ever have to look back in this journal. Who
cares? I'm going to go be a Marauder. And so I got sick. Everybody gets sick. Well, okay. I got sick
and I grabbed a little too much Adrena time. Is that really a crime? Got to treat myself when I'm
sick, don't I? What have I happened to personal responsibility in surviving by one's own bootstraps?
Oh, but you misappropriated one box of Adrena time and you suddenly you're committing larceny.
Pet chicken, pet chicken, pet chicken. All right. What about let me take a look at this stuff here.
We're going to die robot, which is over here. This is in the town or it's down in the do I have to
go back down there? Isn't like the lab, wasn't it? Let me see the geothermal plant in the northwest
portion of the region. So no, it's out of here. Let's go do this first. Is there a way I can
leave here quickly? Oh, he used to follow me around. Workbench. Wait. No, that's just a
regular bench. Where's workbench? There it is. Get out of my way. All right. Let's do this one.
Install installed modifications. Install. This is a shock weapon. Modify light pistol with the mag
to zap. Mods can't be recovered after installation. If you install this modification of this slot,
the current one will be destroyed. No, wait, what's in it now? Magazine size plus 50%.
What's going to make the DPM, the damage permitted up? Yeah, let's do it. Fuck it. So wait,
now I can do this. Wait, where to go? Is that it? No modifications. Magazine zero. Oh, it's
damaged. Okay. How much does it take to repair? Repair is E. It takes more damage. Oh, eight.
Yo, I only have 21 weapon parts. Where's the other pistol though? Am I out of my mind?
Wasn't it? Didn't I have two pistols to modify? Oh, this is the companion's weapons. How do I
take these from you? Can I take these? I need this. All right. Give me this. All right. Let me
prepare. How do I take stuff from you? Inventory. General. Quests. Junk. Can I go to her inventory?
Click her name at the top. Uh, what do you mean her name at the top? Junko. Where? Oh my God. It's
like another, I thought it was going to be like another inventory. Okay. Here's the companion.
I didn't know it was going to be like on the menu. I thought it was going to be like up here,
like inventory, like, oh, Pavardi's menu. Whatever. Give me this. Okay. How do I take it off?
Here. I'll take this instead. I have to replace it with something. Take the machine gun. Give me
this back. Actually give me this too. You take this shitty stuff. I want your stuff. Okay. Good.
There we go. Now it's good. Can I make ammo or anything? Okay. Repair. I don't need to do that.
Tinker. What's tinker? Just make you do more damage? Tinker. Yeah, let's do it. You want to
tinker the light pistol? Yeah. Tinker it again. Tinker it again? Yeah. No. That's good. Let's break
this shit down. Uh, break down. What do you got? This crap. Yeah, this is a bunch of crap. Get rid
of it. Junk. Crap. All right. I think I'm good. Nice. Now this thing does more damage and it's
a shock weapon. I've already used your favorite companion. That's cool. Save the game. Let's go
get that thermonuclear fast driving car. All right. Let's go. Wait. I can go this way. It's still a
light pistol. Oh, Megalo. Well, whatever. You can laugh. I'm not. Should I not go this way?
Do I have no life regen? No, I do. It's very slow though. What about my food? Oh, okay. Apples.
Cool. You can level up the health regen. That's not a bad idea. Oh, fuck off. I knew you're going
to make it. Whoa. Attack. That thing is, there are five damage types. Physical plasma, corrosion,
shock, and enray. Some enemies are horrible, but yes, I know. Shock is better. This thing
has a lot of health. How do I revive? All right. Let's go. Ooh, helmet. Salt rifle. A small
percentage of weapons and armor you find are considered pristine. They have more durability
and they're just really cool. Good to know. What do we got here? Hack. Ooh, can I hack it?
I need four hacking devices. That's a lot of stuff. Sawed off shotgun. A sight. Damn it. All right.
Dumb to hack. Let's sneak. Oh, fuck. There's a lot of people. All right. Is there like a
Maylake Hill? Can I sneak up on these guys and like just let their mechanical throats?
Just go out there. Why are you just going out there? You just keep, you continue to die. I only have,
how many bullets do I have? Not very many. Ooh, flywheel? Bits. Doctor. Another light pistol.
This is a hundred DPS. All right. Well, here we go. This is it. The light pistol sucks, Boomer.
I hope we're doing the right thing. Oh, who cares? All right. Vending machine. A hack skill of 20 or
higher allows you to sell items to the vending machine. Cool. You can have high rep to sell
restricted items. All right. So what do we got? Tarmac and cheese. I need bullets. Light ammo.
Yeah. Let's get some light ammo. Buy the maximum. 50 out of 50. What is this? How many of these
should I get? Five? Sell. Only 9.4 dollars? Well, I can sell this because I don't need it.
Can I not sell? Oh, is this restricted or something? Where's the sell? Sell all. Don't want to click
that. Buy and sell items with bits. The official currency. You have not unlocked the ability to
sell to vending machines. Oh, I thought, I thought I was only a certain level or something. Oh,
fucking whatever. What? Damn it. Almost. Why did it slow him over that? Can't do it yet. Use terminal.
Unlock the door. Warning, this facility is in a state of lockdown. Authorization passcode required.
Enter passcode. Uh, welcome. R. Thompson. Personal files. Personal log. That whole head. Found him
fiddling around with one of the mechanicals, so I had to write him up for tampering with company
property just in case. I'm reading this a couple days from now and feeling bad for what I've done.
Let me just remind myself that I've warned him before. Okay. Personal logs. Doesn't sit right
with me. The company's never been wrong before. The company's been replacing our guards with
auto mechanicals. This right here, I'm going to end up a chief of security with no staff.
Okay. Uh, worse has happened. Mechanicals gone crazy. Lock myself down here. Just trying to
gather my courage. Gonna make a mad dash with the control room. Might be able to shut things down.
Greeting security chief S. Tanaka. This is an automated message initiated by Spacer's Choice
Worker Safety Contingency Protocols. Security lockdown has been initiated. This is not a test
of your behavior during this lockdown. Will be reviewed during your quarterly audit. Anxiety
is a common side effect of life-threatening situations. Fight back against anxiety with an
ice cold bottle of zero G brew. Zero G brew and ale. That's good for what ails you. I can add.
All right. The door is open. There's already people coming here. Under attack.
That's, uh, where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? I think it's flying. Just take
everything. I can sort it out later. Necklace. Can I sell that? Speed grip? Well, I can't sell
it to a vending machine, but can I, can I sell it to a person? Like a town's person? Do I have to
have, do I have to hack a person's brain to sell them a weapon? Okay. Let's go. All right. You go
Z. Right there. Hold Z is what does that do? Oh, X, Z. I'm on my way. Enemy kill. How much stuff can
I even carry? I hear a noise. I hear an organic sounding noise, not a mechanical sounding noise.
Use. What the hell did that do? Do I, did I just divert power? What did I just do? Did I
divert power to the, what did I just press? I hope I didn't just like do anything.
Self diagnostics complete. Navigation systems operational. Combat systems
operational. It's not the best choice. It's the spacer's choice. Okay. Why are you not attacking
me? Hostile actions towards spacers choice. Mechanics are contrary to logical directive.
Conclusion. All hostile auto-mechanicals must be defective in compliance with spacer's choice
policy. You know what's going on. All defective auto-mechanicals must be permanently dismantled.
Please allow me to assist. All right. Affirmative. Mechanicide protocols loaded. Awaiting
confirmation. Yeah. Confirmation granted. I like the sound of that. Go for it. Go take out all
those mechanicals that are bad. Repair log. Corporate just sent a team of technicians to
conduct a complete refit of all of our mechanicals. Lore. I did routine maintenance. Found some strange
modifications to their logic modules. Somebody fucked with them and made them aggressive.
Filed the report, but my supervisor told me not to worry about it. Said the company knew
what it was doing. What did we forget about any alleged modifications?
I wrote this down so somebody would see it. Got my hands on a logic module. Time to do a little
bit of experimentation. Did you know? Borrowed a copy of the Young Spacer's Guide to Mechanical
Engineering. I think it's volume three. I need something to read down in the pit.
Pit. Okay. Logic module. Guy's down in the pit. Hop in pit. You're not real. You're not real.
He's in the pit. Where is he? Is that thing going to go kill him? All right. Where are you?
He's just down here?
Thanks for the input. Got to get it right in the belly button. Get it! Engineering 15. Shut off
the steam valve. Scientist. Oh, is it workbench? Yeah, I know about mods. Weapons and armor can be
modified. Mods can't be removed once they're used, so put them on your favorite gear. Right. All
right. So this is the Zapper. 173 damage. What can I do with this? I can't do anything. I can't do
anything. 173 damage. What can I do with this? No mods. Oh, I can. Oh, it's a scope. Should I
put a scope on a shotgun? Would that be stupid? Okay, this is gyrocyte. Spread is reduced. I mean,
yeah, this thing's pretty good. I'm probably going to use it. Whatever. This is a better scope. It's
better saturation. I'm just pretending I know what I'm talking about. All right, so let me equip that
instead. Doesn't need to be repaired. This is what I'm currently wearing. All right, what can I,
can I do something with this? All right, this needs to be on here. No, no, wrong. Is the one
that I just modified? This one. I guess I can just put it on. Let's try it. Cool. I'll try it. All
right, we're looking for that. There was a guy that was screaming. All right. Where's the
screaming? Oh, shit. Where are they? Where is it? Let me eat some food. Oh, fuck. That was actually
pretty scary. Okay. All right. I'm here. Ammo. Save it. This is too scary. Turn it off.
All right. This is where I shit on the ground. All right. All right. So that guy, where was that
guy? There was a guy like screaming. Is he up there? Security chiefs. Wait, why is him?
Security chiefs corpse. Wait, I don't think I want to use this on a locker.
No, Mr. Ouch. All right. Hold on a second. Do I, why do I have two different markers?
There's that one and then there's this one. Why are there two markers? One of them is for
move mouse over the markers to see where they are or what they are. I mean, I'm on the wrong
floor. How do I move the map up? Objective. Objective. Is this for the same objective though?
Oh, did I get baited? Oh, well. All right. Well, I'm just going to go back up here.
Aim at the markers in the world. Security chiefs corpse and logic module. Right. Because the guy
that's screaming. All right. Let's get the module. It's behind this though. How the fuck do I get in
there? Should I not be shooting you? Wait, was this the thing I activated? The corpse has the key.
I guess I could like pick the lock though. All right. Security officers corpse. I need to get
up here and down this way. So what's the correct way to go this way? I have to go up the stairs
around somehow over here and then up, I guess. I don't know this. I turned on the fucking
ooze elevator. So I guess I'm going to go. You're not real. Is there a way to go up? This is it.
This is going down. Damn it, man. This is the thing that I repaired. It's killing this guy.
It's killing him. Just kill it. No. Load save. Load save. Load save. Where is it? Which one is it?
Quick save. Quick save. Auto save. This one at 319 right here. All right. Come with me.
So I have to go all the way. I have to go down and then up. Where did he just put me?
I have to go back to that pit. All right. So wait, hold on. You're right here. Give me the key card.
Thank you. And give me your machine gun. Fine. That was hidden behind a fucking block. All right.
Now let's go over here. Spard. I can't open. What? Module. Let's go. Tactical shotgun. All right.
Pretty cool. Okay. Now I got die robot. Head back to the landing pad and deliver the logic module
to Ludwig. Got it. I got a shotgun too. Now it's either divert power or divert power. I mean,
now which one of these am I going to do? How far away is this one? It's far. All right. Let's get
out of here. Who do I want to save? What city do I care about? This is a very good question.
Pole? No, I'm going to, I'll make a decision. I mean, why am I leaving? What about the guy at
the bottom of the pit? I guess there was the guy there. Maybe I'll go look for that guy. Save him.
All right. So I got to go to the pit. He's down here. You hear him screaming. What was the way
to go? Should I just go down? What are these things even for? This is probably some other
quest or something that I didn't get before coming in here. I'm assuming. I don't know.
All right. So where's that pit? Where's the pit? Right in the middle,
back around this way and down the hall. That's the pit I'm assuming. Should I just go this way?
And down. Okay. I have to find a way down to you. I'm coming. I'm coming down.
I'll be there in a minute. For a second I thought this was the guy from the beginning of the game.
Phantoms where? You can talk? The phantoms never talked before.
I knew I shouldn't have eaten that Sprat raw. See? See Higgins? This is why you must always boil
your Sprats before ingesting. Higgins. This phantoms got a name. All right. Slow down. What's
going on? Clearly I mistook you for one of the phantoms of my imagination which terrorized me
on occasion. Chester D. Higgins. The D stands for definitely not insane. I use it as a reminder.
How long have you been down here? Hard to say. By my reckoning Higgins has been here somewhere
between two weeks and forever. My recollections a touch fuzzy these days. Okay. Oh Higgins has
been many things over the years. Sprat Wrangler, Saltuna Critic, Aether Wave Personality,
Chairman of the Board, Galactic Defender, Sissy Pig Tycoon. I've come a long way for someone who
started off as a simple engineer right here in this plant. Oh you. We have that in common. You
and I are both engineers. I specialized in auto-mechanicals, drones, sentries. That's a good
talking point. Peridum maintained, upgraded. Did it all from my old workroom just over in the next
section. Okay. Right was that before or after you became a Sissy Pig Tycoon? How do you stop? Look
I don't want to fall into any trouble with the mechanicals. If they wise up to our plans they
will come for us with prodding irons. I'm not afraid of any mechanicals. I can't even spell
mechanicals. Or you can help me and I won't feed you to the Sprats. Your call. Why 46? Spacer's Choice
sent me here to rescue you. You can trust me. Dumb and persuading is the way. You know you remind
me of myself back when I was an intergalactic adventurer. I discovered a flaw. Their hostility
levels were hardwired to maximum. There's no changing that but you could rewrite their targeting
protocols so they attack each other instead. No wonder they're so angry. Somebody messed around
with their logic modules. Yes that's exactly it. I see you're also versed in the noble art of
mechanical engineering. That wasn't dumb that was just engineering. There's a behavior control
terminal in the other room. It should have options to change how the mechanicals act
including whom they shoot at. Oh that reminds me you'll need my passcode to access the behavior
control terminal. Here let me just write it down. Okay. The tail. Definitely start with the tail.
If you're feeling adventurous the ears are a particular delicacy. Actually hang on. Forgot
what you were gonna say? Me too. Time to divert power. Uh just go fuck yourself I don't care
anymore. All right uh let's take your impact hammer because it's mine now and your lubricant
is mine. Okay do I want to save the botanical garden place or do I want to save the uh the high
taxes workers are made out of gold bars? I don't know. I'm not sure what I want to do.
How do I need to go? Reprogram the bots so they don't attack you. Did I already do that?
I did it to one of them. Uh what is it? Long tomorrow? No no no no no no. Am I going the
right way here? Do I have to like wrap back around? What was that power room?
What is it? Another one. Save the capitalists. I don't know what I'm gonna do. I have no idea
what I'm gonna do. Here we go. Do I just flip a coin? Should I let fate decide? Maybe I should
let fate decide. Redirect power. Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait did I just do it? I didn't
get a choice. Safety failures detected. High likelihood of moderate or severe structural
damage. Redirecting power is an irreversible procedure. Power redirection functions failed.
Manual override required. Please activate all three electrical track switches. What? Oh it's
those things those things I have to activate. Oh god the goo tanks. Yeah of course you're gonna
put me on a mission where I have to go activate the goo tanks. I should have just done them.
Where is this one? Over here. Got it. Okay flip a coin. Go to go to random.org and just type in
two and then press enter 50 times and then whatever it is. Once we do this there's the
Hey mister. Whoa. Look I know you want your power regulator and all. She's like wait don't do this
I'm not gonna talk to you. Do you understand what you're about to do? I know exactly what I'm doing.
Well what's your opinion? I don't think you should cut off Edgewater's power. I think it would be
cruel. Well. I'm sorry that just sort of came out all at once. Didn't she want me to do anything?
We've been losing workers year after year and corporate hardly ever sends replacements.
There's barely enough salt tuna to fill our bellies anymore but the town's got some good
people in it. Decent hard-working folk just living their lives the only way they know how.
They don't deserve to be punished. Well this isn't like Fallout 3. I'm not I'm not like nuking a city.
I'm just turning their power off. I'm just I'm just turning off their power temporarily and then
we'll figure it out. Okay Reid tells me Edgewater is going to die without workers in power. The
deserters are a community. I can't just destroy what they built. I think I'm ready to make my
decision. Sorry I didn't mean to babble off like that. I just I felt like I had to say something.
That's where it's way here. Don't worry about it. I was barely listening to you. Oh well okay then.
I made that really clear that I was very heavily listening. I'm like I'm a dick. All right here we
go. Redirect power. Safety failures. Are you sure you want to continue? Redirecting power is an
irreversible procedure. Redirect power to Edgewater. Redirect power to Botanical Laboratory.
I've got I've got my Nivea lip balm. If it lands heads is no no I'm gonna okay is it weird that
I'm just going by how much I liked traversing the town. It has nothing to do with any of the stuff
going on. It's just which town do I think is more interesting to be like walk around in.
The power regulator is now safe to remove from Botanical Laboratory. Edgewater Saltuna
Canary power regulator is now operating at optimal capacity. All right I did it. We did it.
Now give me the power regulator. Thank you. Where is it? Give me this stuff first.
Ah it's behind a door. Hold on. Access the files. Access the files. Open the door.
Where is the open door code? I don't know. Oh I don't even need one. Vending machine.
No I'm good. I'm good. Wait where's the power? Where is it? Triggered the power regulator? Is it
outside? Jerma you literally would have to only have two conversations to make the deserters
come back and then Edgewater gets better. Uh thanks for the advice person who's played
through the game already. Appreciate it. And he's wrong is he? I don't know. Wait a minute. All
right so uh where's the uh oh I have to go actually to the lab and go get it. Oh I don't
want to do that. I don't like that. I have to go I have to go into the place that I just destroyed.
I don't want to do I can't just like there's not a core that I just take
from inside the lab that's I don't like this. I'm currently I'm the I'm stuck in the like person
zoo here. You can't just text them to break up. Right but are they gonna be hostile? It's all
right. I'll just lie. Do I can I put my lie to 50 so I can just tell them I didn't do it?
Their power got diverted somehow and I'm just coming to check on them. You got your lights
are still on you're fine. No that's not a good that guy's got a rifle. Yeah I know I'm trying
to think. F***ed up what happened. I know I heard the news. It's okay everybody keeps staring at me.
It's not my fault the power's dead. Yes it is. You did it. This person did it. Whoa
Miss Parvati. Who's this person here? Hey you're uh what um how are you huh hi hi hello
are you uh that's the beginning of every one of my streams how you keeping that's how every intro
starts great just great I've been trying to keep stuff running just like you only I'm not so wait
they didn't kick you out did they oh gosh no I'm just along with this fella here I've seen you
wandering around here you don't look like you're coming from town I'm just trying to get my ship
off the ground never heard it phrased in such a way before I guess we're all trying to get our
ships off the ground ain't we sorry I just wasn't sure if you were from town or if you were one of
us something's been chewing at me you see what's wrong fact is I've been well lying to everybody
here camp thinks I'm a mechanical genius but I couldn't fix a busted chair don't tell them I
like this okay I like this guy uh never too late to start learning I can give you a couple
pointers we could both be lying idiot engineers I'll take all the help I can get I set my mind
to learning the craft of the engineer you see I want to make something of myself you ever heard
of the young spacer's guide to mechanical engineering comes in a set of three if I had
my hands on one of those data pads I could teach myself the ins and outs those are good
my dad kept a copy with him when he was working in the cannery I know the old community center
kept the copy should find another one back in town if you could find me even one of those pads
I'd be greatly obliged one give me money too I'll pay you for every pad you bring me
if by some miracle you can bring me the full set I'll give you something pretty I've been
saving for a lucky day okay what about the third one I wish I knew I wagered the town
at the full set once upon a time where the third's gone I can't say would you I'd be grateful but
wait you oh you're gonna have to go to the town right you're gonna have to go to edge the I don't
remember the name of the town I swear to god edge don't tell me I'm not I'm not gonna let this
fuck me up edge stone hedge stone edge edge
edge uh what was it called edge hall edge edge wood is it edge wood edge water
edge water right you're all gonna be an edge water soon oh wait this is I get to just take
their power that's the thing about growing old your eyes start to fail elsewise I would
have seen you for the snake that you are chopped you into pieces and roasted you on a spit
this is all you're doing cutting off my power killing off my garden without refrigeration
my food will spoil and my flock will starve I want to ask you this in private away from the
I didn't call myself a snake tell me why did you do it lie give me a lie damn it
this isn't personal Adelaide I need your power regular I don't know I like pressing buttons I
guess are you really this moronic or are you just putting on airs listen here whole head I'm only
gonna say this once go talk to grace and Thomas look them in the eye and tell them their life
here is over and the only thing left to do is go back to edge water this is now your responsibility
and you tell Reid Thompson that I will never return to edge water I would rather die among
my flowers than live under his management different scenario what if I go back and kill
Reid Thompson and then you I I take over the town and I'll be nice to everybody
you offering the cross read off huh this some sort of twisted reparation for what you've done
wait what I can do this looking for a chance to sow some chaos kill Reid if you must what
talk him into leaving if you can he and I are not sharing the same four hold on am I doing a double
cross on a double cross kill Reid if you must what happened to you all this anger had to come from
my son worked in that cannery when the plague started coming he was one of the first to fall
sick we had a store of medicine locked away but Reid refused to treat him said my boy didn't
deserve treatment said the medicine would have been wasted on him yeah so we get rid of the bad
guy we unify everybody and I run the place my belongings and left that's as much of the story
as you need to hear Reid isn't just gonna all right yeah fine
from Edgewater okay I think we got a deal okay guys look you know I got good news and bad news
food's bound to spoil at this rate look the good news is that you have to leave what happened the
bad news is that I'm gonna kill Reid and I'm gonna be your boss no other way reverse that
marauders can't see us in the dark wild canids on the other hand uh go back to Edgewater the
matter's been weighing on me I'm staying put until I know what's become a zoe oh don't even please
don't want that question haunting me all the way back to the cannery I don't want to do that quest
really I have to do that who else do we need I need to convince somebody else
who else do I have to convince I don't know how much longer we'll I don't know how much
I don't know how much longer we'll keep your wits about you keep your wits about you
keep your wits about you stop copying each other clearly you heard her say that keep your wits
about you keep your wits about you keep your wits about you I don't know how much longer
will last without power thank you any luck finding one of those manuals go back to Edgewater
I've been thinking about going back I'm not much used to anybody here I get sick thinking about
working at the cannery I can't do that again don't worry I mentioned those manuals on mechanical
engineering oh come on suppose if I had one of those I could go back to Reed and make a real case
for myself all right let's go get Zoe you can't be far right only 340 only 343 feet kill Reed first
well I need the power regulator kill Reed then kill her
both they'll go kill come back wow you did it yep uh that's just absolute chaos all right so
hold on I'm not gonna touch anything I'm gonna go get rid of Reed uh let's go get her to Reed
fuck I'm a man of my word I'm a man of my word temporarily right so I'm gonna go get rid of
Reed I'm gonna come back I did that I told you I was gonna do that and I did I also come up with
new ideas on the fly all the time and second idea is get rid of you too it's temporarily all right so
Reed now what if I tell Reed about the plan that I'm coming to kill him could I double cross the
double cross and then double cross her and then come back and just double cross again
can I just bounce back and forth what's going on oh wait wait wait wait who are these people
outside this town what just happened why are they on the fucking main road I just got double
crossed just fast travel fast travel didn't exist 100 years ago so no okay you know it comes
a time when you have to understand that they're just in here oh cool take the money out of the
register I you did that I didn't holy shit you're stealing I didn't do it have you been watching me
I gotta make some armor stuff
necklace so I can sell this shit too wait I'm going in I'm going in trespassing lockpicking
hacking and murder are all considered illegal activities avoid being seen if you want to
engage in these activities this place more rotters tomato juice light ammo salt rifle
all right well this you got a lot of stuff here I don't think it was worth it though
okay let's keep going that's all right it'll heal okay all right read
got it inside voices his head show me his head oh fuck you didn't do anything actually I did it
you watched it was me I did it okay all right read I'm not even gonna mess around I'm just
not sure I even talk to him or should I just go in there and just just get him can't talk
to a dead guy did you get it all right all right all right read we're in that tower
yeah all right read he keeps saying all right read all right listen read all right read
but what happens when I do they are they gonna know I killed him what if I kill him and then
just drop him outside the window so it looks like he fell backwards through the glass and tripped
and like broke through the glass this is a fine day friend power flows through our town like a
cool stream of water I trust Adelaide's people have seen their way to reason
so when can I expect them back at their posts I spoke to Adelaide she won't come back as long
as you're here I delivered your message but I haven't convinced Adelaide to come back
let me ask you something go ahead have you taken a look around your town lately it is my job to
keep two eyes on my town I am the steward of this place and this is my watch post your town's
fallen apart Rick I wish you wouldn't say things like that you know okay I'm thinking real
thinking real hard about it I expect you wouldn't understand you don't see the town as I do when I
stand at my window and look out over my so do it now here's what I see I see decent loyal hard
working people I see a family we are all part of the spacers choice family we are all doing what
we were brought into this world to do this is a spacer's choice town we're all part of the
spacers choice family here the company keeps us warm keeps us fed keeps us working loyalty has
got nothing to do with it this is good old-fashioned gratitude how long have you worked here for I'm
trying to remember 25 years 26 when you get to my age the years just rush by you stop counting
all together I remember looking out this window and seeing the veil spread out from horizon to
horizon we were a sprawling town people change but the veil will always be here spacers choice
will always be here our work won't ever end I take comfort in that how do I kill them without
you guys knowing you some sort of freelancer what was your last break I appreciate what you've done
for us I spoke to Adelaide she won't be coming back as long as you are here then we are at an
impasse stewardship over this town has been entrusted to me by spacers choice I am not perfect
I have made my share of mistakes but I have done my best for this town the town's terrified of
plague everybody asked me to steal medicine for him you let Adelaide's son die her son got sick
with plague a couple years back company never gave us enough medication to treat the whole town
so I had to choose you see Adelaide's child or someone else's she's never forgiven me I don't
expect she ever will shit shit shit oh no no no no we're getting we're getting bad guy exposition
actually is not bad guy make you make wire maybe it's time for you step down I'm a spacers choice
man my father was a spacers choice man Edgewater may not look like much to some buttoned up
freelancer but it is my home and you made fun of me attack well I tried what do I say that attack
why do you think about this I gotta think about this what a great time to learn about companion
perks killed who mr. Thompson Reed Thompson you know my boss I can't who I need to leave I need
to get away from here I need to get away from you no no no no no no no Reed was you can't get lost
don't take this the wrong way or anything but I don't ever want to see you again when she goes
she can't just teleport out that's the bad end oh hold on let me see what's hidden let me see
what's in Reed's personal like weapons stash holy shit I'll take it she knows too much welcome
our Thompson from our he sends himself an email if you're reading this then I'm no longer the
outpost administrator for Edgewater whether through the shedding of my mortal coil for
natural causes or through early retirement passed on somebody else you most importantly
it is imperative that you keep the spacers choice family together Adelaide McDevitt and
her followers have taken camp in the old botanical lab their place is here working with us
Adelaide is impervious to reason and refuses to entertain diplomatic overtures the only way to
introduce her and come back is by heading the plant cutting of power and leading her people
back to Edgewater with the power shut off the can like really okay I'm corporate your request
for additional building materials has been denied the walls around Edgewater were built 30 years
ago by my predecessor sir any authorations expansions repairs to this wall must be signed
and approved by your predecessor if you pray if your predecessor is your responsibility to obtain
the last will and testament demonstrating your predecessor's intentions so wait is she gone
I can't even get the hat no that was just like an end the moment like get away get away get out of
here I didn't it's in his storage oh fuck it's a hat get lost but are they gonna tell everybody
I gotta put the hat on now because I'm you now nine armor was his four nine what's this one do
it's a helmet can I just have a helmet I can have two helmets on no this is better now I'm the
villain she's not gonna come back well shit I think I have to sleep in this bed I yelled at her I have
a hat though yeah uh what I wanted to do let's get this to 50 or 60 what I want 40 more lying
yeah okay activate it uh yeah I know I I don't I don't think I can reload that would that's
cheating I I said what I said I said get lost because yeah and I think that's cheating in a
game that way you have choices that you have to make I feel like reverting on one of those choices
is kind of going against the nature of the game that's the only likable character in the game
is that true that can't be true all right I've delivered reads message so what do I want to do
now let's see if I can find Zoe find three volumes companion max says the journal was
wait a minute hold on companion that guy's a companion oh shit hey well we get a new friend
oh man that's fucking funny all right let's go get this uh this book kill them both I still
haven't decided what I'm gonna do I'm contemplating give me a rock for cover how do I know when they're
all dead I wish I had my companion that says that's the last of them she'll be back she'll be back
all right here we go all right time for a new guy we're gonna have a new companion
are you ready we're gonna get the priest he probably has magic powers I just got the
letter today corporate ordered me to relocate to the edgewater cannery effective immediately
it's a shame I was really looking forward to running my own gift shop at the community
center selling rare memorabilia but scripture tells us that all things happen for a reason
work fortifies the spirit and all as for my book collection I can't bear to part with it
don't want those books malding in some contraband lunker like chat currently is over the loss
of their favorite character who they deem to be the only likable person in the game
but I find that to be an untrue statement so I stashed them all the way in a cave by the river
no I didn't do that to chat members I stashed the books I died through them all in a river
retrieve the journal let's go read these messages
da da da da da you think the corporation's yet that the da from eldritch a that the da case
screenshot it read it later to be honest it's rare to see a playthrough that doesn't have
priority we're on rare playthrough now guys you are encumbered oh no of course I am all right
let's eat a bunch of food just eat the bag of bread okay where's my uh list here 83 to 80
eat some canned tuna I have a um bring some drink just drink uh what else do I have break
some stuff down I got like five trip blades 142 130 this is shocked though tactical shotgun and
what am I what I have this on this is a long gun yeah light machine gun it's a long gun
no it's heavy weapons but I still it's not bad okay whatever oh hunting rifle
look at that long gun yep cool nice all right let's go how many viewers did he lose by not
resetting uh I don't know oh how many viewers did he lose I can't believe he told the party
to get out of here I that's a shiny in purple I thought it was I don't know something to look at
I just got killed by an insect bug repeller zap thing oh shit let's get it open journal
all right new companion see that was even who cares nothing's wrong
not everybody has to have the same companion we're gonna get we're gonna get this guy just
wait until he does his first magic spell and I think everyone's gonna have their minds changed
this guy's gonna cast fireballs and shit and you guys are oh this guy is awesome actually he's
gonna be cast in fireballs ice bolts shadow bolts isn't magic in this game if you come to ask
forgiveness for Reid Thompson's murder I'm afraid OSI theology has little to say on the matter what
does everybody know I killed him what are you talking about murderer I didn't do anything I was
told it was a stranger come to town I see no other strangers about but the workers of Edgewater may
not be the most reliable witnesses of course how dare you you know what how dare you accuse me of
something like that I should leave I should just leave I mean I got your book but I should get out
of here this is fantastic well worth all the sacrifices I wait what the fuck is this
French I can't fucking read French it's a law-forsaken joke is what it is French
I was so high and mighty preaching to the yokels about following the plan
while fighting it at every turn you guys said this guy sucks be sure he's fucking nuts
you're overreacting a bit don't you think over overreacting do you have any idea how many years I
spent in no you couldn't possibly know could you I've spent my life searching for the keys to
unlocking the secrets of the universal equation that underlies the plan I had hoped this book
some of those answers I became so desperate I even got myself assigned to this plague-ridden
water to find the damn thing all the time and suffering I've spent liar love liars
both I mean is he is he a med is he are you into medicine I think I'm gonna get along just fine
at least still have your mission work here to give you a meaningful purpose why did you think the
book held the secrets you're looking for this has to be some kind of cosmic retribution what
are you going to see the author had some interesting theories about man's perception
of reality that I thought could be applied to our attempts to decipher the plan
unfortunately he was also one of the founders of the philosopher's school of thought so the book
is banned in this colony a vicar searching for a banned book that's a bad example the story of my
life most lay people are not aware of this but we've not discovered any new insights into the
plan for a long long time I had an idea that we should welcome the truth no matter where we
found it I had the worst idea to share my thoughts with the superior and that's how I ended up
assigned prison duty so if everybody knows I killed the bear an inmate bend my ear with stories of
an original bukonu journal why wouldn't they arrest me what is that philosophism's a false
religion that stands in contradiction to almost everything we know to be true they believe all is
chaos in stark contrast to osi's belief in the plan where's their place but most of the
philosophist perversion of bukonu's thoughts came more than a century after his death but that's
neither here nor there what I need to do now is to find a translator obviously but to do that
I'll first need to secure transport I got you you have a ship perhaps I could make myself of
use to your crew I think so you need to ride out of town I wouldn't mind a ship hand certainly
I already gave you most of my money but I can offer you free spiritual counseling and I'd be
happy to watch your back okay that sounds like a great idea toss ball stick or any blunt instrument
really I'm also a passable gun hand if it comes to that I can usually talk my way out of conflict
though yep that's this oh this is my I'm fairly competent at hacking computers as well and he's
a computer hacker is that all part of your training let's go fantastic let me get my things in order
and I'll catch up with you I shall see you on the ship captain whenever you're ready to leave emerald
veil nice nice all right we got a new companion all right now let's return to we have to do Zoe
right find Zoe actually not that far away where are you max is my best friend Zoe's wait I can
come back to this guy I have the thing for you hi Ludwig never seen the veil lit up like this before
you mentioned a logic module I found one bang up work soldier you're a credit to your uniform
oh that reminds me got a look into getting us a uniform so this is it then the key to humanity's
victory over the mechanical hordes I would reward you with the gratitude of the resistance but
I'm guessing you want something tactile so here's a couple bits for your trouble and a little
something to remember me by and a shock stick oh cool thanks I'm kidding let me see what that is
one-handed cool shock stick I'll put it on in place of this let's check it out
loud weapon cool all right it's always far away damn now put that into the trash why would I do
that fast travel fast travel fast travel is this the entire map um no probably not it's probably
different areas it's different planets it's not the entire game this guys this game is like two
to three hundred hours long just to do these story missions if you did them as fast as possible
the whole game takes about 700 hours to complete all right let's scout it out
I knew that was gonna happen it's okay eat something I'm gonna be encumbered again aren't I
speedrun stream nah nah this thing's fucking amazing all right I'm only gonna use sniper rifle
though oh that's a lot of people what's going on did I get a dog friend it's going in where did it
go did I think I just heard it die no oh no that's their dog okay let's I gotta be accurate
that's gonna kill me isn't it oh shit they're after me oh fuck what's that that's why they ran away
okay new plan we're gonna stealth into this room this way around the back I just have to go in
there and talk to Zoe you see anybody why don't I have a button that I can press in every action
game ever made after 2014 to go and see everything through the walls to see every interactable object
and see all people in all things that I can activate every five seconds the fuck they the
fuck is going on he tripped on his own mind why does that detect me doesn't that make no sense
all right well let's try this again this time I hope they don't trip their own minds
I'm gonna go this way don't do it where's this dog oh no I'm fine nobody got alerted all right
I hear running all right Zoe Zoe Zoe get me out of here get me out get me out
watch out for the lava watch out for the lava what do you mean I need proof
find proof on Zoe's corpse you found Zoe then promptly killed her you could probably tell
grace you found her that way but you should probably see if you can find anything on Zoe's
corpse that grace might recognize oh come on what now I have to sneak back in
I have to sneak back in the compound to take something
okay hold on I have new perks and new skills I need to do hold on let's get some more medical
20 20 medical is a I can do make a mixed rugs together and take them I don't know
dialogue let's get dialogue to 40 so now scramble duration is plus seven seconds
terrifies error effect is 100 and let's go back into ranged oh wait a minute yeah I want 50 for
long guns too that works hurts all right how about uh how about stealth detection that one's not bad
vendor prices carry capacity yeah oh the walk speed no carry capacity let's do it
all right let's see if I can get in here I can't fucking believe I missed oh my god
I can't be trusted uh all right we're good this is too many people just run
don't break my fucking legs please oh my fucking god where did I save it good writer
okay I don't want to fight them just shoot better omega lol just shoot better omega lol
it's not it's not omega lol worthy if I miss a shot okay that's just regular lul worthy
I have to go in the front door can I do wrap around all the way can I get in the back
I should be able to right like can I not get around here fast travel you cannot travel at this time
why no no no no no no no I don't want to yeah I do are there any omega lols in chat all right
here you go wait how much is this worth no price I'm not in the lightest of humors right now
uh Zoe's not coming back you want to expand on that yes she went feral I had to put her down
I was hoping you wouldn't say that I was really hoping
you'd better not be spinning me a story I could bring back her body if you want might have to make
a few trips Jesus yeah that belonged to her well enough guess there's no arguing with you
you pretty much did my job for me least I could do is pay you for your trouble let me know if I
can do something for you I got money for that too thanks yes uh there is something you can do
I'm not in the lightest of humors right now it's time for you to go home all right uh I gotta find
this guy's book but but but but unfortunately it's time to turn the stream off if you weren't here
earlier uh I'm shaving some time off of the streams this week to prepare for a couple things
Thanksgiving is going to be moved around a little bit because I'm streaming on Thanksgiving and I
have an upper endoscopy this week too so I need to I have to like go on a little bit of a changed
diet and I have some procedure shit to do so this week is a little busy I'm going to stream the next
three days in Rome streaming on Thanksgiving too but the streams are going to be like four to five
hours each so we're going to play I feel like I'm just getting into it now I've had an upper
endoscopy it's kind of neat well I had a colonoscopy a few months ago and we're going the other way
this time uh but so that's going to be the end here we're going to transition out to the bits
and everything see you tomorrow we're going to do the same thing to pick up right where you left
off right here I feel like I'm like I said I'm just getting barely into it now so bear with me
this week well um obviously holiday stuff and uh a medical procedure have to take some precedence so
streams will be shaved but I'll see you guys tomorrow I'm going to actually do a hard save
here because I have not done it once the whole game so that would be nice uh first impression so
far feels like feels like there's I this might I don't I don't know if this is a it might just
be talking complete bullshit here in the first few hours of the game but there it seems like
there there are I thought there weren't going to be that many interesting choices but seems like
there are I didn't mean killing the guy like that's something you can do seems like there's
a couple of optional things you can do for each major mission which is kind of interesting I guess
it does feel like it may have maybe if they had like an extra year or two it'd be expanded on but
I don't know yet I don't know we'll see but I am an inch I'm interested enough to play it again
tomorrow it's more limited than I was hoping for it just more fallout type choices yeah I'm like
it's kind of hard to pass judgment on a game like this in the first three or four hours
so a couple of interesting things just happened so well all right that's pretty fucking cool some
interesting developments you can kill this person you can kill that person you can do their mission
you can cut off the power you I mean that's cool but we'll see if it continues but I cannot
pass judgment on it yet I feel like it's too early but uh there you go that's kind of what I think
we'll see how I feel tomorrow I'll see you tomorrow let's transition to the bits
thanks for joining me everybody see you tomorrow have a great night same time same place you don't
play games you're just too terrible for it to count as playing I beat the last boss the last
true boss in Sekiro in under 100 tries just I mean I'm just gonna throw that out there
have you done that yet did you do that yet have you done that just I just need to know I actually
did that I mean yeah I'm not I'm not I'm talking to the one guy
under 100 omega lull I'll see you tomorrow uh let's do the bits let me quit out of here so
I can pull this over one omega I don't know why I go mega lull I just I think it's so funny
I love that emo because it's such it could it could be used legitimately or as a total
overreaction to anything it's great it has so many uses why is it funnier than lul I just
it's because it's supposed to there's a lot there's a lot of layers there
but anyways uh let's do the let's get the music rolling here thanks again for joining me thank
you sad vega for the 250 I thought we were calling the 2019 germa uh awards the germies
that's loud I'll turn it down uh the germies huh maybe I look forward to it though it's like I
I can't wait to see what the nominations could be it's it's just fun I can't wait
but that's not yet that's gonna happen second half obviously of December so we have a lot of
other things to think about first hey spunky spade thanks for the thousand bits if I give you
my bits will you leave my rats alone I have nothing to do with your rats
I'll take the thousand bits but I have nothing to do with those rats I didn't do anything to your
rats yes I will leave your rats alone because from the very beginning I was not I was leaving them
alone in the first place so you got your wish thanks for the thousand bits appreciate it
seriously uh wait does this work I say this every stream let's see if it worked it's always like
four streams behind I don't know why it doesn't make any sense doesn't work
thank you uh lights not on thanks to the 250
germa just a month ago I lost my iphone se and I heard your se ran at the end of the dead rising
stream rip both our se's I guess this tears in memory of them oh and it's lights not on
got it I got it I wish I could get a fucking as a brand new se sealed with no tracking device
bug on it it'd be amazing I wanted an se so bad and let's do the credits camera's not on right
in case it is it's not thank you all the subs welcome back to all of the long time subs and
welcome for the first time welcome for the first time all the new ones thanks something that needs
to be said about the Minecraft king stream this is very important and it's a decision that I did
not make lightly actually this is really really important kill the music for a second I don't
think I talked too much about this but of all the things that we talked about at the beginning of
the stream the thing that is absolutely number one for like true the for everything is set in
stone it's going to be a sub-only server with potential twitch integration like you need to
verify your twitch id and you have to be more than one month sub and the reason why we're
doing that is because Minecraft is probably the easiest video game on earth to fucking script
and destroy like a whole stream so it has to be that way we're it's going to be a multi-month sub
only and the reason why it has to be multi-month is because if it was just sub only somebody could
just sub and then come in and that's you know hey five dollars here you go take it I'm coming in
so just need to be we're going to try to protect the server in quotes I guess as best as we can
so that's the way that is absolutely set in stone but when there's still some bits to do
we have uh sad vega thanks for the 250 this is the best dumb rp playthrough I've ever seen
you really nailed the role of being an idiot down to full chat my character is not even stupid
though he's an engineer he's a medic he's a scientist and he's a liar you have to be smart
to lie well Freudian weapon thanks for the 250 no that's not that's not 250 it's 250 times
one two three four five thanks for the thousand bits Freudian uh appreciate the 10 bucks though
some choices you made may have infuriated me watching you play this was thoroughly entertaining
happy thanksgiving and good luck with the endoscopy I appreciate that thank you
the endoscopy is at the end of this week but for a few days before I infuriated for a few days before
the procedure I have to I can't eat certain foods and I have to kind of the day before
I can't eat anything well the night before whatever so I'm going to be all kind of trying
to change the way that I eat stuff and then obviously I'm going to be on drugs for the
procedures so I'm going to be kind of all over the place so that's uh it's all good though
only eat nuts and fruits uh oh you mean only nuts and fruits well from my understanding it's
anything that has skin on it no corn no peas no nuts no um fruits especially like berries
I just have to be careful no beans anytime I have a procedure like this I always kind of get a
little paranoid that I'm going to do something wrong I also don't I can't take any anti-inflammatory
medication like I can't take any uh like advil or something or aspirin I don't think just be
careful and it's the same the first time I've had to do something like this so it's not like
I'm nervous about it but you know anytime that you have anything like this going on you
anytime where I'm going to lie on a table and I'm going to get put unconscious and someone's going
to like do like things you know like medical I just get kind of like not nervous but obviously
it's understandable like I have to get put under so it's like I have to go under anesthesia and
have like a doctor fucking do like a scope so it just kind of creeps me out in a way you know
no that's the wrong music I'll see you tomorrow I feel the same I have arthritis and I've been
too been too tuned been too many times from my age yeah I just don't I don't like the anesthesia
drugs I just don't there's something about them just there's this chemical that they can put into
you that turns you off and then turns you back on it's uh this is it's just uh rubs me the wrong
way but you know you gotta do what you gotta do it was a huge medical breakthrough yeah it I mean
it absolutely is one of the most unbelievable discoveries of modern history is being able to
be able to go inside people and fix stuff without them even knowing you know other than
you knowing and obviously they know they're there but being that that I don't who the how the fuck
do you even come up with that how who what's the what's the process there to even figure that out
such remarkable medical and technological advances how did we come up with this shit
they used to just use alcohol yeah remarkable but that's my time guys sorry again for these
shorter streams uh this week but I have to go uh help prep for Thanksgiving and other stuff
don't read don't read that negative comment don't read it jerma you only read the negative
comments don't read it out loud don't read it you suck jerma fuck I shouldn't have read that
good night guys I'll see you tomorrow have a great rest of your night