Relax, oh my god. I can't even, I can't, like, I had to, look, I sprinted out of here and took a piss as quick as I could.
It's the fastest piss I've ever taken. I hit the, I turned on the streaming button, and then I sprinted to the bathroom as fast as I could.
I'm here now. Hi. How you doing? You good? I'm not, I'm, I'm just two minutes late. I'm sorry.
I flip-flopped like crazy on the game today. I was gonna play
Spaceport Janitor, and then I found out that Noita has Twitch integration. It was gonna be Noita.
We've been, it was voted on. Noita lost. Then I voted, and it's worth a thousand votes.
I freaked out, and I was like, holy shit, there's Twitch integration, I wanna play it.
And then somebody said, people can, like, hack you if you turn it on. I was like, I don't wanna get hacked, so I turned it off.
We're playing Noita today.
One person was like, dude, don't turn on the Twitch integration, you're gonna get hacked. I was like, what the fuck does that mean?
They could have just been completely fucking with me, but you got me. I was like, oh wow, Twitch integration.
Maybe we'll do that instead. Oh yeah, Pog. One person writes, hey dude, just be careful, like, you can get, like, your channel compromised with the Twitch integration, it's kind of buggy.
Oh, that's all it took for me just to fucking not do it.
So it's off, and now it was gonna play, but I wanna play the, it's a hundred percent true.
It's a hundred percent not true. That's in no way true. God damn it. I knew, like,
this, this, okay, this is within
three minutes of me turning the stream on. Like, within four minutes of turning the stream on, I get a message that says, dude, fucking be careful, man, I'm serious.
That's not how you spell finish.
Can everyone just put their hands up? Everybody just stand up. Just put your hands up.
Is it still, I'll fix it. Noita means witch in Finnish. It does.
Somebody gave a shitload of subs and money, hold on. There you go, I fixed it.
Me, meyaboo just gave 50 community subs.
What are you doing? That's so, that's, that's a, that's an absolute shitload of money. Thank you for the 50 community subs.
That's meyaboo.
Are you high today? No, why, guys, I'm not high every day. Come on, I'm not.
You know what? Yeah, I am. Because I get to say, I'm wicked high, and that's why all the things that I do that are stupid now have an excuse.
But thank you for giving me a permanent excuse.
Forever. I could fuck up a children's puzzle for an hour straight, and then everyone's like, what the fuck is going on? Is he okay?
Yeah, sorry, guys.
I just took a little bit of CBD this morning, and people would be like, oh, okay.
Yeah, like weed 420 makes you like fucked up. I get it. Yeah, keep going, man. Keep going with this kid's puzzle.
Maybe you'll get it eventually.
Perfect. It works out perfectly for me.
What do you mean I spelled it wrong again?
F-I-N-I-S-H.
Finish.
What? I had it right the first time. I had it right the first time.
It's two N's. Those of you that were in pre-stream chat, it was two N's, wasn't it? I flipped it.
I had it, I actually
changed this.
I had it two N's and I changed it.
You're already spelling a language wrong.
But anyways, thank you for the 50 fucking subs. Thank you Super Bruce for the five community subs and DestroyDude for five.
Let's play Noita. Are you guys ready? That still makes you stupid. No, it doesn't because I pressed the N on the keyboard wrong.
Turn the sub sounds back on.
You don't want that. Trust me. I don't want that.
Oh, you don't. You really don't. All right. I promise you guys one day.
I will do
a stream.
That is sub sounds on and TTS on too.
I will just do a just annoy the stream stream.
I'll do it for like a week and then it's going off forever.
Sellout stream.
And it'll be randomized sub sounds too. You'll never know what you're gonna get. I will make sure that there's like
like 50 different sub sounds I can play.
So you just it's gonna be fucked up. You're gonna have no idea what's gonna happen. I will record myself talking
and saying just insane shit. I might do like a full two minute monologue for one of them.
Noita is a rage game. Don't say that. Is it actually?
Don't tell me that. Is Noita a rage game? Thank god the camera wasn't on because it would have just shown me.
Kind of?
Is it? It's like Binding of Isaac. Well, I love Binding of Isaac.
It's a roguelike. Is it? Oh, wow. This actually could be kind of fun. All right, you ready?
When's porn week? We talked about that yesterday already. Turn on the twitch integration. No, hold on. Not yet.
Let me just play first. I don't even know what this game is.
I don't want to turn on the twitch integration immediately and have like 50 things spammed on me when I don't know the controls of the game.
Select streamer mode. Okay. New game.
Explore a new world. The original Noita.
Daily run. A new day. New world. Science. I don't know that. Nightmare. Don't want that. Okay.
I just want to do the regular game first.
Yeah, I don't even know what this game is.
It's just been people have been telling me to play it for like three and a half months.
So you want me to turn on the like spam the enemy on on top of him mode?
I don't even know what left click does. Okay, here we go.
Does this game suck? But we can help you. Well, hold on. We'll see. I don't want to get hacked.
What came first? The chicken or the egg?
Definitely the egg.
Without a doubt had to be the egg. Yeah, without question. The egg then turned into
an alien. And that's how you get Noita. Witch.
X-Men Wolverine Origins waiting room. You better gift a thousand subs when I play that game for 10 minutes.
What a fucking waste of money. What? What? What?
That game is like $30 probably on eBay and I just have to sit here and what that's such a big deal to sit here and play
Wolverine for like an hour.
Just sitting in a chair. I think I deserve like fucking five grand and subs. Do that? What am I talking about?
All right. So this is oh, it's like Terraria. Um, well you can fly.
Okay, automatically right off the bat. I don't want W. I want it to be space, which is good. Is there already space?
Oh shit.
Is this processing or recharging?
Okay, cool. What about right click? Press F to kick. I thought that was a lie.
Okay, let's move. So what do we do?
What is this thing? Wand.
It's a bomb.
Oh shit. I only have two of those though. What is this thing?
Ocean. Equipped with water. Is this how you heal?
F.
Okay, I'm changing that. I gotta change that. Oh, here we go.
Uh, I need to change that. What is that? Input. Okay.
Uh, mouse. What is that? There we go. I gotta change this shit. Okay, use wand. Let up.
I want this to just be space. Only. I will accidentally hit W and it'll piss me off. Okay, left spray
from potion. Okay, left throw, right kick. Please make that something else. I can't make that any other button.
I can't make that any of my other mouse buttons. Why? Why not? I don't want it to be F.
No, not kick to mouse. Yeah, I have weird control sometimes. Okay, to interact E.
Next item. Next item. Select. Okay, save. Replay. What would I need to say to replay?
Eyes. Inventory. Wand. Shuffle.
Number one. Spells. Cast. One. Cast delay. Recharge time. Mana. Shuffle. Yes.
Spells. One. Cast delay. Recharge time. Max mana. Okay, so this is my items.
I have spells too. One and two.
Yeah, I'm a mouse scroller. Entered the mines. What do I have to do? Why do I play? It really is Terraria.
I suck at Terraria. If there's one game I can tell you that I
cannot play to save my life, it's Terraria. You guys know how awful I am with this kind of control scheme?
I'm gonna die in the first level and I'm gonna turn the stream off. This is Terraria, but it's hard and rage inducing.
Oh, come on. I'm not gonna do well at all.
What? You just have to go down?
Oh, hold on. Let's not say that yet. Am I on fire? How do I get the poison off?
Bring the potion.
Why is it not working? Wash yourself off.
Okay, so I'm wet now. That means I can take extra damage from electricity.
I did that on purpose. Fuck you.
Oh, what's this? Blow it up.
That's a... What? Hey!
Why did that not blow up?
All right, douse that fire. What the fuck is going on here?
What is this? Is this gas?
All right, whatever.
I want this heart.
Go from a bow. I knew that was gonna explode. Whoa, this is lots of pixels.
Okay. Now I'm gonna douse that. Oh, there's a little indicator. That's cool.
That's helpful.
It doesn't go that far, dude.
Did it work?
Get extra max HP.
Increase to 125. What is this thing?
What is all this?
Wand? Press E to pick up this new wand.
Oh, okay. So this is shuffle no.
Faster recharge time. Lower cast delay and spread. Should I replace it?
Pick up a magic wand. Why is it not shooting?
Shuffle no. Wands that shuffle cast their spells in random order. The number of spells this wand casts when used. One.
Cast delay. Spread.
Spark bolt. A weak but enchanting sparkling projectile.
How come it's not shooting? What's this one?
Slow orb of void.
You mess with it in the four slots.
This game didn't tell me this. I don't know what the fuck's going on.
I don't know. Why is this not shooting though? Is it? Am I just crazy?
You need more mana.
Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. What about a chili egg?
Pick up a chili egg. Okay.
Okay, cool. What's this thing?
An invisibillium potion?
Okay. I feel like I just said that word wrong. I feel like I said invisible wrong. What does that mean?
Actually, this game's okay. I'm starting to get a hang of this.
It's pretty cool.
Ow. I didn't even see that guy.
What happens if I die?
Minus 15 chat?
You get a game over.
Okay, this guy is firing missiles at me.
Okay, when the music starts. Does it mean that that's like a hard encounter when the music starts playing like this?
Fuck. I just put water on him?
I'm gonna die.
All right. I'm good. I'm all right.
Do I get experience? Roll the egg. It spawns a friendly creature.
Oh, what? That's pretty cool. All right. What's this thing do?
Do they follow me around?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, water, water, water, water, water, water, water.
Water! Put water on me. What's what's that's not water? Oh, fuck this guy. Get down there and kill him.
Go down there and hurt that guy.
Shit.
Go down there and kill him.
Ow! Hey, what the fuck?
Click here for stats. Cool. Okay. Progress. Six new progress?
Oh, Jesus. This is fucking huge.
Okay, cool. This is a lot of stuff.
New game. New game.
Oh, Jesus. Okay. So now what? Do I
run on streamer mode? No, not yet. I need to even find out like how to equip items and shit.
All right. I'm gonna start to try really hard as a headshot right off the bat. Good.
So the whole point of the game is to go down.
Something in here. What's that?
Can I break this with a bomb? What is this?
Okay. Chaotic polymorphine potion.
And I see what it does.
Equip and throw.
Right mouse button. Drink. It's like a Harry Potter thing. All right, let's go.
What are you gonna play? Wolverine.
Yeah, you saw what happened when people did that. When we when I played Ratatouille,
I may as well have just like just
not even turned on the stream that day. This thing seems like more powerful this time. Why?
You guys notice that?
This thing is like stronger.
Gold nugget. All right. So how do I go? Is there like a place I can go back and spend the money?
The starting wand is randomized. Oh really?
Oh shit. Energy sphere.
Damage five. Five. Spread point five degrees. Cast delay.
So the wand is just the thing that houses the spell inside of it. The wand is not its own item.
Oh, yeah, it kind of is, but it isn't. This game is.
All right. What's this? A sword.
Ooh, this is a new- oh wait, this one's got gas in it. What's this one?
Okay, this is a
burst of air. Picked up a new magic-
What happened? What happened? What?
Why? Died from acid.
It was a trap room.
Can I get down to like the first save point, please?
This is new. Why is this a 15 in it?
Unstable crystal. It explodes when somebody comes nearby and this one's double ice.
Oh shit, that's awesome.
All right. It's giving me better and better starting items. I like it.
The rogue light, Jerma. There's no save point. Yeah, but I could probably go back and spend money.
What's the gold for in that case?
Let's go down even further.
Noita. Come on, bounce.
I don't think this is even a rage game for me. This is more of like a I understand I'll never do this game.
And it like doesn't bother me that much.
Really, that kind of doesn't.
What is this?
It's different. Pheromone potion.
Can I just drink it? Cover myself in pheromones? Okay, now what does that mean?
Do hornets like me now?
All right, blow that up. I want to get- I want that new wand.
I want that wand in there. Give it to me. Oh fucking come on. I could just- all right, what is this? Fire?
Just- oh, the berm's gonna explode, right? Oh, watch out for the room that it blows up. Or what's this thing do?
Okay, that's awesome. You know, I can only shoot that a few times. Ten times.
I'm gonna go right. He's mad at that. No, I'm not. I'm fine.
Fuck. I'm so bad at terraria type shooting. I swear to god. This is why I don't play these games.
Because I- you have to- you have to look at where your character is and the whole other side of the screen.
Like if I'm- if I'm right here and I have to look over here, I have no idea what's happening here.
Gold despawns. Oh, that sucks. Can you drown? Yep, you sure can.
Get up. Get up. Go, go, go, go, go, go. Up, up, up, up, up. Why does it want me to- what's this for?
Can I like blow this up or something? You can eat corpses.
Meat. Is that how you heal? Oh shit, I'm just eating dirt on the ground. The hell- is that hurting me?
This is meat here, right? The character can also throw up.
All right, what is this one? Oh, is this a lamp? It's just a torch. I'll probably need it later. Oh, I have a friend egg.
What's the ten- ten percent? Is that ten percent hungry? What's that? Gunpowder. Oh shit. Okay, everyone back up.
Mouth's over it. Your stomach is almost empty. I have to eat.
But is that actually food? You have to actually- this hunger in the game and you start dying if you don't eat?
No, okay.
I'm- why am I in fire? How do I get in the mud? Why did I go in the muddy water?
Okay, I'm fine. So, where did my friend go?
Carve myself in uh, in uh, form ones again.
Nice.
All right, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out. What's this? A berserkum potion?
Okay, berserkum potion. I guess try-
Berserk. You can go berserk.
All right, let's eat these people.
I drink the blood on the ground here? Oh, yeah, I can.
The bloody clothes protect you from fire. Okay, that's good to know.
If I carve myself in blood, then I can't be burned anymore?
All right, that thing's
big and horrible.
Gold, gold, look at all that gold. There's so much gold. Gold, gold, gold. How do I- uh, what do I- what do I do?
Give me that, give me- just go.
All right, I found it, I found it!
Pick up a full health. Increase max health by ten.
Pick up a spell refresher. All spells refreshed. Ooh, okay, that's what that means.
And then here's the money.
All right, nice. Let's see. What can I do?
The fortune cookie? Okay, what can I buy?
Wand. Not enough gold to purchase this. I can purchase this one.
What the fuck is all this?
Okay, it's spread spread.
Firework.
Rock rock. This one is- oh, this one's boring.
This one looks kind of cool.
Void is really good if it works.
Pick the right one. You can customize wands while here.
Really? Purple is boring. Wait, what? Hold on a second.
This is getting- this is getting a little too deep for my brain to understand.
So I can do magic, missile, fire, and energy sphere.
What does that do? It can arc and bounce.
Put the orb spell on the second wand.
Oh, I get it. Okay, so I got the orb there.
I got fire here.
Should I do- okay, fire.
Test it on the statues. Do I lose mana?
No, no, no, don't. Yes, you do.
Mana regen's in its per wand.
It's 10 casts. Put orb on red wand.
Buy the wand to the right. Put the orb in its open slot.
Uh, what do you want to drop?
Okay, um, do I- how about the torch? Who cares about the torch?
Fuck the torch. Well, who needs a torch?
Okay, I got this wand.
And now- oops.
Wait, what's going on? Oh, that's what's on the ground. Okay, so.
All right, I- there's a lot of info at one second and with no tutorial.
All right, let me think.
So I have- here it is.
A slow orb of void that eats through all obstacles.
So it's a projectile. So, what's this here?
Warning, this wand does not have enough mana for black hole.
Wand has max 63 mana. Casting black hole requires 180 mana.
Um, all right.
Wait, how do I- where is it?
So I need 180- I don't have 63 fucking mana.
How much mana does this wand have?
113. What about this one?
180! All right, here we go. Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on a second.
This has 180 mana.
So now I can- but I can only shoot this three times.
Is that- is that accurate?
That's the black hole. It's cool.
So I can only shoot this three times, but it's super insanely powerful, right?
All right, so only do this for like an oh shit scenario.
So I gotta put this somewhere else.
I- I- how can I- can I move stuff in my hotbar?
I don't want that to be three. I want that to be all the way over here.
Oh, okay. So I want this to be my main wand.
Just the shooting. Just shoot.
This is the secondary for the explosive. This is the bomb.
All right, I get it.
Don't- okay, do not use the- do not- what's the guy from Beauty and the Beast?
Luminaire? What is his name?
Don't use him, unless it's a very, very impossible-
It's not Beast, what the fuck?
Oh, what's this?
Press E to pick faster projectiles.
Press E to pick boomerang spells.
Press E to pick toxic sludge immunity.
Oh, we're freaking that shit.
I no longer take damage from fucking poison.
Thank god.
All right, what is this?
None of gold to purchase perk- oh, you can reroll them.
This is pretty cool, actually.
Does this do 10, 20 damage for a headshot?
Or is it just random?
Black hole does not do damage.
Well, I can black hole people, and then-
That's- all right, I can't-
Whoops.
Give me that, that's a jewel!
I got it.
Into the coal pits.
Do these things hurt?
I'm just licking the wood.
All right, that's not gonna work.
A jewel.
Jewels.
All right, easy.
I'm not gonna black hole down there.
I am gonna utilize the crystallized bomb.
Yeah, okay.
What is this stuff classified as?
This pink stuff.
What is the pink stuff?
Slimy clothes protect you from fire.
So it's just slime.
I guess get a bomb.
Thank you.
Wait, I can be completely protected from fire?
What if I eat the slime?
Whoa, don't eat the slime!
You're spilling sick, nothing stays inside.
You pu-
Okay, what does that do for me?
Does it- is there a debuff?
That's disgusting.
So you don't just get a bottle of water.
I'm protected by fire, though.
I'm protected by fire.
Go, go, go, quick, quick, quick.
While- while it's still on.
Ow.
All right, we're good.
Slime makes you slow, though.
What is this?
Bloody clothes protects you from-
Okay, so blood and slime protects you from fire.
And you can eat blood.
You can also eat gunpowder if you feel like it.
But it would be a very bad idea.
Gold vein.
What's that?
How do I get that?
Oh, shit.
Did I get it?
Nice.
Okay, cool.
This game's pretty fun.
You know what?
Okay, this is-
This is all the parts of Terraria
that are cool without the cra-
This is just non-crafting Terraria.
I don't have to, like, open up a Wikipedia page
with 5,000 articles on it.
I just get cool item and just use.
I don't get hit.
That thing-
That's a mega wand down there.
What is that thing?
Hey.
Whoa, he's taking-
Wait, you can hit-
Wait, what?
They can pick up the items?
He stole that.
He just stole it from me.
That thing was insane.
Where did he go?
No.
What?
Where did he go?
He just sniped that.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Really?
They can take the items?
I gotta go find this motherfucker.
Give me that!
Oh, he-
Okay, I think he died.
Wait, I don't want to touch that, though.
It's poison right there.
Holy shit.
What is this thing?
Always casts-
Okay.
It's a ga-
A gas tank.
That's like just a gas-
That's a gas station.
Always casts double spread.
Watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
That motherfucker stole a wand again.
Okay.
What do I just-
I'm-
What do I-
I don't know what it does.
Spitter bolt with timer.
A short-lived magical bolt that casts another spell after a timer runs out.
Is that cooler than this?
How much mana does it cost?
Okay, this is pretty sick.
The firework gun.
Can only fire it once a second, though.
It's still pretty good.
It's got big damage, too, doesn't it?
All right, yeah, let's go.
Hold on.
Wait, not yet.
What's over here?
Nothing.
Any more gold?
All right, well, I don't have any money.
I only have 93 bucks?
I got tons of damage now.
Okay, I don't-
I don't know.
That was weird.
Let's go.
I'm starting to understand how this works.
Pass delay.
Is that thing alive down there?
Black hole on this one.
Hold on.
My brain cannot function that quickly.
I need at least one to two hours of failing
before I figure out the basic function of the video game.
Ooh, slime.
All right, so remember, from the slime fork,
I got to go left and down to get to the end.
Important to know.
Well, watch it.
Nobody just threw that at me.
All right, I'm going up.
Did the little mouse do that?
What is this?
Oh, right.
I forgot about that.
I can't get hurt by poison now.
Well, I'm not even gonna-
I'm not gonna need another item ever.
This thing is insanely good.
Treasure chest right here.
All right, open up the treasure chest.
Okay, if I hit-
Should I shoot it?
How do I open it?
Oh my god.
That's a lot of money.
Okay, good.
All right, I opened up the-
That's a pretty fat treasure chest right there.
Coated.
Get it all over me.
No, give me.
Sorry.
This wand is massive.
How much is there to explore?
This is kind of insane.
Can I kick this?
Okay, can I kick this down?
Is this gonna explode on me if I kick this?
It's infinite?
Activate streamer mode.
No, no, not yet.
Ooh, we got two things over here.
What's this?
Oh, can I-
I'm gonna have to blow this up.
I'm on fire, I'm on fire, I'm on fire, I'm on fire, I'm on fire.
Get the poison to-
Okay, I can stand the poison.
Get the fuck away from me.
Stop, please.
Oh my god, don't die here.
What the fuck?
Please.
No, don't drink the poison.
Okay, I'm fine.
I'm gonna relax.
Fire bats are hell.
I'm trying to get this thing-
All right, what is this?
Concentrated mana.
What's the other one?
Jump, aim up, and kick.
Oh, okay, cool.
What the hell was that?
What did I do?
What is that?
What potion-
Just get in here and drink it.
Worm.
You feel like your future worm food.
Ingesting worm pheromones.
What does that mean?
Okay.
First of all, speaking of pheromones, let's get coated.
And let's get coated in the berserk potion too.
Now I'm fucking angry.
What does this mean?
A berserk curse affects you.
All right, what does it do?
And then what's this one?
Concentrated mana.
You gain mana back faster.
Oh, that's pretty cool.
Give me that whole thing.
I'm wasting it?
I don't know how that works.
Just drink it from the ground?
Okay, let's go.
I have enough money to leave.
Yeah, let's go.
Refill the health.
Refill the-
It's a stain.
It wears off after a few seconds.
Drink it instead.
Oh, okay.
I'm just staining my clothes.
Right click a potion just to drink it.
Okay.
Try black hole before refilling wand.
Oh, I didn't.
Sorry.
All right, what do we got?
This is too much.
It's too much for me to think about.
Okay, this is a lot of-
I don't know what any of this is.
All right, let me ask you a question.
What am I looking for out of all these things?
Is it like-
What am I looking for?
What are the numbers that I should be looking at here?
Check the perks.
Oh, I see what you mean.
Check and see if I can make these better.
Okay, this is wand experimenter.
I don't know what that does.
Extra knockback on spells and teleportitis dodge.
Teleport a short distance away when an enemy projectile is near.
I don't know if I want that.
I feel like that kind of sucks.
It's going to teleport me into a fire pit.
All right, let's take a look at these.
This is question mark.
Let's-
Okay, this is question mark, question mark, question mark.
Mystery spell.
This is always ca-
I don't even know what these are.
Wait, what?
Oh my god.
What, what, what?
Press E.
What's happening?
Those are lightsabers.
Laser, laser, laser.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I don't understand what's happening.
What's going on?
Press E to read spells.
No, press E to purchase wand.
Oh, okay, right.
I like this a lot.
I don't want to get rid of this.
This one is-
But this can blow up walls.
This one's kind of stupid.
And this one is my black hole.
So I'm gonna-
This one-
I don't like this one.
What do these do?
A somewhat peculiar bouncy explosive bolt.
25 uses.
Uses 50 mana.
45 damage.
That's a lot of damage.
That's a shitload of damage.
All right, question for all of you experts.
So this wand has one, two, three, four, five, six slots.
Which means that when I click, left click, it uses this one.
Then when I do it again, it uses this one.
When I do it again, it uses this one.
And if there's another thing here, it uses that one on the fourth click.
Is that how that works?
If it's shuffle, it's just gonna do a random one in here, right?
Okay, starting to understand.
You really want non-shuffle wands.
Starting to figure this out.
Let's see, what's this one?
This one looks interesting.
Shuffle no.
So it just goes one, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five.
Always.
Max mana set, two, two, ten.
Always casts increased mana.
Immediately adds 30 mana to the wand.
Double spell.
Casts two spells.
Gives a projectile a much lower cast delay.
But no respect to your aim.
But these aren't moves.
Luminous drill with timer.
A pinpointed short-range beam of concentrated light
that casts another spell after a timer runs out.
What spell does it cast?
It just does this three times.
So I click double spell.
Click heavy, super heavy, and then click timer.
So I have to click three times.
So I don't click one, two, three to get here.
You hold the button down.
Just click once.
No, you click once and it just goes bananas.
Okay, all right.
I'll give it a try.
How is this good?
This is what it looks like if you accidentally
hit your TV with your Wiimote.
How is this any good?
Remove the spread on it.
Heavy spread.
All right, let's take off the heavy spread.
All right.
It does massive damage.
All right, cool.
All right, this is cool.
All right, now what?
So now I've got my standard tried and true fireworks wand.
I've got my explosive blow up stuff wand.
And I've got, wait, remove double.
What?
The two lasers off.
It already casts two.
It's already doing double cast.
Oh, it's just using one.
Oh, I see, okay.
So should I put, wait, should I put something else on here?
What about like, what about energy sphere?
Oh, look at that.
It shoots energy sphere too.
That's a lot of mana though.
Yeah, you're right.
It is probably very inefficient.
Very inefficient.
Take it off.
Wait, what about these?
What about like the bubble thing?
No, no, over here.
It's kind of like bubble laser.
It's inefficient though.
Okay, now I understand why everybody loves this game.
This is cool.
Less is more, less is more, less is more.
Take off extra lasers.
Did I?
One laser only.
Oh wait, but isn't it doing like three times the firepower?
It doesn't matter.
All right, so let me ask.
What's the point of having three of these on?
What would it do?
No, that sucks.
Put them all on.
Yeah.
What about two?
Okay, this is more consistent.
It's a little less long, but I can fire way more.
That's a pretty good compromise.
Yeah, it is.
Put bubble spark, bubble spark, then laser.
Is this bubble spark?
Bubble spark, where's that?
Bubble spark, bubble spark, laser, laser, laser, laser.
Okay, that's really cool.
This is awesome.
Okay, but no, inefficient.
I'm still, okay, I'm still understanding this.
So hold on a second.
This is, my brain is doing all kinds of computations here.
So when I click once with shuffle on no,
it starts here and does all three in a row.
Whatever is in a row here just does them in a row.
This is not like click once then for this one cast,
click once then this one cast.
Like in a succession, I just click once
and it just plays out like, just plays out the song, right?
If it's shuffle, then it does it in a random direction.
So like, let's say it shuffles on.
It could, I click once and it goes like this way, that way,
that way, that way, and that way to end the spell.
Don't break the temple.
I'm mixing it up.
All right, well, let me just use this now.
I'll get it eventually.
Pretty good compromise.
All right, I got 120 bucks.
Goes through all of them because there are a timer.
Let's see.
Timer and trigger spells can cast other spells.
This is a lot of info, but it's like, look, you know what?
I'm not even going to like,
I'll just get you guys help from time to time
because I, you know, it's, I have no idea what the fuck's going on.
I'll be honest with you.
I might kind of get it.
Not a big fan of that range.
Not a big fan of the range.
Okay, now this is another one.
What the fuck is this?
Spells cast one, cast delay three, max mana capacity.
What is this one?
So this is double, double light bomb.
It's trash and explosive one.
It's just more bomb.
Should I replace it with this one?
So it's just double, double bomb.
Yeah, that's, nah, nah.
I got to change this up a little too.
Move this.
That's better.
So I can really easily switch between the two of them.
Dude, this is like fucking me up, man.
This teleporting, I don't know if I like very much.
I'm taking way too many.
Wait, are these saving his ass?
Yeah, but it's like teleporting me in random directions
that I don't want to be in.
I can't take the spells chat.
No, you can't.
Yeah, I guess you can't like rip it apart.
I'll be honest with you guys.
I'm not sure I like this very much.
It doesn't do enough damage to compensate for the fact
that you got to get pretty close.
I'm not sure I like it.
You can take the spells to the next mountain.
Fuck, I got hurt.
I don't like those guys.
I hate those guys.
They're so accurate.
You can dig with the laser.
And this is different.
Okay, what's this one?
Electric charge.
It gives a projectile electric charge.
It's splitter bolt.
So it's an electric electricity that explodes.
All right, let's try it.
Holy shit, okay.
No, give me that.
Don't take that.
It's mine.
Use it.
Pepe laugh.
I actually kind of like it.
It's pretty good.
Yeah, I like it.
Does it do how much damage does it do?
Plus three damage electric, eight.
So like, you know, 15, 20, 30.
I think I'm going to leave this.
I don't think I want that anymore.
Yeah, that's sad though.
Dig.
I'm digging.
Look, there's water down here.
Who would have thought?
It's a snow level.
Yeah, I'm a big fan of this.
It's a lot of...
It's spammable.
It's very damageable.
It's very cool.
I'm into it.
Oh, this is great.
This is really great.
Actually, this is very great.
Let him burn.
The bubble sparks.
This thing's a lot of health.
All right, you know what?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
He's so good at aiming.
I'm stuck in the wall.
Help.
Am I drowning?
I'm not drowning, am I?
Get me out of here.
He's going to kill me.
I don't have very much health.
I got to...
Fuck.
That hurt.
Do I have any healing potions?
I thought you said right-click drinks.
You guys told me right-click drink, didn't you?
You have to do it in the inventory.
Okay, so it is fucking terraria, isn't it?
Snowman.
Is that an enemy?
It looks like an enemy.
It could be.
Jesus.
Okay, in the inventory.
Berserk potion.
Right-click.
Berserk.
12 seconds.
Okay, I'm berserk right now.
What does that mean?
Get him.
These guys suck.
It's bigger explosions.
Ooh.
Watch it.
All right, I'm going to drop a fucking bomb down there.
All right, eat this stuff.
This is meat, right?
No, this is blood.
Rotten meat.
Don't eat that.
Jesus.
Dude, how are you supposed to dodge that shit?
They fire so...
Berserk mode.
Let's go.
Whoa.
Oh, it really is saving my ass so much.
I complained about it because it's hard to see what I'm doing,
but it really is saving me.
That's fire and I'm dead.
Am I alive?
Potion?
Did that work?
Use the black hole.
I don't need to get...
Potion will put out a fire.
Okay.
Watch out for that shit.
Potion.
Wait, get the money first.
Ooh.
Should I risk it or should I just go?
I only have $193.
Wait, what's this?
It's invisibility.
Oh, good thing I didn't go right in that portal.
Because look at what this is.
Uh, good thing I didn't go in.
Double scatter.
Double double scatter.
Gunpowder.
And then glowing lance.
Let's give it a try.
Okay, this is dangerous.
That's dangerous.
This is dangerous.
But it's pretty good.
Fires.
Okay.
Yeah, fuck that thing.
You can take the gunpowder.
Wait, what?
Oh, thank god you heal every time.
Leave, you dumb fuck.
I did.
I'm leaving.
Spell layout's not good on this.
Not.
Alright, so hold on.
So what, should I do this instead?
Ban that guy.
It says amazing stats.
Alright, wait a minute.
Okay, now I can buy spells but I don't have enough money.
I don't have enough to buy this.
Electric arc.
Stop hoarding the black hole, you cuck.
Buy this.
Alright, so let's make a cool spell.
Alright, so I have electrical arc.
I'm gonna do electrical arc and then all this.
What just happened?
Where'd that go?
Where'd that spell go?
How does that look?
Let's try it.
Dude, this is too much.
Remove the gunpowder with the lightning in the front.
Remove one of the lances.
This is pretty sick, actually.
Take another lance off.
Let's see.
Yeah, three's better.
Can I make my...
This is my favorite wand.
Can I make this any better?
Wait, what if I do electrical arcing here?
Take this shit out.
It's okay.
It looked cool for a minute.
Needs two projectiles.
Oh, right.
Okay, I see.
So the goal here is to try to get things in the middle of this, right?
So if I hit something right in the middle inside that wedge,
I'm putting a laser on the green wand.
What do you mean, a laser?
Dude, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
What happens if I do this?
No, not very good.
That's better.
Laser is the green thing.
Oh, okay, hold on.
Wait, let's try this one.
Oh, yeah.
That's...
I'm leaving it there.
What happened?
Why can I not fire this anymore?
Oh, I have no mana.
How do I get mana to go fast?
That's so slow.
Oh, that's too bad.
What about this?
Only laser on it.
Use double spell.
No, I can't.
Drink the green potion.
I can't do it.
Mana charge speed.
It's too much for my brain right now.
It's a lot of info.
I can't.
I like what I have right now.
This is perfect.
Yes, you can.
I can't do it.
I can't.
I just can't.
It's too much.
I like this.
I'm going to keep it.
Put laser on one and two.
What do you mean one and two?
Stop saying no.
Use it as artillery.
It's okay.
Put mana in the water.
Don't shoot electricity in the water.
I like what I got right now.
Actually, this thing sucks.
I don't want this anymore.
I want to make this better.
It's good for digging.
Yeah, you know what it is.
You're right.
This is going to be the dig weapon.
Yeah, this is dig.
Two lasers to dig.
I like it.
I'm ready.
I'm good.
This is my attack wand.
And I have black hole for when I need to have an insane moment.
All right, let's go.
He's too indecisive.
I think it's less indecisive and more.
I still sort of have no idea what's going on.
Gold is forever.
More blood and gas fire.
What does that mean?
I get to keep the gold through runs?
Gold nuggets never disappear.
Oh, well, that's not what I wanted.
This does so much damage.
We can hit it.
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what?
What happened?
I thought that was a training dummy.
That was not a training dummy.
What do you mean I angered the gods?
I thought that was like a, hey, test out your new stuff.
That's not what that is.
You trained too hard.
That hurt a lot.
He just point blanks at me with a fucking grenade launcher.
Snipe him from back here through the dirt.
I beheaded the statue.
I didn't know that was going to happen.
I thought it was just a training dummy.
All right, get me in here.
Whoa, all right, easy.
Should I be eating people though?
Should I eat people?
Your stomach is almost, but what does that mean?
What, what happened?
What does eating people do?
What is this percentage thing?
What does it mean?
It doesn't do anything.
It does nothing.
Okay, so why am I doing it?
Cannibalism is wrong.
It's not cannibalism.
These, I'm, wait, what do you mean cannibalism?
Oh boy, this is where it gets a little, black hole, black hole, black hole, black hole.
It didn't, black hole didn't do anything.
What the fuck?
What?
Oh my God.
Voice crack, worst one I've probably done in a long time.
I'm dead.
Goodbye.
That was, I just got spawned on by like 40 people.
Black hole is for digging.
Why are they fighting each other?
Oh my God, look at all this progress.
Streamer mode, not yet.
Give me like another one or two runs.
Starting to figure this out.
All right, let's move.
I'm going to go quick and I'm going to go very fast.
I'm going to do this well.
What do I got for wands?
I got spark bolt and bomb.
Let's go.
I'm not being integrated.
No, not yet.
I like this.
I'm having fun.
I don't want this whole thing just getting to be memed.
And I want to, I want to play non-meme.
I like this game.
Oh, we got a new wand.
What do we got?
I'll take it.
Whatever it is, let's go.
Ooh, it's a double shot.
This game is shit.
Install my mod.
Well, do you think this game sucks, but you loved it enough to make a mod for it?
What are you talking about?
And things can crit.
Oh, okay.
Why is the water on fire?
You light the mud on fire.
What are you protected by?
Oh, we got a bunch of jumps in here that about to get bombed from above.
Oh, right.
You can't hover forever.
Okay.
Fall joke.
Thank God there's no fall damage.
That would have been sad.
It's got double tapped.
Like I hit his head on the ceiling and died.
What an embarrassment.
I can't believe I let that guy kill me.
Hurt me, you know, whatever.
This is fun.
Bouncing Burst.
All right.
I'm willing to try everything.
I think I found the one I want to use.
I'm pretty sure I found the one I like.
This is awesome.
What just exploded?
Tabula Smaragdina.
What is that?
Pick up Tabula Smaragdina.
Okay.
Can somebody take out the NES cartridge and blow in it?
Oh, wait, I can read it now.
If all the mountains were of silver and gold,
what would they profit?
A man who lives in a constant fear of death.
Hence, there cannot be in the whole world anything better than our medicine,
which has the power to heal all the diseases of the flesh.
Can I eat it?
Swamp potion.
Whip and throw.
Food poisoning.
Whoa, what's that?
How much more?
Did I just screw myself?
Keep going.
I don't have enough potion to keep going.
I made it.
Okay, what the hell is over here?
It's got to be like a treasure chest over here.
It has to be.
Guaranteed treasure chest down here.
Uh, okay.
Entered the orb room.
Oh, there's a magical sacred orb over here and another scroll of poison.
Okay, I picked up the other tablet.
Among those who devote themselves to the transmutation of metals.
However, there can be no such thing as mediocrity of attainment.
The person who studies this art must have either everything or nothing.
An alchemist who knows only half of their crap
reaps nothing but disappointment and waste of time and money.
Moreover, they lay themselves upon to the mockery of those who despise our art.
Those indeed who succeed in research reaching the-
Hold on.
I'm like drunk reading.
This is what-
Okay, when you get like a drunk text and you're drunk,
it's like, what did you just say?
Hey, where are you?
Why are you not in the hotel room?
I don't know.
Thus, those indeed who succeed in reaching the goal of the magistrate
have not only infinite riches but the means of continued light.
Am I- Did I just go down like the lore path?
Where you collect like four of these and it turns into a fucking demon?
First, eat pick up orb.
We discovered an orb of true knowledge.
Picked up thundercloud five.
Creates a stormy cloud.
Holy, that's- that seems pretty good.
That's a new- I unlocked a new spell?
Oh, that's pretty cool.
All right, let's go.
Fill your water bottle.
Can you do that?
Oh, you can.
I swear to fucking god, I have no idea what's wrong with-
I didn't mean to do that.
Kill!
You took my orb, right?
Okay, that was fun.
Is it like the last boss or something?
This is like one of the last-
It's probably the last boss.
Hold on a second.
I unlocked a new spell.
Where is it?
I unlocked it.
It's the last boss's room, son.
I have to sc-
There's more, okay?
It's still not here.
It was like storm cloud, right?
You have to use it to make it show up.
All right, let's go.
Come on.
Didn't cast it.
Oh.
Does that mean I didn't unlock it though?
Or does it still unlock?
I don't have to do all that bullshit again, do I?
Integrate as-
No!
All right, I have a question for those that want me to do Twitch integration.
Um, you want-
Can I just type in my channel name
or do I have to like go through a major process
and like install a bunch of shit?
Or can I just type my name in?
Go left, hold on.
Just channel name.
Just type your name, okay.
You have to post dick pics.
That's like-
That's of the same level of-
Like they give me 5 BTC and I send you 10 BTC scam.
In fact, that may even be worse.
What's the point of going over here?
Throw a bomb in here.
Now what?
It's just water.
Give me some air, give me some air.
Oh shit, another scroll!
Oh no!
I can't wait to summon that monster again.
Sacrifice of oneself to the pursuit of knowledge
is the highest level of-
There's a mutant in here.
I'll kill him.
This is the final boss.
That would be pretty disappointing.
This is just Terraria.
Yes, it is.
But it's more custom-
Okay.
Do you guys remember the game Magica?
This is Magica and Terraria together.
And remember they made another Magica?
They had this awesome, incredibly fun video game
where you combine spells and could play with your friends.
And then they made another Magica.
And then I died apparently because I ran out of oxygen.
That didn't happen-
Look, that didn't happen like that in that order.
But I remember that too.
Point is, they took that franchise and threw it in the trash.
If they had just expanded on Magica 1
instead of making like a multiplayer fighter game,
that could have been such a great franchise.
Oh, I'm not going left again.
Oh, you guys-
You guys want to get integrated?
Then I'm going to play the way I want to play, okay?
Islands?
Demanded.
You guys want to get twitch integration?
Then I'm going to play the way that I want to play.
Ooh, steel potion.
What is this called?
Stamina potion?
A slime potion.
Cool.
I still don't understand anything.
He's a tyrant.
Kind of.
I'm glad it started with the bubble wand.
I like these the best.
How many floors are there?
Because I got to snow floor and then I got overwhelmed.
How many actual floors are there?
This game is really fun.
Seven.
What did I get?
Four? Five?
Holy shit, this guy is unkillable.
I got to four, okay.
Five?
Oh.
I don't know what they said,
but somebody said I'm willing to be perma-banned to this.
I guess enjoy your perma-ban, whatever you said.
I don't know what it was.
Have a nice day.
That's the first thing.
I don't even know what he said.
I can't even read it.
It should be about seven floors.
What does it say?
Okay.
Jerma, I'm willing to bet a perma-ban on you liking Jedi a canopy
because it's like Dark Messiah.
Well, why would I perma-ban you if I don't like a game you suggested?
Isn't that kind of weird?
I didn't like that game.
Ban that person forever.
I dig.
I try to go down to the center?
Something in the bottom here?
Okay, well that was...
What happened?
Twitch chat is full of nerds.
I mean, it's true.
Aren't you one of them?
I'm one of them.
We're all totally nerds here now.
I'm getting a lot of really hard enemy spawns, don't you think?
It's like, what the fuck was that all about?
I'm like dead.
I don't have enough money for any...
No, I'm not going in yet.
One more money.
The menu sounds like Taco Bell.
Crunchwrap Supreme.
Only $2.99 with our box combo.
Come to the bell.
You fucking asshole.
That doesn't make you an asshole.
What's wrong with me?
That's so fucking funny.
Just go.
Oh, I'm going.
Remember, don't shoot his head off.
Please mod me.
Wait, something's hidden down here.
Is this free?
I can't get that.
There's a fish in here.
Can I touch the fish?
Catch the fish?
What does it say?
Meat of an innocent creature.
Ooh.
Oops.
Sorry about that.
I don't know.
I thought it was like a magic fish.
Okay.
Fireball.
I kind of want fireball.
Bouncing burst.
Glitter bomb.
Wait.
Chainsaw.
Glitter bomb.
I can get both.
No, I can't.
Good tool for cutting meat.
Also has some magical properties.
Chainsaw bubble?
How does it work?
Oh, that's kind of cool.
Chainsaw on two.
All right.
So what about this one?
Should I get a bouncing burst?
I might as well.
All right.
Let's see.
Bouncing burst.
And yeah, let's do this.
That works for me.
Bounce on two.
Yeah, but then I don't have a chainsaw anymore.
Chainsaw on one.
Bounce on two.
Okay.
That's pretty good.
It's so bad on mana recharge though.
Recharge time.
Mana charge speed six.
That's terrible.
Six?
That's bad.
I'd rather have it like this.
Yeah, this is more consistent.
This is the chainsaw.
And I can just dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig.
Did I dig down here?
I can't.
Yeah, I can.
But whatever.
All right.
Cool.
Let's go.
Enemy radar.
Freeze field.
Wand radar.
Hey, Jeremy.
A bit of a long message, but I've been a long time viewer.
We'll just put a quick question.
How many people have you killed?
Zero.
Thanks for the...
I really thought I had something there.
Okay.
Wand radar.
Is that...
What?
Does something show up like a minimap or something?
Freeze field.
I'm gonna do...
I'm...
Freeze field.
Liquids freeze in your presence.
That kind of feels like it sucks.
All right, let's move.
Did I anger him again?
I didn't do anything.
Liquids freeze in your presence.
Wait.
Does this do this to lava too?
If it does, that's pretty good.
Omega lol.
Star Wars cringe post.
Cool.
Because somebody said they want me to play Star Wars Jedi Academy?
Star Wars cringe post.
Oh, dig that out.
That's gold.
Dig that out.
Am I destroying it?
Okay.
No.
I was going to say.
Why?
It sounds like it's...
All right.
I need a much bigger recharge for this wand.
I got to find a recharge rate for the chainsaw.
Come on, dude.
Seriously.
That's just terrible.
This is awful.
Let's be honest.
I'm going to sneak this way, though.
Probably something down here.
Gold over there too.
Gold everywhere.
Hold on.
I got to stick around for a minute.
Is this worth it?
How much gold do you get?
You don't get one.
I feel like I'm doing the thing in worms that everybody hates.
When you just take one of your worms and you just continue to drill down
and just stay safe the whole time.
Oh, is it my turn?
Okay.
I love playing this game with my friends.
That's worth it.
That's 100.
That was like 40 gold.
And then somebody finally gets like right there.
You're like fucking down here.
They just like throw like a...
He knows.
Who doesn't know?
That's like one of the most classic franchises ever.
I know.
Does it recharge faster if you don't look at it?
There is a holy hand grenade in this.
Are they still making worms games?
I'm starting to get like the urge to play one.
But not like a new age worms game.
Like worms.
Like original like worms 2.
Worms Armageddon.
This is a complete just pulling this out of my ass completely.
But I feel like worms is one of those franchises
that would potentially be trying to modernize too much.
And the game is not even close to as fun as it was before.
Is that true?
I have no idea.
I'm making that up.
I don't know.
But I just feel like it could be.
That game seems very iPad-able.
Right?
It does.
Worms Mobile.
And then that's just all they have.
Look, that's a huge chunk right there.
I have to at least get that one.
Says the guy that plays iPad games.
Yeah.
Now I have, you know, E3.
I know that people are going to laugh at this.
Maybe I've already told this story.
E3, like 2013.
Star and I, we shared a hotel room together.
And I was in the middle of playing Family Guy.
The Family Guy, the quest for stuff.
And Star was just sitting in the bed over next to me,
watching me just tap on the iPad and like collecting coins.
I had a town that was huge.
It was like a rival to the best towns in the whole game.
I had every character.
I had Quagmire.
I had Lois.
I had Stewie.
I had Peter.
I had Professor Xavier.
Whatever the guy's name is.
I had all of them.
And I'm going to be honest with you.
I have to be honest with you because I hope that I am.
I spent at least, and I'm being completely real,
and I hate to say this out loud,
at least $100 on that game.
I swear to God.
At least $100.
It probably was like $200.
Over the course of like five months of me caring about it.
I don't know why.
I didn't even care.
I spent at least $100 on that game.
And I don't even like Family Guy that much.
I don't even care.
But that was right when those started becoming a thing.
Like, collect coins from your buildings and wait.
2012, 2013, that was when it first started.
And then I figured it out.
And I was like, all right, that's fucking stupid.
I'm never doing that again.
And then I bought like 1,400 Hearthstone cards
over the course of a couple of years.
It just never stopped.
They just continued to do that formula
in a few different other ways.
Guys, it got to a point where I was buying Hearthstone cards
just to buy them.
And I didn't even...
I was terrible.
I was so bad at the game.
I had no idea what the meta was.
I was fucking awful at it.
But everybody was playing it.
And I was like, oh, I want Grom Hellscream too.
Because this is a Grom deck.
Stars told this story before.
Back when Hearthstone was in its beta
and they were giving closed out like keys to streamers and shit.
I went into a bunch of people's channels with alt accounts
and tried to win key giveaways.
I would sit in a street because people were doing like,
oh, beta key giveaway.
So I tried to find streams that I had a good chance to win.
And I was just sitting there and I'd wait for a fucking beta key.
Here we go.
We're giving another two or three keys.
And I'm like, oh, yeah.
Okay, hold on.
Me too.
Give me one.
These are confessions.
I mean, I'm serious.
Did I get one?
No, I didn't.
All right.
I have to remember the validity of this
because I think Star got a key for me somehow.
I think he like found one.
Or he got it and he gave it to me.
I don't even remember.
Found one.
I don't even like remember how.
I was so obsessed.
I was like, I need to play it so bad.
Please, anything.
And then I got it and I didn't play it.
I played it for like a week or two.
And I was like, I'm not good at this.
I hate this.
I suck at this.
Money wasted.
I'm so desperate to play it.
I wanted it so bad.
All right, that's enough gold.
Yeah, I wanted like 300.
Good thing to know that our donation is being pumped into Family Guy.
You think I still play that?
It's been like seven years.
Die already.
No, the money.
No, I can't get that money either.
Stream, you're a Family Guy, Tom.
Oh my god.
No, I have no juice left.
I'm dead.
I went down way too quick.
Terrible.
Horrible.
Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
I'm okay.
Worms.
Do the worm strategy.
He fucking holy hand-grenaded me.
Why is it bump?
No, stop coming up here.
We want Family Guy.
No, I don't want to play that.
That game sucks.
It is the worst of all the worst potential of iPad.
Just money grab games.
You don't want, I don't want to play.
You don't want to see that happen.
Okay, I get 350.
No, I need, I need.
Something's going to cost 350.
I'm going to be pissed that I didn't do this.
This one's closer.
I can't ignore this.
I don't even know if the game exists anymore.
Hey, Lois.
Get a load of this guy.
I don't even think the game exists.
How come there's been no wands here?
This is minus 50% off.
Prickly spore pod.
Oh, here it is.
Undercloud.
Should I try it?
Can't ignore this.
Hold on.
What are you linking?
This is so stupid.
This is like zero effort.
But it's, it's somehow a lot of effort.
But at the same time, it's fucking zero effort too.
Not that.
Hold on.
But did they have to save to my documents?
Why did I save image as on desktop?
Why is this not saving?
Oh, no.
Get the file name off there, dude.
All right, here we go.
This is zero effort.
I think I like Meg the most.
From the time that I said the word family guy iPad game.
Why don't you start immediately?
You started right then.
And you finished two minutes ago and uploaded it.
All right, what do I want?
I want the, I want the thunder.
I want to try it.
I unlocked it.
Blood is 250.
Wait, everything is 50% off.
Oh, no, it's not.
It's just blood.
What should I get?
Chunk of soil.
Personal gravity field.
Second wand is machine gun.
Blood.
And spore is another one.
All right, well, we might as well get these out of the way.
I don't know what this has to do with family guy.
But what does this have to do with family?
We're on like a family guy kick right now.
Does this have to do with family guy?
There's a real face.
I mean, it kind of looks fake.
It looks a little bit fake.
So handsome.
Okay, thanks, mom.
Yeah, thanks a lot, mom, for saying that.
Real link, please.
All right, I'm going, I'm going back to play Noito.
So why did you, what did you do to my face?
Why did you do that to my face?
I don't understand what the point of this was.
Why did you arch my back a little and give me a weird chin?
I don't understand.
You clicked the wrong one again.
Okay, this is way better.
I don't know.
This could be real.
Somebody said the missing link is not real.
I don't think it is.
It's just old man body.
All old men over the age of like 85.
This is terrible.
But you put like a crispy filter on it though.
That makes it look a little worse, right?
Escape from Dinosaur Island.
I don't, I'm not gonna play this.
What do you want me to do?
I'm not playing that right now.
Yeah, I've seen the toilet mouth one.
All right, this is it.
Last link and I'm done with links.
Okay, yeah, this is good too.
This is your camera.
I know the camera sucks.
I know.
We've seen this one too.
What is this umbrella?
What is that?
Why is there like a weird...
Oh, that's the weird studio lights that I used to have.
What is it doing in the room?
What's it doing in here?
This office was as big as an airplane bathroom.
How did I...
What was this for?
The light gun stream?
But why would I have that?
Jim Carrey on set for The Grinch.
Oh, I'm not green.
So sorry about that.
You know the things that like you...
The things that you remembered for
and the things like the legacy you leave behind
gonna be a real lot of digging to find that for me.
You're gonna have to really do a lot of weeding around.
Mitch McConnell.
Now, let me tell you about the stimulus.
We are not ready to move forward on a stimulus.
Not yet.
Maybe soon we will move forward on that.
Madam Speaker.
Paul McCartney's.
I think Paul McCartney's closer.
Fuck that wrinkly asshole.
Tony Hawk.
Okay, I'm done.
I'm done.
I'm going back to playing Noito.
It was in all caps, too.
That was a bit...
All right.
I'm...
Stop it.
Enough.
Silence.
Do the spells.
Right, right, right, right, right, right.
We're playing a video game again.
All right.
This just creates a stormy cloud.
I need the third wand.
This is kind of bad.
Someone's a spore pod.
Let's just...
I just want to see what it looks like individually.
What am I doing?
All right.
What does this do?
Whoa.
Does it hurt me?
Does this explode?
Does the projectile hurt me?
Very important.
They do.
The projectile hurts me.
So it is being removed.
Blood.
Blood, blood, blood.
Okay.
So what?
You just can cast blood on yourself?
Thunder cloud.
This only has...
Okay.
Move.
I can't move.
Move, please.
Why did I get stuck?
Because you froze the rain.
You were standing in the rain and you froze inside the rain.
I was here.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go.
I'm like into this game.
I need to get to at least floor five again.
Integrate.
No.
If you keep asking for it, I'm not going to turn it on.
I will do Twitch integration after this.
You understand?
If you do the integration, I will subscribe.
Okay.
Fucking hurry up.
Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I subbed.
What the fuck?
I need to get down to...
I have to get down to at least the floor.
Snow floor.
Respect our existence.
I am.
Just wait.
I'm getting more comfortable in the game.
I'm starting to understand how the game works.
It's becoming very clear what I need to do and where I need to go.
Load this up so I can get down there.
Quick commander.
Where's the gold?
There it is.
My favorite slot machine is where's the gold?
By the way, if you wanted to know more lore, more confessions.
Blow up, please.
I thought it was Betty White.
Yeah, Betty White isn't very good to me.
I'll tell you.
Betty White wasn't very good to me lately.
I haven't been...
Okay, let me be clear about this.
I haven't been to the casino to play casino games since January of 2020.
So let's be clear about that first of all.
Who just gave $50 to save Banana Bro integration this year?
Yeah.
Like, very March, April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November.
Yeah, so I went to the casino 10 months ago
and hung out for a little while.
Look out, he's sitting here.
All right, I'm going to die, so don't make fun of me yet.
And yeah, why would I want to go to a casino and like hang around there?
No, thanks.
It's not blood.
Go right, go right, go right.
I'm just taking a look.
I'm not picking that up.
It's going to spawn like this worm boss.
I already did this.
Who gave the $50?
I missed it.
It was 5,000 bits from...
Who was it?
Who gave it?
It was me.
No, it wasn't.
Who was it?
They say banana bros, like Unite or something.
Whatever they said.
It was a lot of money.
Wait, hold on a second.
Let me see.
I should have thought of these things saved.
All right, it was Zurich Dah.
Zurich Dah.
Thanks, Zurich.
Okay, I'm just going to put this on screen for a second
because I don't even...
I don't understand what this is.
Why, uh...
Why did you just link this to me?
What's this supposed to be conveying?
True.
Spoilers?
I...
Spoilers...
So you got a guy, throws another guy to the ground.
What happens in, like, eight out of ten movies
that have ever released?
What were we doing?
Something was happening.
What happened?
There was a reason why I stopped.
What did I stop for?
No, it wasn't for Twitch integration.
Oh, yeah, the donation.
Yeah, okay, we got it.
Thank you for the 50 bucks.
It's a lot of money.
And I'll tell you,
if you want to support the channel,
you don't got to give me 50 bucks.
You're not going to give me 5,000 bits.
I actually probably would prefer if you just subbed.
You know, people that...
People give so much money to this stream.
It's unfucking believable.
People have given thousands of dollars to this stream.
Thousands.
And I can't even comprehend how much money that is.
Ungrateful.
No, no, I'm just...
I'm just saying, I...
This channel sees so much support and so much money already
that people drop in hundreds and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of dollars a month.
It's a lot of fucking money.
And I don't want to seem like I'm ungrateful for it, but...
And integrate us already.
I'm gonna.
You missed subs.
They just came in right now.
ZurichDuh gave 10 community subs on top of the 50 dollars.
And Chrissy just gave 5 community subs.
Thank you, both of you.
DestroyDude gave 5 community subs as well.
Alright, let's talk about this for just a second.
So, one of the reasons why, on top of the fact that I can stay here and stream longer
and not do the end of the stream reading donation thing,
there's been a lot less bit donations, right?
Because I don't read them anymore.
And a small portion of the reason why to do that
is not just because of being able to sit here for longer
with the pain problems that I have.
But also, people that give this channel a shitload of money,
I would much prefer it if you maybe spent less on me and more on you.
I know that some people can afford it, and I know there are some people
that watch this channel probably have fucking millions of dollars.
And that's awesome.
But I would much prefer it if you spent that money on yourself.
Put me at the bottom of your list.
You guys take such good fucking care of me already.
It's unimaginable how much monetary support
just from subscriptions come into this channel.
You guys can do back of the napkin math.
You know how many people are subbed to this channel.
It's not public information.
So just be aware that although I do love that people give me that kind of money,
I really hope that you're taking care of yourself first
and only have me at the end of your list.
Always.
He's begging for subs again.
Please just give me subs.
That's all I want.
Makes three billion...
No, what was it?
If you look at the...
Why, like, streamer net worth is like 140 billion dollars, right?
It's something insane.
Somebody linked the website.
It says my net worth is like 180 billion dollars.
Somebody linked it to me like a few months ago.
And there are a lot of people saying like,
oh, wow, this is so wholesome.
Wow, this is so wholesome of you.
I make a lot of fucking money, you know?
Like, I just...
I'm not necessarily refusing the money.
But you guys know, like, this...
We crossed 10,000 subs back.
I don't have that now, but we did that back in January.
That's absurd.
That's an absurd amount of fucking money to give somebody.
And I don't want people to think that they have to give me like 100 bucks on top of that.
That's already a huge amount that I can't even comprehend people would do in the first place.
Get on with the fucking game.
No, I just want to make it clear.
Because a lot of people were like upset that I got rid of the reading of the donations.
And I can understand that.
There's another part to that, right?
All right, I'm gonna get on with the game.
I'm gonna get on with the game.
Just know that like you guys take already fucking insane good care of me
with subscriptions alone.
It's insane.
So I'm gonna get on...
That guy was a new viewer and I don't want him to think I'm an asshole.
So I'm gonna keep going.
We gotta like get the new viewers to stay.
Destroy the tablet quick.
Did I destroy it?
Does it say how I'm worth?
And the point of me saying that this channel makes a lot of money is not to brag.
It's to tell you that I don't...
That if you want to give a thousand dollars to this channel in two weeks,
take care of yourself first, always.
I am last on that list.
Still flexing.
Yeah!
No, dude, come on.
DevilX just gave $50, 5000 bits and they say for our end of the list Andy.
Okay, thank you.
End of the list Andy.
Thanks for the fucking insane amount of money.
Stop doing the permaban bet on Jedi Academy.
I'm gonna play it like next week or something.
I don't have enough money to do anything.
Don't kill that fish.
All right, let's go.
Millionaire streamer can't afford anything.
Hey, what is this doing?
Well, I can't tell you with confidence.
I can't tell you with confidence I'm not a millionaire.
Let's make that clear.
I am not a millionaire, not even close.
Oh, extra one capacity.
If you had to be there, you know.
If I had a billion dollars, I would open up like 30 clown schools across the country
and put like make like clowns like cool again.
That's what I would do.
Peace with gods.
High mana, low capacity.
Wait, maybe that one.
Clowns cool again.
Yeah, clowns were cool in like the fucking 1400s.
Like the 1200s or something when it was like,
weren't they cool back like in like the like the medieval times?
Like jesters?
Yeah, jesters were cool.
What are you talking about?
People liked the jester.
I'm gonna go with this one.
You make peace with your gods.
I don't know what that means.
People hated the jester.
No, they didn't.
It was like the king's right hand man.
Jester, come and spend time with me.
And they would come out and dance and they'd all be happy.
It was the king's like favorite person.
Clowns were cool when jesters were cool.
They were the clowns.
I want to get that back.
It's coping.
Whatever.
They helped with like policy decisions too, didn't they?
And if this song wasn't good enough,
then they were like fed to a bunch of lions.
Just like, you know, Twitch chat.
My joke's not good enough.
You guys scream at me and tell me I'm just ugly.
It's true.
This has got point blank shotgun in the face.
Come on.
The guys with the guns are the worst.
They're so accurate.
They're way too accurate.
I want that gold.
Fuck you.
Not you, game.
Turn on Twitch.
Do what now?
What do you want me to do?
All right, I'm getting distracted and I have to stop.
I have to play.
No, no, I wanted to...
I didn't want to...
I wanted to cover myself in the water so I could be alive.
I'm getting to floor four before I do any Twitch integration.
Sorry.
You promised.
I told you it wasn't going to happen,
but not until I was satisfied with the base game.
Plus, don't you guys know that once the Twitch integrations turned on,
chat is going to be over?
Because you have to like spam symbols or words and shit.
That's when you can't chat anymore.
It's just going to be a flood of nonsense and no one will be able to chat.
So I want like a couple hours, two, three hours of chat.
And then just one, two, three, or four spammed over and over again.
I didn't say to do that now.
Well, they're getting a head start.
Okay.
If you were really good at video games,
you'd probably really like this game.
Just to tell you.
Just to give you like a little bit of insight.
It's one of those games.
It's one of those if you're really good at games,
you're going to love this one.
Did he actually just hit me with that?
No.
Waffle or pancakes?
Neither.
I think they're both bad.
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
This one is...
Just take it.
It's just a shitty bomb though.
Yeah, this sucks.
What is this?
Firebolt?
And what's this one?
It's just as awful.
Okay.
Well, this sucks.
You got baited?
Well, no.
I don't...
Look.
When I go to a breakfast place,
I'll just give you a good indicator of what I mean.
and I look at the menu,
I never, ever, ever, ever
order the pancakes or the waffles.
Ever.
It's always on there,
but I don't order it.
Ever.
Waffles?
Never.
Now, if my breakfast does come with pancakes,
I will enjoy one.
I'm of the opinion that pancakes...
They give you like a stack of three or four of them,
and it's too hard to eat all of them.
You always just eat one.
Or two, and you can't eat the rest of them.
I got a bomb down there.
It's a bad take?
No, I mean, I like pancakes,
but they're just kind of too much sometimes.
I don't think that's an unpopular opinion.
I'll tell you, my favorite breakfast item is...
Have I told you?
You guys know?
Corned beef hash.
Done on the skillet.
Nice and crispy and delicious.
With a over medium egg on top of it.
Or not over easy.
I'm not an over easy guy.
Over medium egg right on top.
Just laid on top of it.
I like a jammy yolk.
I don't like a runny yolk.
What is going on up here?
Oh, shit.
This is perfect.
Let me in there.
A nice warm jammy yolk is better than a runny yolk.
It's way easier to handle.
There's a lot.
Look at all these people in there.
This is a fucking Minecraft spawner room.
Ax HP.
Nice.
All right.
Leaf.
You're the guy that owns 12 things at McDonald's.
There's so much gold left.
I'm sorry.
The gold.
I know.
I can't.
I saw people talking about pancakes and I fucked up.
Torch.
Electric torch.
Rain cloud.
Chain bolt.
Let's try that one.
Oh, yeah.
Get rid of these like...
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Image and speed.
Mana drain 80.
Okay.
So let's see.
This has 170.
160.
All right.
So this one is the one I want to use.
Get rid of this bomb.
Put that on there.
What does this look like?
Oh, that's a Star Wars blaster sound.
I like it already.
It's a delicious link.
I guess.
Mayonnaise soft drink.
What would that even taste like?
I feel like it'd be impossible to capture the delicious,
deep flavor of mayonnaise in a liquid like that.
Like in a drink.
This would stink.
You would...
And it would...
Oh.
It would smell immediately.
It would just stink.
This is the kind of drink that you open,
and the person that is upstairs in your house
can smell what you're doing downstairs.
Can I combine that with...
Let me try this.
So this is spark bolt and chain bolt.
Oh, that sucks.
Oh, it's because it's not...
It's not a shuffle.
Yeah.
Damage 25.
Damage 3.
That's not bad.
Oh, what about one of these other ones?
Bouncing?
Maybe bouncing?
Let's try that.
No.
No, it sucks.
This one is shuffle.
Yeah, get rid of the bombs.
I think they're worthless.
Shuffle bad.
Okay.
I'm going to keep...
I like the bouncy.
I don't even need this wand.
I guess I could do double bomb.
What is double bomb going to do for me?
That would be pretty cool, right?
Shuffle sucks.
It randomizes the order.
Yeah.
I'll keep this one now.
The rest of these, I don't think are very good.
Maybe a rain cloud.
Might as well try it, right?
It's a watery weather phenomenon.
Eh.
Put bouncy into the second wand.
Okay.
Yeah, because it's...
Holy shit.
Right?
Okay.
I don't even...
This wand is kind of useless now.
Wait, what about...
Okay.
Cast elate to 0.2.
Cast elate 0.4.
Recharge 0.6.
Recharge...
Oh, put this up here.
Mana.
Oh, this sucks for mana.
Whatever.
All right.
That's fine.
This looks good.
Knock back on spells?
No.
Wand experimenter?
I don't know what that means.
Faster wands.
I feel like that's good.
All wands you carry to link herring
gain a bonus to their cast elate.
Holy shit.
Oh my god.
That's kind of ridiculous.
I can just go into a room and just do that.
Okay.
So I'm just going to go into a room,
get in the middle, and go.
All right.
This should be the run.
Wand go brr.
It's green too.
That makes you...
What did you say?
Even funnier.
Oh, automatically.
Right off the bat,
we got a fucking legendary wand.
Shuffle.
Above and below.
Cast three spells.
Ahead, above, and below the caster.
Reduce the spread of the spell.
And then it's a spark bolt with timer.
This thing's terrible.
Why is that cool?
It looks like it could be so cool.
This is not even doing the thing it's saying it's doing.
Isn't this supposed to be shooting above and below me?
Ow.
All right.
Let's go.
It has cause shuffles on.
Oh, whatever.
Safety protocol?
Let's go do that before I go anywhere.
Is it safe down there yet?
This thing is awesome.
I love it already.
All right.
What's this?
Shuffle?
No.
This is energy sphere.
Recharge time.
2.8 seconds.
Holy shit.
Throw this thing in the trash.
It's four spells per cast, though.
Wait.
All right.
Let me try it.
That's awful.
I mean, maybe if I put...
Maybe I'll hold on to this.
If I do, yeah.
Four spells might make this pretty good.
What about these four up here?
I'm holding on to this thing.
Keep the chain bolt, though.
All right.
What should I replace?
This one.
This one sucks.
Yeah.
Get rid of this dumb thing.
Keep going.
Fuck this wand.
All right.
That's what I said.
Why is this fire going on here?
How is there fire in water?
What is...
Something on the ground.
Coal vein?
Oh, it's water.
Oh, drink.
Chain bolt is homing?
Doesn't seem very homing.
Is it?
Okay.
I like it.
You're right.
It's very good.
I don't want to go yet.
I only have 100 bucks.
No, I'm not going yet.
Unbanned the word Lego.
Why would Lego be banned on the channel?
You just said it.
What?
Wait.
Lego is banned?
It's the word Lego banned.
Does it go through walls?
No.
This floor sucks.
There's nothing here.
I have to go all the way around to get anywhere?
What the hell?
I guess I'm going to go over here.
Okay.
Here we go.
Enemies.
Somebody.
Something.
Fight.
A attack.
Oh, what's this?
Herbie.
Chili egg.
Oh, I'm going to save that.
And I can go down here.
I don't have anything that...
I have nothing that explodes.
I don't have anything that explodes.
What about the bomb wand?
Yeah, hold on.
I'll go get it.
I actually might be able to get up.
Hold on.
I love this thing.
I hope I can power this thing up like crazy.
That hurt.
Unban the word Odama.
No.
That's my least favorite video game.
That's staying banned forever.
That looks pretty good.
All right.
I got to go get the bomb wand.
Look this shit over.
Look at all this stuff.
All right.
The bomb wand it is.
Where is it?
It was this one down here, right?
What the fuck is this?
Oh, God.
Heavy spread and TNT?
All right.
I got to move some things.
What do I replace this with right now?
This one?
I'm going to come back for four.
Let's blow this shit up.
All right.
What is it?
This looks good.
It's a double spell fire bolt.
Heavy spread.
That's terrible.
How did I light on fire?
All right.
Let's blow this wall up.
Gold.
Yeah.
How much money is that?
Dude, easy.
I got to get in here.
Can you please turn off the sharpness filter in your OBS?
What are you doing?
Sharpness filter in your OBS.
It's not chat that is sharpening their images.
It's your program.
You turned it on one time during little hope to prove something about pixels.
And ever since you forgot to turn it off.
Sharpness filter?
It's real.
All right.
Let's hold on.
It's real.
You guys aren't fucking around.
I thought they were deep fried like crispy memes or something.
I didn't know.
I was wondering why everybody was doing this today.
God damn it.
This is what it was.
Okay.
Well, turn it off.
It looks...
Doesn't it look worse though?
It looks terrible.
I like want it to look like this.
Does it look awful when it's not on?
I feel like I can't see.
And I hate this.
I want it back on.
Okay.
What do the other ones look like then?
Yeah, I was curious.
I was like, why does everybody have this on?
Even this shit.
Even this.
I was like, what's with the low quality?
Okay.
We...
I was wondering why everything looked like a TV from the 90s.
This was considered having a good cable box back in like 1991, by the way.
Unbelievable.
Okay.
Well, thank you for telling me that.
For a second, I thought it was on the game too.
I was like, holy shit, that's bad.
All right.
Let's go.
How do I get up here?
I don't want to run out of these.
I can't...
That's not reliable.
I gotta go all the way around.
Sharpen the game.
The game is already really sharp.
I don't want any more people to leave that haven't already.
Get that poison shit out of here.
Get it off.
Deep fried.
Yeah.
All right.
Uh, I can't get over there, guys.
I'm gonna have to arc these in a way that it hits and explodes at the right time.
I'm like kind of far away.
Come on.
I got five more attempts.
No.
Yes.
What is this?
Can you replace something?
Return.
After a period of time, you'll be returned to where you cast the spell.
That's a torch?
I just want to see.
Ow.
Don't...
Okay.
Stop it.
Stop.
What the fuck is happening?
Fuck this thing.
I'm not dead.
I'm fine.
I can't die here.
What does this do?
Faster wands.
All right.
I don't blow this.
I gotta...
Can I heal somehow?
Ah!
All right.
It's fine.
Fly to the moon.
I miss every shot.
Okay.
No.
He's...
I'm good.
He's checking.
I don't want to die.
God.
Okay.
Good.
We're good.
Just don't get killed.
That's a big thing over there.
That's a huge enemy.
Instead, you dropped a lot of gold.
That's a lot of money.
Don't touch it.
It's too...
It's a risk.
Too risky.
My god.
No.
I didn't...
Why did I think for some reason
that if you went to the portal
that it took off status effects?
I don't know why.
No.
I'm not...
I'm so pissed off.
No integration.
No.
I'm mad now.
I have to be happy for the integration.
I'm not gonna say that.
Fix this, please.
Fix this.
Okay.
I'll fix it.
Pretty good Game Boy Advance game, I will say.
Okay.
One...
One more.
And then...
Okay.
One more.
And then I'm gonna pee.
And then I'm gonna do integration.
Okay.
I want a good one.
I just keep getting distracted.
No more distractions.
Okay?
No more.
If you have something that you have to tell me,
tell me after class.
No more distractions.
Don't bring up like Family Guy iPad games.
Don't bring up like how funny I looked
when I was...
Had bad posture or something.
No.
I don't want to know.
First wand of the evening.
And it is...
I mean, it's just...
It's just fire shot.
Fire shot.
Next wand is...
It's not a wand.
It's just water.
Who cares?
I'm not clicking on that link.
I told you no distractions.
This is a no distraction run.
Playing as if my life depends on it.
I want that gold.
I have...
I don't even know where it is.
Whatever.
Mr. Albertson, can I use the bathroom?
No.
Not until after school.
That's actually kind of...
No, that's fucked up.
No, you can go to the bathroom if you want.
What is that?
That's too long to wait.
Can I leave this, please?
I'm stuck.
Snow potion.
Did that help?
Not really.
All right, we're good.
I want to get in there.
Is that an up breaking?
Peeing out viewers.
All right, fine.
This looks good.
Oh, what is this?
Slime ball.
Poison to slime.
This sucks.
No.
Oh, wait. Wrong thing.
Looks good.
This looks like it's gonna be pretty sick.
It's very slow.
Why is he going so fast?
Mr. Albertson, can we do chat integration?
No, no.
What a shitty school this would be.
You guys just watch the teacher play Noito?
Mr. Albertson, when are we gonna actually do schoolwork?
I don't know.
Later.
Shut up.
Leave me alone.
This is the run.
Can I hit one of these guys and do...
Any damage at all would be great.
Mr. Albertson, can you help me with my homework?
Sure.
Bring it here.
You need help with your homework?
Yeah, sure.
Bring it here.
Let me see it.
What is that?
No.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, it looks like you didn't fail out question three, four, and five.
Let me help you with this.
Get the trash.
I gotta sit down.
Um, what am I?
What do I do?
What's happening?
What's wrong with me?
What do I do?
Where am I?
I stuck here forever?
Don't shoot yourself in the head with the...
Oh, it's unstable teleportaneum potion.
Well, take it and drink it.
Okay, where...
It's got a thousand subs.
What?
I just, like, choked on my own water in my mouth.
Oh, shit.
Get in there.
I hate that feeling.
Is that not enough?
Really?
Hold on, I gotta...
Play the game?
I am playing.
What are you talking about?
I'm currently, like, just playing the game.
Not fucking kill me, you fireball asshole.
Don't you die.
Oh, come on.
How many times do I have to hit you before you die?
Gowsum.
Snow and water potion combined.
That's a good idea.
Watch out, this guy's gonna throw a bomb.
I gotta...
I dropped a shitload of money too.
What's happening?
I can't move.
I just locked myself in the fire.
Stop, please.
Quit pretending to play the game and play the game.
All right, let's make some spells.
Splitter bolt with a timer.
Odd fireball.
Glitter bomb.
Firebolt with a trigger.
And chainsaw.
We have some wands to use here.
Get the chainsaw first and foremost.
Let's get a firebolt with a trigger.
Glitter bomb.
And split bolt.
Time to make something happen here.
All right, this one is the...
That one's good.
This is bomb, which kind of just sucks.
What does this have for?
Mana charge.
Max mana capacity one.
Cast delay.
It's very, very fast.
That mana recharge though is really awful.
A glitter bomb.
Summons a bomb.
And summon a bomb.
Okay, I'm gonna put a chainsaw here.
Yeah, there it is.
Now this one only...
This is a shuffle.
But what if we do...
Let's just fuck the whole thing up.
You know what I mean?
This is gonna be a mystery wand.
Cast delay 0.3 seconds.
1.5 second charge time.
That's terrible.
Shut this down.
Please, never subbed.
Not donating.
Free entertainment.
That's fine.
That's cool.
I don't care.
I think this is gonna be a super mystery wand.
Like, what do I even care?
I take this off though.
Groomer is an idiot.
Why?
What are you guys doing?
Will you guys settle down?
What the fuck is happening?
Oh shit, that turns into like a million different bombs.
Okay, I like it.
All right, this is fine.
Worm detractor?
I'm in a low capacity.
Or trick blood money.
Groomer's real name is Mitch.
It is not.
It is not actually at all.
All right, I'll integrate just after this.
I'm gonna integrate just after this, okay?
You will get integrated.
Somebody gave me $50.
They gave me 5,000 bits.
That was goo berry juice thanks to the 50 bucks.
That's a 5-0.
Hey Groomer, you're ugly.
Does the engineer dance from the popular multiplayer team base shooter Team Fortress 2?
All right, how about high mana low capacity?
Let's go.
Your currently held wand loses half its capacity, but it gains more mana.
Oh fuck, currently held wand.
Oh well, we're gonna be slime boys now.
Put the other spell on it.
Oh wait a minute.
It's not bad yet.
We're fine.
Which one should I put on?
Chainsaw?
That's not even that bad.
No, wrong.
What?
Main job was good on bomb wand.
Now that's good on here too.
Chainsaw is great for digging.
Yeah, that would be fine.
This one I really fucked it up, but whatever.
I'm not supposed to do this now.
All right, we're gonna have to try to get good with the slime.
Build a statue.
No, I know what happens when you do that.
It's not good.
Currently...
Yeah, this is awesome actually.
I'm actually kind of glad I fucked that up because I can dig forever and not have to wait.
This is good.
This worked out pretty well.
But we have to slime, which sucks.
Let's dig down here.
Come on.
What did I hit?
This chat.
Look at this chat room right now.
It's fucked.
I want the gold here.
I'm just gonna dig and get all this gold.
Who cares?
Toxicity is at a thousand percent.
It is.
It's getting there.
Ooey gooey, ooey gooey, ooey gooey.
What have I done?
I've created a monster.
Don't they say that like the streamer's community is an offshoot kind of of the streamer's personality?
You guys are all in Arkham right now.
What have I done to you?
Look at all this gold down here.
I can't ignore it.
If you're good at something, never do it for free.
This is 2D Minecraft.
I don't even remotely accurate what you just said.
Don't you want me to get money?
Come on.
Don't you see the 69 number?
That one's funny.
It's ooey gooey terraria.
You just said that in front of terraria.
That doesn't even make any sense.
I really do want it, but let's go.
Look at all this shit.
All right.
We've got a pog one situation here.
This is double spell, double glitter bomb.
Jumped over that.
It's actually not bad.
I actually like it.
What's wrong with this person?
Uh, die?
Die?
Not gonna die.
Not going to die.
All right.
Well, I'm just going to fucking destroy them.
Does that look, huh?
Glitter bomb.
Max HP.
Go.
What does this do?
Oh, it's a, it's a weird thing.
Nice.
All right.
Money.
Get money.
Quick.
All right.
There's the end.
We're good.
I'm fine.
Look it.
We're good.
Please ban everyone who's in chat.
All right.
Do a massive ban.
Glitter bombs kind of suck.
The blast radius is awful.
What's with this crap blast radius?
And I'm on fucking fire.
Of course I am.
How do I even light on fire?
Can I not get through this?
Is it too tough?
There we go.
And there we are again.
On fire.
Uh, if you see here, I'm still on fire.
I know this is a glitch with the demo I recorded, but still on fire.
So I backstabbed this guy.
Still on fire.
Wow.
We don't even, we don't even have any real true German 985 YouTube fans in here, do we?
The first video I ever made.
Okay.
Fine.
You know, sometimes I envy being in chat.
I do sometimes.
Because like, you could just write the most absolute fucking nonsense statement ever and
just sit there and laugh while maybe a handful of people like look at it and go,
what the fuck is that guy talking about?
Like, I kind of envy that in a way.
I do.
And I can't even read half the things that you guys say.
But I mean, it was just ridiculous.
It was ridiculous.
And you typed it, you press enter, and then you lean back in the chair and you left
because you knew that one or two people, including me, might see it and go,
this guy's fucking crazy.
This looks good.
Arrow.
Speed up.
Triple spell.
360 mana.
Fast arrow.
This thing is galactically good.
Is that fire or is that honey?
What is this?
I can't pick this up?
Protection from all.
Oh, what?
Okay.
All right, I gotta go.
I gotta get out of here.
I like the arrow though.
We can make it something cool.
With the blood.
Not into the, what?
No, I'm just, I'm saying into this part.
200.
Finally, we get some wands.
Can afford, holy shit, that's a lot of slime.
Four spells cast per cast.
Four slimes.
This is four spells.
This is bouncy ball and fire.
Can afford that one.
I can't afford this one, unfortunately, and I can not afford that one either.
Burning trail, tons of bouncy balls.
That's probably, they'll just kill me.
They're gonna bounce around everywhere and it's gonna light me on fire and I'm gonna die.
This one, on the other hand, is kind of could replace this one.
Four slimes at the same time.
Better cast delay.
Slightly worse mana charge speed.
More maximum mana.
Extra capacity.
Yeah, let's go.
Four second recharge.
Yeah, but I shoot four at the same, yeah, it's a long time.
Get the bounce wand.
All right, I'm gonna replace bounce wand with, yeah, I get this thing.
I mean, this thing could be good if I could just fire a regular weapon.
That cast delay is stupid.
That's ridiculous.
Tiny recharge time, tiny cast time.
It's a spam gun.
I could, should I put the saw on here?
Devon chat, Devon chat.
Really?
What's up?
Let me just, I wanna see something, hold on.
Spark bolt on this guy down here.
That's really, really good, but the, look at that, the recharge time is awful.
Yeah, that's why this thing sucks.
But no, wait, recharge time of point?
Oh, that is bad.
Yeah, this thing sucks.
Yeah, forget it.
I'm gonna get rid of this one.
I'll get the, I'll get the hell on earth wand.
All right, I'm gonna get hell on earth.
Let's see what it does.
Please don't kill me.
Yep, okay.
And this, you want me to use this wand?
This is the wand you want me to use?
This is, this is gonna be very bad.
I will try.
I have no guarantees though.
All right, let's take a look at the other stuff.
Okay, and saw's fine.
Can I make the arrows any better?
Triple speed up.
What about triple speed up?
Like, get rid of the arrows, just for a second.
It doesn't hurt you, dummy.
Oh, well, what about triple speed up this?
So what?
No, don't throw it on the ground.
Go get that.
Projectile speed.
I just get rid of the triple spell and just do speed?
Hold on.
It's like, I can use it much more often, but hold on.
Yeah, I can do it more often.
There's never a slow down.
That's better.
It's brain.
Wait, is it shoot it?
Wait, what?
Oh, it's shuffle.
Whatever.
I got this wrong.
Remove speed.
I'll put speed back on.
Welcome to the wand expo.
All right, I'm ready.
I'm going to change this, though.
Uh, wait, can I make this anything?
I want to make this better.
Slime sucks.
I want to replace it with something else.
It sucks.
It just does.
Let's be honest.
It sucks.
Wand three should be in wand one.
Wand...
Yeah, these two, I'll switch back and forth.
And there's my chainsaw.
Speed up the slime.
Yeah, but I...
Slime sucks.
I'll replace it with something else later.
All right, let's go.
Get the spread off of wand four.
I kind of like it like this.
Speed up the slime.
No.
I'll get...
It's awful.
Let's go.
Uh, worm attractor.
Kills to mana or explosion immunity.
I'll take it.
No direct damage from explosions ever again.
Don't...
Don't make the god mad.
Don't make god mad.
Put yourself out.
Oh, I made it.
Okay.
I think I'm gonna win this one.
I don't even know if I'm firing the weapon.
I need fire immunity.
And then I'm good.
I'm running out of oxygen.
Why am I running out of oxygen?
All right.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I don't even know where I am.
Enough, enough, enough, enough.
So don't do that.
I don't want that one.
It's terrible.
Speed and a bunch of dynamite.
Who needs it?
Actually, better than the slime.
I can't fire that once, man.
I guess I can fire that before I go into a new room.
I've already hurt myself.
I've already taken tons of damage.
It should have never happened.
You're gonna jump out and get me?
Really?
Well, now I am actually in trouble.
Truly in trouble now.
I need something to save me here.
Fill up your glass with water.
Oh, shit.
That person has a sniper rifle.
Oh, why?
What?
All right.
You know what?
Fuck you.
Just crouch in the water.
Fill this up.
What are these?
Teleport, titanium, levatium.
Wait, what is levatium?
Okay, that's pretty good.
Hover around more.
Oh, that's actually really nice.
All right.
Let's move.
I didn't think about it.
Go get crunk.
Crunk.
Follow the lever.
Go get crunk.
What are you talking about?
Sometimes I feel like you guys are a computer.
Okay.
I'm still all right.
This is as far as I've ever been.
Almost just rolled that into me.
Almost.
I give you credit.
You tried.
Where am I going?
There's nothing here.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Isn't this progress?
What do you mean stop?
There's nothing even over here.
Why would I go up when I need to go down?
I'm not going up.
I need to go down.
You're a coward.
Coward for what?
I don't know.
What do you mean I'm a coward?
I want to go down, not up.
Yeah, I died.
The portal is down.
What?
Is there something bad up there that's going to kill me?
He's like this, like this, like this.
Poison.
Drink the poison.
Drink the thing.
All right.
I'm good.
Drink.
You're a chicken boy.
We can all have our opinions.
It's fine.
I'm not messing around.
I'm just going to start doing that.
Just getting out of the way.
There's something over there.
He's dead.
All right.
I think he's dead.
What is hurting me?
What hurt me?
Somebody's flying.
Hold on.
What is that?
Is this good?
Acid ball.
Terrifying acidic projectile.
Increased mana.
I'll try it.
Yes, I'm good.
Get me out.
Where this I've ever been.
There you go.
I don't have enough money to buy any of these besides this one.
But I don't really want it.
I think I'm just going to save my money.
Remove the fire from this.
Yeah, not a bad idea.
Yes, I took the fire off.
I took the fire off.
I took the fire off of that.
I took off the fire.
Why is it doing this?
What's down there?
What is that?
I can't fucking believe it, dude.
Why?
What is going on right now?
I took the fire off.
Why is it still fire?
Always casts explosion.
Get rid of the spread.
I'll be all right.
Okay.
This is what we take a look.
I can only afford this, but I don't think I want it.
Do more balls.
I wish I had more balls.
I could do one, two, three, four,
but then I could do something else, too.
I could do three spark bolts.
Shoot four at once.
You don't need the spread.
Hold on.
Oops.
So then why don't I do those four,
and then spark bolt as well?
Does it even matter?
No.
All right.
How do I get down there?
Do you see that thing down there?
I got to pee really bad.
I got to pee.
I'll be right back.
Hey, what's up?
More money came in.
More $50 donations came in.
Two of them.
Five thousand.
We can't hear you?
You can.
Hold on.
I'm going to burp.
There was five thousand bits from the Beer Hunter.
Thank you, Beer Hunter.
Remember, my new schedule of work has basically prevented me
from watching you stream for several months.
I miss you.
And since I got the chance to catch a stream,
I thought I would pop in and say hi.
But we've all missed you, too.
What the?
I was supposed to say what the fuck,
but you got like a new work schedule.
I was going to jokingly say,
seriously, thank you for the huge amount of money,
and welcome back.
You can catch a stream.
You can.
If you can't, you can't.
It's all good.
Thanks for the huge drop of money.
And then speaking of another huge drop of money,
thank you to Spike Sensei for the five thousand bits.
Aloha, Jerma.
This is my first time ever donating.
Sorry for leeching free content this whole time.
Hope you have a good night and the rest of your stream.
It's not, you're not leeching free con-
But by its very design, this stream is free.
Leeching.
Thanks for the 50 bucks.
You're not a-
You never were a leech.
Oh, nice Powerade.
I love Powerade.
I really do.
I don't even care if you're not supposed to drink it.
Unless you're like working out and I give a shit.
I love it.
All right, let's go.
Swado advertisement joke needs to stop.
I love Powerade.
I love McDonald's.
I love Powerade and I love McDonald's.
What do you want me to do?
Lie to you and say that I don't like it?
Glass Cannon.
Oil Blood.
Or Angry Ghost.
I could re-roll it.
True.
Angry Ghost.
What color of Powerade?
Purple Powerade's the best.
Blue Powerade's okay.
Red Powerade is third place, I think.
And Orange Powerade and Orange Gatorade
taste like stomach acid or throw up.
I don't like either one of them.
Let's do Angry Ghost.
An angry spirit comes to your aid
copying nearby spells and projections.
Really?
I don't see you copying anything.
Oh, anger the god.
Go.
Doesn't look that angry.
No, not really.
Orange Gatorade made me throw up one.
Yeah, it sucks.
I don't understand why they-
I don't know why they still make it.
I have no idea why they make it still.
Nobody drinks it.
It's horrible.
Ah, ah!
Move!
Why can I-
Please move.
Please?
Please move?
What the fuck?
Dude, all right.
I've had enough of this shit.
Did I just get hit in the face by my own thing?
What the fuck?
Why would-
Why am I stuck in the pixel?
That's very angry inducing.
I can't-
I can't even move.
I get stuck in, like, the pixel shit.
Oh god, I'm dead.
What's there to shoot?
Sniped point blank.
No, but right here I got, like, fucking latched on
and they're all just aiming at me and firing at me.
This hissy base is a madhouse.
Oh, I'm dead.
I just, like, I just died.
I'm dead.
All right, fun.
Right, really fun.
In the first five seconds of the map, I'm dead.
What is this-
What is this bullshit down here?
Like, I'm just-
I'm just dead immediately.
You get, like, stuck in the quicksand.
I'm turning on integration.
This is stupid.
All right, let me turn on streamer mode.
I don't want to leak anything.
Is this going to leak something?
Streaming.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, we're apparently connected.
I guess.
I guess the chat is connected somehow.
What does that mean?
Let stream viewers interact with your game through the Twitch chat.
Okay, did it work?
Next vote in 16 seconds.
What are you voting for?
Social security just got DM'd to me.
Voting ends.
New one.
Wait, is this going to just give it to me?
This just gives me shit?
I told you the chat was going to be a mess when we turn this on.
Give me a-
Give-
Oh, yeah, remove the ground.
Sure, that one will be fun.
What does that even do?
Okay, I guess it removes the-
Oh, it's this one.
Circle of thunder.
All right, I want to go down.
Can't fucking believe I just did that.
What the fuck did I do that for?
I just was trying to rush.
All nearby ground disappears.
Well, that ain't gonna-
Thank you, you just saved my life.
Thanks, guys.
I appreciate that.
You literally just saved me from dying.
Too many things to keep track of.
How do I remove fire from the game?
Hey, next time you can vote.
Vote on take fire out of the game.
All the gold?
Yeah, I can't go there because I'm going to burn.
Nothing do I hate more than getting stuck in video games.
Like getting stuck on shit.
Nothing pisses me off more than getting stuck.
Like, nothing more.
Nothing more than that.
I'm already fucking dead.
Just reset it, reset it, reset it.
Reset it, kill me.
I don't-
Reset it.
It's anger inducing, huh?
It is.
I agree.
Oh, I'm changing some of these things up a little.
Now I know why everyone said this is a rage game.
I didn't believe you until-
Until I got to that temple and got stuck in the ground and died.
I don't want you guys to see this.
So your time between votes.
How about what?
60 seconds?
Voting time.
30 seconds?
Okay.
Hide the vote count.
Yep.
I don't want you guys to see that.
Tiny ghosts can be named after viewers, sure.
Yeah, that sounds good.
All right, that's good.
All right, I'm going to try as hard as I can now.
Here we go.
Actually, this one's going to be the fucking run.
No more getting stuck on tiny sand pixels.
Okay, enter the mines.
What did you just do to me?
Did you just headbump me?
I got that money.
Oh shit, I can't even see what it is either, can I?
No, I can't.
Sea of lava.
A huge body of lava is summoned.
Where?
Right there.
Okay.
You know what?
I actually don't like the fact that I don't know what you guys are doing.
Because it's a mystery to me too.
I don't like that.
What's- what is this?
It's dynamite.
All right, let's dynamite over there.
Let's go.
How much mana?
This thing sucks.
Come here, cannibal.
Come here.
Come here, coward.
He flipped me off.
Oh, give me that.
Oh, it's poison.
I can't even get in there anymore.
Shit, I want- whatever that-
Give it to me.
Drain the poison.
One of those fire assholes is right there too.
They got saw blades everywhere.
For a time, all projectiles become giant saw blades.
All-
Okay.
Oh my god, that did so much damage to me.
That was so bad.
What happened to me?
I turned into a snail.
Did you guys do this?
Oh, that's good.
Oh, right, things are saw blades.
Is it still saw blades?
Jesus.
And I got hurt.
Delete poison and fire from the game.
Oh, I'm dead.
I get touched once.
I'm fucking dead.
Do three.
Everybody do three.
Oh, that was ugly.
I can't even do it, man.
That shit does 75 damage.
I was fucking merked.
I feel like this is-
I'm- you know what?
I'm so glad that I did not turn this on until, like, playing for a little while.
If I had done this from the second I turned the stream on,
I would not have thought the game was fun.
I would have been like, oh, that was cool for a little bit, I guess.
No, let's move the fuck on.
This is stupid.
Now there's no going back, right?
There's not a scenario now on stream where I turn this off.
You all know it.
Alcohol trail.
Your projectiles leave a trail of alcohol.
Wait.
What the fuck is going on?
Well, that's an acid potion.
Just start it over again.
Start it over again.
Just start over.
I- start it over.
You didn't check your equipment, you nerd.
Okay, here's water.
It's not acid.
Can I get down to at least the second floor, please?
There's so many potions in the game.
I didn't know acid was a possibility.
Jump.
Shower.
A rain cloud spawns on you.
Oh, cool.
Thanks.
That'll help with the fire.
Actually, very good thing for you to do.
It looks like a big one down there.
Burn him.
All right.
I got the cloud still, right?
How long does it last?
Oh, I don't have it anymore.
It's just a torch.
Just a torch.
That looks really cool for just what is essentially a nerf gun.
Sing the raid song?
Oh, there's a raid.
All right, I'll sing the raid.
Thank you for the raid.
Really appreciate it.
I am so happy.
Thanks.
Who was it?
Busty Lugs VR.
I think that's a VR streamer.
Thanks a lot.
Welcome.
Hope you had a good stream.
Welcome, everybody.
We're playing Noito with Twitch integration.
It's pretty cool.
Pretty fun.
That was sad, wasn't it?
I turned on the auto-tune and just started making horrible noises.
I hope it was painful.
Oh, you guys just did the Yoshi's Island thing to me.
This is not that bad.
Now, that's good.
Yep.
All right, this just saved the run here.
There's a song that goes with this, too, isn't it?
Yeah, it's like...
That's Angry Beavers, never mind.
I forgot about that show.
All right, now when I turn the stream off,
I am going to watch like four episodes in a row of Angry Beavers.
Oh, you...
Copy, Beaver.
Finally made it to the bottom.
Can you believe it?
All right, I'm going to wait for this.
What is this?
Loot, treasure, rain, glisten, and health plus.
All right, give me something good.
Treasure, rain.
Yes!
Holy...
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can't walk over there.
It's going to stop it.
Why did I stand here?
No, I can get it.
Oh, it disappeared.
I got it.
Thanks, guys.
Thanks for the treasure.
Nobody just gave a lot of bits.
Yeah.
400.
I can afford whatever I want now.
Double spell, double spell.
Slimeball light.
It's kind of expensive.
Spells.
It only shoots one.
Energy sphere.
This was like four or five.
It's not bad.
Max mana.
How much is the mana to shoot this mana?
20.
That's not bad.
Could be worse.
Ooh, spitter bolt.
700 mana.
Dogshit recharge.
But, hmm, what about this one?
Giga disk projectile.
I kind of like this one.
Teleport bolt.
Magical bolt that moves you wherever it ends up.
No, don't want that.
All right, I'll take the Giga one.
Go.
Did they hit me?
Can they hit me?
Can these hit me?
Okay.
Well, all right.
I'm good.
Let me see if I want to change this around, though.
This is cool.
This is Giga.
Okay.
I'm happy with all this right now.
That sucks, actually.
Plague rats.
Extra knockback.
Or your projectiles come back to you.
Well, they already do.
That's...
Okay.
So it was extra.
Oh, shit.
Okay, whatever.
So that probably wouldn't have happened if I didn't already have it on there.
You shot yourself in the head.
You need to give a thousand subs.
No.
This is not in the game.
Little hope.
That was looking like a pretty good run, too.
Oh, well.
What is that?
That's going to blow up that...
Okay, that's oil.
I get it.
You become drunk.
It's like a sword.
I'm already on fire.
What does drunk mean?
Holy shit.
Look at the capacity on this thing.
Firebolt.
This has got 11 capacity.
It only shoots one at a time, though.
And it's shuffled.
That's terrible.
Bad.
Yeah, it's kind of bad.
It can't even...
I don't...
Can that even become any good?
Or no?
Not really.
Is it a double cast?
No.
Does it?
Oh, that's pretty.
That's really pretty.
That's cool.
It's burning all, like, the sand.
Let go...
Just kick this out of the way.
I'm not touching that.
Oh, let's blow this up.
Looking good.
Loot.
Oh!
Oh, you guys just did that.
What's in it?
Okay, that was a thousand...
Oh my...
Okay, that's a thousand gold in there.
That's one thousand gold.
Okay.
Looking pretty good so far.
This is the run.
Just don't...
Don't hurt me.
Don't fuck it up.
Don't make, like, lava spawn.
Don't spawn a boss.
Chat, give, and chat, take away.
Is that a tea kettle?
Oh, it's an egg.
Wait!
This is going to be somebody in chat, right?
Who is it?
What's their name?
Do they have a name?
Oh no, that's ghosts.
All right, watch out.
I don't want to hurt you.
Okay.
I want to get in there.
There's something in there.
There's a potion in there.
Oh, sickom.
This is a berserkium potion.
And this is, like, a gem?
Broken wand?
Please get rid of an item to make space for it.
What's...
What do you mean, broken wand?
Your body has burnable gas for a time.
Okay.
Well, I don't...
What should I get rid of?
Fire potion?
All these, if I throw,
I feel like I'm going to explode immediately.
Broken wand.
What does it do?
This wand has snapped in half,
but it still crackles with magical energy.
A stink cloud.
Yeah.
You guys did it.
You can throw it for a random spell.
Okay.
Why did I think the frogs were friendly?
I thought the frogs were friendly.
I'm not even going to blow it up.
Yes, it is.
It's just all poison down there.
I can't even touch it.
I need some more money, first and foremost.
Hash.
Did I just hit myself?
I did, didn't I?
I'm moving fast?
This guy just died.
Am I moving that much faster?
Maybe a little.
Why do I care about money?
I have a thousand gold.
What am I doing?
I forgot about that.
Poison.
It's flexing.
Sure.
Okay.
Picked up a spell refresher.
This is a teleport wand.
Wait.
That's kind of interesting.
What is it?
Always cast gunpowder arc.
And I fly wherever I move to.
So this is a firewall or a fire walking from Diablo.
It sucks.
Yeah, it probably sucks.
This looks okay.
Four spells at the same time.
Always cast magic arrow.
And it's going to do all this.
Lower cast delay and spread it everywhere.
Black hole spark.
No.
Odd one.
No, it's not.
Fuck this thing.
I tried black hole before and it was a disaster.
Good.
Okay.
It's just the gigasaw thing again.
And what is this?
Bubble spark.
A bouncy inaccurate spell.
But this is huge spread and double spell.
Oh, it only casts one.
This thing sucks.
Bubble spark.
Third one is probably the best stats.
Axe mana.
Mana charge speed.
Cast delay.
This one's kind of good too.
I kind of want to play with this one though.
Always casting this as OP.
How much damage does it do?
10?
I guess that's good.
I'm going to get it.
I can just put other spells on this.
A bunch of hissy appear out of thin air.
What's hissy rain?
Is like a bad joke.
All right.
How about this time?
Everybody has to agree to give me the good options.
I need the extra help.
This is a really good start.
This is a very good start.
Look at this thing.
It's very good.
Good starter wand.
And you gave me a thousand gold
and you took it all away in the next room?
Really?
Hey, here's a thousand gold.
Let's spawn like late game enemies on you
and have you die.
You track projectiles for a while.
Wait, these can't hurt me.
What's wrong with this frog?
What happened to me?
Why I'm a fish?
He just ate me.
Give me something to work with.
Try harder, boomer.
All right.
Fine.
That's how you want to play it?
I'll play it like that.
But if I were in the chat right now,
I would be pressing four.
Hey, guys.
I don't know.
I'm kind of new to video games.
I heard that there's a new Diablo coming out.
Do you know what the iteration is?
Is it three or is it...
I know there's a new Diablo coming out.
How many in the series have there been?
I don't even...
It's tricky for me.
In my mind, I don't know.
Huge worm appears.
I'm assuming he's here.
I'm assuming this huge worm is over here.
Yeah, there he is.
In the first room?
In room one?
Room one.
Why would you do this to me?
I didn't...
I just walked down out of the entrance.
All right.
I just gotta leave.
Get out quick.
Wherever he is, he's distracted.
Jesus Christ!
Is he blocking it?
What's he doing?
What's wrong with him?
Oh my God!
I just blew his head up.
Is it gold?
There's no gold.
Should have drank his blood.
I don't know.
I don't even have...
I can't even do anything.
Oh, I have 80 gold.
Yeah, I want the saw.
What the fuck?
You didn't even do that to me
and I just did it to myself.
Ooh.
This is my oh shit button
and this is the one I'm gonna use.
I'm gonna get...
Okay.
Improve my wands.
All your wands in new vicinity
get slightly better.
Did they?
Nice.
Nice, I can do this forever.
Why can I do this forever?
It's infinite.
Okay.
Now, what...
And the next one will give me health.
Perk lottery.
Goldest forever.
High mana, low capacity.
Wait a minute.
Should I do that one?
Lottery, lottery, lottery, lottery, lottery.
When you pick a perk
there's a 50% chance the others won't disappear.
That's actually pretty awesome.
All right.
Now give me like max HP plus 20.
On this list,
is it gonna be like a give the person money?
Or give the person health?
I want it.
I'm not gonna use that.
It's gonna kill me.
Fuck that thing, seriously.
Okay.
Regeneration field.
That's what I want.
Give me that one.
That means it's gonna heal me, right?
It's carrying a bomb.
Yeah, let me get a regeneration field.
Dead.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
There it is.
You guys rock.
Thank you.
Oh, I can't get in there.
Don't fall.
Guy's holding the bomb.
Scared the shit out of me right now.
I want nothing to do with that.
Can't go that way.
Maybe I can go that way.
Nice job.
You kicked it the right way.
Fuck.
It would suck the damn screen.
Why?
I'm never picking that up ever again.
I'm not...
If I see a saw blade,
I'm gonna rip it out immediately
and throw it in the trash.
I'm not using that ever again.
You know, like typically,
I would be so embarrassed.
That's very embarrassing.
But like, no.
That weapon sucks.
It's too difficult to use.
It's not even fun to use it.
It's not good.
It's bad.
Nice try.
Ooh.
I'll take that.
Summon random homunculi.
A group of helpful little homunculi's
are here for you.
Oh, is there people in chat?
There you are.
Look it.
Oh, wow.
There's four of you right there.
Well, let's go.
Let's go, Wizard of Oz crew.
Nice.
Good chug.
Good chuck.
CC monkey.
Well, I thought you died.
Hey, sad funda.
You're in the game now.
Those are fake viewers, are they?
They should be here.
Isn't that how it works?
What a horrible hallway to be in.
Oh, he just got sniped.
It's a really bad hallway.
Actually, really horrible.
Terrible.
Bad hallway.
Sorry.
He's...
You shouldn't have followed me down there.
Should not have followed me down there.
What's with these enemies?
They're terrible.
Very difficult role in the first room here.
Yeah, something good.
Rain cloud.
Whatever.
What was that?
That's a...
Wait, that's electrifying this.
New friendly ghosts.
A 8-bit ether and Red X Yeti.
Welcome to my...
If you guys didn't know,
these are my $5,000 level Patreon tier contributors.
You know, we jump in the game sometimes.
Hey, give that back.
Give that back.
That's my...
You can't just take wands.
How do I get that back?
All right.
Give me that wand.
I need money.
I'll stand on that.
You know what?
Fine.
Give me...
Whatever.
Just give me the wand.
That's pretty good to get right now.
I need health again.
Where's water?
No.
Okay.
Like, dilute this so I can stand on it.
That looks good.
I don't have that much money though,
but whatever.
Need health.
Okay.
Holy shit.
What is this?
I wish I had money.
All right.
Where's the money one?
Remove ground.
That's great.
What?
Everything stays.
You have angered the gods.
I didn't do that though.
What?
What is this?
Give me...
I don't know.
Give me this.
It's just...
It's just war and peace with you guys.
Hot and cold.
Fire and ice.
There's a thousand dollars.
You're Satan.
Somebody said,
I feel bad now.
Oh.
I see a health plus on there at number three.
That's a good one.
All right.
Can you guys just give me a god run
so I can get to like the end of the game?
I've gotten to like the last...
Second to last floor.
I can't beat it.
Give me a god run
so I can just smoke every floor.
Is that a bad thing or a good thing?
I have to kill this to spite you guys.
All right.
I think it just...
Last time this...
I...
Wait.
Wasn't it...
Did I get the chest?
I don't even know.
Drink the blood.
Drink...
Okay.
Fine.
I'll drink blood.
All right.
I drank the blood.
Why am I still on fire?
Help.
Ooh.
What's this?
Fireball.
Yeah.
I'll take it.
He's stuck down here.
All right.
Drink his blood.
So you're seeing things more clearly.
Oh, I can't...
Fuck it.
Let's go.
Nearby materials transmuted to acid.
You know, okay.
Torch integration sounds like a good idea
but I think it only works out
if I activate it
on the third floor or something
because I don't have any items.
I thought it was going to be gold.
Oh.
Oh well.
You can disable things that you don't want.
Oh.
That's fun to mess around.
I see a couple of options that I like on there.
I'm not going to...
I will not influence the vote
but I'm just telling you
at least I swear to God
I didn't even look at what it was.
It's a rocket.
I thought it was a bomb.
Already right off the bat.
Okay.
I got to get...
I got to get up there.
50 HP.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Give me another one of those.
More.
Okay.
This looks like it's going to be the run.
If you understand.
Bubble Spark.
Super cast speed.
This is the one.
It is.
So don't mess this up.
You know what to do.
Look at this.
It's so good.
It's unbelievable.
It's very, very, very, very good.
Get...
I can't touch...
Get out of the way.
Fire.
Nothing else.
This looks like another wand in here.
Holy shit.
This thing sucks.
This is the worst wand of the entire game I've played so far.
Yes.
Shuffle.
0.5.
Recharge time.
Whatever.
Just take it.
What am I getting here?
What are we doing?
Treasure Rain.
Hell yeah.
No, no.
Bad place for it.
Bad place to do this.
Get all the big ones.
Come on.
There's another big one over here.
No.
Nice.
300 bucks.
Thanks.
Thank you, guys.
Really working out here.
Doing a great job.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
Tons.
Big thanks.
Major thank you.
Big thank you incoming.
Thanks, guys.
Don't kill me.
Pirate.
No begging.
Kill him.
Wait, you want me to beg?
We want you to beg.
Hold here.
Yes.
I don't even know what twitchy is,
but I feel like it's not good.
And I feel like I don't want it.
Loot.
You guys have...
Look at you guys working together here.
It's a beautiful thing.
And that's a mega wand.
Purple.
Triple spell propane tank.
Propane tank.
It's a mega wand.
I don't even know what that means.
It shoots 10 propane tanks?
Wait.
It shoots two at the...
Okay.
So it's going to shoot four at a time.
I feel like that's going to come in
not very much handy soon.
I just need to see what it does.
Holy shit.
Okay.
That's...
I don't...
Okay.
It hurts being in that.
I don't know what that...
I don't like it.
I don't want it.
Is this all gas?
It hurts if I touch it.
Do not do one.
Ow!
Don't do one.
Do not do one.
Don't do it.
I'm going to wait and see what you guys do
because there's a health pack right here.
Excess thank you.
Triplicate bolt?
Triplicate bolt.
I want to see what it does.
Teleporting cast.
Don't want it.
Bubble spark.
And...
Hold on.
Wait.
I can do another bubble spark here.
Does this work?
Kind of like a shotgun.
Oh, it needs mana.
It needs too much mana.
That's so good.
Wand four has mana cast.
Wait.
Hold on.
Are you saying switch this?
No.
What if I had to do this though?
Become invincible for one minute.
Oh, thanks.
What does this do?
I think that's all right.
No, it's not.
Too much mana.
This is perfect.
Put it all on the fourth wand.
You're wasting immortality.
Well, what do you want me to do?
You wasted it.
Move.
Do something.
Triple cast, Germo.
Triple spell.
What are you saying, dude?
Hold on.
Spark bolt on three.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Spark.
Okay.
So you're saying that put these down here
and then put this down here.
That's pretty...
That's really good though.
But is it good enough?
What's...
What did you do to me?
What did you do?
Who did you just summon?
Projectile repulsion field.
Breathless.
Faster levitation.
I can't...
Okay.
This one.
Yeah.
Is that good?
Run, you fool.
I mean, this is really good.
No.
He's stalling.
I don't...
I don't want to...
This is like...
You guys summoned a boss.
Go to shop and replace one.
Oh, wait.
I can get with this one too.
Move this to here.
This to here.
And then I let...
Wait.
This one is...
What the fuck did I...
What am I doing with this one?
Sea of...
Don't do that right now.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta go.
I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go.
I gotta go, I gotta go.
Why is there poison in here?
What is this?
What is this Star Trek beam?
And why is it filling the entire game?
Oh, shit.
Get rid of this...
How do I get rid of...
I gotta get rid of that fire.
I don't know what that is.
Okay, I'm gonna...
That was...
Jesus.
No, it's gonna follow me up here.
You know what I think when I see that?
I just think of like a soda.
When you pour a Coke for the first time.
What on earth?
Summon egg.
Summon a shitload of eggs?
Fire?
This is...
I just...
It's a friend gun.
Holy shit.
This is unbelievable.
Okay, let's go.
I'm just gonna be a Diablo II necromancer.
Thanks for the 80 HP.
It's recharging.
Oh, I have too many people out.
All right.
There's too much shit on the screen right now.
And I need to douse myself.
What is shooting at me?
Too much on the screen.
Way too much on the screen.
I have no idea what's going on.
I gotta turn like the particles down.
I have absolutely no fucking idea what's happening.
Are they shooting me?
What the fuck is going on?
Put me out!
Go into the water!
All right.
It's two all over the place.
I can't do it.
Now, give me a shielding ghost.
So, hold on a minute.
What was going on there?
Summoned an egg that houses a friendly creature.
Or just give her the fire thing?
Energy orb.
Critical plus.
Full scatter spell.
Oceans appear.
Are those good?
These are.
This better not kill me when I'm done.
What is this Skittles one down here?
Okay.
Should I eat the Skittles?
No, I'm not eating anything.
I'm not touching any of this shit.
I kind of have to go this way.
Controls are backwards.
Get out of here.
Drink it all?
I can't leave.
Okay.
Get...
Wait.
I think I...
I have explosives, right?
Don't...
What are you doing?
No!
Fuck me!
Why did it aim back at me?
You have angered the gods.
I didn't do anything.
I'm trying to leave.
Please, let me leave.
Blow up this thing over here.
Be angry, but just...
It's going to collapse, isn't it?
Your projectiles leave a trail of water.
I can't even move.
Oh, shit.
There he is.
He's so mad.
He can't even get in here, though.
This is so anti-climactic.
Oh, no.
He's charmed.
He's having problems, too.
Drink it.
I'm drinking it.
Go left?
Hold on.
The controls are backwards.
Wait.
What's happening?
Oh, my God.
Where am I?
Okay.
I think we're...
Dude, I'm...
Okay.
We need to slow down.
I need to slow down.
And give me...
HP.
There's a golden wand in here.
Is it electrified?
This is electrified.
Shoot it.
Fuck.
No, just...
It's electrified.
I don't want to touch one.
It's electricity.
I want a crew.
How come they're not...
What's wrong?
Why are they not summoning anything?
Who is good and who is bad?
I don't know.
Okay.
Health.
Health pack.
Don't shoot the friendly.
They turn hostile.
That's going to be hard to do.
Don't shoot the friendlies.
Good luck.
There's like 15 of them.
I don't even know what just happened.
Your friend killed you.
All right.
I'm so addicted to this game,
but I will never complete it.
I will be honest with you.
I don't know what's wrong with my mind.
I thought that just said expired nuts
for a second.
I like to start on one.
Did you guys do that or did I do that?
I don't know.
I don't know what you guys just did,
but this fucked me all up.
Take cover.
Boom.
How much fire on this map?
I'm just getting out.
Just get me out of here.
I don't like that map.
Didn't like the spawn, right?
Didn't like any of...
Burning trail.
Explosion.
Should I...
Hold on.
An explosion for this one?
It just explodes when you press the button.
Of course it does.
And now I don't have any more money.
So we're just going to go.
You need a projectile on it.
What the fuck?
I just put it on.
You have trouble...
Turn it off.
Get this off.
Get it off.
Get it off the bar.
Get it off the hotbar.
Projectile duplication.
Stainless armor.
I feel like these both are good.
You take 50% less damage
as long as you don't have any stains on you.
I'm assuming that I have stains on me right now.
How do you get rid of stains?
Oh, you use oxy clean.
I need to walk around.
Okay, I take 50% less damage
as long as I don't have any stains.
What should we play tomorrow?
Any ideas?
I'm dead.
Let's find what I lost.
Okay, cool.
What do you guys want to do tomorrow?
More of this?
No, I can't do more of this.
I'm not good at this.
I love this game.
I love everything it stands for.
I love what it is
and I love all what it's about.
I need like two people to play this.
I need to split my body in half
and have one person control the aiming
and the shooting
and one person to move around.
Does anybody get that?
Because like aiming at the enemies
and oh, I got to shoot those guys
and watch out for the projectiles
that are right here.
I need to split myself in half
and have one person have the mouse
and one person have the WASD.
Because I need like two people
need to pay attention in this.
It's focusing on where an enemy is
and aiming and shooting at him
and then watch out.
There's a projectile
going to hit you in the face.
Just split myself in half.
What was that?
Oh, that was not bad.
It's called Motor Skills.
Hey, I beat Dark Souls.
Hey, no, excuse me.
I beat Sekiro last boss on stream.
You know some streamers
that fucking gave up on that.
I beat that on stream.
Final, true final boss of Sekiro.
I beat it on stream
with less than like 50 attempts.
I mean, Motor Skills.
I don't know if that's what it is.
Played Binding of Isaac.
Yeah, and I did very well.
Binding of Isaac is a little different
because Binding of Isaac is,
it's like zoomed in.
It's easier to like,
because an enemy over here
could like shoot a projectile
that moves like this and hit you.
Well, I have to pay attention
like in this sphere here.
Like I need to be,
it's not just like a cube this big
like Isaac is.
The game's very good.
Like this is a very good game.
I find it to be very, very fun
and very challenging
and very interesting.
I already know what you guys are going to pick.
And it's making me very upset.
So in that case,
I'm going to just run to the exit.
Oh, he's not even invisible.
He's just kind of,
sort of opacity dragged down.
Scammed?
Kind of.
A little bit, yeah.
Who's trying to talk to me?
That's a lot of money
but I can't go get it.
Ow!
I told you I couldn't go get it.
Please put me out.
No!
Oh yeah, I got it.
Well, play Fallout 2.
No, thanks.
It's a good game
but I'm just not really into it at the moment.
Bubble Spark is my favorite one.
Vertical Barrier.
That's a good one.
Luminous Drill.
Oh, so what should I get?
Definitely Bubble Spark.
Definitely Luminous Drill.
Definitely Vertical Barrier.
It tuned down for fuck's sake.
Time that guy out for like five seconds.
Thin Vertical Barrier
that will harm passing creatures
including you.
Okay.
I can put that up in front of me.
That will cast first.
Now that's Shuffle.
And then Bubble Spark.
And Luminous Drill.
I don't know what happened.
It harms you.
I aimed like...
What? It puts it like right where you spawn?
Where you're standing?
I know but I didn't think it was going to like instantly kill me.
I didn't know.
It's a static projectile, right?
But like I thought it was going to be like where I aimed the cursor.
Like it would place it like in front of me or something.
Where I put the cursor.
Not just like right where I am.
But did it?
I don't know.
You cause of death.
You are dead.
Oh that's...
That's unfortunate.
No.
Do a mayo making stream tomorrow?
All right.
Let's get...
Let's...
I need to get back to the...
What's it?
The Heesee Temple or something?
I got there once and then I had one more floor to go
but it was crazy.
I couldn't do it.
I guess you said mayo.
Now you know what I want right now?
I just want a turkey sandwich.
I want a turkey sandwich.
Thinly sliced turkey breast.
A layer of nice...
Nice thick hearty mayo.
Maybe one just slice of avocado.
Just a thin slice of avocado.
Ice piece of like American cheese on it.
Cheddar cheese maybe.
He's a big crispy lettuce.
Or you know how about a chicken cutlet sandwich
with a big crispy piece of lettuce on it.
And...
Squeeze mayo.
That's all you need.
I have this theory that people say gross to American cheese
are people that pretend to hate McDonald's
and then eat it like three times a week.
Dude, it's gross.
Well, I look...
I didn't say...
Hey, this is the...
Of course it's gross.
But it's still...
I still like to eat it.
But why?
I mean, just because things are a little sloppy
and a little...
You know, not the best thing in the world.
I mean, you don't like to have it from time to time.
If that were the case,
the alcohol industry wouldn't exist.
Portal to someplace.
Portal lead...
You do...
Oh, did you guys just teleport me to the...
This is the run.
This is...
No, it's not.
I'm taking a ton of damage.
This is not the run.
This is not the run at all.
Like these are all like late game enemies
that just instantly killed me.
Stage three is late game.
All right.
But hold on.
Did you see how many people were spawned?
There's like 12 people around me.
This is the run.
All right.
If I do not get to the floor...
Okay.
You ready for this one?
Ooh, you guys like beds.
You guys call me the gambler.
You guys like them a lot more than I do.
If I do not get to the bottom of this room,
I will give 100 community subs.
Of this room here.
I'm freaking the fuck out.
Hold on.
I'm going to shut the fuck up for this one.
Give me that.
What?
They're going to do three.
I think that's a boss.
It's a boss.
Yeah.
Good game.
Good game, man.
Do it again.
If I don't get to the bottom of the next one,
I'll give 50 subs.
It cuts in half every time because I keep winning.
We're going to go now.
Blast cannon.
Peace with the gods.
Or plague rats.
I don't know what that means,
but I just know it's probably not bad.
I have to go now.
I can die already.
Oh my goodness.
What happened?
I don't know what happened.
I have no idea what's going on.
What happened?
Why did that happen?
Oh, they're going to drown me with these potions.
They're going to do with the fucked up potion thing.
Hurry.
Get up.
Hurry and get up.
Scammed.
You picked it.
I didn't.
That's your own fault.
You should have looked at the fine print.
Drop it.
Safe.
Actual NA aim.
It's like I seriously...
That was bad.
Okay.
I made it.
Now it's 25.
I need these wands.
I haven't upgraded a wand in like 10 minutes.
Chunk of soil.
I can't even buy anything.
Worm detractor.
Bomb materialized.
Electricity immune to electricity.
A helpful little homunculus comes to your aid.
Well, you really don't want me to lose, do you?
Thanks.
That's down to 25.
You know it.
I know it.
Let's go.
Here's the remarkable thing about this.
With me needing to give subs if I lose.
With the default wand that I got in the beginning of the game,
I've gotten further than I've gotten in the last hour.
Give me a break.
I haven't upgraded one of these wands.
Easy.
That's a lot of money.
Stop spraying that shit.
I need that money.
What happened?
Oh, I took a little extra damage.
I didn't know you take extra damage when you're...
There's your 25 subs.
Hold on.
Doing it.
I'm doing it.
Sub it up.
It's not 100, but it's 25.
Pay up.
Gift.
Gift 25 subs.
A custom quantity.
35.
Take it or leave it.
Wait.
Hold on a minute.
35 like right now.
Like start over.
Double or nothing.
You got it.
Let's go.
50 subs.
Double or nothing.
Let's do it.
Floor one.
Floor number one.
Here we go.
Double or nothing.
Floor one.
And by the way, I'm going to make this fair.
I made this fair.
I'm not going to move until you guys get to vote.
Double is 50.
It is.
All these options are not very bad at all.
We have this no summon gigaworm, right guys?
Slimy.
Ooh, slime.
Everyone gets covered in slime.
No, don't slime me.
I don't even know what this is, but I'm going to pick it up.
It's slimed, bitch.
Okay.
I don't even know why.
Like right now, like that didn't do anything to me.
That doesn't get you closer to the 50 community subs,
but that person was just so ready to say that.
Like, yeah, fuck this guy.
All right, that didn't help us.
Oh, well, whatever.
Still, get slimed.
Okay, hold on.
Do I have any water?
Brine?
That's water, right?
Salt water.
Well, don't touch that.
Don't touch that.
Don't touch that, you idiot.
What are these?
Acid trail, fire trail, transportation, barrel man.
I don't know what these are.
I got to get through a safe space.
A safe place, safe.
It's not safe.
That's not safe.
Oh, they want a double or nothing again, don't they?
Want another double or nothing.
Back to 100.
That's not how that works.
Nope, we go down to 25 again.
Brimstone?
Summon hollow egg.
What is brimstone?
Fiery explosion.
Does it work on here?
If you win this one, chat has to give you a kiss.
Melee immunity.
Extra health or explosion immunity.
Let's go.
Wait, I'm on fire.
I'm not fire immune.
Hostile ghosts.
Okay, watch it.
Why am I on fire?
This is such a dog shit setup too.
I have the list.
This is so bad.
This is the worst setup ever.
I didn't even pay attention
because I thought you guys were going to drop lava.
I got to go now.
Oh, wrong button.
I win.
12.5.
Yeah, back to 12.5.
Well, it's whittling away down to 12.5.
Can't even afford any of this.
But I am going to change this shit
because I don't want that.
I want to give myself at least a chance.
Armed creature.
Our nearby creature gets a random wand.
Okay, well, it's good to know.
Water trail.
This wand doesn't even have anything on it.
All right, well, whatever.
Wait, do I only have?
What's the best for this?
0.22, 0.33.
Terrible mana.
It's awful.
0.250, 0.5.
Hold on a minute.
Water.
Ooh, that's cool looking.
That's not a good idea.
Okay, I can drown.
I kind of like...
Wait, did I just screw everything up?
Fire immunity.
Oh, it's over.
I can just blow myself up down the whole hallway.
What's the best for that though?
0.5, 0.5 max mana.
This one probably, right?
Bring them on.
Bring the worm on.
Just dig straight down.
Okay, I just need to be able to get to the bottom.
Sniper down here.
Oh, that was a worm.
I'm good.
I just, I need to...
What do I hear?
I get down.
Now you're down to what?
It's 5.5, 5.6.
This is the best one because I can just go right down and go...
Hello?
Where did you come from?
All projectiles eat the ground?
I can't even move.
It sucks.
This is not even fair.
Wait!
Go, go, go, go.
No!
What?
I thought I was immune to explosions.
I was immune to explosions.
How am I?
I was immune to fire and immune to explosions.
How do I die?
Blue gas.
Oh, you're immune to explosions and immune to fire,
but you can't breathe in a little gas.
Six subs.
All right, I'm just going to round it up to 10 because that's like 6.5.
A droople of nothing.
50?
50 and nothing.
And this is it.
The last time I'm doing this.
50 and nothing right now.
That's bad.
I already see what it says.
I'm going to get the fuck out of here now.
Wait, there's a wand over here.
Oh, who cares about the wand?
There's poison everywhere.
Uh-oh.
Bad.
Very bad, very bad, very bad, very bad, very bad.
Go.
Oh, this is a terrible place for this.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
The world's closing in on me here.
All right.
I got a new wand.
What is it?
Kind of sucks.
Chest right there.
Perfect.
Pond of money.
Good.
Let's go.
I'm not going to drown.
Why would I drown?
Stop moving.
All right, did I give you guys a chance?
All right, fine.
I'll even wait till 10 seconds.
I want water.
I don't want this potion.
Projectiles leave a trail of poison.
All right, that's fine.
I don't want this.
I want water.
That looks really, really cool.
Okay, fill it up with water.
I'm ready.
I think you guys got scammed.
Yeah, you did.
By you.
What?
Lower the timer.
Okay.
We're going to do something here.
I'm going to restart after I win
because I'm going to win.
See?
I already won.
I'm going to give you guys a chance.
I mean, I just won.
I mean, it's destroyed everything.
For a second, I thought that the ceiling was crashing on me.
All right, you lost.
You lost.
It's okay.
So now what we're going to do is I'm going to change something here.
I'm going to give you guys one more chance.
I'm turning the time between votes down to 10 seconds
and I'm taking the vote time to 10 seconds.
So let's go.
I don't think you guys are going to pick that.
I don't know, but I have to leave immediately.
This is total chaos.
I'm ready to fight it.
This is going to happen very quickly.
I have to just leave very, very quickly.
Go, go, go, go, go.
This, by the way, this is for 100 community subs.
I'm on fire.
Stop being on fire.
How much fucking health do you have?
You have perks to enemies.
Shit.
Okay, I'm good.
I'm going to be all right.
I fucking hate those bees.
What is happening with this?
I'll leave off the creatures.
Oh, you guys just saved my ass.
You saved me.
You guys really are nice.
Hostile ghosts.
Shit.
Okay, move.
I'm starting to panic a little.
Just a little.
I'm starting to panic a little bit here.
Shitter leaf?
Uh-oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
The water saved me.
If there was no water, I would be dead.
By the way, why not?
We're currently no longer on any bets at the moment.
Hey, you just-
Skate Tone just killed the fish.
I didn't do that.
Five second timer.
It's the five second timer.
You guys don't even see it on screen until it's too late.
It's got to be like 10 seconds.
All right, this last one is going to be-
I can't even buy anything.
I guess I can get this one.
What does this even matter?
Okay, if I die here, then-
No.
What does worm-
Worms find you attractive.
Good luck.
Okay, here we go.
If I make it to the bottom,
if I do not make it to the bottom here,
then all bets are off.
A huge body of random liquid?
What is going on?
They're on my team?
Make it 12.
All right, for 12.5 subs, if I get to the bottom, I-
I- I don't-
I don't even-
I don't know.
I'm confused right now.
I don't know what's happening.
Where did I just go?
Okay.
What am I spraying?
Okay, um, I think I'm doing okay.
Sniper!
Oh no, I gotta give 12.5 community subs.
Let's just round it up to 15 so it's easier.
Times 10 or nothing.
Oh, that's it.
Times 10.
That would be 120.
No, no, all right, this is it.
I'm done.
Here, I'm gonna give 20 community subs right now.
We'll go in the middle there somewhere.
Oh, I just gave 20.
What if we 50x'd that?
This is no longer even a noisestream anymore.
This is just gambling for community subs on random shit that I-
This is not even-
I'm not even playing the game anymore.
I- I told you this was gonna happen, too, didn't I?
I knew this was gonna happen.
This is why I waited so long to do this,
because you knew this is what was gonna happen.
This is a pretty good start, though.
I can come out alive?
Nearby things turn into acid?
Okay.
Okay, what's happening?
Why-
What's- what's happening?
What is shooting out of me?
This is bad.
I never agreed to that.
I said imagine.
I said we were done with the betting.
That's 5,000.
Yeah, I said what if we-
I said what if we 50x'd that?
I didn't say this is 50x'ing it.
I said, oh, imagine.
I said no more betting.
I said it was over after I gave the 20.
I never agreed to anything, Mr. Nixon.
No, that's true.
The house always wins.
When it feels like it.
Okay, how about this one, guys?
This is not me saying imagine, by the way.
This is me saying that-
I'm not saying like, oh, imagine if I said, oh, dude, what if it was-
No.
If I do not walk in the portal of this room-
If I do not walk in the portal in this room, I'm-
Hold on, before I say anything,
let me make sure I have an opportunity to do that.
If I do not walk in the-
Okay, if I don't walk in this portal-
If I do not walk in this portal,
I will give 100,000 community subs.
Okay, the tower didn't come good.
Look at the map?
What do you mean, look at the map?
What map?
You didn't walk in.
No, we're not gonna play semantics.
I went in.
I walked in.
You can't play semantics right now.
If I do not make it down this chute right here
and live to tell the tale,
then I will give 500,000 community subs.
Imagine if I went right into lava.
Yeah, no more betting.
No more betting.
You got-
Holy shit, this is awesome.
Help tell-
Oh, there was a time when I fell down the hole.
And bet a bunch of community subs and then-
But it turned out in my favor.
I won.
There you go.
I win.
Okay, if I do not direct hit the next enemy,
if I do not hit the next enemy directly,
then I will give 500,000,000 community subs.
By the way, I didn't fire a shot yet.
I just want everyone to be very clear about this.
I did not even fire a shot.
I said the next enemy,
the next enemy that I fire at.
I didn't say it had to be a lot.
I didn't say when.
I just said the next shot, the next enemy.
I didn't fire a shot.
I did not say I have to do it in this life.
I just said the next enemy that I shoot at, I have to hit.
Or I'll give 500,000,000 community subs.
How much money is that actually though?
Like how much actually is that?
Two and a half billion dollars.
But I forgot to say after that,
that community subs in Germaland.
It's a new game that I have coming out soon.
It's a new game where we sit here
and we pretend that we're all part of a giant world.
And I give two and a community sub in Germaland
is a one quarter of a tenth of a quarter of one tenth
of one quarter of one cent.
So if you do the math out in this new Germaland,
I forgot to add that to the end of that.
It's 2.5 billion dollars.
Imagine thinking I had even.
Oh, that's so fucking funny.
I was so scared.
Streamer O's chat, two and a half billion dollars.
No, but I forgot to put the amend, the, the, the,
the amendment there.
That this is where in the German 985 funland
and on German funland, every dollar is worth
a quarter of a tenth of a cent of a penny
of a quarter of a penny of a quarter of a cent.
So, I mean, it's kind of like when you're on the moon.
It's kind of like when you're on the moon
and the gravity is like different.
It's kind of like that.
I'm in Germaland right now.
So this is like my rules.
I'm in my own land.
It's a quarter of a tenth of a quarter of a percent.
So, 2.5 billion dollars.
Turns out to actually be where I am here.
When you do the conversion here, it turns out to be,
it turns out to be another, another 20,
another 50 community sub.
There you are.
So I, I didn't tell you that.
Imagine if like, all right.
We like, obviously we're making.
I, hey, but wait a second.
Hold on a minute, folks.
Hold on just a minute, folks.
Wait just a second here.
I did say that all the bets were over
and there was no more betting.
And this was all just for fun.
I said there was no more bets.
I said that.
I said it was over.
We're not doing bets anymore.
So that was a fun one.
That was a joke one.
I did say that beforehand.
I did say, I did say, all right.
We're not doing betting anymore.
No more bets.
And then I said, oh, 500 million subs, right?
Like that was a joke.
It was a, it was like joke in Funnyland.
Semantics Andy.
No, I did say, I said bets are over.
We're not doing bets anymore.
And then I made like a joke or like a comedy thing.
Oh, my chest is killing me.
Imagine losing, imagine losing a two and a half billion dollar bet with your chat.
Oh, my fucking chest is killing me.
Look, obviously this is like just a joke, right?
Like it's just for fun.
But if I did, if I gave 500 million community subs, that would mean that each one of you
would have, would get, would get like there's 8,700 people here.
If each one of you got an equal portion of that, like each one of you would be getting
like 650,000 subs worth of time on the channel.
That's like 7,000 years.
Oh, my God.
That's so funny.
All right.
Double or nothing?
Double or nothing.
I will give, I will give five billion community subs.
Double or nothing if I don't get the bottom.
Double or nothing.
Five billion subs.
That's official.
Five billion community subs.
Double or nothing.
I don't go...
I don't, there's, I don't.
Oh thank God.
Thank God.
I've won.
I went.
No, I don't have to get 500 billion.
I'm going to get five billion communities.
All right.
How about triple or nothing?
I get 30 billion community subs away.
All right.
That was official.
That was if I double enough that that was official
Dollars that's so fucking funny
Oh, I'm so glad that I like doubled or nothing and I officialed it and I like that's it. It's been stamped
It's only official if he wins
No, I told you I I am gonna compromise i'll compromise to give you the the currency value of the germa 985 currency
Which is 50 community subs?
It's a tenth of a quarter of a quarter of a tenth of a quarter of a
quarter of a tenth of a quarter on a frog in a log in the bog in the bottom
Of the sea worth of a cent. It's 50 community subs
Pay up what no I closed out that transaction
Oh the no. No, I when I paused the game and I said, oh no
Here's what we're gonna do
I'm gonna we're gonna go through the we're gonna go previously to the tenth of a quarter over tenth of a percent of a tenth
Of the quarter
Let's do 50 community refreshing
That's a tenth of a quarter over tenth of a percent of 10th of the quarter of a 10th of the frog in the log of the
Bog of the border the phalaea and the hair of the log in the bottom of the sea
Here we go.
Devil or nothing? No! I told you already. I told you already before we even did the 500 million. I said I've done no more bets.
It's over. I said that and it was very clear. I said anything going forward is just a fucking comedy routine.
Five billion subs. No one even has that much money. Chat is enabling Jerma's gambling addiction.
Only four only 499 million 999 thousand.
Wait, I want to see official 30 billion. I'll get 30 billion community subs if I- If I what? If I what?
Excuse me, if I what?
Excuse- I'll get 30 billion community subs if I- If I what? Didn't even say anything there.
I could fall- I could have fall- all right, that was official. That was- I double enough that that was official.
That was official. The thing that I just did was official. I never told you what we were betting on.
I'll get 30 billion community subs if I- if I- and I said it was official the last one which was double to nothing and then
this is it. I didn't say what- if I what? I could have said if I even fucking Oreo.
That was official. That was- I double enough that that was official. That was official. I double nothing that was official.
All right, see why I don't want to turn this fucking thing on in the first place. All right, turn this- turn it off!
I'm doing a- I'm doing a run on my own. I still- I think that's so funny.
And here's the worst part about that. It had to be the bouncy one.
If you watch that clip, it literally bounced if we were in a tiny corridor and it bounced
bong bong bong bong bong bong bong bong around the guy a hundred times.
Everyone doesn't love- what? What are we minus twoing? What? It's fun to gamble without consequences, isn't it?
I mean, yeah, because like, well, you- what? Do you think- do you think I would like actually put up a five hundred million dollar bet?
Put it back. Wait, wait. What is this? What are you guys linking?
One-fourth of-
No, no, you didn't listen closely. No, you didn't listen close enough. That's not what this is. You didn't listen close enough.
One-fourth of one-tenth of a quarter of a percent is fifteen thousand six hundred twenty-five dollars.
No, I said you didn't hear me. You misheard me.
I'm crying right now. You misheard me.
I said one-fourth of one-quarter of one-tenth of one-quarter of one-tenth of a frog in the log of the bog of the
pay at the bottom of the sea.
Somebody said, what is this? Chowder? What's chowder? How much is a frog in the log on the bottom of the sea?
That's the part that you're not calculating. A frog on the log on the bottom of the sea is like a dollar.
Oh, it's one-fourth of one-tenth of one percent of a dollar.
Oh, my fucking back hurts right now from laughing at this. A dollar you haven't paid? I get fifty community subs.
That's the back, right? I can't fucking believe I missed the shot.
Stop! I don't need to see the math.
I don't know why this is so funny to me because like I'm just thinking if like somebody like I'm just thinking if somebody really like
actually made that bet.
Oh, this is killing me.
Okay, I have to stop. I gotta go. I think I actually have to.
What does this have to do with anything?
Seriously, what does this have to do with anything?
What does this have to do with money?
What? Is that your opportunity to link that? Oh my god.
TURBO985, this is the legal community subs claim court and we are contacting you to notify
that you currently owe 499,999,950 community subscriptions to the chat of TURBO985. If
this debt is not rectified, you may be subject to Twitch community arrest. Please contact
us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us
at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv
or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or
text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us
at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv
or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or
text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv
or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or
text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us
at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv
or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or
text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us
at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at
www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv or text us at www.twitch.tv
or text us at www.twitch.tv