What is going on in this chat room? This is just- it's just a bunch of words. Just nonsense words.
Wait, what do you mean Nightbot? Nightbot isn't modded? What? How? That makes no sense. What?
Where is Nightbot? Where is he? So there's this Nightbot. Wait, I can't see. Not- I gotta-
Nightbot isn't- why is Nightbot not modded? What the fuck? All right, now it's- now you-
all the fun is over and now I understand. Okay, I see. You've been purged. Yeah, Nightbot is
my security guard who's sleeping at his desk. I just had to go and like shake his desk for a second.
Okay, I just shook my desk and all my fucking monitors are screwed up. Hold on, what the
fuck just happened? I just shook my desk and my- my desktop on my computer flickered and all my
icons have moved and my- hold on, I think my display thing pulled out. Yep, okay, I don't know
what to do about this. Yeah, okay, well it doesn't matter. I have three monitors and the middle
monitor's DVI cable just got unplugged. It's okay because we don't need it. What do we need that for?
You understand? You know what we're doing tonight, right? By popular demand, and I do mean popular,
we're going to play my favorite video game of all time. Ever. I have a top five.
It's up there. It's probably number one or two or three. I don't know. It's definitely in the-
I would say, you know, it's not fair to have a top five video games you've ever played in your whole
life. They're all number one. You don't get to choose in that point, I don't think. We're going
to play Super Mario RPG Legend of the Seven Stars. Now when you ask me why are we doing that,
because a few weeks ago we talked about our favorite games and would you ever stream some
of your old favorites or have like a nostalgia relaxing kind of stream night and I'm like,
I don't know. I've played them a lot. Probably not. But then I just said, fuck it. Sure, why not?
So we're going to play Mario RPG. That's the plan. Didn't you say Chrono Trigger was your
favorite? They're all my favorites. There's five or six of them. I have beaten this game many times,
although I don't remember everything every time, right? Small details get lost. Even some of the
large details do as well. But I do end up playing through this game like once every three to four
years. It's a great one. If you've never seen this game, you've never played it, then you're in for
a treat. In fact, if you've never played this game before, just go get it and delete me from
right now. There's no, just enjoy it. It's a fucking fantastic or experience it with all of us
if you want to. And why don't we switch over to it right now? This, by the way, has some of the best
music ever from any video game. Uh, Yoko Shimomura, I believe, uh, is the composer.
And I am a purist when it comes to this kind of things. This is Mario. This is not Jeremy. This
is not Jax. This is Super Mario. I'm not going to name, all the characters have to be their actual
names. I can't do it. Because every conversation that comes up throughout the course of this entire
game, it's Mario, Mario, Mario, hey Mario, Mario. I don't want to be called Peter. I don't want to
be called pee pants. Hey, pee pants. Hey, uh, Larry. No, this is Mario. If there was character
customization, sure. If I could change Mario's hat and pants color and take his mustache off and
make his nose bigger, okay, then that's not Mario. But it is. I'm going to do it just like it shows
up on TV. No, I'm not going to do Jario. I can't do that. This is, that's Mario right there. What
do you mean boring? No, it's, you're, you're ruining my childhood. Settle down. This is Super
Mario. No, I'm going to, I'm supposed to be relaxing. Hold on. Hold on. You know what's funny about
this? Everybody when they were younger just made this their name. And it's not correct.
You would go to Blockbuster and rent this shit. And there would be a few save files from people
that got, I don't know, a 10th of the way through the game. And it was like Steve,
Matt, Andrew, Catherine. Nobody ever did Mario. And it's, that's who that is.
No, I can't do that. I'm a purist. It's going to be Mario. Come on. Let's go. Who the fuck is Ralph?
Oh shit. It's right. I rented this from Blockbuster. That's right. Sometimes I forget where I got it.
This is Zack.
Calm the fuck down. This is not like an exciting game. It is. All right. Quiet.
The game starts off like any other Mario game. You got Bowser. You got Princess. You've got the
castle. And you got Mario. We get in there. Ah, I remember this. Yep. Wow. So you can jump. You can
run. That's pretty much what you do in every Mario game that you've ever played. You can jump.
No, you can't. See, I'm one of these, this is, I, this is my favorite kind of RPG. Oh, Jeremy,
how come you don't like most RPGs turn-based? Because I don't like having to randomly fight
enemies. Chrono Trigger did the same shit. You don't have to fight people. You can just run
around them. There's no random battles. I hate random battles. I want to see them on the screen.
Anyways, you got a B and A and X and a Y like the Super Nintendo controller. A Y, by the way,
is your special moves. B is defense and running away. X is items and A is attack. Now this game
implemented one of the, I've made this video. I've already made this video. I'm getting nostalgia
not on the game, but on the video that I made like six years ago. Yes, there are timed hits
and there are timed defenses as well. And usually I'm pretty good at this, but you know, it's been a
few years. I didn't get it. It's right after he lands. So it's like do, do, do, A. A is time,
A is timed hits when you block and when you are attacking. Although I'm not getting experience
right now. That's why I don't want to really do much of this. So I just want to get through it
because this is the tutorial essential. This is a walkthrough. Yes, it's not. By the way,
some fun trivia for you. This is the first isometric 3D-esque game that Nintendo decided to
release. This game did not do that well because it was released at the very end of the Super
Nintendo's life cycle, which as you know, most of the other consoles were already being released by
then. It is a cult classic status at this point and because it sucks. I'm not kidding. Actually
ban that person for at least 10 minutes. Like, I mean, that's, that's a 10 minute timeout. Like,
how dare you. Don't let Bowser bruise you, Mario. Mario, prepare your chef for a great beyond.
It's a block. Every time I grab my head, that means that I did it.
You want to see what a non-timed hit looks like. See, you can take zero damage in this game.
Mario, the chain. Aim for the chain. See, if this is the first time playing, you'd be like, wait,
what? Oh, what the fuck? I can aim for the chain. And you'd go, what? Oh, no, I know. I'm like,
brain is pro. Hit the chain. Drop Bowser. Sounds like a plan. 15 damage. You guys want to see what
a non-timed hit looks like? Because I, Toads are going to come out and explain all of this
and about it. Yeah, I'm giving you spoilers. I don't want to like be the person that says,
we're going to watch the movie and then I'm going to tell you everything that happens in the movie.
Toads in this game. That's all you need to know. Mario, the chain. I am aiming for the chain.
That's what I'm doing. Boom. What was that sound? No. It's a chain reaction. Hang on,
Pink Link. Coming, Mario. Fight, Mario. Fight. Fight. This should finish you. I can't do it.
I was going to do the, you know what I'm talking about, the, when he, you know what I mean.
Ah, did you think I was just going to give it to you? You're always in my way. This is it.
I'm going to take you out, Mario. Foiled again. Shit. Oh, Mario. You had me so worried. Let's get
out of here. Now what the heck's happening here? You're probably saying, wait, well, this is not,
this is Mario beats Bowser. Princess Peach, they don't go back. They had, they, they,
and that's it. But who the fuck is this guy? That's somebody I've never seen before.
Ooh, we're in the castle, didn't we? Super Mario RPG. You're feeling sleepy. Very sleepy.
And there go the stars that were broken from the sword. And here's the overworld map. We get
launched over here. What happened here? The sword went right into Mario's head.
Don't narrate this anymore. I can't, I'm sorry. I know I really am. Like, the sword drops down,
and what happens here? We got a rob. I'm like the fucking audio book. All right. All right.
I'm good. Hey, Mario. Lots of people use something called a door to go in and out of their houses.
Anyway, I came by to pick up Toad School since she's a bit late. Quiet, Archer. Thanks in 10
community subs. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. You can jump on the bed. Go turn the
light on. Watch is ready. Good night. All right. What else can we do here? Lots of stuff.
Here we go. First save point of the game. The save points scattered around.
Fucking Ralph. Oh, no. Ralph save. Actually, I feel bad about Ralph save.
Ralph's not even, I don't think a real person. Hey, I thought the princess was here with you,
Mario. Where is she? I hate this. I hate this. Nobody can do Toad unless you do that.
Toad is just Marge, but a little higher pitched. Mario, what's with the silent treatment? No,
I'm not going to do that. You're not telling me something. It's Bowser again, isn't it? Oh,
no. Here we go again. Mario, would you please bring it back like you always do?
It's worse. It's not worse. It's better. Let's go up to Bowser's key. Mike Tyson.
Who goes there? A trespasser. This castle now belongs to us, the Smithy Gang. It's our first
step towards taking over this world. And if it weren't for nosy characters like you,
we'd practically own this world. So let's see you deal with this.
Took out the bridge. So we, I mean, what do we do now? Why does this guy sound exactly like
a Jerma character? Because I'm sitting here doing that. All right, let's go. I'm excited. I love
this game. All right, Jay Leno, Mike Tyson, or Toad? Which one do you want me to do? Pick one.
I'm seeing a lot of Leno. Okay. You're back so soon. Did you forget something? No? What happened
up there? The bridge to Bowser's key was out now. It's just wonderful. I don't know what we must
bring out from the Chancellor of Mushroom Kingdom at once. Let's go, Mario. From the Chancellor of
what's going on. Where do we go? Oh, excuse me. Oh, that bump on your head reduced your HP level.
One of Mushroom Kingdom's famous items out of pink. The mic. Received a mushroom. Do you know
how to use items? Of course I do, Toad. Oh, I see. You're just so well traveled and experienced,
Mario. Now, why did I rush back? I had something to tell you. Oh, I remember. I came to warn you
that mushroom was swarming with monsters. I just barely made it back here in one piece.
This is Meowth. You're right. Mario, please do something. Perhaps I can help. Do you know
about Time Tits? Yes. Hey, you better watch out. He knows about Time Tits. He's going to punch
your lights out. He's got more black than white, huh? Why did I rush back? I had something to tell
you. Oh, that's right. We need to tell the Chancellor about Toadstool. I'll see you over
at Mushroom Kingdom. Have you seen this? Have you heard about it? Just in case, take these with you.
Three mushrooms. The Chancellor. I'm so glad Germa isn't an actor.
You know, you don't get me. What? I've played this game 500 times. I'm just having some fun
with the voices. All right. You want me to really give you acting? Fine. On the next dialogue,
you'll see what a real actor looks like. But first of all, we want to do this because this
is the best song in the game. The battle music is the best. The mushrooms heal you, as you probably
I blocked that. It was too much damage. What?
You get random events like that. HP max. That's good. The boss music's about. Yeah, the boss
music is very good as well. Yeah, this is also back when Mario punched hard with both hands.
Now he kicks and flips, right? This experience. I don't really need this right now, but let's
go ahead and get the coins because the coins are currency. You use these to buy stuff at the shops
and upgrade weapons. And let's, you know, let's save toad. Yeah. Toad gives you useful stuff as
you go through. To exp. Now I have to figure out how I want to do this. All right.
My life was flashing before my eyes for a second there. Here's a little something.
Thanks. I appreciate it. Oh, this is fine. Cause the experience you level up. That's not a toad
voice. Don't worry. I'm just getting warmed up. Now there are hidden blocks in the game, as you
probably could have guessed. What are my first impressions of the game? Um, I don't know. Not
that good. I mean, it's like, what is, I don't understand. It's an RPG, like turn-based. I fight
two. This is not even hard. I fight two things at once. That's it. Um, like, okay. That's not hard.
I only like hard games. No, I'm sorry. I don't like this. I only like hard games. Let's save toad.
Okay. So this is me too. I only like hard games too. Now the game actually does get,
the game does get a little challenging just in regards to some facets of the game,
facets of the game. How do you say that? Boy, that was a close call. Here's a token of my appreciation.
Flower tap. So if you wanna know what a flower tap does, this is the interesting part.
Flower is mana. So when you have, you can get flower tabs, flower boxes, flower jars,
and they increase your maximum mana by one. Neat, huh? That's pretty cool. Syrup is a mana potion.
Think of mushrooms as health potions. Check for secrets, you know? There could be secrets
anywhere. The one thing that I never ever actually did in this game, and never really explored,
even though I've played this game a thousand times, is the frog coins. I never did anything
with them, and I never cared to. All right, there is a toad that's been beaten up. Oops.
They're mostly useless. Oh shit, I shouldn't have read that. I just took a lot of damage.
Yeah, that's my understanding from that as well, because frog coins are just very novelty things,
weird accessories that you can get.
There is a permanently missable frog coin where you have to jump off a toad's head who starts
walking during a cutscene. Really? See, that's the kind of shit I love. That's coming up really soon,
actually. Is it? Uh oh, I'm gonna miss it. I'm gonna get healed too. Three hour stream of
Germa fighting Kulex. No, actually. I will beat Kulex first try. I hate to say it, I'm sorry to
say it, but now when I fight Kulex is another story, you know. Where's Toad? I know you're over
here somewhere. Where's Toad? Isn't he hidden over here? Oh, there he is. All right. Oh, that's scary.
Uh oh. Really gotta pad out this playthrough. This is the first mini boss in the game. All right,
gotta get a good voice. Hey, are you looking at me? My hammer and I don't like you. Mario,
you better be careful. He's definitely got a mean streak. Now you got my hammer angry. You
shouldn't have done that. And there's two. The Hammer Brothers. So we're gonna do something fun.
We're gonna... 33 damage. We're gonna use it over and over again just to get rid of this one gone.
See you later. I do have to be careful because Valor up now means that they're... they take more
damage and they dish it out too. All right, six. I can do this two more times. See? Kulex first
try live. Uh oh, this is actually important. I didn't get it. Oh fuck, I'm gonna die.
Die. I'm gonna die in my like 11th playthrough. Uh oh. I can just do it with my hand.
I don't want to use the honey syrup. Okay, I gotta get this right. Now, there it is. Okay, so I'm block...
when you block shit, you... you might not get it right. They're weirdly timed. That whole animation
has to go by first before you block. Uh, I think... yeah, I'm gonna do it again. I really want to just
jump on him, but is it really worth me taking a honey syrup? He's probably... he's got like five
health left. How did you know? I just do. Why is it that whenever I play bad games, you're here,
but whenever I play good games, you're not here? Well, which one is this? I don't... I don't know
which one is this. Got a flower jar though, and we leveled up. Max HP 25, 23, 2.
It's magic attacking, magic defense. Level this up correctly or I'm gonna unfollow. See, when I was
younger, I did a thing and I kind of just continue to do it. Uh, I pick one option
and I do it every single time with each playable character. So I would just have, like for instance,
Mario would have hundreds of HP. And I don't... I never really changed that up.
Because there's three people in your party, so I figured, all right, one of them is going to be
good at everything. Uh, I want health. I do. Actually, maybe... hmmm... I gotta plan... I gotta
think about this. I'm gonna do health. Power. Power. No, I'm gonna do health. Caring about HP.
Yeah, you have to care about HP in this game. Otherwise, people die. You'll die. Let us pick.
I'm not... I gotta let you guys ruin my childhood again. Fine. I'll let you guys ruin my childhood
again. You guys are really onto this recently, ruining my childhood every day. I mean, I mean,
every day. I don't mean every... I mean like just today. I don't know why I said every day.
Okay. Uh, sure. Why not? Here we go. You guys can pick. Don't fuck this up, though, because like
you literally will ruin this whole game. What do you want me to do? Like really don't fuck this up.
Okay. All right, we're doing power. Uh, thank you for choosing the thing I'm gonna pick for Mario
every time. By the way, forgot to mention that's what this was. Why can I get this off the screen?
Get off the screen. Why can I not take... There we go. All right. Power. Attack went up from
33 to 24. Defense 2 to 3. Now this is physical attack power. So if somebody casts a magic spell,
this is not gonna do shit. I hope you guys understand what you've just done.
All right. Thanks, Mario. I was running so fast. I wasn't watching where I was going.
Whoa. Mushroom Kingdom's just ahead. We're almost there, Mario. Hey, where did this hammer come from?
Hmm. Hey, do you know what this is? It's the hammer, brothers. It's significant. No one stands a
chance against you when you whop them with this. You never know. It might come in handy.
Sit, sit, sit, sit, sit. Let's get a move on. I'll see you in Mushroom Kingdom.
You can probably guess that, uh, that is a weapon. Attack power goes to 34.
Now the game begins. Mushroom Kingdom. I thought this was for crafting? No. Here's the Mushroom
Kingdom. Hey, Mario. Look what you're standing in. Gotcha. It made me jump. Just a fan. The star
means it's an in and a save point. And the mushroom means it's a shop and potentially...
Yeah, gotcha. Good. Items and weapons and all that good stuff. Mario, what a pleasant surprise.
One of Frog Fuchs' grandchildren is running errands in town today. I haven't seen him, though. Oh,
you're here to shop. What are you looking for? Here we go. See, shirt, pants, shoes. Uh, jump
shoe. It'll use jump attacks against any foe. This is really good. Antidote pin prevents poison.
But I need... you gotta get... you gotta get armor first. Get pants. Mario's not wearing pants. Uh,
shirt and pants. And I also did this when I played this game all the time. I am gonna get
a lot of shit for this. I already know it. There's gonna be a lot of RPG min-maxers that are gonna be
what the fuck is wrong with this guy. Um, I max out my inventory with revives. Every time. I have,
like, 20 pick me ups. Because I'm terrible at video games. So I just have a ton of
heals and pick me ups. And I'm probably gonna get made fun of. But I'm already accepting that.
It's not optimal at all. I know. But for right now, this is fine. I don't have enough for the
jump shoes. Let's equip. Uh, somebody just gave a lot of money. Defense and magic defense. And
pants. They're not for me. They're for somebody else. Uh, phylactery. Let's just give 100 bucks.
Thank you. For the 100 dollars and 11 cents. They say,
I will give you 500 dollars to play Paper Mario and the Thousand Year Door on stream.
Well, uh, I'm sa- I'm sorry to say I will never get that money. I'm never gonna receive that money.
And I'm not gonna do that. I appreciate it, though. Thank you so much for the 100 bucks.
Oh, this is tha- oh yeah, this is the person that's playing on the Game Boy. Wait, this is important
stuff. But no, phylactery, let's say that, like, you're up, you have to be up to over five, six,
seven, eight hundred dollars. No, thank you. Here we go, ready? Don't talk to me now! Nothing up
there? He's only the last level of the game or something. And all the inns, people are just
sleeping. It's not like I'm always sleeping. Yes, it is. You're always sleeping up here.
Don't talk to him, he's gaming. Paper Mario is better than this. Well, that's the thing about
video game opinions. I get to have one and so do you. I happen to think this is the best game
that Nintendo's probably ever made. And if you like it, then that's- if you like the other one
better, I'm glad you do. But you're wrong. It's so nice to see our young ones having a good time,
but you're not that old. I always look for boxes. Wrong, wrong, wrong. Oh, look, here's like the-
the- look, the wicked, like, caffeine person.
All right, let's go. Hey, did you see a crocodile around here? He talks like a
mobster wannabe. I'm sure he's up to no good. Hey, wait a second, my wallet's gone.
Now, shit, I'm sorry about your wallet. All right, let's continue. I think there's-
anything else to see in here? Oh, yeah, that's right. This kid.
I love that. There's the sprite going up and down.
Look, I'll help you. In fact, you might be better than me, kid. Keep at it.
All right, let's go talk to the chancellor. Do all toads, like, talk- like, toad? Or is
there some toads that talk like this? Wait, no! Is this the part? Is this the part you're talking
about? This is the part you're talking about? This is the part you're talking about. Fuck, I- I ruined
that. That's the part you're talking about, isn't it? I missed the coin. In all my years,
I've never done that. I missed it. It's over. I might as well just delete this game and- and
stop streaming. But what about this toad? This is a toad, right? That- that- this is a toad.
So would he also talk like this? Or does he have a lower voice?
Oh, excuse me. Where- where is the princess? She departed for your house hours ago.
I feel the worst. Could Bowser somehow be behind all of this? Spore's alive. You're telling us that
Bowser has abducted the princess again. Never mind. It will be up to you to enter the keep
and rescue Princess Toadstool. No, you're not getting this. Yeah, guys, this is back before
Mario talked. This is my favorite part. Not yet.
Got a map.
Go to the cellar and prepare for your journey. The vault guard shall assist you.
Where is it? Come on, it's over here somewhere. So this is up- I believe this is going to- this
is the princess's room? Yeah. The princess hasn't returned yet. Can you imagine how the chancellor
must feel? I'm just checking for stuff. Found Toadstool's- Hey, what are you doing? I'll give
you this in exchange. Just leave everything where it was. What? Okay. Mario, the chancellor has filled
me in. Come, let me show you around. This is gonna get fucking tiring. Help yourself to the
treasures. This mushroom will restore your hit points and flower points. Unfortunately,
mushrooms you find as items only restore your HP. So beware. This is a flower. The more gathering
you do, the more flower points you'll have in battle. Find them. This is a coin. The small
ones are worth one and the large ones are worth 10. This one's a 10. Do you know about flower
points? Yes. You sure are smart, Mario. All right, now walk that way so I can get the secret.
All right, let's go. Hmm, I gotta think of- I gotta think of one. I'm back here. Oh, get back here.
Oh no, that reptile stole my grandfather's coin. I can't cry. Big boys don't cry,
but it's just not fair. I gotta do. Good luck, kid. Yes, gee, you're soaking wet, aren't you?
I'm all right now, sorry. There's nothing like a good cry. But why was I crying? There was some
reason. My grandpa asked me to buy some things for him here. When I walked into town that croc
stopped me. Oh yeah, he took it from me. He stole my coin. I chased him, but he was too fast.
Hey Mario, let's see how you're going to take on Bowser. Wow, he doesn't stand a chance.
Wait, you're the Mario? I know all about you. You've got more jump in you than a box of frogs.
I'm Mallow from Tadpole Pond. I'm a frog, but can you believe it? I can't jump. It's embarrassing.
How about it, Mario? Will you help me catch that filthy thief?
Yeah. The young frog Mallow, who doesn't look at all like a frog, joins Mario in his quest.
New party member. And I planned ahead. Put on those pants, Mallow. What do I have for items?
I do a flower jar. Let's use it. I need a couple of mushrooms, I think. First, let's save it.
Wasted the flower jar? I did not. All right, let's do uh... Hey, Mallow, what kept you? I was starting
to worry. Wait until you hear this. You see... Wait, I've already heard. Old Frog Fuchs has told me.
He seems to know everything. Hold on. No, listen to me. The truth of the matter is, well, um,
the coin was stolen. What? Well, if that's the case, I guess we can't trade. That's a shame.
Oh, but there's no need to worry. Mario here is going to help us. Is that so? Well, if Mario's
on your team, you'll have that coin back in a jiffy. Not so fast. Take this with you. You'll
probably need it. Pick me up. Uh, but I need to buy a couple more. I love this job. What are you
looking for? I'm looking for like a couple of these. Want to do these? One more of these.
Inefficient, but it's one more of those. Okay. Hey, what do you think you're doing? Get off
there this minute. I order you to stand before me. I now order you to jump. In this world,
there are things called hidden treasures. Use your awesome jumping ability to look for them.
And he's got one sitting right here somewhere, don't he? Okay, bye. All right. So we have to
try to... We have to go to Toad. Mario, I have something to report, sir. I saw him. He's here
somewhere. He just zoomed past me a second ago. Did you see him? Did he look something like this?
Why, yes, exactly. He's the one who took my coin. Why didn't you stop him? Because I forgot my
bazooka at home. Sheesh, give me a break here. Get back here. You smugs will never catch me.
A snail can outrun you morons. Later. That's him. Hurry, Mario. Let's get him. Got anything for me?
No. You're too slow. You're too slow. Bandits way. Let's go. Hmm. There he is. He probably
stashed it in that bag. Let's nab him. Are you trying to tell me? Go on, hold on before you get
hurt, kid. He does a very high speed. He can one hit. One hit. Thunderbolt now. Use Mallow's
stretchy arms. I love the hammer sound. It sounds so great. You missed me. Now this is a frog.
I mean, it's like a human frog. This game has battles and not just wacky dialogue.
Um, no. There's lots of wacky dialogue and there are lots of battles.
Oh, I forgot. This game doesn't just have wacky dialogue. I'm just checking. You couldn't jump to
save your life, kid. So I guess this is goodbye. And he stole one of the coins. Oh, fuck. All right,
here we go. Is this when I... Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no. Where do you... Sometimes you get stars.
I know there's something around here, isn't there? What about over here? Oh, there has to be.
Right? If you find a star in this game, you're guaranteed to level up like at least once or
twice, at least. That is... Okay, it is the next room. You're right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you're a persistent bugger, but I'm a hundred miles ahead of you. He is pretty fast. Any chests
or anything? He is fast. I feel like you lied when you played this game five hundred times.
No, I played it like once every three or four years. No, sorry. I don't go to sleep at night
saying all of Krakos' lines out loud. Why don't you? Wait. Stupid. There he goes. It's not worth it.
It's not even a thing you should be looking... Give up already. That treasure box is tempting,
but now is not the time. Oh, it is absolutely worth it. It's definitely worth it because we're
going to level up like three times. This all counts as a full battle, by the way.
There it is. Bingo. Mallow has reached level three. His HP has gone up by four. His defense
is terrible. His magic attack is... Mallow, I believe, has the best magic in the game.
I think Peach has... Oh, spoilers. Fuck. HP rain. All right. What do you guys think? Where should I go?
All right. Special. Magic attack. Magic defense. I can't click down there. All right. We're doing
magic. Thank you for voting. So this brings us to 18 attack, 13. One point at each one.
That's probably what I would have done too. Although, make sure you guys give Mallow some
HP because he is very, very, very weak. Very weak. Like, super replaceable weak. I mean, no.
You guys do not want me to use him. Okay. That's why you bring all the pick me ups.
I got another flower tab. All right. I think there's something else I can do over here.
Winter Squash. Just gave $50. Thank you, Winter Squash. 5,000 bits. And they say,
Jeremy, the other day I spilled pasta sauce on my keyboard and I ruined it. At first I was annoyed,
but then I remembered the time you spilled PBR all over your keyboard live on stream and I
immediately felt better about myself. Keep up the good work, streamer. I don't drink PBR. I've never
spilled PBR anywhere. That would imply that I had to have purchased it.
Yes, that was not a PBR though. I think there's no, I'm good. Let's go. Dead end. And they won't
give up. I'll just have to hide. This is where he starts adding mileage every time you go and find
him. He's gone into hiding. Let's see if we can sneak up behind him and catch him. Full health.
And hey, what's up? What's this you fools couldn't chase down a pumpkin?
Found you. Your eyes are much faster than your feet. At this rate it'll take you a hundred more
years to catch me. Your eyes are faster than your feet. At this rate it'll take you 50 more
years to catch me. This is getting old. It'll still take you enough. You got me fair and square.
I'll give you back your coin. Did you really believe me? I was lying.
Boss time. Eight. Oh, he hurts. By the way, there are timed hits also on special attacks. Oh, fuck.
Oh, I missed that one. I don't tell you, Mallow, Mallow is weak. Very weak. I might even have to
take a mushroom. Oh my god, that picked me up. Oh boy. He's good. All right, now I actually have
to heal him. No, Mario does the damage. Heal yourself. Got a freebie. That means at the end
of the game, or end of the round here, we get something cool. I'm gonna, Mario's gonna heal now.
Uh, if I go for damage, I'm just gonna go straight up and jump on him.
And then Mallow's gonna heal him. He means he didn't use the item. I was just testing him.
He's almost dead. Shit. Yeah, Mallow, Mallow is kind of just straight up support. All right,
I'm gonna have to use the honey. This is a real game for real gamers? I mean, yeah, it is. Did I
get it? Fuck. I didn't get it again. Shit. I think you have to wait another second after the bomb
blows up. All right, I'm out of uh, mana. I think he's close. All right, let's go with honey syrup.
Do a raptor noise? No, I'm not gonna do a raptor. When do I get psychopath? Psychopath is incredibly
helpful. Do it. Do it. Do it. All right, weird mushroom. You think it's healed? You know, fuck it.
I'll show you this. I'll show you this. This is cool. See if I can get it. Got it. When you hit that
second strike, that's the time tip. I think you can do this too. Let's see. When it flies over.
Yeah, there it is. It's right at the very end when the cloud starts to close. Fuck. Seriously?
God damn it. Yeah, that was a oof moment. You're right. Take the honey syrup. Finally. All right.
Still going. Why do you have so much health? Get out of here. How much health do you have?
I only, okay, I only have two anyways. There it is.
Yes, amigos. All right. We got it back. ADXP. 10 coins. Flower tab. And a Mario level up.
25 to 30. That's a big jump for attack and defense. That's a milestone of a level.
And I learned fire orb. Yes, I did. Don't mess it up. Malo has more defense than Mario.
Little dancing flowers. All right, we'll go with power. Sounds good to me. That is what I,
I would have picked power as well. We did it. We got grandpa's coin back. I can finish my errand
now. Hey, look at this. That croco guy left a wallet. I'm going back to the shop at Mushroom
Kingdom. Are you coming? There's the fast travel shortcut out. Got a wallet too. Okay. So that is
that part. And got a wallet. Let's actually, let's, yeah, I'm all right with this. Let's test this out.
42. That's pretty good. Time to grind. No, there actually is a spot in the, close to the end game
that is an insane grinding spot. You kill this same little blue thing and it has the most
experience pound for pound. It takes one hit for the thing to die. It's pretty much cheating. All
right. Back to Mushroom Kingdom where there's something wrong here. Something going on. It
looks normal to me. Shit. All right. The fireballs always got me. They always did. I never block
fireballs. It's after, or is it before or is it like second after? I forget. The fireballs get me
every time. Use Thunderbolt? Not yet. Thunderbolt is, yes, it is incredible against these enemies,
but not unless there's more than two. It's a waste of flower power. My opinion. The magic can't be
blocked. I always thought some of it could though. Like you can block the slimes that come out of
people. The little like globs that like, yeah, you have to, the stars don't come out of you.
Then yeah, that's true. Thanks Mario. I'll continue to stand watch, but now everyone seems suspicious.
By the way, look what I got. 10 coins. Please leave the correct amount of money for items.
Manager. All right. I need, I need, how many of these do I have? 10 coins for one of, how many?
Two? I already got pants. How many do I have? Four? I need like at least five or six of these.
I'm gonna probably, I'm gonna get like seven, eight. Let's get another two. I'm gonna need them
and then another one of these. Two more of these. Okay. How am I doing? Looks like a pretty standard,
um, pretty standard inventory. I got the, what? So worth $123. Yeah, that's true. Okay. Sell the
wallet. How is this selling a wallet? Aren't I just taking the cash out and handing it to the person?
Yeah, I got bad news for those of you that want me to return this wallet.
Turns out it ain't worth it. That's, I could get everything. Okay, fine. I'll be a good person.
We got, uh, Malice doesn't have a weapon. I don't think Mal gets a weapon for a while.
Excuse me? You want to, what? How can you shop at a time like this? Just take what you want and leave
some money. I wish you luck. All right, let's go save everybody. Level up a little. He's too scared
to stop you from jumping on his furniture. Now, do it. Two damage. I thought it was 20. Ow. Jump
on the furniture. No, I'm not going to, why would I do that? You guys, okay. Return the wallet is
something that is, all right, come on, you can do more than two fucking damage. Return the wallet is
a big deal to you guys, but jump on the scared guy's fucking nice furniture in his house is okay.
You understand how I'm having trouble with this with you guys? That was too darn close. Thanks for
the land, Mario. Hey, that's the wallet that the crocodile swiped for me. Can I have that wallet
back? No way. Thank you so much. Here, I'll give you this as a reward. Go on, take it at 123 points.
But I had to do the right thing. Everyone's safe in here. It's testing. So nice to see our young
ones having a good time. It's scary outside, so let's play indoors, okay? But I want to play
outside. It's too dangerous. Yeah, she's like, oh wow. Look, I can go higher. Here, go fish.
Yeah, she thinks it's cool because they're jumping. She's a huge fan of jumping.
When is a German jumping stream going to happen? You saw it yesterday.
Oh, the Kinect streams are German jumping streams. Hey Mario, look what you're standing in.
Gotcha. Still running the business. Still playing your game. Was the princess kidnapped by those
things outside? Are they a part of this? Oh, shut up. See, I'm wide awake. Now I guess it's time for
me to win big cash. There's a casino in this game. Bet you didn't know that. Yeah, he's just bouncing
on the door. Stop that. Trying to get at least one more level up for Mario. It's pretty important
because Malo is almost 100% useless right here. In a moment, Malo will be very, very useful.
Say that to his face. I'm standing behind them, but I'm talking pretty loudly. They can both hear me.
In fact, they turn around and look at me all the time to ask me what they should be doing.
Yeah, she's right. I guess we can put it off until things cool down around here.
I found the perfect place for a wedding, but now we're all stuck inside.
Everybody's stuck. Now we can leave. Town is being attacked.
There are things in our kitchen. Help. Look, scary things. Get rid of them.
Hope my little brother's okay. I'll handle this. It's too scary. There's two scary people here.
There's two in this room and I feel a level up coming soon. Probably Malo.
No, I was wrong. Am I gonna beat this whole game on stream? Um, I don't, I don't know.
Probably. Maybe not all today. It depends. I don't think I'll be able to do it in one sitting.
This game is like a, this is like a 18-hour game. This game takes about 20 hours to go through.
So I don't think that'll be a one and done stream. Malo. Nope. Thanks Mario.
But what about my son upstairs? Oops. I forgot all about him. I'm scared.
Boing, boing, boing. Now this guy can jump. Now Malo's gonna die. You're killing his friend.
What are you, why are you doing this? You're bashing his friend's head. Stop this. They were
just playing Mario together. Oh no, this is dangerous. They're monsters. They're trying
to get, they're trying to kill us. Really? Thank you so much for everything. Here's a little token
of my appreciation. Got a flower tab. You're gonna grow up to be just like Mario. You hear?
Am I? Yes. I can still jump the highest. I love this little kid. I love this little kid.
Oh, that's, I love that little kid. He's so cute. Okay, let's go. Faster. Go faster.
No, the poor kid's gonna throw up if you keep telling him to go faster.
All right, what do I get for health? It's not, not very good. Let's change that.
What do I have for, uh, flower points? 18. How many tabs do I have? I got a lot of tabs. I mean,
technically, I'm not supposed to use these, but I'm gonna need them. When I say technically,
you're not supposed to use them. If you use a flower tab, it fills up your flower mana
all the way. But you can only do it from the menu. So that's why it's not what you're thinking.
The flower tabs increase your max mana. Yeah. And they fill up your mana as well.
Here we go. Yes, there it is. All right, Malo is level four. A nice jump on the HP.
28 HP. Yes, you decide. You do. Mario is hard carrying. Yeah, that's kind of how it is
for the first hour or two of the game. Sometimes even more. For the first like two or three hours
of the game, Mario is just hard carrying. All right, that's it. We're doing a magic attack and
magic defense. Again, I wonder if we get Mario too. Now that was really scary. Everyone's hiding in
the princess's bedroom. I and some others couldn't escape in time. I hope no one got hurt.
Uh oh. Toad's lagging out. Come on. Come on, cocks. God damn it. 700 ping Toad.
He's getting the G mod disconnect message. I don't even know what that is. Ooh, that magic
defense is really helping though. Three damage. Mario's taking 10. Oops. Malo better than Mario.
Maybe eventually, but not right now. Use thunder? No, not until it's necessary,
because I'm going to waste all of my flower points before I really need them. And I'm gonna
really need them really soon. Saved by Mario again. How could I ever thank you? I love that.
He goes like this and puts his back against the wall and slowly goes upstairs.
Trapped again. Not so fast, pal. Look at him. Can't even bounce. Hey, maybe we could bounce on his
head. I mean, I don't need a device to bounce though. I can jump higher than you and I don't
need a device to do it. So if I had a device like yours, I wonder how high I could go. And then you
walk out of the room and that person just is floored and they have to rethink everything.
Come on, Mario. Saved by Mario again. How could I ever thank you enough? Toadstool's room. You're
in one piece. Thanks to Mario, of course. Saved by Mario again. How could I ever thank you? Oh no,
the Chancellor's still in the throne room. What? That's terrible. But with Mario around, we're
safe, right? You bet. There we go. Now, hey, wait, hang on for a second. Please take this. The
Princess will be happy to know you have something of hers. I love how sometimes Mario just does like
the gym from the office. Like flower tab, right into the fucking camera. I'm like, geez, okay.
Saved everybody. I'm scared. You may not sleep in the Princess's bed. Have you no manners?
All right, I am going to. Here's what we're going to do. I'm going to, I'm taking the tabs. I don't
care. I need them. What are you doing? Wait, dude, what the fuck? Idiot. What the fuck, dude? What's
wrong? Are you serious? I'm changing streams. Like I, I, I'm going to a different stream. That was
it for me. I did. I'm going to do that anyways. All right, relax. There we go. Now people are asking,
when are you going to do Thunderbolt? When there's at least three. Watch what we can do here.
Check this out. Goodbye. And that's a Mario level up right there. 35 HP, 32 attack.
Terrible defense. And I mean truly awful. Let's go. What do you think? What's the plot so far?
Bowser kidnaps Princess. Mario thwarts Bowser, saves Princess. Unfortunately,
giant sword crashes down from the sky at the very end and knocks everybody out and takes everybody
out. Therefore, what the heck's going on with this giant sword that came out of the sky?
That is not a spoiler. You just watched that part. We're at the same movie theater
and we just watched the same scene. Let's say for instance, oh no, that's who did it.
And it was, it was Gary. Whoa, just revealed on the screen and I go, holy shit, dude, it was Gary.
And you look over at me in the, in the same fucking theater and you go, what the spoilers, dude,
idiot. All right, we're going to do power. Thank you for voting. You got to get Mario some HP guys,
or some magic power. Mario needs like not, not all right. Well, no HP. There just ain't,
there ain't no point. Why would I get Mario's like arms tired for no reason?
Never hear of a glass cannon. The vault guard, I come here to save him and he runs into the next
room. Oh, so much for him. Damn. More free shit. I'll take it. You're all right. Hey, it's safe.
You're good. Nevermind that. Guess what I found. It's a gold coin, a gold coin and it's all mine.
Oh, I found this in the cellar. You can have it. Wake up pin. Yeah. Prevents mute and sleep attacks.
And it also gives you a little bit more defense. So I'm going to give this to Mario because,
I mean, look, 1822 versus 1970. Like that's much more important. Keep Mario.
Mario is in need of it. Yes, yes, yes, yes. Okay. No one takes our treasure. That's true.
All right, let's go. I think I'm ready. I'm going to save the game.
I need Luigi. I'm going to make everybody really, really upset about this. And I'm going to say this
and people are going to be very, very, very mad. Um, not maybe not mad, but, um, this is a spoiler.
Should I say it? Yeah. Who cares? It's not a big deal. Um, link from the legend of Zelda
is in this game more than Luigi. It's pretty, it's pretty bad. Where do you think everybody went?
Well, gang looks like we have ourselves a new home. We can bounce around all day and there's
no one here who can stand in our way. Let's bounce the night away. Hey, not so fast pal.
Look at him. Can't even bounce. Maybe we can bounce on his head.
Listen up gang. These guys are going to put a stop to our party. Are we happy about this?
You're asking for it. Ooh, you're going to get it. You picked the wrong people to bounce with,
bub. How about a fat lip to go with that ugly mustache? Here we go. Fire in the back.
Check this out. Mac is stunned. Don't worry, only four damage, not a big deal.
Nope, save it. I always tap A. Six, four, yeah, you got enough. All right, we're still fine.
64, Nintendo 64. All right, I guess I have to take care of Mario here. Oh yeah, six.
I'm going to use mushroom on Mario.
And they're back. Also, I'm going to use, how much do I, what do I have for flower points? Three.
All right, I'm going to jump. No, I'm not. I'm just going to hit him. I'm just going to whack him and
then I'm going to get on the boat again and it's gonna stun him and they can't do shit. Oops,
didn't work that time. I just got instant spawned. All right, so let me do the,
this is kind of bad actually. All right, honey syrup. We got, we both have pretty good health.
Do it again, quick. Can you stun him? Stun him would be nice. Do it again. Stun him.
This is why I wanted to save all those. You're wondering why I wasn't using the honey syrup
and why I wasn't doing thunderbolt because shit like this happens. You can, you can get destroyed.
He's done. Ain't gonna be much left after this. This motherfucker can't even attack me. Done.
That's it. See you later. Yeah, that boss is very easy. That boss is not easy at all if you don't
understand that Malo has thunderbolt. If you don't use thunderbolt. And I got a star. I beat that,
I beat that when I was four. Yes, so did I. Well, I was like probably, I was more like 12.
This is not good. This is not good. The mustachioed one is strong. Strong, yes.
Yes. We must warn the boss. Come on. Now I'm the fucking king. Gracious. Oh, it's you, Mario.
What a relief. Once again, Mario to the rescue. But who were those? Chancellor. Sir, thank goodness
you're all right. Mario, so it was you who got us through all this. We owe you a lot. First the
princess and now this. It's too much to bear. Mario, how about we ask my grandpa for help?
He knows everything. Excuse me, but who the fuck are you? Oh, hello. My name is Malo. I'm from Chad
Pol Pond. Well, any friend of Mario's is welcome here in Mushroom Kingdom. As I was saying, Mario,
you are, you are, or as I was saying, Mario, you are our only hope. Why can't I do that?
Mario, please, you must rescue the princess now. Mario, I'm in your debt too. Let's head over to
Grandpa's place in Chad Pol Pond. He can help. Wait, why did I even come to Mushroom Kingdom in
the first place? I guess I'll find out. I don't know. Could Mac, the sword-like monster who crashed
into Mushroom Kingdom, have anything to do with the star piece that Mario found? Our heroes move
on towards the Kiro sewers. Mario, all we can do is wait here. Don't let us down. Goodbye. Uh-oh,
sewer level. Resident Sleeper. Uh-oh, Resident Sleeper coming up. Uh, I think we just surpassed
Ralph. Oh, wait, wait. Oh, wait, wait, wait, hold on. This is the high score. Oh, now look,
I lost good at you. Oh, you idiot. I'm like, hey, hey, hey, hey, item shop. All right, here we go.
Hey, Malo, what kept you? I was starting to worry. Hey, mister, I got my coin back. Oh, well done,
lad. Okay, here's the thing I promised you. There, make sure it doesn't get stolen, eaten, or whatever.
Your grandpa needs it, okay? Got a cricket pie. You bet. Mario, thank you so much.
Grandpa will be delighted. You know, I hate to admit it, but I love this job. What are you looking
for? Who are you? What do you mean, Luigi's in, where's Luigi? Luigi's in this game more than he
is in Mario 64. Where is Luigi? In here? I don't know that. Luigi's not here. Why does Malo sound
like your dog? Because they're both like seven. No, there's no Luigi. I've played this game 500
times. There's no Luigi. I know that for a fact. Okay, so I got, I have plenty of items. Let's move
on. We're going to go to the sewers. He's behind the big house. Luigi's not in this game. He really
is here. Luigi, where is he then? Behind the big house. Is this Luigi? Trample the monsters. Smash
them all. It'll do you good. Trust me on this one. Is that Luigi? I don't know. That's not
Luigi. That was a half-assed phone did Luigi. Like, come on. I wasn't even trying. Kiro sewers.
This is the entrance. Grandpa says to watch out for Balo, whoever that is. It's probably a little
dark down there, so keep alert. Kiro sewers. I love this. This is the best sound. One of the best
top five sounds in the whole game. Ah, all right, let's go. Read directions on how to enter. Sure.
Stand on the pipe and push down on the control pad. If you're pressing several buttons at the same
time, you will not be able to enter. To re-enter a pipe, jump off once and try again. Thank you.
All right, so this is a little bit of a maze scenario. Although, I mean, not really. It is,
but it isn't. It is. I'm just checking it out. I wanted to check it out. Check out some stuff.
There are pipes everywhere, leading to god-who-knows-what.
And there are rats, so this now became your favorite game. Shit. Shit. It's an automatic
letter grade. Boink. He's tired now. These little mice. Yeah, they're kind of like, um, like little
mousers, right? I missed time. It's okay. What was that? What was the name of the mouse in Mario?
Mario 2. With the bombs? That was Mouser. Why am I getting question marks?
Ooh, pure water. All right, let's go. Shit just jumps out at you. This is, uh, the game that I
make a reference to every- oh fuck. Oh no, this is not good. This is very bad. I forgot about this.
All right, this thing's hard. This thing's really hard. Really hard. Um, I was going to say it's
Dark Souls reference. I was going to say it's- it's one of the things that I reference every
single fucking game. It's really high damage. Don't you dare. I didn't, so I- I did not. That
hurts. Does Thunderbolt do anything? I wonder how bad Thunderbolt is. Zero. Oh god. I'm dead.
Good thing I got these, because I'm a scrub. Oh, it hurts a lot. It don't matter. Okay,
the carny kiss. I have to block. 80. Come on. I think I'm just gonna block, because look at
how much damage this is gonna do. I'm gonna heal Mario with- no. Use the honey syrup. Pure
water's for ghosts. Okay. Uh oh. I didn't fucking block it. Shit! It's hard to block. It's a- after
the sound? All right, come on. This is it. Dead. Yes! A lot of- and flower jar and a lot of coins.
Good. And I got a true form pin. Fuck yeah. True form, uh, means you cannot be turned into a
mushroom or a scarecrow. It just essentially turns you off. I'm gonna give that to Mellow.
And I did get a jar, so what do I got? I don't have any pick-me-ups left, but I have two.
Uh, I'm not gonna use this yet. I'll use it later. But that was good. Now I have to go back and save
it. I gotta make the speedrunner jump. I got it. I actually- I did it. I can't believe it.
I actually cannot fucking believe it. That- literally speedrunners take hours doing that.
I just did it. I watched somebody sit here for four hours doing that one time.
Ah! I forget! I forget what to do! I forget where to go! That's all right. Still got what I wanted.
Guys, I'm gonna have to fill two backpacks full of pick-me-ups if you don't start picking HP.
You were gonna do that anyways.
No one gets HP. Yes, you have to have some- you have to have a tank. I want to save it. Save it.
Because I don't want to fight that stupid thing again. If you need a tank, you're not DPSing
fast enough. What are you on about? How are you supposed to DPS without- how- without being
protected first? You can't, like, attack something. That's not gonna work. Drain the water. Ah! Sorry.
Miss. Fuck off with that. Got it. Sometimes I try to trick ya. Not me. End of level. Use pure water?
Oh, lazy. I have to hit X. Mario's level five! Ooh, that's a big- that's a big increase. Help me,
please. Pick something good. Hope you do. Now this is a fight. Damn. 43, 42. I can't do this.
All right. Seems HP has taken- no? Okay. Uh, I'm gonna close this in 10 seconds. Five, four,
three, two, one, zero. I- what am I supposed to do? 10, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three,
two, one. HP. Thank you. The water's been drained. How is that rigged? That's not rigged. That was
an- I was in a democracy election there. The water has been drained. Ah, it's okay.
I'm glad we went through all that for three HP. Three HP could mean life or death, guys.
Jerma, are you allowing multi-click on that? Because I think I single-handedly won HP. No,
I'm not. It is only on one click. Are you openly admitting that you were spamming the click button?
Openly admitting for manipulation? What the heck, man? Uh, yeah, I want to go up there. Okay.
I want to get up there. I forget how you get up there. How do I get up there?
How do- I know there's a way to get up there. I gotta go through that one and then you jump
up there and then you jump up there. Shit. How do I get that one?
This must be Belong? Is that a fire hose or a tongue?
It's a snack attack. And you're it, mate. Let's try fire.
Room service has been kind to me. Where's me bib? Good block. Perfect block.
God, standard. The hunger. The hunger. He's dead. He's gone. That was one of the biggest things of
this game when it first came out. People- I was trying to keep a seal on that because
Malo's gone now. He picks a character and they're gone. He ate them. That was a big controversy
when it first came out. It was like, what the fuck? The character's just gone? That was scary.
Oh, that's weird. I must not have played past that part. I don't think anybody else did either.
I think when that happened, everyone just kind of assumed that was the- like the end of the
kind of- that character pissed a lot of people off. I don't think very many people played past
that. That's why I believed it, too. Ooh, stick for a body and full of straw.
Give me a scarecrow. Raw, raw, raw. Scarecrows cannot do anything but magic.
That's fine. I'm going to take a honey syrup. Sleep socks. No shit, that's not good.
It's all right. I'm just going to keep jumping on them. I'm already a scarecrow, so I don't know.
I cannot do anything now. Let's hope that Malo wakes up. Oh, I wish that it just hit him.
I can't do anything. I can just defend. That's it. Hey, look, Malo woke up. I don't have any more
honey. No, I don't. Nope. I have to punch him to death. Pure water? No, he's not a ghost.
Uh, I can't stand it. The hunger. Uh, hey, Mario's back. Should be pretty close.
That was scary. If you defeat me, you still won't beat me. Beware the flood.
Malo must have been lying when he said water would come gushing out of here.
Mario, do you hear something, or is it just me? It's water! Quick, Mario, hit the button before
it washed away. You couldn't have stood on the button. That means he's so light that he's like
a pound. This is the Midas River course. Want to crash course? No. I know you've got to float down
and swim, and there's coins to collect. There's a broad coin right here. Got it. All right,
I don't- I think I skipped this one, if I remember. Which side do I go on? Left side?
Broad coin. And I'm gonna go in. Should I- all right, should I go in this?
I don't remember. I know you go in one of them. There it is. Come on, give me it. Give me it!
Give me that flower tap right now. No! Please! Get it! It's mine! Yeah!
Yeah, now we're over here and we bounce. We should get- I can't.
I think I'm gonna go right this time. I'm gonna go in the right hole.
Give me it! Yes! Give me those coins! Spray them! There we go again. Getting spit out.
I think that's the end of that. Oh, I'm- yeah, I remember this part. That's right.
Now for the barrel jumping. Um, give me some point. I do- I remember this, but hold on. You
jump from barrel to barrel. Time your jumps and grab coins along the way. Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Jump onto the next barrel before they collide. Right, okay, let's deal with that. Now I know
exactly what's going on. You- you can stay on it. You'll- if you don't have to jump. All right,
let's go. Almost forgot to tell you, leap over the fish that pop up or you'll lose coins. All
right, let's go. All right, straight. And again, straight. Change course. Watch out for the fish.
Fuck, I missed one. No! I thought I got it! Oof! Change.
Hahaha. Stay on this one. No, I want to stay on that one! I tried. Change course. Oof, that was
close. What? How did I not get that? There it is. Wasn't that fun? You got 61 coins. Trade the coins
you got from Midas River for frog coins. As a first-time-only bonus, I'll give you one frog
coin for 60 of your coins. If you didn't know, frog coins are the green ones and tadpole ponds
got more info on them. You got 61 coins, so you get one frog coin. Yeah. I will hold your
one extra coin. Here's something I picked up. You can keep it for good luck. You got a knock-knock
shell. Knock-knock shell is Mario's next weapon. Knock-knock shell. Kick to attack. By the way,
I think you can do this over and over again. All right, I'm gonna take the first pee. I'm gonna
pee my pants. I've been drinking water. I'll be right back. Two hours and no piss. That's a first.
Hey. Sorry, I want to grab a drink too.
Jesus. Is it time for PBR? No. This is a pineapple juice. Oh, just gonna have a cold one.
That does sound really fucking weird. I'm just pouring a pineapple juice into here.
All right, he's peeing in a glass. All right, back to it. So we just got out of the sewers.
We're now going to tadpole pond to go meet grandpa. Where is this?
Hi, can I help you? Malo, it's you. We've heard all about your adventures with Super Mario.
You guys beat up Balaam, right? You know about that? See Mario, the waterways of the world bring
news to us here all the time. That's why grandpa knows all the news that's fit to hear. Are you
really the Super Mario? Hey everybody, you'll never guess who's here. No, these are not talking frying
pans. These are tadpoles. They're huge. He's the real thing. Doesn't look anything like I thought
he would. They do say he can jump better than a froggy. I wonder if it's only a rumor. I sure can.
Well, grasshopper, what's new? Grandpa, Mario's been helping me. I know, child.
That rainstorm we just had, that was you, wasn't it? Oh, watch it up there. You're supposed to make
me look like I'm floating. Welcome. So you are Mario, yes? I am Frogfusus. You've come to seek
wisdom from me, have you not? I've been waiting for you. Yes, old, wise people can often give good
advice. But how rude of me. Let's get more comfortable. Come along and we'll talk.
Clear. Full reverse. Tadpoles, don't just float there. Make yourselves useful.
Form a bridge for Mario. Everyone talking about the music. It stopped for one second.
Yes, come into my sanctuary and partake of my wisdom, children. Let's see. That smithy
character that appeared at Bowser's Keep, he is quite formidable, yes? And Mario, you wish to
rescue the princess quickly, do you not? But, oh, if all of you do the truth, Toadstool is no longer
there? Uh, what? Patience, young one. Let me explain. Here is what happened. You were rescuing
Toadstool from Bowser's Keep. After defeating him, and just when you were about to free the
princess, you heard a loud crash and saw a sword split the sky. This, whoosh, out of the blue.
The shark sent the three of you flying. Bowser and Toadstool are still lost somewhere out there.
Now, listen to me. You're worried about the princess, but first you need to take care of
Smithy. His underlings are wrecking havoc in our world. Mac, whom you defeated at Mushroom Kingdom,
was one of them. More will be coming. Grandpa, I almost forgot to tell you something. We found a
star in the castle at Mushroom Kingdom. Do you know why it was there? A star, and most interesting.
This may sound illogical, but I believe shooting stars can grant wishes.
And now, more than ever, I believe they will play a vital role in the fight against Smithy.
Was that too much to absorb? Would you like a recap? No. It's quite a situation we have
on our hands, ain't it? Wow, everything sounds so dire and serious. I guess Mac was only the
first of many, Mario. Some of them will make Bowser seem nice. Mallow, you speak as if these
things do not concern you. You will accompany Mario on his adventure, too. Grandpa, what are
you talking about? I'm only a simple tadpole. This adventure isn't for me. Mallow, my boy,
I've kept this from you until now, but you're not a tadpole. What? I was sitting here on a rainy day,
enjoying a snack of crickets when I happened to see a basket floating down from the fog.
I peeked inside and saw a little baby staring right back at me. The name Mallow was written
on his belt. I felt sorry for the little bundle of puff and took him in to raise as my own grandchild.
He had powerful magic, and I knew he was more than a piece of fluff. I thought surely this child must
be from some far off land. Grandpa, you mean I'm not a tadpole? Stop that! Mallow, now is not the
time to cry. Go with Mario on his adventure and find your real family. Your real mother and father
were out there somewhere. Hey, Mario, the boy's magic is sure to come in handy on your adventure.
You'll take him along, right? Grandpa, I won't cry anymore. I'll go on this adventure with Mario
and find my real family. Then it is settled. You must embark on your adventure immediately.
First, go to Rose Town where they need your help. It'll be quiet around here with Mallow gone.
Maybe a snack will cheer me up. Wait a minute! That's right, I'd forgotten all about it.
I'll give you something for the cricket pie you brought back. Oh, you shall have the staff I
used when I was Mallow's age. Oh, it must have to be here somewhere. The froggy stick will come in
handy. Do not forget to equip it. Froggy stick? Holy shit, boy, he's going off script.
Here we go. So you can also spend frog coins here. Welcome to the Frog Coin Emporium. You're a first
timer, aren't you? Listen up. The green coins you find periodically are frog coins. Accumulate them
and you can buy items at Tadpole Pond. So as you see, this is the real currency. Bracer
raises defense, raises allies' battle power, raises party's entire, all the party's defense,
raises the whole party's attack power, but I don't, I never used them. This is the premium currency,
yes. Welcome to the juice bar. Are you a card member? Even Todofsky has a membership here.
Sorry, you're limited to this menu if you don't have a current membership card.
You can buy a froggy drink. Party recovers 30 HP. These are actually pretty good. I'll buy a few of
them. Put the froggy stick on. Did I get the secret coin that I only have one chance at? No,
I didn't. Melody Bay. Play notes by jumping on the tadpoles. Let's hear your melody.
Now this is, there are a ton of deep secrets in this game. You have to play certain songs
for Todofsky and some of them are very difficult to figure out which ones you should play. It takes
playing through this whole game and knowing very specific random things. Is that something you
composed? No, that's not the right melody at all. Yeah, he's looking for like the right melody.
I'm the composer Todofsky. I am trying to create my next masterpiece, but I've got composer's block.
You want a music lesson from moi? No. Fine, be that way.
He's still explaining the game. I've got this dream of becoming a composer. I want to be as
famous as Todofsky. My favorite song? It's Frogfusious's suite number 18,
so la mi re do re do re. Todofsky's fond of it too. Okay, there it is. That's one of them.
So la mi re do re do re. I'm just gonna write it down. So la mi re do re do re.
So la mi re do re do re.
Okay, I don't know which one of these is do. It's the start, right? Do is the first one,
right? It's do re mi la. So this is up here would be do. Is it descending or descending? I don't
remember. So do re mi fa so. Do re mi fa so la so. Do re mi fa so la. Do re, this is the second one.
Do re do re do re. So now I just do this. Isn't that something you composed? No, it's the other way
then. So it's up this way. I did it backwards. It was upside down. So this is do re mi fa so.
Do re mi fa so la. Do re mi re. So I need do re do re do re. That's it. Is that something you did?
That's not what? See the five lines between the second and third lines from the top.
Okay, so between the second and third lines from the top lies do. Keep going up and the notes are
do re mi. Go down and you'll do do ti la so fa. Okay, right. So it's do. Okay, I need this. I need
this. I need a screenshot that I can't screenshot this. It's on a console. So going up is do re
mi and then going down is do ti la so fa. Do re mi ti la so fa. Use your phone. Oh my god,
I fucking missed it. Okay, I'll get it. Okay, the notes. Second third lines is do. So you got do.
I'm taking a picture. Okay, so do re mi is like up that way. So that's do re mi and then down is
that's do ti la so fa. Got it. Okay, let's get it on there. Use chat screenshot instead.
All right, so do is between the second. So this is do between second and third line.
Do, right. So then I need to do. No, no, no, no, no. Back it up. Back it up. Fuck. I need to.
Thank you, Otter Fiend for the 10 community subs. Thanks a lot, Otter. Thanks for the sub drop.
I'll get it right out. Okay, so the out. So I mean, it's so. So that is do ti la so fa. Okay.
Then that we need to do la. So there we go. We got do ti la is mi. So this is do re mi
and then re do re do re. Re, re do. So this is do re do. I almost jumped. Do re do re. Got it. There
it is. That's it. This is the melody I've been looking for. Thank you for the inspiration.
Please take this as a token of my gratitude. Received an alto card. If I ever need help with
my compositions again, I'll look for you here. Until then, adios. I feel like I do that a lot,
what he just did. That like look at the air with your hands and go oh. I do that all the time.
All right, so I got my card now. Oh, I'm going to bed. Can't wait to graduate from music school
and start composing. I just stole that person's music. May I help you? Oh, an alto card. What
would you like? You can buy elixirs now. Party recovers 80 HP. That's a little out of budget,
though. All right, now I think let me go back here and ask you another question. I think he's back
and he gives you vague. Yeah, he's gonna give me vague things that I need to find.
Well, maybe not yet. I think I probably have to unlock it. Just grind until I have 99 elixirs.
That would be the most boring fucking thing I could ever do. I would hate that so much.
Okay, a rose wave. You can't jump on or off when the block is blue.
Try jumping when the block turns yellow. Now these move around in different places. I can go,
yeah. I have to go across. Shit, it's okay. Did he find Luigi? Um, a long time ago. I did find
Luigi. He's doing like crack behind one of the houses. Let's get that coin. No. Okay, can I go
from here? That didn't really... I had loved the froggy stick. I was gonna say I hate the froggy
stick and I just immediately corrected myself. The giant enemy spider. Yeah, those things suck.
Blocking these at all. All right, so I need to go around. I eventually will come around this way.
Oh, I remember this part. I'm gonna knock them both off and go get the treasure.
What a fun game. I'm not timing it right. The giant enemy spider is based on real Japanese history.
Is it really? That's really cool. Jebaited. He's jebaited. Are you sure? I feel like I've
heard that before. All right, I can't screw this up. I already did. I'm just gonna block.
Damn it. Shit. Oh, I blew it. Oh no. Now I have to... Wait, hold on. Okay. I fucking desynced it.
Now I have to desync enough times again to resync it. That's good enough. I'm gonna lose my fucking
mind. Shit. I remember this. I remembered even years later doing this and being like,
nah, I kind of don't care. I just keep going. All right, nobody move. Got it. Frog coin. What?
I can get that. All right, wrap it around. Watch out for those bandits. They steal. A penny? No,
that's ten. That's ten coins. The big ones. Damn it. Miscalculated. Pick it down. Yeah, money's
worth a lot. Come on. I gotta spend money. Let's see. Does this keep going this way? It does.
I missed all of it. Every single one. I still didn't. Unbelievable. That's truly not fucking
believable. Okay, let's go. I don't... No, hold on. I think there's other things I can do here.
What else can I do? What else is this gonna do for me? Something cool? Nothing cool at all?
There's no secrets? There has to be a secret. No secret. Maybe there is. I don't remember.
All right, let's get the heck out of here.
Full health. Watch out for the bandit. Damn it. He got it.
Well, why did you run into me then if you're just gonna run away?
No face cam, resident sleeper, no tuber reactions. What am I even doing here? Holy shit, he almost
insta-killed me. Fucking fart on stream. I'm not going to do that, so don't worry.
Those of you that are concerned, don't ask me why. Those of you that are concerned saying,
no, don't, don't do that. Why are you assuming that I would do something like that? Why would
I do that? Why would I just turn like my ass up and just go like...
Why would I do that? Guys, I am a super embarrassed farter and I want to just explain this.
I don't fart unless like I like go into a closed room and make sure that nobody is within like 50
feet of me. If there are people within like a hundred foot radius of me, I don't do it and I
like escape. This is actually kind of bad. I'm gonna die. Damn it, why did he run away?
Why did you run? Jerma, do you hear me? What? Snuck that one. This is cool, right here, go.
Wait, don't do that. It's the army. All right, people, form ranks. Attention,
shelled warriors, hooded sorcerers, and last but not least, ground wing goombas. This is our finest
moment. The koopa troop is invincible. We shall be victorious. The bridge is down,
but we'll find a way to get back in. Move out, on the double. Snap. That's right, Bowser in this
game, whenever he doesn't move, he snaps his fingers. It's fucking awesome. Bowser and his
troops must be on their way to Bowser's keep. Come on, Rosetown's just up ahead. Rosetown.
Ooh, you all right? See, arrows come flying out from the forest and when you're hit, you can't move.
See, look, I can't move a muscle. Now I know how our scarecrow feels. Since the day of shooting
star fell into the forest, arrows have been showering our town. Get inside, quick, get inside.
I tell you, it's scary out here, where someone's gotta pump the water, like this. One, two, one,
two, one, two, one, two. Someone's gotta do it. I'm desperately waiting for the comedic moment
where I can make a noise when I get hit, but this ain't a comedy stream. This is a nostalgia stream.
Item shop. Ding. And then to get this one, you gotta, you gotta fall to the ceiling.
But hey, why don't we uh, why don't we go in here? Should I go in here? What do you think? I think
it's time to go in here. I know, I know. I'm just very excited. No, no. The audio's desynced? Like in
the game? It's not. Luigi's behind the house. Oh, maybe I should go find him. That's weird. Here we go.
It hurt me with your childish pranks. Attention, Toadstool, you're coming with me. Zip your lip.
Help, help, somebody help me! Oh my god. It's, it's, it's, it's mom. Mom, we have a guest.
Yes dear, I hear you have. Hello there, aren't you Mario? For real? Well, you have the hat and the
funky stash. Are you really Mario? Wrong number. You bet. How do I know it's you? You might just be
pulling my leg. Show me, prove it. All right, okay. Mario, you want to play with me? I'm playing save
the world. Now, Gaz, Mario might be a little tired, dear. Aw, come on mom. You never play with me. It's
no fun playing alone. Oh dear, Mario. I hate to ask, but could you play with Gaz for a little while?
Yes! Okay, Mario just bought the farm, so you can be Bowser. I'll be Gino, okay? Ready? Let's play
from where I left off. All set. Oh scary, but just watch me. Better watch out, Bowser, because Gino's
gonna blow you away. Take this! Your turn, Bowser. Easy, Mario. It's just, it's just a game, Mario.
It's just a kid. Ow! Oh no, if he keeps this app unfinished. All right, you asked for it.
The super duper custom patented one star, one star on Yelp. Shooting star shot.
Oops, I think I missed. Oh, Mario. Mario, you, Mario, you good? Everybody shut up. This is the
most important thing in my whole life. There he is, there he is. Shh. It's not Luigi.
You know, for the longest time I thought his name was Geno. I was like 12. I thought it was Geno.
That was a 10 out of 10 Mario dream. Yeah, Mario, maybe you shouldn't eat like a pint of ice cream
before bed anymore. Mom, you'll never believe what I just saw. It was amazing. I just saw Gino walk
into the forest. Neat, huh? Yes dear, that's nice dear. And isn't Gino the one who broke my lamp the
other day? Oh my, it was just, this is real. I swear mom, really, it's true. I saw him outside.
All right, Gaz, let's hear it. What are you trying to get out of this this time?
Mom, I didn't do anything. I really saw Geno. And she's, I guess it's implied that she's like
screaming out. Oh, this boy is impossible. Sorry if I hurt you, but what would Geno want in the
forest? What would Geno want in the forest? I'm going to buy some shit. Mario, good to have a
customer at last. What do you need? What do I have? I have eight, I should, I need syrups.
I have, I might as well get five of these. Maybe one or two, a couple more of these. Hey Mario,
it's so nice of you to drop by the shop. What can I do for you? Thick shirt, thick pants.
Oh, we need thick shirt, thick pants. Jump shoes are actually really good. Wake up pin
prevents sleep. You won't be turned into a mushroom, prevents fear. These are way too
expensive. Let's see, I'm going to sell some stuff too. Jump shoes, they, as you see,
drop your defense, but they make your magic attack really good, which is my, obviously my jump
ability. What is my defense at right now? 22 and 19. 22 and my magic, yeah, that's actually, no,
that's good. I go up to 23 magic attack. Yeah, I'm putting on. True form versus wake up. Mushrooms
and it prevents mute. I don't think this upcoming boss does air crows, but do lose. Sorry, put the
thick pants on. Put the thick shirt on. I'm going to keep the wake up pin, but I'm going to sell
this other stuff. Okay, I think we're good. I'm going to maybe get a couple more items.
All right, that should be all right, I think. If it's not, it's not. Everyone is, you're about
to hear the best song in the whole game, by the way. This is, yeah, I would, I've seen a lot of
resident sleepers. I would wake up for this one because this is the best song in the whole game.
Still in Rosedown. I'm laughing my ass off. Yeah, this is the, we're going to be bopping here real
quick. Into the forest maze. You ready? Are you ready? Are you ready? No, I don't, I don't, I want
to hit the arrow. All right, we got it. That's why I'm going to be shooting pretty hard the whole
song. That was a lot of fucking damage. And now he's poisoned. That went pretty good. Malo's like
dead. He is going to die. Nope. I'm going to use one of the mushrooms because shit. He's almost
dead. I don't want to use any unnecessary mushroom. Don't worry guys, the song comes right back right
now. I think there's something in these. I know there is something. I think there's like a frog
coin or something in one of these. Star? Yeah, I think it is a star. You missed! What? What do you mean I missed?
You missed? How does that make any sense? What the hell? Did I check this one?
What is this song called? The song is called Beware the Forest Mushrooms.
There are probably 500 remixes of this song on YouTube. This is one of those songs that
everybody just seems to love over and over and over again and everybody thinks is like the
greatest song that Nintendo has ever put in a game and they won't put it in any other fucking game.
They won't put it anywhere. I don't even forget about like Gino and Smash Brothers. Why don't
they just put this song in? Why? It's only in this game and everyone's like yeah that's probably the
best Mario song ever. I don't want to hear like 15 different Nintendo official remixes of Rainbow
Road. I want this! Gosh darn it. Square owns the rights to the song? Do they? No, I don't.
What? All right, I need some levels here guys. So there are these characters that Square owns in
this game. What the hell are you going to do with these characters? I never understood that. Well,
you see the thing is like everybody like really loves these characters but Square owns them
and they just lock them in a fucking box and nobody can look at them. Nobody can buy them.
Nobody can look at them. Hey can you guys like do anything with those characters? No.
Can you sell those characters to somebody that will? No. Please? Oh I got Psychopath. Good. Please
go. I'm not even like Smash but like if like some of the characters that they brought into this
game into the universe they're really cool. They're really fun interesting characters. They
could be put anywhere. You could put them in another Mario game for all that matters.
You guys are going straight up magic huh? What are we doing? 29, 30, 21, 22. He's doing a lot
of damage. Square didn't even let Final Fantasy music in for the Final Fantasy characters in
besides one track. Shit I missed it. Like how much? Was it just like a stupid amount or something?
I wonder if Nintendo ever approached Square and said hey can we just buy all the intellectual
property of the characters that are in that Mario game? This seriously is like a Disney and
Sony fucking bullshit. That really is what this is. Disney and Sony come together and do like
Spider-Man movies and then yeah that's the same the exact same thing that happened. That was a
rock because now there's a bunch of these cool characters that we it's just no sorry you can't
say anything about them ever again just but I just enjoy the thing that existed that one time. Why
can't you just enjoy this thing? I do enjoy this thing. Well good. This thing was 20 fucking years
ago. Well enjoy it. I know but can I can you do any can I have another one? No enjoy this one.
I do I I already do. I love it so much that I want you to do another one so I will buy it.
No go back and play that one again. Oh I'm getting angry. He's losing it.
Oh first time today. I didn't do all night. What an embarrassment. It's all Disney's fault.
All right we got Mario here. Hey thank you. Jerma sucks for the five community subs.
Appreciate that. Thank you. We got super jump. What do you guys want to go now? We do everybody
gave me so much shit when I talked about in the very beginning of this stream that when I was
younger I just picked power only for a character HP only for another character and magic only for
another character and I was called a doofus and now you guys are doing that exact thing.
Okay that's 65% want me to continue to do power. Jeff just came in with five community subs. Thank
you Jeff. Thank you Jeff and Jerma sucks both of you. You said not to ruin your childhood. Yeah
that's true. I did say that. Don't do that. I know it's in one of these. Is this the last one?
It's in this one. Did I like bait myself on a thing that I'm misremembering?
Thank you the fax machine. This is three sub drops right in a row. Fax machine with five community
subs. Thank you. Jeff, Jerma sucks and fax machine. This is just like ET on the Atari.
Malo's dead and like I said it doesn't even need to be a Mario just anywhere. I would love it if
Malo was taught like fucking healthy eating habits in like a DS game or something. Like I would
fine it'd be cool. Why? It would be cool. I don't know. For your son or daughter to think it was
cool. That would piss me off. Why would that make you so mad? That would piss me off if he was like
in a vegetable eating tutorial game. Just play WoW Classic. No I'm not going to play WoW Classic.
I think I'm I got an opportunity here. I need to take a mushroom. How am I doing on I got a flower
jar. That's just easy. Might as well. I was gonna say remind me to pick those up. Some of them are
poisonous though I think. Yeah pick those ones up. No I'm looking for secrets. Wait a minute. The
first Jerma stream I tuned into was WoW and it put me off from watching you for years.
Holy shit. Well what are you doing here? What made you come back?
You know like okay as like a broadcaster that is that like is so horrible to hear that but I
understand why. That's the worst part about all that. Like hearing that oh no dude I watched that
stream and I was like I'm not fucking watching this person for like years. Like I'm like oh
fuck man really but I know why you said that. What do you mean lol broadcaster? What is this?
I'm sorry am I doing like am I doing like messages in fucking like I was gonna say
smoke signals but I couldn't find the word. Check this out this is gonna be fucking awesome. No
don't all run away I wanted to get this. Broadcaster lol. That's a lot of coins. He thinks he's a
broadcaster. Whatever. Now let's heal up. Wasteful but I don't care and I'm gonna take this flower jar
and I pissed off at least two people. They're not gonna watch for years after I did that.
Here we go. Follow them. Now there is a secret in this forest. I forget what it is. You don't
actually follow Gino. You do a different path and it gives you a huge treasure. I don't remember
which way it is. I forget. I'm sure I'll come back. And it's got double tap. Do you want the
directions? Uh no. No I don't think so. Somebody gives it to you eventually. I want this to be an
organic experience. He thinks he's broadcasting right now. Where are you Gino? There you are.
No. For some reason I have this weird image in my brain of if I ever did like an event
where I was on a stage or something like it for twitch like oh twitchcon and here's germa985
and then all you guys come a bunch of people are there that know me and I'm doing something
something live in person and they announce me as like and here he is ladies and gentlemen uh your
favorite broadcaster germa985 and the crowd just erupts in fucking laughter you know like is that
is that what would happen like he's just a broadcaster and then I would get wicked nervous
backstage I'd be like what the fuck man I would have like my magician's outfit on
I bought my cards on my like tricks of my coins and I would show where to go was I too slow
where is he I'm lost where no where did he go now I feel bad all right we're just gonna electricity
man that's a lot to the uh flying bug bees have you played any of the mario luigi games I've not
I've played marshmallow such right I did play superstar saga I played superstar saga and that's
it where'd you go come here got it 999 998 999 a thousand a thousand arrows for cover they run
fun this is yes you are another one thousand I will shoot Mario this is this guy he must be
one shooting all the arrows happy I am look at their expressions when freeze they do
more practice do I need oh no he's not stopping we gotta do something who do you think you are
Bruce Lee you can't just go in there with your fist flying there's too many of them will be
creamed huh oh no so it's coming let's hide and see what we can learn look what I found warrior
but but disturb me you must not practicing I am more arrows must I shoot more statues
gotta get I don't know I don't know what to do stop no uh stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
stop stop I don't know which one I don't know what to do stop hold it right there you don't
know what you're doing return that star to me stranger you are and strange looking at that
teach you we must who's in charge yeah and who might you be I serve a higher authority
that star piece belongs to everyone you can't keep it angry I am a lesson I will teach you
she knows the hedgehog hey chill out Mario that's dangerous out there you're gonna help huh
whack that weirdo save the guy in blue me too I will do what I can but from over here
I'm not afraid and I'm not going to cry yes you are yeah stop it that's enough
yeah strong you are but stronger am I hurt you I will so long part now we must
thanks for the help but who are you Mario you just ditched me back there
huh don't I know you you look familiar so you're the Mario we know about you
knock knock insulted I am do the Mario shit I fucked it up
now three against one not fair fix it I will shoot an arrow I shall when a target it hits
that button locked thank you I gotta get it this time I'm going for the fucking record
psychopath 556 HP what's with these folks that hurts all right no more why
try healed no ow that's like 50% of all of my health okay I'm fine I'm a off bolt
Mars dead try for it again I got why back 84 just got destroyed psychopath
290 that hurt a lot Gino beam here we go this is why you came to this stream
I didn't do it right nice broadcaster lol all right so if anybody I can't die here
he's dead don't worry here we go let's do it again I didn't do it right again
fuck what am I doing wrong because he like jumps in the air and lands how am I timing that wrong
more aid static oh that's not good uh use the mushrooms this is a heal round
just yolo it no I can't do that I gotta play it safe 12 oh shit okay uh
I still don't know the timing for Gino specials neither do I I really don't
know dead yeah you just have to hold y yeah but then you let go and you hit y again
and it does an extra thing flower box thanks for the help you really got me out of a jam
why are you staring at me you know I'm more than just a doll don't you the hell have you guessed
the truth I'm a visitor from above and this is the form I'm borrowing briefly you mean like from
the sky or something higher than that I'm afraid do you too know anything about the star road got
it completely in the dark well it's a big mess up there right now and it concerns you too let me
explain you've heard of wishing upon a shooting star at the star road your wishes transformed
into a star when it's granted it then turns into a shooting star and falls down to earth so you see
the star road plays an integral role in granting wishes but ever since a sword destroyed the star
road everything's come to a halt no stars have been made since the way things stand yours is a
world where wishes can't come true anymore are you saying this star is part of your star way
that star road my fluffy little friend yes that star is a broken piece of the star road
I'm here to find them all and repair the star road the broken star pieces there are seven all
together for peace to return we must get rid of smithy find the star pieces and repair the star
road I'm but it's hard to pronounce so just call me Gino after the door I chose him because he'd
looked the strongest out of all the dogs now grab the star Mario I don't know what to do for a voice
I've never had a head cannon for Gino to me it was always just do nothing it was I don't
have any head cannon for Gino two seven that just means you thought he sounded like you yeah all
right that's what he is come on let's get the show on the road Gino who is searching for the pieces
of the star road joins Mario and Malo things are definitely looking up whoa I heard everything
oh well I've known that that star was so important I've got to inform Smitty and I'm off the secret
to the shooting stars has been unraveled find the star pieces and bring peace back to Mario's world
on the next episode I gotta get out of here back to Rosedown pipe vault to moleville the game has
now opened up I'm gonna sneeze here's the real song for Rosedown I want to go meet my favorite
character what's taking daddy so long do you think he's still looking for the treasure
what was that he's out getting cigarettes thanks a million Mario say were my treasures okay
they sure were oh that's great news what a relief what they're gone Mario you're the only one who
can reach them all right I'll take your word for it excuse me I didn't hear you uh I'm sorry oh well
since we didn't get hit by any arrows I'll tell you a secret enter the forest when you hit an
area with four paths go left left straight right in that order you'll surely find something left
left straight right nice hey everyone's having fun again um there is some there's a very elaborate
thing in this town I forget where it is what's like the what's the guy with the seed isn't there
like another part of this town all right left left straight right
I would bet anybody any amount of money that I would destroy them and twitch things of humming
this song it's off for them because this is it's out of sync hold on so you tell me that game
audio is early does this help how about now me me jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump
jump no no it's off what happens first
jump jump jump the game is now late I don't care I'll delay myself another five seconds
okay ready jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump
jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump it's up to you malo he's a fraud caster
all right I forget I don't I left left straight right got it here we go left now is it my left
left left straight wait is it my left or the game's what is it what I don't know what it's trying to
I forget is it like my left like relative left okay here we go left left straight
fuck right jackpot this is not the wrong way look at all these treasures frog coin full health full
health tab oh yeah the greedy grinner three full healths and whoa that was great the tab is good
I'll be taking that one
well I'm sorry did you not know that was every hearthstone card when it lands
hearthstone hearthstone hearthstone hearthstone hearthstone hearthstone hearthstone hearthstone
hearthstone hearthstone thanks the cozy stream tonight yeah absolutely this is very cozy is he
going insane I don't think so what do you think tell me in the comment section who thinks there's
a comment section what are you guys doing those comments pipe fault all right now
this is this is gonna be fun you guys don't know what the heck this is oh yeah old school mario
oh this is very high damage stop it I'm bad which one which one which one which one last
one which one which one which one which one no I want to get the frog coin I'm gonna go
in that one no no what was that you guys have a lot of health oh my god they have like 300 hp
each that was like a rare spawn all right nothing in there what an old school this is just old
school mario I love it they don't make them like these anymore they don't make these anymore
except that's that's they still continue to they've made they keep making them in fact you can make
them now you right now can go make an entire mario game if you want if you'd like to why can't they
I want to I want to make mario rpg how come I can't have the eyes I know mario rpg template
and mario maker square owns the rights how much would it really cost from mario rpg ip
honestly how much is that actually going to cost it can't be worth more than like a couple million
dollars right it can't be maybe like five to ten million dollars maybe tops oh shit here we go
I can't wait I love this place it's my favorite to Yoshi's Island this is when they used to have
Yoshi be Donald Duck instead of talk like this Mario glad you finally made it to Yoshi Island
home of the mushroom derby say that Yoshi now that you're here we could use your help please
talk to a few of my pals here and what you can't understand them well have a board and I'll be your
interpreter oh Yoshi what are you cracked racing's my life and I could run all day
what are you looking at if you want to challenge me you have to bring
cookies it'd be so much better if we could all race together
Boshi here is the fastest runner but he's full of himself
what are you looking at you won't challenge me you'll bring cookies where do you get cookies
I forget check the mail hey there's a letter in here but I can't read it I can read honeymoon
reservations for two mushroom travel agency there's a letter in the honey wait what was it
honeymoon reservations for two mushroom travel agency there's nothing in here
and you're gonna bring cookies and then he lets us like race together doesn't somebody give you
free cookies somewhere I swear somebody has a cookie one of you guys has a cookie think you
can beat Boshi take my cookies good luck there we go thanks I've got major support on my side
so I can probably win today Yoshi got some cookies so you want the cookies all right
consider yourself lucky today you got yourself a race one on one hello again uh get ready the
mushroom derby is coming up want instructions I actually don't remember how to do this
press a and b alternate alternately alternating alternately alternately along with the rhythm
the tighter the rhythm the faster you go so yeah you have to go with the rhythm so it's like
didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't press the y button during a race to eat
a cookie it's energy will help you go faster uh I'm fine let's practice two I got it I'm gonna
destroy him let's go to the race
and I'm ready I cheated wow unbelievable you just beat Boshi
but we don't need a boss anyway I just want to race
oh what the fuck was that it's got like bit by a bug come on Boshi let's see what you made up
hmm all right oh here's the cookie stash we don't need a boss thanks to you Mario I finally beat
that rascal and we can all race together now here's something to remember me by got a Yoshi
cookie what you're carrying a lot of things I'll store these two for you don't worry I won't eat
them that makes a total of two next time you're in trouble during battle use this give me a call
yeah you can Yoshi has a summon apparently um I don't have any I'm out of room oh god damn it
I can get like a bunch of Yoshi cookies all right who needs to heal who cares
Yoshi give me those back how do I get the cookies he said he's holding them for me where
there's nothing in here where's your cookie stash where's the cookie stash he said he was
gonna store them he said he wasn't gonna eat them you're looking at me no nice weather huh
that can't happen twice he gave you it no I want my cookies he said I have two
he gave me one I eat it to all the potato chips what does what does that mean
yoster isle to moleville here we go moleville somebody stole all the cookies
moleville dining went to the mountain with little might but a star crashed into the mountain and
now they will be trapped 10 coins for a night y'all stay in the night no we're just coming in to save
the item shop come on in don't be shy everyone's uh so I could do nothing southern accent everyone's
up on the mountain but I'm stuck mine in the store so what's unique here we are punch glove
finger shot symbols everything is so expensive punch gloves finger shot symbols mega shirt
and then work pants are really really good too work pants who's gonna wear the work pants
probably mark gino mega shirt mega pants gino's gonna wear the work pants
let's get a couple of mid mushrooms a couple of maple syrups
why didn't I finish red dead redemption 2 on stream because the game is 150 hours
okay here we go punch glove the shell finger shot for the I played don't beat the whole thing
off stream mega shirt mega pants and then work pants makes you do way more damage
I'll give you the wake up 10-2 because you need something how many hours have I streamed dark
souls um I don't know that's a good question you can sell the rest of these sell items I think it's
time to get rid of these mushrooms how much is a yoshi cookie worth one dollar damn these are 75
cents 75 fuck it sell them I'm not gonna use those this this is that's good stuff all right
that's all right I have a lot of honey syrups I'm gonna be replacing these with mid mushrooms as we
go all right got plenty of money got three dollars and 43 cents I guess all right I got a
full inventory it's an emergency dinus trapped in the mines all right we're gonna go save somebody
in the mines a lot of houses my mom par helping out on the mountain do I have an instagram I
don't have an instagram I think I said this like years ago I said if like anyone ever shows like
they have balls on instagram and it's monument it's not me what does it go we can talk like
how's your most of our allies have run off what are we gonna do we've only had experience
fighting mario these new guys are too much shut up all of you I'm the biggest baddest brood around
and you don't forget it but if mario hears that I have been kicked out of my own castle
my reputation will be ruined even I have an image to keep up you know let's show who's the boss
around here all right the mine they're trapped in the mine everyone's trying to get in the men
folk are doing their best from the inside I'm digging in from the outside we gotta help them
I knew it was bad news when the star fell on the mountain sure enough it's causing trouble
forget something over here let them in I I can't oh dear I sure hope the kids are okay
I know how you're feeling but moping around here ain't gonna help a thing
that's what I've told her but I don't know if I'd be feeling any different if I was her
we're getting nowhere fast we'll never reach the kids at this rate see that up there that's the
old entrance to the mines but we can't reach it anymore if only that fella mario were here
he could reach that in a heartbeat well speak of the devil I'll be a goomba's uncle if it
ain't him in the flesh mario you're a lifesaver mario have you heard the news will you rescue the
kids yes thanks mario well there's the entrance up there here hop on our shoulders it's time
to attack these things are hard to uh no they're not don't know why lucky oh yeah that's the one
two three punch from mario and symbols the dumbest weapon in the game lucky means you get to bet
want to double your coins challenge the system win big or lose it all i'll do it where's the
yoshi hello seven please choose malo's next specialization are you guys actually gonna do it
you just you're gonna do the thing let's get the fuck out of me I'm sorry I did I just I
touched my microphone I'm sorry I apologize well there you go we're sticking with magic power and
magic defense only oh god I think there's a star in here hey have you heard there's a rare item
hidden in the mines if I find it I'm gonna sell it to someone in town I'm in it for the money
you see how I dodge that shit uh these things back here are more dangerous
lucky oh crystal
damn it I always miss these now okay I got it why is malo so bad uh because he's only had points
put into magic damage and magic defense which means he's really really really really good
when you do any of his magic attacks other than that not really worth having to party
the image mario has the highest power of the whole group what the fuck this is why geno just
got to put him in every party he's the best all right I'm going for it I'll do it I'm going with
the audience you were right you guys got it nice work I am pleasantly surprised you know it's
gonna happen eventually mario uh-oh coins beautiful coins grab the coins listen up let's
leave this half-wit mario here and split anyone got beef with that oh shit he woke up oh no he
took the coins chase croco and get those coins back oh boy it looks like a dead end here but
not to worry I've got a bomb never leave home without one don't stay so close he stole the
coins that we won that is kind of what happened and they're off ah once again oh lucky just get
get it over with it's huge overkill but I didn't want to fight for that one there we go what do
you think that one there was no stakes on that one you guys could have picked but where are the
stakes it was two coins the last one was like almost 20 you got all the flowers and mario good
good work doing power again guys you get the whole bottom row yeah catch him catch him
come here let's start this off with the bang 50 48 thank god it missed 652 oh I'm good oh he's got
the work pants on right that wasn't very good not bad full hp let's go miss I need to hydrate
oh I'll take another break in a minute here 18 miss again what the hell I'm gonna use some mushrooms
because they're just taking up tons of space and I want to get rid of them never mind drink water
drink now I'm fine I'm fine miss again let's put all these misses you want them back you've gotta
take me down first oh right he takes your ride all of them all right we need to heal with uh
malo's heal chomp if I didn't block that that would have been really really bad hp ran to
yourself you need to stay alive all right we're good with the chomp 12 we're fine so what is the
official speed run on this game what's the what's the time on it an hour two hours
10 hours yo genuf here's your junk I'm out of here two hours and 46 minutes damn it 50 coins and
10 experience and Gino has reached level seven Gino's max hp his attack his defense his magic
attack you can take a quick look and I'm going to let you guys decide on what you're going to
do if you pee in the cartridge send you the yep all right okay guys this is important what
what are what do you want to do much harder than I thought it was going to be
this is going to have to stay up for a little bit y'all want different things
how do you vote you just have to click the screen with your extension enabled okay I have to call
it 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 hp it is you got good choice it's a very good choice because it went
up by a lot got the coins back and picked up a bomb too hooray ah we made it we're out
oh fuck no come on okay we're good that was a low brain move all right here we go where's the
secret item I know it where's the secret seems like you found something mighty useful my kid's
done I might have trapped back there let's blast through and find him thanks Mario now stand back
let me get things going let's follow the tracks of the end what the star is probably in the back
thanks a million Mario let's mosey along now oh I guess you're right I just be a burden on you
fellas well then I'm counting on you why can't we have like the mole guy thanks a lot Mario
I guess I'll be going back to tell mom about everything oh oh oh I forgot it's here
oh fuck I forgot I thought you had to buy I thought you had to buy it through somebody
through a fence disappointed it's a lot of coins it's like a hundred coins that's that's
more than that's a hundred coins once again no that's way later in the game is it I guess it is
that was an absolute shit load of coins like 541 coins are you kidding me if I if I had only made
it over here think about that I would have gotten four oh well do it again get that anything else
I think I'm good get out of here just one bomb there's a trick to getting the star as many
times as you want so you can over level really quickly here a bunch of broken mechanics bugs
I mean like this good day the name is Nello Punchinello Punchinello
never heard of you they say I'm a hothead but I'll show them you you will make me famous
so long it's dark Cheeto it actually kind of is Cheeto isn't it it's like that thousand health
yee-haw I see we're already famous oh yeah this this guy kind of is annoying
is this emulated it is not I mean I don't know I have no idea is it emulated it has to be what
am I talking about this is the Super Nintendo thing like that Super Nintendo box with like the
classic SNES box yeah the SNES mini thing it's on an actual NES of course it's of course this is
emulated I don't even know why I thought that for a second I'm going to jail not bad not bad
now let's up the ante bigger bomb how's how are we doing on health okay let's keep up the
punching go ahead and do a thunderbolt damn it all right settle down have I said a bad word
all right it's clobbering time actually am gonna use some stuff here because these things like
will kill you oh that's not good it's okay uh mushroom on mellow use the Disney lawsuit special
move what is the Disney lawsuit move what the hell does that mean he said it's clobbering time
that's the thing right it's clobbering time yeah I don't think the thing has said that in any movie
must be dreaming I'm ruined I didn't want to do this but now I have no choice
I think he's bluffing simmer down fluffy I'm not gonna waste this on you who knows what might happen
then take your best shot enough got my pride now you're in for it
huh what the hey why isn't it working mario if this ain't explodes we're history
this is a fine mess let's scram now yeah oh it's gonna blow
yeah what our earth was that well we won the battle now I hope we don't lose the war
we're a diner in the star oh there's the star I guess my question's just been answered
come on Mario let's go yeah
uh
there it comes 39 I'm not 39 who told you that was a fucking liar
come on let's get the show on the road who told you that I don't know oh just
care to read the warning of course mine car guidelines press
a or y to break press b to jump get mushrooms and press x to accelerate mobile safety board
I wonder what the record on this one is 3d all right slowly slowly slow ah fuck I forgot it's a
okay we're good grab that I fucked it up again all right we're good nice the records in a minute
57 is it I mean this is pretty damn good whatever I'm doing shit give me another one this is a flash
game I mean I can I can see that oh that was close I need another one quick I gotta beat the record
I only have 10 more seconds I didn't get the record I tried to slow down sorry restart it
I'm not gonna get the world record I am going really fast though let's go hurry up no no slow
where's the kid oh I think I lost the kid on a turn I wonder how those kids are doing I sure
wish they'd hurry home settle down I asked Mario to help out so I reckon he'll be back
I just have this odd feeling that they'll be dropping in at any moment they still
gotta use the door like everyone else ma settle down we're home gracious they really did drop in
on us oh my poor babies are you okay little mite are you hurt no we're okay ma isn't that right
Mike we had fun man man he's been knocked unconscious you poor baby you're safe now
Donna haven't I told you often enough to never go into the mines by yourself that's enough ma
just be happy to have him back we even thanked Mario proper either thank you Mario I'm so embarrassed
we can't thank you enough for everything what's that the roof you say that don't matter none
it ain't nothing at all you just leave any repairs to me give me a holler if you ever need a hand
with your place thanks again for bringing our babies back to us oh and by the way you found
Dinah might and a star piece but where is toadstool just want to make sure you understand that it's
me Luigi I drank a potion and turned into a mole I'm back I have to catch my breath after that
come back here mr beetle don't you want to come to boosters and play
yeah don't you run away we just want to play we'll take good care of you
oh like what they said okay mr beetle don't you dare touch that beetle it's a present for booster
that's right just hand it over nice and easy yeah uh like they said or we won't be your friend
booster really really likes beetles but he can't catch his own
that's right he's busy keeping the princess from the sky entertained
yeah so we're catching beetles for him so hand it over that's right oh please
oh no it's getting away quick catch it catch it fucking idiots welcome to my pretend store
would you like a shiny stone yes if you bring me fireworks then you're a shiny stone
hey there remember me from the mines I found some neat stuff and I'm opening a miner's store
take a look yeah I never really thought about this giving fireworks to a child
item one a lucky jewel it's sure to bring you plenty of good luck
I'll sell to you for a hundred coins I'll take it that's all I got for now someone's luck at will
how's this thing doing things sucks they have a talk in town they say you save the kids so what
do you need I need one I don't have I all right I need to get rid of stuff I'm gonna start selling
stuff yep it's time to clean it up I know I'm losing money on this but I have to free up some
how much is lucky jewel 50 okay all right all right I'm so hungry I sure wish I had a carbo cookie
I wish I had a carbo cookie too what he's doing why is everybody ever doing the dot dot dot
there's a rumor that booster's new girlfriend fell from the sky she's supposed to be pretty
too just like a princess now who would have thought a girl could fall out of the sky
maybe it's toadstool nah this hole my wife dug is a shortcut to the trolley it's amusement
ride I named mobile mountain ain't that nifty drop in here and you'll be right at the trolley
tracks it only cost you 10 coins the high score is uh two minutes and 32 seconds you want to ride
it no fine be that way the record of mobile mountain is two minutes 32 just go to the inn
and rest if you're tired I'm passing little ones aren't allowed on the trolley I can't wait to get
older now it's just a ride all right let's go booster pass my the wife they are aren't they
yeah it's a fish in there I forgot about the fish thing doesn't even hurt pre-recorded stream why
are you saying that what the fuck are you talking about it's artichokes
how do I know which one is real and which one's fake I don't know I've never played this game
before I'm going for them I'm going to get them I'm going to take them out of the sky
bingo I knew there was one over here got it all right let's get them this guy knows magic
that hurt a lot six I didn't even know that was here I thought that was part of the background
that means someone's gonna die who's all right I have to be careful
once again there it is finally first time I've seen it the worst speedrun I've ever seen
um I'm sorry to hear that all right I'm really not using items right now I really need to and
I'm still alive he's dead now right like if that okay this is getting a little ridiculous
stench you you have so much HP it's kind of annoying actually you guys have fucked
up that's a good way to get rid of all your mushrooms that you don't want like that okay
anything else down here no don't touch that one that one's fake two three close them all up
you've been sealed pick them flower what a god of a gamer booster tower this is uh one of the
oddest parts of the game the place is fucking weird booster is such a nice place I miss my
fortress I miss the good old days toadstool screaming in terror of mario rushing in to save
her oh jesus mario oh okay okay uh calm down don't let him see you like this hey how you been
no not like that idiot wrong tone needs more confidence you what are you doing here
if toadstool were at my castle waiting to be rescued she'd be crying like a baby
oh did I just hear some voices I can't believe it it's mario I'm up here that voice it's toadstool
I thought she'd gone away but she's been stuck here well I guess I'll be returning to my castle
now out of my way shorty it's locked what you're still here that look on your face
I get it now out of my way shorty yeah yeah I'm a piece of work ain't I all this power and looks
too I know I know what you're thinking a big strong guy like him would be great to have along
right I'm gonna do something they might regret later I'll let you join the koopa troop you can
thank me later mario and his friends have joined the koopa troop or so they're pretending bowser
joins the group by the way for those of you wondering the first game and one of the only
games where bowser is a playable character the first time they did it and yes malo is gone
bowser's inside yeah I said the I said the I said one of it's the first and one of the only I
didn't say this is the only time they've ever done it as way goodbye to malo he's gone you'll
never see him again well I want the middle you can't count mario kart that's like saying
that waluigi is like a play well I mean you know you know I'm saying if party games don't count
I'm talking like a main like mario video game you can't count a party game for I can't you
cannot replace mario unfortunately uh what do you have for items nothing yet welcome to booster
hello there booster is busy right now so he can't play come back some other time or you can try to
force your way in like right now blizzard it's chilly in here I still don't know what terrorize
even does I get to stand on your desk all right so uh let's take a look over here and over here
and over there there's the jester we're gonna kill the clown yeah I'm going for the clown
first try jevil any news on that game is undertale uh delta room whatever coming out soon
or is that gonna not be a thing for a long time seven years what I don't even want to fight you
let's go back this is a little fun puzzle I can't do this right now though I can later
booster the first booster the second booster the third booster the fourth booster the fifth
booster the sixth and there's booster of the creep all right mustache beard eye patch okay
kind of is it yeah booster's voice
what's the big rush
I'm booster and this is my famous tower of amusement normally I welcome visitors to play
with me in my sniffits however a girl fell out of the sky and into my lap recently since then I've
been busy keeping her happy and entertained I no longer have the time to play so please enjoy
yourself at your own risk please refrain from bothering booster holy shit they did a lot of
damage oh fuck gotta be careful bye-bye let's heal while I still have a second mid-bush
oh take a honey syrup though I love the base on this one flower tap he's just hiding
all right here we go remember I told you I was gonna have to do this later got it
first try yeah found a masher that is a new weapon for mario it's much better take a look at that 97
versus 77 it's ridiculous 97 attack in fact now that mario has that item I'm going to give the
work pants to mario mario cannot use the work pants never mind give bowser the work pants well
geno's got the work pants and he's doing damage shit too fast you miss malo well you might see
malo again eventually what was that loud noise outside check out boosters pass
that is a new area I think are you guys ready are you ready
how did they get the rights I can't believe they got the rights to mario
oh that thing on the left sucks doesn't take it only takes damage from
um magic I think it's a pain in the ass earwig well that was not correct
I know that one of them is hard to kill and that's a little bit
nice weather we're having I want to fight you you want to fight I do bash his head
snippet three is the most powerful
all three uh snippets are dead save mine game booster style is this on the SNES yes it is
superintendent entertainment system you can get it from the little SNES mini or by some other means
know how take a look at boosters family portraits in order from the oldest to the youngest
wait can I remember this I tried to I was doing I'll go for the one on the right
I'm gonna level up soon here okay here we go then it was okay then I think eye patch then it's a
little messy for me here I think then it's sunglasses and then regular glasses and then
here we are that's me the elder key they gaze into each other's eyes mario she's a bit shy
look the other way will you you can turn around now she says she's been locked up ever since she
took a bite out of booster so now she wants to help us stir up a little trouble the chomp new
party member unlocked chomp now you get the work no you don't chomp work pants 105 damage
don't have any more armor for gino but it's fine
I did that move sorry I'm an idiot all right got the chomp new weapon browser and
I love the architecture of this place this is really weird and interesting
and this full fine all right go across this way oops it's so weird it is so weird
there's a primo con these things that get hundreds of damage
that's the other one here in my life the best part of the game is mario challenges you to a game
of yahtzee I know what you're talking about that is pretty interesting part so weird mid mushroom
good let me make these jumps what's up there check cover behind yeah frog got it nice
there's always something figured I would have figured really this booster wario's dad do you
think but we'll never know the answer to that question wario's not in this game so there's no
spoiler I want to get all the frog coins it's important to me hey malo reach level eight
without even doing anything maybe some upgrades well I may as well just pick special every time
because there's no way anyone's you're never gonna pick anything else ever I'm just gonna
do special every time because that's what you're gonna pick that's what you're doing
oh that was two from 38 to 40 damn it you know I still don't know um what the mechanic is in
this room since I was 12 I just jump to the ones that are the tan tiles and I think it works
that's the right w exp isn't zone you guys I'm not gonna involve you guys
how do I get it wrong every single time every time room key zoom shoes oh yeah zoom shoes
let me take a look here 67d should I just give him to Bowser speed up by 10 huge magic defense
Bowser's kind of unstoppable if he's on yeah we're giving the zoom shoes to
zoomer ha ha funny it's like the word zoomer but it's funny ha ha zoomer
I'm so glad that you just said all that and stuff because I was gonna say like here are the zoomer
shoes so like thank you thank you for literally doing that before I did so people won't make fun
of me all right we got uh I should bop that person yeah no what do you mean yeah
no I used to be pretty good at avoiding these this way Bowser's beefed up 148 damage
the rest of this game's gonna be a breeze
oh
time hits to do yeah die what the hell
all right somebody else already needs to level up there is big hp increase don't do it yet
now do it put it again stop try it again I screwed that one up try do I count the fact
that it's Mario Mario and hp are on the same plane they're in the same like column that's 39
percent what do you mean no that's too bad that's 35 percent 33 that's it thanks for voting
okay what about the flowers those are very look at that they're overlapping into each other
that bubble is very now people are panicking now you're freaking out those bubbles are
overlapping I have to count it look at this everybody's lost the damn mind thanks for voting
chugger chugger oh chugger chugger this is my personal railway
bye it's you again I'm amazed you made it this far it's quite amazing you are since you're here
maybe you'll clear something up for me my bride to be is chanting Mario help me Mario help me
Mario help me is she showing her happiness hey wait a second maybe Mario is another guy
what if you're this Mario she keeps talking about trying to take my bride away why don't you take
the best instead I didn't do it I ran out of bombs so long that was the joke well the joke
was I was thinking about leaving that on for an hour I was that whole time that I was sitting
there I was internally debating if me muting my microphone and going eating food downstairs
just getting like some like pasta or something and just eating and spend like a full hour down
but then I was like no I want to play I want to play this game I want to like continue to go
frog coin how many problems do I have chat would go insane during that hour yeah they would
you know this is where it gets weird right it's mario doll everybody's playing with action
figures in this universe huh you did come to rescue me I was so frightened and lonely
but now that you're here the door won't open I think we need booster's spell to undo the
lock on it what should we do what should we do booster's returning isn't he I know hide
somewhere and wait till he opens the door good luck hiding from booster in his snippets
I failed this all the time when I was younger it was this was so hard for me to do
boy shouldn't we be concentrating on the girl right now about that girl in my life
who thinks I should marry her well speak up the wedding ceremony would make a great party
ah party we would have one of those it can be fun so what is a party
well you drink punch and eat cake I think drink punch and eat cake it sounds complicated
I don't know if I can buster the energy to do it let's walk through it what there's a wedding
rehearsal time we will now begin the ceremony walk down the aisle with me hey turn to make a
beautiful bride to me wait Mario always shows up about now to ruin the fun
we've got to take that into consideration you know someone go and get the Mario doll
it isn't here of course it's here you lazy slobs couldn't find water if you a fish
it's behind those curtains number one you go and look
oh it isn't here I wouldn't go and lose my Mario doll you idiots
number two you go look too
it isn't here we can't give up it's got to be somewhere number three it's your turn
wait a minute this is better than a party look out because here I come
um wait wait a second it's right out there I found the Mario doll
but we're never going to be able to reach it up there oh the sorrow what am I going to do
I'm about to lose it I can't get that doll there's no way we're going to be able to get it
how are we supposed to do this I can't goodness you're so kind thank you for getting my doll
I'd like to reward you here take this and you may have me just follow you wherever you go
all right enough is enough cancel the rehearsal we're going on with the show
here's the password Mario I like killed my voice in the first like two hours of this game
doing some some fucking whatever it was I like can't even do the booster I want to do
wait you took all the trouble to come here so stick around
night guy we got great guy and knife guy let's just terrorize it worked didn't block that one
that does so much damage it's so good echo fine I gotta kill my guy first I think he's the most
dangerous and oh you can't do anything right yeah that's right yes he is carrying a knife
how many times did you beat this game uh probably two to three hundred times
something like that give or take maybe one or two you played it 500 yeah I haven't I didn't
beat it of those 500 attempts I only beat it 200 times flower jar and experience who's gonna be
Bowser good Bowser Bowser click click while I go get a water I'll be right back wait hold on
don't click yet okay now click we're back okay well I just realized forgot about something yes
uh you guys ruined it uh when I see penis time everyone make a penis it's penis time
right now I know I'm gonna pick this and then I'm gonna go be a bee so I mean that's not gonna
happen thank you for voting and we're gonna do power I would agree 90 attack power and
Gino as well maybe a good look possible how did he know Gino boost one of the best abilities in
the whole game now I will be right back after this I'm gonna refill my water I'm gonna like
a snack I wonder what magic power it is people spoke thank you 30s that's a lot 33 36
no shit I can't be rb yet I have to do this first you go right into this thing oh yeah with the bugs
please let me go won't you please yeah where's my bride to be I want to play hide and seek too
yuck I don't want to play anything with you what a poor sport well we really should hurry along
every cake is waiting for us after we climb this hill let's go no I don't want to marry you
help Mario help me oh it's Mario we didn't plan on this Mario you aren't invited to our wedding
besides we still have the rehearsal I'll be happy to race you to the wedding hall but
it better not get in my way ready let's go this is the booster hill track forget what you do here
you can only move left or right and jump you can't go forward or back but you have to jump on their
heads I think touch the snippets or any of the barrels and you'll fall back yeah but if you jump
on a snippet jump on the barrel with a snippet to sprint forward and I believe every time you touch
toadstool you get a flower tab so it's pretty big deal like there's a really big deal I don't
want to screw this up come here shit what I should have peed first I should have peed first
this is this is hurry up and pee the song this is in my head whenever I have to really pee
I'm not getting that no fucking way oh no it's getting it's getting more intense
I'm at it you got six flowers congratulations okay I have to pee I'll be right back
uh so by the way I have confirmed tomorrow tomorrow we will be trying to
complete the base game of terraria it may or may not be the last terraria
maybe that is the plan unless something happens we're gonna beat vanilla terraria maybe
if we can do it maybe okay I'm just eating cheese right now don't mind me what kind it's
white cheddar one of those little cheese circles they're good baby bell that's right I'm the best
photographer around would you like a wedding portrait we'll take it then take a picture
I think it's later actually all right let's go let's do this every new town has a shop
and we want to go in there new stuff I'd like to buy some things we've got super hammer
handgun glop glove chomp shell happy shirt happy pants b-tub ring
well let's get the home I think the masher and jump shoes are better
the zoom shoes at least work pants I don't think many of these are going to be any good
amulet great item bad smell all right this thing's crazy I'm gonna give that to Gino
Gino needs armor happy cape happy shirt this is malo but I'm not using malo right now
handgun super hammer mark this is not as good should I buy the b-tub ring I'm not sure I haven't
used this for anything every time I play through this game I just go what is that and I don't do
anything else about it handgun punch gloves I can get rid of the mega shirt get rid of
finger shot get rid of wake-up pin I'm gonna keep just in case I need it fine cell
mid mushrooms have seven of them will be fine I'm gonna get another maple syrup though
that should be good all right let's go merry more oh I'm so exhausted I heard there's a casino
where you can get big bucks but I just can't find the place does it really exist
it does it doesn't I can't wait to go hello how may I help you it's luck how may I help you today
I'd like to buy some things I'd like to rest a while I like to rest a while we offer a very
special deal for a limited time if you choose to stay in our lovely deluxe suite you shall
receive a once-in-a-lifetime gift now which room will you choose I want the deluxe suite
excellent choice sir we shall attend to you in a minute sir this is the gift we promised you upon
selection of the suite we hope you will enjoy it got a flower town the bellhop will show you
to your room please enjoy your stay it's fancy this is the room please make yourself at home
please feel free to use this terry cloth bathrobe after bathing ring that bell for room service
and please be sure to turn the lights off when going to sleep anything else
looks like he wants a tip will you give him one thank you very much sir please enjoy your stay
look at this big suite hold on a minute two beds let's get some rest now I'm well rested
I feel great it's too small for you what do you mean it's too small for you what are you talking
about mario you're not supposed to take a shower with all your clothes on I want some room service
took you a full two seconds to get in here
I'm thirsty pick me up 10 coins caro caro cola 100 I want the caro caro cola
here you are sir bought a caro caro cola please do not hesitate to ring it looks like he wants a
tip thank you enjoy your stay did I burn my skin just kidding you want a tip from you didn't do
anything all right I want to pick me up how much money am I giving this guy 84 cents
you've paid for only one night stay would you like to stay longer yes I don't have 200 bucks
what happens when I no like honestly what I don't think I've ever done this yes stay again this is
day three okay I have 84 coins I've stayed for two days three days now okay let's go
have I ever done this before hello how may I help you stay more sir you seem to have stayed three
times for the price of just one night I'll have to receive a hundred coins for each night you
have extended your stay wait a minute you're broke I have no choice but to make you work for the
remaining amount what do I have to do bellhop escort this guest over to our suite remember
to do a good job okay come on I don't want to be a bother but could you please help me
this way end it up here here you are the suite this up here this over here there's all those
things and uh I could use a tip few finally here hey you're mighty handy around here you deserve
a tip go on take it thank you I just threw it away in front of her can I sleep in here
I'm gonna take a shower in your shower now oh come on I can't sleep all right I did it
please see our guest out what I slept like a baby thanks I'm trying to flock her fuck
you are not a guest now please come here and we shall discuss this matter
you're not off the hook yet what are they gonna complain what's going on
bellhop escort this guest over to our suite can you please help me out
it's the same person finally you're mighty handy you deserve a tip take it a mushroom
use the toilet please see our guest out god damn it told him trying to fucking stand here
don't good job now don't you ever spend another night here without any money
what's the last thing you heard me say I feel like I was gone for a while isn't this just
splendid this place is heaven even for the rich and famous you went back up to the hotel room
all right well hi we're back welcome to the stream everybody hope you have another day
hope you have a good day lovely wedding hall or four star hotel please enjoy your stay here
what you're seeking the man in the face of a totem pole how could I forget him he's up
there the wedding hall all right all right stop the wedding ah shit the wedding already
happened like four days ago oops I'm coming I'm coming looks like he needs to go somewhere fast
so don't even bother trying to sneak inside what the heck who's the guy with the totem pole for a
face he imprints his toaster word no don't tell me they're getting married I'm not letting you
in here and you can forget about the back entrance it's locked which I think it is now
that's the kind of adorable video game that I love here's the cake chef tort we bake a cake
for the big wedding it must be masterpiece yeah the groom to be ordered something special
wait until he sees this let's jump up there do speedruns rat just checking check everything
that what are you doing oh that's nice you stepped on you fools
halt who goes there you look like mario but the door shut tight listen mustache you and your
overgrown turtle friend can take a hike go scat make like mario jump out of here get lost it's me
oh oops we got a problem I better go tell booster
and we'll bunch say you want to help me bust this door down on the count of three we'll run
together timing is the key ready here we go first try booster sir mario is here
you crowds you don't break a door down with anything
you shut it shut it shut it shut it mario is that you mario i'm hurry i'm scared
we're pretty sure mr mustache can't break in here but that turtle looks pretty mean it could be
trouble they have no idea what they're up against i'm lightning in a bottle i'm an earthquake in a
can i'll bust this open in no time i did it oh watch what you're doing great now i've dropped
my shoes my ring my brooch and my crown he's t-posing by the way i don't think i've ever
noticed that booster sir uh booster i uh don't bother me now okay everyone the bride is growing
impatient let the wedding begin what's this water coming from your eyes are you leaking my dear
ah this tastes salty poster sir uh i believe that the bride may be um crying crying but that's what
people doing this sad how disgusting this stuff must be corrosive it tastes like the sea what
could be making her cry anyway i believe she's crying because she has dropped some of her wedding
gear of course she dropped her gear but those tears will ruin the cake make her stop before mario
breaks in uh but mario was already in poster sir hurry and find her things we have to get
on with the wedding in the meantime perhaps we can do something about the cake tenfold good buddy
you find her stuff i'll move the ceremony forward hurry booster sir you're supposed to be on the
right the bride should be on your left just testing you like this yeah booster sir i found the ring
booster here's the brunch doctor sir i found the shoes hey wait wasn't there one more thing
oh you're right the crown hurry and get all the accessories from the snippets and save princess
if you quit something good might happen maybe you'll get to see a uh sneak peek of the carnival
oh i'll look for the last one give this to booster got the brooch you're jumping to you the same
person i'll look for the last one go give this to booster i'll look for the last one give this to
booster go go go go go go go go go go go go go crown oh here it is hey you're mario so you've
come to crash my wedding i presume mario you're finally here shriek what is bowser doing here
what a waste of time i got bigger fish to fry you know when when bowser and um and
been boomer they're in the same room kind of have to change it a little i know i'm in good
hands when you're around mario here's a kiss for my hero oh isn't that just great you're gonna kiss
him when i'm the one who saved your skin me too i want a reward i'll take the kiss give me a kiss
stop it all of you idiots mario let's start with you
so now tostul and i are allies i'll never live this down what the i love he turned over it but
this was like now that's one for the scrapbook come mario let's get back to mushroom kingdom
the chancel is waiting for us sorry to have kept you waiting we've made the most amazing cake
you won't believe it air is cake but there are bride and groom where is everyone this is big
trouble the bride is sleeping you're taking the bride away but she won't be anyone to eat the
cake what this can't be if we've worked all day on this you fools stop stop stop
go for the cake attack the cake kill the chefs what stop stop stop stop
oh what are you doing chef toy the cake is moving that is not moving back to work i know it was
moving uh what is now but chef toy the cake is moving talk to more of this no really truly
why would i lie because you are idiot see it is not moving oh
oh the cake's alive run see i was right i don't know why out of the art world by the way um
the that that sound that i made i heard it and then i saw it and then i saw it again
that's the when you hit with uh for undertale that's at the flower and undertale
when i don't want to get i'm gonna give spoilers for undertale so just fucking just don't listen
to this for a second there's a certain noise that that flower makes when you are doing when
something happens oh it's you just rewind that and listen to it you don't know exactly what
i'm talking about blow the candles out here we go i can't speak up because it's a spoiler for the
game and i don't want to spoil the game but what if you've never seen it before you've played it
before all right this guy actually sucks i have to be careful here yeah this actually is kind
of hard after i yeah i'm gonna die when was last time i saved the game two hours ago that's not
true please get all the spells in the game have i saved all stream i don't i don't know how
attack up defense up and let's super jump on this cake jump on cake i just did
first to go down i have to pay attention this is no more messing around
weird how much longer am i gonna scream for i'm probably going to call it a night after this
town that'll take us to cleanly just about like six six six over six hours six and a half hours
something like that how far am i through the game i am probably just at the uh probably just about
the halfway point maybe another hour or two to get to like the halfway point mushroom mario
what does pog stand for um a pog champ it's an emote on twitch but you're gonna stop playing
your favorite game at six hours but you're gonna see you play the simpsons for 12
yeah but the difference the difference between the simpsons stream is i've never seen it before
plus that was a mission i was i was on a full complete mission
i love this game this is like when i'm dead i'm not on like a crazed mission to beat this game
thank goodness all right got the first part of the cake now
is this a better game than bloodborne uh i don't think that's fair because is this a better
video game than bloodborne probably not but it was maybe 20 years ago it's hard to compare
is this better than this even though this is 20 years old they're both very very very good
one of them just happens to have 20 years of technology on the other all right i need to
i might need to take one of these froggy drinks was 30 hp for everybody yeah i'm going for it
freebie good 140 that's pretty damn good here we go all right oh maybe we're out of
this is booster's wedding cake they'll have a fit and point people on it hey all right number one
where's my cake there's a 70 chance the object now you're standing on is the cake
this thing is the cake okay everyone here's the stubborn how do we eat this i say we boil it
number two what do you say uh way too messy why don't you just swallow it well i didn't
one gulp that's easier said than done come on booster you can do it open wide my nerves are
shot i feel like i've forgotten to tie my cord before a bungee jump here it comes
so wait wait wait what did the cake just move concentrate sir this doesn't feel right
it's so delicious it's so good it makes me want to cry congratulations sir the wedding is now
officially over thanks everyone it's a wrap let's go i don't know but when i was younger that was
my favorite things they jump over you as they leave it just was so why that was wonderful
mario you're my knight in shining armor finally let's get back oh what a day can you believe it
i almost got married to that thing but i hope someone marries me someday so it's dual princess
of western kingdom has joined the party be sure to bring it back safe i'm sorry wrong game i'm
thinking of chrono trigger you play the organ and the fucking thing opens up right wrong wrong also
awesome best video game ever forgotten chrono cross is better uh that's debatable it is i i would
tend to disagree although there's way more characters in chrono cross the creepy guy just
left does that mean we can go on with our wedding oh razz i'm so happy let's get this wedding over
so we can stay in the suite and then go on our honeymoon let's do it all right you'll have to
excuse us time to get married okay everyone we're gonna start this from the beginning back inside
please i'm supposed to officiate this wedding i forgot that's it good luck i wish you both the
best isn't there like another thing to do here oh here we go is it okay get a little closer
ready one two hey you by the long face this isn't a funeral you know all right i'm gonna be kind of
three say ah did you get it did you get it very cool what is it lip smack like for instance when
you can yeah i'll turn this you get to turn the audio up to you know what i'm saying it's like
this all right let's get back to mushroom kingdom although i see how we're kind of at the halfway
point there's another false side of the overworld there but we still have a little little way to go
am i gonna do mario rpg tomorrow tomorrow the plan is terraria
and depending on how long we do that i may maybe we'll just transition back to play this
let's say we play terraria for like three four five hours and we're like all right that's it
maybe i'll hop back on this for an hour or two or something and you're gonna do the word problems
part of the game with no walkthrough word problems what do you mean word problem
i don't know what you mean mario welcome back you look like you're in one piece
princess i'm finally home and with mario and some wonderful new friends they saved my life
let's go find the chancellor we don't come on mario we mustn't keep the chancellor away
oh i know what you're talking about holy shit i forgot about that that's hell that area is
actual living fucking hell i love that area that's the hardest part of the whole game
that's the only game that actually that's the only part of the game that's a real true challenge
besides maybe the ship and then the last few encounters that is hard very hard
chancellor the princess is back thank goodness this has been a true nightmare i'm a nervous wreck
i know i've worried everyone but i'm fine i can take care of myself with a little help from mario
come everyone let's get out of this drafty door mario i hope you know how thankful we are
but you must tell me one thing how on earth can you trust bowser trust bowser what are you talking
mario what are you doing with what is going on here big gods chancellor listen everyone
relax mario's got things under control mario you brought bowser into the one place where you
have all of his enemies are yes yes i see bowser perhaps this time you told us your story
what exactly did you mean when you said you had bigger fish to fry
can't tell them the truth if this gets out i'm finished excuse me sir perhaps i can set the stage
and the others can add their comments along the way the princess bowser and mario were thrown in
different directions after a terrible explosion something huge crashed through star road high
above bowser's place and went boom where the fuck did mario go there was a gigantic sword now
bowser's keep has been taken over by monsters to work for some creep game smithy they've thrown
me out of my own i mean i decided to take a vacation they can't do this to me
anyway i was working on a plan to get my house back mario walked up to me and begged me to let
him join the koopa troop i had no choice but to let him in it was pathetic that's not what happened
no it's okay mario we know bowser's stretching the truth a little and mallet how about you why
are you traveling with mario well because mario is helping me find my real home and my parents
that's why we're on the road together what this is dreadful news awful horrible
i hope you find your real parents soon and um gino was it why are you and mario
the star road has been destroyed i'm here to fix it mario is helping me search for the star pieces
i need them to rebuild the road star pieces the star road grants our wishes unless we find all
the star pieces and fix the star road we can kiss our dreams goodbye what this is dreadful news
horrible isn't it indeed for example say bowser kidnapped you without the aid of the star road
you'd probably never be rescued actually that sounds pretty good to me let's just forget about
all these star things ah great bowser then you can just kiss your precious keep goodbye hey what
ah let's see mario can't find stars poster will be mine but i won't get my keep back and
wish mario finds a star so if i want to keep back i need a star thing but ah run that past me one
more time just ignore that idiot i just don't think i could take a word without a world without
wishes we need to go and find those star pieces now princess you can't be serious you're not
thinking of joining them are you this is sheer madness you're a princess what will people say
hey i don't care things seem so hopeless right now i'm tired i think i need to go lie down in my
room for a while mario malo gino and bowser you too look wait that's fucking mario now that
thanks to mario the princess is back i now declare this date to be known forever as
hey wait a minute you don't suppose who would have been this smithy who attacked our kingdom
i fear we have no cause to rejoice in fact mario we must ask you for yet another favor
please on behalf of all of us you must defeat smithy it is the only way we shall ever live in
peace again princess told stools home safe but she has decided to stay with him but sorry guys
it ain't gonna be like that please mario take me along with you please don't worry grandma
helped me through this one so no one will ever notice that i'm gone let's find us a star
but i wonder where it could be i have absolutely no idea do you
mario at times like these what should we do we should ask grandpa my grandpa should know
okay then let's do it just as i thought toadstool joins the party once again you want to go see how
how toadstool is uh pretending to be still here grandma thanks for putting up with all my selfish
demands don't worry princess a little invincible do you see the world it makes them friends help
destroy smithy just make sure nobody looks at my face mario's beside me everything's going to be
all right so don't worry you take care grandma you hear i feel like i'm growing younger just
talking with you people i thought you thought that was a skull that's all right i did i've
already found the question mark i did i'm gonna save it i think this is a pretty good stopping
point i'm gonna hang out and do the bits and the subs and stuff how long is the game probably
another another full stream and we'll probably do it it's probably like another seven-ish hours
in the game six to seven hours something like that maybe a little bit more but yeah i i love
this game i hope if you've never played it before then you get to see and enjoy it too
and those of you that have played it before remember how much fun it was
oh wait wait wait wait wait we missed the score up again but there are a lot of little easter eggs
that we have not even seen yet so we'll probably see those well depending on how long we go tomorrow
this felt like a video game play it was awesome yeah sometimes i mean yeah obviously i was doing
like voices and stuff but it's fun just to hang out very comfy for real but i will see you guys
tomorrow we'll keep going after terraria maybe i'll jump back on here for like another couple
hours depending on how it goes but that's where we're gonna end thank you for watching as always
let's get the bits open and go back a little earlier today here we are see you tomorrow if
you're coming back or see you next uh next time whenever you decide to join us again
and thank you to gnarly for the 250 two dollars and 50 cents uh i had this really weird dream
last night you were streaming minecraft in the middle of the day with a bunch of mods installed
there were no jokes gaps or even gaffs or even commentary from you you kind of just kept quiet
occasionally mumbling to yourself you seemed mad at one point there was a jump scare and instead
of reacting with a scream or a laugh you just sighed and muttered god damn it under your breath
i wonder if you were even aware you were streaming i will never i don't think ever have an accidental
stream i go through so many rituals before i press the start streaming button there's no
it would be impossible what do you mean rituals just i just have like rituals like routines that
i do before i start you have any plans to do any other rpgs i think with the voice work it's great
i would love to see some more chill rpg streams yeah i mean chrono trigger is one of them after
i uh the next stream or two of mario rpg i could do that next that's also one of those just
you know greatest game of all time type stuff yeah maybe i if people like this and people
think this is a fun stream and a relaxing chill stream i think it is it's kind of up to you guys
but it seems like this was fun for a lot of people tonight so i mean kind of was testing the waters
tonight so we'll see but thank you too we also had lacronda gave 50 dollars before i was live
yeah lacronda gave 5 000 bits before i turned the stream on holy shit they say i go why isn't
germa streaming yet late streamer and you go live what kind of which are you that's 50 dollar
pre-stream bits and i didn't even know what happened lacronda if you're still here thank you
that's a lot really appreciate it 50 bucks it's time for slime thanks three dollars did you know
super mario was originally going to be called a superb mario until miyamoto convinced nintendo
that they should drop the b from the title really it's gonna be superb mario
miyamoto said convinced president of nintendo to drop the b is this is this is bullshit this
might be both this is bullshit isn't it superb no i'm getting it is it i mean it sounds like it
could be i don't know though he would adore bowser's inside story it has the same kind of
goofy charm not no random encounters that sounds cool why would they make that up i don't know
i guess it's real that's cool hey tingy thanks for the 250 you didn't even last 10 minutes
without swearing this stream i was much more relaxed today look at the stream title hey smelly
boy thanks for the 250 like 15 minutes in and you're still in let's player mode what no i was just
described look i played this game a lot of time so i'm just like really excited to explain and
talk about everything that i'm doing you were explaining the concept of currency
what if you don't know what that is oh my god what the fuck jesus 69 again this is what is this the
fifth fourth fifth sixth time fifth time in the last like two weeks that phylacter lich has given
69 subs this is like the fifth time you've done this maybe more they don't if i liked your lich i
don't remember well regardless that's um that's another 69 subs from phylactery on top of the
hundreds and hundreds of bits worth of dollars that's that's crazy everyone will be a sub soon
yeah sometimes i wonder what some of uh their occupation people's occupations are
i'd be a doctor in that case can you look at that i got this like itchy thing on my back can you
look at it no but for real that's you've given an astronomical amount of money to the channel over
the last month so thank you you are responsible for hundreds of fucking subs you've given hundreds
and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of dollars thank you i still cannot believe that you would
give that many subs there pretty much every single string thanks a lot we also had oh my goodness
where are we over here all right right here may thank you may posting for the five dollars
germa are you gonna try to fight culex during this playthrough yes and also on all your times
playing this game how many times have you got a perfect hit with geno world that's the real
ultimate gamer move as far as i'm concerned i'm not sure i don't know if i i do know like the secret
jokey part but i know i'm not gonna do it i'm not gonna do the joke and those of you guys that know
the geno world meme i'm not gonna do it this playthrough i'm gonna actually beat it right i'm
gonna actually beat it but yes i'm going i'm going to i'm going to beat culex on this playthrough yes
oh no now phylacterlish gave 18 subs to make it so they had 420 gifted subs on the channel
think about that think about how many how many subs that is you're responsible for 420 subscriptions
they have fulfilled their promise of 420 get that is true phylacterly did you did say that before
and you've achieved that a few different ways it's the weed number it's the weed number
i know it's the weed number i know i know what the weed number is and then fly for shy
not to be upstaged fly for shy dropping 20 community subs 20 i want one so bad
you you stick around you you probably get one thank the both of you that's
20 subs and then like 80 something 90 something right from phylactery thank you for the enormous
sub drops something is a sign of weakness stay strong i don't know why i think that's funny
but thank you both of you again hey i don't even like taco bell gave 250 thank you
jerma can you stop doing all the best streams when i have to work i'm sorry the duality of
chat jerma why do you have to do the best streams when i work jerma why do i always
catch your worst streams that happened both of those happened tonight and you know it we
we caught it earlier that's funny just pure duality but um i don't i'm sorry that
you streams that you want to watch are conflicting with your schedule but you can watch the vod the
vod and the chat will exist for at least two months it's not the same i know it's not the same
but it's still something thank you though thank you thank you thank you i don't even like taco
bell also thank you to uh pigeon for the 250 hey jerma again i'm so fucking excited to meet and
hang out with you at twitchcon and i never really got into this game but i played this shit out of
superstar saga what are your thoughts on the mario and luigi games i did i played superstar saga but
not the other ones in the series because there is what two three more after that something like
that i did superstar saga then the dream team or something something like sleeping something
about sleeping they sleep in one of them what's the one where they sleep superstar saga
the time with the moment they sleep bowser's inside story the sleep one is the newest one oh
luigi's dream it is dream team isn't it partners in time bowser's inside story dream team and
paper jam okay so there are quite a few of them but yeah i'll be at twitchcon i'll be poking around
i have no official meeting greets or anything so i'm kind of just going to be just kind of
walking around randomly i don't really do any planned real meeting greets or anything
like we talked about it a few times i kind of just am going to exist there but i have nothing
official i'm probably going to be like in a mustache and shit i'm going to be like i'm one
of those like i like glasses and mustaches i should be like if you find me then you get like
a thumbs up i'm gonna be like glasses mustache grow beard a mustache would be part of the beard
i guess and i guess this is the part in the stream where we get a shitload of community subs because
uh your boy just gave 10 20 20 came in from fly for shy and then almost 100 came in from
file actor elitch and then 10 now from you boy oh my goodness thank you thank you for the subs
thanks for the community subs guys you shock me every fucking day i said i wasn't gonna swear
in the mario streams i forgot how am i ever gonna get that ad friendly stream it's never gonna
happen might as well just forget about it now but uh thank you thank you to uh tramston for the 10
bucks thousand bits from uh tramston mick chicken fund this is for the mick chicken fund
i mean that is good that's at least three mick chickens so and then i'm going to use them for
that i promise thank you to the ten dollars thank you gnarly for the 250 i think it would be cool
to see you play a mario rpg game without prior knowledge of it like bows is inside story a lot
of bows is inside story fans here huh there's a lot of people that say play that one play that one
play is that it's it's really good it's just a really good game okay superstar saga is the
best one geno's in superstar saga a lot of people don't know that gino is actually in that game
weirdly enough it's true inside story was the best one okay i will keep that on all that knowledge
upstairs in the brain hey game watch thanks for the 10 bucks game watch hey jeremy i would meme
but today is my two year sub anniversary i love your stuff since the first raven's cry video and
your streams are consistently the best part of my week here's to another two years raven's cry is
the best worst game i've ever played i you know sometimes you wish you could just memory wipe
yourself and do something again that first experience in raven's cry was so funny it was
so awful but somehow was still worth playing just because you needed to know what was going to
happen next you can't be on that ship with the be brave guy and not play the rest of the game
at least put another few hours in how could you do that how could you get like launched across the
map from an animal or watch like an animal throw what i think that the was wasn't there an animal
throwing rocks at people there was a guy there was a there was like a rock throwing animal that
was whipping rocks people yeah it was it was like a monkey or something right he's just throwing
rocks at i wish that company would make i wanted to make another game please do i hope they made
enough money to make another game i said i really do i truly believe that it was worth playing it
was worth it i don't care how much money it was they probably don't exist anymore though
unfortunately but thank you game watch or game watcher for the 10 bucks here's to another two
years uh erdemius erdemius thanks for the 21 dollars erdemius 21 bucks coming in from erdemius
89 hey streamer it's my 21st birthday on monday and i wanted to thank you for all the years of
top tier content i wanted to know if you had any life advice from a longtime boomer to a new one
thanks well first thank you thanks for the 21 2100 bits happy birthday on monday which is i mean i
don't know if you're eastern time or what what time zone you're in but it might be monday so
happy birthday probably maybe right now but any of any life advice hmm let me think that's pretty
open-ended question i think the best advice that just general life advice i can give is everybody
figures it out eventually some people take longer than others i took a long time to figure it out
but eventually you do figure it out for the most part drink water is a good one too
no that actually is a great piece of general advice um replace at least one or two drinks
a day with a glass of water you are going to exponentially help your entire life i'm when
i was younger i used to just drain mountain dew code reds i didn't drink water when i was younger
i didn't and it's really not good for you i have since pretty much eliminated most of and this is
this is not i'm not going to be like i don't drink soda anymore because it's bad that's what i do
i just don't drink it for every single piece of liquid that goes in my body
i kind of was one of those people for a little while i don't know why you just you just kind of
are you'd go to like restaurants and you'd sit around and people would order oh yeah what
i'm taking my you drink orders what would you what are you having i'll have a coke
i'll have a coke we'll have a coke yeah i'll take a coke i'll take a lemon tea please i don't drink
soda and everyone's like where is the guy that doesn't order the coke but then i would just be
envious like watching everybody drink their cokes and i'm like i kind of i wish i kind of wish i had
one of those
but i drink soda sometimes i'll drink soda just if you know something you just feel like it
that's fine sometimes you just want to have a soda because i feel like it go for it sometimes
you want to eat like three double cheeseburgers from burger king do it i love every second of it
just don't do it every day in fact don't do that like
once a week in fact don't ever do that you shouldn't you should go to you should go to
in and out instead they have much better burgers don't they don't go there either make them at home
this is the voice actor real stream i don't know i really am just like
oh hey i've gone through all of my range this whole stream i'm reaching for new ones too i'm
reaching out to try to find other ones you know when you got to do 50 characters you kind of have
to figure out which ones don't sound alike and that concludes my life advice but thank you
urdemius for the 21 bucks do mickey oh oh donald what are you talking i had i was close it was
really close i had it if i worked on that i could probably do it uh thank you to sai sai chan for
the two four six eight ten twelve fourteen you gave about fifteen dollars here almost twenty
dollars here and they say i'm just posting a bunch to get all the food fight emotes don't mind me
me food fight emotes what are those let me see what who do you get that bite smoothie
bite pop bite fries where do you get these pizza emotes and stuff that's cool hamburgers and
mashed potatoes people just gift you them if someone cheers people get them randomly oh
that's weird cool though well i hope you got them and they said uh this is a good game
they said i know this is a little spammy i'm sorry i'm almost done now you're you're good don't worry
and i don't mind if he doesn't see these messages like i said just getting all the emotes
well you're honest that's good thank you so much uh sai i think it's sai i chan they say enjoy your
20 bucks total thank you i will i'm happy that you decided to give it to me hope you got your
emotes thank you to gray tax for the five dollars durham it's been a while sorry about that this is
not much but i wanted to give you something because you helped you've helped me so much
last month here in the dc area my house burnt down oh my god i'm so sorry i fucking hear that
and uh today i found out that a co-worker that i liked has passed away i've been watching his
dreams a lot and old videos to help cheer me up thank you for everything have a great day
or stream i'm really really sorry to hear all that that sounds like a really really hard fucking time
hopefully that gets completely situated hopefully you're safe number one and anybody else that was
there whoever it was family friends hopefully you're all okay and i'm sorry um for your loss
here losing somebody that you cared about that sounds like a shitload of things to go through
in a small amount of time but thank you gray tax for the five dollars and thank you for
hanging out here i as long as well as everybody else here i'm probably very happy to cheer you up
or anybody for that matter so stay safe stay strong because that's a lot of stuff to go through
i wish you and your family the best i really do have a great day we also had community subs come
into a lot not just the ones that came in very recently here we had otter fiend 10 subs tonight
germa sucks with subs jeff with subs the fax machine with subs we touched upon them but still
it was a lot of community subs tonight i just want to make sure i touch on them again
thank you to paul manifold for the 10 dollars i like gino with a smiley thank you paul manifold
for the thousand bits the 10 dollars they say i'd like gino i do i do too that's the guy from
smash brothers um paul manifold is not in smash brothers no you're talking about gino
he's not and gino isn't either so that's equally as funny
oh you know gino is in smash as a jpg image oh i was seething i was inconsolable because it's
not even new artwork or new model it's just like the png from the back of the fucking super nintendo
box you couldn't have had any new artwork somebody could have drawn them or something commission
anything why does it have to be like the the super nintendo image from like the game informer poster
he's coping right now i am i am gino will never be in smash no he won't absolutely not it's never
gonna happen there's been almost two there's been like 15 years of people demanding that gino is a
playable character in smash brothers and it's never gonna happen they have had like three
opportunities with tons of square involvement yeah paul manifold actually is a higher contender
than gino at this point because all the every bullet point every single it all pointed to
gino was probably going to be in this game that's it unless they do a second season pass
and they just add just just fucking because they add all the characters that everybody's upset
aren't in the game they'll be okay this is the only way this is gonna happen the next few dlc
characters are gonna be big great reveals right season pass two is gonna be like the all right
everybody relax waluigi isaac from golden sun gino they're gonna do if they do that that's what's
gonna that's the only way it's gonna happen isaac is never gonna get a game you delusional idiots
well i was a little nicer with my take on that yeah that was very mean take i'm still holding
up hope the more that like somebody said earlier the more that i say it'll never happen the more
that it maybe would if no it won't no it's not gonna happen at this stage they would rather put
in anybody else it's nice to dream people said banjo would never happen and look how that turned
out yeah but but microsoft has really started to push its kind of collaborative efforts with the
other big three especially nintendo square and nintendo have a a decent relationship i guess
but banjo is one of those characters that is is such a huge beloved rare franchise from the
nintendo 64 era gino was in this game for 12 hours and then you can see him in the background
in superstar saga i think he's a great character i he's a great character he's really interesting
really cool they could have developed him a little more but banjo getting in over gino makes a lot
more sense they do have a gino me skin and it's hurting me nintendo is probably the reason why
they probably haven't done like a gino dlc or something because i have to assume
they're probably scared that they'll release something like that and like 112 people are
going to buy it because it's probably only 112 of us that actually care about this character
you could probably fit us all in an auditorium we we they could be like a gino we love gino convention
and you could fit us all on a school bus i'd be there in my gino hat in my gino shirt my
gino shorts my gino lunchbox and i'd be so fucking raring to go it'd be awesome
but way more people are going to buy the banjo dlc and i know they have the pass right but i'm
talking about like in years prior as well i don't know did they even do a pass for the wii you want
to did you buy could you buy them solo you're underestimating the size i'm just i'm i'm just
i'm taking the piss right now my point is there's a lot fewer people that even know who this person
is versus some of the more currently relevant nintendo or not characters i do love it i think
it's a great character i think malo is a great character i think croco is a great character i
think some characters you haven't even seen yet are great characters too is sans gonna be in smash
i don't i don't think so no i mean i i don't think that would happen he said no so he wants
him in he has insider information nobody tells me anything i don't know shit i am the least
informed person that you probably watch on twitch at least in regard i mean like in regards to like
video game stuff like no no no no i'm talking no i'm not talking about like video game related
news and information this is not i don't have any of that
all right but uh thank you paul manor for it for the 10 dollars i really do love gino as well
uh i look forward i look forward to maining you in uh smash brothers switch 2
hey airless thanks for the 250 jeremy elberton is my favorite broadcaster i think he's all right
jeff putus thanks for the 250 hey germa can you wish my good friend daphne a happy 23rd birthday
yes absolutely happy birthday daphne have a good 23rd birthday jeff says hello happy birthday
make it a good one wait isn't pluto a planet again remember when everyone laughed at me
and talked shit to me and called me all kinds of names when i said that that was gonna happen
everybody remember that everybody remember that happening i do uh one day ago nasa boss
jokingly declares pluto a planet no no no this is the real one is pluto a planet nasa administrator
a nasa administrator may reignite the argument hold on i'm gonna read this whole fucking thing
strap in for this one in 2006 the international astronomical union caused consternation when
it declared that pluto was no longer a planet several bodies of similar size had been found
in the cupra belt so the iau created a definition that included the criterion that a planet must
clear the neighborhood around its orbit which pluto does not pluto was reclassified as a
dwarf planet a dwarf planet a dwarf planet in a move which upset anyone who grew up learning
about a solar system consisting of nine planets now nasa administrator jim brutenstein has
reignited the fierce debate of a pluto status by unexpectedly coming out in favor of it being a
planet just so you know in my view pluto is a planet he said in a tongue-in-cheek clip posted
to twitter you can write that the nasa administrator declared pluto a planet once again i'm sticking by
that it's the way i learned it i'm committed to it sorry link the article just type just
uh you know how easy this article is to find just type in pluto planet is in fucking google
it's everywhere you got it guys there's a debate right now between is pluto a planet or not
a dwarf planet is a dwarf okay hold on is it remember when i said pluto is a planet and
everyone's like it's not a planet what is it what does it come at what comes after dwarf
it starts with a p i don't know what that what is it what's the word it comes after dwarf p
something it's a land lanet planet a planet a dwarf planet but it's not a planet though but
it just gets called a dwarf planet so what is it then a broadcaster oh fuck off that's that's
purge worthy that's purge worthy for me that's it that's purge worthy the dwarf planet it's a
planet all the moons are jupiter of jupiter are planets too no because they're moons they're not
dwarf planets hey thank you for odin weapon for the 250 i gotta say it's fun hearing all your
different voices for the dialogue quite the impressive range thank you thank you thank
you man boy for the three dolls how about some director's commentary what do i mean director's
commentary super mario rpg my favorite game of all time this is a nine minute video oh no i'm not
linking this i'm not going to be the one that links us this is like peak this is like peak
youtuber voice this is peak youtuber voice jeremy hey everybody welcome back to enlighten where i
talk about one of my favorite games of all time yeah this is this is peak tuber voice
you find just type in fucking tuber voice germa mario german super mario rpg favorite game of
all time all right you know what fucking here you go just take just here take it don't watch that
if you do tell me the comments how you feel about it uh errorless gave 250 as well and they say
please don't delete this it's autos big adventure 2 i'm not going to delete autos big adventure 2
i actually have grown to love that video critical chaos thanks for the 10 bucks
10 dolls from critical chaos thanks for being funny you never failed to make me laugh thank you
for the 10 dolls i'm happy you think that i'm happy that you can have fun thank you so much
critical chaos wiki this thanks for three bucks friendship with malo has ended bowser is our new
best friend until we potentially replace bowser with peach i'm not sure i usually do mario bowser
gino it's what i've done every single time so it might be time to change it up
maybe we throw peach in there maybe i've replaced gino for the first time ever
that would be bad i don't know if i can handle that i don't think i could do that
i don't know hey sir canine thanks for the five dollars hey germa it's kevin's mom from connect
sports how have you been since you gave my son permanent okay they're talking about like the
boxing when i see you're streaming now i hope that's going well for you remember han solo that was
the last song kevin heard thank you sir canine for the five dollars they end this with good job
you hey shit thank you for the five dollars hey shit what was that though i couldn't pay that
much attention to it hey shit what was that uh thank you superintendent charles for the 250
joel has come across those sims 4 mods i hope that i hope that he has a lot of fun
those are the best mods ever hey shit but what you one guy called you hey shit and you read it out
loud but what was there anything to it or was it just hey shit no hey shit i love that uh joel
was playing this right now all right we're gonna we're gonna have to raid joel because if they're
doing a sims 4 of like fucking horror house you guys are probably really like that so but thank
you superintendent charles chalmers thank you abomination zero for the four dollars
obligatory i give you money joke thanks for the money hey errorless thanks for the 250 i loved
this game as a kid and was great seeing it again thanks you'll probably see it again really soon
because now that it's started i would like to finish it way sooner rather than later
dr clay thanks for the five dollars here total super mario rpg it is the only one for just me
when i play the game i get lost in a phase then i find out i'm stuck in geno's maze
it is tough especially when you don't know what you're doing but i do i do and they say i don't
know about you but i would love to see an hd remaster of this game not to say the original
isn't awesome but seeing these graphics in full hd would be amazing especially if the original
renders were used i would love that and i would also love a actual super mario rpg too that would
be great they were going to do it but they canned it i don't know why problems for some reason but
let's get the credits rolling we only have a few more bits to do so let's get those credits on
screen this is going to be a lot of subs on this list considering the amount of community subs
that were given over the last 30 to 40 minutes was it going to be a sneak peek of the carnival
tonight or did i dream that oh it's because it's like you that's going pretty fast uh i already
did the carnival that was just a joke i was making because they said like if you're good then you get
something special and i said that like yesterday so i did it last night i did and i'm incredibly
excited for it i'm almost cannot contain myself did the carnival stream happen though it's happening
on the 21st of september so in just about three weeks is everyone going to be the same or subs
going to have access to special stuff everyone is going to be on the same playing field completely
but we had uh we had 10 dollars from ahahua ahahua ahahua i think i'm saying that right it's ahahua
i'm doing it right thank you for the 10 bucks they say best streamer been watching for seven
years your tft youtube videos still haven't gotten stale thank you for the years of entertainment
thank you for the years of your attention seven years is a long time to continue to still think
that the things i say and do are interesting so thanks for hanging around for that long thank you
the 10 bucks even live for seven hours you should have consumed a bunch of water yeah i've refilled
it a few times i'm good but thank you for the 10 bucks appreciate it all of you thanks for 250 can
i get an f in the chat for my frogs that died recently no idea how or why and my week is ruined
i'm really sorry to hear that rest in peace to your frogs i'm sure they were great great great
pets i love frogs i love frogs of toads back in massachusetts when it was a lot it was a lot
wetter they were frogs and toads everywhere just randomly in the grass every time you'd see a toad
or frog it would just be like oh yes and walk over and just look at them and they would just be
staring up just like hanging out they're cute and they eat a shitload of bugs so they're awesome
the amount of frog the amount of bugs that the mosquitoes and flies that frogs and toads eat
they're helping you out they're taking care of you you just don't know it but thank you all mew and
again i'm really sorry to hear about your frogs take care thank you oh chase for the 10 dollars
love you germ can i pm you i do not have open pms i don't unless i'm in the discord and i do
this because i found over the years that it's impossible to keep up with i used to have like
steam friends and steam open and it can i could be added but it's just it's i'll be honest it's
just kind of too much for me to handle and when i actually am streaming and i actually and after
the streams and before streams i would rather focus on making content making streams hanging out
i don't really have a whole lot of time to have like open pms and just kind of talk to people
i do show up in the discord all the time or in pre-stream chat i'll hang out here for a couple
hours i was here um two days ago i was in the chat for about two three hours just hanging out
when i wasn't feeling good but if there is something that you want to get across to me
i you and it's something important right and i would put i would say important as in you know
use your you know common sense and due diligence to know what like would be important um then there
are mods that you could ping in pm and they can get the messages to me but it also kind of that
same type of uh way of thinking the same reason why i don't do um like reading bits and subs on
stream anymore i mean obviously we hang out for like an hour or so at the end of streams
but when i'm like in when i'm in like the mode to stream and hang out and talk and do all this stuff
that's what i want to do so you don't have any nudes nudes uh no but no i don't the to kind of
end that whole thing i don't do like open pms i don't really i the only way that i really reach
out to like the collective community is through discord and hanging out in the general or in
pre-stream unless if you want if you need to ping a mod about something that's something that you
think is important then we could figure it out but thank you do appreciate it thank you for the
ten dollars thank you thank you thank you do i yeah do i browse my own subreddit i do not all
the time but i do check in from time to time to see what what they're doing over there i check
you know sometimes i just want to know you need to know what people are saying
he needs when he needs an ego boost no uh thank you snoozing coffin for the 250 hey i'm going to
dallas for a month it's pretty exciting because it'll be the longest time i'll be on my own
pretty much i've only been on a plane twice i'm still anxious about planes you fly a lot now don't
you to la or california and back how do you deal with that were you never scared about it or did
you just normalize it with time and it will be exciting in a different time zone closer to the
normal stream times too i've flown on enough planes where it's just it's it's just a car
that goes in the air it's a very loud car yes flying flying used to make me nervous until i
realized and i thought about there are people that fly three four five six plus times a week
every week and they just kind of get on and get off get on get off go about their regular day
so the one time that i would be flying be like gosh i really don't want to get on a plane there's
a guy walking by me with a briefcase that that's his like six is sixth or seventh plane ride today
and i'm just like oh why is he seems like he's everything everything's cool all right this yeah
this is easy then the one thing i can't do is i can't sleep on planes no matter how much i try
does i could be the most exhausted in my entire life i could stay awake for two or three straight
days and i would not be able to sleep on the plane those are actors the guy walking around
with the briefcase in the airport is not he's just doing that because he wants people to think he's
a businessman that's what he does on his days off he just i'm gonna okay it's my day off
i'm gonna put a bunch of blank computer paper in a briefcase and like shuffle the papers around at
the terminal and like check my watch open up a laptop and look at it close it and then i
feels pretty good no they get paid to do that no why would anybody be paid to do that
he's honored by the airport to just be a guy how many of these guys are there they what they just
have like a hundred fake business people having an illusion of people traveling it's so people
like you don't get scared by planes so what about the people on the plane
if there's like two or three hundred people on that plane is like only four people that actually
bought a ticket first class is a scam to make you think you're getting a good a cheap ticket
so what all the people in first class it's not real and they're like oh those are like a thousand
dollars a seat but they're not actually used so oh good thing i'm not sitting that has two more
crazy mine was only 342 what a shitty fucking imagine having to like imagine having to sit
on an airplane and you're not even working you're not doing anything like flight attendants for
instance right they fly every day multiple times a day but they are they're they're they're working
they are at the drinks talking to passengers they're doing through safety protocols they're
in contact with the work crews in the luggage imagine if like you just sat in the seat and you
didn't you didn't do anything i would not be able to do that job what about an air marshal you have
an air marshal has like a specific they're like a specific task they're like security your job
is to just be on the airplane with an ipad in your hand i think i would lose my mind
you just get to watch movies on the airplane but yeah but you but that's just bring a d i guess
you could just bring a ds and just play the ds or like warcraft or something but but then the the
jig is up because wouldn't everybody do that if you were a career pretend in the airplane actor
they're all gonna have wow accounts and you're gonna look around as the one person that bought
the ticket and it's gonna be like 60 laptops people are gonna be playing wow in the same server
you're gonna know who that you you're sitting next to you're gonna have your own like in crew wow
server it's gonna look strange when you're like wait a minute i just want to get to go to the
bathroom and all these people in this strange all these people on this plane are in the same
molten core raid that's kind of odd is it is there a gaming convention going on
like where i'm going i've played mario kart ds multiplayer on airplanes with people well we
found the actor how is it is it fun all right all right all right but no planes i i take i take
planes all the time they can be stressful when they're long and when you can't really sleep
but you do get to go across ridiculous amounts of land and sea like five thousand times faster
than you would normally so it's kind of it's it's worth it to you know gotta go through security
you gotta go do all this you gotta sit on the plane who are you sitting with do you how big is
your seat oh fuck i'm like gotta go to the bathroom however long it is usually i anything less than
like three to six hours for me is i can completely handle totally fine i just wish i could sleep
they just changed the sets outside the airplane and it takes a couple hours
so what you're adding on top of this saying that you're not actually leaving the plane what does
plane take you so everyone gets in there there's like 150 actors and there's three people that
bought a ticket and they put up a gremlins to pretend outside scenery they make some noise
and then but how do you explain where you end up is that just down the street is that like the
truman show where we have like two miles of actual livable earth the entire the entire airport is
moving like a floating disk island you never wonder why all the trees look the same that is true why
the fuck do all trees look why are all trees the same you might be on to something here
you just go on an elevator so wait you got like seven layers of hell you just go in an elevator
you go to like layer one and that's like what like simpson addy layer two is like i don't know boston
new york layer three which is like in different layers of the crust just different classic wow
layers i love this it's so stupid all right let's get out here birds aren't real either
all right i'm done oh we gotta move on i'm going to bed thank you wolfgang for the five dollars
say you should have gone for the head in mickey mouse oh you should have gone for the head don't
why did i do that why is it always donald anybody listen tell somebody it doesn't matter who it is
to do a mickey mouse impression they're going to go i don't think i can do that
i'm not sure and you go no no no just give it a try they're always going to end whatever they say
with donald donald donald and they always start with a laugh yeah they always go like
oh it's no it's it's it's all right bye thank you future game for the 250 my uh family has a
water cooler in their house and it's amazing i have a liter bottle i constantly fill it up with
that's awesome some services ship water in gallon jugs but walmart also has machines that you can
use to refill jugs for really cheap that also saves on plastic from not using water bottles
i really recommend chat get one great fucking idea i'm gonna get one of those
let's go raid uh joel okay goodbye i'll see you tomorrow terraria
and uh how about long we do that maybe some more mario rpg to close out the night all right i'll
see you guys tomorrow take care see you later go say hello joel they're playing the sims for
modded see you later now i have to spell their name correctly because uh i always fucked this up
wait joel is ending the stream joel is ending the stream
oh soon at any well i i already like pressed the button all right go say good night say good night
all right hurry up i'll see you later bye quickly before i just i before i runs out
see you tomorrow goodbye tell them to send you somewhere else