Hey, whoa, what's going on? Why are you so much faster than me? Oh, you said run like double tap W. Oh, I was gonna say this doesn't make any sense.
Hey, what's going on everybody? It's Jerma here and MLC Stealth. Hey guys.
Today, timed chaos build like you know it. Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the show.
We are going to be building something very, very, very special today. Going to be building a burger meal.
And what that consists of is what MLC Stealth, explain to the audience.
Well, you know, if you go to McDonald's order number one, you get yourself a cheeseburger, yourself a Coke, you get yourself some fries.
That's what we're going to be building today. Those three items. Hell yeah. Burger fries and Coca-Cola classic.
Oh, you know what? Dr. Pepper. How about that? So we got six.
Do you not like Dr. Pepper? Are we about to be really mad at you? I don't want to get hate.
All right, let's let's get started. Got six minutes to build a burger, fries and a soda.
So here we go. Ready? Are you ready? I'm ready.
Three, two, one. Burgers. Let's do it. All right. So I'll start with the soda.
Oh, we're going to be doing we're doing separate things. OK. Well, we don't have to.
No, that's all right. No, that's a good that's a good plan.
OK, I just tried making a circle. I don't know. Hold on. What on earth is this?
That's like a that's like a space invader.
A nice cup.
I don't know. How do you make rounded edges in Minecraft?
I don't know. Like this. All right. This burger is way too long.
Bring it up. Bring it up. Go, go, go, go, go, go.
This is going to take probably longer than like six minutes to build this.
Just like a red tower. All right. Oh, I'm building this upside down.
What? OK, we need the meat, the meat. All right. Big cheeseburger.
There's no way I can make a drink big enough.
You have to make it. You have to make it. Oh, nice.
Like burnt meat we're using, by the way.
Mike, that's like a pancake. That's not a cheeseburger.
No, it isn't. Just wait. It will be. Look how big that is.
Hey, they left it on the grill for way too long. All right.
It's not their fault. Yeah, they did. Not only that.
This is like leaving the burger on all day.
Somebody went to like take a poop.
He realized he was still making a cheeseburger and like, oh, jeez.
Oh, yeah. This is what happens when you leave a burger on the grill for an hour and 45 minutes.
Oh, it's like the time. Oh, it's getting dark.
No, it's not the command.
I forget the I forget the command already.
All right. Hold on. Let's see. Cheese.
She's got to go. She's got to like overlap a little bit.
It'll be like melting over the sides. Two minutes.
Oh, we got to hurry up, man.
Go, go, go. This cheese is way too big.
Help me with the burger. Forget the fries.
If someone was lactose intolerant, they would die.
No, this is no. Hold on. This is way too big.
What is this?
Dude, this is the worst trick.
What?
It needs to be tower with a straw in it. That's like what I was supposed to do.
It looks I don't even know what this looks like.
This looks like a juice box.
All right. Let's go. Go, go.
Here it is. Finish it.
Oh, you're making the fry box. Good for you. Good for you.
We're making like awkward team hunger force here.
We really are. Fry lock. Come on.
I got this. I don't think you're even going to be able to see the meat on this thing.
Yeah. This much cheese on a burger.
I would I would spit it out.
Oh, man. That is way too much cheese.
All right. Three minutes have gone by.
Three pieces of cheese.
Just like grab one piece and he just like grabbed whatever.
He took like he took like three quarters of the stack.
All right. Tomato. Tomato slice.
Tomato slice doesn't have to be that big.
All right. That's a good tomato slice. No, it needs to be a little higher.
It's going to be like a stacked up burger.
I keep on like miss clicking.
It's still not day, by the way.
Oh, I didn't do slash. That's why it's slash time.
No time for that.
All right. There's a lettuce.
Lettuce is going to go right here.
Lettuce is going to come out a little bit.
Nice fries. Nice golden fries.
These are like the fries that you get at a buffet.
You can see like the wrinkles. OK.
This this does not look anything like a burger at all.
Why in the world is everything like so lopsided?
Because the guy threw it together.
Did you hear? Oh, man.
The guy was drunk when he made this.
There's going to be more fries than that fry.
They're deeper inside. What are you talking about?
I'm not going to be able to finish this.
Get over here and finish this with me.
Oh, my God.
This is like a maze. This isn't even a burger.
This is a maze. This is a labyrinth.
Help me. Help me. We only have like one minute.
We have like a minute and 20 seconds.
All right. I'm coming.
What is this?
Help me finish the lettuce.
Oh, no. I'm freaking out.
You're just throwing rain into a can.
Oh, no.
This is a piece of lettuce. This is the whole cabbage.
Dude, it's only one minute.
I can't get up there. I'm stuck.
Oh, we got to finish this.
I made it way too big.
This is the least bun sandwich I've ever seen.
Look how tiny that bun is.
Compared to everything else that is this huge.
The guy that made this was shit-faced.
He just grabbed every ingredient he could find
and just threw it together.
This isn't even a hamburger.
This is like the ingredients of a hamburger.
30 seconds. We need the bun.
20 seconds.
Just build a tiny little bun.
That's good. Now finish it.
No. All right.
10 seconds.
Oh, no. This is bad.
This is really bad.
Five, four, three, two, one.
That's it.
This is the worst one we've ever done.
You're not even going to be able to hold on?
Do you know how you take a bite and you get bun?
You're going to have one bite of bun in that.
Oh, hey. Nice electrical socket you built over here.
Oh, man.
Oh, man. This is bad.
Well, anyways, that's a great burger.
Way too much lettuce.
We don't have any rounded edges.
That's because I don't know how to do round.
Actually, the drink does look like a juice box,
but I think it's the best thing out of all three items,
to be honest.
The easiest to do. A rectangle.
All right, so out of these three things,
I would probably want to drink the drink
and throw this in the trash.
Let me like...
Okay, it's time. Set the day. Here we go.
Now we can see. Nice.
Nice sandcastle we have.
My goodness.
Okay, so for those of you watching,
this is the cheese right here.
Oops, oops, oops. This is the cheese.
This is the burger right here.
Look at how un-proportional this is.
Is that a tomato?
That tomato has been...
Somebody just took the whole tomato
and just put it in between the buns.
Imagine taking a bite of that burger.
Yeah, like I said, you would spit it out.
So juicy.
With the whole tomato in there.
Wow, that is bad.
This is real bad. So anyways, give this a rating.
And let us know. Name this meal.
And yeah, it's a burger meal, guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
Really do appreciate it.
And hopefully somebody eats this.
But take care, everybody.
See you soon.
And goodbye.