Don't let him. Don't let him get away with this. Don't let him get away. He's not here. He was
here 45 seconds after he said he was gonna be. Don't let him get away with this. Controller.
Hi everybody. Can't get away with it. Welcome back to another unfilled few days coming up here.
Move some stuff. Did that tweet go through? Did you see it? What's wrong with my audio?
Uh, what's wrong? What's wrong with your audio? Go in the back of your speakers and grab that
little cord that connects to your headphones or whatever and just you'll get it. This is not like
an AM radio station but man it might work. Touch that dial now. Where's the baking stream? Uh,
Friday. Easy Bake Oven Stream is Friday. Green Screen DLC for free is Saturday. What's wrong
with your face? I don't know. Nothing. It's perfect. Just the way that God made me.
Okay? God gave me this big bump in my nose and that's the way that he created me. Don't blame
that shit on God. And then all of a sudden I get interrupted. Excuse me. No, no. That's not how it
happened actually. I gave you a perfectly sculpted nose and you broke it on a trampoline. You jumped
on a trampoline and landed on your back and your knees came back and hit you in the face
and broke your nose. I was perfect. That's kind of what happened actually. Real story. Add it to
the wiki. I could say anything and you guys would add it to the wiki? Okay. How about um, I was,
okay, I was born with an extra pair of hands. I had 20 fingers. Okay. That's all that. I was
gonna put it on there. We knew that already. It's already there. It's just there already.
Now we're gonna play Saw today. I know people, we were in the pre-stream chat talking about this
and it was like, what are we gonna do today? It was a one-guy opportunity but I didn't see
any that I didn't want to, I didn't take any one-guy opportunity of. Does this game suck?
That's, that's my question. We got the illusion of choice. No, you got the reality of suggestion.
I will take your suggestions but that doesn't mean I'm gonna do them. Hurry up and stream the
fucking game. It's been four minutes. I'm just, I am one of the only people on this website and
I'm gonna, I'm gonna toot my own horn. I'm one of the only damn people on this website that starts
their stream within like five minutes of pressing the fucking button, okay? So give me a little bit
of that slack. I deserve it. I deserve that and I just got a bunch of money. Holy shit. I deserve it.
No, but for real, I may, I may start my streams late but when I turn, when I hit that fucking
button, we go within five minutes. I know a lot of people on this website give you like a 20 to 30
minute window at the beginning where they turn their streams on. Like some people have like a
15, 20, 30, 40 minute intro and that's how they run their business. But I run my business, you know,
with wrappers open and ice cream half eaten and shit. The prices are very low. Uh, Freddy gave 50
subs. 50 community subs from Freddy Dredd. Freddy's back again. Derma sucks lol. What the fuck?
I seriously wonder what would happen in this community. If you don't, we're gonna do an
experiment one day. I'm not gonna tell you when, but I'm gonna, I'm gonna see. I'm gonna have a
starting soon screen that has like a 25 minute countdown. I wonder how many of you guys would,
at like the 18 minute mark, I'm just gonna crack and be like, where is he? Where is he? Get up!
Give me the stream. I'd crack at 28. Yeah, you'd crack at the one minute mark. Roast him. Roast him.
Roast him. Why am I, don't roast me. What did I do? But Freddy, seriously, that's another fucking
50 community subs. It's insane. What do you say we get started? Hey, it's been, it's been exactly
seven minutes since I've pressed the stream button. And uh, what was that? Oh look, right here, right
here. I'm ready. Okay, here we go. New game, let's go. I don't know who, wait, what is this?
Why are you linking me to this? I don't know who Derma95 is and thanks to this game, I never want
to know. Oh, uh, Space Form Derma Slots is a slots game, like the strip slot son, what?
Midi game, ignore it. Yeah, whatever. Well, what do you want me to do? This is, if somebody has an
opinion on something, whatever. You can't expect every person that ever, well, hold on a minute,
this person doesn't understand every single reference that's ever been made on this stream?
He has not had the countless amount of experiences that we've had. I'm just like a,
I'm just a dickhead on his stream, uh, his steam recommended list. Like imagine seeing that Derma
Life is Pain face and clicking on that and being like, who is this fucking person? I don't give a
shit about this guy. What do you want me to do? It's whatever. It's, you can't have people like
just every single ever experience that I ever have with another person online. He's gonna,
somebody's not going to be happy. It's fine. It's all right. Just wait till they see this,
when they see the shpee video and I guarantee you, they'll be fucking, they'll be on board.
Where's the, where's the scary game? Scary cam? No, no, I'm not doing, there's no, but this is not
a scary game. Like the audio settings, let's run with the audio setting. Is that like, give me an A,
give me a B. What's that spell? This is like a, what should I do? Which one of these,
I already like put, I just come in and I go like this and then I start the game.
Let him out. Help him. I don't know where he is. It's me. I think it's me. This is fine. No,
I hate, I don't want the music. Five. All right. You guys ready? Wait, I have to one, two, three,
four, five. One, two, three, four, five. Hold on. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen. Is it synced? One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten. Is it synced? Good. You should be seeing it. Okay. We're good.
All right. Let's go. This game's, I'm not, this game, we're going to be done in probably like 10
minutes. Normal or insane mode? I don't want to play this game on insane. Why would I pick insane?
No, we're doing some fucking, we're doing some normal. Some clues are revealed in the dark.
$50, $100. Holy shit. Hold on. Every choice has a consequence. Wait, there's consequences? Is
this like a bad, is this like a gory game? It's a telltale game. It's Saw. Yeah, but it's
Saw the video game. That doesn't follow the movies. Like SpongeBob Battle for the Bikini
Bottom was not based on a SpongeBob episode. They just made a game. Wait, this does happen
in the movie. Looks like this is keyed in. Okay. So get the key that's in your eyeball.
Here's what happens. Whoa. It's waiting for one of these times that he like kind of
forgets the key. He's just sitting right on the table. He's watching. He's like, oh shit.
Oh wow. There's like 40 more people in other rooms. I'm doing it. Left stick.
Wait, do I have a key? Wait, what am I supposed to be doing? Press B. Oh, I pressed B.
It's a QTE. I don't have an Xbox controller, man. What the fuck?
Escape the bathroom. There it is. Okay. Wait, should I look at the things in the ground? What's
that? Have you a health bar in this game? What are you fucking even doing this game? Wait.
One, three. I just figured out a puzzle. One, three, four. Okay. I just didn't even mean to do that.
Wait, no. Four, one, four, three. What is this? This isn't doing something else. What is this
doing? Four, three. Why is it doing this? Four, three, seven. Four, three, seven. Okay. Four,
three, seven. That's a puzzle. He definitely rushed this one. Like this game, I guess it takes place
after Jigsaw went public and now he's got to keep his like share prices up and he's
got to continuously grow and shit and you got to get like, it's got to be 100 people a day.
Also, this can't be fucking that good. Find Jigsaw's next clue. This game suck. Wait,
I just went in here. Oh, detective. Turns out you're a fucking idiot. You went back in the
room that you escaped from. This is an ugly screen. Anyone out there? Help. Oh, no. That's
my room. All right. Hold on. I've got to look for achievements. What just happened? Co-op.
That's easy. You just gave me the solution. Well, what is his task? You have to dig through
needles. You have to stand there and be scared. What do you mean teamwork? Well, which one is it?
Do we have a timer? We have a timer. One hour and two. We've got an hour and 20 minutes, man. Just
relax. Wait, it's okay. Hold on. You are trapped. Search the toilet for the fuse before you pass out
from pain. What? What do you mean? Then use the fuse on the fuse box to power the door. Press the
green button to open the door. How do I search the grab? What the fuck? Did I get it? You know,
I got it. You have a fuse. You can use it to activate a fuse box. Turning on a fuse box will
power a door. Turn on lights or even create a deadly electrical trap for your enemies.
Once the electricity is on, watch out for nearby puddles of water.
Okay, I did it. Why are there enemies? Classifies as an enemy in a saw game.
All right, we're good. Come open the door. That was a record time. Wow, that was a good guess.
You have bare feet. Certain hazards in the environment will injure you like a broken
glass ahead. Okay. So I climb on box. Like just jump to that and climb on it and just shimmy over
there or just lie on your back and just earthworm backwards slowly. That work? Why can't I just
jump on that? Do like cats do? Wait, that didn't even hurt. It's not really a hazard then. Okay,
just to be aware of that. I'm gonna step in that all fucking day. All right, what's in here? Do I
need to do anything or does it not matter? This door is sealed, right? This is just a game where
you do QTEs and like watch people get their heads ripped off and shit. Health hypo. Okay. Press and
hold X to use a health hypodermic. These will restore your health. The longer you hold down X,
the more health will be restored. Okay. Cool. Thanks. Let there be light. Press Y to turn on
your light. Right now you have a lighter. Other light sources can be found and each is unique.
First of all, hold on a minute. I got $100 from Pluto passing by and then $50 from Koike. So I
want to make sure I address that because there's a lot of fucking money. Pluto passing by gave
10,000 bits, a hundred fucking dollars. Jeremy, it's my 21st birthday today. Here's some birthday
bits. Thanks for making me laugh. Love you and chat. Thanks for the hundred fucking dollars.
No, no birthday face cam. I'm sorry. It's not gonna happen. Happy 21st milestone for you living
in America. Nice job. Nice job. Nice job. What am I? What do I mean? Nice job. Nice job on
getting there, I guess. What do you mean? Nice job. Like he didn't turn in his paper early.
Oh, wow. You turned in your thesis like two days early. Nice job. Nice work. I mean, still,
Jeremy, you still got it. Oh, I wanted to talk about this. This fucking reminds me.
I actually was looking at my degree the other day. And in the in the I was going through some
personal files that I had to I wanted to get situated because obviously I moved.
And I got my full every class I've ever taken in every grade I've ever gotten in college.
And you want to know something funny? I got an F in pickleball. I swear I got a fucking F and
poke. I don't even know how I could prove it. I could. I have the document. I got a file. I
got an F. I don't know how. How do you get an F in pickleball? What do I do? I just not go.
I have no idea. We could go all of my grades. I got like an F in like a media class. I don't
even know how I got like a D my one of my GPA was. All right. This is important. I know I got a game
to play. What do you guys think my cumulative cumulative whatever that fucking hard to say
word is? What's my what was my GPA? What was it over the course of the whole time I was in college?
Since it's lower than four. I can tell you that it's lower than three. I can tell you that it is
higher than two and is lower than three. One point eight. You can't I don't think you can even
graduate with like a one point five. Right. Two point six. You got it. Two six. I don't even know
what that is. That's like a C. Right. Like a C plus something like that. But because I would get
A's in some classes and then I would get F's in classes that I just didn't give a shit about.
It's bad. I know. Like I was either I was either I got it like an A minus or an F.
So it evened out over the years. I got a I got a light. But anyways thanks for the hundred fucking
bucks. Also Goiki thanks for the fifty dollars. Jeremy hello again. I'm excited for this game
because I like the movie even though it's shit. All of chat saying this game is shit too but I
don't care. I'm excited. Me too. You should be. I got an F in pickleball. I'm trying to go through
my brain as to where why and how that happened. That was supposed to scare me but it was too late.
That's supposed to fall when I first walk over here. But I don't say anything.
But I have a key. I have the key. Here we go. It's gonna be another door closed. You don't walk in
this room. You know what you do here. You just stand right here and you peek in the room to
trigger the infrared beam that triggers when somebody comes in to try to close the door.
Peek in. Get the fuck out. And the door will slam. Bolt it shut. Wait what. Okay well oh yeah.
Why can you do this? All right go on.
Uh oh. You know how much of a pain in the ass it would be to have these
old TVs. Why do they have to be fucking old TVs? That's one thing I don't understand about how our
movies officially saw. Why isn't there like a flat screen back there? They're cheaper. You know how
hard. You know how expensive this probably is to get to work. Like this shit wasn't like this
like three days ago. He came down and like put a bunch of trash down here and like painted blood
on the walls and stuff. It wasn't like this down here. This is a huge project. Will you appreciate
your life? Sure. It's his craft. Wait what. Is this a game where I'm gonna get chased by a monster?
It's not right? Uh somebody else will read this. Construction has completed on Whitehurst. Asylum
for the insane. We've finally done it. I'm told all the staff has it at nauseam and somebody
else will read this. Actually it's not that long. It's okay. I think we can make a real difference
here. Whatever somebody will read this. I can't. How do I really get chased around? How many of
these things exist? You don't do this by yourself. One guy in his like 70s is supposed to be
able to do this. This is like a two to three hundred person project. Find the key to his
search the body. Saved a woman in the surgical theater. Okay. All right. Read file. Read the
puzzle pieces. Oh sorry. Nothing personal. I'd grab something quick though if I was you.
What are you talking about? You don't say sorry and then do it again.
Do I have my arm going? He hit my arm off. He took my arm off with a swing of the bat.
Combat stance. Hold the left trigger to enter combat stance with either your fist or a weapon.
Press A for a light attack and X for okay. A and X. Block with the B button. Okay.
Fucking hit him. Put the lighter down. Are you fucking serious dude? How did you miss? You missed?
How are you a detective? He punched through it. You can't block a fucking. Swing. Swing. Swing.
Oh my god. That's like scripted. Wait. Huh? What do you mean?
Did I not make it? Wait. Are you serious?
There was no autosave anywhere from that point forward. Okay. No way. What? No checkpoint?
All right. I'm gonna. Let's go. I gotta play this game. You think I'm not gonna fucking play this
game? I can't believe there's no fucking save. X. Come on. Hurry up.
It was four, three, seven. We don't even need to listen. Imagine. Oh detective. It's time for you
to play again. I got the door open. Wait. I. How did you do that? Not done being scary. Yep. Yep.
Yep. I know. Help. Somebody help me. Holy shit. What happened? Dude. I know. All right. Get up.
What does give up do? I wonder. Put it in. Put it in. I think that's locked until one minute.
You can't beat that within the minute. It's locked until exactly one minute.
Don't walk on it. Fuck. Whatever. I'm strong. Okay. We're good. Take it all.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Hold X. It's dark in here. If we get up quickly, this just happens.
Because yeah. This is guy. Scary. We don't even need to watch this. We already watched it.
Who cares what I mean? You know, we kind of, well, let's might as well. I get that. Okay. Don't
fucking lose here. I don't care. I still, that's a loud TV. Save. What do you mean save? Where?
How do I save? There is no save. What are you talking about? Save. It's too early to save.
Okay. Yep. Yeah. There you are. I'm going to save you. All right. Here we go. This is sealed. Wait,
is this timed when this actually, did I miss a trigger point here? Did I not look down here?
Did I go too fast? Did I break the game because the TV kept playing? I didn't, right? Now that
this door is sealed, there's no way. It's probably timed. You went too, I went too fast. I did. No,
I didn't. What the fuck did I just do? Did I just take a heal? She's dead. I stopped doing drugs.
Wait, audio tape. Oh, come on. All right. Let's go. Where is he? All right. Press A for a light
attack and X for a heavy attack. Block with B. Counter attack. What? He's got me cornered.
Dude, this game doesn't make any sense. Attack. Attack. A. A. I am holding the trigger. It takes
so long to cue up a swing. That was before you realized there was a bomb in your brain
that only would activate if you said that you were going to leave
on a twist, on a twist, just like all the other ones we do.
Many of you are, somebody will read this. Wait, find detective David Tapp. I've concealed a key
inside his body. Wait, many of you will want, hold on. I can do better than this. I can do better.
All right. Let's go in here. Door's sealed. All right. Let's heal. That was completely
incomprehensible. All right. I got the door open. Save. When does this game auto save?
I'm just walking on fucking glass. God damn it. Is there more glass? Shotgun doors. Jigsaw has
booby trap doors in the asylum. Quickly press the appropriate button as the bullet descends.
If you press the wrong button or fail to press the right button, you will be on the receiving end
of a shotgun blast. Oh, great. Can I go in? Some locked doors can be picked with items around the
world or unlock. I need a pin. I need a screw. I don't want to go in here. Wait, isn't there a lady?
What the hell was that?
I can't understand. Too much. Too much. Hold on. Let me monitor. Let me hold on. What does it sound
like? Repeat that. How bad is it? I know I was like kind of having a funny little joke there, but like
let's see. This is really bad. It's just like a cell phone dropped call. You can't even hear
fucking anything. Hold on. This is, no, this just sounds weird. This just makes me sound like,
you know, here's the thing. The thing about this that I want to really talk about, this is
welcome to every single, every single talk ADM radio station that you've ever listened to in
your whole life. And they think they have the audacity to bring everybody back in here and
talk to this. Yeah. I gotta get this right. How's this? No. How's this? No. All right. Hold on.
Make your choice. Make your, make your, make, make your, make, make your choice. Make your, make your
choice. Make your choice. Make your choice. Let me just work. This is better. Inside there's a key.
That key. There's another key. That's better. Five nights at Freddy's.
Kylo Ren. Everything. Wait, is somebody just getting drugged over there? Is drug going into
that person or something? I have to go stop the drug flow? Whatever it is. All right. I'm ready.
Guys, everything is Kylo Ren. Every, every low radio voice is Kylo Ren. Wait, pick up what?
Antigen. Health item is going to be used instantly when Tap picks the item up.
Cannot be stored in Tap's inventory like health hypos. Do a dinosaur roar. All right. I'll do,
you want me to do a dinosaur roar? And then take that and lower it because that's how they did the
T-Rex. Take that lower and add like a bunch of weird shit to it. T-Rex is like a trumpet or
something, right? Isn't the T-Rex like a trumpet or a trombone that they bucked with an elephant?
What am I thinking of? Wait, that's not what it is. What's the very, very popular, I'm doing
the T-Rex like, the T-Rex sound effect is just the Jim Carrey annoying sound that they slowed down.
All right. Where the fuck am I going? It's true. Yeah. I mean, I know. Silly streamer made a silly
noise. I need a thing to unlock this. Wait, blood. There's blood in here. There's no screws or
anything I can pick up. You have enough like a screw. I have to punch its head off. Ajax,
thanks for the five community subs. And Poofinator for the 10 community subs and my dead cat for the
10 community subs. What the fuck? That's a lot of community subs. Let's get a screw. Remember,
the screw is loose in your head. Where is this? What? I was just over here. Hold on a minute.
I opened this already and it said there's nothing in there. Fucking game sucks. Some of the doors
are rigged with lockpicking puzzles. I saw the puzzle rotate each piece to match the symbols
along the inner ring of the... I gotta pay attention. Save. There is no save. Where do you
expect me to do this? Rotate each piece to match the symbols along the inner ring of the chamber.
There is no save. There's just restore checkpoint, but that's blocked off. What the fuck is this?
What lock is this? All right. Does the game save? Where's my auto save? Save the woman in the
surgical theater. Find a key to unlock the main hallway door. Save, save, save, save. Insert your
memory card. There's a 500 gig memory card in here. Whoa. Holy shit. Let me see it. Let me see. Let
me see it. Come on. Let me see it. I haven't seen it once. What the fuck? Is this even Twitch? Is
this even a Twitch chat? Unbelievable. Thank you. What the fuck? I look like forever to see it.
Expect that every time. I'm sorry, Mr. Jigsaw. If you lock somebody in a room with barbed wire
around them and they have to like crawl out of it, the fuck are you talking about? You're just like
torturing people. Yeah, it was to symbolize their greed. Oh, so you wrapped barbed wire around their
head and put them in a giant meat grinder. Yeah, they were greedy. Oh, you feeling all right? Are
you all right? You drink water? That's perfect. That's a perfectly normal thing to do is wrap
somebody up, cut their arms and legs off, bury their head in sand, surgically implant
tubes in their body that they have to pull out and then connect to a wall. And then those tubes
then feed to another person's mouth. And yeah, the guy had insurance fraud. This might be a little
too far. Maybe now that I think about it out loud. My name is Rose. I am eight years old. My mommy
says I have polio. Polio is bad. I have it worse than Uncle Jack. He can still walk though. He seems
drunk. So I am now in this machine. A breeze spoke me so they can call it an iron lung. Her says she
will write what I say once a day so my diary doesn't forget who I am. She is my only friend.
So Jigsaw, let me get this straight. Yeah, are you talking to me? So you removed a little girl who
needed this to live to put somebody that like did heroin in it. Yes. Okay. It's your choice.
I'm going away for a fucking long time, dude. I, what's the fun of this? Who's paying the utilities?
Him? Yes, he, he made so much money that he, he, he did insurance fraud and he made $200,000 off of
other people and- Jigsaw, how much money do you have? It's not about how much money I have.
Yes, it was $6 billion to make this facility where I torture people that are bad, that we're greedy.
Jigsaw, why didn't you build like 30 schools? Well, um, because you need to be taught a lesson
and no question, you just try to get the key out of your ass. Well, I have your sternum or your eye
wherever I decided to put it. Some of you have noticed the walls starting to buckle in some areas
and have some become permeable. Please move all violent patients out of these rooms. Thus they
break down the walls to escape the construction manager. I talked to some more areas so we can
break walls. The walls in the asylum are rotted and weak. Break them open to reveal a new path.
Mr. Green is just Jigsaw. No way. I feel so strong right now.
Minecraft. Fucking Minecraft. Why? That's funny. Fuse. Okay. I got a fuse. And then can,
can the bottom drawer be opened? How do I save the game? Is there no saving? How do I save the game?
Saving is greedy. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna fucking die. What is this? The key to survival lies within.
Save the woman in the surgical theater. Find a key. Pick up the scalpel. Okay. So we get,
and what do you mean the knife will betray you? Read the toe tag. Jim Omen. Wait, do they? Hold
on. We've got like this Omen. Jay Omen doesn't have a key buried into his heart. He smoked
cigarettes. You spent years smoking cigarettes and now die with a knife from a guy that you don't
know. M. Johnson. Okay. No. Okay. A. Faulkner. Om Robinson. Arnie Faulkner. All right, Arnie.
I don't know what you did. What am I gonna get attacked? Okay. At what point do you make a
little noise and be like, you gotta give something a code, right? Like wiggle, like wiggle your toes,
like a Faulkner, right? Is the guy alive? Not anymore. What about this guy? This guy just dies.
No, he's such a fucking weirdo. I wouldn't be surprised at all if that was like,
like she was eating a lot of Oreos. I just really like Oreos. Your Oreo addiction is too much
for me to handle. The hell is this? You get it? Tech. I've determined you've had too many
Pornhub tabs open. Bolt some doors by pressing X. This will keep most enemies from opening the
door. Yeah. You're right. Pornhub tabs open. One sitting. This is unacceptable. And I'm looking
at his computer, like his computer's open. I get like into his office. He's got like 50 Pornhub
tabs open. Yeah. I can do as I say, not as I do. Right, Jigsaw? Fucking asshole. Okay. I'm getting
actually concerned about the game not saving at all ever once. This is concerning me. I have to
sign in? How am I not signed in? You have to sign in? I am signed in. Is that really what's
fucking going on? That can't be. Is it? I'm not even fucking signed in. Your call is okay. Do you
want to exit the session and test your network? No, no, no, no, I don't. No. What did you do?
Oh my God. Thank Jesus. Wait, there is no save file. Oh my God. No. What the fuck just happened?
Are you kidding me? Wait. Oh no. No, man. What the fuck? I can't even believe it. I can't even
believe it. No, this game. I want to play this. I can't believe it. It's not on this one. Like,
did it go somewhere else? Shit in my pants, man. Oh shit in my pants. Oh, this is just diarrhea.
Oh my God. I can't believe it. Why would it take me out? No. Oh no. I don't. I can't.
You got to be kidding me. I got to go fast. I got to go really fast. Fuck. This sucks. Just
absolute asshole. Oh no. I want to play this. Oh, this sucks. Total ass. I can't believe it.
This is a second fucking checkpoint. Oh, God damn it. I'm so disappointed. My disappointment
just is immeasurable right now. Okay. Let's go. I'm going to go fast as hell. I'm going to skip
every cutscene. I'm going to run. I'm going to punch. And where is the prompt? There's no,
there was no prompt. I was spinning it. I'm so mad. I'm so fucking mad right now.
I'm going to need to like just be quiet and just shut my fucking mouth and beat this.
Shitload of people here right now. What the fuck happened? 8,000 people here. Okay. Fast,
fast, fast, fast. 437. I was wondering why I wasn't getting any achievements. Fucking not even. Fast.
I don't care about anything. We're not stopping. We're not helping anyone. Hey, watch it. Yep. Yeah.
Yep. Okay. Sure. Bye. Wait, it's this one, isn't it? Which one was it? Get out of the bathroom.
I want some privacy. Okay. I'm fucking around. I'm not even trying to bump around. Get it immediately.
I have a full minute to do this, guys. It's not a problem.
Watch out for the barefoot. Take the pain. All right. Let's go. All right. Achievement. Yes.
Pressure. Oh my god. I was wondering why I wasn't getting these. How would I not be signed in?
How am I not signed in? How? It's impossible to not be signed in right now. All right. Speedrun. I
gotta go. Lighter. There's a checkpoint every 15 fucking seconds. I can't believe that this
went this long without me understanding and realizing that. Wait a minute. I'm like catching
up to this guy. Am I not supposed to catch up to this dude? Wait. He's not going to be up here,
is he? Yep. Okay. There are going to be lots of sacrifices to make. Hello. Help. Yes. Get that.
Okay. Yep. There's rugs in there. Careful. Nope. I didn't even give him a chance. Yeah. I know.
Okay. I pressed A. You just have to counter everything. Okay. We're good.
Okay. Holding. You don't understand it. You do like a full crow hop before you swing a light attack.
Why did I watch that again? I didn't need to watch that.
Door is sealed. Yep. All right. Get that key. Move. This door is sealed. All right. Go. Yep.
There's a note here. Good. Okay. Who is the jigsaw killer? I don't know. I wonder. What did
I do here? I don't even remember. What was it? Everything's sealed. What did I have to do?
There's a key inside his body. Yeah. I know. Well, how do I get the fuck out of here? Oh yeah. You.
Give me that. Okay. Bye. Glass. Yep. There's a shotgun door. All right. We're almost back.
Thank God you can skip cut scenes. I say that as I can. Okay.
Nail. Got it. Good. Okay. Everything got health.
Pick this up. Touch that. Read it so the game knows I looked at it in case I need it eventually.
Okay. Keep going. Go, go, go, go, go. Hurry the fuck up. I'm not going fast enough.
Instant health bandage. Got it. Okay. Cool. Nothing in here. Go. Out. I win.
And in any of this shit. And that's it. Key. Unlock the door. No, I want to go down.
Out of this. All right. Go. Good. I've made it back pretty much to where I was.
Find a key to unlock the main hall. I was down here. Remember I was like, I built a school. Right.
Remember when I did that? Something like that. All right. Let's go.
Would you like to know more? Okay. Remember there was somebody in here?
Yep. There was somebody in there. That's crazy. Okay. Remember this? The gulp. I remember the gulp.
That was pretty funny. And then there's a key. I almost just, I almost just died right there.
Okay. The key to survival lies within. Right. And then you have to, uh, cut into the, to,
Oh, right. A Minecraft punch. I don't know where to put your head. Hey, save. The game is saving.
I got it. It's fine. You're getting participation trophies.
It's always so funny. Back in the Xbox days when they, it really was just tied to if you progressed
in the game or not. What does that even supposed to mean to do? If I get it wrong
and the knife stabs me instead. All right, let's go. It's this guy, right? Yeah. It's Arnie.
All right, Arnie. Sorry. Body punches you. That's so dumb. That's real. Okay. Use the key. Yep.
Okay. Here we are. We made it in both doors. I know the Oreo lady. Yeah. Wait. Okay. This,
this is probably, there's gotta be a reason why you do that, right? Watch out for that glass.
All right. Now I just need, uh, over here. Made it. There's Mortal Kombat at himself.
Some ways through the asylum were more dangerous than others. Use left stick to walk over the
hazard and use right stick to balance. He even did like a front flip too. He treated this like
it was a ball pit at McDonald's. All right. Is there anything else here? It's right here.
Thank God I signed it. Why would you do that? Just go across it. What the fuck are you doing?
I got the key, right? Is this guy open? Yeah, let's go. Oh, thank God. Yeah. No, it's fine.
To be fair though, wouldn't you sprint across that shit? Why would you balance beam? No, just,
just do a full sprint and jump and leap the fuck over the whole thing. How would you balance beam
that? No, that's not the way to do it. Look at the distance here. That's not that far. If you go,
this guy had the right idea, but he just rolled off. I have like, my like steering needs to be
aligned. It pulls a little to the left. What the fuck was that kid? Freedom. Can you rescue
her detective tap? Can you rescue her detective tap? Is she in there? Hold on. Is there something
over here? Freedom. Freedom is an illusion in $600 million facility. Is this baking soda?
Antiges. I have full health. I would have have not full health. You either fall down on the spikes
and die or that's it. What is this trying to tell me? I need to find a coupler.
All right, I got a nail. I got nothing. Unlock the cabinet. Oh, thank God. The puzzles
are 100% brainless. I mean, and I mean 100%. Like there's been nothing that you really need
to even spend more than one to two full seconds understanding how it works. That just makes me
happy. I don't want to do puzzles and shit. Fuck that. Who wants to do puzzles? I said the fine
thing. He's dumb. I mean, that's fine. It's a checkpoint. Okay. Now what? Dig saw box open.
Who am I? Name blacked out. Patient ID 825-3612-3127. April 14, 1998. Fund initial
assessment, whoever it is, presents as well as a well-spoken man with a firm grasp upon reality.
Patient 34 years old, married for two years with wife four months pregnant, denies necessity of
psychological treatment but is kept appointment at the request of his wife with sister visitation
due to a concern of a growing isolationistic tendencies. Patient displays high degree of
verbal acuity and is very observant. Initial test suggest a very high IQ with an extraordinary
ability to recall facts but their expressed pride in his intelligence and knowledge
exhibit who cares about any of this. Patient is polite and cordial. All right, that's all I need
to know. They have an affection for his wife and animals and stuff. He's not. Let's display them.
After initial consultation, they don't need to come in anymore. They just follow up here.
Patient displays tendencies towards depression and narcissistic personality disorder. Okay.
What was I hopping for? Come on, game. What the fuck is this? Where's the blood?
Well, ask in you. Wait, a crutch? I want the crutch. The crutch is definitely more powerful.
I just bolted. I'm just going to queue it up. All right. It's the swing is so bad. Just counter
everything. Only parry. Oh no, not another one of these. All right. Just take it slow. Don't be an
idiot. All right. I feel like I'm playing condemned. Where's the guy that's going to run around the
corner? The two by four with a big tray. Oh, it's okay. I'm fine. I'm fine. A pipe. No, I want the
crutch. I can't help two items. Just put one down your pants. Like slide the pipe down your like
back or front of your underwear. What do you mean? You don't have a pocket or something. Just take
it. You might need it. Dual welding. Sorry. Wielding dual wielding. I go down here. I feel
like I'm not supposed to be over here. Oh, yes, I am. All right. Checkpoint is faster than I am.
Are we in this? The cop that's been chasing you and interrogating me.
You see here the face is obsession and to make a choice, your life will depend.
Is this her? I got the fuse. Dark. Darkness also illuminates. I guess. I don't know. What is it?
Writing poetry? What does that mean? Dude, one time. Did I talk about this before? I was in the store.
This is like a year or two ago. I was in the store and there was poetry books on the shelf.
I've talked about this before. Have we? Where it's okay. It's a poetry book. The book is probably
can't be more than 50 or 60 pages. And I don't know if this is supposed to be for like aesthetic
reasons. I don't know. I was trying to figure it out. Half of the pages, the poems were one or two
sentences and it took up the whole paper. It was just the entire page was like one sentence.
And then like the next page was like three sentences. Next page, one sentence. Oh, it
wasn't a kid's book. YouTuber poems. Oh, well, this is what? What's this? Wait, I have a fuse.
They're going to deactivate them. All right. I did it. The room has been deactivated or something.
Oh, I was just a pinata. Don't do it. How far back will it put me? It's going to be a
audio tape. Here we go. But he's here. He's in the room. Sometimes to search the room to find the
obvious detective. Because I kind of trapped myself in here. I kind of forgot which one I turned on
first. I've been here for a few hours. Get us both out of here. That'd be great. Sure thing,
Jake. So I'll take care of it. It's going to be really good. It's going to be really good.
I do. He wired that wrong. That was he fucked up the wiring. He let him down.
I just got it. What? No, I pressed A on this thing.
Okay, it's it. What about fuck the puzzle? It's in the gun draw. Oh, it's still a fuse box.
It's this one. Oh, I got the coupler. Okay, cool. I have 12 seconds. Wait, the audio tape.
Give me the audio tape quick. Too many people. I didn't even install the fuse box. Is that going
to be bad? When I blew up the room first. It was like lights on the wall. Wait, hold on.
It's a secret entrance. It's a bomb right there. What's wrong with what's going on with this one?
Yep. Rink it. Can I even do this? I didn't break the whole game. Did I? Is it broken?
I don't think I was supposed to do this yet. I didn't get the fuse yet. Oh, where the fuck is
the fuse? Oh, right. Okay. Now I see what you're understanding here. Okay,
go. Did I just get it? I just picked it up. It's happening right now. Okay, it's lit up.
Now I have to follow the path. He was on battery acid when he did this. How did he get on the
ceiling? Well, this is like you didn't even try. This is not even right. Is that supposed to
fuck with me? I don't even know what he's talking about. So what? I have to connect the line with
your eyes and then the door will present itself. It's the gun. Yeah. Okay. Well, I'm already way
ahead of this. My IQ is too high. I did this. I already got that. I already did this. I opened
the gun. I did this backwards. I did this in reverse. So where do I go? What did I just get?
What do I have? Holy shit. I can't believe you did this fucking whole thing backwards.
What does it pick up? What? Oh, crutch. What did I get for doing this? Another fuse box?
Back up to the ladder. This game suck. Anybody know? Oh, I got the coupler. The coupler.
Who the fuck is this guy? Hey, come here. Watch out. This glass. Get over here. I'm coming up there.
What? Why is he waiting? Wait, why did I do that? Are you all right? There's no reason. Oh my god.
I was right in the fucking mouth. And I didn't even say anything. This is... Holy shit. Um, okay.
Wait. I, I, I... You just have to unbolt the door, dude. You just have to unbolt. Oh,
you could have been my friend. We could have had... We could have gone together.
I could have had a person with me instead. Holy shit. That was unbelievably horrible.
Okay. What's in the box? Oh, nothing in the box. Just the thing that goes...
All right. I have the coupler. Now what? I got it. Everybody fucking relax. Relax. Relax. It took
like not even 60 seconds. Lower the office. What office? This one? All right. Press button.
I got an exit. How do I get over there? Where are you going? I don't know. Where am I going?
What do I do? Can I move this? I like drag this out of the way. Oh, there we go. Sick. Oh,
look at that. Sick. Checkpoint. All right. I have two nails. What do I do with this shit?
You missed a secret room. Secret room. Secret room. I'm like, I'm blind. Oh, I'm all right.
I still... What do I have? A person's leg? That's a baseball bat. Right. Okay. Let's keep going.
Glass? Who's making that noise? I'm here to rescue you. All right. Call the police. Make a
telephone call now. Okay. Somebody in there? Somebody in this room? Did I save you? Aren't
you the police? Am I? All right. I'm the police. Oh shit. Pick up pipe. No. That's way better. No.
Pipe has more slots left. Dude, I'm telling you, man. I find somebody. I do a full combo, full five
slot, eviscerate on somebody. Whoa. That'll do probably 700 damage and create yellow numbers.
Whatever. And there's a wow reference. Whatever. Who's this guy? He's superhuman. Barricade.
Sometimes a bolt of door is not enough. Keep enemies from breaking through a closed and bolted
door. Move something heavy in front of the door. But everybody's like, hey, I have a pipe. Just hit
him in the head. Just fucking hit him. I mean, you have to do this. What do you have to do?
Well, come in. Thanks for the free item, you fucking idiot. Quick. Block the door. Barricade
the door. I get the tutorial message. One of us. What have you had? You may have had something
very important to tell me. OK, move it back. I didn't get a no tutorial. I have to do this.
We didn't spend very much time trying to kill me. That's encouraging. Checking. Why am I
checking for items? Who cares? Just beat it. Just beat the game. This game's probably like three
hours long. OK, what's the percentage chance that this is longer than the movie? Is this game's
story mode longer than the movie that it's based on? Find out. And I just probably played for like
three or four hours and never played this ever again. We'll see. You're never going to see this
game again. Yeah, that's a guarantee. But it only happens if you die without having been signed in.
Yeah. Oh, just. All right. Take some. Free. For the amount of health that I have and the amount
of danger I've potentially been in. I feel like insane probably wouldn't be that insane.
All right. Let's let's let's go. What the fuck? Getting a good gamers score from this.
And here is over there. I don't know. What is that? What is this? Have I been in here?
This is headphones. This is the person on the drugs. This is the minor price.
I want that fucking vacation. Let's go. Oh, there's a key in there.
It's sitting on the table. Wow. I can just go in and grab it. Uh oh. It's not going to be that easy.
Crap. I really like bombs. OK, we need to find the code for the door.
Nothing in the cabinets. Oh, shit. It's a fuse box. OK, fuse. Fuse. Can I do it? Now what? Five,
seven, nine. Quickly. Hurry up. Five, seven. Go backwards. Still going to blow up? Uh oh.
Oh, no. No boss fight. Now I'm in another room. TVs and bombs.
That's all this guy's got. You got a surplus of old televisions and bombs and you rescue her?
Detective Tapp? Question mark. Can you? It took a lot of yard sales for you to get
all these TVs, Jigsaw. I mean, that's known. Where'd you get all the bombs? I don't understand.
Where do you get them? Where would he? What do you mean? Where would he have built them?
Until now, the Jigsaw Killer has never left anyone alive. Amanda Young is now the first
and only known survivor of the Jigsaw Killer. Details about Young are forthcoming. She is
to make a statement regarding her capture. He saved my life. These are the words spoken
by Amanda Young, only known survivor of the Jigsaw Killer. I mean, at what point? Hold on.
Do we know? At what point? Where does it think we know in the story? Because this is just Saw.
I think, no, this takes place. We have seen Saw 6 at this point, or Saw 5, because there's a trailer
for Saw 6 on the disc. I remember seeing it. So it assumes we've seen all five Saw movies.
So just want to make sure you guys are aware. There's probably going to be some spoilers,
but Saw is one through five. I mean, I already know. Maybe you do. I don't know. Do you?
We had Chiyo Chan give five community subs. Thank you. We also had $50 coming.
There's 5,000 bits earlier that I missed. I'm a terrible streamer. I'm very bad at everything
that I do. I mean, you new viewers that are here right now, I might just skip over your
$50 donation. Just want to make sure we're aware of that, apparently.
There's Green Templar. Thanks for the fucking huge amount of money.
They say, Jeremy, I want to say thank you for the entertainment you've given me. You're so
unique and have... Oh, look at that. I'm fucking unique. Really innovated the streaming formula
with your comedy and your creative use of the tools available to you. I do have one request,
though, if you can. I really like when you play strategy games and really recommend you play
Total Warhammer 2 as the rats. It fits your theme, and I think it would be fun for a stream. Stay
safe. I think I've completely given up on ever doing anything that has to do with managing
2,000 units over the course of a giant map that I have to feed units into diplomacy and shit. I
don't think I'll ever do it again. I had an absolute mess of a time trying to play something
like Mountain Blade, and then people were like, hey, you should try Crusader Kings. And I'm like,
nope. Is this like Crusader's Kings? Shove? What the fuck? It's different.
I don't want to watch this fucking show.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here. I'm coming.
How am I going to get injected? Oh, shit.
All right. Antidote. Hey, just breathe in the antidote. Okay. Antidote going in. Toxin
being released. Antidote. Antidote go that way. And then antidote. All right. Antidote going in.
Bingo. Did I win? I just made us way more powerful. Look at that heartbeat now.
We have the heartbeat of a small fish. All right. Antidote. Toxin. Yeah, get the toxin out of here.
We don't dump that that way. I'm going to give you more of that toxin. Wait, and then put the
antidote over here. Look, Jigsaw, you didn't really explain the rules very well. Antidote.
Okay, I think we're safe now. I'm still alive. Just match the color. What do you mean match the color?
Sorry, I was talking. I was talking over the cutscene. Is he going to explain it again?
Red, left, blue, right. I wasn't paying any attention at all. Like zero. I was looking
at chat and like talking about stuff. Red, left, blue, right. He literally said it.
He literally said it. Red, left, blue, right. All right. What's coming up first? I didn't, I
wanted to put it to the left. I wasn't trying to make it go right. Red, left. Okay. Blue, right.
Okay. Red, left. This is fucking, um, it, it's just, I'm trying. No, why is it doing,
I'm trying to go the other way. I'm, it's just putting them down auto, free stuff, fucking thing.
You made the blue go, I didn't do anything. It's just automatically doing the, can I move the device?
Okay. Blue goes right. So I'm going to do, it's going to go, go, go, go, go. So we're going to go,
let's go put it down there. You're thinking too far ahead. Jigsaw, your puzzle's dumb.
I can, what, I can't, I just like dig my hands through like my Play-Doh insides to find the
fucking device. Why do we have to do this? I don't want to do this. Okay. Now blue. Okay. Red. Red.
No, blue. Blue. Okay. Now blue. Now red. Blue. Okay. Now blue again. Blue. Oh shit. Hold on.
It's just as stupid as just, just alternate them every time. Am I overthinking this like crazy
right now? Is it just alternate every time? And that's it. What's the point I have what,
why have a puzzle? No, it's not. That's, that's not that simple. Is it? Oh my God. It's actually
that simple. Okay. Now we go. No, it's not. It's not that simple. The fucking things moved. Fuck.
Are we going to go blue? Okay. Now we're going to go, um, blue again. No, no. What happened? What the
fuck is happening right now? What? Oh boy. This is, it's storing. She's dead. Oh fuck. This is bad.
I don't know. Uh, I'm just going to wait till you guys tell me what to do. I'm not even kidding.
What do I do? I'm not even going to press any buttons until you say whatever it is.
Okay. Uh, now what? Red. Which one? Blue. Blue again. Red. You fucking assholes. You lied to me.
She's dead. Do it again. Oh my God. This just sucks. This actually sucks. I don't want to do
this. I'm going to only listen to you. All right. Is there a, is there a mod in the chat right now?
Is there a mod in the chat? Uh, I'm going to only, I want one mod to tell me how to beat this.
Okay. It's just alternate only. So it's just blue, red, blue, red, blue, red, blue.
Just go. Let me have to start storing them in shit. No mods. Uh oh. Uh oh. Okay. So, um, here we go.
Blue. Blue first. And then now it's going to be, uh, blue again, right? Can I pause it? Okay. If
the game's stupid, I can pause it. Now it's red. Okay. Now we've got a double scenario here. We now
we do blue twice. Blue twice. Blue twice. Blue twice. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Red.
Then red again. No, blue. No, no. Blue again. Blue. Blue here. Okay. Now red. Okay. Now,
um, now blue. Okay. Now red. Okay. Now blue. Okay. Now red. Okay. Now blue. Okay. Now red.
Okay. Now blue. It was just the same thing. I overthought the fuck out of that.
That was the most overthinking ever. It's okay. You're okay. What did you do? I'm not him. I'm not
the one who. It's okay. I'm okay. I know. Look, we have to play by his rules. I saw him. I saw him.
Who is he? What did he look like? That's all you care about. I just nearly died.
Me too. We're all here because of you, detective.
Ooh. Damaged goods. Chapter one complete. I thought this had eat light source. Why?
I'm here. I already remember. I made it through one of his tests before right now. We have to be
careful. Doors aren't what they seem. I can't wait till she walks through one of these and
gets killed. I have a feeling this entire asylum is trapped. Play by the rules and we both might
make it. He's watching. Already survived one trap by him. How clearly I failed the test.
That's why he brought me back here and with a fucking cop. No less. Just be sure of this.
Jigsaw's in control. Not you. Okay. Knock it off. Okay. I just needed to know if you could.
She died? You don't. Can I kill her? Oh, he's in control, huh? Knock it off. Oh,
nothing in there. I am in control. Oh, I found a clue over here. Can I do anything with this?
I got back up. Back up. Back the fuck up. I got a lighter. You're wasting durability. Yeah,
you're right. Alright, Jigsaw, open the door. A little too long wind in here. Let's go. Wait.
Help. I'm coming. I'm here. You're still with me, right? Okay. Nothing in that work table.
Pick up. What is it? A mop handle. Oh, absolutely. Here. I'll trade.
Oh, be careful. Hey, you think the man you killed cried for help the same way as he lay dying in
the street. What was he on? You covered it up, but like anything buried inside you. This really
could be Kylo Ren. Everyone you love. It's like the same lines. I give her a weapon. I really mean
this. I can't give you anything. Why can't I give you something? I hope he says the word
unit. Look out behind you. He's electrocuting her. Okay. Well, I'm glad I don't have to worry
about another person. I would have been a pain in the ass. Has there been anything in any of
these draws ever the whole time we played? What's the point of this stuff? It's here.
Here. All right. Stay calm. Friend or enemy. I don't know. We didn't have a chance to
determine who that was. All right. Watch out. This is a tank that
find the boiler room key. Go in the acid. Uh-oh. No, I don't want to just reach in the acid.
Why did I do this? Why did I do that? There's nothing in here. Oh,
wait, I open this to live or die, live or die, live or die. Find the, find the, find the,
find the, find the truth. Find the truth, truth, truth, truth, truth, truth.
Find the remix. What does that mean? Body bag, shotgun shell, and tripwire.
Oh, I get a shotgun. I get a gun. I hope I get a gun. Even walking can be dangerous in Jigsaw's
world. Watch the ground for shotgun tripwires and disable them before they go off. You can also
rearm these to use against enemies. Oh, that's right here. Okay. Well, how do I turn it off?
Buddy, how do I turn it off? So, all right, now arm it. Wait, now arm it while I'm across it.
Okay. I'm going to forget that that's there, but try to remind me. I almost blew my fucking head off.
That was, that was close. I'm not going to lie. See the janitor about the steam. I need a wheel.
Why? What's the thing with steam hurting you and killing you and stuff? Are you telling me
that you can't just like full sprint and like slide underneath that? Just take your shirt and
like cover your head and stuff and just run, sprint, slide. It's hot. Yeah. Slide on and just,
just sprint as fast as you can. You'll get like a little bit on you. It sticks to you.
You know, the one of the seals broke today near the boiler. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Treasure. Next time. Seal breaks might kill someone. Yeah. Well, you didn't tell me where
the wheel was. Uh, is this the game's excuse to just get you? I don't understand why I keep doing
it. I feel like that's the game telling me I was out of bounds for too long. What? Escape the bathroom.
Uh, what are the rules? What's the rule book? Darkness illuminates. All right. Put down the
darkness illuminates. Uh huh. All right. Turn the light off. Light switch. Be in this toilet over
here. Get all these needles. I got the key. Is that a key to the helmet?
Okay. Rescue. Go to the janitor's office. Okay. And his office is this way. Where's that bomb?
Where's that? Where's that tripwire? It's over here, right? That's not, where is it?
Is it right here? Where's that tripwire? I don't know where it is. Your shotgun collar reacts to
specific enemies with shotgun collars. When you get near one of these enemies, the lights on the
back of your collar will blink. The closer the enemy, the closer the enemy, the faster the
blinking and the faster your own collar will detonate. Try to stay far away from enemies with
collars. If you keep your distance long enough, the enemy collar will explode and deactivate.
Ah, don't come near me, man. Get away from me. Get away from me. Get away. Get away. Don't you know
what these things are? You fucking idiot. Stop. Leave me alone. Hold the door. All right. You're
fucked. Dead. Wait, but his collar is still on the ground. Where is he? I got his, wait, oh,
there he is. I was gonna say this is his arm. Oh, this is where he explains it. Okay. Pick this
lock. Oh crap. I can't do that. What's he doing? I want to select this one. The number is Jeremy.
What do they mean? I don't know. This is shit. Unlock. Jigsaw chest. Gear. A nail. What's in
the jigsaw chest? Oh boy. Wait, I have to, I didn't know there were other sizes. All right,
there's this huge, come on. How far on do I have to go? Got it. Doctor, his brain's too big.
Shotgun shell trip where I end bandages. Excellent. Oh, got it. Now we've got to go
over, we have to go the way that guy came. Bathed up over here. Probably a dead body in it.
Search the area to find the valve wheel. Oh, no, I want to press his hand. Way cooler.
Storage. Oh, the baseball bat in here. What do I care? I don't care. Nothing. I break this wall.
No. Need a hand, Jeremy. And then why didn't you do the Pepe laugh thing?
How would you write that and not write Pepe laugh? Have you ever been on the internet before? Come
on. The wheel is nearby. It's probably right behind this. Behind the chalkboard.
Wow. I almost just walked right into that. Okay. That would have been bad. I'm knocking. I can't
see that shit. How am I supposed to reliably see those? Oh, there it is. Nothing. Wait,
what was in there? I don't know. Rip wire. Okay. That's the point. Oh, no one's even hurt me.
I'm untouchable. Yeah, I gotta get this open into the utility room. What the hell did that just say?
What did that just say? What did that just say? That was a huge amount of text. What did it say?
Oh, I think that guy died. Well, what is this? Probably said don't touch electricity. Table lamp.
No, I want the, I want the wooden leg. Uh, they call these people insane, but I don't see that.
Somebody else will read this screenshot and look at it. This is the guy they told us about.
There you are. Where am I? Who are you? Who is, who is me? Step on, come over here.
Do you see it? He sees it. What the fuck? He doesn't see it. Does he? I crit this guy. Nice.
Nice. All right. How do I get this guy to come over here? Come over here. Hey, this way.
Where is he? Where is he? Fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Okay. Hold on. Here we go. Oh my God.
That was fucking horrible. Well, I got him. Turn that off. Don't die. This, uh, I think there was
another wire here or a shell that I couldn't get before because I had full inventory. I like it
matters. Oh, it don't fucking hurt. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Full nails. All right. Now back to
that door. Table lamp hog. Yeah. It's time to pick up the table lamp. You're right.
Oh, nothing. Wait, nothing. Why are they still lit up? What is this? Okay. Now I get the hell
out of here. I go, um, uh, this way. Wait, what did he have? Oh, he's a mop handle. I got the wheel
back to the steam room, which was down and just making sure he didn't stand up.
This guy got out. How did this guy get out of this chamber?
I keep getting achievements. Wait, is that thing going to explode?
Okay. That was, wait, I think I ran out of material. He's really dead. Yeah. He's very dead.
Okay. Steam room this way. There's electricity everywhere over here. What room am I even in?
What is this place? I turned it off. I just found like a new area. Diffuse.
Take it. Joe Biden game play. I don't even know what that's supposed to mean.
What is, how is that? What do you mean true? I I'm just like progressing through the game.
What are you talking about? Please read. Hold on. It was an important please read comment.
Please read. There's no risk in this game because you aren't actually in danger. If you fail one of
Jigsaw's games, you die. You should have to snap a rubber band against your wrist or pop a balloon
next to your ear. Why? I don't want to do that. Oh, fuck that. I'm not popping balloons next to my
head. All right. Where's the steam room? Fuck balloons. That hurt? Why did that hurt so bad?
Wait, where am I? Furnace. Spoiler room. No escape. No escape. It felt like 20 feet.
It did not fall that far. Use an Estus. Good. Okay. Not what?
Okay. I don't have a wire. What do I do? I don't have a wire. There's no wire. I don't have a wire.
Got one. Okay. 40 seconds. Uh oh. What was the point of, what was the point of me doing that?
Go, go, go, go, go, go. How much time? Good. Oh, the acid. Remember? Okay. Furnace. Spoiler room.
We just can't, what? The trip wire. Trip wire from like 30 minutes ago. Whatever.
Be fair though with me. That was a while ago. And where the fuck even is that? Okay. On your,
do you see it on your screen? I don't. Like, I don't even know where it is now.
It's right there. Okay. That shit wasn't even on the screen. Let's turn the fuck up.
Turn it back on. Turn it back on. Turn the steam back on. Turn the steam back on then.
Turn the steam back on. If that's the problem. Turn the steam back on. Can I check this body?
Oh shit. They're killing each other in there. Not much chance. All right. I'm going to wait
till he puts his face right here and I'm going to hit him right the fucking teeth through the door.
Is he eating him? Hey. Hey. Hey, you. I'm talking to you. Can I climb through? Can I get in here?
It's open. Can he throw grenades? Dude, I wish you could just whip shit. I would just throw this
at this guy's head. Okay. Well, whatever. Let's go and go up. Can't go that way because the steam
is there. He's eating. Well, whatever. I'll take, I'll take him. I'll just wait till I do a drop
down R1. I'd like you, Jerma. Thanks. What happened in there? I don't deserve this. Oh fuck. Steam.
Wait, is that like a fake steam? What the hell was that? How did that just pop up for a second?
All right. There he is. Right? He's right here. The guy's in here. Let's go. I have the high ground.
He's got a knife. No. No. Fuck you. Get away from me. Plunging attack.
It didn't work. Throw the steam on. Quick. Burn him. He dropped the knife. Wait. Why? Kill him.
Is he dead? Okay. He's dead. I want his knife. Where's that knife? The knife fell down here.
Give me that knife. It's right there. I want that fucking knife. Game sucks. Whatever. Say please.
This is, this is a real Halloween stream kind of game. Don't you think?
I bet it's late. All right. I made it. Like rats in a maze. Oh, this is going to be fucking
fantastic. Isn't it? I can't wait. Please give me a checkpoint because this is going to,
I know this is going to be horrendous. Uh, I have a weapon. I got a gear. So, all right. Turn this
off. What does this make it go? All right. Makes it go this way. I got to follow the rules.
Follow the rules or die. Skip lore. Okay. Then over here. And now what? How do I,
how the fuck do I get that turned off? Run through it. I don't think I can. I think it's going to
kill me. Oh, this is go down. 5,000 bits and a 50 fucking dollars came in from fat Batman.
Like that name. Thanks for the 50 bucks. They say, Hey, he said my message chat. So he knows
I like him more. He said my message. So he likes me more. Uh, well, I mean, everybody eventually
is going to be a one guy. You know that didn't say no. It just did. Where's your only fans.
We already went over that. That's not, I don't have that. What lies beneath. Okay. But hold on.
What's this thing? I don't know. Let's find out how far of a drop is it?
Whatever. All right. Let's dumb ass mazes. More dumb ass dialogue, please. Come on.
There's something to work with. It feels bad, man. It's a 2.6 maze that is that you make up
on my, my college GPA. What was your college GPA? Uh, I don't want to do this. I don't want to do
this. I'm done. This is a 2.7 puzzle. Shut up. No, wait, no, no, no. Go back to that.
Two point fucking seven GPA puzzle. Got it. What I can say. I didn't do it. No.
All right. Here they come. They're going to be running through the ballroom or the,
wait, I hear them starting and stopping. No, why is that? I need a checkpoint.
I'm not doing this yet. This is, I'm going to die. Super Mario level bullshit. No. Okay. So go.
Wait for me. This game is fucked. I know. Wicked fuck. You have made it into the heart of the
boiler. Throwing punches. Throwing punches. Why don't you say help me? Anyone out there? Help me.
Fucking punch you in the face. Somebody help me. I'm thick on my head. Minecraft Steve.
Bricks. Oh yes. Again, I gave us bricks in it. Oh, this became one of the best games ever.
This game has bricks in it. Thank God there's fucking bricks in this game.
Can't see. Oh, this guy's doing this. Holy shit.
Oh, that was so dumb. I have to do this shit again. Whatever. Hey, go away. One go one in one go,
please. Oh, good. It hit me. But who cares? How would that guy be able to see? He's chasing me
around. Come on, man. How hard is this? Oh, my chest. How would he not get shot by these?
Oh, don't shoot. I didn't know there were two shotgun trips. Oh, God damn it. Chest.
You got baked to death. Kind of. All right. In one go. Right. I can do it in one go just to prove I
can. Oh, it's tricky. But all right. All right. All right. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Here
he comes. Okay. Help. Yep. Okay. Where's the tripwire? Right here. Just arm it. Give me a brick.
All right. Now arm it. Come on. What? He punched me. Give me the brick. Brick.
Okay. Help him. I can't help him. Wait. Where is he? Where the fuck did he go?
Where is this guy? Where'd he go? Where is he? Hello? Why is he not here anymore? Where is he?
He tripped. Oh, he tripped this. We didn't even get to see him die. I've got to take a brick with
all this important. Holy fuck. I almost walked over that. Okay, we're good. That's all the traps.
I got the valve. Yep. Might as well take them all. Oh, please get out of here. What the fuck? All
right. Which one is it going to go into? I don't know. This one, I guess. Okay. Then down here.
No, it can be this thing and like this thing. Then wait, I got to connect this bullshit. Okay.
Hold on. No, no. There it is. Okay. I'll connect this shit. No, this way. Okay. Now get this. This
connected. Connected, I guess. I don't even know where it's supposed to be going. I hate this thing.
No, I want to... I got to connect these stupid fucking valves, but it's like,
which one is the right one? I don't know. It's wild guess time. It's not this one. Not that one.
Not this one. Not this one either. Not this one. It's this one. It has to be. It's right here.
Yeah. All right. That's stupid. Who made this dump? Why would you make it like this? All right. Give
me it. Give me it. Give me the key. Give me the key. Open the boiler. What? Open it. Didn't it just
say get the key from the boiler? Behind the boiler. What the hell did it even just say?
Okay. I like the furnace gate key. Is this a map in this game? That shotgun's freaking me the fuck
out. All right. Am I insane or did I get the key? Do I just keep going? I already got the key.
The way the fuck was the damn thing? Check my inventory. I don't even know how to do that.
It's in your body now. Oh, I don't know what I just did. Okay. All right. Well, what the hell
does it want me to do now? Objective. Behind me. Turning into Adam Sandler. What a stupid map.
I can't have an arrow pointing. Why does it have to be a star? Is this it? Why is it? Wait.
Why would I do the... What's the point of doing the furnace puzzle if this is just here?
What? God. Don't. Please give me a checkpoint. Please. Checkpoint. Please.
Please. Oh, I got to get out of here. Can I walk past this? I guess so. I don't know.
No, I got to go out here. Oh, please. Steam coming out. Can I go? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay. Fine. Nice fucking YouTuber reaction there. I would say so. Okay. Now go right and then straight
and then hell. Okay. Am I going to get hit by this? Is that steam? I don't know what that is.
Is that steam? Is that going to kill me? I don't want to walk fucking by it. It's going to hit me.
Okay. Now we're going to go left. Okay. Got it. And then this way. I made it. I went sick.
Looks like you were quick enough to save yourself, but
thinking about yourself is what you excel at. Unlock the furnace room.
I got a checkpoint there. That's pretty good. Thank God. Let's get locked in. Of course I didn't.
All right. You have anything else for me? Here we go. Rescue Jennings Foster. Locate the furnace
room. Give me that pipe. Protect myself. Bolt this door. Can I? Or you'll end up reading this
eventually. Maybe. Wait, there's a syringe. I can syringe people. This is pretty awesome actually.
Okay. I'm keeping the syringe case file. Uh, you'll, if you pause the stream and just rewind,
you'll, you can read it. I'm going to try to steam clean this something. Okay. The lock. I
got to go, but love your term up. Have a good one. Good to see you again. Make sure you join
us next time. There's nothing even in here. What a waste of, waste of time. Waste of time.
Million viewers are gone. Can't be real. There's not a million people, uh, on Twitch.
Take the case file. Somebody else will read it. Where am I going now? All right. I need to go.
Where am I? I'm not even on the map. Here I am. There I am. Okay. Here we go. Step on glass. Use
them. Okay. Not bad. Not bad for my first day. Got a gun. I don't want to syringe you, but I will.
What's on his head? Why does he have like a little canister on his head? Is the guy going to explode?
Don't do it. Is he? I'm safe. Okay. What does it do? Oh, it closed on his head. Run. Run.
That was actually horrible. I can't believe I just got through that. All right.
Watch the glass, man. I wasn't looking up in the shock and going off in my face.
That's some fucking Tom and Jerry shit right there. Oh, let's see if I can get this.
And do a Tom and Jerry bit. First aid cabinet. I've so, I don't even need any items.
What's the point of me doing this? Three drugs, I guess. Bat. Do I still have syringe? No.
One time use. Okay. Furnace room this way. And here we go. What's my next goal? TV. That will
tell me that's not telling me anything. No tripwire, right?
What's he doing to this guy? Is he going to squish him? Okay. Here's what I think. If I'm
a diabolical sick fuck, he's on a plate and he's going to just on a piston, he's going to squish
him up into the ceiling like he's a fly with a fly's water, right? It's going to slowly go up
and it's going to scare the shit out of him. It's going to go really fast and stop and it's going
to, no, I'm not going to really, really slow, but we can fast to the ceiling. No, here we go.
I'm going to pull you back down all the way and you can, we'll sit there for like another 40
minutes or so. This is fucked up. This is weird that I'm saying this. This game suck. Oh, a camera.
Wait, don't, why would you do that into your own eyes? Picture is worth a thousand words.
The picture is, what does it say? I don't like that. Find the truth. It's a pharmaceutical company
that's going to blot you evil shit or something. No, this is, I don't like that. This sucks. Give
me the lighter instead. I'm going to need this though, aren't I? But I don't know what that means.
Am I missing something? What the fuck is that? That's very disorienting. Yeah, it is. Push and
pull your way forward. I need to even look at that. I can read backwards. Can you use the lighter?
Please God. I'm going to need this. I'll get another lighter. Don't worry. Push and pull your
way forward. I'm with the pig thing. Push and pull. Zet-y. Puppet. I puppet. What does it say?
All right, let's go. I'm going to pull this. What does it say? Cart. Yeah, I can't pull it or push
it. Push or pull your way to, I don't know. Wait, was it one of the, more than two? There's a few
of these. Oh, here we go. Oh, it's going to be like that traffic game. That was thankfully easy.
I'm just walking around up there. I'm going to run right for the camera right in the face.
Well, everybody coming? Hold it from the other side. That's going to happen. Every,
so glad there's an actual checkpoint here. Okay. It's so dark. I, even with the,
with the flash I wouldn't have been able to see this shit. Where is it? Right there.
There's another one. Is it set? Wait, set it. Okay. Set that one. Then I'm going to,
there's going to be a guy that breaks through and I'm going to run around the circle. There he is.
It's the psycho right there. Oh yeah. The door is open. Only one door open. Follow me. Wait,
he didn't even get hit by the mung that I put. He did. Wait, I have one minute to do this.
How do I get this guy to come out? 56 seconds. Wait, why does this guy have like a VR helmet on?
We have both so bad. It's like a JRPG. Miss fucking kidding me. Your time is up.
You'll see. Okay. Give me, wait, he's not dead. I think I got him. I think I got him. All right.
How do I, how do I get this guy out? Eight seconds until what? Eight seconds. Wait until he's
released. So what? This guy's like worse for wear than everybody else was. This is going to do
anything. Okay. I got the furnace for him. Okay. What? It's all right.
You aren't, I was, I was, uh, yeah. Fuck. I know I can't, there's nothing I can say about that one.
I mean, holy shit, dude, was that on purpose? No. I mean, I was trying to,
I was trying to say that thought it was a on, and I thought it was a on like this,
on like a cabinet or something. I don't know. I'm stupid. Talk to me. God damn it. I'm yeah.
Why am I just silent? Why wouldn't we want to work together? Oh no. One minute. Whatever will we do?
Can we fight through the door? I can't hit him through the door.
Where's the other guy? Oh, he's waiting. Fucking right next to you, dude.
Open the door. Okay. I'm going to be ready right when the door opens.
The timer up. Oh, it is now. I hit him right in the groin. Okay. Don't fuck around, dude.
Why is he taking a full step forward? Just wait. You see what I'm doing? I'm hitting A.
Jesus Christ. I hit him. I'm you. Okay. Hey, he does like this full step forward. I'm not
having him do that. Unlock the furnace room. Wait, don't fucking go fast. See right here.
This is what happened last time. I went to open this. See, it's like, hey, you can touch this.
That's what happened. See what I'm talking about here. Look at that bullshit. I thought I was
fucking mad. I'm back to normal. Now we're going to open the furnace door, the mannequin arm,
furnace door. Whoa, wait, check, check, check, check. Always check, check, check, check, check,
check, check. Fucking can't even play this game. I'm fucking about to just rage quit and leave.
Fucking come on. No. I have to do it again. Oh, just have you both come out already.
Okay. Look out. Oh no. Watch out. There's a bomb over here. Oh shit. What's that?
Come here. Guys, I can't. What? Okay. I'm going to. Okay.
Why would you put that in this game? What's the point of that? It's just there to
be like a joke. Same one. I know. You don't think I know this? What do you think? You think I'm not
paying attention to what's happening? I know. I get it. I'm not. I know. I'm trying to make this
not a reality. I just. Armin again. Quick. Armin again. Armin again. You had to have seen me do
that. Okay. We all have five IQ. 37 fucking seconds. No, please. Just end this shit. It's right here.
2.6 IQ. Okay. Come on. Is this like for pity to make it so you don't get overwhelmed?
You give me your pain. I was just not hurting. Okay. Okay. All right. There's no bomb or anything
here. Open fucking door. There is nothing here that can hurt me. Nothing here can hurt me.
Nothing here. Okay. Nothing here can hurt me. There it is. I gotta stop this thing from
sliding down into his body. All right. It got it. I don't. I shouldn't just run up there though
because. Well, go on. Do your intro. We're rolling. You even put an innocent man in jail for your
crime all to preserve your perfect life. Couldn't stop the guilt from eating away at you rotting you
from the inside. So unless the officer you involved in your crime can hold the blame.
We will see what you really have. No, you're dead, man. You're dead. He's dead. He's not going to live.
He's not going to live. It's through this. Jason, it's been a real pleasure being your friend.
Oh, hurry the fuck up. Hurry the fuck up. It's a complicated thing. Stop.
How fast do I have to do this shit? Not going to work here.
Fucking hurry. Go. Stop. There's one. All right. It's going back up. I got it.
Okay. Now this one. And then. Shit. Now. Just suck your stomach in. It can't be that easy. It's not
that easy. I'm going for it, man. Just relax. Relax. There's another one. Done. Oh, this
one's a little weird. All right. Damn it. It can't be that. It's simple. Can it? Come on. One of
these. It's got to work. Come on. No. Get. Go up. I can't. Wait. Can I go up from like.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. Why'd you tell
me to do that? Okay. Now I can. Come on. Up like this and then. Reach. That doesn't reach. Why?
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. You're fine. All right. That's it. Right.
That's another one. Please. I got time. I'm hurrying. I'm going as fast as I can.
No. How is that not right? Give me control back. Then stop talking. Oh. Got it. Wait. What? No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. What am I doing? I went. I thought it was just for nothing.
Tap. You self-righteous son of a bitch. Easy, Jennings. You're just reacting to the shock.
Just calm down. You fuck. You fucker. You're the reason he picked me. You. Me? You killed a man.
You a murderer. He was homeless. He didn't have a family. He meant nothing to anyone. What about
the innocent man you put in prison? What about his family? What did you do? But he didn't have to
put an innocent man in prison?
Put him back.
I don't even want him about the steam. He'll figure it out. I need some help.
I got to get this camera out of here. The camera is the worst item in the whole game.
And here we go.
Before you are to do or test your faith,
continue blind with your sight intact. Make your choice quickly. When the timer reaches zero,
the bombs located all around you will detonate. Wait, what do you mean? Here's a path. Okay, this
one. Okay, so what? Am I supposed to not touch them? Did I just walk in a circle? Why? How are
they going to explode? Is it upstairs? Wait. Oh, wait. What the fuck is going on? That's right.
All right. I did it. One minute, 38 seconds left on the clock. There it is. Door sealed.
Wait, this is the beginning. How did I pick this one? Fucking hurry. What do you mean hurry?
This is the most disorienting thing ever. Oh, I have a map. Who cares? Just use the map.
No, no, you're not supposed to look at your map. Can I just have my head explode and just
pick the other door? This sucks. I'm stuck in a wall somewhere. Give me the other door. Fuck
this door. Give me the other one. Do you think when those explosions go off,
it saws upstairs in a chair and he like rocks? He's like, whoa. Where is he? You would feel that
everywhere in the whole fucking building. All right. I want to, let's go make your choice. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Don't do the one with the blind one. Oh, no, we're going this one.
Before you open your doors, each will test your faith. You continue blindly or face a greater
challenge with your sight intact. Make your choice quickly. Hopefully it's like four enemies
because that's not a challenge. Okay. Let's go this way. What's the greater challenge?
Nothing can be a greater challenge than that. Oh, no. I know how much you suck at this.
It's balanced over a board. No, I'm going to be squashed. It got me.
Sorry. That's way better. I don't care. It's fine. It's way better than the other one.
The other one's so bad. I wish I could skip this dialogue. Before you are two doors,
each will test your faith. Your sight intact. This one. Make your choice quickly. When the
timer reaches zero, the bombs located all around you will detonate. It's scary. Okay. Go.
Hey, good. All right. Is there a place where I can stop? Oh, shit. Oh, I don't know if I'm
in the right place. Don't wait. What the fuck? No way. What happened? Oh, come on.
Yeah, I was just blue. I was supposed to time that one. Why did it blow up your head? I don't know.
I leaned into it.
Okay. Is that enough room? Don't hit my arm. Holy shit. I made it. Okay. Good.
Now what? Wash your hands. Now what? Go over here. Nothing in here. What did I just take?
I don't know. This game is dumb. What happened? What did I just get? My hands. What did I just
get? I had to push. I knew what I got. Don't touch that. What? I got a coupler? Okay. Oh, yeah.
All right. Turn it off. Oh, okay. I'm not that bad at these. I'm pretty good at these.
There you go. Everyone's like, oh, he's going to fit. Nope. I don't know. There could be a
fucking bomb right there. I don't know, guys. What do you want me to do? What is that? It's
something in the... Pick up the... Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Where am I? Where am I going? Water bottle?
No, I want the water bottle. How do I get the water bottle? What does the water bottle pick up?
Okay. This is sealed. Go. I got to hurry. I know. Yeah. I'm going. There's a bomb. Find a key.
Find a key. I get it. I got a key. I got a pee really, really bad.
I got a pee really bad. I'll be right back. Take a pee break in a second. He has to clean the
pee up off the floor again. Where are you getting again from? What was the first time?
Somebody just walked around under there. Can I punch a flashlight with the hand?
You know what I was trying to say? What was that? Find a key to the utility door.
I'm so glad I have an actual flashlight. Open. Open. Yeah. Full health. That rat was huge. Yeah,
the rat was huge. What am I going to do about it though? Stunt trap schematics.
Okay. Ammonia. What do I do with the ammonia? And where's my gun? Where's my shotgun? Where's my
grenade? Got in here. Key in the toilet. Utility key. Tell the shit stain story.
Restore power to the security checkpoint gate and then enter the utility room.
Where's that utility room? It's over here. It's a pain in the ass to get back.
Paste file. Screenshot it if you want. Oh, a button. Doesn't work. Where am I going?
I need to go all the way around. Someone's going to jump at me or something, right?
Why the hell would they have this backtracking? Who doesn't love a good backtrack?
P story. I thought I went to the bathroom. P'd one time. P came out of me
every time that I go to the bathroom. I hope you're laughing at that one.
This is what happens to those who fail their tests or make the wrong choice.
Save this man, but you can save yourselves. Find the combination to open his cage and
reroute the power back to the two so quickly when he touches the water.
I need another number is okay. Oh, nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing. Uh, what's in here?
Nothing. What is this? Oh, there's a number on the wall here. It's five.
Five, five, two, three, five, one, two, five, eight, two, uh, jigsaw. What the fuck is all this?
Eight, three, six, six, two, one, two, six, one, five, six, five, six, five, five, three, five, two,
five. Like I just got hit in the head with a wrench and somebody came over. How many
fingers am I holding up? Um, holding up three was five, five, six, three, five, six, five, three,
six, two, three, six, two, two, six, three, one, five, five, five. It's not five. How much time do I
have? Oh, I got ages. Okay. Stand on the weight. Eight, six. Okay. Six is a number. Okay. Uh,
three, four, two. That's not it. Seven, six, five, five, three, six, five, three, six, five, three,
six, twelve seconds. Four three, five. Go this way. What are you doing?
Sensitivity on this thing sucks. All right. Four, three, five. Let's go.
That fast, didn't I? Wait, I need, where the fuck am I gonna get one of these?
Kidding me. Uh, Google dance. Pixel is reusing traps. Uh, is it in the room here? No, what
What about right here? Reusing breath. Stupid. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Got it.
Re-route the power. Oh, security checkpoint up the stairs. Goodbye, Jigsaw. It's been fun.
Oh, TV.
It would have easily been disabled by police procedure, but those procedures were ignored.
Who do you think ignored them?
It's the walking into the explosive trap. I killed him ironically, is what someone said.
I killed him ironically.
Alright, let's go.
Welcome back, detective.
Detective, what? Is that me? I'm dead. Is that me? Oh, my name's Todd? What's my name? Cap. Who's that?
Where are you? What the fuck are you doing? Why would you do that? What are you thinking? What's wrong with you?
Hey, any last words? Do it!
Please, you guys.
Oh, that doesn't happen to you guys.
Hey, you guys don't get... Oh, your head's squished.
Didn't he have a weapon? Where's his door shove?
Where's his weapon? He had a big bat. What the fuck is happening right now? Where's the bat he just had?
Finish the game already. Please, get me out of here. Wait, wasn't I already in here?
Locate the grave site. Please, locate the grave site. Toilet, uh, poopoo, haha. Ban that person for 10 minutes.
We gotta make an example out of this person. Ban them for 10 minutes.
Can I press the button? Oh, alright, I can press the button.
Dude, this is easy. This is fucking easy. This game is fucking easy.
Have you found your god? What happened in here?
Okay, that's...
See, I'm a good person. I will at least scroll so you can see it.
And if you want to roll back, you can read it.
Hustled room. What's that? Oh, somebody opened it.
Glass everywhere, please. Ooh, utility. Open this. I don't have... I need a circuit thing.
Oh, how far is this guy's reach?
A gun? Give me that gun. No, give me that gun. Give me that gun.
Why are you waiting for me to come down here? Only enough for me. Give me that gun.
I can use this, right? Please tell me I can use the gun. Yes. Yes.
What do you mean there's only enough in here for you? There's five bullets in here, dude.
Alright, I got a gun. How do you fire the gun? Can I snipe somebody?
Shotgun shell. I wish I could get a shotgun. That would be amazing.
Okay, nothing in here. What's the point of this? A flashlight. I already have one.
Lockpick, okay. Ooh, achievement.
Scalpel. Wait, scalpel versus gun? Are you kidding me? Do I even have to make this fucking decision?
Read that. I have so many achievables.
Oh, there was just a knife in here? Waste of time.
Now let's power this shit back on. I don't even have a map of this place.
Okay, on the only scalpel forever.
I'm going to try to use the gun wisely.
I keep walking on this glass. Does this guy have a healing on him?
Alright, I gotta be ready to fucking shoot somebody.
Alright. Yep, alright. What's wrong with me? What's going on?
What's that gas? Turn the gas off. I gotta turn the gas off.
Punch the door. Wait. Oh, please. Not this shit.
How the fuck am I supposed to get this?
Run out. Get out, get out, get out, get out. Heal.
Get out of the room. Get out, out, out, out, out, out of the room.
This door's sealed. I can't even heal. Do it. Drain the whole thing.
Oh, okay. I gotta have it be on here.
Fuck. There it is. Okay, that's that one.
Damn it. Heal. I can't see it.
I think this is it. I got it. Is it closed somehow?
This is fucking close to shit. I can't...
I don't know. I don't know. It's too fucking...
I'm dead. I'm dead. Just die. Oh, come on.
That was close too.
How far away was this? Imagine dying to pipe mania.
Yeah, imagine dying to fucking die.
What do you want me to tell you?
Where is this? How far away is this pipe wheel?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yup, yup, yup.
Okay, remember this guy?
I'll take that gun. Thank you. Okay. Good. Let's go.
All right. Get this right.
What do you mean he's doing the fucking dial?
What are you talking about? I didn't just pick it up?
Okay, there it is. There's that one.
Let's go middle. Out.
Fucking already dead.
Take a fucking heal. What are you doing?
I hate these fucking...
It's not even a puzzle. It's just like dumb.
I have to get the fuck out of here.
Fucking delete this game. Delete it.
Remove it. Delete from the Xbox.
Eat, drink, paint dinner.
I'm going to drink it. How do I drink it?
Oh, not you. Not you.
Hey, guys. I have an idea. No.
I'm saying in the game, I just picked it up.
No. What the fuck are you talking about?
What?
All right. I've got the coupling device.
Here we go.
Go back in and break the wall.
No. I don't want to.
I don't want to.
I just walk into a wall.
All right. Checkpoint.
Don't fucking move. Don't move.
I've got a gun. As you know, I have a gun.
I'm ready.
Who holds a gun like this, by the way?
This is the way you hold a gun
if you're afraid of what it's going to do.
I've got to get a brace to shit.
All right. Hold on.
I'm ready. I'm going to shoot somebody in the head.
Uh-oh.
I got him. All right.
I see it this time. I see it.
I see it. Okay.
It's not going to happen.
Y'all were waiting for it. It's not going to happen.
I saw them. Pick it up.
A. A?
Okay. That was stupid.
No more of those, right?
No more.
I saw it. Wait. No.
That's an arm? Okay.
I want to go up.
I can't make a mollusk.
Somebody's up here.
Ooh, a lock pick.
Damn it. Damn it.
I have a flashlight. Do they run out of battery or something?
Why do they keep showing up?
Breakable wall? How do I just punch?
I don't want to shoot the gun. How do I just punch?
No. You dumbass.
I just want to punch.
How do I drop the gun? I can't drop the gun.
There's no drop gun.
Heavy attack? No. I just tried to pick up.
Oh, well.
Left bumper?
Oh. Left bumper. Where's the gun now?
Okay. I'm ready.
Gas.
Stunt trap.
RB cycle. Stunt trap.
Do I just throw it at people?
Can I make anything else?
Yes.
Don't make me start doing that.
I don't want to start doing that.
Where the hell am I going?
Out in the courtyard. The graveyard.
This way.
This glass is just like fine.
Do I have no heels?
I don't have a heel. How the fuck is that possible?
I used them all?
Here, my honey. Please come down.
I made your favorite food.
Well, prove that you are who you're saying you are.
And what's my favorite food?
Hmm? Why don't you prove it?
What is it? Pop tarts?
Nope. Wrong.
It's not my favorite food.
Okay.
Sorry. Wrong.
McChicken? You know, it's close.
How do I get in here?
Go that way? Down there?
What is that?
Locate the grave site.
Salmon? No. Close, though.
Actually, not even close. Not even remotely close.
Oh, I have to trigger the event.
Okay, who cares?
Yeah, that guy kills people.
I know. I know.
He kills people.
Is there anybody behind me?
It's got kind of loud sounds behind me.
You guys hear that?
McChicken?
I mean, I love McChickens. Don't get me wrong.
What is my absolute all-time favorite food?
What's my favorite food?
I think I used that help.
Wait, I want to unlock that door down here.
Wobster? No. Gross.
Um...
It's probably chicken related.
I'm not sure it's chicken exactly.
It's probably chicken related, though.
This is a tough one.
It probably is like a good crispy chicken sandwich.
Bomb in here.
I need another...
What's that?
No, I don't care. I have a gun.
I don't need that.
Did I just waste one of those?
Can I take it back? Give me back.
Give that back.
Did I use it?
I think I used it.
Fucking hurry, hurry, hurry.
Oh, it's that thing.
I'm the McChicken guy thing, right?
Are we coffee pasta?
No, it's not.
Oh, gear, paint, and paint thinner.
All right, let me just get...
I have to do it, but I want the gun.
I don't want that.
I wasted a fucking gear.
All right, back out of here.
Bring that paint thinner.
All right, so now I just have to go back?
Do I have to just backtrack?
I mean, the guy was choking somebody up here, wasn't he?
What's the point of coming in here?
I didn't get anything new.
Is something else open?
I mean, I guess I have to go...
Where am I supposed to go?
In there somehow, but...
Go back?
How is he such a noob?
Who's hacked? Courtyard?
My stream got hacked.
I'm here.
Drop down here?
No.
We can't hear you.
You can hear me. I'm talking right now.
I did it. Oh.
What the fuck, dude? Come on.
What's going on here? Cut it out.
I'm not muted.
Now you're making me angry.
Now you're making me very angry.
I guess I could go back up here and look around.
Did I do everything up here?
Hit the mute.
What?
Fix it. There's nothing to fix.
Are you guys drinking?
Are you drinking or something? What's going on?
Let me go this way, I guess.
Holy shit.
I know I haven't been here yet because this is here.
Pick it up.
How close do I need to get to this before I can actually touch this fucking thing?
What the hell is going on?
I'm afraid to do this.
No shotgun or anything in here?
No. Alright, we're good.
Let's move. Careful.
That was so sloppy, but whatever. I'm here.
Your late partner holds the key.
Oh shit, this guy squished.
I can't go that way.
He's laughing?
Why is the violin doing the bug thing?
You know, I was telling something fucked up was about to happen.
Here come the bug's violin.
Somebody's laughing.
No, I don't want that.
Fucking holy shit. I almost walked into it.
What's that?
Where is it?
This is kind of scary, I'm not going to lie.
It's actually kind of scary.
What bandages? Why did I take these?
I need these.
No head exploder.
Okay.
I'm ready, I've got my gun.
I'm not afraid.
Okay, I got him.
There's more of you?
Alright, who do I shoot?
Who wins this fight?
Oh, the guy with the bat won.
Now I'm fucking coming for you.
Wait, no, he's still alive.
Get out. What? Who's doing that?
Where are you? Who's throwing those?
Is he above me?
Okay, where the fuck are they coming from?
Elizabeth?
There you are.
Is there a thing? There is a thing.
Is there a thing right there?
Got the key. There's one right here.
Okay, don't touch that.
Okay, bye. I'll save her life.
Anybody going to heal?
Holy shit, nice.
Oh my god, I get to do this. Where is he?
Hey, eat shit.
What was that?
There was a fire underneath me.
Okay, I'm actually glad that happened.
Oh, right.
I forgot that you exist.
Shoot him.
Fuck you. Get away from me.
Okay, let's go.
Don't just jump down.
Stunt trap.
How do I use the stun trap?
Alright, shoot him. Get up this time.
Did it actually go right?
Okay, this is fucking stupid.
Where's the molotovs?
They're like a case of them.
By the way, I got just lucky last time
because I ended up opening the right box.
You have to pick up the box that's on the right grave.
I didn't even look last time.
Did I? No, I didn't.
I just opened one.
Alright, we have our...
This is the final chance.
He's kind of getting sick of saying these lines.
Listen to how tired he sounds.
You gotta get the key.
Fucking, you know, whatever.
You're making this not fun anymore.
Oh, he's alive.
Alright, I just like...
I just like Vulcan neck pitched him
and he died.
Okay, don't fucking explode.
Don't get your head exploded.
There it is. Okay, disarm.
Now, what was the person's name?
Okay, I got molotovs.
Something Smith?
Something Sings?
No.
What the fuck?
There's another one. Watch it.
Jacob Schmidt? Director Stevens?
Okay, this is it.
I got the key to the Cedar Ward.
I'm ready.
I have five molotovs.
You have the key to Cedar Ward to save her life.
Got it.
Can I get a checkpoint, please?
We're completing that.
Search the Cedar Ward for Jigsaw's next clue.
Can I just walk through this?
What? The way that I said Jigsaw?
Who cares?
I said Jigsaw, I said it fast, whatever.
What's the point of this?
Stupid, what's this here for?
Why is this here? How can it happen?
Oh, that's not one. Yeah, I thought that was one.
This area contains violent patients.
Find shelter from the bombs.
Uh...
No, there's a bomb in here.
Wait, there's a guy in there.
There's a Minecraft guy in there.
What did that do?
I just powered something.
Sanctuary.
Did I miss something in there?
I tried pressing this button.
Oh, I had to be in the exact perfect location.
Okay, here we go.
Holy fuck, you just...
Alright, watch it, watch it, watch it.
Here we go.
What the fuck am I doing?
I just threw a bottle.
That wasn't a molotov cocktail.
It was just a glass bottle.
And I only had one.
Okay.
That was dumb.
Key pole. Uh, 838.
You just threw a piss bottle at him.
Oh, I don't have a weapon.
Or patience.
Do I have to wait for 40 seconds?
Close the door.
Now I have patience.
Holy shit, I did it.
Where's my key?
Ooh, a secret way to go.
Okay.
Gonna be in the toilet, right?
There it is.
That's really, really hard to not get done instantly.
Storage key.
Lock the storage door.
Okay.
Moving on.
I do have to say, I'm getting sick and tired of, um,
disarm the room full of cartoon dynamite.
You have no other tricks up your sleeve.
You ended his life.
Who saved yours?
How does Jigsaw call 911?
Does it just give two scenarios to the dispatch?
Also, bus full of senior citizens
is about to fall off a cliff
down on Fourth Street.
Are you safe?
All right, well, get me out of here.
First you took his father. Will you take his mother next?
What the brain?
Explosion rocks downtown.
Okay. Uh, you could read this.
Uh, wait, hell, this is about us.
Lead officer in the Jigsaw killer case
resigned yesterday due to unknown circumstances.
Shooting death earlier this week of his partner,
Detective Stephen Singh, is suspected to be a factor
in the resignation.
PAP could not be reached for comment.
PAP was a fine officer and a defender of the law
who will miss him.
Detective Mark Hoffman, a similarly
decorated officer,
will be taking over the lead position.
Okay, explosion tape, whatever it's called.
Uh, dear Mrs. Singh,
we have received notice from Stanworth Elementary
that you have not responded to concerns
raised by your son Franklin's school counselor.
Okay, please
respond within 10 days.
Uh, kind of
this apartment is something going on.
Fire detective David Tapp
has antics got his partner Stephen Singh killed
which in my book makes him too dangerous to carry a gun.
Who knows when he plans to go rogue.
Criminal charges against
Tapp. Got my husband killed.
He's no better than Jigsaw.
Right, stick it to him. Some lore there.
Pfft, you
already there? I guess not.
What tapes?
Look at what you did in here!
Look at the true
destroyer of
lives.
It's me. Okay, let's
get the key.
You destroyed their lives.
I just tortured them to
death and killed them. Here we go.
Who said that? Here we go.
Looks like we're going in here.
Tortured to death AND killed?
Say it ain't so.
Yeah. He's leaving me notes
on how to make stuff. Jigsaw,
you know, you could just be a
DM.
I feel like that's a good avenue for you.
You don't have to do all this fucking weird shit.
Wingless angels
must fall. Wingless
angels must fall.
Sure. Okay.
What was that? Is somebody here?
Nothing to the work. I need a
weapon. Oh, there's
a weapon. Am I
safe? You and LSD
fucking messes you up.
Where is this person? Alright, I'm getting the bat.
He's not going to be there.
Skip steps.
Oh, you idiot.
Alright, now I got a
bat. Nothing scares me now.
I'm going to try DMT.
No. Alright, I'm ready.
I'm going to gear. Oh, it's
the TV's doing this shit.
Falling. Falling. Falling.
Angel. Alright, come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Big money.
Big money. Big money. Come on. No whammies. No whammies.
No whammies. No, come on. Big money. Stop.
Ugh.
Oh, you are here.
Hey.
Can you open the door?
I'm being such a fucking weirdo.
It's a letter. There's a flashlight.
There's a lighter. No, it's a lighter. I don't want
a lighter. Why would I want a lighter right now?
It's so much worse.
Alright, open these doors.
Power this thing. Alright, well.
Let me time this up.
That guy's
not scary.
I need one of those stupid things.
I can't go in here.
It's just sitting in one of these dumb drawers that I didn't look in.
Is it in a drawer or something?
Where the hell is this?
Of course, right there. Give me a room.
Okay.
Let's do the same puzzle that we've done already
a thousand times except it's way bigger
now.
What the fuck am I supposed to do about this shit?
I
I hate this. I don't want to do this.
I'm done.
I'm fine. I don't want to do it.
I'm done. I don't want to do this.
I'm done. I don't want to do it anymore.
I'm done. Okay, I finished it.
Open this door.
Alright, now you can close your mouth
because you're irritating.
And I will take an upgraded bat
too, thank you.
Oh my god. Bonk.
That's funny.
Do I have to destroy the angels?
Wait, this is not an angel.
Oh, I do.
Okay, that was easy.
Okay.
Oh my god, a ton of money came in.
I just really lucked it.
Ishanji gave $70.
7,000 bits.
And this is, I believe, like an hour ago.
Enable face cam.
Slash enable face cam. Slash disable
flaccid lock.
Slash hug germa.
I don't know any of that. I don't understand
that line of Java
that you just put in. Okay.
Thanks for the 7,000 bits.
Thanks for the $70.
Is that why you guys are saying hack?
That's 70 fucking bucks. Thank you.
And then non-descript civilian
gave 10 community subs.
Thanks for the huge amount of money, guys.
Thanks for the gigantic pile
of money that you just dumped
right onto my lap.
I'm just like scooping it up as we talk.
Ah, thanks. What's that?
This guy's got a cube.
Alright, if you're going to explode
then just don't come over here.
Wait, if he punches me
is he going to blow up my head?
I drop this switch and boom.
Well, don't let it go.
Out of my way.
This thing's wired to blow.
It's going to blow us all up.
We're all going to die.
Press A.
Out of my way or
this thing will explode.
Careful with that guy.
If he lets go of that thing, we're all going to blow.
What the fuck is this in here?
Ooh. Alright.
Wait. Come over here.
Follow me.
Where is he?
Okay, now I've got to open
this door. Here we go. Ready?
Oh, he had a coupler.
If I get down there
how do I get down there from here?
This is crap.
I just have to do one.
Alright, well that was easy.
Anything else? I need health.
Alright, turn it off.
Turn the fucking thing off, man.
It's off, right? That could be me.
Alright. I wonder how
far ahead to the game is over.
Anybody have any idea?
How close am I to the end of the game?
I feel like I'm getting close.
Okay.
I mean, I think I'm here.
Tap. Tap in.
Tap in. Tap.
Tap time in. Time. Tap in.
Alright, I'm tapping in.
Rescue Melissa Singh.
Don't move. Don't move.
I'm coming up there and I'm going to
cut the blue
wire or whatever I need to do. I'm coming.
I'm going to do this elaborate
fucking puzzle. She's dead.
I'm an iron maiden.
Time for a lawsuit.
Okay. Magnetic
puzzle.
Move. What am I moving?
Okay. We're moving down. Then we're moving
down.
Oh. Okay.
Whatever. I skipped the steps.
He'll be fine.
And then we got to go over.
Then we got to go up, left, down.
And then right.
And then down. And then she's going to get
killed. I
think.
Okay. I did it. The game doesn't even
care. I win.
Hey, don't worry. He fucked up the programming
on this thing. I'm going to get you out of here.
Oh. That one worked.
Only one more. Oh.
This is the fastest probably anyone's ever done this in the
game. Okay.
This one. Whatever. We're going this way.
Alright.
Cool. Wait. That one worked.
That was a six, right?
How do I salvage this?
Fuck up, Jigsaw.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Hurry, hurry. I'm only
four hundred pounds. Beat me more.
I'm up to five hundred
pounds. That's not enough.
Yeah. Is the game over?
Does escape suck? Anybody aware of that yet?
Oops. Sorry.
Oh.
Oh. Okay. You mean that
storyline wise. Okay. Let's go.
Escape with Melissa. Find the
clue. Alright, Melissa.
Follow me. Hey.
You good with the gun? I know a thing or two.
Oh. Awesome. The best line
that you could just say. Literally everyone, every
fucking person says that in every movie.
Every TV show doesn't matter. Every single
one. Nice.
And then they spin.
Flip, flip, click, load, snap,
snap, zip, flip. Oh, you know, you might.
You've used a gun, I think, before. Yeah.
I have. Whoa. Nice.
That's surprising to me. Your character
does not seem to be
somebody that would use a gun like that well. You've
surprised me. Thank you, every movie.
I'm sorry, David. You deserve this.
He said if I made it this far, I could choose
to leave. Oh, no. You're taking the headphones?
I'm not. Sorry. Oh,
please. There's a trip to Hawaii
at the end of this. You fucking idiot. Nice. Thanks.
I'm going to get the trip to Hawaii. You can go fuck off.
Yeah, take your, like, seventy-two
dollar headphones. I'm getting a seven-thousand
dollar trip to fucking Hawaii. What an idiot.
We're so close to the end, too. You're going to
take the fucking. Unbelievable. What a moron.
You paint these?
Right now, Jigsaw is sitting there
really getting a little nervous.
Oh, everybody takes
the fucking headphones.
That's getting close. I'm not really
going to have to pony up, like,
seven grand.
Usually they're dead
two hours ago.
I have a spiked bat.
More TVs. Okay.
You want to step closer to solving
the puzzle of catching me?
It is a dangerous game,
detective. Best games
always are. Ah, you know, I'll take the
headphones. Never mind. I'll take the headphones.
This is, ah, I don't care.
Locate the puzzle pieces
in pine, ward, find,
whatever. Let me guess.
Key in the toilet. Oh,
I wonder. Hmm.
Nope, man, this is something different.
This is a gear in the
toilet. So many little treasures
inside of the syringe
toilets. All right. There's somebody
in here that I got to save
or find or I don't know
where. I still have this thing on my
head.
Same shit every time.
I'll be honest.
Just let it be open. Just open it.
That puzzle doesn't
it's not even there for any reason.
Why is it there?
Just let me open the cabinet at some point.
Right? Like it doesn't do anything.
How that works.
Um, I mean,
okay, if it were me,
well, I could just leave without a
problem. Somebody's here.
Okay, are we ever going to find out who's the
person that's upstairs making all that noise?
Hold it from the other side.
And look at this.
I'm here.
I'm coming.
Yes. Am I the
I'm scary. I'm the scary
guy. Where are you?
Oh, what happened?
Did I? Why do I feel like I did that?
Hey, hey!
Get away. Get away. Get away from me. Get away from me. Get away from me.
I'm sneaking through. Get away from me,
please. What?
Is it still blinking?
Why did mine blink? Did I get
Wait, was that a shotgun thing?
Was it a tripwire?
No, it wasn't.
Was it?
Oh, come on.
It was? No,
shit. Are you kidding me?
That's so stupid.
Oh, my God.
I don't like the lamp.
Use the paint thinner bomb?
I don't even know how to use this.
RB. How do I use
it, though?
RB.
Like RBX
or something? Is this a juke classic?
Sick.
There are four traps in the entire game.
Use RB.
I'm doing it right now.
Jigsaw's plan here. Kill a hundred people just to convince
someone that they're not, that they're kind of a dick?
Yeah. I mean,
that's kind of every one of these movies.
It kind of stems from
you are a
Alright, roll this at him.
Throw it?
I got you.
You piece of shit.
Ah, you couldn't squeeze through the wall.
I could.
Wait, did he squeeze through the wall?
He's gone now. Not my problem.
Oh, my God.
If I didn't
stop.
If I didn't stop,
it would have happened again.
I hate that.
What a dumb thing to have in this game.
Sometimes you're just going to get your
head exploded.
The goal here, I don't know,
is to locate the puzzle pieces in Pine Ward.
I'm about to take the headphones.
So, God, I'm sorry.
What have I done? What do you do?
It's a heal.
It's like I'm kind of just pissing into the wall here.
Alright, what was that?
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
You don't have anything else.
Turn on the lights.
Okay, one.
Same shit again.
I just paint numbers on
walls in
a 207.
Oh, look out. I painted a number on
a wall.
You'll never find out what the solution is.
207.
Which one is this? 209.
It's 208.
It's going to be, I know, there's going to be something here.
It's just shooting the head.
What is his name? Remember his name?
You couldn't protect anyone.
Okay, let's go. Oh, come on.
Come on.
Bag of puzzle pieces. One, I thought that said 12.
This is going to be an unpopular opinion
and I cringe at the amount of letters this paper will
receive.
I think this is a Reddit post.
I'm going to propose the following. What if the jigsaw killer is good for our moral fabric?
If you follow the
methods of the jigsaw killer closely,
you might see what he's trying to do.
Make people better themselves. This is one of those comments
that you have to go all the way down and you have to click
the show deleted comment because it's got
minus 500
clicks on it.
It's been negatively downvoted so many times.
This person is fucking nuts.
I got one of two puzzle pieces.
Another one of these unpopular opinion pieces.
Lies corrupt. Remember being
slandered. How does it feel?
How does it feel? I don't know.
Okay.
The timer stopped? Oh, the timer stopped.
Nice. Why'd the timer
stop? Fuck off.
Lockpick to get a lockpick.
Give me a fucking break. Wait, somebody's talking.
I heard somebody.
Turn on the lights.
Find the room before the boom.
Okay. Let's keep going.
I didn't go in 206.
Just nails. Cool.
Wow. Should I even open
I don't think there could be a thousand dollars
in those and I don't even care.
Good. You found the pine ward piece.
Find the other pieces
in the oak ward to save life.
This is just the beginning.
How does it feel to be judged for
auctions? Alright, what's the time to beat on this?
I'm going to look it up for me real quick.
There's a saw for the
Xbox 360.
This is five hours?
Six, five, six hours?
Oh shit.
Alright, I'm getting. Can I fall
in this? No, that
I didn't even
do that. Okay, whatever.
That's so dumb.
Literally one person
said five.
That is the name
you have given me.
Your words have changed how people
perceive me, regardless
of the truth. Now that your words
are useless, what is
left?
Hmm, I'll see if
I can come get you.
Six to seven hour game.
Well, that's to get the
vacation. You know, I
still have an opportunity to get the headphones.
You know what I'm saying?
That's the same joke. Well, it's
relevant to how much longer I want to
stream this game for.
I wish I had the gun
right now. Why can't I not have the gun?
Wait, stun trap. How do I
throw?
Nice.
You're the reason I'm here.
You did this. You're the reason.
You're the reason this
is all happening. I want that key.
What's wrong with him?
Why is he losing health?
Wait, he can come up here?
That's the game.
It's alright. Okay, well now I know
what's going on.
Stun trap. I got like a thing that said
activate the stun trap. How do I do
that?
Alright, it's a
stun trap.
I'm just doing this again. I'm going to cheese this
again.
Wait, wait. What?
Why is he starting to bugle very
This is really important for me to see if I can do this.
Is that hurting
him? Damn it, it's not hurting him.
I wish it was.
That's a flashlight. Fuck, he's kicking
my ass.
Alright, I got the health back.
Can I get his weapon?
He was very nonchalant about
that whole thing too. I'm going to get
that key. You're the reason I'm here.
I'm here because of you.
You're the reason why I
got into this situation in the first place.
I don't want the camera. Fuck the camera.
Explosive trap schematic.
What's in there? Never that easy is it.
Never that fucking easy is it.
What the fuck?
Really? That cog besides the
other cog. I don't even know what you're talking about.
Now I've got to connect this.
Done. Why is it so loud?
Because this game is not
good. I don't know.
I think this game expected me to run
around all over the place. Fight this guy.
Why do I still want to play this though?
This is strange. I shouldn't
want to still do this.
Turn this shit off.
Wait, why is this open? This was just
open. This used to be open. Why is this not open anymore?
That was open before. Why is it
closed? I closed it.
How did I close that? What did I
do? Oh, I pressed
this button. Tell me the next
part. How would I? No.
Alright TV, tell me what to do.
Zero seconds left.
Hello TV.
Tell me what to do. Why is the TV
not telling me what to do?
I guess I can go over here.
What is this for?
Turn this on?
Do I just turn it on? What if
I think somebody is out here?
Did I get them? Is somebody following me
around? Somewhere?
Where are they?
Is this all for the other guy
to immerse? Oh shit, yeah, big bits.
Big bits.
I think this is for that other boss
that I just was fighting.
We had 10,000
hits.
I fucked it up? How did I fuck it up?
It's 100 more dollars. It's fucking
insane. Thanks for the 100 bucks
slime for
10,000 bits.
Thanks for giving me and my friends so many laughs over the years.
I've been watching since early TF
tuber days. It's a long time.
The content's always been something me and my friends
quote all the time. I'm fucking quotable.
I never get to catch the streams, but just
wanted to donate and show my love for all the years of laughter.
Hey well,
here's a new quote for you.
Rome wasn't built in the day.
Go for it anyway. Don't step in that.
Sick ride.
All right.
It still wants me to fight a boss.
I've already fought him and I've already killed
him. I'm about to take the headphones.
Where are they? I'm about to take them.
I'm going to take the headphones I think.
Where does this want me to go? Just straight then bang
a left and go straight. I'm stupid. What's the point
of the glass?
I'm just going up.
Right, okay. Did I just do that?
Oh, wait.
Where's this person?
Why did I shoot him?
He was going to die anyways by walking into the fire.
You're going to spawn camp me?
You even let me come out of the spawn?
Oh, there he is.
Okay. I have to get the really
embarrassing head shot.
Remember doing this shit to people in
Team Fortress?
And the door would open, close, open, close. You'd kill everybody in there
and then there would be a sniper.
The door would open, boom! You got head shot.
It was insanely embarrassing because you were spawn camping.
This is so dumb to aim.
I didn't get him.
Is he still up there?
I can't see.
Fire, go away.
I don't have anything on me. Fucking scream.
I'm going to scream, I think.
Explosive trap.
Make two of them.
Gas trap. Make another one.
How the fuck do I use these things?
I don't even know how to use them.
RB. Yeah, but
L2 and R2?
That doesn't do anything.
Falsely accused.
Crank the sink.
What the hell was the point of that?
Key in the toilet?
There are no toilets in here.
Let's go that way.
How do I get over there?
Because we just go.
Easy bake oven waiting room?
See you on Friday.
Fucking hundred and fifty.
It's another one of those tax bracket increasing screams.
Holy shit, guys.
Ready dread.
Hundred and fifty dollars.
Just woke up? Did you have to restart the game again?
Yes.
I think when you were here, yeah, I had to restart twice.
The second time was
a trillion times worse than the first.
Because I was an hour into the game.
Thanks for the hundred and fifty fucking dollars.
Thanks for the hundred and fifty bucks.
Thanks for the insane amount of money.
I'm gonna nail this guy, okay.
He keeps wanting to give me the camera. I'm gonna take it.
Don't ask me why I'm doing this, but I'm doing it.
I'm taking the camera.
Where does it want me to go?
Locate more puzzle pieces in the oak ward.
Fuck, I missed the shot.
Do it again. How did you get up there?
Alright, the camera's the stupidest thing.
I'm putting it back.
I don't want it. It sucks.
I don't care. This thing eats total ass.
Why would you ever use this?
It wants me to use it so bad.
But no.
I can't even find the flashlight anymore.
Is it gone?
It was back behind that door. Pain in the ass.
Oh, it's the worst.
It's the worst. It's the worst.
We were the same person.
I believe that credit should be given
where credit is due.
You ruined the man's life
with your constant insinuations.
Words are
powerful, Oswald.
But so are actions.
Glad I still have this stupid ass camera.
This thing's going to get me killed.
You know what the hell happened in here?
This one doesn't look winnable.
That thing looks like it just kills you.
Closer than we think.
What if Jigsaw is one of the officers
that's tasked to catch him?
Say, detective. Tap.
They think it's me.
Wow, somebody else is the reason.
Not me this time. Interesting.
Ow. What did he say ow for?
Holy shit.
Who's going to win the game of
Rock'em, Sock'em, Robot?
He still thinks he's alive.
Over here.
No, don't even use a bullet on him.
Put the gun down.
I want to drop the gun.
Did he drop the gun?
Why use a bullet on him?
Where's the gun?
I was going to say that's
going to be really fucking dumb.
I fucking hate this game.
Did I get him?
Alright, gun. Let's go.
Don't step on this
stupid thing. Look, you can't see this shit.
Give me the lighter. Thank God
I can get rid of this stupid thing.
It's worth doing this every time because
you get the health. I need it.
Add.
Alright, let's move.
Now I gotta go to Oak Ward.
Is it this way or the other way?
Doesn't look like it's this way.
Somebody painted stuff here.
Why is this game
long?
It's not.
It's kind of not.
It's only been five hours.
I think it just feels that way because the game is
not good.
It's not very good.
But, you know,
it's fine. Okay, we need the last
puzzle piece and then I'm going to
assume that this is the climax of the game.
Are you kidding me?
What's the
password? Dude, can you just tell
me? Move them?
Am I going here?
Wait, you got
what is the password?
You already have the password.
What's the password? Somebody just have it?
What is it? I don't care. Fuck it.
I'll do it. What is it?
I don't care. What is it?
I'm serious.
Somebody has to just look it up, right?
74?
That's not it.
264.
Someone will have it eventually.
457.
556.
985.
7...
797.
775.
765.
702.
No, that's...
Okay, what?
I'm not trying to be funny. I just want you to tell
me the answer. I'm going to look it up.
I don't want to go get it.
No, it's going to take too long. Fine.
4...
You keep saying the same one. 435.
That's not it.
No, it's not.
It's in this link.
I tried to look it up. It's not in the guide. Yes, it is.
Rome wasn't built today, but go for it anyway.
Don't step in that.
Jeremy here. What?
I just tried to look it up.
Where is it?
It's going to be right here. Where is it?
I don't see it. Where is it? Where is the number?
Okay, number, number, number, number, number.
Where is it? I don't see a number. No number.
Am I locked in here now?
Cool. Okay.
Um...
What is this solve?
I can get to the door.
I win.
Wait, is it not...
Was I not supposed to do that?
Go, go, go, go!
What happened to the puzzle up there?
Did I miss it or something?
Rigid arms contain the code.
Sucks.
I turn this on.
Spotlight. See, this is what it looks like from my angle.
This is what it's like to beat the streamer.
You guys see from over here.
And it's like, wow, there he is, like on stage.
This is what I see.
My internet turn off?
Oh, hold on, let me fix it.
Hold on, let me fix it, let me fix it, let me fix it, let me fix it.
Hold on, let me fix it, let me fix it, let me fix it.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Fiverr omega lol.
I gotta change my server.
It's all fucked up. It's the server.
Alright, I'm, hold on.
I will be back in ten seconds!
Hey, and we're back.
What's going on? Welcome back to the show.
We're here? I'm here, right?
Yeah, I'm good. Alright, yeah, we're good.
Sorry about that. I, uh, VPNed. I was using the server.
I was on fucking shit the bed.
Hey, you gotta fucking have that fucking good security though.
You know what I'm saying?
This is the last thing you heard me say.
206.
Are you kidding me?
Slander is not an easy thing to face.
Okay, goodbye.
Thanks.
Can I walk on this? What the hell is this?
Why did I end up?
Can I walk on that?
I feel like I can't.
What the fuck was the point of that?
That's the strangest thing I've ever seen.
God, that was just odd.
Abnormal.
Alright, back to that
door with the thing on it
that adds 206.
Now what? Is there a timer going up?
My god.
I can't be serious.
You can't be fucking serious.
God. Where's the valve?
Where's the valve?
I don't even have any
fucking healing.
I'm about to fucking die.
Turn it off. I can't.
I get it? Take the headphones.
They're right there too.
I could just get them right now. I could grab them
right now.
They're right there.
The headphones are right fucking there.
This is the minor
I could get the minor prize.
Prize right now.
Where did I just end up?
Where the hell am I going?
I don't know.
I have to go down.
What a dumb system.
Puzzles. Not even a puzzle.
It's just anxiety
I'm doing it first try. Open it.
No stop you
over sensitive piece of shit.
It changes from fucking on you
really fast. Where is the
right one? What the
fuck is happening?
Where is it?
It's a
game.
This is a three on rotten tomatoes.
I mean the movie
too. Both of them.
What was the point of this? To get another just to get
replace my gun? Really?
That fucking prize is looking kind of
good.
They can't be much longer.
Can't be much longer than this.
There's so much left.
They can't be.
When I get out of this
and I get to the
I have to get the second puzzle piece
key. Then I'll determine
if I'm going to take the prize or not. That's
on me to decide.
Where the fuck am I going? Use 206 to gain injury into the
objective room.
Where is that?
Where are we going here? That's death. I would have just
walked into that and died.
What is this?
Why am I laughing at that?
Up the stairs?
Does anybody have any
idea where this is supposed to be?
I don't remember anything.
A puzzle. Oh I wonder.
Wait I remember this part.
Isn't it like up here?
It's up here.
I out here and then
this way.
Click on down.
Alright.
Can't make anything.
Can't get out of this.
Squeeze.
Still playing this?
Go this way.
Why not have an arrow?
Why is there to be a star?
Why not
a pointing arrow?
I need the arrow to point in the direction
that I need to go.
I need a GTA thing up here.
Don't fall off this. I'll be extraordinarily upset.
Damn I want pizza.
206.
Bomb.
Shoot the lock. It doesn't work like that.
Alright.
Well he's dead. Good.
Why is the music still doing this?
Molotov. I have 5 Molotovs.
But I want the gun.
Let's just have fun with them for a second.
Is it it?
I got 2 of 2 puzzles.
Alright return with the puzzle pieces to the trap entrance.
Where the hell was that? Who knows?
I feel like I'm playing Resident Evil.
But
just not even close.
Have a good night.
Should we do a good night? Should I leave?
You guys want me to go?
You guys want me to leave?
Alright where the hell is the trap entrance?
Here I guess?
You're at the end.
I feel like I am at the end.
You know what? I'm definitely
can't give up now.
To get pizza.
Yeah I'm going to get a big pizza.
The biggest pizza you've ever seen.
30 minutes max.
Okay.
Quick I want a fall joke.
I don't think you're going to get one of those.
Fall joke requires a checkpoint.
That is within about 5 seconds of my last
attempt.
This way.
Backtracking bullshit.
Is it an explosive?
No it's just stairs.
I just saw a line and I freaked out.
Oh you're killing people.
You are absolutely murdering.
You're slaughtering people.
I can tell my man with your words.
That did nothing to you.
It's two heels I feel like.
Quick quick quick.
The gas is going to fill the room.
Where is it?
The gas is going to fill this whole fucking room.
Come on.
Where is it? I knew it. I told you.
I did it on purpose.
That was on purpose.
I knew it because I wanted to fucking.
Let's go. That was on purpose.
On purpose.
Wasn't pretending. On purpose.
Fucking the checkpoint is right there.
Where is this fucking thing?
Take it please.
No. Okay.
Next up is.
I don't know man.
How the fuck am I supposed to know?
That's not right.
That's it.
What happened? Why is it not doing it?
Oh it's not correct.
Do another one. Do another one.
Do another one. X.
What are you doing? I'm hitting the
button X. The button fucking
X. X button.
Okay. You decide to do it now.
What happened here?
These fucking absolute dog shit.
Really? No.
Fuck. It's like right fucking
there. It's so close.
But it's just so fucking far
away at the same time.
Just kill me.
Am I just putting this in the game like
more than five times?
Imagine not going inside out.
Fucking
forgot it was in the room.
Fucking hate this.
I need that major prize.
I'm not vetoing it. No. No. No.
No. No. I got it. I got it. I'm gonna calm down.
I'm gonna settle down.
This is gas and booby trap.
This is not even
soft. This is fucking
Kevin McAllister does this shit.
Not Jigsaw.
Okay. Let's go.
Inside out.
I don't even know what inside
out should even be.
All I see is shapes. I don't see
anything else. All I see is shapes.
I don't see anything else but shapes.
It's just shapes. Nothing else.
Why would I go inside out?
Outside in? That's what I was doing.
Why would you tell me to go inside
out? That's not right.
That's not right either.
That's not right either. That's right.
This is the one. This is the one.
Okay. Alright. Alright. Alright.
Heal. Fucking
heal. Heal.
Use it.
I don't want to do this again.
Okay.
I don't even care. I don't even want to look at it.
I'm going. I don't even want to look at it. I don't even care.
Where's my lighter?
Now what? Over here?
Okay. Now we have made it. Then go left.
Solve the puzzle to open the trap door.
Solve the puzzle. Solve the puzzle. Solve the puzzle.
Find the truth.
Okay.
Oh no. No.
No. No. Not these. Not one of these.
Wait.
It's a brainless
version. Thank god it's a brainless version.
Holy shit. I'm so happy
that this is just an absolute moron edition.
Where's this other piece of his face?
Where's his face?
Where's the piece of his face? Where's his other cheek?
There it is.
This is the wrong spot.
Okay. Hold on. Let me just get it right.
Okay. And then...
Saw on a wheelchair?
I don't remember. Is he?
Now we got to do... Where's this piece go?
Okay. Now we got to go right here.
And then...
His shoulder.
And then this piece goes over here.
No. It doesn't. Where's his shoulder go? Right here.
And then this piece... I don't know.
It's got like a...
I don't know.
And then this goes over here.
And this goes right here.
And this goes here.
It goes down here.
And this goes...
over here.
I win. Time to find the truth.
This is the end of the game. It has to be.
Four minutes for this.
Why'd you do that, man?
Wait. Who?
Who is supposed to do that?
Was he supposed to do this?
Get up. You're an asshole.
What do you think I'm doing?
Where's the...
Where's the power source?
It's complicated, Frank. Whatever your name is.
It's hard to do.
And then...
Why's everybody so rude?
I'm going as fast as I can.
Okay. And then this now
has to be changed.
Better than this.
This is not correct.
It's got to be...
Yep. You're alright.
Stay tight.
Hang tight there for a second.
Oh my god.
I should just shoot him.
This is a joke, right?
This is a joke?
This goes down.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
This goes like this.
This connects up here.
This one goes like this.
This one connects up here.
This one goes this way. This one connects up this way.
This one connects this way.
This one goes this way. This one connects up here.
This one connects like this.
This one connects like that one.
This one connects up here.
This one connects like this.
All there.
This one like this.
Here like that.
Here like this.
This one like this.
Up here.
Like this.
And then...
Oh I fucked up.
I.. I..
This is the dumbest thing ever.
But I didn't what I just do
Every single one of these has just been am I okay? Is this the witness?
I'll go over here and do this line puzzle and then walk over there and do that line puzzle and then do that line
Puzzle and then do this line puzzle
Waste of time that was a waste of time go and connect connect hurry up and connect
Shut up. I don't mean talking to me. I don't like it
Is it more than one after this?
Thank you, sir. This is the last one. Okay, I got three minutes to get this dumb shit ready
Okay, we're going sideways sideways sideways connect these ones
These ones in connect. No, there's another one after this then like this. I don't know. I don't know man
I just I'm lost on this shit. I really am I don't do this kind of shit. It's like a fucking mathematician bullshit
Shit
God it's wrong. It's wrong on every level iron and I know that
Fuck you guy, fuck you guy. I'm working shit. How do I get you connected to this? Yeah?
It's over we're still here still trapped you just swap shackles
Did you see what he looked like anything
by a scumbag like you dirty
What did he look like I don't know we're checking my mail then going to get some water and
He's just listening. He's just right there. I
Think I know who Jigsaw is. I think he's in this place. We just need to find him. Oh
mega lol
Asia
There's more to this
Slow down wait for me
Find jigsaws next clue
Say
I know I know the developers thought it was real cute to put this shit everywhere
I know you got a colleague called him he did safe to go down here
Dude explains like the glass
the RC cars that are on the fucking ground I
Don't know about this. I don't know about this. I don't know about this
Thought somebody said I do guy I thought you said I had 30 minutes left
Was that was that was it just bullshit pick up stun traps schematics already have this
You give me shit. I've already gotten
flashlight thank God
Never put this down. I don't touch that
It's three more boss puzzles
Be real with me or is that true?
Correct wait, but there's like there's like five more hours left one more. This is it. What do you mean?
Oh
We actually know
Listening to these people and play the game. Okay. What's that eat eat eat eat eat?
Let's call it an explode. He's dead locate the crematorium. We did the second floor
Hey
I'm standing on the objective right now. This is the crematorium or something. I don't know
That's turn this steam off
Actually three more omega lol, actually three more actually three more whatever I
Get to the second. How do I turn this shit off?
Got the key
to go down
Ten hours left. I have played this is only one more
When I just down here, I don't think so you
See the chest over here. I looked it up two to three hours left, man
I'll keep this fuck the gun. I played it. There's like another at least an hour or two
I'm gonna get to the end and fucking quit the game, aren't I?
I'm gonna get to the very end and I'm gonna quit the game. I
Got I have to follow the rules though
No streaming past six hours. That's the that's a rule. I can't break it. I
have to medically, uh
But I can't just take the minor prize
Was that letter because you bet your ass I'm never opening this game again, like wait, I'm not gonna play this game again
Why would I do that?
Can't even make it play it tomorrow. No, I do. I I think you're misunderstanding me
I don't want to play this game again. Like I don't want to play this game. Oh, just do it tomorrow
No, I don't want to play this game again
This is one and done man. I don't want I
Locate the crematorium
What's the what's the coach giving me? I don't care. Somebody has to know it
Somebody has to know this code
You guys have probably read ahead in the guide like three hours already. What is it?
Don't you know tell me tell me don't tell him tell him tell me I don't care
I don't I'm not gonna go look for this seven. We have not somebody did chat can't do it. Yes, they can
five
Up trusting Chad
Actually 420 is it it's it's 420. It's 420
Okay, if it's not 420, you're in big trouble all of you collectively you're all in trouble now all of you
Perch the chat just once just to let him know
seven one six
Needs to play the game who needs to play the game when you can just fucking cheat
Who's me you?
You're dead. Okay, good
Free Victoria. Oh, it's just like I was half a guy. Oh
Okay, the trap
Molotov oh the security door
I'm just let's go. I mean like let's go. I
Wanted to listen anymore TV bullshit
No one wants to do these have you ever woken up?
Just you brush your teeth and shit and you get ready and you're like, you know what I would love to do today
It's like electricity pipe puzzle thing the thing that like nobody's wanted to do since like the fucking 80s
Nobody wants to play this. Nobody wants to do this. No one wants to play this nobody I do. No, you don't know
You really don't I know you don't
I'm certain that you don't I'm positive
You don't have to you don't have to pretend with me. I know
This is gonna be connected up here
Okay, open the fucking door
Ever this app on my phone. It's fun
Yeah, you probably played it once and then you just uninstalled it and you were like, oh that was fun for five minutes
Those things are like a fun little like in the newspaper brain teaser
We want to do it. Yeah. No, you that's true
Yeah, you did install that played it and you realize there was an ad every fucking two games and you were like
I don't want to play this anymore. I'm done
Why would I want to watch a 30-second ad every time I do a five-minute puzzle?
No, thanks
With the TV turned on I made this game leading I did I press the button
Now we turn on the electricity we just electrocute the guy there's gonna be a guy over here and he's gonna freak out and
Break through a wall then I can electrocute him
Why even like just hit him head
What
I don't know. Oh, no, you've attracted a guy
Careful this guy coming
You're scared
by a surgeon's hand
Flashlight already got it point
Okay, the crematorium
It's this way
Sorry, you got a fucking go around the circle locked one of these guys again
Okay, well open the door and just let the guy get
Try this guy's not gonna attack me while I'm doing a puzzle, right?
You wouldn't like it
I know you
Okay, I'm opening everything it's a waste of time. I don't know
This sometimes like valves in this shit that I need to pick up and I won't let's go. I'm fine. There's nothing there
You're right. So what's the point? It's gonna be
X marks the spot. There's a button explode that almost killed me
A little close. What's even in there? There's nothing in this. It's empty
How'd you do that? All right
Fuck are you thinking man?
Get away from me, please
That's that close the door. He's dead. He should explode by now, right?
Okay, he had to have exploded
All right X mark I gotta go to that X or something or I don't know
This is I like this part. Okay slow
Then I'll break the wall
There's the X okay found it. That's a pretty good run pretty quick pretty good speed run on this body
wire
We've got a pair of scissors. Oh
then
frozen hand surgeon hand holds a key
What have you say
Or so
Crazy and stuff. I know
Yeah, you missed a secret room six to seven rooms back no
All right with the next one
What is all this? I?
Gotta go. Oh
No
No, I don't want to do that
please
Just close behind me. Oh
Something wrong with you
Bye, then you need to leave. I can't leave. I'm locked. I'm stuck here. I'm stuck
I'm drafted
Interested in finding me
Of your health
Yeah
Yeah, but I
Changed I didn't even tell you guys I I did pre stream, but that don't even pre stream is
Fuck I forgot to mention all this shit. We're gonna talk about this. Um, I have I forgot to talk about this
So shit, okay
gas in here
Is there
Activate the circuit breaker
I
Can't scream tomorrow
Okay, all right. All right. I gotta go. I can't my health is important. I gotta take care of myself
I'm all right. Here's what's gonna happen. You ready?
This is the deal. You ready for the deal
Community content nights gonna be Thursday
Easy bake oven Friday green screen on Saturday, but for
after
Community content night. I'm gonna finish this game. I want to see the end
After community content night because the community cut the community night. It only takes
Actually, what like three or four hours something like that?
That that's fine. You know, I could probably another hour or two in the game, right?
Sucks don't finish it. I
But I said made that thing about the major prize and that's really been my head right now
so I
Kind of kind of there, but I'll see you guys on Thursday unity content night. We'll finish this
I can't stream tomorrow. Can't I got this way too?
I have to I have I don't even have like half of like the costumes
I need it for the next three days
I got it. I got to do it like this
I gotta get it like costumes and a bunch of toys and shit
It's gonna be it's gonna be a little while, but I'll see you guys on Thursday. We'll do community content night
I'm gonna finish this. Maybe I'll just completely forget about this and not even care
I probably will but we're gonna end this room. We can do the bits
I'm gonna do the bits fast because I've got to get out of here like fucking body
Damn it. I gotta get this shit. I gotta I'm I gotta get I gotta fucking figure out what the fuck is wrong
Alright, alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye
We'll see you tomorrow. No, no, no, no see you Thursday. Fuck idiot. See you. I'll see you Thursday Thursday
We're gonna go through the bits
Quick nice and fast and full of energy
We'll see you on Thursday. Thanks for watching everybody. This has been saw the video game
Tomorrow is Thursday. What?
Well, it's it's 10 o'clock PST
All right, you ready for lightning bits? Let's go baby. You ready next Thursday
No, no, no Thursday is like the day after the day that it is for some of you right now
A donut 500. Thanks for the thousand bits your face is immaculate. Thank you so much
I got a big zip that you haven't seen peaceful Haley. Thanks for the 250 Jeremy. You're definitely gonna love this game
It's great with a pepe laughing face. The game sucks. So I mean it is fun though. I just have its moments Captain Kitten
Thanks for the five dollars. Mr. 985. It's my birthday today with everything going on the world. I'm stuck at home
Ocean like at you and chat to keep me company. Thanks for all the work
You put into your streams really looking forward to the green screen DLC for free
I added the free part, but I had to make sure to make that very very importantly added note there. Happy birthday
Captain Kitten, thanks to five dollars prove that it's not Thursday. It's 10 o'clock Pacific time. Just look at a globe
Or a pharynx thanks for the five dollars Jerma
I was the one who mentioned I had coronavirus and your streams were helping a lot
I want to say that I'm all healed now
Thanks again for lifting my spirits during that time. Hope you're doing well glad to hear it
Scary shit
Hopefully you would very well taken care of and I'm glad to hear that you're doing well
Cheers to your recovery. Thank you with the five dollars
Go story the first thanks for
$20 that's a lot of money. Thanks to the 2,000 bits. Say mr. German 985. You remember me the response here
I bet you thought you'd never see me again. Thanks for being so nice to me. I appreciate it so much
I'd like to give you what I've won here tonight. Here's 2,000 bits. Of course. I remember you
Of course, I do see in like 20 minutes
Your response here. Thank the seriously though. Thanks for the $20. It's a lot of money bad cobalt. Thanks for three dollars, Jerma
I gave a message a few months ago, but I was going through some rough stuff
And they were you pushing me forward. Unfortunately times are still a bit tough
But they're better than they used to be
You're a fantastic human being
Human being it be an and I want to thank you again for all the amazing times you give me over the last seven years
Love you content. Look forward to new stuff every day
Also, whoever reads this whoever reads this is cute. I
Read it out loud. I read it. Therefore. I'm cute
Nobody else's kind of egotistical, but thanks for the 300 bits. I really hope stuff turns around for you
Thanks for hanging out and that's a long time to even think that the e-clown guy here is still funny
Seven years is a long time
Thanks a lot. I wish you the best. Take care of yourself
He's a sicko. I'm a sicko sicko streamer. Why what the fuck are you talking about?
Stains thanks for three dollars Jerma. I need some help. Okay, let's see if I can help you during lightning round
Recently, I've been having dreams with a guy from dirty jobs shows up
Swinging a ball peen hammer at me. I think I have micro
peen issues
Do you happen to know how does make it stop? Did you just make me say micro penis you did?
Congratulations
Professor plaid. Thanks for the five dollars. Don't use weapons in this game. Fists are much better. It's actually kind of real. I think you
Jam may get for the three dollars. Hi Jerma, but I'll be asleep by the time you get around to reading this
I'm in the UK, but I'll be watching the VOD when I can I'm in the last week of University
Your VODs have been keeping me sane the first time I've been able to watch live
So I thought I'd send you some appreciation for what little money I have to celebrate
Cue you talking about not giving money, but shut up. You've done more for me than you'll know. Thank you for being you
All right. Okay. All right. I will shut up. Make sure you don't get an F in pickleball like I did
I wish you the best. Good luck and
potential, you know, you know
preliminary congratulations on your passing of your
University year what is pickleball was the most fun sport in the world?
Snoozing coffee. Thanks for 250. I recently finished God of War 2018. It was so good. Did you ever play it off stream?
I did and then I got four or five hours in
Maybe I was a little more than that. It's probably like eight hours in and I stopped
But that first like two hours is one of the most fun
I think I've ever played in a video game that was single-player that first hour of God of War was like holy shit
This is insane. This is most insane game ever played
And then it was okay, and then it turns it was just a video game after that, but that's not a bad thing
It was a very very high quality video game
Like I would probably say that if I had a
Brain that actually functioned well on a daily basis that that would probably be one of the best single-player games that have come out in
a long time
Although I only have about 12 hours potentially of experience in a game. That's about twice that I
Can only imagine all the perfect joke opportunities to do an Irish accent the rage induced moments during Valkyrie fights in the story
Yeah
This is bad. I have to tell you this I got halfway
I got like 12 hours in the game
And then I just stopped playing for like a couple months went by and then I just read every spoiler on like the Wikipedia page
Sorry, but whatever it's still cool. It's still a really cool game. I
Found my perfect keyboard low profile and quiet. It's 170 bucks
I have difficulty justifying an investment like that help get an Amazon basics fucking $10 keyboard save yourself
1700 percent wait is that correct maybe an Amazon basics fucking $9 keyboard who cares
They all do the same thing good keyboards are worth it
Yeah, but you could just get a $9 Amazon basics keyboard and fucking save $1,000 or whatever it was
Ex whimsical moose. Thanks for two feet. By the way, I'm a hypocrite asshole lying a fuckface. I have a course here
Listen to this you ready for this one. Oh
Whoa Amazon basic keyboard. What what's that? That's
That's not an Amazon
Basics keyboard anymore. Is it it's a course here fucking keyboard? I got it
I got the course here. I'm the one that I dumped the drink on
Yeah, I got that same one because it was my favorite keyboard. I got it. I cracked get an Amazon basics keyboard the $9
Thank you ex whimsical moose for the 250. Hello, Jeremiah first donation. I'm 28 years old
Happy why was I just gonna say happy birthday like today? Wait. No, I'm fucking that up
Just want to say not all your fans are these dang zoomers
I didn't grow up with you and you haven't saved my life
But you're one of the few e-clowns from when I was 19 or 20
There's still watchable and even funnier than you used to be even if you never beat stalker shadow of Chernobyl. Keep it up
also play
Exanima you played it in 2015. So I know you own it and it's updated a ton since then you can be a wizard now
I made a video on examina. Maybe I'll go back to it one day. Put it on the list
It's at least one person's birthday today. Yeah, they've already we've already seen them
they've already been
Here play that instead of finishing saw
that was a
common rider based
But ex whimsical moose gave 250. I didn't even read this
Hey, Jeremiah, I love this game and it's sequel for how funny bad it is
Also, you always tell us to keep safe, but I was wondering how you Kim and Otto are doing
Also, I'm hype about this weekend streams and stay safe chat
We're doing good. We'll see how it goes here over the next few weeks
Nevada
Stay-at-home order in Nevada is gone
We've entered phase one of
reopening
Hopefully it's not gonna cause a big problem. I know some restaurants are starting to open up again a little bit
Some other businesses are starting to open
Casinos are all still closed. The strip is still closed and it will be probably for a pretty long time
Can't imagine any of those properties are gonna open up until
June July
Who knows it depends on how this goes?
Yeah, we're we're doing all right. We're doing just fine
Trying to stay as safe as possible try to take care of each other here of Otto, obviously
Yeah, we're doing good
pump
Punk Pikachu. Thanks for the four dollars. Jeremy yesterday at Walmart. They played I'm Han Solo
And I felt the need to tell you how famous you've gotten
Anyways, love your streams. They make me laugh no matter how much time has passed a
Fame wait, I didn't make the hun solo song. They played I'm hun, but I didn't that's not my song. I
danced to it like
three years after it was a meme and
Like after five youtubers made jokes about it. I think I was I was a little late to that party
No need to be so modest. All right, fine. I wrote the song. No, I didn't that's how I can't fucking say that
That's bad. I didn't do that
It's like I didn't and like somebody was like, well, I what if you what if you fucking actually wrote it?
And you were sitting here right now and you're listening to this asshole
Hey Wembley TTV. Thanks for the 250
I really hope that I'm never put it in a saw like contraption and
Jerma has to take over to save my life. I'd rather take my own chances. Thank you
Well, I opened the door and shot the guy in the last one. So I mean that you do it. There's a good point there
Hey, mostly toasted toast. Thanks for three dollars. I'm starting to feel like this game isn't about cutting things
Make me home. Thanks for three dollars Jerma. It's been forever since I watched live therefore
It's been forever since I've given bits. I must make the opportunity count. I will
And it's a dad. It's a blank to continue recording this message. Cheer another hundred bits
And shit will see if you end up putting another another 250 in there. Hey one blondie. Thanks for the nine dollars and ninety cents
I'm making a D&D wizard. Do you want to name him? He likes illusions. Sure
see-through s e a
No space t h r o u u
Ostrich
It's fucking good, I mean terrible
Okay, so but so see-through is terrible
But hell scream is the greatest character ever made and the best name ever made ever for any character ever
Okay, hell scream
See-through. All right, it's pretty bad. It's bad. It's worse than hell scream, but not that much worse
I would put up next to each other and you wouldn't build it would be hard to tell
Hey BS. Hey
BB BS 88 BS 88 unit. Thanks for the $15. No message. Just 15 bucks. Just dropped on my lap. I'll take it
Thank you
MTY 98 a thousand bits $10 just given to me. No message just a thousand bits. I'll take the 10 bucks
It's a lot of money. Thank you
Shitty view bought another thousand bits $10. What even made you want to play this game today? I bought it like
Four months ago was five months ago or something. This was sitting here. I
Gotta play it gotta make time for these things. Thank you shitty view, but hey me game friend
Thanks for the $5. Don't listen to the haters. This game pogs. Yes, you need to sign in to save
Yep, I get that one out. Hey, honey wizard. Thanks for the three dollars. Hey Germans
I just I used to watch your vods exclusively for months before going to bed until I recently started getting night terrors narrated by you
Glad to finally catch a stream while it's live. Sorry to hear that. Hey Mick Muscles
Thanks for the thousand bits $10 German. Why are all these puzzles shitty mobile games? I don't know. I wish I knew a
Dingled jangle. Thanks for the $27 and 50 cents was 30 bucks
Thanks for that all the way from Dublin for the boy all the way out West
I'm a little teapot see my vest see my vest. What's that mean?
Well, I just read like a weird fucking weird thing
Thanks for the $30. That's it's huge amounts of money
Omega well, he read it. I I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what that is
I and I just read it and I might have said something fucking stupid. I'm sorry. I don't know if people write
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. What did I just do? It was a Simpsons joke. That's from the Simpsons
Oh, okay. You got penis cursed. Okay, whatever you say. Thanks with 30 bucks. It's a lot of money
Hey anything else show official. Thanks for the $15 German. Do you think that you'll look like Neil Breen when you become older?
What do you think?
This doesn't this I don't think I don't think this link actually works
Link I don't think this link is a correct link. It's just it's just a discord and then like a bunch of numbers
I don't think this is accurate. I don't think this is correct
Yeah, sorry. I don't I can't I'd like to just type in his name. Let's just do that Neil Breen
No, no, I don't think so. No, no, no, no, I had to look like this now. So when I'm older
No, maybe somebody else
Thanks for the $15 though hair air of the moon. Thanks for the $5. Will you play saw to after this?
I don't know. I don't I don't think so, but I could get yelled at to do it
We could think of you like the saw
Saw crew. I don't know. I'm sure it'll happen. Hey s10w slow update. Thanks for this 250 German
I was having some trouble paying for your only fans. So think of this donation as my month's payment. Well, that's
That's hilarious considering it's $30 a month
Please enable my account again so I can use the new see the new pics
Honestly, this stuff you do is way extreme way extreme for only 250. Anyways, peace and love whatever
Thanks for the okay the saw squad. Hey BS 88. It's in a unit. Thanks for the $5
It's amazing how funny you can make a shitty game. Cheers with hilarious morning. Good morning
You gotta be you gotta be in Australia, New Zealand, UK
Asia where that's far. It's the five dolls. Hey, thank you Zion swaz. Thanks for the five dollars
Yo, I don't got a lot of money
Sorry, but here's five for bringing joy to everyone during these hard times streamer. Anyway, the first
In second halo games are now on Steam
I know you said you'd never play more but their campaigns would be better than a shit co-op reach stream on the hardest difficulty for no
reason
Baby, if the curse is too strong though
I at least recommend any halo OST for when we need BG music for a stream
Or at least these serene songs playing for the Silent Hill and fable OSTs. I don't know why we do that. Wait, is this like
I have stopped
Doing that have you noticed
Recently games have come up. It's like oh easy normal hard insane and I used to be like, I have to play on hard
I'm a live streamer. I have to what are the other streamers played on insane mode? Oh, oh biting nails. I
Guess I have to know I don't care. I don't fucking normal. I don't give a shit
like if you be the game on insane and like
Other streamer be the game on insane. I'm good. I'm glad I hope you fucking win. I
At this I don't care. I'm not picking insane on saw. I'm not gonna do hard mode on
Halo OST. No, whatever. Well, that's the you target, but very very that's not the name of the game
Okay, right. I'm stupid. Hey gay wizard. Thanks for the five dollars, Jeremy
I want to say that I've been a fan since like 2014
But this is surprisingly my first time watching a live stream. Welcome, even though the game sucked
It was a blast watching you being part of chat
Your humor has gotten me through some dark days and I just want to say thank you
I wish I could donate more but anyways gay rights, baby. Yeah, I don't you don't have to give me money
I know I say this a lot but you you don't have it's not don't worry about it
I really hope some of you guys are not
Like saving up money to give me on stream. I hope that's not the case
They carry yourselves. They carry you shut up and take the money
I'm gonna but every so often I'm gonna make sure that I'm gonna tell you this I spent my food stamps on bits for you
Don't do that
Use it up eat food. But thank you though. I appreciate it refund all the donations then
Well, you guys think I have a button here that will just I press it and it just
Deposits all the money back to every human that's ever given money to the stream. That's no there are no refunds
Give me my money back. No, there's no refunds
It's in the twitch term services you buy bits and use them bits are consumed by the stream or the eats them and shitty shits out money
That's how it works. Hey goo berry juice. Thanks with three dollars. Hey funk King
What's with that? Why are people saying funk King? Is that a way to say?
fucking
Whatever it is, whatever
Hey funk King
Man, this game sucks, huh? I
Don't really have anything to add to that
So just thought I remind everyone of the good thing to come out of the saw franchise. What a classic
Wait, is this like a movie clip of like somebody getting that they had ripped off? Oh, I've
This is a it is a classic it is
Hold on, you know, let's uh this way it is a classic
Game skip
The video is so funny cuz like how did he fall down I want to play a little game
Like the whole bike explode
Like just disintegrates underneath
Like so how wheeling in and doing this shit you want to play a little game
You
Do that for the green screen I get like a tricycle
What a classic great stream. Nonetheless, I can always count on you
Chat take nothing and make it funny. You can always count on you chat to take nothing and make it funny
What do you mean chat? Well me I do that too. Don't I I do that. That's I do that sometimes
Hey Tobias, thanks for the thousand bits long time follower first time donator. Welcome and thank you
Today's my birthday. So we have a bunch of fucking birthdays. Everyone said that whose birthday was it?
It's been a bummer in quarantine, but your streams have been keeping me afloat in these trying times
Thanks for being a bright part of the crazy world
You've been make you better make Chad a birthday cake with the easy-bake oven. I don't even know what's in that box
I know this I think 12 recipes
That streams gonna suck by the way, I just I need to make sure I've laid that concrete down for you
I'm just going to make
Candies and cakes and pizzas and shit in an easy-bake oven. I don't know
I want to make sure you guys aren't expecting anything from that that could be birdhouse stream too and then eat it
No, I won't eat it disgusting. I'm way above that. But anyways, thank you for the thousand bits and happy birthday
I will make a birthday themed
Cake thing. What are you gonna do while the food is baking? Holy shit. I don't even think about that
I don't know like jumping jacks push ups and stuff like stretches. I'm gonna be careful. I don't like forget that it's in there
That might happen. All right, I gotta be careful. I got to have like a
Okay. All right. Hey tree fiddy. Thanks for the five dollars. Thank you German for everything on my birthday
You were the only person I felt like I had
Having you around made things not suck so much. It seems like that's the case every time you stream. It's the thanks, dude
I appreciate your drive and your dedication to the community. I wish words could describe how much you've made an impact on my life
From the bottom of my heart. Thank you and love you
That means a lot but I've mentioned this before and I want to mention it again
I really hope that you can take the steps necessary to try to improve your life and hope things get better
because I'm just a streamer on the internet and although I can
Hopefully be here to have fun and have a good time with the community. I can't necessarily
Fix any problems that anybody has and obviously I know that people aren't asking me to do that
And that's never something that was no one's ever like hey, by the way
I what I know that what this advice questions and stuff like that
But I just hope that you can find something else that can make you happy as well as me as well as this community because
That means that you're gonna get healthier
You guys are really feeding his God complex, but like again, I say like I say it again
I'm just a guy on the internet
That's just me. I'm just an e-clown and we're in an e-clown community
And I can't necessarily help anybody with their problems and I don't necessarily want to
I'm gonna be you know, let's get the honesty out here because I don't know I get questions a lot about hey
What about this? What about that? What about this? And I don't really know it's I don't really have good answers
A lot of the time I don't want to put people in the wrong path
Or tell people something that might not even be true
Because if you put a lot of weight in the things that I say I don't want to be like well
This is how you do it. This is how would I do because I've you know in the past
I've tried to give some decent advice as best as I could
But my advice is not really that good
It's not adequate. I don't think or what some of you guys might necessarily need
Remember should I change the dosage of my medication? I'll call your doctor
You should call to your doctor
So I'm nothing of a psychologist myself
Don't tell me what to do, but I
Obviously everybody in this community that's been a part of this community
If you just even if you watch for 10 minutes, I wish you the best of health
I do and I hope you take the steps necessary to get there
But just be careful putting a lot of weight in
Somebody like an online entertainer
Because I might say something that might not even be good enough. It might not be real
It might be something that's not the best advice to give somebody and if you take that completely and you
Absorb all of it
It's maybe something that would should never should have been said in the first place. You know, I mean, did you eat ass? Yes
Irma is not an expert at anything even streaming, right?
Enjoy your parasites what from eating ass
Shit wait, did I say to do that? I did did I? Oh
No, don't do that don't do that. Oh my god, that person's disgusting, but they could be real is that real?
All right. I've never I've never eaten ass again. I never did. Why would you who does that? Somebody does it's gross
I do who does nobody does disgusting move on. Nobody's I don't do that. I really don't I swear to God 100%
No jokes. Don't do that. Hey creepy teeth. Thanks for the $5
Irma have you ever thought about playing the Batman games? I feel like it'd be a fun stream
I'm not sure anything can ever top I can't play Batman games because I played the ultimate Batman game where you could ghost ride
the Batmobile into a wall
I'm not sure I could ever top that any of the Batman game could do it
Let's get the credits on here
Why not? Right? It was a shitload of subs. You'll see a shitload of names
They're gonna fly by very fast because there was a lot of people that was subbed today
It is the lots of community subs and lots of just resubs and new subs. It's a lot of people
Good morning. I just read that person's name first time ever
Thanks guys. Seriously. It's a slow lightning around. We're almost done. It's been like 30 minutes
That's a quick. Okay 30 minutes
Usually I said it for like 40 to an hour and the 40 to an hour
Hey goiki. Thanks for the $5 to give credit where credit is due
This game is pretty faithful to the movie just like the saw puzzles in the movie. This game is stupid and tedious
Hey Tom sup. Thanks for the $5 streamer man a little over eight years ago
I was finishing middle school and I found your channel looking for tips for playing Scout glad you took them now
I'm graduating college. I'm watching ever since I still suck at Scout your work in the community around it mean a lot
It's been one of my few constants this whole time looking forward to the easy-bake stream more than my virtual graduation that morning
If you are enjoying what you do because we sure do I am
I'm gonna continue to do so as long as it's still fun
I don't have a time frame on when I I'm gonna stop doing it this ever
Because when it's not fun anymore, that's when I'm done. That's the only fucking thing I care about if it's not fun
I'm done. You'll know you'll know when I'm you'll know
When it's time for me to retire
Because it's I you'll know that I'm just I want to take a step back. It's not really that fun for me anymore
Based honest now. What do you say?
Hedonist he didn't what is that? What does that word mean? I think I should know what this means. He didn't
Person who believes that the pursuit of pleasure is the most important thing in life
I mean, I just don't want to like pretend on stream. I don't want to like fake. Well, I'm having a good time. I
Can't do that shit you think I could sit here for more than six to eight hours and like pretend to have a good time
No, I in ten minutes. I'd be like I'd be gone
No way you pretend to be bad at games. Yeah
He's exhausted. He's it's a geez. Oh, it's exhausting
If I'm not having a good time on streams
Consistently and I'm getting I don't know. I don't have a plan. I just I didn't have a plan eight years ago
I didn't have a plan ten years ago. I didn't have a plan twenty years ago for well like any of this shit
I'm just still here doing it and that's the way it is and it seems to have worked out. All right
We'll see and it's shocking to me that people have been here for ten years. He's the just like the Roman Empire
Yeah, that's the Roman Empire crumbled, right?
What happened to the Roman Empire? Okay, you want to be I'm a hedonist from the Roman Empire. What happened to the Roman Empire?
But how's my story end? I stopped having fun. Oh
The Romans are extinct. It was a volcano in barbarians barbarians attacked. Oh
You're not the Roman Empire
Another channel is going to raid us to death. Oh
well
Eco mania. All right. All right, we're done. We're done. We're done. We're done. We're done
Hey Wembley TTV. Thanks for the 250
This game is pretty much a mobile game with all these puzzles and lackluster combat just add in lives and pointless non-skipping phone adverts
The most ironic thing about all this Konami got the rights for the series to publish this
So, you know, they did a good job looking after the horror titles after the 2010 looking at you Silent Hill series
That's been turned into a Chinko machine and it's dead since PT
No, Konami makes more money from one person sitting at one of their slot machines than a hundred people buying games
They figured that out a long time ago
Fortunate hey River Roria. Thanks for the 250. Hey, mr. 900 800 500. The stream was good
Thanks for the comedy and the humor and the jokes Hickman 2 is one of my favorite games
I'm so excited for that stream. Also, by the way
Here is something here
All right, that's the sound effect. I think that's that's how they're made their exit. Hey rip Alex Trebek
Thanks for the $5. Hey, Jeremy, if I consider getting a standing desk
I know standing can be a bit of a meme, but it helps for stretching and not sitting all day, which does suck
Xoxoxo stinky poopoo epic read it. Okay, nice ending. I'm glad you gave me the TLDR here at the end
Well, I don't have a standing desk because I just got
last year a brand new desk
very nice and I
It would be a shame to have to spend the money that I did on this nice desk and then replace it with another
expensive desk
But what I could do is I could get one of those
but standing I I
Don't really like standing and doing stuff. I it doesn't I
Move around too much. I fidget all the time and I would be gone for a second. I come back
I'd be I don't really like standing up to standing still
What I does it doesn't really work for me
But your health I know
I'm getting this figured out. Don't worry. I'm figuring it. I'll get it. I'm gonna get it figured out. Don't worry
Thanks to $5. Hey on zeroic. Thanks with 300 bits
I'm giving you bits. So you have to go through one more bit message. I'm just that evil
You're not the last one
Appreciate that evil money
Thank you Pritzla
The three dollars German my birthday was over the weekend another birthday. Happy birthday
There's like a lot of other people are in the same boat as me. So cheers to everyone in chat. We're also having quarantine birthdays
Happy birthday. Yeah, happy birthday all the quarantine birthdays
And it's been a pretty decent chunk of time
From what somewhere in the around the end of February
It's a March April May. I mean, it's that's a whole chunk of time. There's probably a lot of people that have had their birthdays
in quarantine
Thanks with three bucks. Happy birthday. Hey spin, man. Thanks with five dollars, Jeremiah
I recently lost my 4.0 in high school in the last semester
It really mattered this whole corona virus dealio and distance learning have been really taxing on my mental health
One of those thanks for being here through it and cheering me up when I really need it
Generally, you're generally one of the best guys on this platform. I thank you
Incredibly humbled that you would even say something like that. It's like a five hundred thousand people that stream on Twitter more than that probably
Thank you. I
Sometimes I can't fucking believe it, but just lost you 4.0. You're gonna be alright
You're gonna be alright. I'll tell you anything anything over like a 3-2
You do what you're doing. Just fucking fine. You're doing just fine. I should I got 2-6. I should tell you I got 2.6
Which is what is a 2.6 GPA BPA to grade
Calculator, what is it like a C minus C plus?
Two point
Dude, that's a that's a fucking B
2.6
It's a B minus
That's fine. I'm I dude B minus in college B minus on stream go to my twitch metrics website. It's a B minus
Always B minus that's fine with me. It's not a D. That's a B minus. I just typed in looked it up. Hey Ozals
Thanks, don't even run the yeah, I was gonna say. Yeah, I did right fucking crazy. Hey Ozals. Thanks for 250
Jeremy because you stream so late. It's now my birthday
It's weird to be giving money away on my birthday, but yeah, you're the best e-clown you deserve it
First vaude of yours. I remember watching is the fire watch nudes video
Which I laughed my ass off in 2016 just turned 17. It's crazy. How fast it goes by wish Orlando me
Happy birthday. That'd be awesome. Happy birthday Orlando. Hope you had a really really well
He didn't hide hasn't happened yet. Technically, you're right. It's tech extreme so late. So it's your birthday now
What do we do? What time is it 3m 4 o'clock in the morning 5 in the morning? I guess it's like it's about to happen
Happy birthday a space butterfly. Thanks for the thousand bits. Jerma. It's my sister's birthday today. She's a big fan of you
You love the Titanic joke, you know the one they happy birthday to said debt. They were there
Omega birthdays. I showed the fire watch video to my parents. They didn't think it was funny
What the fuck is wrong with them? Don't show your parents that video
Why would you do what what's your context to show your parents a video of a guy naked on the internet?
What's what what's your context there? Hey mom and dad look hey, I got this a naked guy, okay
Yeah, what do you don't why don't you like it? I don't know. What do you want me to do? It's funny
Why I mean I thought it was
Fun, but a happy birthday acidette. Thanks for the ten bucks space butterfly. Appreciate it
Somnus thanks for the five dollars Jerma since all of the furry conventions the world are getting cancelled
I'm gonna host a virtual furry convention in your chat
At least 5,000 furries are going to attend it's happening tomorrow
It's really weird if you were not lying
Anything else show official five more dollars. Thank you. I posted the image to the discord you goof check the arc section
Well, I clicked it in the fifth idea. It took me to a login page for discord on my web browsing
Universal remote guys. I saw them though. Furries are already here. Oh, wait a minute. It's 11 o'clock Pacific 11 12 1 2
It's 2 a.m. Eastern. The furries must be here. It's the furry time. It's
Wednesday furry meetup. Oh
They're already here. Who cares as the only way you would know if somebody was a furry in the chat
Is if they told you it's just people's names
It how would you this is chatting don't worry. They will they always do no, they don't
What do you mean?
They will Hermes got a fursuit. I did technically it was a frog, right?
Christmas a Frito man. Thanks for the thousand bits
What the hell is this
shrewd Simon shorts sewed shoes
17 summers speeding storm spreading sunshine successfully
Simon's small shabby shops. Just what is the what the fuck is this? Why am I reading this?
Simon's squeaking signs still swinging silently specifying Simon short Smith's soul sir shoemaker
Thanks for the ten dollars tongue twister. Oh, is it I get this
True Simon short shrewd Simon short sewed shoes
17 summers speeding storms spreading sunshine successfully saw Simon small shabby shops still standing staunch saw Simon self same
Squeaking signs still swinging silently specifying Simon short Smithfield soul surviving shoemakers shoes sewed sold supers finally
I'll do it double cursed. Whatever a stripes beast. Thanks for 250 germa ever since the blackjack stream
I've had this idea where you have a casino based dream. Will you play no limit pocket with chat bits?
no limit poker and vomit every time you hit it big also just found out about
Any Harvey today gonna miss the big guy any Harvey wait trying to see if I
Know who this is. I ever
Watch
Wait, it's not it's not a real joke. Not real
I'm trying to wait. Oh
It's a bit wait. Oh
I thought I was trying to see if I knew who that was. I was like, wait
I don't do I know who this person in you got baited. Oh
Scottish joke. Oh, I'm just like trying to figure out. Wait, do I know who this bird? I have I seen any of the things before? Oh
well, um
Rip r.i.p. I said real. I don't know
Thank you. Thank you. Appreciate it. Thanks for the
Eldritch thanks the five dollars German
My water heater is broken and I had to take a bath from five pots of boiling water mixed with cold tap water
If you play Kingdom Hearts on stream
I'm sorry
To hear that that sounds terrible and no five pots of boiling water. You're gonna be careful with that shit. I
Imagine you holding that pot of boiling water with the steam coming out of it and just like oh shit easy easy
Slowly slowly poured in you're gonna burn your hands. Be careful. But thanks to the five dolls. I will not be playing Kingdom Hearts
those games are too long and
I've already beaten them play through the first two. I have no interest in playing the third one
at all
Unfortunately, thanks for the five dollars. Hey moo means moo
thanks for the three dollars local streamer eats ass and receives a blu-ray copy of
Bong Joon Bong Joon Ho's best picture winning 2019 film Parasite. It's a great movie. Actually
There's actually a really good movie. It deserved it. It was fucking awesome. That movie was crazy. It was your thoughts
Okay, I don't want to spoil anything cuz I don't want to be like the guy that I'm the movie spoiler TV show Ruiner
Did not it was great. Okay. Thank you. Goobery juice. Thanks for three dolls
Do they make standing desks that size in your case would be standing stool. Wouldn't it ban that person for a week?
Pepper the doctor. Thanks for the three. Wait, you've already been like banned before it's like strike three
You've been banned before. Oh
You don't want to fuck with a third ban a third band is like three days
Pepper the doctor. Thanks for three dolls intergalactic twitch streamer ranking. You got to be kidding me
Did you watch the no more heroes 3 trailer with fu food? Yes when I'm playing it after it comes out
I'm gonna play the day it comes out
The day that no more heroes 3 comes out. I will be the I will be the first person streaming it on twitch
That's a lie because that means that's a stream at like 12 o'clock and the night I'm not gonna do that the next day
I'll be the first person to stream it on twitch at 4 o'clock Pacific. Yeah, wait, and that's it. I'll see you guys on Thursday
Thanks, everybody
Get some sleep. That was saw the movie the game
Have a great night. See you guys on Thursday
for community content night
And it may be the end of song. Maybe the end of song make a trip to Japan
What do you mean?
Fuck saw don't play
them raid raid raid. All right. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we're a
People saying Vinny. It's many up to
this many up to
He's doing a charity stream
See
It's Vinny's birthday. It's not
This is birthday two hours ago
Was it it's not you guys lying to me. Is it actually Vinny's birthday?
All right. It was okay. Then go say happy birthday. I'll see you guys on Thursday
This is the birthday party. That's a happy birthday. I'll see you guys Thursday. Have a good night. Goodbye