Hey, what's happening? How's everybody doing? Getting started a little later than I wanted to.
I had to take care of something that was a little stressful, but I was taken care of.
Sorry, I'm about 20 minutes past where I usually would like to start, but we're good.
We're good. We're good. We're good. We're gonna play Man of Medan. There's in Medan?
Medan? I don't know how to pronounce it. With italics. It's gonna be a co-op nightmare stream.
So it's gonna be scary. This game apparently sucks. I just want to get that out of the way.
But we're gonna do it in co-op. And I heard that doing it in co-op makes the game exponentially
more fun. This is a game on choices, on talking to people, on making decisions as a party of two,
on who stays and who goes. We're gonna need your help on deciding on who that should be.
And at the end of the day, we're gonna do whatever the funniest lab out loud YouTuber storyline is.
No, I'm just kidding. The game solo apparently is really, really bad.
The game with a friend is apparently very fun. That's what I've heard. So without further ado,
we're gonna see if Mr. Italics, you guys all know Italics, we're currently squad
streaming right now. If you don't know who Italics is, where have you been? Huh? You don't know who
that is? You can probably see the stream right now. But let me move this. Can you see this?
I thought this is funny because if you don't know, Italics and I currently live together.
And I thought that because we're both on a VPN, that this was our like fake locations. I was like,
wow, that's kind of funny. Chinese market, China South Sea. Wow. That's weird how it's routing us.
He's like, no, dude, that's like where the game starts. Because it's like multiplayer. I thought
it was like, oh, this is where this person's from. I don't know. Chinese market. Like, how do they
know? So we're gonna do a new story. What's gonna start? I think we have to pick characters. Play
this in co-op. No, no, I'm just gonna, Italics is gonna be in the call and he's gonna watch me play.
What do you think we're doing? Why would they show your address? I don't know. I didn't know this
took place in China. Yes, my name is Rowdy. My name's been Rowdy for over a year. All right,
let's see if we can get Italics in here. Hello. Yes, I am present. Hey, there you are. Hey,
everybody. Present and currently accounted for. Yeah, did you push the start button?
Oh, I thought I didn't know you were ready. Are you ready? No, I mean like
the start squad button. Oh, I didn't. I thought I did that. Whoa. So wait, now there's a squad.
Yes, that's what happened when you push the start button. What?
So now of course, yeah, I got a custom link here for you. Twitch.tv slash squad. What? Oh, dude.
All right, are you ready? I'm ready. I want a, I want a let's go Pikachu. All right, there he did
it. Let's go Pikachu. All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, this is important.
What do you have on your screen? Do you have anything on your screen right now or is this,
do I get to choose this? You choose. Oh, chat, who the hell am I going to do? Personally,
I would pick Bulbasaur. Well, there's not a third one. Joe or Charlie, which one of those sounds more
me to you? You're definitely a Charlie. Am I a Charlie? What is chat? Why is everybody in chat
saying I'm more of a Joe? Charlie Joe. Charlie's are like, which one's more likely to have facial
hair? That's definitely Joe. I mean, that's pretty true. Your name starts with J. You should be the
one with the J and there's an E in there too. Okay. Oh, there's a, there's the same letter.
Yeah. Another, another, right. The same letter. I just, I picked you. That does know the alphabet.
I also know how to count. I know the alphabet too though. So that's why I picked Joe. All right.
Are you ready? I think you're ready, right? Uh, yeah, I'm ready. So we don't know if there's a,
is there like a part where we split up and we have to mute each other in discord? Uh, that is
probably going to happen. We are on each other's team when it's beneficial to us and we're trying
to hamper each other. I guess when it is also advantageous. Interesting. Okay. Dude, I'm,
I'm ready. I hope so. Cause this is what we're doing. There's not a plan B. You know what?
I'm not ready actually. If it's this, let's do something else. All right. Which one of those is
Joe? Are you Charlie then? That makes you Charlie. I guess I'm Charlie. Whichever person I end up
being, I guarantee you that they're both douches. It's too loud. Well, every cut scene is loud.
Does this take place in the forties? I thought that this takes place in China.
Not that that let go. Does this take place in the forties? No, it takes place in China. That's a
time period. Yeah. But that China didn't exist back then. They weren't even on the map. In fact,
I think it was Matt Damon who put them on the map. That's the first time I learned of the great wall.
I think this is us. You should read up on it sometime. All right. That's Joe. And then which
one of these is Joe? I think, um, that's Joe. All righty Buster. We better mosey on back to the ship.
You're Buster. Whoa. Buster is just the thing you call your friends. Stop the presses. That's me.
Looks like old Charlie Charming's got a little business to attend to. No, that's who's Charlie?
Can I fight? Hey, Charlie's on the left. No, this is Mark. He's on the right.
Why? Why did I find out my future? All right. This is you. No, no, I don't think any of these
people. Yeah, they are. What's in store for me? You are. Is this you? Are you watching me? Yeah,
I'm watching you. Are you curious or are you dubious? That's you. This is me. Yeah. I'm
punching stuff. Oh, what? I'm curious. I guess I just want to know what you're punching stuff.
Will he, uh, I'm over here just throwing. What? There's a training dummy and I'm fighting training
dumb. Oh, I thought you were like punching people. No, it's not. You're like, I'm over here punching
things. I'm just like, what? I'm getting my like fortune told. Um, all right. I got to turn subtitles
up, but I don't have an option to hold on. There was a QTE in my game within the first 30 seconds
of the game. Start accessibility. Where are my subtitles? Why are these not on? My subtitles
are already on. Okay. Mine are on. Okay. There we go. I'm ready. Okay. I think you have to ready up
too. What? Yeah. Cause I paused the game. Oh, I see. So it's like in smite. Yeah. I get, I get two
pauses the whole game. All right. Here we go. Hold on. My QTE is getting more challenging. I mean,
this is a, this is a really advanced training dummy. What do I see? Uh,
what do I see? What are you? Hey, hey, I'm trying to look at stuff. I just got an achievement.
I just beat that training dummy. Sure. Better than anybody ever has. You just fucked it all up.
I was supposed to look at that and you like grabbed me. You got another quarter on you.
What do I look like? Five dollars in 1940s money, by the way. I'll give it a whirl.
Just thought you should know that. Wait, now it's my turn. No, I'm getting my fortune told.
Oh, this is hopeful. Will Joe return those two quarters? Wait, what? I'm my, I'm asking the
fortune teller whether you're going to return the 50 cents. I just loaned you. Oh,
it's the smash dummy. I thought he said I can't. All right. I'm no more fucking around.
Wait, did you miss one? No, I did not. I missed one. Are you playing with mouse and keyboard?
Can I die? What if I die here and Joe's dead? Have a nice day. Why am I playing with mouse
and keyboard? I can play with controller, right? Yeah, you can play with it. That's what I'm doing.
Hey, Chuck, we better get back to the ship. We don't want to get stranded. Come on, man.
Just let me ask another question. We really need to get back. Now you interrupted my fortune,
so I guess we're square. Did you see what was on the red tile? Yeah, but like,
I'm not the fortune teller, so I don't know what those things mean.
Yeah, I don't know. The first one was a flower. I can't hear anything. No, this is the loudest
segment in any game. Really simulates what it's like to work on one of these cargo ships.
This is so fucking loud. This is way too loud. Oh, did you pause? Guess what? If you alt tab,
the game pauses. Oh, you paused it. All right. Well, you got your pause in.
There's a five second countdown. Yeah, that's so no one has an advantage.
All right, so what's in there? You get three guesses what's in there. Drugs, poison. Really?
You're going with drugs? Yeah, drugs, poison. Where are we? We're in China.
Chinese statue that the American military stole and somehow gets dumped at the bottom of the ocean,
discovered in modern times and curses the people that find it. I can't hear anything.
Who the fuck is that? Oh, I failed the QTE. Oh no. So you get to be passed out. I'm going to jail.
All right. So we're going to have separate stories here then. Oh, okay. Oh shit. I hit. Did you alt
tab? I alt tabbed. Hold on. Yeah. Okay. Thank you. Wanted to make sure we were clear who did this.
All right. All right. Are you ready? Are you ready to mute each other to go to our separate ways? Or
should we just talk to each other? Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to mute. You ready? Yeah. Separate
ways. He can't. He can't. He's gone. Well, aren't you just going to watch me because you're knocked
out? Do you have any choices to make while you're unconscious?
Somebody tell him yes, because I can't. I'll alt tab.
Don't spoil it. Yeah, we're not going to spoil each other's game. We're going for it.
All right. So I'm in jail and he's. All right. So, God.
There's poison. I knew it. I'm going to turn this shit down, but I can't pause the game.
All right. I'm going to, I need to, I'm going to lower the volume. So what was in there?
Uh, ghost gas? Joe, why would you increase the sedation? Why would you do that? Are they asking
the questions? I'm going to, I need to lower the fucking volume here. Tal is Charlie. Yes, I know.
Yes. Can I help you? Tell him I'm lowering the volume. I know. I know. I know. It says I'm
lowering the volume. Are you doing something important? Okay. He'll understand. Now you're
ready. Yes. He'll get it. Okay. Wait, wait. I can, I can also have lowering the game volume.
So I was sorry. I was, I was lowering the alt tabbing would keep me paused. So I'll,
okay. I was lowering the game volume. I suggest you the same thing because it's fucking loud as hell.
All right. You good? We're good. We're back. Let's go. All right. So now I got a picture here.
What if I take a wicked long fucking time? Use a bind? I know it's too late though to pop.
Come back soon. Will he just eventually come find me? Okay. Is it first aid, uh, bin over here?
First aid locker? That was scary. That was fucked up. Is that him? That's not Talos, right? All right.
Get the mouse off the screen before everybody freaks out. Nobody picks up a key like that.
All right. Check the fingernails. Are they dirty? All right. They're pretty clean. Actually,
that one's dirty. Okay. I got a key. Should I like unmute and be like, Hey, I got a key. Do you need
a key? He's got a pen. Should I move them? Uh, I need to move this guy. I, how do I move the,
the dentist or whatever this guy is? What the fuck was that? What is, what's this camera angle?
All right. The graphics are actually pretty damn good. I like the, I like the graphics.
I like the camera. It feels so, I feel like something bad is going to happen any second.
Is this me? All right. I wonder if, is it Alex in here? Found him. I had enough time to read
all the lore. What took you so long? Um, hold on. Just do, do this right now. But if you haven't
done it, um, and when I mean do this, I mean you have to help me do this. How do I make a key bind
to mute myself in discord? Okay. Walk me through user settings, user settings. Got it. The key
binds under app settings is the fourth app settings. Key binds fourth one down. Got it.
Add key bind top right. Add a key button. Blue button. Got it. Okay. Drop down menu for action.
Got it. Mute or deafen and then key bind click and then type the key that you want it to be bound to.
Got it. Hello. I have to, I have to press it again. It's not pushed to talk. Toggle mute.
It should be working. All right. So did that work? Let's test it. Hello. Hello. We're good. All right.
I'm ready. Uh huh. You're good. Okay. You did it. That was, that was a fast turnaround. Honestly,
I probably made discord tech support look bad. Probably did. All right. Here we go.
Professional streamer. When did I ever say that? I'm just a fucking guy, man.
Oh, right. I found a fucking body. Well, you, somebody just told you that. It's okay.
All right. So here we go. Are we controlling this? I believe we're controlling this. Oh,
come on. Come see the body. There's no punch book. Okay. Sorry. I didn't do that. I did.
I did that. It's like, goddamn it. Another pause.
I was pushed. I honestly, I was pushing every button to see if I could punch you before you
punch me. I love this. Can you get in like really close? I'm not already like getting closer to the
camera. Waiting in an elevator. Oh, QTEs. Press A to keep calm. Press A in time with the heartbeat.
Oh, it's a, it's a rhythm game. Okay. Do we, um, does that two or is that the way it is? It's just
two. I am manually beating my own heart. I knew you were going to fail. How did I fail? I knew it.
What? Look what you've done. That's the first L of L moment of the stream. I, but how did I
fail that though? Did I press A again? Maybe I just, I don't know. That was weird. Oh, lol.
That was a funny moment. That one's going in a YouTube video. Is that open? I feel like you and
I just woke up from getting our wisdom. Who did that? I didn't do that. I didn't, I didn't do that.
Pause by Talc says in the top left. That wasn't me. I just, I'm the first one that said I didn't do
that though. What happens if you push right bumper on the controller? Me? Nothing. That's all I did.
I pushed right bumper. That's what I, dude. All right. Well, we're currently walking around in post
dentist days. We both just had our wisdom teeth taken out. This is where you freed me. Um,
I'm like, wow. Can you, how can you, can you come back over here?
You're stuck over there, aren't you? Do you have your own camera now? Yeah. Do you? Yeah. Oh, okay.
Where are you? There's an, oh, there's a note and there's a note and stuff. I read those already.
They're meaningless. Are they meaningless? All right. Well, you are direct. You can like relay
this info to me later. Did you take whatever? What's the, what about the safe? Uh, it's locked.
All right. Most safes do. All right. So we're going to get the combination. I have no means
to open it presently. There was also the body in my room. There was a box behind the body.
Just making sure you know that. Um, where did you go? I'm looking at, um, your childhood photos.
Use the key key. What do you mean key key to a safe? It's a dial. What are you talking about?
Is it a dial safe or is it a key lock safe? Oh, are we getting secret spoilers? What the
fuck are you guys talking about? I found the guy you killed. I didn't kill anybody. I mean, you,
you went to the infirmary. This is the doctor. It's a dial. So I'm just putting two and two together
here. Everyone was screaming at me. They put the key in the safe. Have you guys ever seen a safe
before? Why would I put a key into the same? Oh, they just scared the shit out of me. I thought,
okay, yeah, I thought that was me, but that was you. All right. Who ever designed these things
to probably go back to engineering school? I don't, what was down where you were the body?
Why does right bumper do that? Maybe right bumper is put on pause. Maybe you have it as like a left
click or something from like a bind key or something. Use the key on the door. I did.
What door? I think I found something. Why would they give me full motion control of the face?
Is that you making the noise? What the hell? I don't know what I'm what the helling right now.
I can't see what my character sees. I see you sneaking up on me though.
You said, what the hell? What did you? Yeah. What did you? What the hell? Man. Oh my God. Door.
You guys are a couple of mouth breathers. This looks like poison gas on the ground.
What was that? Did you see that? No, there was a kid. You didn't see what you didn't see that.
Was there a kid? Holy shit. How did you not see that? This guy was you go. I'll go first.
No, you go first. I mean, I want you to be able to see the kid. Take a right. There's a flashing
thing at the end of the hall. Yeah. But the kid went to this way. Listen, horror game kids never
stick around for more than at least a second at a time. That's true. That's true. They are only on
screen for about a tenth of a second. What is that? Hey, Joe, help. Oh, never mind. We should
have gone right. This is main story area. Press the repeatedly on the door. Metallics failed.
What do you mean you've failed? Listen, I want to see the kid now. What? He could be over here
still. All you had to do is press a. Oh yeah. That's what y'all you had to do to hold your
breath when the guy with the gun was walking down the hall. Funny coincidence. Let me try this one.
We try to get it here. Hey, Charlie, I'm gonna need your help over here, man. All right. Ready?
Am I dead too? I think we were supposed to scream. No, that wasn't that wasn't scary,
though. That could have been just somebody saying like, hey, I guess that would be kind of startling.
Well, we have to examine that. No, everybody's dead on the ship now.
Except us, because aren't there like 35 playable characters in this game?
That might be the free to play version. Who's the lucky winner? They're turning into a mobile.
Wait, something over here. Oh, I need to walk. Every character in this game has died.
I'm going down these stairs like my grandfather. This is how my grandfather goes downstairs.
All right, I'm down there. Do you think you're gonna come downstairs? I'm trying,
but the camera reverses and it made me change the forward backward. You're gonna let me go
downstairs because I just see both of our feet. All right. There's a room over here.
Can we go in here? I physically can't see anything. This looks like a no. Is there a door
right there? No. This floor is old LB to walk faster. Is that true? It is very true.
So, uh, is it just me or are you getting a real strange feeling right now?
Do I look like a guy who likes to talk about his feelings?
Oh, there's like everybody's dead. Tough guy. What do you mean strange feeling?
Everyone you've guys have come across are dead. Yeah, we found three bodies so far. Something
weird going on here. You're getting a weird feeling about this. Like three people are dead.
So strange. We're in the military and we see dead people all the time, but this is different.
Hold three. I found a, I found a dentist in the, in the cabinet, but you get a weird feeling about
something here. There's the kid. There's the kid. There's the kid. You see that kid over there?
What kid you're talking about? Oh, so you do. Oh, so I must be the telepathic one. He was over here.
You guys get a weird feeling about this. What happened in here? Somebody just really likes
mannequins and posing them. Who's got the gun? I think I have the gun. You have the brass knuckles.
Wait, where'd you get a knife? Oh, you're going to backstab you.
Oh shit. Are we still together? I think so. Come here. What happened to you? What happened?
What are you like? I'm not doing anything.
Are they saying mute? I think we're supposed to be muted. All right. Mute.
Wait, what? I didn't want to do that. Holy shit. I didn't want to do that.
Why did I do the pro? I thought it was like, I thought it was going to go over there and like
open the door. What? Hey, anything weird going on? Something weird going on? Yeah, something
happened. A Tommy gun wielding man with a man fuchu just, uh, just shot me like a lot. What?
Hold on. I, so who do we, what the hell is that? Monster. Oh shit. Why do I have to get the mud
bumpers this small? If only I had one that was even 5% bigger. I'm going to do like a scratch.
Oh, the misty mountains go. Is that the first chapter? I think that was the tutorial mission.
I learned a lot about the nature of companionship and friendship
and who should have a weapon taking point against the monster.
Um, well, you see what happened on my screen was you were a little kid
and you shot the kid. I shot at the little kid. Well, no, you weren't a little kid. I didn't know
where you were. And the little kid ran away. And then I, I shot at a device that I didn't know I
was shooting by the way. I thought I was going to go over and open the door, but I ended up shooting
into the thing that. Yeah, that was me. I don't know, but I, I don't know. You killed me though.
So that's one for you. One point for you. One point to Gryffindor.
Oh no, this is supposed to be the anthology intro, right? Yeah. We're doing, we're going to kill the
other stream of the mouth. He's going to go like, welcome to, uh, castedly tales of death and
destruction and decay. Our next story. That's what's going to happen. I'm fucking lost.
All right, but what if the credits just rolled and we were back to main menu?
Uh, if the credits just rolled right now, that would be bad because that would mean that
we spend that much money. That's true. It's going to open. Here it comes. A man and his wife spend
an evening on their anniversary. Here we go. Yep. And if Madonna's filmed in front of a live studio
audio, he's holding that close to his face because he can't see it's BF Bugleberry.
I am the curator, the curator of stories, stories of love and hate, greed and beauty, life and death.
Stories such as this one. I'm here to record the story you choose to tell. You see, this tale is
only part written and the choices you make will complete it and determine whether the lives of
those with whom you are interfering continue to flourish or whether they are snuffed out.
See, I got all a writer's block recently. You're going to have to help me out to write the rest
of my story. Decisions according to our own moral. Am I getting paid for this? And we have to live
with those decisions. Unfinished stories. But you shouldn't fear death. That was just something
Telltale did. Inevitable. It is the tax one pays for having lived and it comes eventually.
Oh, taxes, taxes. What the fuck, taxes? None of us want for it to come too soon,
do we? Sometimes you will be determining a story together, sometimes separately.
So make sure you mute. So one of us may not make a complete sense to the other because we all have
different perspectives. As in life, the actions you take matter. The choices you don't say it
will don't say it. He already did. I'll be a close eye on your progress. It's not my place
to interfere, but I might be persuaded to offer the occasional hint. Here's one for free. There
are pictures in this world that can show you some possible future. It's just a really elaborate
escape room. You can find them and study them. They may just help you to make better decisions.
Or should I say decisions that result in outcomes you would prefer? We'll talk again
soon enough. We'll have the opportunity to account for all the actions that you've taken.
Do you know where Zoomer haircuts come from? I don't know. Justin Bieber? Have you ever seen
Brad Pitt in Fury? No. They have military cuts like that. I thought that was Justin Bieber.
Justin Bieber did that, right? No, Bieber had long hair and then he had short hair.
But the Bieber is like, I don't get my hair cut. Oh, so me. I have a Bieber. Witty Brad.
Okay, you're Brad. Brad's motivated. Wait, are you seeing this? Yeah, I'm seeing this.
Got a couple of brews. Motivated Alex. Wait, Brad. Brad's brother. Julia's boyfriend.
Are we both that stupid that we couldn't figure that out together?
So, hang on. Does the guy with glasses not have a significant other?
The water. Diving. Maybe you can show me how the pros do it. You don't have 20-20 eyesight.
You're not a Chad. Encouraging, annoyed. I get to read your mind here. Say nothing.
We get to be like the guardian angels watching over our two people that we're protecting here.
Like you and I eating popcorn. Like, hey, you're his guardian angel. I'm his.
What's he gonna say? Oh, easy. Be cool. What? Julia and Conrad are, you know, how do I say it?
Super fucking loaded. So? Don't sweat the little stuff, man. It's not cool. Don't make me regret
letting you tag along. Why'd you choose saying nothing? Because I didn't want to fucking start
a problem. Tag along? Seriously? I thought I was invited. All right, amigo. Calvary's
almost here. Cool. Sorry I'm a little snappy. I'm just a new medical school would be stressful,
you know? Total shocker. And man, the long distance thing. Julia, it's been rough.
It's been like two weeks. Okay. Yep. Right on cue. What? Conrad doesn't think we have enough.
What if we both just do silence each time? We don't communicate the entire time.
Relationship updated. What's in there? Oh, it's got a seed box. So, uh, can I get your input on
something? What's in there? Yeah, what? Just, uh, kind of a big thing I'm trying to make a decision
about. What's in the seed box? I don't know. That was weird. It was a device or something.
Kind of a big life choice, you know? Is there something under the carpet? I don't know what's
the right thing to do. Go with your gut. Okay. If it's right, you'll know. We're giving each
other advice. Yeah, that's changing our, uh, direction wheels. Julia, reckless. Conrad's
sister. Conrad, Julia's brother, relaxed. Foolhardy. I think I recognize that guy.
Sorry. Connie, this is Alex. Hey, what's up, man? Conrad. Watch it, sis. Lady killer.
I recognize him too. Yeah, that's somebody. Who's that? Is that the dude that plays Iceman in X-Men?
Wait, why are you deciding what the- What are you deciding?
I would have gone with minutes, way less needy.
So, first dive, you and me? I imagine you two over there doing the same thing.
I get a better view when I'm behind. What? No. Warmer back there too. What? Oh, here come the
other characters. Why did you puke? Why did you- Where's the old crust bucket skipper anyhow?
Why did they do like the puke thing? Impatient. Captain of the Duke of Milan. Courageous. Okay.
I'd invite you to make yourselves at home, but- Awkward. Ready to go? How come I didn't get a
beer? Because he asked me- Conrad asked me if I wanted one. Why didn't- Because we're cool now.
What do you- What do you got? What are you selling? What the hell is going on? I don't know. You
wouldn't say, hey guys, like sit down. You're going to hurt somebody. That's a lawsuit incoming.
All right, who's dead first? You want to just pick one and just like just that's it? Like,
okay, let's just pick who cares if we like them or not? Like we're going to try to- I was saying,
let's guess who's going to die first, but you want to like pick someone to kill. I thought that-
You want to go lie down? Yeah. You know, maybe I should. Because I vote for myself.
I vote for the guy that fell down. All right. Mute. Over here. That's pretty far out of the way.
I'm just thinking about backup targets in case we don't find anything on the dive cam.
Listen to me. I've never heard of this wreck you're looking for. Usually these things are
crawling with divers. Yeah, this one's different. I'm just saying if it gets too late, I know some
nice places where you can just take, you know, a nice dive. A nice dive. Um, Brad did his homework.
Who was that? Was that Italian? Okay, look, you're the client. I'm just saying we don't have unlimited
daylight. I'm going to go help Conrad and Julia with the camera. What you got? What you got?
Feast your eyes on this. We found a plane. A plane? Brad's calculations were right on the money.
Always bet on Brad. Kid's a whiz. We should thank him. You gotta, you gotta keep that person
around. We are ready to dive. They waited until they came out here to find- Technically, we should
call this in to port authorities as an unreported wreck. Well, technically. Are you sure you don't
get any money? Do you want money or not, bro? We could be rich. Wait, are you saying we shouldn't
dive? Can't dive? What the fuck? Um, fine, you don't want to dive? Okay, let's not dive then.
Guys, look, I think we gotta listen to our experienced- No, I wanted to dive. Oh, I see.
I'm sucking up right now. I see. What the hell? Wait, what?
What? No, no, no, it's not. I'm just saying she's right, not because she's beautiful.
I mean, she is beautiful, but that's like a coincidence. I feel like I'm watching- She's
the captain. Look, we paid for this dive. Generously. We're diving. We're diving. To the client.
But if anything goes wrong- I just can't wait to be the first one down there. Can you imagine?
Untouched? First to die. God, I just can't wait to be the first one to go down there and
guarantee the dive. First. I'll set up the tanks. The boys will do the final checks.
Take a look at the camera. See if you can find anything useful. Righto. He looks right over into
the lens, like in this camera. He's like, hey guys. I believe we're back. Hey, hey. Hey, sweetie.
I think we're in good shape. It's probably not a bad idea for you to have a clue how these things
work. Gotta say, not too happy with our captain at the moment. Did you see that? They see what?
Seriously, where does she get off bitching about? What is that? She's making a small fortune on the
street. I don't see anything. Yeah, not that small. I don't know if that's like a bug or if it's
supposed to disappear when I look directly at you. All right. I'm going to get these
rebreather set up. Why? What are you laughing about? This is just ridiculous. All right. Are
you right? And then we'll go through the final steps together. Cool. Just holler at us when
you're ready. Don't pick up the binoculars. She's in the frame. Don't pick up the binoculars.
It's a waste. Maybe you'll see something I don't. I don't know. Wait, didn't you say what the heck
was that? Yeah, I was like a game glitch. Game glitch or did you see something? That kind of
question will get somebody killed. This is out of focus. Oh, what was that? Did you see the thing?
No, I'm looking for the sun to look directly at it. It's not here. I didn't see anything.
The first impression on the lovely Fliss. Okay, now three, don't call her the she's a person,
not a thing. And four, do you ever even think about anything else? Hey, ladies got a thirst
and I'm here to quench it. And what's with all the numbers? Oh, yeah, I forgot. Bro's afraid of math
and that's fine. Gotta say trying to like get into your conversation. I saw that.
Wait, no, I can't pause on my side. Well, I will never push this button. The next time I push this
button, I will uninstall the game. It's RB. RB? Arby's? That sounds good to me.
We paid top dollar to come out here in the middle of nowhere to do whatever he wants
without any namby pambies breathing down our neck. Is RB's good? Have you ever had it?
I'm serious, Connie. All right, I'm gonna get these rebreather set up. 29 degrees,
they do in Celsius the same, America. Is this? No, this is China. Are we still in China? Are we
still supposed to be in China? Do you know how to use that? Not really. Wanna just let it do its
thing. I'm just like turning. What? I just got like a QTE when you came over and said slam dunk.
Oh, captain, my captain. Slam dunk. You know, we have rules out here for a reason. You guys gotta
respect that. At least you showed me a little respect. I'm stuck in here. Even if you're the
only one in the group. One of my options to speak is I like it when you're strict. I didn't catch
that. Hey, I like it when you're strict. Sometimes I just want to be kept in line. You know what I'm
saying? I don't mind a little submission now and then. Is there no way for you to turn that off?
Turn one off. That thing where you have to hit on me like every two seconds. Somebody wrote this.
I'm just standing next to you. Can I be like, hey, dude, you're a fucking annoying person.
So is it working? Do you have brain damage in my upstairs brain or my downstairs brain?
I have to tell you. I can't leave. I'm getting a little concerned about the cavalier nature of
this dive. These rules are all pretty basic stuff. I look left and right. How much experience do you
have with these kind of dives? Oh, you're in this? Yeah, I stood right next to you.
Why are you in this conversation? I've done a couple of wrecks over the years.
So you heard all that. You know, experienced. If this is your first unreported wreck, then you
should know there's a very specific protocol you have to follow. For all you know, this could be a
war grave. Disturbing it would be illegal and immoral. How is it immoral? I love just the wheels
turning in your head. You know, you're even more intoxicating when you're angry. And I am ready to
get wasted. You have literally never spoken to a woman before in your life. Have you? No. Hmm.
It shows. No. No. Hey, come play with this thing. It's cool. He's very confident for someone who's
never spoken to a woman before. Wait, something down there? No, there was a computer. Wait,
didn't the guy say? Look at the pictures. This is a fake license. I don't know what that was.
They misspelled height. Height is misspelled? Yeah, H-I-G-H-T. Really? I didn't pick up on that.
What's up? How you doing? Sorry, that bruski got the better of me.
Was there something important on that license that I'm supposed to know?
Geez, man. You should know how to handle your liquor. I was trying to- Just try to bond with
Conrad, like you said. My guzzling bruise? Come on. Okay, okay. You go hit the high seas.
I'll be up when I'm good. Uh-oh. All right. Tanks are ready.
All right, tanks are ready. You ready to go for a dive? Hold on. Listen, hold on. Hey. Hello.
Hey. Hey. That was strange. I gotta get my steps in. How are you feeling?
Shouldn't have had that beer. Shouldn't have had that beer. Can I talk to you again?
You know your brother can't handle his drink. Oh, shut up. Just a little seasick.
Yeah, my brother's fine. I'll be up as soon as I- Come and take- Conrad, give me a hand. Okay.
Wait, did I just? Yep. I think I just got a yoink. I just yuck you. It takes all that CO2 that you
normally just exhale into the water and instead it gets totally reused. Then it reduces decompression
time on your way up. State of the art. Okay. O2 check done. Is that a- No, that's a streamer
backpack. I mean, TwitchCon is in just 20 days. Thanks for sending me streams. Thanks for sending
me straight. Oh, hey guys. What? Jesus. Why are you so loud? I almost completely forgot. When I
was looking at the dive cam, I saw this huge hole in the tail. Kabooey. That's your way into the
plane. Oh, nice work, man. I actually did see that. You're welcome. Am I going down? I'm gonna go see
what Fliss is up to. You behave, Connie. When you dive, I'm gonna take control of the boat and just
leave. Nope. Definitely. Definitely. You're on camera. I'll take the wheel. Let's get a before photo.
Selfie stick. Because of the- I thought I was holding the shield. I thought I was holding
the shield. You ever have to use one? On a shark? Nope. What the fuck was that? Think about the
implications. All right. Here we go. You ready? I think it's time to mute. Yeah. Hey, good luck.
See you later. Or not. Don't you fall backwards in a dive? You go backwards in. Why mute? Because
Alex is getting a completely separate story connected to the one I'm doing, too. I think
I've seen the same thing you've seen. Oh. Well, eventually. Yeah, eventually. In about 25 seconds.
Unless I become the other character. You might. Howdy, captain. You fancy a pint with your second
in command? You are not my second in command. Third in command. No. Fresh and eager cabin boy.
Are you that? I'm the shark. I'm controlling it right now. Over a frosty amber liquid.
Pass. I have to stay focused on your friends down there. All right. Mute. Pretty nice ride you got
here. Where'd you get the cash? Shut up. Leave me alone. You know it's not polite to ask a lady
about her money. Fair enough. I was just thinking about buying a bug myself and I thought maybe-
At this point, just go sit over there. Sorry. I haven't got enough on my plate for the moment.
Rowdy is Fliss. I just freaky fighted you out of your own body and now I'm Alex.
It's all good. All right. So here we go. I'm controlling. Was that you or me? I'm on the
boat. What? I'm on the boat right now. I'm Fliss. We're not in the same- We're at different video
games. Okay. I thought- I thought I was just seeing what you were doing. Oh, no. All right.
Let's mute it. Wow. That is not your everyday wreck. I hope those clowns don't get me in trouble.
Mattel found a picture. I hope he's okay down there. Wait, binoculars. Nice.
Oh, Monka S. Monka S. Hold on. I- I missed it? What do you mean blind?
These things are all fucking scratched up and like scuffed up. What are you guys talking about?
Oh. Oh my god. It's a fucking buoy. All right. Let's talk. Can I talk to you? Let me get one
of those beers. I want a beer. It is you- I got to do some boat maintenance. Like, let's go.
I gotcha. Serious. Enjoy your vacation. Yeah, sure. Enjoy your vacation. Watch me.
All right. I gotta go clean like the bathroom or something. All right. To go boat maintenance,
I gotta go like re-oil the engine. Clean the sofa. Go fishing. Change the oil. What does- what
happened? What does- what happened to the maintenance? What is this? Okay, that was a gun.
That was a gun. Well, he's finding all these secrets. That's not fair. Am I gonna read a book?
Should I hold on to this? All right. Grab the book. Shroud of Innocence. God damn it. That one
wasn't me. I- you did that. I know. I pressed right bumper because somebody in- I got- mm-hmm. Yep.
What? That's all I needed to hear. That's all- what do you mean that's all you needed to hear?
I just wanted to make sure I'm not the crazy one. That right bumper actually pauses the game for no
discernible reason. One person said hit right bumper and I was like, why? Okay. And I just did
it. So I'm an idiot. All right. See. What was in the bag? No, it can't go in the backpack. All right.
So what do I need to do? Boat maintenance. I don't know what that means. What's in there?
No, don't go. What do I do here? Can I like change their oxygen levels? Oh, that's- what is that?
Clouds? What? There's another boat coming up on our- wait a minute. Give me the binoculars.
What? Okay. They're just here now. We have unexpected guests. Okay. Don't- don't talk about
the divers. Just relax. Do not mention we have people in the water. No. What do you think they
want? Maybe they're fishermen. Maybe that's their buoy. Okay. Be on guard. Be ready for this. I don't
know. Just be on guard. What's that about? That's not the Coast Guard. That is not the Coast Guard.
So we're not under arrest. Uh-oh. What's happening? I think I'm going into phase two.
Uh-oh. Hey, guy. Hey, get out of here. Get out of here. What do you think you're doing? Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. I hope I just didn't like kill italics.
Why did you just- money? Why are you flashing your money?
You think it's more like 30. I can do 30. All right. You guys drive a hard bargain,
but I'm with you. Here. Let's just throw in the whole pot. Let's go. No.
You are an idiot. What? They left, didn't they? That doesn't make you any less of an idiot.
That's true. A funny way of saying thank you, Conrad. Hear a piece of work, Conrad.
I'm not all work. I'm a little play, too. Are you trying to flirt with me?
Is it working? I don't even know what it is. Well, he sucks. When you think of something,
I'll just be over here taking in the view, flirting up a storm. Hashtag wink.
They're going to come back. We've got to get out of here.
Okay. I think they're on their way back up. And I was getting used to it just being you and me.
We need to light the grill. Oh, oh. Pick me. Pick me. You can call me Grill Capitan.
You may light the grill, but I will never call you that.
It's time for food. Watch this be how he does. I didn't have to do anything. He just like...
Okay.
Are you serious? I thought about it. I thought about it. I thought about it.
Yeah, I'm on the boat, too. Yep, that's true. I thought about it.
It was so close. I was set. I was a millimeter away from letting the boat just burn.
Everything's all right now. Hey, welcome back.
You almost killed me again, but this time I was smart.
There was a little mishap. A little issue with barbecue.
Jesus. Looked like the whole boat was lit up.
I thought the video games were to escape reality. Anyway.
These fishing guys came by and ran into the dive line.
Yeah, these idiots. They were just like, who cares?
Did you get ripped up? Did I get ripped up? Did I mess you up?
Just fucking perfect.
No, but I did pull the flight stick of the plane and it broke the plane in two.
Interesting so far. Let's see. Frankly, I hate it.
Getting to know these intrepid adventurers then.
Alex and his little brother Brad trying to swim with the big fish.
Both seem out of their dead. And Julia, the love of Alex's life.
If only she felt the same. What about Conrad?
A bold fellow, you might say. Or maybe you'd say arrogant.
And then there's Captain Fliss. Strong, forthright, stubborn.
She appears somewhat immune to Conrad's charms. So far, at least.
Let me reassure you. You can help them to make some decisions they'll value later on.
You're doing well. Thanks.
We can't let you lose yet. There's still three hours of gameplay.
You're doing very well. You didn't let the boat burn from the barbecue. Good job.
You have the intelligence of at least a nine-year-old.
How well preserved was the plane? Brad, it was insane. It was like traveling through time.
No shit.
Well, it was like traveling through time and accidentally ending up in a dimension
where the past is underwater and everything is covered in barnacles and sharks.
Sharks?
Yeah, well, just one shark.
Wasn't Conrad going to get us some more beers after he helped Fliss?
Maybe he decided, hey, I'll drink some.
And then he got drunk.
Why don't you go get more beers in the ocean?
And since he was drunk, he forgot to bring it to us.
And he just kept on drinking and he drank all of it.
I think there were four beers in that case.
That sounds like he had some experience with this kind of phenomenon.
Yeah, I've been studying it for years.
I'll go look for him.
Yeah, why don't you get a run to the grocery store and get us some stuff?
I left it below deck if you want to check it out.
OK, now I'm.
Oh, wait, what's that?
So what are you seeing?
I'm about to grab the camera.
Oh, I want to see the cool pictures you took.
Nice.
OK.
Pretty cool looking.
This is how you took these.
This badge.
Conwin Island.
I was totally right.
All right, what else?
Can I put the camera down?
Oh, that's a good one.
Oh, that's scary.
I don't I did you to act.
All right, put this down.
They only dive 30 meters.
OK, yeah, OK.
But Oculus, let's take another look.
Let's take another look.
What about this thing?
Didn't mean to ruin your big moment.
It's OK, really.
Come on, you're supposed to be like the techie.
You can't like open this up
and take the battery out and use it to power some.
What's going on down here?
Uh, there's everybody else.
I'll go get them.
Why don't you just do it here?
Who's that?
Hey, you see my brother or Fliss?
Uh, no, I got distracted.
Let's go get him.
Sure.
So which one is, uh, you know, where the magic happens?
Where is it?
It's Alex.
Is he upstairs now?
Oh, no, that's not OK.
Hey, we're standing next to each other now.
Conrad, beers.
Where are they?
We are, yes.
Oh, yeah, the beers.
I was just getting them now.
Nice.
There's four in there.
We can all have one each.
And that's it for the whole entire trip.
All right.
Now that everybody's here,
let's take a look at the navigator's pad we found.
Maybe we can figure out why the plane was out here.
Where did you put it?
It's in your case.
OK, I'll go get it.
Hey.
Hey, uh, hey, are you going to say something?
No.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
I think I like this.
I think I accent.
All right.
I'm just OK.
Alex.
Holy crap.
Were you guys like in the plane?
I'm talking about your, uh, your adventure.
Got out in the nick of time.
Skin of our teeth.
Well, our skin was almost in a shark's teeth.
What?
Uh, yeah.
Didn't I tell you there are sharks around here?
Uh, but you saw a shark.
Most of them are.
I did see a shark.
Yeah, I thought it was you.
It almost got me.
So does the accident mean we can't do any more diving?
That's a good question.
Let me just say this once more for the record.
Going into that plane was super dangerous, obviously,
and twice as illegal.
Where are you?
Now damage is done, so we just have to lie about it forever.
Or else we're going to go to jail.
I'm exploring.
Oh, OK.
Well, my lips are sealed.
So we're going again tomorrow?
I thought I was going to learn something there.
You should be looking at this, because that's just all of our adventures.
We're all going to stay on the boat.
I think it's too dangerous.
I think it's too dangerous to go in the water.
I didn't even get to do anything.
Brad are for Brayson Lee.
You got a girlfriend?
Barbecue.
Are you with me?
I do.
No, I'm talking to Conrad.
Oh, I mean, I did.
Broke up with her, though.
Just too much to handle.
Women, right?
Yeah, women.
There's another boat just rolled up.
They exist.
You're correct.
They definitely exist, especially the one you just broke up with.
That one, for sure.
Right here.
Hey.
Yeah, I know, right?
That's how I feel.
What the heck?
We got places to be and things to do.
Here comes the drinks.
Enjoy it.
All right, if you drink, you die, guaranteed.
The first person to take the first sip is the person that we kill first.
Check it out.
I don't think we'll have to try.
I think they'll just die.
Screenshot that.
Who wants to find some sunken treasure?
So what do you think, Adam?
Coordinates?
Those are coordinates, all right.
Maybe the plane's destination.
You think we could get there by tomorrow?
It takes a couple hours if the weather's...
Is this what I found underwater?
I think so.
You find anything else?
There was a flight plan on board that seemed to indicate it was a rescue plane.
Yeah, that makes sense.
After the war, they turned long-range bombers into rescue planes.
And then this plane must have been shot down because it was riddled with bullet holes.
I found one lodged in a fuselage.
Huh.
And it was full of life rafts.
It must have gotten shot down before they could deliver all the rafts.
There was only one missing.
From the photos Alex took, you can see the flight badge on one of the corpses.
That means the crew is from Conwin Island,
smack dab in the middle of the Pacific theater.
Called it.
Reckless, all of you.
Excuse me?
I told you to leave everything down there alone.
Oh, come on.
We've been through this already.
I'm not talking about the love.
Then what?
Superstition?
Is that it?
Really?
The dead don't sleep well in these waters.
Constant conflict.
Makes me feel silly enough to you all, but I was raised on this shit and it sticks.
You're right.
We should have been more careful.
That's not me.
I'm sorry.
I'm lying.
Okay.
Maybe.
True, but I'm lying.
I don't know you.
But you're lying.
You should have never gone down to that plane in the first place.
It's bad luck.
You think you can scavenge down there and it makes no difference,
but every single thing you bring back has an essence.
It's like a ghost you invite to the surface.
Here we go.
Huh.
I never thought about it like that.
You never think about much of anything.
Well, maybe I never heard about such cool ghost stories.
They're not cool ghost stories.
Not like for fun.
People drown in these waters and you have to respect their resting place.
Damn straight.
Fred, you got a fun ghost story, right?
Yeah, I heard a story.
Happened right around here too.
Let's hear it.
We could all use a good show.
I'm turning this character around.
Let's hear it.
I bet you can spin a good yarn.
It's kind of messed up, actually.
Scare away, little bro.
Okay, here goes.
This story is true.
It had happened right near here in an old lighthouse.
Classic setup.
Wait, true story?
Where'd you hear this?
Wait, can somebody take a sip out of their fucking beer?
Are you making up the story to go along?
Ah, well, down by the dockside.
Dude, these are empty.
Where'd you get these?
Skin like a leather book.
Eye patch, wooden leg, the whole nine yards.
And for a dollar, he told me his secrets.
Okay, here we go.
The lighthouse stood atop in a toll.
Isolated from the rest of the world.
A lone beacon in the night.
A sailor's respite.
The lighthouse keeper would hear the waves pounding the rocky shore.
One misty morning, he comes upon a woman covered in blood.
She's stumbling down the beach.
He hurries to her aid, and she falls into his arms, sobbing.
As he hurries her back to the lighthouse, he asks where she's from.
He doesn't waste any time.
Smooth.
Let me interject.
Key of the one-track mind.
The woman answers.
That's what you had to do?
That's what I had to do.
Just give a response?
Of course.
I was doing, it's pretty popular nowadays.
They're alone for years.
You just watch a video, and then you say two things about it,
and that's the whole screen.
So they go to the top of the lighthouse, and there,
splayed on the floor, is a man and a woman brutally murdered with an axe.
Always an axe.
I mean, do people even use axes anymore?
Okay, fine.
Then it was a meat hook.
They were slashed with a meat hook and hung from the rafters.
Wait a minute.
Are you changing the murder weapon?
I thought this was a true story.
A lot of blood.
A lot of carnage.
You can, things get told over generations if you lose a little bit of detail.
Who did it?
The woman says, it was my brother.
And she turns to the closet and says, he's hiding in there.
Great, blame the brother.
So the lighthouse keeper creeps over to the closet, opens the door,
and sure enough, there's a man inside,
but he sliced out his own insides with a meat hook.
Horrified, he looks closer to see the dead man's face in the dark.
Closer, closer.
And he sees, it's his own face.
And then it's eyes bulge out and screams.
Nice play, Dex.
You're so gross.
Ah, that's terrible.
Super twist.
Nice.
Nice one, Squire.
You let me go in.
Thunder.
Summoning thunder.
Maybe I'm a cheese there, corn dog.
Okay, you've all had your fun.
We should all turn in.
There's some weather hitting, are we?
Uh-uh.
No, no, no, no, because according to standard vessel regulation,
we're all required one more beer before hitting the hay.
What regular issues are these?
It's standard issue regulatory institutional protocol subdivision 1099.
Uh-huh.
Where'd you read that?
The internet.
Oh, so you found a website that tells you to drink beer under every circumstance.
I'm just following orders, man.
I'm into this website.
And for good, buddy.
And I'm out.
Yep.
Yeah.
Well, you really can't add anything.
No, nothing to add to that one.
By the way, the ship's gonna sink.
Like, imminently.
Yes.
No, I mean, seriously, I saw a photo.
Oh.
All right, storm incoming.
Is this, like, the Kingdom Hearts characters?
Scary guy.
It's Mickey.
Oh, God.
Oh, is this, like, is this you?
I'm on the bed.
I punched the guy in the face.
Oh.
So about that boat from earlier.
About that.
This they would just know.
Was it the same people?
I don't think so.
I can't tell.
They're in, like, hoods.
Well, it's raining outside.
Uh-oh.
All right.
What's your decision?
Uh.
Captain.
You would choose the captain when you're all tied up.
You gotta choose the captain.
The captain, it's gotta, that's the decision maker.
Just keep the tape on my mouth.
Don't take it off me.
Talk.
Of course he chooses her.
Yeah, the brother and sister.
Why wouldn't I choose brother and sister over that guy?
That's like Deadpool in Wolverine Origins.
We both can't talk.
We didn't think this through.
Neither of us can speak.
Hold on.
What's going on?
Why?
What was that whole scenario?
I didn't ungag you and you didn't ungag me.
So we both can't talk.
Is that what we were supposed to be doing?
Yeah.
I got the captain because I...
That's just like we play it.
Ow.
Oh, it hurts.
Why does that always hurt?
Hey, so...
No one's ever had that in a movie taken off and go...
The bad news is these are kind of maybe the fishermen I missed off earlier.
Oh, god damn it, comrade.
Great.
Just great.
And the good news?
I recognize them.
How was that good news?
I thought you were gonna ask the good news first.
You're such an idiot, Jesus.
We have to get free right now.
So are you seeing what I'm seeing or are you in a different room?
No, you're Alex, right?
Yeah.
You're what?
Are you...
Wait, I'm Alex and...
Who are you playing as?
Conrad.
Yeah.
No, I know I'm Conrad.
I didn't know if he was controlling anybody in this room.
I didn't know if you were anybody, somebody else.
I'll be back for you later.
I tried to help.
All right.
See you later.
You can go fuck yourself, you piece of shit.
You're the little lady.
There's no QTE there.
I would have dodged it.
This guy just...
Seriously.
Uh, all right, I...
I'm gonna try to save this.
Oh, no.
Don't do it.
Slow down.
Easy.
Uh...
No, he...
When he opens his mouth, bad things happen.
Should have kept the tape on my mouth.
Kill Conrad.
Yep.
You would not believe what I just saw.
They got fucking...
There's a carnival up there.
There's clowns.
There is food and shit.
It's really...
It's kind of fun.
Really?
Did you see what I saw?
Yep.
It was pretty interesting.
That's, uh...
Considering I was watching half the things that happened through this looking glass.
They're just traveling clowns.
That's good news.
All right.
Here we go.
What's the game plan here?
Uh, I don't know.
I have no idea what's happening right now.
I just was sitting in the room.
Oh, that's you.
You're controlling.
We found some scissors while you were gone.
Oh, that's good.
So you have...
Do you have scissors?
Um, I think I still have scissors.
Do you have a weapon?
Did you see, like, a man in...
Yeah, that's the guy.
That's the guy telling the story.
That's the guy writing in the book.
That's what I thought.
He's watching.
He's...
So he's a clown too?
Yeah, he's making sure that we make the right decision.
How much money they have?
Yeah, they said that to do the full juggling act, it was going to be $1,500.
We need to make sure we can pay for it.
So the next part of this game is a real-time reenactment of what it's like to be
a hostage on a boat for 24 hours.
We're just going to sit here and shit our pants.
We came here on a boat.
Maybe we can take it.
Yeah. Yeah, it's a speedboat.
The main gun. He's got a gun.
Okay, that's a gun.
We got scissors versus, uh, scissors versus gun.
Keep that in mind.
At least one of us can get on their boat.
Get some help.
If you can distract them, I can get on that boat.
The dude with the gun won't even realize until I'm long gone.
Seven seconds.
I can get out through the window.
We gotta break these off first.
Too loud.
They'll hear it.
We're gonna break them during the thunder.
During the thunder.
Good call.
Hey, where's, uh, where's the brother?
He can just tell them a scary story.
You guys, distract them.
Break the window.
Stay focused and get to the boat.
All right, here we go.
Okay, let's do it.
Do I have to break it?
Do you have to break it?
Time it with the lightning.
Remember?
Wait, hold on.
With the thunder, right?
What? Why would you do that?
Why wouldn't you wait for the next thunder?
You were just saying we had to time it with the thunder.
It's gonna happen again.
Now we got, oh, is that me?
How are we supposed to stab him?
What? No, this is me.
Give me the knife.
Get him.
All right.
Buster, it's amateur hour over here.
All right, we've got our own hostage.
I got this.
Let me handle it.
Okay.
What's going on out here?
Wait, do you have one, too?
We both have hostages.
Let's finish this.
All right, I'm going for the gun.
Be ready.
Oh, that didn't.
What? How could you?
Oh, you still have your hostages, all right?
I still got one hostage.
All right, we still got an ace.
Why?
Oh, hey, I can't let sister die.
No.
An eye for an eye.
What?
No.
What happened?
Who's?
We got shot.
Who?
What?
Why did you let that happen?
Why do you go to the gym every day, Alex?
If not for this?
What?
Bring them downstairs.
Take this.
Use it if you have to.
Hold on.
Wait, did you?
Who is?
Did somebody get shot?
Yeah.
He got shot in the leg.
He's fine.
No, who got shot?
Sit.
Upstairs, the girl who's pointing the gun at.
I can't believe we had two hostages and we didn't get that.
Julia's dead?
Yeah.
He's shot her.
Yeah, but then you like shove him out of the way.
I thought, I thought that's what happened.
Why am I getting blamed for this?
We had two hostages in control of the situation.
Which one of you is?
I didn't lose the first hostage.
Why am I getting the blame?
I did lose the first hostage,
but I was going for the gun.
What?
It's okay.
See?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
She's got shot in the face?
What happened?
You guys are overreacting.
We're good.
This is basically the same thing that would happen if we just let them go.
We would have still been hostages if we let them go.
We're hostages now, so.
How could we have been so stupid?
Well, lucky it's not worth.
I could have been killed.
What were you thinking?
Me?
This isn't just about you, Julia.
We could have turned it around and we wouldn't be in this mess right now.
All right?
Shut the fuck up!
I'm not gonna take that from you.
There is no harm in just talking.
We're just talking.
The volume down.
All right, can we get two more hostages again?
I wonder if we can get two hostages.
This time let's go for two hostages and we're gonna play it correct this time.
I like this one.
Knows when to keep his mouth shut.
What?
S, I have a controller in my hand.
There's no S on my controller.
All right, what do I do here?
Okay.
Well, I gotta see like the secret code to get help.
Milan requesting weather update.
Over.
Be like Duke of Milan seeking.
Here we go.
How bad is the storm?
Hey, uh, just requesting any information about this storm you can give us.
It's a little bit hairy out here.
Yep.
There's gotta be a code coming in from the east.
Gotta hit you pretty hard.
It should pass through your coordinates within an hour.
Sound a little stressed, Duke?
Okay.
Please let me know if you need assistance.
Not used to a little weather freaking you out.
My uh, my charter's been a little difficult.
Not exactly going as planned.
We're starting to have some serious problems with...
Hey.
This is being dipped.
So obvious.
Do I get to move around up here?
Oh my god.
He just saved me.
He just fucking rescued me.
You want to talk about like scripted event where she can't die?
Even the fucking bad guy just reached his hand out and saved my life.
What is she stabbing?
I gotta help.
No, I gotta hold.
Hey.
Alright, this is important.
We gotta work together here.
Okay.
Um, we're all in the same room.
I got hit in the face with a frying pan.
What the fuck, Alex?
Not the time.
Oh, you were gone.
Good job looking after number one.
In the face.
Real smooth.
Uh.
Great leadership, Fliss.
So Alex isn't feeling too hot right now.
This is so hot.
Uh, this, yeah, it got louder.
I turned the game volume down.
I don't trust this guy to drive.
He doesn't have any depth perception.
It's funny because I trust this guy.
Because he literally saved my life.
I got, uh, I got scripted.
Why is it picking up that much momentum?
I told you I didn't trust him to drive.
Everybody would have just planted against their insta-died, by the way.
All of us would have flown into the side of that and all of us.
Our boat would have capsized immediately.
Everyone's still alive.
This could have been different.
We did, we did a good job.
Frustrate.
He wants more carnage.
Everybody's still alive.
Kind-hearted creature I am.
I'd like to offer you some forewarning of what's to come.
Tempted?
Uh, should we, should we?
Say nothing.
Prefer, um.
Uh, do we want a tip?
No.
No tips.
Did I choose or did you?
Someone can't decide.
That doesn't bode well.
I said, say nothing.
I said, I don't.
Anyway, now that you've reached a point of significant distress,
I presume you're eager to get back to your story.
But here's the thing.
Everything may not be entirely as it seems.
It's like, yeah, mom, I know I have to do homework.
Like, you just, you came right in the middle of the movie
and like turned on the lights and then started talking.
Mom, I want to watch the movie again.
You shouldn't have said that.
Yeah, but like the trash is full.
It's like, all right, fine.
I'll, I'll do it.
And then she goes to the bookcase and pulls out your favorite book
and it's hollowed out with whiskey bottles.
She starts chucking right in front of you.
All right, here we go.
So where's, uh, is Tom Hanks in this one?
So should we try to keep, should we try to keep everybody alive?
Even the, the bad guys?
Even the bad guys?
At this point, I don't know what it takes to kill anybody.
Go.
I really thought somebody was dead in the hospice.
I thought I, yeah, it looked like somebody got shot in the face.
Did they really have to show all of us doing that?
There was like loading the next game play segment.
Jesus.
Nope, no thanks.
So we have friends now because they're not pointing guns at us anymore.
Apparently, apparently we're just in this together now.
All right, so we figured out who we are by the, yeah.
I'm Conrad.
I'm Julian.
Why are you faster than me?
Just am.
Flashlight, what is this?
This looks like signatures from, hey, hey, what the fuck?
That was like information.
Why would you do that?
They didn't finish writing that lore.
I mean, wouldn't you have wanted to know that?
Did you think I was going to hit you in the head with a clipboard?
That may have been very, very important information.
All right, this is a really cool like Disney interactive experience ride line.
With the actors too that are like, keep moving.
Ooh, that was scary.
Pirates of the Caribbean.
They're right there.
In the modern era.
I just got yelled at.
What do we, what was that?
Handcuffs?
Wait, wait, we can't go that way?
Oh, Conrad's from Salem, Massachusetts.
I dropped my handcuffs.
I just, I just don't know where you want me to go.
There might actually be clowns.
Supermassive loves clowns.
So, I mean, they, yeah, there might be clowns.
I'm just like AI pathing algorithm.
I'm not even a person.
What are you looking at?
I was looking at some clothes.
Some clothes.
What is it?
Anything, anything there we're looking at?
Just some clothes.
You already looked at it then.
Decided I wasn't ready to buy anything yet.
Just browsing.
Leave me alone.
What was that?
Can I, can we investigate?
What?
I, I moved to the steps.
What's going on?
I'm creating a situation.
I don't know how.
This is so dumb.
I love it.
Something over here.
A letter.
You go that way.
I'll go this way.
This is going to get knocked out of my hand.
Do they know where we are right now?
There's going to be some knowledge here.
They know the secret.
They know what happened and they know what's down here.
It's pitch black in here.
We should have killed those hostages when we had the chance.
He's actually going to give us a lamp.
Thanks.
Now we can really tell ghost stories.
He's kind of a nice guy actually.
I kind of sweet-talked him on the boat.
Wait, you had that the whole time?
Why didn't you just put alcohol in your mouth and just like spray it with the lighter into the guy's face?
How is this fucking place?
Dude, even those meatheads seem spooked.
You think this ship is the Manchurian gold?
I do.
We are in the vicinity of those coordinates.
It's still safe to this day.
We can't just sit around.
We need a plan.
How did we?
Nobody died, by the way.
I'm just trying to figure that out.
We're not exactly in the best position to be making any moves.
The second they let their guard down, we've got to take advantage of it and get off the ship.
There's got to be a big finale.
Yeah, man.
This whole rust bucket's one tetanus shot from the bottom of the ocean.
One of the options was, I'm hurt too bad.
Is Conrad really hurt right now?
Yeah, we've got to stay sharp and keep our eyes out for the right moment.
Did you do something?
No.
They spent a distributor cap.
I guess I got punched in the face once or twice.
Yeah, you got punched in the face like once or twice.
So, okay, what exactly is a distributor cap?
In layman's terms, please.
Pretend you're talking to someone who doesn't know anything about boats.
There we are.
Well, typically, a distributor cap is designed to distribute voltage from the coil to the correct
rotor, which in turn...
Glasses guy has to explain it.
It's an essential part of the engine.
We're not taking the Duke of Milan anywhere without it.
It's like, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hold on.
Can I see your glasses for a second?
Yeah, sure.
Can you say that again?
I don't.
I don't know anything about anything.
24 British archaeologists have gone missing.
What?
I picked this up in the bunk room.
I did?
Sounds like this guy is mad at another guy named
Patterson for playing sick to get out of guard duty.
Oh, found the way out.
I guess it's like the third time that happened.
They really must not have liked it in the cargo hold.
Go hold?
What the hell?
I think Conrad found something.
I'm going to check it out.
Love dialogue.
Wait, hold on.
Oh, what?
Why did it just...
Because I found something.
Oh.
More important than whatever you're talking about.
Apparently.
Do we need both people over there?
Hold on.
This is creeping me out.
Let me try to...
Are you over here?
I'm looking at glasses.
And they don't know what to do when you like push A.
That is a map, I think.
Got a map.
Come take a look.
I wonder what happened.
My...
Come take a look.
What?
Are we trying...
Is this you?
We're like ripping each other out of our cutscenes.
Was that you that I just stepped in front of to look at this?
There's a little dog and the name is...
Chip mascot.
We don't know the name.
Private Miller's letter.
We'll be soon and get a job as a mechanic and we can get married and have two children.
We'll be happy together forever.
Got it?
All right.
So who's going to have the stomachache?
I can't.
We gotta go through the vent like a spy.
I can't get it open.
What's going on in there?
Oh, I'm going to puke.
This is ridiculous.
And they open up the door and then we jump them.
Every video.
And then you actually puke on it.
Everybody shut your pants.
Go.
That's not a bad idea.
I think we just gotta find out.
Do you want me to just smash through this wall?
What?
All right.
Yeah, let's go.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Big man on campus.
Someone should create a distraction.
Here we go.
This is going to be loud.
My stomach hurts.
I got shot.
Yeah, okay.
Conrad.
I don't feel good.
Dude, the classic stomachache.
Come on.
All right.
I'm going for smart.
Well, never mind.
We're going.
Wait.
Yep.
Come on.
Stomachache.
Stomach hurts.
That was a little kick.
Did you do a bigger kick?
You really want the president coming after you guys?
Because he will.
Each and every one of you personally.
This is all improv.
Hey, do you hear me?
I'm talking to you.
Hello.
They're not even going to attempt, I guess.
They're not even here anymore.
They like went to go get lunch.
Why are we all running?
Replace it.
Oh, nice move.
Why would you not replace it?
Because we had to get out of there quick.
Oh, she's about to go off the rails.
Julia and Conrad.
Don't barricade.
Use that as a weapon.
That was huge and heavy.
I love where they've done the place.
Come on.
There's only one person with a gun.
It wasn't that guy.
Look, they can't shoot all of us.
Everyone just charge them.
I thought I was you first.
Oh, shit.
What have I done?
I've done it.
It's been a while since our last pause.
Action.
You take that way.
I'm going to take this way.
Let's check in here.
Just keep moving.
No, I don't want to keep moving.
What if there's like med packs in here?
Oh, fragrant.
Where's reach in and dig around?
Press S.
I see you.
I was trying to come in
and it wouldn't let me, but I couldn't see you.
I just thought I was getting bounced off the wall.
You just did the,
I'm a guaranteed player controlled character.
That's like the second time they've done that.
What did you get?
Like rats?
Yeah.
Or bats?
I got rats.
All right.
Well, nothing in here.
There's no sense of urgency right now.
Yeah.
Well, the thing is like all the other characters,
the NPCs are just standing awkwardly
in the middle of the hallway.
I feel like I'm playing Spy Party.
Dozens of people on board.
That's why I was saying that guy.
I would have absolutely,
I would have sniped you right there
because there was no way you were an AI.
I mean, yeah, there's no way you were actually like,
you were definitely player controlled.
All right.
Well, this seems important.
What did he say?
I don't know.
Probably doesn't matter.
What was that?
What's that?
I just knocked the board off the wall,
but I didn't do that.
It just fell.
The ghost.
I can't go in there.
I got a little rat scare.
I didn't touch anything.
Are you in this room too?
Are you in the bathroom?
No.
I gotta go for now.
There's some commotion outside.
That usually means I'm about to be real busy for a while.
Right again soon.
There's a little boy on board and it sounds like Ted.
Oh, I am in the bathroom.
Mess with me.
There ain't no way we got to stow away.
All right.
You keep looking in the bathroom.
You keep finding secrets.
I haven't found any of these creepy NPCs.
What?
The captain is always like two steps in front of me,
just waiting for me.
That wasn't you?
That was not you.
I thought that was your shadow.
Oh, I see.
I saw that.
I'm trying to get to it.
These are like tank controls.
We have split up to a point where I don't even know where.
Oh, there you are.
There you are.
This place is fucking massive.
Is it super massive?
Good luck leaving.
Wait, how did you?
What?
Good luck leaving.
The something scary just happened music play,
but I didn't see anything.
I saw the guy.
The guy?
Yeah.
You aren't seeing like...
I ain't seeing nothing, man.
I read like one document.
Are you going to like hide in a closet
and am I going to like shoot you again?
Hope not.
I shouldn't have hid.
I should have just stayed out in the open.
How do you read books?
I'm waiting for you to open it so I can read over your shoulder.
It won't open.
That's actually what's happening.
There's structural problems with the ship.
Some electronic equipment is malfunctioning.
I saw a clown down the hallway.
Clean the floor.
Added lead to the soldiers.
Spell book.
Very informative.
Hey, I found something over here.
What is that?
A tooth?
All right, I found a dinosaur tooth.
Okay, now I got to find something cool.
No, it's dinosaur head.
Check out that dinosaur.
That's a dinosaur head.
I only find books.
One of them's got to have whiskey in it.
Uh-oh, there's a painting here.
Oh, this one's long.
Why is there a flashlight?
My book.
I don't even know who that was.
It's got multiple pages.
I don't have time for this.
Do you want me to tell you a story?
Sure.
No, you don't want to hear it.
All right, why was it just completely silent that whole time?
That was weird.
Nobody said a word.
Like none of our party?
They were just kind of walking?
Everyone was just walking with their mouth closed.
It's because they don't want the other bad guys to hear.
Well, I guess I won't read the rest of that book.
Did I get left behind?
I don't know, did you?
This is very difficult to multi-box.
Hey, let's just put like four pages per book in everything you find,
but you don't even have time to read it.
What is that thing?
What's with the sand castle builder?
The like bucket.
I don't understand.
What is that for?
Is it like the engine, the battery, the boat?
It's a Burger King crown.
Look, it's the distributor cap from the Duke.
Oh, the distributor cap.
Yeah, I'm sure.
All right, I think it's time for this guy to get read.
You know what I mean?
I thought we were sparing everyone in the whole game.
I'm going to go get it.
Wow, really?
You're going to fall for that?
See ya.
Oh, no.
Is she going to get read?
Just get it.
Did you make us do this?
Yes, just all of us go.
You know which upper body strength that takes?
Holy crap.
All right, you and I are going to have to read this guy.
Are you up or down?
I'm up.
Don't drop that.
Throw it strategically to distract them.
I'm trying to warn them.
Okay, if you have the opportunity to read this guy, do it.
I physically don't know who I'm supposed to be
because I haven't made a decision in 10 minutes.
Here we go.
What?
What is going on?
He doesn't have a weapon.
That's the famous one-handed chokehold.
He's got a flashlight.
So?
And he's been drinking Gatorade.
Wait.
What the fuck?
What if we just all get caught, get put back in the same room
and escape the same way and have to do all this again?
I didn't do that.
Rowdy is deciding.
This is...
I like the way we game this game.
Oh, shit.
No.
It rolled right into him.
I see you.
Come on.
I just led.
Wow.
Hey, at least I got him.
Let the record show that I'm not responsible for anything that has happened.
At least I fucking chipped a tooth.
That's all I care.
Did we actually get put back in the room?
I think I'm on my own.
So, see you on the other side.
See you later.
Good luck.
Where are you taking me?
So, he's Alex.
What if I got too close and he did that to me from this way too?
Get back there.
Be ready.
Take him out.
Oh, no.
I'm going to be ready to take him out.
You picked the guy with the gun this time.
Guy before had a flashlight and you just like rolled backwards
while he grabbed you by the neck.
How are we going to take the guy out with the fucking gun?
I don't even think this guy knows where he's bringing us.
Right now, inside of his head, he's going like, oh, fuck.
I actually have no idea where this is.
I think it's over here.
All right, come out.
Damn it.
A hat on a stick.
These fucking places cursed.
Now you tell us.
Can I put the hat on?
Look at this.
Madam.
Bearing updated.
Donald Duck hat.
Holy shit.
Can I walk him into that?
Will he get steamed in the face?
Have we been here before?
I don't know.
Christ.
Oh, Christ.
That guy.
That guy's probably still right here with us.
I mean, you die on a ship.
Your ghost stays on the ship.
You have no idea what you're talking about.
That guy's still here.
Well, that was like 70.
That was like 80 years ago.
I think that guy probably walked around for a little while.
Maybe like a decade.
And then was probably just like, I'm kind of done with the boat.
And just like got in the ocean.
And just started swimming.
Ghost swimming.
And is probably on land somewhere now.
It's been like 20, 30, 40 years of that probably.
Nothing I've ever seen.
I would do that if I was a ghost.
I don't know what the fuck this is all about.
But we got to keep moving and find Olsen.
Why would I stick around in the same place?
Olsen?
To hunt.
Fuck that.
I want to see the ghost world.
I don't, wait, I'm going to stay inside of the closet here
and scare the next 200 people that live in this house.
No.
I'm going to see the fucking whole ghost world.
I'm not going to stay there.
That doesn't sound like fun.
Uh-oh.
Painting.
What?
Wait, you want, look, you want, Luke?
I got to look at this painting, man.
Like, I'm not even allowed to look at a painting.
Oh, this place is cursed.
It's so scary.
It's a cursed place.
Don't look at that fucking painting.
You're allowed to have like an outwards monologue for everything here, but not us.
Oh, here comes incoming re.
Okay.
Jesus, man.
It's just a door.
It's just a steel wall, man.
Where's the gun?
I want the gun.
All right, so there's evil, evil magician, evil wizard.
All right.
Where's the gun?
I don't know why.
You pick up the flashlight.
Are you serious?
Page 39.
Warlock streamer 33.
Come on, get it right.
That can't be a good sign.
So we now have to...
Oh, I didn't even give it a chance.
Laughing?
I don't know, it's been a long time.
Is this going to be Joe or Charlie or...
Charles T. Perez from Boston.
All right.
This is Charlie.
Anything else?
Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, that's fucking Charlie.
Oh, no.
Now I'm actually alone.
Now I'm really alone.
Hello?
You can't...
No, I don't want to be actually alone.
What the fuck?
Is Brad dead?
That means Brad's dead.
Quickly.
Get the tooth.
Shit.
My phone's ringing.
Hello?
Uh-oh.
Oh, wait, what?
What do I do about this?
Is it...
What?
I can get out.
I can get out of this.
I'm gonna be fine.
Where was he?
Where were you?
Uh, safe...
Do I run?
Save Brad.
Is that made up?
Was it just...
That was fake?
He was just telling another scary story.
What?
I don't understand what just happened.
So he died.
Or is he?
Because he was a ghost before.
But then he wasn't.
And then he was.
On here.
Free blood.
Nice, okay.
How do I...
How do I drink it?
I get like a cup or something?
That's...
That's pretty good.
Nice.
I'll have to...
I'll remember that.
Probably get some like health back or something.
Wait, I'm gonna play piano.
Open door in the back.
But wait, there's a...
Snacks?
What is this?
It's a book.
It's got all kinds of symbols on it.
It's a...
It's a Satan book.
That's a Satan book.
Okay.
Yeah.
All should silently assemble in no more or fewer than five true individuals of sound,
mind, and spirit.
It should number three female and two male, firstborn, faces obscured with blood.
Know it is important to the sorcerer and the spiritual well-being flock
that before the festival of Akra Mahamarai Ken,
ritual of Threskeia is performed to went away demons by means of Kabal.
The pentacle shall be drawn and each member shall stand at each of the five primary points.
A lady born of the sea shall be rendered unconscious
and placed at the center of the pentacle.
It is from there that the assembled should recite the incantation of a Sorus
sword in hand with all exhaustion possible as is written,
we five stand at the furthest point where yet close enough to touch.
The five starred, great power turning 90 degrees to yore
to describe the unicursal out.
The pentacle is faith soared forward in using rents.
Turn degrees to describe a covernal signal constitutes the with reverence.
Turn to face north with exhaustion exclaim.
Some words missing there?
All right.
This is important stuff here to rid the unfortunate body of its unclean blood
skull dagger blood tree.
Remember those.
The body should be transferred to a casket of thick wood skull dagger blood tree.
I got blood sacrifice.
Is there more?
All right.
We got to have the skull, the dagger, the blood in the tree.
The sword forward.
You, Brad?
No, I'm reading a long, long, long thing that we need to, we got to have.
Okay.
Sorry.
I didn't realize I was, I thought I was looking at you anyway.
No.
Carry on.
Hey, are you Brad?
He's like, he's, he's in my game now and he's like being fucking weird.
I just want to make sure that's not you.
It's like, I got a weird phone call like a few hours ago and it kind of sounded like
your voice, you pranking me.
Just want to make sure it's, just tell me.
The pentacle is sacrifice.
Page 34.
Each member takes a step inward and then is still in the stance of Ram.
Reciting unison.
We are one and so is the Lord.
Oh, sore us.
But the sacrifice we ask you to cleanse our aura to rid us of the demons that plague us.
We spill the life of man in your honor.
That we may ourselves worthy of your trust.
Only when the in can let should the five converge upon the S as drawn.
Each member should in turn to rid.
Okay.
Good.
Throw it in the fire.
Blood investigate.
Hey, are you Brad?
Yeah.
Somebody joined our server and they're named, they're named Brad.
They're griefing.
It's not you, right?
Tell me if it's you.
Anything else on here?
No.
Where's that piano?
I want to play.
There has to be something with like the piano keys.
I knew it.
I just stopped playing like a fucking evanescence.
What was that?
What are you talking about?
You guys didn't, everybody learned how to do that.
Am I too old for that?
You guys, you guys might be too young.
Every single person learned how to do the
because that was like the most popular song in the world.
So go turn on the power.
Hooray.
The thing's gonna go up.
This is gonna be so fair.
I knew it.
Geez.
Really?
Yeah, probably incoming re here.
This is blood.
The skull.
I knew we were going to get read.
Just grab it.
Take the skull.
What are you doing?
Get the skull.
All right.
Apparently I can't pick up the skull, which I know I need it.
Blood coming from the ceiling.
Well, just remember that there's a skull in there outside the boat.
Can I just jump over?
And what was I supposed to see something?
What was I supposed to see?
Wait, this is the same room.
So give me the skull.
This is the box in the beginning of the game.
That's the gold.
Oh, so it's a gold.
There's gold in there.
Gold bars, gold coins.
And the government was trying to keep it.
And it's a conspiracy.
Okay, this is the water coming down.
Interesting.
Cool.
Should I not be standing in this like gas?
Did I go back in time?
Where's Brad?
It's the same book, right?
This is the Satan book.
Standard operating procedure for handling hazardous chemicals.
Department for...
It sure is.
Avoid storing chemicals.
Leaks the wire rope clean and stored in any chemicals.
Make certain that...
What?
Its color band is...
Make certain that...
It's properly marked before.
Its color band is visible so the cargo can be identified quickly.
Refer to paragraph 26B.
The cargo must be secured to avoid movement during passage.
Pass the stowage with fresh water.
Grease to drums help protect them.
Water during stowage.
During inspection, stowage procedures.
The marking on any container.
And consult the Navy shipment.
Marking handbook if required to determine.
Why am I reading this shit?
Because I don't know.
It might be important.
Is it not important?
Why would I read this shit?
I feel like this is important stuff.
Does it look important?
I don't know.
What do you mean does it look important?
It's a hazardous chemical removal.
Yes, it is very important.
Another dead person.
Wait, this is...
Wait, wait, this is where Charlie was.
Uh-oh.
Now it...
What?
There's the guy with the hat on.
It's...
Oh, there's Brad.
Hey, are you Brad?
Just like...
I'm just...
I need to know.
Brad.
Are you Brad?
Can I tell you this information?
Can I...
What?
Are you trying to...
All right, mute, mute, mute, mute, mute, mute.
Hey, what's wrong?
What the fuck?
Did I make this in the movies?
Wait, did I...
I spoiled it?
Hey, are you Brad?
Well, he asked me earlier if I was Brad.
I was confirming the same thing with him.
We both spoiled each other's game?
No, we didn't.
W doesn't exist?
What the fuck?
I am so mad right now.
I think...
I think I killed him.
What is happening?
I can't move the controller.
It's switching from keyboard to fucking controller.
On a whim.
When it decides to.
All right.
You okay?
That guy saved you.
He tried to kill me.
Thanks.
I could have drowned.
I can't believe it.
You killed him.
I did.
No, I didn't.
He's fine.
Now I'm back here.
Okay.
Hey, are you Brad?
Brad's in front of me right now.
I'm just...
Listen, I don't know anything that's happening.
I'm just kidding.
I'm kidding.
It's weird.
I have no clue what's going on.
Not in like the good way either.
Like the literally just...
And fucking keyboard.
All right.
I got to mute.
Wait.
No, that's you.
That's you.
That is you.
No, that's not you.
Are you Brad?
Stop asking that.
All right.
You have to sit on board.
I'm understanding what's happening in this game.
So we're not supposed to be working together.
Us doing this in co-op.
It was like a bad idea.
We were supposed to just like be playing together.
Like, hey, what do you find?
What'd you find over there?
Are we Brad?
No, I realized that like 20 minutes ago.
I realized that after he asked me if I was Brad.
And I'm like, what are you talking about?
And then I had...
And then he was Brad.
You know what I mean?
That was a cycle that we were in.
And yes, I know that hitting the key is changing the keyboard.
I know.
Guys, I knew that after the first 200 people said it.
But really, why is it taking so long?
Just can't open this thing by myself.
Alex has found his secret.
See, we went into this thing and it was going to be like,
oh, it's like a co-op horror experience.
No, we're actively playing like against each other.
And we just don't even know.
Mad because Brad.
Because we like aren't supposed to be sharing information with each other then.
You know what I mean?
It's going to be lobster under here, I hope.
Yeah, we're like hallucinating.
The monster and somebody...
Oh, no, you're the monster.
You just strangled that guy.
You killed...
That's not Brad.
That's me.
That's not a monster.
It's me.
Just like it was in the beginning of the game.
Oh, what's it have?
Mad because Brad.
That's fucking funny.
That's a good one.
All right, let's use the key in the safe.
All right, what does it say?
What does it say?
Read it.
Not read the letter.
I thought saves don't use keys.
They don't...
I mean, maybe back in like the fucking 20s.
Summary of Manchurian Gold.
Study of response of human beings to ingesting chemical designate Manchurian Gold.
Okay.
Chemical ingesting crystal dust form by subjects A, B, C, D, and E.
All volunteers provided by base sergeant.
Test successful.
Results consistent with biological specimen test reports in supplied files.
Full report forthcoming.
Further studies strongly recommend a stimulus response relationship
in subjects under influence of chemical.
Please note, latest test results do not supersede...
So the Manchurian Gold is just a bunch of unstable chemicals.
High caution must be taken to avoid exposure of chemicals to solution,
extreme heat, and electricity.
Five subjects.
Right, okay.
All right, where else should I go?
Can I go in any of these other doors?
Pause the game.
I gotta fill my water bottle.
Oh, God.
It's me.
Hello?
Oh, it's me.
It's Bliss.
It's okay.
This is Italian.
Should I even say...
Are you Brad?
Like, I keep running into Brad.
No, but he...
Okay.
But he doesn't know.
So he's gonna like kill me.
What's going on with that light?
I just missed the QTE because of that.
I'm just chasing him down.
It's me.
It's Bliss.
I see.
I know what's happening.
So I'm reading this thing here.
It says that this...
It says like a pentagram on it and shit.
I'm like, I've been reading it for like 40 minutes.
It seems like pretty important.
Yeah, it's weird.
Because in my game...
What have you been doing?
I've been like really just bored reading material.
Well, see, me and the other character are playing checkers.
We said whoever loses has to cook dinner tonight.
Oh, that's weird.
All right.
I'm gonna get back to reading, I guess.
Yeah.
No, there's a lot of books in the game.
There are too many books.
It's like kind of ridiculous.
But it's all good.
This one here.
You're gonna get ca-
This is too long.
I'm just gonna leave this room, guys.
It's like way too long.
I guess I'll try to play piano again.
I almost missed that.
Should I stop like-
It's weird.
Like I'm at the buffet.
You're at a buffet.
There's a bunch of like just elderly cruise liner type buffet people here.
Just clamoring for the free cheeseburger line.
This game's fucking boring, then.
Because I'm literally just walking around the same room.
Playing the fucking piano.
It's like terrible.
I didn't think it was this boring.
Is it?
Somebody's in the window.
You got somebody in the window?
What the fuck?
There's a face in the window here.
Fresh air.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm still in the-
Wait, what the fuck was that?
I've been in a loading screen for like five minutes.
What the fuck is that?
Oh, it's Brad.
Are you Brad?
Are you controlling Brad?
He's in the piano room with me now.
Actually, I found out if you just don't play the game for about five minutes,
the AI takes over.
All right.
It's us.
This is us.
Get ready.
Am I Alex or are you Alex?
Who was it?
I am Julia.
Okay, so I'm Alex.
Imagine maybe to look at your feet to walk up the stairs.
Like imagine if you look at your hands when you punch the keys on the keyboard.
I can barely hear you over this.
Jump.
That's what I did too.
I don't know if you're actually Alex.
Oh, you are.
Okay.
You're deciding.
Yeah, we're going.
Harm Rad.
Help me.
Close it.
Lock it.
Work.
Nice job.
Are you Brad?
Am I Brad?
You have to be.
There's so many people.
Who's Brad?
Oh, we're playing in five player mode the whole time.
We've only been controlling one character each.
So we're all, everyone's still alive.
We did a phenomenal fucking job.
Chad is Brad.
So by the way, there was a period about five minutes that I was not here during the last chapter.
I was gone.
You were actually gone.
Oh, hello.
Yeah.
Things appear to have taken a turn towards the spiritual, wouldn't you say?
Were you Brad?
I mean that sincerely.
Like the chapter's over.
Okay.
Like.
Yeah.
Chapter's over.
Are you Brad?
I was Brad for a time.
Brad made some questionable decisions.
How to stop it.
How to save the lives of your four unfortunate stowaways.
You will, I hope.
They said four?
Although it seems the ship's previous occupants never managed to.
Quite a lot of deaths that night.
Let me help you out.
Give you a little hint.
Need a Brad flow chart.
No, I don't.
No spoilers.
Get out of here.
No hint.
Perhaps you think you can piece things together from the clues you found yourself.
Good luck with that.
Perhaps you've started to realize something.
This is just the guy that binge watched the whole season before you've had time to sit down and watch.
He may not be dying.
Talk about what he thinks.
Whoa!
I hope that helps.
Welcome to Pell and Tell or Fool Us.
At Fool Us.
Well, I'm so excited to find out what your poor unfortunates are making of all this and how
you might avoid any more unnecessary tragedy.
Go on.
Back to it.
Speak soon.
Panda Fate 3.
Have fun.
Okay.
We know who we are.
What the hell is wrong with you back there?
I have to pee.
Brad, you lost your shit.
I did too.
That's why I was gone.
What are you talking about?
Come on.
No.
That's ridiculous.
What the fuck is going on with this shit?
That was a pretty good Jay Leno impression.
I gotta be honest.
It feels like there's some like, like evil, like literal evil going on down there.
Let's just stay calm and relatively sane about this.
Okay?
This stuff I saw.
It's like there were these old soldiers and they were bodies.
They were dead, but then-
This is all your fault, by the way.
It might be.
Doesn't sound that crazy right about now.
If you don't ever split up, nothing bad can happen.
That shit crazy like dinosaur old.
Not that that's a bad thing, but she just like up and vanished on.
Alex wasn't the only Alex.
Who are you talking about?
There were things walking around with his face on them.
Alex's face.
It was horrifying.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
My face?
That never hurt you.
That's rude.
You know that, right?
No, I know.
It's just, let's-
No, I'm Alex.
Okay?
This place is too fucked up to just be fucked up.
You know what I'm saying?
I mean, like something is going on here.
So what do we know for sure that we can all agree on?
Chemicals.
You breathe in a minute.
It's a ghost ship.
Wow.
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard in my life.
Did you see a ghost or anything?
We're turning to water.
Manchurian gold isn't actually gold.
It's a fucking chemical and it's leaking all over cargo hold to-
Yeah, I'm pretty sure this isn't exactly what our
friendly fishermen are expecting either.
This should go over well.
What do you think actually happened on this ship?
A goddamn mystery box is what it is.
The ship was bound for San Francisco.
Mystery box?
But it hailed from a water purification plant in China.
Apparently that's where it picked up the Manchurian gold.
I saw 1947 on the newspaper.
Is this a ghost ship?
I mean, I guess-
Am I crazy or are we on a ghost ship?
Like ghost ships are real and this is one and we're totally on it.
And no, holy shit, we're so totally fucked.
I was going to say the same thing.
Pretty quick tonal change there.
According to this letter I found, the guards here were absolutely terrified of something.
I agree.
Everything you say, honey.
We found a note that said a bunch of guys tried to get out of guard duty
because they were really freaked out by something.
This place is weird.
There's a lot of unnatural shit going on here.
It is unsuper freaking natural.
Everything about this place is wrong.
We know more than we did before.
That's something at least.
We're wasting time.
Whatever we do, we have to do it now.
Time to get off this ship.
We're not going anywhere without the distributor cap.
The duke needs it to run.
Nope.
Hold on.
We can leave it.
This ship's gotta have a radio.
Time for the radio quest.
If we can find it and use it.
That's great, but do you think it still works?
We just need to find a way up there.
Time for the radio fetch quest.
All right, we got the whole party here.
Okay, I'm Alex.
We gotta get out of this damn ship.
No shit.
It's a classic problem.
Who am I?
Totally effed.
You're Alex, okay.
Yeah, I am Alex.
Okay, you were just Alex.
I walked into a corner, but I thought you were walking into a corner.
Yeah, this is why I was confused.
Because you were Alex 15 seconds ago, and then it just gave me control over Alex.
Yeah, I've been told in local mode you get to pick who you want to be.
It's weird that you don't just pick who you want to be.
Yeah, why can't we just choose?
Cigar?
I know it sounds crazy, but maybe it was these guns that took down the plane from our dive.
I guess I'm just standing over your shoulder.
Am I handing this to you?
Have we?
Did you just pass the lore baton to me?
Here, you look at this.
Oh, you put this back.
I'm done with this.
I didn't even say anything.
Not even one line of dialogue.
Just I set it back down for you.
Yeah, you put this away.
Honey, I left my play chat again for dinner.
Thank you.
Can you clean them up now?
We could use this boat.
Great.
Do I have to come?
Confirm.
All right, it's got holes in it.
Let's go get some duct tape.
You can put duct tape on it.
All the characters are together.
Seems like they should exchange everything that they've learned so far.
We're silently just walking around.
It just feels like really empty in these parts where it's just
there's five people and we're all just NPC walking around.
Like, yeah, just some dialogue or some back and forth or something.
What is that?
Hey, a little help over here.
Oh, yeah, we're actually playing Spy Party now, aren't we?
I think this is our way up.
Give me a lift.
Okay, I was gonna say if there's a QTE available, fail it.
I'll pull you up.
See, there he goes.
That's like a standard NPC walk up the stairs.
My turn.
These are the heaviest characters too.
Yeah, they do feel like they're way like full of concrete.
Like there's shoes of concrete.
Don't waste your time looking.
Nope, don't go this way.
Just go the other way because there's nothing there.
We're just all walking around without mouths open.
This is where I chased Conrad before.
This is where I chased Conrad.
So that was me being chased.
Oh, that was you being chased by Conrad.
No, I was being chased as Conrad.
Wow.
No wonder they have such a hard time.
Here we go.
We're gonna do the five person push through the door.
Jesus.
Maybe they didn't write the dialogue
because half the people that play this game
lose a character by this point.
So they just didn't.
Oh, shit.
That's right.
That's true.
Now it makes sense because they might not even be here.
Someone's supposed to be dead by now.
So let's not even write them lines.
That's true.
I didn't even think about that.
They really are just ghost NPCs
because they're not supposed to even be here potentially.
Wow.
Interesting stuff.
I really shouldn't be laughing.
But also...
Can I get out of here?
How did we leave this room?
It was funny.
What was in here?
I haven't found a radio yet.
No, but there's gotta be a radio on this shit.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Just put Julia here.
She sits there.
She's just completely out of the way.
She has no reactions.
She's not supposed to be here.
Oh, I found another book.
A blank painting.
I got Behring updated.
The world.
Secret found.
China to America.
And then we got another...
This is the boat that the beginning of the game started with.
So it was coming from China.
China to America.
And then it goes...
And then the red gets stuck over here.
That's where we are.
What is this?
Are we already separated?
Yes, I think so.
Technically.
Where else?
We're just walking around.
What does this say?
Uh, ship was blown off course.
Cloud cover was bad.
Yeah, she is just sitting there, huh?
They couldn't establish a position.
Storm.
It says lightning strikes.
Search for crew member overboard.
Search called off.
No comment.
Is this us?
I think that's us.
Funny streamer, make me laugh.
All right, fine.
No, I was just reading it.
Like you were asking me to do that?
Hey, funny streamer.
I have your stream open while I play co-op.
I'm watching your stream right now.
Do something funny.
No freaking way.
This thing actually still works?
Well, radio science hasn't changed much in seven years.
As long as there's power.
I'll give it a whirl.
How are we still getting power?
It's ghost power.
Ghost energy.
It's working.
You have to go very far.
Storm Thursday.
Beast pressure.
Oh, I skipped it.
Military battery.
You skipped it.
How do you skip it?
You skipped the cut scene?
Hey, is anyone out there hearing this?
Hit Luigi if you don't work.
Shit, we got him.
Um, coordinates.
Oh, you're the one doing this.
I see.
And I thought this was just an uninteracted cut scene.
12 degrees, 30 minutes south.
151 degrees, 20 minutes west.
How do you know all that?
Please get here now.
We need help.
Wouldn't the captain know that better?
Yeah.
Please repeat.
Are you sure you're not reading the back of the Tyson chicken nuggets?
You gotta let your finger off the button for them to talk back.
150 degrees for 20 minutes.
Roger.
Yo, guys.
They heard it was an emergency so they're like,
they're gonna come and be new pirates.
You invited the new antagonist to come find us.
Why did I panic?
Because I tried the calm approach
and they didn't listen to me so then I decided to scream.
You need to get that radio working.
I think someone should wait here.
It's gonna be like a second gang of pirates.
I gotta be honest.
I don't think I'm gonna make it down there in my shape.
I'll go.
150 degrees.
What's wrong with him?
I should be the one to go.
He got punched in the face like three hours ago.
Come on.
Sounds like you're scared of someone stepping out of your shadow.
Scared of my idiot brother getting himself killed?
How about showing me some brotherly love?
All right.
Hey, if you're sure you're up for it,
I believe you got it, bro.
I'm coming, too.
Hey, wait.
No, don't send him.
No, my bodyguard.
I can take care of myself.
Whoa, whoa.
If Julia says she can handle it,
she can handle it.
Case closed.
Okay, Julia.
Wait.
That team's dead.
I can't.
The two worst people.
It's like Star Wars trash compactor.
Shoot.
That's so fucking funny.
Immediately, the two potential worst people do this.
You guys can handle it?
The two weaklings.
We're like, can I go, please, mommy?
You doing okay?
Yeah, sure.
If you think you can handle it.
Immediately.
We're okay.
What are we going to do?
It's going to be a miracle if we can actually have everybody live.
We've got to find out where we are.
Okay.
We'll wait here by the radio.
Oh, I didn't realize that I have to be these two.
Here.
Dude, this is just the broken clock is right twice a day.
Somehow we ended up saving all five.
It ain't over yet.
There's going to be a spectacular like death parade at the end.
Hey.
With clowns.
After you.
Okay, here we go.
Is this us?
Yeah.
I'm Brad.
Are you?
Hey, am I though?
Might not be.
Guessing these are the lower level.
No, I'm just fucking around.
I'm actually upstairs.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
Don't lie to me.
I'm upstairs.
We were trying to get the radio to work again.
The frequencies are so stupid.
We should probably mute you.
I wish I could actually, you know, enjoy this.
What the hell are you talking about?
I think I think he thinks.
In any other circumstance, you know, this place would be the coolest place to explore.
Like, like ever.
I'm going to say no, not at all.
Says the girl on the way to die of a wreck.
Well, he's muted right now.
I think he think he muted first, not me.
He muted first.
I have to be a really, really good NPC here.
Wait, are you reverse pranking me right now?
I'm just curious.
How so?
Are you like reverse pranking me?
Reverse?
Yes.
You're up there doing the radio stuff, right?
Yeah, what are you doing down here?
Down here?
There's three different groups.
Oh shit, I blew it.
What are you doing down here?
Oh shit.
Oh, I knew from the beginning.
Oh, he knew.
He doesn't know.
All right, so what the hell are we supposed to be doing here?
Are you reverse pranking?
Would you think I was an NPC for a second just because I was holding the light?
Ten days in the brick.
No, I thought that you were pretending to be an NPC too.
And then I was going to freak out and be like, wait, is he actually down here?
Pretty good, pretty good attempt.
Ten days approved.
All right, let's see.
Engaging with the soldier in a drunken argument.
Every one of these hallways looks exactly the same.
The amount of times that I have Warcraft keyboard turned down a hallway
is probably like two hours of this game so far.
Now, where did you go?
Here, come check this out.
I just pulled him.
I got yoinked.
I just yoinked him.
Looks like the engine room.
Good place to find the generator, right?
Are you breath?
The ladder's broken off here.
I think I can just wait.
Oh, that would hurt so bad.
Yeah, just come down.
That's a back problem for the rest of your life.
You should have seen what happened to him earlier.
This is hurting me, just watching it.
He's fallen three times.
And what's the other guy's name?
Oh, God.
What's up?
That, it was, it was, it was.
Oh, not this shit again.
Did you see it?
Hello?
Isn't this just the same trick?
This is the same thing.
You're not.
It's the same thing.
Follow my thinking here.
We know this ship was carrying manchurian gold,
which was actually some kind of dangerous chemical, right?
And there's just like weird fog everywhere.
This is not a 12-hour game.
This happened twice in the last three hours.
Yeah.
Maybe it's fucking us all up, like in the head, you know?
I mean, I definitely saw some crazy shit
that I could have sworn was real, but maybe it wasn't.
We know the crew were scared shitless of something.
None of it happened.
None of it was real.
It was just a hallucination.
This couldn't have anything to do with the plane wreck we dived.
I mean, maybe there was a connection.
Maybe they made contact.
It's a theory, I guess.
Oh, God.
The thing we sent the guy with glasses down here,
we never would have figured this out.
Yeah, I know.
All right.
What does this say?
Netherlands.
Diesel engine number 1734, year 1920, type L87CSE.
Okay, cool.
I can't believe we are absolutely encroaching
on like the last arc of the game.
We have to be, right?
This is only like a four to five-hour game, right?
Uh-huh.
And they've already figured out
they just talked about the trick.
Yeah.
They just, there's gotta be like,
there's gotta be a gotcha moment
where you thought you had it figured out.
But then, hold on.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
Should I pull this out?
Hey, hey, I found it.
I think I just told them.
Stop finding all this stuff.
And it's working.
I'm trying to find stuff, too.
Yeah, this is it, all right.
But over there.
Just throw the switch and let's get back upstairs.
That's so ridiculous.
You're over there exploring
and whoever just finds the thing first
just sucks the person over.
Oh, wow.
What?
What do you mean?
What's the hold up?
You failed the QTE, so they let me do it.
I just did it.
That's why you had to call me over
because, you know, you're very book smart.
But when it comes to practically using your hands,
you need some help.
I did it.
And then you stepped in and did it again.
Mom, it's my turn.
I'm super Nintendo.
There are things on the ship that are trying to hurt us.
Over.
It's not real.
We think the name of it is the Iran Medan.
Really?
The Iran Medan?
Why was there no subtitles there?
What did he say?
The Iran Medan?
The Duran Duran?
What was the name of the boat?
What was what's this called?
Iran Medan.
Look at this.
Hey, come on over.
The fisherman must have bothered over from the Duke of Milan.
You think it still works?
Looks like it's got a little juice left.
Maybe a couple of minutes.
Should we bring it with us?
I mean, it's heavy.
What is it?
Hang on.
No, seriously.
What is it?
Uh, it's the Ghostbusters proton pack thing to dive with.
Scuba gear stuff.
Those guys aren't even real.
Actually, they have to be because we have a shared hallucination yet.
Yeah, I don't know.
He can't hear you.
He's not awake.
Yeah, but he's hallucinating.
He's hallucinating.
Rip right side, look right into the camera because he sees us.
So have we not concluded that the hallucinations are a result of this
strange miasmic gas that has been pouring into the boat since we got on it?
I mean, yeah, that's what it is.
Oh, oh, oh, he can hear heartbeats.
How do you not turn around?
All right, all your Super Mario RPG practice should have prepared you for that.
Oh, he's going to get up.
Don't breathe in the gas.
Hold your breath.
Wait, am I?
I'm like seeing that's not there.
Yeah, here comes hallucination.
I know.
No, we don't.
Are we going to do a mute scenario?
Incoming mute.
What did you pick?
Nothing.
It was you.
You was on.
That was your pick.
What did I?
What was important about his hand?
I don't know.
Maybe he had something in it.
We didn't get the cap.
Did we get the cap?
No, he has it.
Is this the same voice actor?
Maybe they changed to...
Did they Dario this guy?
Again?
Again, the comm meter.
He set the title of my stream.
He said the title of my stream.
I'm sorry.
I did not know that.
He said the title of my fucking stream.
That freaked me out.
I'm sorry.
That's the title of my fucking live stream.
I got so hyped up over that.
Didn't this guy get drowned earlier?
I don't know.
What?
Okay.
How many pirates are there?
What do you mean drowned twice?
I may as well have got up from the seat
and like spun around walking.
He said the title of my stream.
Please.
We've got no problem with you.
We just want to get out of here.
Please.
I'm sorry.
But if you're breathing,
then you don't get much of a choice in the matter.
Oh, they're taking my choice away.
Not again.
I'm changing on me.
What?
What's changing?
Stay away.
Stay back from the mist.
What?
There's no mist, man.
Don't breathe it.
There's the guy.
Don't breathe the mist.
The guy.
Did you see him?
Don't breathe it.
What man?
The guy from the book's shelf was in the background.
Why can't we breathe the mist?
What does it do?
He was in the mist.
Life.
Bringing things to life that shouldn't be alive.
It's inside now.
Inside with us now.
Please just calm down.
Stop.
It's in one of us, isn't it?
Got to have to tell him like he has the flashlight
and I have the gun so we have to trade.
You're holding a flashlight, man.
I'm holding the gun.
Let's trade.
Put the gun down.
Now.
I wish you said it.
Why are you telling me what to do?
Yeah, you were in the mist.
It's happening.
Well, I guess we're dead.
Wait.
Hey, all right.
Look, there was something back there.
Maybe a mist or fog.
Maybe.
Did you just admit to breathing the mist?
That's the guy with the gun.
No, look, we held our breath.
We did not breathe any of that stuff.
Oh, fancy divers.
But you expect me to buy that?
We've been for hours.
That's actually a great argument with divers.
You've been holding your breath this whole time.
You're holding your breath right now.
The mist in me don't die.
See?
I freaked him out.
So I got some bad news for you.
I can feel it swirling around gently inside.
Wait, what?
Wait, what if that's one of us?
And what if we breathe the mist and that's one of us?
No, let him do it.
What are you talking about?
Just let him do it.
I wouldn't even let him do it.
There is no...
No, no, I can't see it.
You're all right.
There's no mist.
Stop lying.
I don't see it in me, can't you?
You're all just lying.
The mist is inside.
Where's the flashlight?
The flashlight was hovering.
Hey, man, come on.
Just put...
All right, now the premonition has been fulfilled.
Fucking shit.
We're fine.
I saw him kill himself like an hour ago.
You did?
In a premonition.
But where...
I honestly don't know if there was another outcome for that because
he's been dead for centuries.
Hey, we got a gun.
No, we don't because this is two people that don't want guns.
Oh.
So we threw it back.
Well, so what?
Maybe if you sent down the wrong two people, he would have killed them.
We sent the two least threatening people in the crew.
I don't know.
Wait by the radio.
Why?
I'm going to check the next level.
There might be some more gear down there we can use.
Uh...
Just wait by the radio.
I'm going to hang back here as well.
See, I thought they were pulling like a...
You breathe the mist and like was that one of us?
And like he was back at the wall with the flashlight.
Nobody's good.
I don't think we can because there's no...
The only times we've hallucinated, we've been by ourselves.
Like Alex right here.
So Alex is going to be hallucinating.
Why can't people fucking just slowly go down a hole?
Don't say the name of my stream again.
He's invisible.
How did he not see that?
He's like a splinter cell enemy.
Oh, he's left eye.
He's blind.
He just didn't turn left at all.
Who's in the background?
The guy that's watching us.
All right.
Um, so you're...
I am Alex.
You are Phyllis, right?
I'm down there with Julia.
So you're in...
Wait, you're not Phyllis.
It's Phyllis, the captain?
Yes.
All right.
I am breathing mist in my own fucking room here.
What's happening?
Who are you?
I'm breathing mist into my own fucking office.
You're breathing mist?
Is the mist coming in through the air conditioning?
In the office?
It's vape juice.
Vape juice.
Uh-oh.
There he is.
The sledgehammer, boss.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
I was looking at my fucking phone.
Oh, why was I doing that?
That was stupid.
I'm fine.
It's okay.
You weren't meant to die there.
Holy fuck.
I looked at my phone again.
Holy shit.
More mist.
So when you said that they were transporting drugs earlier,
you might have been right.
Was I right?
The mist drug.
That's going to be revealed to be some kind of crazy advanced biochemical warfare.
That's the allies we're going to use.
The mist just came out of it.
The 1940s American military was going to use these weapons of biochemical war.
Where'd you?
All right.
We have to mute.
Mute.
What the fuck?
Is that me?
Oh, this is the laundry room.
Dead guy.
Of course.
They will restrict you a moment around the plants
to prove difficult to look for Jones.
Your primary objective is clear,
but your secondary objective is when you reach your destination
is to locate Jones and his men and get them back on home.
I'm going to sit online.
You must be vigilant and be very concerned with your personal safety.
You got another one.
Okay.
They've been captured.
They're still alive.
Only that their last notification was approaching the plant and they were silent.
The plant is high security.
They're expecting you.
Sergeant Jones and five of his platoon have been missing
during a reconnaissance mission at the water purification plant.
Water purification plant.
So they're putting something in the water.
The mist was supposed to the best is that I get it.
I don't think he gets it.
Now I get it.
The thing is, where did the talics go?
Nothing else over here.
And we can't go back.
I can't go back that way.
Explain the whole plot to me.
Okay.
What the fuck?
Who are you?
That's what the hell I'm supposed to do.
Is there a hallway I can go down?
Yeah.
I'm like, how am I lost?
This is like the only.
I can't let go.
Fliss.
You okay?
I'm in different clothes.
What the fuck is going on?
What the hell happened?
The rats are going to get me.
They're not real.
The rats aren't real.
Let's get out.
What the fuck is going on?
Is that a talics?
Should I have said that?
I don't die.
I can't communicate.
What did you do to me?
What the fuck?
Why did.
Who's doing that?
Why did that happen to me?
What?
Kill the rat.
Should I?
No, the rat's not real.
The rat's not real.
Don't do that.
Well, I would have stabbed him and killed him.
If I had stabbed the monster,
I would have killed like somebody else.
Are you Brad?
I am now.
You hungry?
I heard some like,
stomach noises.
I just wonder if you need a snack.
I didn't want to stab.
That was.
I didn't want to stab you.
So I'm like, oh, I'll get the monster in my.
Let me see.
Duke of Milan?
No engine.
Yes, that's pretty much the end of it.
Looks like it.
You know, I was hoping to die.
I could have done nothing.
Yeah, but whatever.
I, I we've been going out.
So you got scared on my screen.
You were running away from a rat.
Yes.
And on my screen, the rat busted through my chest
and was killing me.
And I had a choice to stab the monster,
which was you probably,
or the rat in my stomach.
And I realized, wait, the rat's not real.
I just, I killed myself.
Rat in my stomach.
He was everything I ever wanted to be, you know?
I just wanted to be able to tell him.
I'm sorry.
And now I'll never get that chance.
He's fucking dead.
God, I'm so sorry.
Wait, that's not the end of the game.
I'm so sorry.
You killed the person with arguably the most personal connection
to any of these characters.
Nobody would care if Chad died.
What's his name?
Drew.
Wait, hold on.
That's the end of the game.
No, it's not.
Conrad.
That's the end.
I guess that's the end.
That's how you make core games nowadays.
By the way, on my screen, there was a piece of paper
that confirmed my theory that it was a military weapon
when roped.
So literally the next scene.
That's it.
Game over.
You're dumb.
You're dumb?
Oh, I thought he said I'm dumb.
I was supposed to say fuck you.
You can't do better next time around.
Impressive.
Almost everyone survived.
The last fucking cutesy.
Oh, god damn it.
Really?
And the distributor cap?
Boom.
All right, yeah.
Apparently, I broke that, but it wasn't my fault.
It's all about...
Wait, hold on.
Give me some credit here.
My game broke.
I teleported into a room
and then the cutscene jumped around in three different rooms.
You got to give me some credit here.
That was bullshit.
I teleported into the laundry room.
But then...
And then my character changed clothes.
And then a guy was being eaten by rats
and then I got a knife and I had to stab myself.
You got to see what happened to me
when you were the monster
because it had to have been more abrupt.
Till we meet again,
maybe in Little Hope,
maybe somewhere else.
But be certain,
we will meet again.
It's inevitable.
Regardless of how many people survived,
that is somehow worse than the Blair Witch ending yesterday.
Restart and don't break the distributor cap.
You want us to go through the three hours and 40 minutes?
How is this only three and a half hours, by the way?
We were playing on streamer time, too.
Wait, hold on.
So how did you break the distributor cap?
I don't know.
There was a door and I tried to open it
and then I had to mash A and I successfully mashed A.
Then an elevator fell down
and then it broke the distributor cap that was down there.
I don't know how to even save that.
I can't skip it.
All right, let's...
You want to go back and try to save everybody?
Apparently, we can do a scene select.
Okay, let's do the scene select.
All right, hold on.
Elevator was Jerma's fault.
How?
Was it?
What did I do?
My character like teleported around
and then like I saw something break.
I'm like an innocent bystander for this whole game.
I don't think I chose one.
Oh, I did choose not to kill you.
I think I took too long getting to the elevator.
I don't know.
What is this?
Is this post credits?
Yeah.
They're going to kill everybody.
Protect the government secret.
So that whole thing was for fucking no reason?
Did I write this game?
Did I do this?
So even if all five got in, then it's all five go anyways.
Unless you protect the cap, apparently.
Oh, you got to get the cap.
Did you escape on the boat?
And then everyone died.
See, nothing that we did mattered.
No, like you can make it matter.
Oh, wait, is it preview?
I know that guy.
He's in a bunch of movies.
Little hope.
In 2020?
That seems like a very long time away for episode two.
Well, here's the bad news.
It's a separate purchase, I think.
Is this?
I think it is.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Jack can correct me if I'm wrong.
Wait, hold on.
Slow down and back that up and just reverse it for a second.
I'm pretty sure this is a standalone purchase that we just played.
This is a three hour and like 20 minute experience, essentially.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
It's $40.
And then episode two.
How much was it?
Was it 30 or 40 bucks?
How much was this?
It wasn't 40, I don't think.
Is it 30?
All right, is there okay?
All right, all right.
That's apparently it's 30.
Yeah, and they didn't do the way out where only one person has to buy it
to like play with the other person.
So we both bought it.
That is technically one ending you can get, right?
So I mean, you could technically play through this game like a few times, right?
I think this would be worth it if you, at least I'm down, I'm at zero, so.
Wait, you get this game at zero?
No, no, no, like OBS is at zero.
Oh, but I hear you.
I'm still alive.
Anyway.
Okay, because that was like that transition was just like, you know, it'll be great.
I mean, I mean, I'm at a zero right now, essentially.
I don't know why I'm still at zero.
What?
Yeah, it must be VPN.
Maybe it's a VPN spoken up because I'm still fine.
Maybe it's, yeah, that's weird.
You should come back.
It's very soon here.
It's actually not Cox.
No, not Cox this time.
You want to try to do the last part again?
See what happens.
Yeah, I'll give it a try.
Let's do that final scene and see if we can do it.
I'm going to invite you.
Hold on.
So like, okay, if you do that.
Technical difficulties.
Yeah, do you think?
I'm just gonna hang up for a little bit.
So if you play this game alone, there goes kind of all the fun.
Yeah, I mean, whatever fun you have is absolutely not present.
Because, oh, is it?
I mean, once we figured it out that it was like, wait a minute, are you Brad?
Oh, hey, am I Brad?
Wait, who are you?
That was like, oh, that's kind of fun.
But if you do that by yourself, you don't get to ask your friend.
Are you Brad?
Mad because Brad.
$30 for are you Brad?
I mean, it seems like there's, I wish there was more there.
It felt like the first, I guess, can people like die on the boat?
I don't know how we didn't lose somebody on the boat.
How do I stab myself in the stomach at the very last QTE of the game?
And no one died during the hostage situation on the boat?
That makes no sense.
We like dropped the gun, dropped the knife, like dodged.
QTE fail, punched in the face.
How do you play this game in couch co-op?
I don't know.
I think you just all watch, I think you watch a movie.
Because wouldn't you know all the information that the other people know?
I guess.
So how would, where would the secret be if someone's the monster or not?
Maybe I guess they just don't control the monster.
It just cuts part of the scene.
Oh, I wonder.
Anyways, are you, are you, are you green?
Are you good?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm inviting you.
No screen thinking.
It is weird that we went through the whole game.
I mean, I know it was only three and a half hours, but still.
And one little decision at the very end dictates the entire.
Okay, so this is matters of the heart radio room, right?
Is the last scene.
I guess so.
Would you like to overwrite the current save?
No reason not to.
Is it the end?
No, it's not the end, is it?
Okay, here we go.
But anyway, my thought was if they made it where one person buys it and can invite
a friend for free for co-op and it might be worth $15 per person.
Maybe, but let's see what happens.
Let's see.
Let's try to get it because we had all five people.
Yeah, we had, everybody was alive up until the last second.
Yes.
And then the actual thing is saving the boat.
Okay, so we're going to, I'm not going to stab anything.
And then what, what, what you had to tap something to save the.
The, um, the.
All I have to do is open a door.
Somebody said the elevator was your fault.
Also, I don't know if that's true or not.
All right, here we go.
So same thing.
I'm you off list.
I'm Alex.
Why I'm going to check the next level.
There might be some more gear down there we can use.
Just wait by the radio.
I'm going to hang back here as well.
All right.
So when I did this last time, I apparently took too long doing this.
Just go and grab the thing who stays, who goes.
Okay.
He said the name of my stream.
I saw the big guy way too excited about this.
Uh, we just spotty swapped.
We didn't know.
All right.
So what was the thing?
What's the thing I'm supposed to grab?
We got to get the cap from the big guy.
And then we separate and then I, what was I supposed to get?
It just, it did just kind of end.
Just don't activate the elevator.
Don't activate the elevator.
This must have been what we just heard.
Okay.
Here we go.
What's that?
Does it matter?
We need that distributor cap here.
He had to have come this way.
You have to find the guy as fast as you can.
Okay.
I'll try.
I don't think I even have anything I can do.
I think I just.
Here we go.
All right.
He's holding it.
And then he reads down the hallway.
And then you have to jump successfully.
Yeah.
Should be excellent.
Okay.
I'm good.
There he is.
Okay.
It's Alex.
Don't open the door.
Somebody's saying.
I'm not, I'm not going to open the door.
Okay.
So where, where am I now?
So he's like just sitting in the corner down here.
I'm not going to make this jump, Alex.
I'll have to find another way around.
Did that happen last time?
I don't know.
I don't remember that.
Him just dying in the corner?
No, no.
I remember that.
But I can open this door, right?
They said don't open the elevator door.
Yeah.
I can open this door.
Okay.
Now, where is he?
Oh, sorry.
RB.
Okay.
This scary thing.
One letter short of BRB.
Maybe that's why.
Minus two.
I, I took care of it.
Thank you, Chad.
Oh, okay.
Then now where is he?
Is he in this, this laundry room?
I was laundry room.
There.
Okay.
Let me see it.
I looked at this.
Okay.
Just trying to re-flip, retrace the steps.
You found a secret.
Good.
All right.
I didn't even know this was, this was here.
Okay.
I found it.
Fuck.
All right.
Do you, I'm, I'm about to be in possession.
You just can't look.
I just have to grab.
I'm, I'm going to get it.
What the fuck did you do that for?
Got it.
Okay.
I have the cap.
Alex has found a secret.
Did you just do that?
You, it, it yoinked me into the door.
I have the cap.
It doesn't look like you have the cap.
It looks like you're fighting a rat monster.
All right.
The cap is, we, we're good.
That's a sca, I knew it was coming.
Don't stab anybody.
Who are you?
Say nothing.
It looks sad.
Okay.
I'm afraid.
No.
Now don't do anything.
No, I'm not going to kill him for the joke.
I want to beat the game.
Okay.
Shit.
Now what?
How many times are you going to try and like?
It's okay.
There we are.
Fliss.
Gotcha.
That's five out of five.
I'm not even going to apologize.
Oh, Fliss, it's you.
All right, let's go.
That's a solid five out of five right there.
Hi, everyone's safe.
Everyone's alive.
That's all I needed was this piece of boat.
Now I can leave.
Okay.
If we get like gunned down here again.
They're going to set off in the boat,
that they came there in.
We did it.
Oh, you did it.
You saved everybody.
Did they write any dialogue for this ending?
Where's Conrad?
All right, let's try it.
Conrad's not on the boat.
There's only four people.
Everybody got their, the true timeline.
Everybody got their wish.
Conrad was just an hallucination from the gas.
That explains a lot.
He was kind of a monster.
This was about curing gold.
Well, that turned out to be quite a bit different than we expected.
You know, I just keep going over it and over it.
And it doesn't make any sense, you know?
And I know what I saw.
Well, guys, I found the paperwork that explains it.
Don't believe in whatever it was that I saw.
I saw Alex.
It wasn't Alex.
It was one else.
But they look just like Alex.
And he was sneering at me.
He doesn't really like explore very much of this, huh?
Oh, there he is.
It's kind of like, hey, if you breathe this stuff and you become a monster,
time to go home.
This guy.
Yeah, I feel like this game needed like another two full hours to like keep that going.
Well, they kind of did the you're a monster, not really in the prologue.
And then that there wasn't another thing for the rest of the game.
That was the joke trick gotcha moment in the first 25 minutes.
And then they just did it again two more times.
And I guess let's see how this let's see.
Let's see our critique from our professor here.
Rewinding to fix the story.
Pathetic.
Congratulations.
All your charges are still breathing.
And that's something I suppose.
Things became a little intense, but Alex kept his nerve.
Well done, Alex.
Well done, you.
Oh, it's all about decisions, isn't it?
Decisions made in a hurry in a panic made with the heart instead of the head or vice versa.
Sometimes those decisions take a long time to have repercussions.
But there are repercussions for always repercussions.
Scream and watch out this dude's British.
We meet again, maybe in little hope, maybe somewhere else.
But be certain we will meet again.
It's inevitable.
All right, apparently we need to watch this.
I thought you just started singing.
I was like, holy shit.
Okay, I'm going to.
Oh, sorry, please.
All right, we're not supposed to watch after the credits.
Did you skip the credits?
Won't you spare me?
Oh, no, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We had to skip this.
We had to skip this part.
We got to get the credit.
Don't skip after this.
Here we go.
They're going to just shoot us when we get to the beach.
Already lived.
Oh, Danny, no.
Danny.
All right, they saved us.
Danny was alive.
Aren't they just going to they have gas masks on or just like.
So out of nowhere, this thing just sent out an SOS.
I guess we got a real life ghost ship here.
Well, what's rowdy pause the game.
Please reconnect your controller.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Trying to ruin the perfect ending at the last second again, I see.
Well, what the hell is this?
Danny was dead and he wakes up to die again at the end.
Credits if you don't save him.
That is so hilariously stupid.
There's a lock on one of these.
I don't know if you were there with me when I investigated this room.
But they don't have a gun.
Never mind.
Danny is he breathed the mist.
And just like every other like HBO show you watch.
Here's the trailer for the big thing they got coming out next month.
Why are we watching this unskippable?
It is unskippable.
All right, we did it.
We did do it.
And that's not coming out till 2020.
I mean, there's only three months till 2020.
But yes, that seems like a long time, though, to have anybody like continue.
Oh, yeah, the dark, the dark picture is anthology.
To be clear, it's $30.
Not 40.
But you know, I'm not sure I agree with the C and four months mentality.
They're saying that for the for twice as much money,
probably less now that there's sales.
You could buy full price Detroit become human.
Yeah, I can't say.
I mean, it was it was funny.
There was some stuff that was interesting.
But I almost wish that they didn't do this whole.
Let's make like eight of these little games and just make one good one.
We're too good.
We don't want to do one or two, three.
Why eight?
Why not do three of these or two of these?
Why does it have to be that many?
Because I don't know.
It's in four and then in half.
I could just spend a little more time on each eight.
It's a lot.
Yeah, it's what is that?
They really want to do eight of these.
Is that for real?
But are they all $30 each?
I don't know.
That's like the most expensive DLC.
If they want to tell their stories, let them.
Yeah, but where we have to we're the ones buying them.
I guess we don't have to.
But I'm not on a subway sitting next to a guy telling like a scary story.
I think if you plan for eight, you have to be extremely confident about
how many sales you're going to get.
And I don't know if because Man of Medan seems to be kind of universally not anybody's favorite game.
So people will be willing to try the second time.
And if both the first two aren't up to par, then how are they going to make eight?
No one's going to buy three, four, five, six.
I mean, here's like a $500 IQ play.
Just wait like seven years for them all to go on like a steam sale.
Just wait for the Dark Pictures anthology, like eight game series to be like $11 in like 2028.
That's normal IQ.
Is it though?
It makes you I mean, that's pretty smart.
I like the idea.
I mean, until I would say the most fun part of the game was like that middle section when
you were like coming to get me.
And I thought you were the bad guy like in that middle section.
I think after that point, there was nothing left to tell.
Once once we figured, okay, once we figured that out, then it was kind of like, wait, oh.
And then they did like the kid runs across the screen two more times.
And then we just knew, you know, like, yeah.
After even if you even if we didn't talk about that, you ruined it, but you didn't ruin it.
Like when you said, hey, are you Brad?
Here's what I really thought.
Because what you didn't know is I took a five minute BRB because I'd take the dog outside.
And I just thought it would be funny because there was a guy on the ground with a bullet
in his chest and I thought he was cursed.
And I thought if I touched him that I would like wake him up and he'd become a zombie.
So I was just like, I'm just going to be here.
The second that I came back, you yoinked me into the next scene.
And that's when I was just getting chased by you.
So when you said, are you Brad?
What I thought was not that you were a good guy that I shouldn't kill,
but I thought you had taken over control as the ghost of the ship.
And you were going to it was going to I thought they were going to do like a
like a way out thing where we're actually adversarial for like the rest of the game.
Unfortunately, unfortunately, you didn't get my texts.
That's the one unfortunate part about this whole stream
because I wanted to change rooms.
I wanted to go into your room and you come into mine and like we're just like
for like I think people would have known immediately.
I don't know.
I really I think that would have been like instantaneously.
Because yeah, I would sound so much like better on your microphone.
I only had the camera on sometimes.
That's what I was asking.
I was like, hey, I'm like, hey, is your webcam on right now?
But I would have to leave it like full unmuted
because you wouldn't know where the button was.
I wouldn't know where it was.
I'd have to sneak into your room.
But all right.
Final thoughts.
Final thoughts on episode one.
Standalone Man of Medan.
I would say I like the idea of the shared co-op play
with a friend horror game unless you're going to play it in five player local
and everybody pitches it.
True.
But it's also it's six dollars a person.
It opens the door couch co-op.
You can play couch co-op local with five players.
Have a little movie night for three and a half hours and pass the controller around.
Yeah, you can just have fun with it.
I think it opens the door for potentially having horror games
and having co-op experiences that are like that kind of way out experience.
Try to do more of that.
Hey, you're both playing at the same time, but you're not doing the same things.
But you are.
But you aren't.
But are you?
You are.
It's an interesting take on co-op.
But just the problem was very good.
I don't think it was very good.
There was nothing in between the moments.
There were like probably four story beats in the game.
But the only thing you do between there is kind of you walk down the hall
and there's a piece of paper at the end.
And then the next thing happened.
Yeah, it was a lot of hallway walking.
And I mean, let's OK, here are the pros to this game.
It's very, very, very, very nice looking game.
I thought like the especially when they did when they did close ups,
I thought it was fucking fantastic graphics until they showed their teeth.
I didn't dislike any of the actual actors or the voice actors.
I thought that was all good.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was I was holding up to no comment and no response.
The graphics were fine.
Yeah, it was just kind of it was it was until dawn until dawn was so much better.
Like until dawn was five letter grades.
How come halfway through the game, there was a literal I am the captain now.
Look at me.
Yeah, I guess I am inevitable.
Yeah, I felt weird.
That did happen.
That did happen like more than once.
And there were a couple like dialogue options that just were out of nowhere.
What do you mean?
Mike, could you explain that again to me?
But in like not nerd terms, so I can understand.
And they would just I remember when you were like tonal shift, kind of weird, right?
Yeah, at least they said the name of the series.
Yeah, I did.
I did ruin Alex's proposal to Julia.
He proposed to Julia underwater when they were diving.
And I thought and I told him that he was being stupid.
Damn.
But that that's the end of that.
That's the end of the man of the Dan.
I haven't gone to the bathroom in four hours.
So and that's a first for me.
I'm going to go pee.
OK, I'll be back.
What time is it?
It's been about four hours.
I'm not sure there's anything else.
Is there anything else we can do for like an hour?
Maybe.
What was the point of the satanic book?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, that wasn't I wasn't full of shit there.
I found a Satan room with a Satan book and told me all these Satan spells.
Was it just a red herring?
I think it was just a hallucination.
Yeah, it was just that was not real.
And I was making it all up.
See how fast you can kill everyone in the game.
You want to try to just kill everybody's faster again.
That's not a bad idea.
Just fail every QT.
Yeah, let's try to kill everybody as fast as possible.
See what happens.
All right.
Yeah, that's what we're going to do.
We're going to play the game again, but we're going to kill everyone
as soon as possible to try to do it in less than 30 minutes.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to go pee.
OK, I'll just mute you and everything.
I'll be right back as Pete.
Hello.
Hey, yeah, you get disconnected.
Did I?
Oh, we went down.
Yep.
I turned off the VEEP.
So the VPN makes any difference.
Yeah, it looks like the VPN lost connection.
Huh.
Well, that's irritating.
But it's people saying it's Twitch.
People saying I don't believe it is.
But why would it be working?
We both went down at the same time.
It says people saying Twitch's servers are shitting the bed right now.
A bunch of streamers are going offline.
Maybe so.
Maybe that is.
Maybe it's not the VPN.
Either way, it's not Cox.
Yeah, it's not.
It's not an Internet issue, apparently.
For once.
It's Twitch, apparently.
OK, you ready to try this?
See if we can do this.
I'm going to say we should start like halfway through the story.
Is it possible to skip like dialogue?
I'm assuming we can probably...
We can probably just go to the part where the boat gets...
Well, I think if we wanted to start from the beginning,
if you just don't look at anything other than the next objective,
doesn't that just throw the story into the next beat?
Because can't you fail a bunch of QTEs as the two sailors?
Can you start from the chapter after we do the punching
QTE and fortune?
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, that's what we should just skip the prologue.
I got an invite for you.
A bunch of QTEs.
All right, so scene selection.
We've got Chinese market, the Duke.
So Chinese market, I believe, is...
This is all you.
The Duke is the boat.
So like we can't just skip that Chinese market part.
We have to start at that when we are on the boat.
Okay, we're just going to start at the Duke.
And here we go.
Start the timer now.
Here we go.
All right, try to get as fast as we can.
Have everyone just say nothing.
Yeah, just only just don't talk.
I'm trying to skip.
Well, you've artificially...
All right, here come the beards.
Uh-oh, we got twitched.
Wait, we did?
Are you down?
Are you zero?
Yeah, I'm...
Oh, well, if you're not, then I guess we'll just keep going.
But it's getting kind of miserable.
Yeah, this might be like a...
This is making no sense.
Apparently, Twitch is just going down.
Because you're fine, right?
Yeah, I'm fine completely, like 100%.
Okay, so it's...
Are you on VPN right now?
No.
Me neither.
So, yeah, something's going on.
Who's DDoSing Twitch?
I don't know.
That's a good question.
Let's just try to get rid of this.
Yeah, well, the thing is I...
Oh, you're out of the game?
I'm...
No, I'm going to have to alt-tab in a second.
And that's going to force pause the game.
There's Alex.
I'm going to try changing servers.
Well, thankfully, this all started really happening when we finished the game.
Yes.
Think we got enough?
If we run out, we can always call for backup.
All right, say nothing.
So, look, I've never been down there before.
All right, I got out water.
Don't blame me.
Blame Twitch.
No, no one's blaming you.
Don't worry.
I'm blaming me?
I want to see what happens.
Let me know when you're ready.
Are you playing different characters to see this stuff?
No, we're trying to see how fast we can have somebody die.
We're not going real fast.
We're going at lightning speed at the moment.
All right, let's try here.
You doing a new server?
Yeah.
Okay, try again.
Twitch TV server problems.
Ready.
Choose an EU server.
Diving.
Um, I don't know if we failed it.
Maybe you could show me how the pros are.
Up that high.
All right, say nothing.
Always.
Well, anyway, let's get this all loaded up.
I think he was going to say something there, too.
Careful.
That dive cam is like super expensive.
Be cool.
What?
Julia and Conrad are, you know, how do I say it?
Super fucking loaded.
So?
Don't sweat the little stuff, man.
It's not cool.
Don't make me regret.
Oh, cool.
Uh, is it a DDoS?
You tag along.
No, the internet's fine.
It's just...
Well, no, I'm done with the people saying that it is like up to Twitch or something.
All right, amigo.
Calvary's almost here.
Cool.
Sorry I'm a little snappy.
I'm just...
The new medical school would be stressful, you know?
Total shocker.
And man, the long distance thing, Julia, it's been rough.
Just random people saying that.
Yeah, well then I'm like...
Yeah, it's probably not, oh.
I'm just very shocked.
Me, too.
I guess I keep these in an underskills location.
Flushing.
Hey, so, uh, can I get your input on something?
Yeah, what?
Just, uh, kind of a big thing I'm trying to make a decision about.
About finishing med school?
And you said no.
So you were talking about wanting to do this and then down there you said no.
Imagine if him being in med school allowed him to solve anyone's
medical problems throughout this game.
Or if that character backstory was written, uh, after the rest of the game.
Teeth.
No one's figured it out yet.
Is this gonna take another three hours?
Um, I hope.
No, I hope not.
Hey, what's up, man?
Conrad.
Watch it, sis.
Lady killer, right here.
Good to finally meet you, Conrad.
This is Brad, by the way.
My little bro.
Hey.
Bradley!
Feel like I already know you have heard so much about ya.
All right, so remember, every dangerous potential scenario, uh,
do the option that is trying to get that person killed.
So is that Julia?
Yeah.
Is Julia blonde by the end of the game?
Geez, you have to think about it that hard.
She's blonde now?
I'm gonna guess the answer is no.
Maybe it's just the lighting.
First dive, you and me?
If you can keep up this time.
Whoa, whoa, cool down.
Don't go crazy with excitement.
We'll both do it.
That's so funny.
What a boring, shitty play through this could be, if you really wanted it to be.
Yeah, absolutely no personality.
No personality, no decision making.
I like my main character's blank slate.
I like to put myself into their shoes.
I'd invite you to make yourselves at home, but, uh,
so is everybody on board and ready to go?
So it turned out that she was full of shit.
About the, like, don't disturb dead people thing.
Oh, yeah.
You're selling, I'm buying.
They weren't cursed at all.
It was just the military miasma.
All right, when's the first scenario where everyone could just die?
Well, there's an underwater segment here in a second, isn't there?
There is, yeah.
And the barbecue explosions.
But you already messed that up.
Yeah, all right.
What's the fastest way we can get out of this?
Is just go say we're ready, right?
What about over here?
That's pretty far out of the way.
I'm currently scrolling through this iPad.
Listen, to be honest, I've never heard of this wreck you're looking for.
Usually these things are crawling with divers.
Well, how do you do that?
Look at this.
This one's different.
I'm just saying, if it gets too late, I know some nice places where you can just take, you know,
a nice dive.
Just think about it.
I'm gonna go help Conrad and Julia with the camera.
I'm just so slow to process all information.
Feast your eyes on this.
Whoa, hey, look at that.
What is it?
Looks like a bomber.
Can you zoom in?
Oh, yeah, definitely a B-29.
That's good, right?
Are kittens good?
Are miniature horses good?
Hey, I freaking nailed it, bro.
Don't I get a little end zone dance?
Watch me.
Oh, yeah.
So the B-29 is a super fortress.
During World War II, they built these suckers to cruise at the highest altitude possible
while maintaining the ability to carry nuclear warheads.
They were just, like, so dope.
Ah, so dope.
Oh, my God.
Look at me.
Sorry, yeah.
Please keep going.
Fliss, we found a plane.
Yeah?
Yeah, looks like World War II.
We are ready to dive.
Technically, we should call this in to port authorities as an unreported wreck.
Technically.
Are you sure you don't want to do this the right way?
Have a good think about that one before you respond.
Guys, no one knows.
No one cares.
No harm, no foul.
The computer is starting to answer for us.
Look, we picked for this guy.
Generously, we're dying.
The AI has taken over.
They have to push the story along somehow.
Say nothing is an illusion.
Can you imagine?
Untouched?
I am going to do some reading up on B-29s.
So what happens if we don't control the game at all?
I tried that and eventually it just forced me to go to the next area.
I still don't know what happened.
I may have pulled you.
Maybe you should check on your bro.
Yeah, no, it was unexplainable.
Okay, we're gonna have to move.
We both just stood here for 10 full minutes.
Hold on, what's the thing that moves us along?
I think we have to go downstairs.
I have to go downstairs and then they call us back up.
Oh wait, no, you're down in that new cutscene area.
I can't go in there.
Oh yeah, I can.
Okay, here we go.
Yeah, I have to do this.
I don't know what's going on.
I feel like these, there's no...
It's like, oh, relationship updated.
You've seen that like a bunch of times in the top left of the screen, right?
Yeah, I don't know what it means.
What the fuck does that mean?
It's kind of like Alex will remember that.
Yeah, but they don't accept.
Maybe it only matters if you're a single player?
I don't know.
Because the AI has to control some of the reactions.
He's stoned out of his mind.
All right, here we go.
You can't go in there.
I know, but we have to like do all the random things and then she goes, tanks are ready.
See, okay, what is this, what is this a painting of?
This premonition here, is that just of the storm?
Where Brad is like, oh no.
Oh, yeah, it didn't have to be annoying.
All right, let's do it.
I'm doing it.
Literally none.
This may as well be striking in human.
I'm just an android that hasn't been programmed yet.
If she tries to keep me from doing this dive one more time, that's it, gloves off.
That's fair.
Just don't force her hand.
All right, I'm gonna get these rebreather set up and then we'll go through the final steps together.
Cool, just holler at us.
Nothing to say.
Do what you want.
You're not gonna listen to me anyways.
But if you take one thing from that wreck, you're gonna make us all criminals.
Relationship updated.
What about me?
Nobody ended up being a traitor.
Nobody got into any kind of relationship.
Well, the people were gonna get married, I guess, but.
Every time I take a group of you people out, it's the same thing.
No regard for anyone else's customs.
These rules are all pretty basic stuff.
How much experience do you have with these kind of dives?
Oh, shit, this is a hard one.
Like, if you're silent for this long, through this many questions, you might be a serial killer.
No, you just don't like fucking ask it.
For all you know, this could be a war grave.
Disturbing it would be illegal and immoral.
They just said to cool it with your desperate pickup bullshit.
I haven't said a word as Conrad the entire game.
Just respect the rules down there.
Don't do anything stupid that'll get my ass in trouble.
I haven't said anything.
No, nothing.
Hey, at least I'm honest.
Still gross.
All right, are we ready to go in?
He's so desperate, he said nothing.
I'm standing next to you.
I'm standing right next to you, like, as if I can see as far as you.
There's nothing to even find out here.
Maybe there is.
This is freaking me out.
What the fuck?
I just got a little oopsie.
Oh, are you?
What?
Oh, you just you just like took me out of it.
Well, I was in a trance.
Just the camera zoomed in on my face and I just took I had it was in a trance.
Are you up?
Oh, yeah, I'm up.
Oh, at this point, I've got a bit of it happens.
It happens.
They just go, you know what I'm saying?
Do I not press A?
What's going on?
What is going on?
Jerma has to talk to Julia.
Okay, so this is the rebreather.
Way cooler than a regular scuba setup.
It takes all that CO2 that you normally just exhale into the water.
And instead, it gets totally reused.
Then it reduces decompression time on your way up.
State of the art.
You guys are going to enter the game world.
Maybe done.
Yeah, we're not going down at the same time.
So if you have the squad stream open, no one's missing anything.
Oh, yeah, just good old squad stream.
Ready to take the plunge?
Oh, hey, guys.
What? Jesus, why are you so loud?
I almost completely forgot.
When I was looking at the dive cam, I saw this huge hole in the tail.
I probably should put like a disclaimer somewhere,
like on this top of the stream that just says this is a fuck face run.
Okay, you little clown.
Someone has definitely come in here.
You behave, Connie.
Like, oh, good.
I got here just in time.
We just started.
Can't wait to see what they do next.
Say nothing.
I'm not taking any of this stuff.
And now I have nothing to say.
I'm so high.
God, come on.
These two are baked out of their minds.
This is just like, we like...
It just husks.
Oh, shit.
What should I do?
You're not in a good state to go down there.
No, you shouldn't be going down here.
All right, so there's a moment in the plane
when I take off the rebreather.
And swim into a cramped location.
But there's a QTE, so I want to see if that does anything.
I think...
You're Conrad.
I'm underwater.
You're on grill duty.
Wait, what?
I mean, I'm seeing the underwater segment.
You just Conrad and wasn't I, Alex?
Yeah, we got swabbed last time, though.
Did we get switched again here?
Howdy, Captain.
No, I'm...
Oh, yeah, it did swap us.
You are not my second-in-command, third-in-command.
No.
Fresh and eager cabin boy.
Still a no.
You're well-paying dashingly handsome seafaring client.
It's requesting the pleasure of your company over a frosty amber liquid.
Oh, she's been infected.
Okay.
You snooze, you lose.
Pretty nice ride you got here.
Where'd you get the cash?
I feel like it'd be cool for a game about choices
to give you a choice as to who you want to be.
That's true, yeah.
Sorry, I overstepped my bounds.
Switch computers.
We just take turns, each chapter,
choosing which squad to go with.
You know what?
I better spend some time keeping the Duke of Milan shipshape.
I really hope that I can just burn the boat down.
It's not gonna happen, though.
I'm gonna get stepped over.
It's gonna happen anyways.
That is not your everyday wreck.
I hope those clowns don't get me in trouble.
Well, I just gotta cut on my leg and tetanus, so...
No, put it down.
Hey there.
How's it hanging?
I get it.
Busy, busy, busy.
You can monitor the dive while I do some boat maintenance.
Not a prob, Bob.
Okay, whatever.
Can we take a second to say that it's weird
that to play multiplayer, you don't pick multiplayer,
you pick not alone?
Yeah, that is weird.
It's like they know that we're real gamers.
Here comes like a storm.
Why do I say weather looks clear?
I have to keep an eye on those clouds.
Hey, the weather looks clear.
It doesn't like a storm come.
It's getting mighty crowded out here.
Wait, did we even do the thing?
Did you do the barbecue yet?
Did I?
No, no, I'm just...
I now have to...
I'm swimming with the fishes.
I got no mask on
and I'm not gonna be pushing any buttons here.
Where's the boat?
I just saw it.
What the fuck is going on?
Three?
What happened?
Did you go make popcorn during the segment where she's drowning?
Are you doing something here?
Well, I hope that she was gonna die,
but no, she's actually fine.
I have no control over the game right now.
There were three separate failed QTEs to get out of this pipe,
which I feel like is...
I can't get up.
B doesn't do anything.
I haven't pressed B.
What did I do?
Okay, italics.
I think you need to like come press QB.
Do I need to do something?
Yeah, I'm stuck.
I'm looking just at the front of the boat.
I'm going as fast as I can.
It actually needed to wait for you.
How dare you talk?
I was silent last time when I played the real game.
Don't they come board?
What's going on here?
Where's your like boat friends?
Hello again, little blip.
What you doing all the way out here?
They said italics is breaking character.
I did say something.
I chose a dialogue option,
but I was silent when we played the actual game.
There's nothing here.
Okay, I'm being a good boy.
There's nobody here.
Hey, don't worry about it.
I'm a people person.
If you could just pull that open,
why was I going to shimmy it with a knife?
Maybe they're fishermen.
Maybe that's their buoy.
Maybe...
Got to chat.
We won 100%, not 98%.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Do they...
All right, I'm getting ready to break the ship.
So that should be your cue.
Okay, you're breaking the ship.
I'm breaking the plane.
All right, hold on.
Don't do it yet.
Okay, you just did it.
All right.
Well, I'm going to zero.
So they got me.
What's that about?
Wait, didn't we just do this?
I guess I haven't...
They're like coming right over to it.
Oh, this...
I don't think this...
Did that happen last time?
They just take off.
They don't even stop.
Yeah, this happened last time.
Yeah.
I thought I broke the plane.
20.
No, make it 30.
More like 40.
You know, I think this whole thing could have been
avoided if you had just handed this person the money.
You know what I mean?
Like, hey, come over here and let me hand you the money.
I guess they didn't need the money.
That could have been like, hey, I really want to pay for this.
I'm really like that.
That was like, yeah, I'm sorry.
Hello.
You going a little brain trip there, Flissy?
Here a piece of work, Conrad.
I'm not all work.
Are you trying to flirt with me?
Is it working?
I don't even know what it is.
Well, when you think of something,
I'll just be over here taking in the view,
flirting up a storm, hashtag wink.
All right.
I have to put a disclaimer on the top of the stream.
Guys, hold on.
I didn't do enough in my playthrough to get proposed to this time.
He doesn't like me anymore.
Well, I got to write, like, he doesn't like me.
Somehow it feels worse than saying no to a marriage proposal
is knowing that they were going to propose,
but you did something and now they're not going to.
It feels bad, man.
This has to be up here.
Wait, it's going to be one word, not two words.
It has to be one word.
This is not.
Okay, there.
That's better.
What are you trying to type?
I did.
It's not important.
By the way, as to the missing text,
I did have Discord open the entire stream.
So if you could just typed it, I would have seen.
Oh, well, I'm fucking stupid.
Don't worry.
Okay, I think they're on their way back up.
And I was getting used to it just being you and me.
We need to light the grill.
Oh, pick me.
Grill Capitan.
You may light the grill, but I will never call you that.
Here we go.
Let's see.
Oh, I have to make a decision this time.
You have to go.
I have to make a choice to try to kill.
Yeah, of course.
Damn, I'm sorry.
So what's the easiest way to kill anybody?
Why is it just looking sad at him?
Nothing happened.
Okay, fail every quick time event.
This is where it happens.
Have you not been doing that?
I've only gotten one chance.
Why was there only one explosion?
I just had a little trouble firing up the grill.
Conrad?
Whatever.
It's like they're seeing shit.
They say a sentence and then they like just get lost.
Like super, like in their own head.
Yeah, it's like, unfortunately, we did not leave it as pristine.
My great aunt.
What?
What's wrong with you?
With dementia.
Oh, that's a cool looking thing up in the sky.
There's no cockpit anymore for starters.
Well, that's just fucking perfect.
All right.
It's time.
No, everybody survived.
Weirdly enough.
I don't know how it's possible when it's not possible.
Got you a wink.
Yeah, I noticed you haven't been saying anything.
There's no these intrepid adventurers then.
Alex and his little brother Brad trying to swim with the big fish.
Both seem out of their debt.
He just looked down.
That was a scripted line.
He read that.
His script is in the book.
And he the love of hers.
That was a really good line.
He didn't write.
A bold fellow, you might say.
Or maybe you'd say arrogant.
And there's Captain Fliss, strong, forthright, stubborn.
She appears somewhat immune to Conrad's charms.
So far, at least.
Let me reassure you.
Let's get his head to make some decisions.
They'll value later on.
And so I failed to stream cutie and regret zero.
Really?
It hasn't happened to me since the last time.
Well, but we're not on the same server, though.
You're going somewhere else, right?
Well, preserved was the plane.
Pretty much what you'd expect.
Oh, we get the beers.
It was insane.
It was like traveling through time.
No shit.
Hold on.
I'm gonna change it again.
We get the beers and we sit around and we do a beer thing.
Brewskis.
Action.
Silent, scary story.
Incoming.
Well, it was like traveling through time and accidentally ending up in a dimension
where the past is underwater and everything is covered in barnacles and sharks.
Sharks?
It was a gray reef.
Hey, I thought it was pretty intense.
Wasn't Conrad going to get us some more beers after he helped Fliss?
Maybe he decided, hey, I'll drink some.
And then he got drunk.
And since he was drunk, he forgot to bring it to us.
And he just kept on drinking and he drank all of it.
I can't wait to hear your scary story.
This kind of phenomenon.
Oh, that's right.
I'll go look for him.
I didn't even I forgot about that.
That's going to be a terrible story.
It's going to be a good one.
Yeah.
You're right.
So which one is?
Oh, God.
What's going on?
You know, where the magic.
This is giving me secondhand anxiety.
OK, that's enough of that.
You get them beers?
Oh, yeah, the beers.
I was just getting them now.
Why is it so much better like this?
It's not working.
This game becomes like a letter grade higher with the do nothing road.
Yeah.
Now that everybody's here, let's take a look at the navigators.
Boyfriend was trying to understand my inner thought.
Where did you put it?
It's in your case.
OK, I'll go get it.
If I say he did not find them.
You got the map pad dive master?
Yeah, I got it.
I have to know guys.
I have to say that I'm going to talk because I have to tell the story.
All right.
I'm just going to like stop here because you done again as well.
Yeah.
What?
Julia, I'm just trying to have a type web server.
You're on mind to me in this court.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Fine.
Let's go and get the pad together then.
Keep saying nothing.
Nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing.
Fine.
We'll go with the pad.
Wait, did I just ruin everything?
I think that's what I was originally on.
Because, well, I went down to zero like twice.
Maybe that server is doing better now.
I don't know.
OK.
And action in three, two, one.
Let's go.
Go.
DDoS, go away.
Wait, I don't tell the story.
It doesn't matter for Brace and Lee.
You got a girlfriend?
I'm going to guess that's a no.
Dudes make too big a deal.
All right.
I have to say I will tell a story.
What's the big deal about girls?
Right here.
What?
This is, this is just.
Here it comes.
Here comes the story.
Hello there, sailor.
Excuse me?
Careful.
If you did decompress too fast, then you should go easy on me.
Oh, that actually happened.
My choice matters.
I think if I got the bends, I would know by now.
Not always.
Sometimes the bends can be super delayed.
It could be hours or a day or two.
The bends?
Yeah.
It's when you come up from a dive too fast.
Oh, oh, yeah.
A decompression sickness.
Nerd.
Little nitrogen bubbles that get stuck in your bloodstream.
Hurts like a bitch.
It's really serious.
Divers get sick and die from decompression sickness every year.
And that is why the good Dr. Conrad says drink them if you got them.
Because either you're fine or you're going to want a little something to ease the pain.
Julia.
I'm telling you not to drink any alcohol right now.
Oh, come on.
Telling you take orders from this guy just drink a beer.
Oh.
Take that as a no then.
That was long.
That became really sad.
Yeah, that was just like, whoa.
Who wants to find some sunken treasure?
So what do you think, Adam?
Coordinates?
Those are coordinates, all right.
Maybe the plane's destination?
You think we could get there by tomorrow?
It takes a couple hours if the weather stays steady.
Wow.
You find anything else?
I've got a story for you.
Reckless.
All of you.
Excuse me?
I told you to leave everything down there alone.
Oh, come on.
We've been through this already.
I'm not talking about the low.
Well, don't everyone talk at once?
What does it even matter?
We should have never gone down to that plane in the first place.
It's bad luck.
You think you can scavenge down there and it makes no difference.
But every single thing you bring back has an essence.
I can hear that.
It's like a ghost you invite to the surface.
Here we go.
I can hear what she's saying.
I've never thought about it like that.
You never think about much of anything.
Well, maybe I never heard about such cool ghost stories.
They're not cool ghost stories.
Not like for fun.
People drown in these waters and you have to respect their resting place.
Damn straight.
Fred, you got a fun ghost story, right?
I do.
That is now...
Now that...
You have to say yes and then...
Yeah, I heard a story that happened right around here, too.
Let's hear it.
I'll use a good show.
Let's get away a little, bro.
Okay.
Here goes.
This story is true.
It had happened right near here in an old lighthouse.
A classic setup.
In an old lighthouse.
True story?
Where'd you hear this?
Come on now.
Brad.
Reveal your sources.
Brad, you all right?
In a lighthouse stood atop in a toll isolated from the rest of the world.
A lone beacon in the night.
A sailor's respite.
The lighthouse keeper would hear the waves.
Are you telling this story?
It's doing it on...
I can't control it.
Covered in blood.
She's stumbling down the beach.
He hurries to her aid and she falls into his arms, sobbing.
As he hurries her back to the lighthouse, he asks where she's from.
He doesn't waste any time.
Smooth.
She just did a gym from the office.
The woman answers.
We got it.
We finally got one.
In the lighthouse.
My parents are upstairs right now.
Twists.
Of course, the lighthouse keeper says, that isn't so.
Of course, he's lived there alone for years.
The woman becomes hysterical, and his sister parents are upstairs.
So, they go to the top of the lighthouse, and there, splayed out on the floor,
is a man and a woman brutally murdered with an axe.
Always an axe.
I mean, do people even use axes anymore?
Do they, Brad?
Okay.
We're sticking with axes.
He's pissed that you interrupted his story.
Just let him talk.
Another fourth wall break from YouTube.
That's so funny.
Who did it?
He doesn't want to finish the story anymore.
Because you interrupted him.
He's gotta be the woman's husband, right?
So, the lighthouse keeper creeps over to the closet.
Opens the door.
And, sure enough, there's a man inside.
But he's cut his own throat.
Horrified.
He looks closer to see the dead man's face in the dark.
Closer.
And he sees it's his own face.
And then it's eyes bulge out and screams.
So gross.
Super twist.
Nice.
Nice one, Squire.
I think he told a better last time.
She's just fuming about being told not to drink that beer.
She's very aware of the camera, too.
I love it.
She keeps doing the blink right, look right into the camera.
No, no, no, no.
Because according to standard vessel regulation, we're all required
one more beer before hitting the hay.
I love that so much.
It's standard issue regulatory institutional protocol subdivision 1099.
See this.
Where'd you read that?
The internet.
Oh, so you found a website that tells you to drink beer under every circumstance.
I'm just following orders, man.
I'm into this website.
10-4, good buddy.
And I'm out.
Okay.
This is where it goes to shit.
Here they come.
Here come the failable QTEs.
And rapid fires, et cetera.
I feel like I wouldn't be sleeping that well
on a boat in the middle of the ocean during the storm.
No, no way.
How would you sleep through that?
They look like they're sleeping so soundly.
I'm telling you, man, I don't know about you,
but if I hear even the handle of the door of my bedroom turn in half an inch,
I'm up ready for battle every time.
Yeah, I hear that and I get up.
I'm ready.
I mean, you can only hear it sometime.
No, you got to be ready.
Shit.
That's how you get woken up.
I didn't fight this time.
These people's entire motivation is money.
What was the conversation that you had on top of the boat?
I don't even remember, but don't take off anything.
What was the conversation these people had when they rolled up next to you?
Oh, they run into the buoy and then they go,
you bro, you damaged our boat.
And you can be like, oh, here's some money.
Conrad starts to be like, here's some money.
Here's 10 bucks.
Here's 20 bucks, loser.
And then they drive off.
They've run into like a fishing line thing, whatever it is.
So they're looking for money.
Well, no, they're just like fishermen that are just driving along
and they've run into our shit.
I'm not un-gagging anybody.
It's giving me an opportunity to do it again.
We're just going to sit here, be good,
and then we'll never have to go down to the ship.
Yeah, we're like just following the orders.
We didn't do anything wrong.
Everybody's still taped.
We're not going to be able to communicate on the top of the boat.
Oh, what?
You could have done that the whole time.
Yeah, why would I take you, love?
We've been down here for like three hours.
You couldn't just get this tape off my face?
Wow, anybody could have done that for anybody.
Why's it got to be me?
He's like, I liked you better yesterday when you weren't even talking.
Hey, so good news, bad news.
Bad news?
I don't see how this could get any worse.
So what are we going to do here?
Bad news is these are kind of maybe the fishermen I missed off earlier.
Oh, god damn it, Conrad.
Great, just great.
And the good news?
I recognize them.
How was that good news?
I thought you were going to ask the good news first.
You're such an idiot, Jesus.
Choose well.
I am.
He's just, he's just stares at him.
Nobody knows you're out here, little lady.
You're all alone with us now.
Let's make the move, son.
You can go fuck yourself, you piece of shit.
I couldn't get out.
We didn't do the escape thing.
We're not even going to make an attempt.
No.
What's happening here?
I feel like I should talk here and just talk a ton of shit.
Try to talk about easy.
Fuck you.
I'm gonna kill you.
The one time I talked, I had to antagonize to make sure I got hurt.
Oh, yeah, I guess we do have to say something sometimes.
So we're not going to do anything.
And she's going to just break.
Unless it's an aggressive option.
Only aggressive options may be picked.
Yeah, aggressive only.
Oh, Jesus, Conrad.
They got me.
Punched him right in the eye.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, this just happened.
No, but she was in here asking me what was happening and I didn't respond.
Deep stick.
Shut the fuck up.
I don't think they're gonna hit her.
They haven't hit Fliz.
Very chivalrous pirates.
Well, the climax of the story is coming up right now.
Hey, Tiny, or are you just taking in the scenery?
We have to get them to the next part.
There's no way.
He always gets lost in his own mind.
Once we get Julia back, maybe we can take it to my surprise.
Okay, so we're going to be violent here?
We're going to be violent here, I guess.
Yeah, just absolutely reckless.
I got the scissors.
I'm gonna stab that guy when he comes in from the door.
We just have to wait and see what they want to do with us.
So what's the plan here?
We already failed this.
Yeah, we failed this already.
We may as well, like, actually do this one.
Yeah, it's a speedboat.
He's got a gun.
I have to be reckless.
If you can clear the cards right, we can catch him by surprise.
Take him out.
I think I've seen some shit.
What do you think?
Seven seconds.
I can get out through the window.
We got to break these off first.
I hope I can fall off the fucking side of them.
Good call.
Here, I'll climb out this window.
Take a look around.
Just scope it out.
You guys distract them so they don't see me sneaking.
But if we fail, then they come in and we can fight them.
So which one's better?
Yeah, definitely fail so we can be aggressive.
Three, two, I'm sorry.
I got really, I panicked.
I got really into it.
Oh, my God.
I tried to use left thumb stick.
Wait, how did we get into this?
Stupid.
It's the same situation.
No, no, no, no, you're the hostage now.
What?
Brad's down.
Did Brad get down by running into that guy?
I don't, why don't we get to see what's going on in the boat?
Wait, where are you?
I'm on the ground.
Oh, I see.
Go for it.
Oh, shit.
Shooting down in a boat.
Smart.
Dude, nothing.
The flag's there.
Can you stab him?
Get off our boat.
Is it the same timeline?
The way to get Conrad killed is you have to, I have to try to escape.
Yeah, maybe we can sell some of these plates or cups.
I found the gold.
Which one of you is going to tell me about this?
Manchurian goo.
I don't think so.
All right, make a break, boy.
Anything to like it, to try to get yourself hurt.
We're gonna be fine, JJ.
Ah, could we have been so stupid?
We're lucky it's not worth.
Could have been killed.
What were you thinking?
I, never mind.
That's it?
That's all you fucking thought?
All right, shut the fuck up.
What do you got?
You know what I like from you?
Nothing.
That's right.
Nada.
Complete fucking silence.
Get it?
By the way, I love this stream.
Don't say anything.
You ruined it.
You're gonna ruin it.
I didn't say anything.
I'm being chat.
He's chat.
Oh, I see you're being chat.
You know what I don't, okay, if you have a game that has like,
be careful you can die and QTEs are in the game,
but the QTEs don't do anything.
What's the point of having them in the first place?
They don't do anything.
They just do, but only like, up to four times.
So are they like three?
FYI, it's gonna be a long countdown.
Like I have a choice to make and it's ticking down as slow as possible.
Oh.
So we're gonna be here for at least another like,
maybe hundred and twenty seconds.
Requesting weather update.
That's all right.
Over.
But I know what you're saying, like,
that's why I actually liked Detroit Become Human,
because at least, whatever you thought about the story,
you actually, like, I lost half the cast in the game.
Trying not to.
We did so bad the first run,
and everyone was fine up until the very final cutscene.
I mean, it's actually the supreme help.
He wasn't gonna kill me.
Everything's better when we have each other.
There's the classic frying pan moment from earlier.
Pan joke again.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna help this time,
because I held on last time.
What the fuck was that?
Where are you?
You have to call out.
Hey, move it.
Now.
Yeah, I don't think I did enough.
I didn't help either person.
It was a telltale like, who are you gonna help?
I think, I figured if I ran, I figured if I ran to help.
I, I, my mind clouded over, I, I blinked.
At least you tried.
I thought if I ran, that the bump was gonna hit a bump,
and it was gonna fuck me up.
How did we find this while the ship is sinking?
At this point, we're basically like,
the hit new summer blockbuster movie,
but this is the second evening showing
where the projector boy fell asleep in the upstairs loft.
Things could have been quite different.
We didn't speak, and we did everything wrong.
Kind-hearted creature I am,
I'd like to offer you some forewarning of what's down.
Let's hear what he's gotta say.
Yeah, we could, let's get some tips.
It's a good idea.
Uh, yeah.
Okay, you're in agreement.
Clue, it is.
The merchant of Venice, act two, scene seven.
The prince of Morocco pulls a scroll from the eye of a skull
and reads, all that glisters is not gold.
Often have you heard that told?
Anyway, now that you've reached a point of significance,
I presume you're eager to get back to your story.
But here's a thing.
Everything may not be entirely as it seems.
Here's another weird-
That's when I figured out the whole game.
But, but what's, what, why is this guy in the fucking game?
Nobody shouldn't have said that.
Yeah, you know what I mean?
Like what-
He's supposed to be like the guy through all the anthology games.
And maybe they've got an idea where so many games down the road,
you actually either play as him or play with him as an antagonist.
So he's like, hey, you're getting to know like the eventual episode seven villain.
Cause everybody loved Peter Storm Aaron until dawn,
but Peter Storm Aaron until dawn, no spoilers.
He was it.
He was like, he was, he was a character.
He was an actor in that.
Nevermind.
He was an actor.
We can't skip any cut scene.
We've tried.
Oh, wow.
That's different.
Are you failing these?
There is nothing for me to do.
You skip the cut scene, you skip the game.
That's true.
Oh no, we have to walk.
I was going to say, yeah, this segment right here is pretty,
pretty lengthy until we get put in the room.
Nope.
No thanks.
Shit.
I think maybe if we just walk in a straight line and don't stop to look at anything,
it might just advance.
Somebody just teleported across the screen on the left for me.
No, don't interact with anything.
Just walk in a straight line.
Didn't, didn't this do get like shot in the leg?
Wouldn't you be more than limping right now?
Probably.
Like not able to walk.
Hold on.
There is something you can do.
Which, which character are you?
I'm Julie.
Oh, try this.
Okay.
We're good.
We're in the room.
Oh no.
What, what even is that?
Yeah.
What did the, what, what is, I don't know.
That's a handcuff or we're skipping jump scares.
He's the guy in the haunted house.
When you go with a group of friends that doesn't just
want to get through it as fast as possible.
Go, go, go.
I don't want to see this.
Like the clown, the scary clown could dismiss the queue because
your friend wants to go so damn fast.
What are they going to do with us?
Oh shit.
This is just the haunted house with the friends.
That's what this is.
I was just becoming the monster.
Okay.
All of you.
We made it actually was not that long.
That was a full 10 straight minutes.
Funny story.
I just kind of sat there while you walk knowing that you would
you like me over to the new and I kept turning around trying
to like piss off the guard enough to make me do something.
Pirates are actors and they can't hurt you.
Hey, it's pitch black in here.
Give us.
That's my joke.
I used that yesterday.
Sorry.
Did you?
That's funny.
I got a copyright claim.
That one.
That's it.
All right.
Now how do we go from here?
Um, I think we just move the table.
Yeah, we just didn't move table.
Leave it open.
Wherever we are.
It's not good.
I can't believe it's taken this long for us to have something like
We can't just sit around.
We need a plan.
Yeah, we're not exactly in the best position to be making any
All right.
Good stuff should be coming up because they're going to hear us and break in.
We just don't run.
Got to take advantage of it and get off the ship.
Just don't do anything.
And I don't think all of us are currently strong enough to mount an escape.
We cared so much about the beginning too.
We tried to like do like the double hostage.
I'll go for the gun.
They don't matter.
It's going to be difficult to get anywhere without it.
I got shocked.
Maybe we can.
Yeah, kill all hallucinations by the way.
No, you can't hotwire it.
We need the distributor.
That's the only it's probably the only way to kill them.
I think they just really want you to be the reason why the main cast dies.
Got to take advantage and look around for a way out of here.
All right.
So let's go to the thing in the wall right here.
It's like in the corner, right?
Get that fucking thing open.
Hey, what I found over here.
What's going on?
Uh, he has to try and fail while we continue to look around the room.
I don't know.
We might have to trigger something here.
We might.
Yeah, I think we have to like touch something.
How about if we do that doing that forever?
Oh, here we go.
There's Alex.
Come take a look.
How's it looking?
I can't get it open.
There we go.
Well, whatever I was doing was not important.
So this time we're going to don't make any noise.
I think we just don't make a decision to barricade.
I had to make a decision to barricade or run or like hide.
So just stand around.
So we're just going to make a noise.
I have to make that choice.
See if they can get caught, I guess.
Oh, you're going full silence no matter what.
Oh, I mean, my decision was...
Okay, barricade the door.
Conrad, you do it.
Nothing.
So yeah, you go over and you go like,
Hey, you fucker.
Hey, you stupid fucker.
You dumb fucker.
One-legged fuck faces.
Yeah, you smarmy barmans.
Yeah, no, you.
I'm going to rip your pirate parents off your shoulders
and stomp them into rainbow-colored stew.
I'm warning you.
I am an American citizen.
You really want me as president coming after you guys?
Because he will.
Each and every one of you personally.
Very personally.
Can we just not run?
Hey, can you hear me?
I'm talking to you.
I...
We go through, then I can...
Do not pull the cover back.
His leaf is open.
I'll do nothing, I guess.
What?
Oh, no.
He got me.
I got the one non-playable character for this next segment.
Great success.
Isn't she not?
No, she's not.
Yeah, she's not in either crew.
You don't play as her for a long time.
Not to the end of the game, I don't think.
I'm the reason she got snagged.
Yep.
Gotta get her.
No way.
No heroics.
We gotta get as far away from here as we can.
What?
You can't decide to go back?
No.
So hard to kill all these people.
That's the premise of Cabin in the Woods.
Look, through the haunted house.
That room was blinking.
Please come in here.
No.
I think I'm all right.
Just keep going.
Why am I...
How do you walk faster in this game?
Left bumper?
Hold it.
That's why I thought.
But I don't...
It doesn't actually go faster.
I think it's a placebo effect.
But you're always faster than me.
Am I?
Yeah, you're way ahead of me.
Well, I'm just...
I am also walking as the guy who got shot in the leg.
But I was still this slow the rest of the game.
Maybe everyone's hiding in the hole for a big surprise party.
Because of the bullet.
This isn't happening to me previously though.
He didn't get shot in the leg last time.
I just bumped the camera.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, Jerry.
I'm supposed to go this way?
This way?
That way?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
All right.
That did not happen before.
I didn't even see that.
I was probably reading some lore.
Kind of important to see that.
I got yoinked last time.
Like this, actually.
Hi.
Wasn't I shot in the head?
Yes.
Sort of.
There's someone down there.
So you already got both these people caught.
Nothing happens.
What happens if you just don't go down?
What happens if I just don't do it?
I'm just not gonna do anything.
I'm not gonna throw any stuff down there.
We should grab it.
Sorry, I almost did something there.
Accidentally.
Okay.
I actively had to try to do nothing there.
I almost fucked it up.
I think the biggest problem is the whole...
Holy crap.
You actually control a party of five characters gimmick because
you only get to control one character for a very brief amount of time,
and then if you choose not to,
that dude's just like,
I don't care.
I'm going anyway.
And you didn't tell him to do that.
I didn't tell him to do anything, actually.
That's what I mean.
I just sat there.
You don't actually have any control.
Somebody mentioned that until dawn
has a period where like the first few hours or so,
the first couple hours,
nobody, you can't like anybody killed.
The only difference though is this game is only like three hours long
until dawn is like at least like what?
Like six, seven, eight hours at least.
So that can happen.
Wait, what?
When did that happen?
So I have an option to throw something here.
What if I just don't?
If you just throw nothing?
I mean, I can throw it at him.
No, we don't.
We haven't got to play in like a full, like three minutes.
Yeah, we've just kind of just been watching the.
I think that's, I think it's like length.
I think that's the problem.
Because when you got to that point,
like two hours into until dawn,
when it really, really started to get going,
you had a whole game there that was still going.
This is like two or three hours in.
All right.
And who died at the end of the game?
Who fucking killed that guy?
You stabbed yourself in the stomach by credits.
It just kind of jumps up on you.
Where are you taking us?
Very, very quickly.
I don't know what they're telling you.
Yeah, get out of here.
They're like closing it down.
I can't move.
Can you move?
I can.
No.
Yeah, can I?
Who am?
Okay, I'm flissed.
I'm not even touching the controller
and Alex is phasing into the wall at the moment.
And it's also a close-up of somebody's ass.
And ass is gone.
All right, let's go.
I can't.
I can't do anything.
You ready?
I'm ready to take him out.
I'm stuck in the wall.
Stop.
Because wait, but like we're going so quickly right now.
We are like getting to the point.
I'm not going anywhere.
But just in general,
we're like at that halfway point of the whole game.
We're trying pausing it.
What's wrong?
Like my characters, there's no, I can't control anybody.
There's a stationary shot.
Alex is trying to become into the wall.
Am I being pranked?
I don't think so.
It happened to me before too.
Because I, maybe if I just get to the end of this area
and you get forced into a cutscene.
It's just frozen.
And then we walk this way and then.
These fucking places.
Okay.
Touch hat, touch hat.
No, I can't.
Sorry, Jeff.
Okay.
Question.
Do you think if you push start on man of Medan?
Hold on.
If I press start.
No, no, no.
Not you.
Like if, like if you started a new game
and then walked away from the controller and came back,
would it be at the credits without you doing anything?
I don't, maybe.
Depends on what you mean.
Like the computer will do it for you.
Like will they force you through each segment of the story
after a certain amount of time
without you having to physically touch the controller?
It's possible because there is a movie version of the game.
You know, it's shared movie experience.
So I have to imagine that it's built into the game somehow.
Christ.
Oh Christ.
That guy.
That guy's probably still right here with us.
I mean, you die on a ship.
Your ghost stays on the ship.
I'm telling you, if I'm a ghost, I ain't fucking sticking around.
You know what I mean?
I'm going to be going on a ghost vacation.
I remember that.
I remember when I did that, that was that we're about,
we're about 67% of the way through the game
because it was at that point in the game.
Even better the second time around.
Oh, okay.
This is where he goes, no.
You all right, dude?
Look out.
Shoot it.
It's right around the corner.
I'm going to get it.
Okay.
What just happened?
I don't know.
All right.
Let's go.
It's time for someone to die.
Is it going to be me or is it going to be Italics?
That's the question.
Hey, what?
I am actively going to try to kill Italics.
Come on, we should keep moving.
Is my Italics is still stuck?
Hold on.
You're still stuck?
Yeah.
Somebody in chat said that the only way that they could fix it
is by re-inviting someone to their game.
Wait.
That's why I was asking, hey, if you didn't do anything,
do you think the game would complete itself?
Because I was wondering if you would just by yourself
able to advance the law.
You're definitely going to have to be pulled in here soon.
I'm like almost at the point where you have to be.
Well, I'm at the very beginning of when we took control.
And you're just standing there?
If you look closely on my screen on the left side,
you can see the calves of Alex walking into the wall
over and over again.
I'm curious of what happens here then.
I also did this at a portion of the actual playthrough.
And you did you like me to the next scene.
It was very abrupt.
Well, let's see what happens.
That's about to happen.
There you go.
This part here.
Look.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, no, there's something here.
So funny story.
We've already missed, despite trying our best,
two guaranteed opportunities to kill a character.
What are they?
Uh, the first one is drink the beer after the decompression.
And I was silent on the beer, so I did not drink it.
She also doesn't die until the end of the game.
If you do that, who would do that?
First of all, you have to be reckless to swim up to the surface without decompressing.
And second, they give you like a public service announcement
sponsored by the government about why you shouldn't drink beer
because they probably didn't want someone to watch this game.
And it's like a don't try this at home moment.
So what's in the beer?
Well, the beer reacts with the bins or whatever that you get from decompression.
If you get the bins and you drink beer, you're just basically gonna die eventually.
Just don't do it.
All right, well, I'm currently being choked.
The second way is, you know, when they do the thunder window escape,
you actually have to succeed at opening the window.
So Conrad can die on the boat.
The best part about this is you explaining the scenes.
Oh, fuck off, game.
I have no idea what you're doing.
Fuck this game.
I mean, you don't have to tell me twice.
I'm stuck here.
Failed the second QTE.
That zombie grabbed me.
Then I might get my face pulled into the ground.
And then third attempt for a QTE, zombie comes out of the ground and grabs my face.
Like, I'm gonna break your neck.
Like, I'm literally murdering you.
Last chance for a QTE, like, he does like a, you're dead thing.
And then it goes to black and it just shows her line on the ground.
And then it cuts back up from black and I go,
it was like three or four QTEs that I failed.
And then I was like dead on the ground.
Yeah, I failed four underwater with no oxygen mask.
We're live.
And the zombies aren't real though.
That's true.
They are an illusion.
That is true.
That is an illusion.
All right.
Are you, are you back?
Yeah.
All right, guys, welcome back.
Here we go.
Are you ready?
Here's the decision to make.
Compelling gameplay going on over here.
How are you doing?
Oh, I'm chilling.
You're still stuck?
Yeah, no, I'm good.
How the hell does this play out then?
I don't know, but I ain't moving.
Because this is a new, are you still Alex?
It's me and Julia.
You're still Alex.
Alex and Julia are here.
I don't, yeah, Alex, I'm supposed to be Alex, but Alex is walking into the wall.
He's just going, man.
So what?
Keep your head on straight.
Who's going to try to come after me?
I'm curious how this is going to work because you.
Well, Brad's gone.
So wherever Brad is, he's off on his own.
You should have been yoinked by now.
Are you just playing the game against the AI?
I mean, technically you're supposed to come in now, right?
Um, I don't know.
I think technically, you know that Conrad can die on the boat if you fail the right QTE.
Stick to the script.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going to stick to the script.
It's like hard to die in this game.
I'm like reading all the ways to kill people and it's it's like a challenge.
I feel like I'm looking up the achievement guide.
Don't go outside.
Why not?
I got bad news.
Do you have any spoiler for you?
The next opportunity for a character to die is not until we get to play as Fliss.
I mean, I am Fliss.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe that's what I didn't know.
Don't go outside.
Don't don't don't don't don't go outside.
Why not?
Don't go outside.
Go to the door.
Women don't go outside.
Don't open this again.
I'm trying to pull him into the game.
Oops.
Someone said pause and unpause, but that didn't change or disconnect my controller.
Just fuck around for a while.
What?
Don't do it.
Don't go aside.
What do you mean I can die if I go out there?
Isn't that the point?
So what the fuck do you want me to do?
You won't die if you go outside.
All right.
So what what do you mean stay?
What if I stay inside?
But then how am I going to pull italics into the game?
I feel like I've been streaming for 14 hours.
You know what I mean?
Like it's just I'm finally got pulled.
Thank God.
And like Twitch's servers are like getting shit on.
That's what I mean.
I'm just going outside.
I'm going for it.
I'm finally get to play.
We need to italics has to play.
I'm I am playing just now.
I'm in the room with the poison.
Yeah, but don't doesn't he need to come up here?
Remember this?
All right.
Do I do I have anything I can do?
Do the do the McDonald's menu tier list.
Hang on.
I finally get to be Brad and see what was supposed to happen the first time.
What?
This is where I went AFK in the original playthrough.
And I want I want to know how this new content.
Never before seen DLC of Brad eat the berries, eat the berries.
There are no berries here.
Hey, Brad, I am Brad.
Remember when you were like, hey, are you Brad?
That was so funny.
It was though.
It was pretty funny.
Everyone was so mad.
Wait, are you Fliss right now?
Yes.
Did you just silence treatment me?
In the game?
Yeah.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
If you didn't just talk to Brad.
Oh, I didn't get to see this last time.
This part actually would have been cool.
See, you would have asked me that same question.
You see chat.
He just asked that question.
But I already know how it goes down.
Yeah, but if you didn't know that how it went down and you're like, hey.
Listen, here's the facts are I didn't know.
At this point in the game, I didn't know that it was just not a monster.
By the way, I'm actually real human.
I just thought you had come into control of the monsters
and we're playing as the bad guys now.
Oh, I thought that would have been a cool way to do it.
Where one of the players gets infected by the mist
and you're now the antagonist trying to like
dungeon master the other person's game.
Guys, I can't eat any fucking food.
What are you talking about?
Food?
I can't eat the food on the table.
It doesn't have a glowy thing on it.
This food cart.
What do you want me to eat?
All right.
So I think it actually turns out I picked the right point to go AFK
because I don't think anything happens in here.
I think this is just.
Oh, wait, maybe it does.
I think I have to spin the bullet.
What are you doing?
No, not you like this.
There's another food cart.
There's no food carts.
Oh, wait, what?
I still don't understand.
And I'm here for it this time.
Jolly Jack.
I actually am.
This may be more confused.
It's really kind of annoying that they have to replace that every day.
I mean, that's a cool gimmick, but somebody has to replace all that every day for a quarter.
Oof.
Actual nightmare.
And no berries, guys.
You guys are fucking with me.
There's a food cart with thousands of berries on it.
You are full of shit.
Back left of the room, north left, left.
What direction do you think I'm walking at the moment?
It was all just a dream.
How do I do this?
You went AFK during the looping dream segment.
Is that what you did?
Yeah.
That's so funny.
This is the part that I like missed before.
And this is what it transitioned into, I think.
So then do I just have to wait for you to get up here?
Probably, because that's what yoinked me.
I mean, I did the thing I was supposed to do this time and it didn't.
Nothing different happened.
So now I'm going to open the door.
Yeah.
Now I have to kill you.
Yes.
So now I have to just like leave.
Okay.
Here we go.
I think I end up jumping off here anyways.
I just did it myself instead of make you scare me into jumping.
This is a nice speed run tactic.
Okay.
So.
All right.
That's you.
What was that close up?
Except you're like a zambie with a fist bump.
You didn't wait.
You didn't look like this before.
What?
What just happened?
You didn't look like that before.
Did you just mess it up?
No.
What?
I didn't even get a chance.
It's because I stayed in the room.
Wow.
It's really hard to kill people in this game.
Neither of you found a weapon.
So I didn't find a weapon so I couldn't kill you.
It seems like speed running is the best way.
Like fail everything.
Don't talk.
Keep going and you just will win.
Except maybe you won't save the boat.
I killed this person.
We're just playing it perfectly again.
We're just doing it again.
And I got up to like, yeah, you better run.
All right.
I'm going to encourage him this time.
Do it.
I'm not convinced that he's dead.
He's not.
He wakes up at the end of the game.
Nothing changes.
The only character that died last playthrough is that character.
It's the same run.
Nothing changed.
No.
Nothing has changed so far.
Somehow we're making the same choices.
Although technically everyone did run.
We're just playing the game again.
A second time through.
Yeah, I know.
We just liked it so much we played it twice for the people
that couldn't make it to the first showing of the stream.
This is just a Twitch rerun.
We're watching our own stream again and reacting to it.
Yeah, we're just re-watching the stream.
Okay, can he kill us?
If we make a bunch of noise, he's an actor.
Who's he talking to?
So this is the Conrad.
So this wasn't in the blast?
So am I the player that has to run away from you both at times in a row?
Are you doing this right now?
I guess.
Are you like invisible person?
And then I start running?
Hey!
You mentioned this.
I know like the hey are you Brad is the meme of this stream.
But if we were on the couch playing this together,
how the fuck would this play out?
Did Star just join the call?
No?
What?
That definitely sounded like a, you know.
If all of us were on the couch, we should test it out.
Let's go plug this in and go on the couch.
Playthrough number three.
Where is the weapon?
I have to have a weapon or else no one's going to die in this run.
Can't go that way.
I don't know where the weapon is.
There was no reason for him to be going insane the first playthrough.
He hadn't even seen anything scary.
But what happens?
So the game just doesn't want the two people
to really be in communication with each other?
Because obviously it's going to be-
I guess that's the whole point is like play co-op but don't talk to the other person.
Because then it's like, oh hey dude, are you like on the stairs?
No.
That's why a way out was so fun because you had to communicate until the end of the game.
And then it was like, all right, let's not talk to each other
because it's obvious we're not supposed to.
And then the game was over.
It's meant to be played online with strangers?
There's an invite button.
And don't play alone.
To your friends list.
What the fuck am I doing?
I like lost all track.
Is there a puzzle here?
Oh right, I gotta get that.
I forgot the key.
I think I have you trapped because I knew the key.
If there's a key, there's a lock.
I have to do something.
No, I do.
Because I'm like, I'm holding you back.
Well, I knew that.
But besides that, do I have to look for beer?
Why is she standing here?
There's no berries on the desk.
So you really are supposed to be like, hey man, you want to play Man of Medan?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, there's like a co-op mode.
It's cool.
Okay, I'll talk to you in like four hours.
Not that many.
Four is being very generous.
That is true.
All right, so I got the thing.
And now I have to forget like the progression here.
I can't leave from here?
I'm not sure if there's a moment in the game where you're waiting on me.
Am I?
Because I'm just kind of existing in this room.
Okay.
You eating a gogurt?
That's what it looked like.
Oh, where's the candle?
You, am I waiting for you?
Oh, the game showed me because I'm too dumb.
Now you're waiting for me.
Oh, okay.
I'm waiting for you to get a candle?
And it has to spook me.
What can I do here?
Can I look at this?
There ain't nothing on here.
Water purification.
Headed to San Francisco?
Berry's spotted.
I think if you play this in, um, what happens if I fail this QD?
Fail it.
Ah, was that me running after me into a room with me?
Right?
Okay, so we're currently...
There you are.
Why are you so sexy though?
You found me.
Good work.
So what's happening on your side?
Are you just whispering in my ear?
No, you, I'm just standing completely still.
And you're scared of me.
Well, you're not standing completely still for me.
Just kill me.
Bart, get over here.
Here's a great QT's coming up.
Don't.
I won't, I get up.
He's just...
Hey, uh, you failed too many times.
So we gotta just throw you.
This is so, this is so funny.
It's me, it's Blitz.
Did I trap your hand in the door?
No.
Well then, what stopped the door?
You closed it.
You closed the door.
But your hand was in it.
Somebody's hand was in it.
Oh my god.
That was a fucking mess.
The game is having trouble trying to figure out where,
what to do because we're doing this so fucking wrong.
What?
Did you just teleport?
I just saw...
What is happening?
Did I just go in?
Hey, he's done it.
Ladies and gentlemen, all it took was seven failed QT's in a row.
Did you finally see the cut scene?
No.
The cut scene was amazing.
I looked down and you're just lying on your back.
You should see the, you should see the fall.
The fall was good.
Oh, my stomach.
I got first character kill.
I, oh my god.
All right, here we go.
Part two.
First blood.
He's here.
Through here, quick.
Hey, can you help me out?
Can you help me?
What was the point of that?
I didn't even, I didn't choose anything and I just helped you up anyway.
Run or jump or nothing?
Uh, neither.
Is he gone yet?
Did he just leave?
Nope.
Looks like we're jumping.
Hey, can you help me up again?
Nevermind, it looks like we're both down.
This is, to be fair, this is accurate to most horror movies though.
Yeah, but like failing every QTE is so difficult.
All he did is shove you down.
I thought, did he have a knife?
Where's his knife?
He just like checked you.
What?
He was in the room with us.
He walked inside of the room with us.
Yeah, it's me, come on, let's go.
They played the stair cutscene twice.
All right, can they start dropping like flies here?
Let's see.
Imagine playing a horror game and you have to google how to die.
I think.
I know, right?
We'll be all right here.
Three people could be dead right now.
How could you fuck this up so badly?
We've failed every QTE and made every horrible decision.
Including not making decisions.
Things appear to have taken a turn towards the spiritual, wouldn't you say?
I think this game just rewards an indecisive characteristic.
If you just don't ever make any choices in your own life, everything will work itself out.
I was really hoping there was going to be like a bottle of alcohol in this book.
He, or rather you, should have been a bit less careless.
Have you figured out what's going on?
How to stop it?
How to save the lives of your poor unfortunate stowaways?
The poor unfortunate stowaways are chat at this point.
We're trying to save their lives by getting everyone killed.
The deaths that night.
Let me help you out.
Give you a little hint.
Please.
I still don't understand what's happening.
Are we looking for gold still?
You're a gold bars.
Who's the monster?
Well, then how are you?
Are you actually the maybe forces at play here?
Are you imitating chat?
Sign.
I'm asking.
I'm asking if it's even some of the more I don't understand.
I mean, that's supernatural.
Perhaps you've started to realize something.
Everything.
Perhaps you're starting to realize berries.
May not be quite what they appear to be.
I hope that helps.
Well, aren't you excited to find out what the poor unfortunate
for making of all this and how you might avoid any more unnecessary tragedy?
Nothing is as it seems.
Everything you see is a lie.
It's like very on the nose.
Everything's a lie.
Okay, I cannot.
You know what?
I'm going to be real with you.
I really can't fucking believe it's the only way we can explain all this.
We have done this whole thing again.
I thought it was going to be like five people die on the boat or something.
Okay, we're about to do the whole thing.
Only one person per chapter can die because you have to code all those outcomes.
Yeah, but just for a second, I tried to catch up.
You can only die when you're allowed to die.
Why this?
This just doesn't add up.
Should have switched character.
I think there's a common misconception that if a character lives or dies,
that's the only indicator of a choices matter game.
The real thing is we're not even making choices.
You know what I'm saying?
Like we haven't chosen to do anything.
Okay, we're going back right now.
So I don't care if they haven't died by now.
I care because we just didn't play like we what the fuck is going on with this ship?
That's funny because I got to be honest.
It feels like there's some like like evil, like you chose not to play the game.
That's true.
Let's just stay calm and relative.
I'm talking about the first playthrough.
Okay, that's stuff I saw.
It's like there were these old soldiers that they were.
There's never like two paths.
Which one do you want to do?
That doesn't that actually they all lead to the same thing.
Now, it seems the only Alex.
What are you talking about?
There were things walking around with his face on them about his face.
He was it's horrifying faces.
Alex is so ugly.
What the fuck?
Why did you say that about me?
Sorry, I'm just parroting the last stream.
This is the second stream.
Maybe like one thing could but not all of these crazy things.
It's too much of a coincidence.
There's got to be something going on here.
What can we absolutely be sure about?
What do we know that's real?
We're wasting time.
Whatever we do, we have to do it now.
Time to get off this ship.
We're not going anywhere without the distributor cap.
The Duke needs it to run.
What's the next stream tomorrow?
This ship's got to have a radio.
That's great.
But do you think it still works?
Streaming tomorrow.
So we have to go through this again.
Is there like a way I can I can I just like get off this damn ship?
No shit.
I think we're speaking clinically.
Speedruns going pretty good.
So the speedrun is going really good so far.
We might set a new world first.
Why are they doing this again?
I just got here.
You just got here.
How do you know we're doing it again?
Uh-oh.
Find the radio.
Find a way up.
All right.
It's around here.
Just follow me.
I know where it is, Zephyr.
I did the same thing last time.
What did you do?
Right?
Did I?
I did the same thing.
I leaned over on the side of the chair and that got hurt again.
Like I moved too far over to my right.
Why did I do that twice?
This is freaking me out.
This is actually getting in my head.
I'll pull you up.
Is there some gas coming in that I need to be aware of?
Maybe it's the amount of time that we've been in the game.
I leaned over on the right.
And if I lean too hard, my right arm rest will move.
And it kind of catches me sometimes.
And I hurt my fucking elbow.
Someone is teleporting.
Do a deep sniff.
This is where I chased comrades before.
Yeah.
Okay.
We're almost at the end of the game.
Over here.
We do the radio.
And then that's like the final scene.
Got to wait through here.
The way we've been playing has been making the characters glitch around my game.
Oh, I'm certain of it.
Because I'm hosting this, right?
So that means that I'm dumping data into your computer's brain and it can't take it.
Because it's just all these things are happening too quickly.
Loading in.
Okay.
Let's go find the radio.
Should I scream?
Should I just say nothing?
Say nothing to the radio.
Where is it?
It's in here, right?
What are you doing?
What's my character doing?
Scream?
No, I'm not going to say anything because that tells them that there's people here.
Maybe they won't show up at the end.
Where is this damn radio?
I remember that.
No, but there's gotta be a radio on this ship.
They're...
Okay, it's about the lore.
Radio is back here, right?
Yeah.
And then it's Mayday, Mayday.
Do you think it's easier to navigate your character in this game or Resident Evil 1
on original console?
That's Tasa.
No freaking way.
This thing actually still works?
Wait, I'm doing this this time?
Good old shortwave radio.
Resident Evil 1.
It's a number station.
Military bandwidth.
Okay, let's ask something else.
Yeah, we don't know the name of the ship.
Therefore, we're not given...
Come in, please.
Do you read us?
Over.
Okay, at least there's someone listening.
The signal's in and out, though.
Listen, that was our only chance.
What's wrong with you?
Imagine being kidnapped, abducted, held hostage, torn onto a ghost boat against your will.
You get a working radio.
You say nothing.
No, at that point, that's when one of the characters just starts laughing.
This has got to lead somewhere.
Maybe we can find a way to get the power back.
I can't believe it.
We need to get that radio working.
Unbelievable.
I think someone should wait here in case our message comes a dream.
What else can go wrong today?
Obviously.
I can do this.
I should be the one to go.
No clowns in this game, either.
Except for all the main characters, but...
That's it, then.
I'm going.
I'm coming, too.
Actors, I like you.
Really? No.
You're not my bodyguard.
It's not your fault.
I'll take care of myself.
Then that's that.
I'm going.
Okay, Julia.
We got the same outcome.
Fuck.
We should have said, let me go.
We've done the same outcome.
The same thing.
The same run.
The only thing that's changed is you T-Posed on the ground.
We're doomed to repeat history.
Oh, we have to try to get shot by that guy, right?
Keep telling him that there's no mist.
Just be like, what are you talking about?
I see the mist.
There is no mist.
What are we going to do?
We'll wait here by the radiant.
He thinks we're dead.
We're just embarrassed, okay?
Gosh.
I can't believe we just said it with such confidence and gusto
that we were going to be the ones to jump down there.
And then we just...
I don't know, guys.
I was expecting a different outcome.
Hey.
That's so stupid.
Bubbles.
After you.
Okay.
Straight.
Forward.
Left.
Hug the corners.
Save time.
Okay.
Your cameras.
I still see you.
That's me.
I thought that I was Brad.
Eat the food on the cart.
You missed the food.
Go back.
Hey, are you Brad?
You missed this food that you missed on the cart.
Gold on table.
Look, it's different down there.
Looks like the engine room.
Good place to find the generator, right?
The ladder's broken off here.
I think I can just...
Wait.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You know when you love a movie so much?
Okay.
Just come down.
In the theater.
And you're out of the seat.
That was so good.
That was the best movie I've ever seen in my life.
Let's go watch it again.
Right now.
Let's get in there and watch it right now.
You go to the next show and you move.
Oh, God.
What's up?
That...
It was...
Why are we doing this?
We didn't like this movie.
Are you hearing my jokes, like, on a delay?
What?
I...
When we first started it, I said that.
You did?
Yeah.
Were you muted?
No.
I said, uh, hey, projector boy fell asleep and he forgot to run the audio.
So we were all being silent.
But we're seeing the second showing in the evening.
When did you say it?
It's a theory, I guess.
Oh, God.
All right.
Let's get going.
That's not the same joke.
If they take...
They both take place in a movie theater.
I said it's like when a big movie opens and there's a second evening showing.
That's basically the same thing.
Except in this one, we're being silent.
Well, get fucking plagiarized.
Does that mean that I wasn't listening to you?
Can you walk forward?
I can't...
I don't know where I'm going.
Please move your character.
Hey, it's the rebreather.
The fisherman must have bothered over from the Duke of Milan.
You think it still works?
Looks like it's got a little juice left.
Maybe a couple of minutes.
Should we bring it with us?
I mean, it's heavy.
I don't even know what you decided there.
All right, this is important.
This is important.
Get shot.
It's the mist.
The mist is doing it.
Yeah, we have to tell him that we have been breathing this mist all day.
Just be like, oh yeah, we've been breathing it in.
We breathe it in every day.
I think we messed it up pretty bad last time.
I don't know how to do it any worse.
The way to do it is to keep saying that you breathed in the mist.
So like actually have to try.
Why would he scream at us?
Because keep saying that there is no mist.
Okay, so we have to keep telling this guy that there's no mist.
There's no mist hiding, you little foots.
And we're sharing all that gold, huh?
There must be plenty of that.
Wait, here it comes.
Oh no, he didn't say the line.
It's like Scooby Doo.
Okay, quick thinking.
Please tell me we're safe.
Yeah, totally.
I mean, these doors are vented with stand also stuff.
Okay, so we have to say the mist is fake.
You're stupid.
The mist is not real.
There's no mist.
Okay, say you breathe it in and then say it's not real.
Raise your hands up.
No changing.
Just put the gun down.
Nobody has to get hurt.
I bet being completely silent here is the optimal.
We have to tell them that there's no such thing as a mist.
I picked the worst option.
There's the Aria monsters thing.
What did you just say?
What mist?
What's going on?
Is this me?
That was you.
Yeah, I couldn't control it.
Which one do I do?
I think we're supposed to say that it's not real.
Like he's like crazy or something.
There's no mist.
What are you talking about?
There it is.
Why would he shoot her?
And not the guy who's like there's no mist, dude.
Hey, dude, what are you talking about?
I am effectively telling you, me, that you're wrong.
I'm gonna shoot the person fucking next to you.
Like unabashedly out of your mind.
I'm basically calling you crazy.
I am essentially saying, hey, shoot me, please.
I would like you to do it.
That girl.
Don't worry, just raise her head.
She comes back the next scene with like a bandage around her head.
He was just trying to scare her.
Okay, so here's the opportunity for us to screw this up somehow.
Well, we already know what happens here.
Do we?
Better choreography than Game of Thrones.
Who was that?
Over here.
This must have been what we just heard.
Doesn't matter.
We need that distributor cap.
So this time I'm gonna kill you.
Brad is invincible.
Brad is invincible?
I mean.
Are you Brad?
No.
All right.
Is this like a bad guy in the game or is this like a Diablo 3 loot goblin?
He's he's just like, oh, I fuck.
Oh, no.
I pressed the button supposed to be running away from him.
It feels like we're chasing him.
My brain turned off and I just like did the QTE.
Well, you did the QTE.
I did the I did the first QTE.
I don't think it matters though.
No, it doesn't matter.
I'll follow him.
I'll just find the little gold coins that are in a trail.
Does anything matter when we saw that everyone gets gunned down at the end?
Unless you fix the boat.
That is true.
There's one choice that really matters.
And it's up to you to save the piece of equipment.
I'm not gonna make this jump, Alex.
I'll have to find another way around.
And then I'm gonna stab you.
But then how do you die?
Because you killed yourself last time.
Uh, that's it.
I don't know.
Then I would just I just get gunned down.
My control is like fucking broken.
What the hell is going on with this thing?
I've seen this one before.
I have an actual headache.
Like in real life?
Yeah, from this video game.
Oh shit.
I think I think the miss is seeping through.
Well, we're almost done.
We're almost done completely.
So, um, who's left to kill?
Wait, can I just get eaten by rats?
Fuck.
So do we want the everyone dies to gunfire at the end or no?
Well, it's only gonna be like two or three.
But you're like, yes or no, because I have to choose now.
Uh, may as well just get us all killed.
Because didn't we already go back and do this the right way?
We did.
We've seen both of those endings already.
However, really a choice that I made right there.
Oh, no.
Like, did I make a choice or did I just try to open a door?
Okay.
I'm gonna try to be as menacing as possible.
Wait, why are you different?
Am I different?
You're a different monster.
Alex, it's me.
What?
It's a different person.
Put the knife down.
What?
So what was the...
I gotta watch to see what monster I was.
You were like a two-headed, a great show.
Now you're just the...
Give me the knife, okay?
The captain guy.
Give me the knife.
Olsen.
All right, now what happens if I stop?
What happens if I stop now?
You're still going.
But if I stop...
You went right for center mass with at least one of those.
I did?
Yeah.
Oh, right.
The reason you didn't see the two-headed monster is because, uh...
When I was playing as Alex, we had found the two-headed monster in one of the coffins.
So it was in his imagination.
That's right.
Oh.
This time we speed ran.
All right.
We did it.
We did it as...
We've played through the game twice.
We've played through the whole game two times.
I mean, played is very loosely stated.
So now what happens if...
Because we didn't tell anybody on the radio where we were.
We did.
Yeah, we just locked up.
So if nobody knows where we are on the radio, then we just live here now.
Brothers till the end.
Guess we're not going anywhere on the duke.
Pretty much stuck here.
What a way to go.
Starving to death.
Wait, what do you mean, what a way to go?
And that's it?
There's no food.
There's just people.
They could resort to cannibalism.
By a little time.
Maybe some old crates got some potatoes in cans or something.
I don't know.
Yeah, I mean...
I think, uh, I think I'm gonna go back in.
No way.
Hey, there's gotta be some food somewhere in there, right?
Ashes, cans, whatever's in there.
It's not worth getting.
We're gonna starve out here.
I'm gonna try to get the Duke of Milan out to sea.
Make a boat.
Take those crates.
How are you gonna do that with no engine?
Yeah, well, nowhere is better than this fucking ship.
That's it, Ben.
Are we saying goodbye to each other?
Why aren't we doing this together?
Um, I don't know.
It's odd to me that these two brothers just escaped
their own version of hell and are instantly separating.
I'm coming back for you.
Why are you not going?
What are you doing?
He's just gonna live on the ship and eat, I guess.
For you to do that, you'd have to assume the other person's absolutely dead,
but you fist bumped at the end.
So you just don't care that they're gonna die?
To go back in here for any reason.
I don't know.
Okay, there's only one other person here that can kill him.
Wait, we didn't have any food on the boat?
Imagine if two people were rowing this massive boat.
There's a whole downstairs kitchen.
It's Gendry.
He's just running around in a circle in like the crazy drug ship.
All right, now for the post credit where the dude wakes up
and I guess presumably kills Alex because the helicopter shouldn't be coming.
Yeah, there's gonna be a Danny versus Alex.
At least there was actually a different ending.
Drugged out fight, yeah.
Which makes it better than Blair Witch.
Which also says choices matter at the beginning of the game.
That's it.
Game over.
You're done.
For now, at least.
You could always try again.
See if you can't do better next time around.
Not a very happy ending.
Or maybe it is.
Better.
What makes you happy, really?
He knows.
He's watching the stream.
And the distributor cap.
Boom.
Unfortunate.
It's all about decisions, isn't it?
Decisions made in a hurry, in a panic, made with the heart instead of the head.
Or vice versa.
Sometimes those decisions take a long time to have repercussions.
But there are repercussions.
But what were the long-term repercussions?
There wasn't a scenario.
Is he suggesting that in a future anthology game, those choices are going to matter?
If they're separate games, I don't see how that's possible.
But like, we just overwrote everything that we did.
Until we meet again.
Maybe in Little Hope.
Maybe somewhere else.
But be certain.
We will meet again.
But I can't speak.
Yeah, it's not an anthology.
Cool.
All right, you ready to see the...
McDonald's menu item tier list.
Now.
You guys fucking crack me up.
New content.
He's chafing a little, I think.
Why would he be sitting above deck this entire time?
Is the real question.
No ship radio.
You could fish, though.
And stay alive.
Well, don't they have a grill?
They have a radio on the boat with a GPS.
It just can't move.
And he's got beds under the deck.
And a kitchen.
They've got a George Foreman grill.
The radio antenna broke.
Fishing isn't that easy.
Well, too.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
It's Dan.
Oh, you motherfuckers.
That happened to you before it happened to me, apparently.
Wait, I got jumpscared first?
Yeah, like a second before.
I just saw someone in the woods.
So I like anticipated it.
Man, the whole stream watched this trailer for the next one three times.
It wasn't even a Twitch bounty.
Claim the Twitch bounty.
We did it.
Yeah.
We stretched a three hour game into however long that ended.
Seven hours.
All right.
Let's give another review.
Time for review two.
Okay.
So I have to go through twice and trying to do absolutely like just a dog shit run.
Just a dog shit run.
Can you do me a favor, though, and watch the clip of Conrad falling?
I do want to watch that.
Does anybody have that little clip of Conrad falling?
I got it, yeah.
You've already got it.
Wow.
It's impressive.
I don't even have it.
In the door of me.
Let's watch it.
We're going to watch it on stream.
So this is the Conrad falling experience.
All right.
Hang on.
Give me a count in the door.
Okay.
Let me get it up here.
So this is from Alex's perspective.
This is him.
I'm going to start playing it and let's check it out.
Did you do the countdown?
Then three, two, one.
In the door.
Well, then what?
Stop the door.
You closed it.
Yeah, but your hand was in it.
Somebody's hand was in it.
My God.
The game is having trouble with trying to figure out.
Did you just teleport?
I just saw what is happening.
Hey, he's done it.
Ladies and gentlemen, all it took was seven failed cuties in a row.
Oh, the good classic German laughing.
Right at the end.
Oh, because I walked over and it was just the camera panned down.
Yeah, it was like super delayed lap.
I had no idea what you were seeing.
Yeah, because I didn't see any of that shit.
I walked over and the camera panned down the hole and you were just lying on your back.
So imagine like Conrad.
Okay.
So you did see his body though.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
So it wasn't a secret that he died.
This game is fucking ridiculous.
Yeah, this was the movies.
I think it was like a fun co-op experiment that kind of lost sight of the foundation.
Yes.
The core principles.
One hundred percent.
It was like an interesting idea.
I wish there were more co-op games, but you got to have some core tenets of gameplay
that were missing.
Well, so hot.
You want to do the next one?
I'm going to do round three.
No, I mean the next game.
Oh, are we going to play the Blair Witch project one?
I guess we have to at this point.
Kind of have to.
All right.
Well, that's a clean seven hours.
Wasn't clean.
Streams went down at least ten times.
It was an incredibly filthy, dirty stream.
It was filthy, but yeah, that was Man of Medan.
It was a game.
Yeah, that was Man of Medan.
We kind of knew what we were getting into, but yeah.
Just be glad you didn't do Blair Witch.
I heard it was not very good, but I will see you guys tomorrow.
I'm streaming tomorrow.
That was Italics.
Again, everybody say hello to Italics.
Go follow that stream.
He streams too.
You know, he's a fucking streamer.
Person that's in the call.
Italics.
That is how you actually pronounce your name.
Who is the Man of Medan?
I don't know.
I think that's the name of the big boat.
Isn't it?
That was like the gigantic boat.
At least that's what I thought it was.
Is the boat name Man of Medan?
Yeah.
I mean, no, I don't think it is.
It was the Duke of Medan.
Yeah, it was the Duke of Milan.
The Man of...
Whatever it was.
That was the small boat.
Man Milan.
All right.
Well, I'm going to get out of here.
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to wind down.
I'll...
Yep.
Hey, want to go to McDonald's?
Uh, no.
I ate McDonald's yesterday.
Fuck.
Anyways, that's the end.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Tomorrow is...
Let me just double check to make sure I got everything correct here.
Tomorrow, we are going to do Terraria.
I think we actually...
Both of us are like on the same page.
So, unless something else happens, which I don't think it will.
We're going to finish Terraria tomorrow.
Those streams are cursed, though, because something seems to go wrong every time.
But we are finally going to close the book on Terraria tomorrow.
It's going to be a chill stream.
Thanks for joining me.
We're going to go out here.
Do the bits.
Say hello to the subs.
Plan B?
I do have an extreme Plan B.
But I don't think we're going to need it.
Because we did confirm that it was going to happen tomorrow.
So, don't worry.
All right, now I need to get out of here.
And let's say good night.
Thanks for joining us on Man of a Dan.
It was...
I don't think the game was...
Look, the game was not that good.
But the experience was fun.
Because, obviously, we were just dicking around and having a good time.
Playing this with one or two, maybe three or potential four people on a couch.
There is some value there.
There is.
I had a blast.
I hope you did, too.
And if we don't see you tomorrow, maybe we'll see you next time.
So let's rewind a little bit here.
Let's go back to earlier.
Lazy Luke had $3.
They just said Subway 300.
Thanks to three bucks, Lazy Luke.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
Thank you, Wiki.
This for the three bucks.
This is truly the Citizen Kane of video game stories.
I mean, it was cool.
It's an interesting...
Look, Super...
Go back to Until Dawn.
They did a similar kind of game last time.
I almost feel like they tried to do too much of close to what they did before.
They're almost like, this game felt like it was...
Hey, remember Until Dawn?
There's monsters.
And there might be other people.
And there might be...
There could be other...
Is it a monster or a person?
Or is it a...
Is it a monster?
It is a monster.
This actually seemed like it was...
They rewrote Until Dawn.
And it just wasn't as good.
And it was way shorter.
But the good thing is they made Until Dawn.
And that game...
I loved that game.
So this is one.
Maybe in like two and three, they'll start to...
There's been some criticisms of this game already.
I have faith that Supermassive will, over the next few games in this anthology,
maybe kind of change it up a little bit.
Because I mean, they did do...
That they made Until Dawn.
If not, then that's a letdown.
Because there's not very many good horror experiences.
There are some.
But it's kind of hard to find a really, really truly good horror game.
At least in the last...
I'll wait.
At least in the last three or four years.
Five years or so.
Play Silent...
Yeah, Silent Hill 2 came out like 15 years ago.
I'm talking about like now.
I don't mean that there's never been a good horror game.
You know, there's never...
No, I'm talking about like the last like five years.
There's been a couple.
And I've played some of them already.
Resident Evil 2 was...
Resident Evil 7 was...
No.
Resident Evil 7...
The first like six hours of Resident Evil 7 was an awesome horror game.
And then they lost me for a little while.
And then the end was pretty good.
I didn't like that kind of mid to late game in Resident Evil 7.
On the boat with, you know...
But I don't want to give any spoilers.
But once it became not a scary game anymore, it was kind of just...
You know, I don't want to talk about it.
Because I don't know if people haven't played it yet.
But there was a big string there.
And I streamed that whole game in VR.
The whole game.
They lost me at that end part.
But the first like 6 to 12, 6 to 10 hours of Resident Evil 7 was fantastic.
We'll see if the next anthology games are any good.
But thank you to Demons V for the $15.
They say blood sacrifice and then like a face.
Thank you for the $15 Demons V.
Really appreciate it.
Sticks Renegade, thanks for the $2.50.
I'm fucking revoking your gamer license.
What gaming did I do tonight?
You can't do that.
But thank you, Sticks Renegade.
I didn't know you were an authority on the gamer licenses.
Shitty Viewbot, thanks for the $10.
Just admit, German buddy, you fucked up.
I did.
I know I did.
But it's all right.
I did.
I messed up.
But thank you for the $10, Shitty Viewbot.
Errorless, thanks for the $2.50.
Hey, Jerma, can you give these bits to italics, please?
Yeah, let me go to McDonald's and I buy him a McChicken.
Thank you, though.
Thank you, Trampston, for the $5.
I'm going to come through this monitor and give you a peck, a punch on the nose.
What?
We are going to, this is going to be an interesting,
this is going to be a very interesting credits
because the stream, Twitch had a ton of problems earlier tonight.
And the stream turned off like probably five to six times.
I am curious as to see if any of who even is on this list.
Still pretty significant.
Now, it was definitely not Cox because they were portions where
italics stream would be at zero and I would still be fine and live.
And other people were talking about how there was other streamers having problems.
So I guess it was because it stopped.
So I don't think that was a Cox thing tonight.
But thank you to, thank you Trampston.
Appreciate it.
What's the name of the song?
This is an original song by Blordo.
This is an original made for the end of this stream song.
Speaking of which, I have, I still have stuff that I have to put on.
It seems like every day something else is like happening
that like I can't just sit down and do it.
But I do, I have new stuff from Blordo.
I have it.
I have to just set it up and do it and set up the scenes and everything.
And I just haven't, I just haven't been able to sit down and do it.
Yes, you will see that.
I'm, it's, it has to be.
Like the next time I stream after this weekend, it'll all be there.
It has to be.
Like I've held on for too long.
That is good shit though.
You guys are gonna like it.
OST.
A German I-95.
Need some more emotes too.
Yeah, I gotta do a whole, once the carnival stream is done,
I'll have a lot more brain power to actually sit down.
There's a lot going on this in September.
The carnival stream is coming up really soon.
TwitchCon is right after that.
So my brain is kind of all over the place this month.
But good night everybody.
We'll see you tomorrow if you show up.
Am I going to TwitchCon?
I am.
But I am going to because of the carnival stream.
I'm not gonna go the whole time.
So I will only be at TwitchCon for like a day or two.
So I'm not gonna be there from Thursday to Monday or what a lot of people usually do.
But I will be there for at least a day or two.
When's the new Discord channel going up for videos, art, and all that?
I'm gonna talk to...
I will have like a little mod thing tomorrow.
Tomorrow after my stream I'll just get that all set up.
I'm also gonna get a hard date for the activity book stream after tomorrow's stream.
So I'll give you all this information soon.
I'm gonna see who's around tomorrow to talk about it all.
So stay tuned.
But I will see you guys tomorrow.
Take care.
Until then, goodbye for now.
See you later.