Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some Smeep Smoop Smoop.
Today, gonna be not killing that spy because it's a real person.
Playing as the scout with the cleaver and the ball. The big balls.
Uh, what am I doing here? I'm just gonna go for kills with this.
And if I get him, I get him, you know? Hey, what's up dude? Oh, damn it. Give me that ball.
You prick. I would have had that too.
There it is. Get out of town. Get out of town. I'm running circles around you.
All right. This guy's dumb too. Ready? I'll get this.
No shit. No, don't let him cap it. Get him.
What? That was bad. That was real bad. At least I got that guy. That's one.
If I don't, I've got to get at least five of those in this video.
I don't care if it takes me like two hours.
Look buddy. I mean, I don't ask me what the hell this guy's doing.
Get it. Bang. Nice. That's two. That makes two.
Got to do this at least a few more times until I am satisfied.
I have an insatiable hunger to throw this into people's faces.
It is my thirst. It's just not... Will you quit jumping around like a freaking jackrabbit?
All right. You know what? I'm just going to start shooting you now.
I know I'm breaking the stipulation rules, but I have to kill this guy.
He is just... Is every single soldier on Hightower a rocket jumping soldier?
That is an inquiry. I want to be answered.
I feel like every single soldier that's on this map at all times is using the rocket jumper.
Like, look it. Even on our team. And this guy's going to burn to death.
See you. Nice. Look at... You see the guy just...
That guy just rocket jumped over his dead body.
Stop rocket jumping!
I'm just not going to do it again. I'm just not going to do it against a soldier anymore.
There's just no reason to. He's just going to rocket jump, but I'm going to miss him.
Look, look. Ready? Oh, I would have missed him. Don't worry.
My goodness. That headshot was unbelievable.
You get it. You'll get it. Okay. I will give you that one.
Everybody gets one. Now you're dead. You're not even there anymore.
But yeah, now when you come... Here we go. Here we go. I'll get him.
Here we go. Here it is. Sir... He was just...
Don't worry. I'll still get him. No, he's going to headshot me.
I'm going to get right up close to him.
I'm going to try to taunt kill this guy. Actually, you know, you know what?
There it is! Just screw you! You took... I had that.
I seriously had that. And you took it all away from me.
And don't mind me. I just want to go up here and taunt kill this sniper.
God damn you. Or I'll do this.
Either or. Either or. Neither nor.
Give me the health. Give me the health. Give me the health.
What the... What am I doing? Why did I just do that?
Oh, I'm going to predict your movements because I'm smart.
That was the dumbest thing I've ever done. Hey, see you later. Home run.
No! No, you fuck. No, I can't believe it.
I can't believe it. You...
Of course that'll happen. And it didn't kill him, but yes, it did.
Oh, Lord. All right. I got it. That makes four.
That makes four. I just got to get one more.
And I am the victor of this challenge.
Just... I want to do that. I want to do that.
Hey, look. It's just a scout at the door.
That's the noise it has to make.
You know, I'm going to be patient here. I'm going to fall off this.
Let me be patient. I think I've been spotted.
In fact, I'm almost certain I've been spotted by that soldier that's down there. Maybe not.
Okay. You may in fact be... I don't know.
I'm too afraid to go check.
I love how we both have the same idea.
Dude, there's been like three snipers up in this roost like the whole game.
You tell... Okay. Here we go.
He doesn't see me. I wonder how long it's going to take.
Don't mind me. I'm just part of the set.
I'm set piece scout. That's like what my name is now.
Don't let him do it. That's five. That's five.
I can't believe I just died from that.
What is that? What dog is that? What cartoon dog did I just do?
Come on. Come on. Comment section.
I need your help.
Here we go. I'm going to get one more for good measure.
One more for good measure. One more for good measure.
Here we go, baby. Nope.
Nope. Nope.
Nope. No.
No, don't kill me.
What's going on with my neck? Did you see that?
My guy was his head was going like, what the... What was that?
Outrageous.
All right. This is the last life. This is the last life, I think.
Give it to me. God damn it.
I'm going to keep you in the co...
Oh, see, big mistake number one was you doing that.
Yeah. All right. The deed is done.
Now it's time.
No, dude. Come on. Mr. Pyro.
Holy shit.
I've said this before and I'll say it again.
When a bald ass Pyro is looking at you, he's a spy.
He just is. That's just the way there is.
I can't believe I didn't see through that.
I thought it was... Whatever.
Let's wrap this up. Let's wrap this up right now, please.
Well, thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
I think I got like five kills, six kills with this thing.
No, let me get the fucking taunt kill.