Now it didn't take me 15 minutes to write a tweet. I wanted to make sure that my drink was chilled, cool, cold, didn't have any ice, put it into the freezer.
I was told don't do that because your drink will explode. And I was just like, what? This is just baiting me for something weird, right? Like, what do you mean?
Dude, don't put your drink in the freezer for five minutes. It's gonna explode.
What? And then I was told, well, if you put a can or, you know, something that has, you know, compressed air, don't do that, right? Of course.
But this is just me putting a cup in the freezer for like five minutes to chill it out. It is true. It's true. Well, don't be careful then. I didn't know that.
I mean, I knew about if you like a can of soda, you don't want to really do that. Good night, Jerma. You going to bed? Well, good night. See you later.
You're going to bed? We're about to watch television commercials from 1980 to 2000. You're going to bed?
All right. Probably got something to do. Whatever you're doing. Have a good night. It's five in the morning right now.
I don't know. Where could you be right now where it's five a.m.? We're like, Hawaii? Is Hawaii like, well, how far back is Hawaii from right now?
Asia? Would it be? No, it'd be earlier. It'd be like, wouldn't it be like one or two, two o'clock in the morning?
What time is it in Hawaii right now? Right now? Five a.m. in Australia.
Okay. This always confuses me. Isn't Australia is ahead of the United States, right?
It's technically it's like 14 or 15 hours ahead, not behind. So it's is it right now? Is it the seventh?
It's the seventh in Australia and New Zealand. Depends on your perspective. Five a.m. in Iceland. Yes. Okay.
So this is your perspective. So at what point you don't go backwards to go forwards, right?
Well, I guess you kind of do. What time is it right now in Asia like Japan, China?
Like, what time is it right now? And is it it's the sixth, right? Is it still the sixth?
Is it the fifth in Asia? No, it's six a.m. in Korea. Is there anywhere on Earth?
That's actually a pretty interesting thing to talk about. Is there a place?
Is there more than a few places on Earth where it's over the course of three days?
Like, is there a time period where it's the fifth in this place, the sixth in this place and the seventh in this place?
There's no magic kind of hour where that happens. Sorry. That fucking hurt.
Are you high? No. What are you talking about? I'm sorry. I looked over.
Look, I'm just like kind of getting here. I'm getting ready for the day, getting ready to the stream.
I'm talking about this. I look over at the mod chat and I've never seen this before.
So they're just kind of like, what is he talking about? What I saw?
VR Josh wrote ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm like at least eight or nine has I've never seen that over here.
That's never happened. It was like this is no.
Dr. Clay, what the fuck are you talking about? No one is three days ahead.
No, no, no, no. Let me listen. What I mean by that is, is there just let me explain for one second before it freaks out.
So right now, OK, four hours ago, five hours ago,
when it was eleven fifty nine p.m. in China, it is technically the fifth over there.
It is then about six or seven a.m. here, which is the sixth.
And Australia, it's the seventh right at eleven fifty nine p.m. in China.
I'm asking, is there a period where it's like the time zones go over a few days?
He's dumb. No, what the fuck? You idiot. Australia, the 24 hour cycle.
It's 24 hours. I know, but I'm saying in that 24 hour period, is it possible?
Dude, there aren't two sons. No, that's not what I'm saying.
I need to like write this down because I feel like you're all wrong. I feel like you're all wrong.
If I take a plane and travel the world, the entire globe and beat the time zones, is it still the day it was for me on the plane?
Precisely. Exactly. OK, everybody shut up.
We're watching commercials today. What are you saying? You're exploiting a glitch.
I need to like write this down. Eleven fifty nine p.m. in China is seven a.m.
in the United States, which is the next day in Australia.
Somebody help me here. Oh, excuse me. Thank you, scientists that came in and fixed this.
For the two hours between ten and eleven fifty nine UTC each day, three different days are observed at the same time in different places.
For example, at UTC time Thursday, ten fifteen, it is Wednesday, twenty three fifteen in American Samoa, UTC minus eleven,
and Friday, zero zero colon fifteen in Kiritimati, which is UTC plus fourteen for the first hour, UTC ten o'clock to dash ten colon fifty nine.
This is true for both inhabited and uninhabited territories.
But during the second hour, UTC eleven colon zero zero dash eleven fifty nine, it is only true in an uninhabited maritime time zone.
Twelve hours behind UTC, UTC minus twelve.
So there you go. You just got absolutely decimated.
I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I'm. I was right.
There was a scientist came in. No one cares. I do.
It would be funny. Yeah, somebody got it right.
That's a prank. No, it's over.
There are three observed days in one day in one small period.
Explain what you just read without reading it.
OK, so there are boats and I don't know as I'm right.
I'm right. All I know is that I'm right.
I have my reasoning when it's twelve when it's eleven fifty nine p.m. in China.
It is therefore colon eleven dash zero zero UTC four a.m.
You got it right here. Somebody has it as an image.
Look at this. Look at this shit. Look at this shit. You ready for this?
Oh, you guys are in trouble now. The overlapping time zones.
Here it comes. Hold on. Let me get this on screen.
Oops. OK, here we go. So here it is. Check this out.
I would like all the people that just unsubscribed and unfollowed
because this guy is such a moron.
There's no way he can't even tie his shoes every day.
I want you to look at this. What are the filters on this?
They look. Oh, excuse me. Oh, excuse me. What happened?
What's this? Oh, is this the overlapping time zones where that shows you
we have three. We observe three different days. Interesting. Interesting.
Explain that. This is the middle of the ocean next to Alaska.
There are three observable days. Thirteen.
Explain what a time zone is. Time is a no, it's not.
What? Address the Eminem, please.
The last image that was saved here and I just clicked it.
I thought I watched a video on this. Yeah, everyone's calling me crazy.
This is how it's actually this. There's more than two observable days.
And like for an hour a day in a very specific time period,
which is very much explained in this graph,
which if you can't understand what this means, I mean, I do.
So on the left side of the line, it could be 1201 a.m. on January 3rd.
It would be January 2nd on most of the earth.
But the right side of the line would still be about 1101 p.m. January 1st.
You guys ready to watch commercials?
Bro, just watch the commercials. There's so many people here that got like popcorn and drink.
Like they're sitting around like a bunch of people waiting.
And she's like, I don't want to, I don't want to do this.
Belly belt, that is unbelievably funny. I'm going to have to steal this.
I'm Tom Scott and I'm currently standing in the middle of the ocean during three simultaneous days.
Behind me is a big boat.
And that, that title, Tom Scott, that's a great video idea.
The title of that video is this video is over, like something about three days.
You know what I mean? Like it is three days long in this video.
Something, right? Like this video, it is three days on this video.
I don't know. He's so much smarter than I am. He'll be able to do it.
He would have a banger title for that too.
You know it would be super informative.
It would break everything down like incredibly well.
It would be so detailed. I would understand it so easily.
This video took three days to film. Yeah. Perfect.
Wow. Cool. All right. You guys ready?
We're going to watch commercials. We're going to watch infomercials.
We've done this before.
And it was confirmed that everybody told me that this was one of the best things I've ever done,
which is all right.
Like, hey, what's, what's the, what's your, hey, community.
What's the, your favorite thing I have ever done ever in the last 12 years?
The time that you watched infomercials on stream.
So, I mean, have to give the people what they want sometimes, right?
So here it is. These are, there's a collection.
And I didn't know this, but I mean, look at the title of this.
This is volume number 956.
There's a lot of these.
So, got some content for a little while, I think.
What are you saying?
You wish my wife a Merry Christmas.
Have a Merry Christmas.
All right. Just click, click, play.
No, I'm not ready.
I need to explain what's happening today.
Dude, did you pirate Elden Ring?
What? What are you talking about?
No, I've, I've bought it the day one.
I like I bought it two days.
What do you mean? Prove it.
I played it on Steam.
No, there's no wall penis.
I would show you.
Okay.
So here we go.
This is 80s commercials.
We're going to break these down.
I'm going to be frequently pausing.
Those of you that are just going to be pissed off with my pausing.
And we're going to begin.
Look, we had to spend a little bit.
We had to have people trickle in to hang out.
All right.
One more image and we'll go.
One more image.
This is pretty good, too.
We're going to wait for this people.
Everyone's like favorite stream ever.
Imagine if we didn't stall for like 15 minutes.
This is a good one, though.
Oh, shit.
What have I done?
No, I'm good.
Where is it?
There it is.
Green M&M.
Live here.
Sun up.
Auto.
Live here.
Sundown.
Midnight.
Boat.
Earth.
Some of you guys got really into that.
And I'm telling you, I was correct.
Auto.
Live here.
All right.
You guys ready?
It's time to watch some commercials.
Some of these are actually Christmas related.
So, I mean, a lot of ads happen on Christmas time.
And let's see.
I don't know what these are.
I have no idea.
I know as much as you do.
But I do.
I'm going to remember some of these, I think.
Maybe not the 80s ones, but the 90s ones.
Finally, time that person out for one second.
Ready?
Here we go.
Make sure you can hear it.
We'll do it.
It's ad.
It's just ad roulette.
Mr. T and Emanuel Lewis in a Christmas dream, sponsored in part by all your friends at
Okay.
Oh, his damage.
So they had damageable chests?
Good source of vitamin A.
That's important.
And another thing.
What?
It tastes good.
Ma'am, I'll have a bowl of that Campbell's soup, please.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Are they eating Campbell's soup at a diner?
Why is the diner serving Campbell's soup?
So you go, they go into the restaurant and they order.
Oh, I'll have the soup, please.
And it's just they they dumped it into the into a big container.
Hold on.
Good for you.
Oh, it's good for you.
Lunch.
Oh, by the way, lunch of champions.
This is on the news.
This is all over the news.
It's literally all over the news.
That actually kind of looks gross.
Doesn't that kind of look like shit?
That's not like a good photo.
But wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That says Campbell's vegetable beef soup's a real good source of vitamin A.
That's important.
Okay.
And another thing.
What?
It tastes good.
Right?
Ma'am, I'll have a bowl of that Campbell's soup, please.
This look at all the cans.
Isn't the whole point of going to a restaurant that you wouldn't be served
Campbell's out of a can dumped into a container heated up?
I'm very confused by this one.
This is just a kitchen cabinet.
And let me I'm going to be very, very clear about this.
I Campbell's soup is great.
Campbell's soup, chicken noodle, tomato.
I grew up on this.
I love this stuff.
But this is weird.
This is very strange to say like, oh, yeah, we're at the diner.
Oh, don't you know?
By the way, I'm like some random like sheriff.
Oh, yeah.
Don't you know?
It's got vitamin A in it.
It's like, why?
Why are we talking right now?
Why are you telling me about this?
Eat carefully.
That was weird.
Here it comes to Diet Coke with 100% Nutri-Sweet.
A taste that's one of a kind.
Wait, this.
Why is there a jet?
These dances.
Oh, do you remember when America went to the moon?
That was a lot in that one.
Hold on.
The thing about soda commercials that I think is just so strange.
And I know chip commercials do stuff like this, too.
But it's like, who cares about any of this?
Right.
Just just drink the soda.
It's good.
Like you ever see the like the this is a completely different tangent.
But you see like the chip commercials where they have the it's like, oh, well, here's here's like a potato chip commercial.
And it's always a couple of celebrities.
And they're just they're way too obsessed with these bags.
They're way too obsessed with this shit.
They hold they hold it vertically.
They hold the bags vertically at the bottom like this.
They like they cup it like this and it stands straight up.
The bag always looks like it's made out of glass.
It's this weird tube.
It's like, look at these celebrities.
They eat chips.
So do I.
Who fucking cares?
Who cares that celebrities eat chips?
Who cares?
I do, too.
You do.
It's not like a thing that we have to I don't get it.
It's the same kind of world with soda commercials.
People are like partying.
Everyone's having such a good time.
Look at where we went to space that time.
It's like just just drink the drink.
This is a lady taking a take.
What was she doing?
Was that like a waterfall taking like a waterfall shower?
What was that?
What does this have to do with drinking soda?
You know, it would be a much better commercial.
And I'm serious.
Get me on the marketing team.
Just do what everybody does.
This just have a guy.
You have a guy.
Girl, no matter sitting down on a couch.
It's just kind of dark in the room.
And have him just go like this.
This would be more realistic.
That would actually be a terrible commercial.
You know what I mean?
Just like the side air burp that everybody does.
The bad thing about television is that everybody you see on television
is doing something better than what you're doing.
You ever see anyone on TV like just sliding off the front of the sofa
with potato chip crumbs on their face?
Some people have a little too much fun on television.
The soda commercial people.
Where do they summon this enthusiasm?
Have you seen them?
We have soda.
Jumping, laughing, flying through the air.
It's a can of soda.
Have you ever been standing there and you're watching TV
and you're drinking the exact product that they're advertising
right there on TV?
And it's like, you know, they're spiking volleyballs,
jet skiing, girls in bikinis.
And I'm standing there.
He's right.
What, you can't have the same take?
I actually do like the...
Is that the American flag?
Dude, people slam sodas in commercials too, by the way.
Have you ever noticed that?
People go like slam, slam, slam, slam.
And you're telling me there's not going to be a real gross side burp after that?
They're full of shit.
What's that?
Why is Q-Bird in this?
Who's the weird Q-Bird guy?
Why would you have a hamburger under the tree?
This is a weird present.
And the hamburger looks upside down, but right side up at the same time.
I wouldn't put my food on the ground.
Can you imagine waking up on Christmas morning?
It's like, all right, what have we got under the...
Let's see what's happening.
Everyone's so exciting.
And it's like a Burger King or like a Hardee's or whatever.
It's on the ground in front of the tree.
I can understand a bag, right?
There's a bag of Hardee's or a bag of Hardee's.
I can understand a bag of Hardee's or a bag of Hardee's.
There's a bag of Hardee's or a bag of Burger King, but it on the ground?
I don't know about that.
By the way, I've never had Hardee's before, not once.
I've never eaten it before.
That's a lie. No, it's not.
I have never eaten Hardee's or Carl's Jr.
Never in my entire life.
It's mid.
I've never had it.
They just look huge.
Everything looks gigantic in Hardee's portions.
All right, I like this one.
This one's more realistic, but it's funny because the kid didn't get a single bit in his mouth.
You eat all that soup and maybe you'll be okay.
He picked it up a little too fast and it all dumped and he just, oh, shit, there's nothing there.
Wet and cold and hungry.
Very few things are more satisfying than a hot, very beautiful love.
That one's actually pretty good.
Campbell's tomato soup.
Do you still love me anymore?
Soup is good food.
What?
It's a world of celebration.
Hold on.
Why?
Do you still love me anymore?
Soup is good food.
That was strange.
It's a world of celebration.
Everybody said, she didn't say yes.
A hot, nourishing bowl of Campbell's tomato soup.
Do you still love me anymore?
Soup is good food.
God damn it.
Are they making it in their house?
That was in the same house.
They made it in the house.
You know what's awesome about these ad compilation videos?
You can tell what they taped.
This is what they taped.
You can see the intro and the outro of what show they were actually taping and cut out.
If you're looking at video cassette recorders and you're confused by all your choices,
just look at the most important feature of all.
The picture.
And Sony Betamax records a sharper picture than VHS.
That's not just my opinion.
In tests throughout the country, more people said the picture was sharper with Sony Betamax than VHS.
So why doesn't anyone else talk sharper pictures?
Because no one else can.
Betamax, a sharper picture.
What?
What happened with Betamax?
Betamax was supposed to be better than VHS.
And people just didn't care?
The guy in the commercial even says it.
He's like, how come more people aren't talking about Betamax?
Because we're better than them.
In tests throughout the country, more people said the picture was sharper with Sony Betamax than VHS.
So why doesn't anyone else talk sharper pictures?
Because no one else can.
Betamax, a sharper picture.
It was too expensive.
Oh, that's what killed it.
Jimmy Carter on the Cuban agreement. I love him.
Betamax was better, but it was not as cheap.
Interesting.
Get in class!
What the fuck are you kids doing in the hallway?
You can't control your feelings.
Get off the desk!
Food's not even...
Can you not eat in school?
Oh, there's after school.
Alright, I will say...
I would do something like this.
I would.
If I was hanging out with friends or something, we would like, well, come on in.
Go on there.
I would do that.
Looking out the window, like, Dad's out there with the big mower?
And he's just like, Dad, what are you doing out there?
He's so excited to cut the grass?
No, that's a tractor.
But still...
I guess you're just kind of vibing out.
But why the guy in the tractor?
The Cuban agreement. I love him.
Hanson, here we are.
We're at school.
School.
Way to school!
Where? Studying in school. Kids studying in school.
Oh, it's like after school. Guy in a tractor.
Why is this guy here?
School dance.
School.
In school.
After school.
We're coming out of school.
This isn't a school.
Where's the guy in the tractor?
How do they get McDonald's at school?
I don't know.
This is one of those products that
the parent that buys it doesn't read the box.
It doesn't see the commercial.
And realizes that it makes that kind of sound.
And then they go,
Well, this sucks because now I'm going to have to listen to this.
And then they just take the batteries out overnight one night
and then tell the kid,
Oh, it's broken.
And then the kid goes, What?
Oh! And then they just do it normally.
And they don't need the extra added echo.
Action figures each sold separately.
From Mattel.
Bottom of Tell.
More food dancing.
Milk.
I mean that was alright.
Somebody said
Milk is fucking gross.
What?
Hold on.
Why is everybody just
chugging milk?
Where are they?
The questions I have with commercials like this are where are they?
This is like Burger King,
McDonald's, a restaurant.
Everybody's just drinking
I guess
They're kids?
It's the local soda milk shop.
That's what they're going for.
This guy, you know, he's like
John Travolta in Grease.
Milk.
These two kids are hitting their heads.
Are we bubbling spa?
Oh!
Wait a minute.
That was actually a pretty good reveal.
The kid's like look I see him, look I see him.
He's like no, come on kid, give me a break.
The mom sees him.
That was a great ad.
That was a great ad. They did a great job.
That was very clean.
It was right to the point.
Fun little plot twist.
That's a good one.
I'm going to give it an A-.
That's the whole special.
Oh my god.
Getting so many intros and outros.
Bob Hope here telling you to make sure you drink as much milk as you can.
Not the 1% stuff, not the 2% stuff.
Of course folks are talking about the full fat whole milk.
Drink it as fast as you can.
Texaco.
Big oil.
Why is Bob Hope presenting Texaco like it's a new museum that he's cutting the tape to be able to go to the grand opening of a museum?
The logo is already here.
Why are we revealing this?
It's already on the sign.
It's just this gas station.
That's the first thing he asks.
Bob, that's the first thing you ask when the aliens land?
Regular or unleaded.
He should have screamed.
I don't think that's the reaction you have.
I mean if he screamed it would have been so funny.
If it sucked him up I think that would have been so funny.
Regular or super unleaded.
He meant if he was like, regular or super unleaded.
They sucked him up and took off.
And then at the Christmas special that he's at right now, he's not there and he shows up like 30 minutes late with the aliens.
And they come onto the set, they got like costumes, alien costumes, and they're wearing Texaco gear.
Like wow, even the aliens use it.
I probably missed an opportunity here.
I want to say it one more time.
Regular or super unleaded.
He didn't even yell it.
He would need to scream this.
He's not, they can't hear him.
Wait, but they said it's flashing empty?
They need gas.
Regular or super unleaded.
They stopped in the galaxy to pick up a little bit of fuel.
Texaco history.
Texaco system 2000.
They run on gas.
Regular or super unleaded.
Texaco captures a golden era for women.
It's because the sign was so big.
A rich rich weaving of opulent texture.
An interlocking of elegance and style.
Of Rolex?
And the brilliant touch only a diamond can give.
At Seiko, great technology inspires great design.
Seiko setting the standard for the world, for the future.
Something about old commercials with the voiceover guy that had almost the bia voice.
They always talked like this.
The Seiko watch will finally get.
It was so low that it was almost unbelievable how low this person is talking in these old commercials.
Technology inspires great design.
Inspire is great.
I don't think humans can do this anymore.
Seiko setting the standard for the world, for the future.
I can't do it.
Now Seiko gives you the moon.
Oh, it's all the same guy.
Of the world's first analog quartz chronograph.
And tailors gray with dashes of gold tones.
To an elegant dress circle.
Seiko adds a date window.
And creates a bold alarm chronograph to sport everywhere.
At Seiko, great technology inspires great design.
Seiko setting the standard for the world, for the future.
I don't know.
Bro, that's a lot of fire near that tree.
To be a part of your holiday weekend.
Lots of motor royals talk protection and mileage.
I want proof.
New York taxis drove over a quarter million punishing miles with no oil related failures.
That's Havilland Supreme protection.
Not bad, but.
Proof, after a million miles of state trooper driving no oil related failures.
That's Havilland Supreme protection.
No kidding.
Proof, in fuel economy tests it delivered improved mileage.
I'm still skeptical.
Texaco Havilland Supreme.
They've got the proof.
Monday, it's an all new Little House movie.
A two hour Christmas special.
With the holiday spring tragedy when Laura's baby is kidnapped.
Why did you leave her?
Bless all the dear children, Monday.
Holy shit, what?
He seemed really annoyed there.
He got proven wrong.
Dude, that's not the problem.
Isn't that Werner Lutz?
We went to high school together.
By golly, you're right. I thought Werner was dead.
Texaco's super unleaded superstar power for more car power.
Hi, Bob doing yourself hope here.
And after the aliens, I'm a completely different man.
I was going to say something about this.
Oh, right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, so here's the interesting thing about this.
It doesn't matter how much gas is in your car or what kind of gas is in your car.
If you press like a quarter of a pound of pressure on your on your gas pedal,
you're going to go three miles per hour.
You could have zero gas in your tank.
I mean, like a sneeze of it.
Just enough to get into the intake, right?
And floor it.
And you'd go.
And you'd I mean, you'd go fucking 100 miles.
You'd go fast.
And then you mean you'd stall out eventually.
That's really bad for the engine.
You're right. I thought Werner.
I'm not saying to do that.
I'm just saying this doesn't make any sense.
He's not even pressing the gas.
Texaco's super unleaded superstar.
Is it implied that he's flooring it?
And his gas is proof.
There's no proof.
Power for more car power.
Hi, Bob doing yourself hope here for Havilland supreme motor oil.
Texaco's formula with its nine additives gives proven engine protection
for air rust and corrosion.
And Havilland's friction fighter reduces engine friction to help save gasoline in your car.
Next time you change oil,
get the motor oil that gives you proven engine protection.
And check this out.
He blows a fireball.
Save gasoline.
Havilland supreme.
What happened to the car?
Stay tuned for more of Bob Hope's Jolly Christmas Hour.
Right after this station break.
The NBA team.
Who's got the guts to grab Mr. T's gold and chain him to Murdock.
By taking downtown Tokyo away from Godzilla.
And on Reptide, Murray the powerful.
Murray the ruthless.
Murray the media star.
I think we created a monster.
And on Remington Steel, one of these masterful mystery writers has murder in mind for Laura and Steel.
What just happened?
When a neighborhood starts to die,
it seems there's nothing anyone can do to save it.
Did she just fly into him?
Riding in...
A wheelchair?
And they explode.
Why do they explode?
Why?
I want the context of what happened.
But that's not true.
With enough caring, a neighborhood can live.
Citibank knows it.
And Citibank knows it takes a lot of people
and a lot of hard work.
For over 15 years, we've helped restore
communities throughout the New York area.
We provide more money for more housing
than any other bank in New York.
We have a commitment to this city.
After all, it's our city too.
It's your Citibank.
Metro North. Drills for disaster.
Story at 11.
Oh, we're back to Bob Hope's.
Oh, home of holiday Christmas hour.
No, no we're not.
Bob, he's a pro.
I can't beat him.
He's driving on regular unleaded, but you've got
Texaco Super unleaded.
Whoa!
An identical turbo car
and can boost power.
These people are not in a race.
Are they? What is Bob doing here?
It does look like Trump.
Bob, he's a pro.
I can't do it.
That's Donald Trump right there.
That's Donald Trump.
Okay.
If you said Jerma, I'll give you a million dollars
if you tell me who this person is.
I'll give you a million dollars in cash
and a handful of briefcases.
Who is this guy on camera right now?
That is Donald Trump.
And I would bet my life on it.
I fixed the race.
He's driving on
regular unleaded fuel.
I have super unleaded.
By the way, aliens?
Super cool. They're super funny.
They're super sweet. I learned a lot from them.
Regular unleaded, but you've got Texaco
Super unleaded.
You know what's crazy? All the weird
commercials Donald Trump used to do,
I would not be surprised if
he was here just doing that.
Even against a pro
in an identical turbo car,
it can boost power, improving acceleration
up steep roads almost 12 percent.
I won, I won.
When you need more octane superstar power
gives you more car power.
Next time you get the Texaco Super.
Why does he have one of these
in his trunk? This is not a
gas station. This is implied that he carries
this around with him. He just has
a gas pump?
This is not a station.
I won, I won.
And then he goes
blows into the fireball. It's his
thing he does in these.
Behind the new Texaco star.
There's a new Texaco.
LaSalle Seiko.
Superb design.
Responding to the challenge of the
highest quartz technology.
LaSalle Seiko.
Thinness at times
almost two dimensional.
Form that reaches for perfection.
And now LaSalle Seiko
gold in the preeminent 14
karat timepiece of this decade.
LaSalle Seiko.
Among the world's great possessions.
I'm not a watch guy.
I feel like I'd be super aware of it all the
time. Like it would, it would
you know if I'm wearing a long sleeve it like pops
out and yeah. I don't know. I feel like
I'd be so aware of it. Oh yeah that's that.
I have that on. And let me
show it to you. I mean I'm not against
you know this is like oh are you against
jewelry or are you against accessories?
No, no not necessarily.
But like you know if you have like a regular watch
it's like oh this thing is a watch it tells time or
something right? But I don't know I feel like I would be
always under pressure to show people
that I'm wearing one of these watches.
If it's on it's almost like
you're wearing it and it's this big
gold beautiful how much does it cost? It's expensive
and it's beautiful and it's class
right? I feel like you don't I don't
know I feel like you would be constantly going
and then the cashier at the grocery
store is just like okay
that'll be um that'll be
$49. You know what I mean?
I feel like I'd be constantly under pressure.
I don't want to be like I don't want to be under pressure.
You eat smoke for 12
hours. What?
So hot you feel like you're working inside a
furnace. Yeah you get a
headache. Oh okay.
You want something strong.
Anisyn. Anisyn.
23% more medicine. I thought he was telling
us like this is a crazy fact
that you need to know. What a wild
fact. You like eat smoke
all day. That's what I thought it was. Inside
a furnace.
You eat smoke
for 12 hours. So
hot you feel like you're working inside a furnace.
Yeah you get a headache.
You want something strong.
Anisyn. Anisyn.
23% more medicine
than regular pain relievers. Anisyn's
I thought that was a snickers bar.
stops pain fast.
Headache's gone and no stomach
upset. That really
takes the heat off. Anisyn
more medicine.
Take a close look at a new small
car from today.
I'm going to give that commercial an A-.
This is an A- because it was super
to the point. It's just hey
headaches suck. And you know if
I'm working and I got a headache I got something
I need something. This is an A- for me.
Headache's gone and no stomach upset.
That really
takes the heat off. Anisyn
more medicine. That's not Bob Hope.
Take a close look at a new
small car. That's not Bob. If it was Bob Hope
he would have been saying
something along the lines of this.
The thing about it is headaches
are really really tough. But you know it's
not a headache and he steps out of the way and there's a
Texaco gas pump behind him.
Fill it up with super unleaded. Texaco
gas is cleaner. He would step out of the
way and it would not be a headache commercial anymore.
From today's Chevrolet
new Spectrum.
In Spectrum you discover both sporty performance
and everyday economy. The performance
comes from 5 speed overhead cam
drills that boast a test track time of
0-50 in 8.2 seconds.
Spectrum economy. Uh oh.
The performance comes from
5 speed overhead cam drills
that boast a test track time of
unleaded fuel only.
Not super unleaded
fuel. Uh oh.
0-50 in 8.2 seconds.
Spectrum's economy comes from
the highest gas mileage of any sedan in America.
Discover new Spectrum.
The sporty car of our everyday driving.
That's not how it works.
Play a game if you guys want
where we watch the first 5 seconds
and if the product's not there we have to guess what the product
will be. I like that. That's
fun too. Again, that's a lot of candles.
I've seen this one.
May they be the warmest ever.
We'll do that on the next one.
Hold on a second. Let me blind this
pilot for a few seconds.
Wait a minute.
The UFO is coming.
It's right here.
He made a pact with the aliens.
Did you see that?
He's signaling to the aliens.
Okay.
If we were playing the game
to pause after one second.
I would have said it was for cheese.
I would have said it was a cheese commercial.
But that's not what this is.
This is...
I was going to go all in
for a cheese commercial.
Or a cough drop, yep.
You bet your ass we're missing out on some
prime quality video
content because
you know for a fact
there's going to be at least a dozen
product tie-ins with Texaco on that special.
Sound of Music is amazing. I mean you're talking about one of the most
classic pieces of media ever
produced.
There's no penis on the wall.
I think that's it for this one.
We're going to move on to the next one.
This was a good one. That was quality.
What is on the wall?
There is currently nothing on the wall.
I promise. I would show it if there was.
Alright, so that's that one. Pretty cool.
That was 80s commercials.
I'm so sorry. I gotta
stop that. I'm trying to make a point
as to what people do to go back
because everyone was like, that joke was bad. But like it wasn't though.
Alright, so
This one
Do I want to do 80s? Okay, let's play
the game. Let's play the game
of
Should I do 2 seconds or 3 seconds?
Do 90s?
I mean, I'll do it. I'm going to do this
a lot. Just the whole time. Do a 90s
one? Alright, let me get a 90s one.
We'll do a 90s one. Alright, 90s.
This is 90s
commercials, volume 410.
Here we go. Oh, we're going to do it.
Right? This one's kind of cheating
because this is when I grew up.
This is when I was younger.
So, I'm going to know a lot of these probably.
We'll see. Let's play it. 2 seconds
or 3 seconds? 3? Okay.
Here we go.
What a show.
This program is
brought to you by Barks, the one
with bite. It's going to be Barks Root Beer.
I think we already know that.
I'm going to put
my bet on Barks Root Beer incoming.
Okay? You guys
making your bets here? Barks
Root Beer. Let's see.
What the hell was that? What happened?
Why did they just kick that guy?
Oh, it's temporary tattoos.
Dude, that was such a trope
in the 90s. The old lady
that's sitting there
leaning into the camera saying
no, no, no. Every gum commercial,
every
soda commercial, everything
that was geared towards the younger
audience, grandma was
telling you, you can't
have that. No, this is
for grandma. No, it's not.
No, it's not.
It's for me.
Barks Root Beer, the one with
bark 2s.
Okay, this is obviously for a CD player
or a, I got to get it right though.
Was that a tape? This is 90s.
Is that a tape player or a CD player?
When in the 90s though?
I'm going to say that's a CD player. I don't know
what company though, but let's see.
It's a CD player.
Okay, I swear
this is a real memory. I hope, I don't think
I'm making this up, but I feel like I
actually did this. These are the CD players
that didn't skip because
back in the day
when you had a CD player, it
was feeding you the music
in very real time, almost like a record
player. And if you moved
and I'm talking even touched it,
it would go,
and skip, skip, skip, skip, skip in your ears.
You couldn't touch it because it was reading it in real
time. They came out with this
technology where it was no
CD skipping. And what I imagined
it did is it like took
the audio, buffered it, and
then put it up to you, right? Like about
maybe like four or five seconds. And I remember
people, it was such a huge jump
in the music world
that I remember people would take those and be
like, hey yeah, look at this.
See? Put your, put the headphones
in, see you, you're not skipping, right?
Not skipping, and like they'd break
them because they were trying to prove a point. And I
feel like I did that to one of, one that I had.
Like I had this weird memory
of me doing that, being like, look, see?
Smack! Smack! And it not
skipping, and then the thing kind of sounded
like shit for the next like ten times I used
it, and I stopped using it. So so many people
were so obsessed with proving to
you that it would work
that they made it not work. Anyway, they had
little bars on them, and it was
loading, it was like a little loading bar.
It was like one, two, three, four, five. If you had
five bars of juice,
it was like you could, why are you saying F?
What happened? Well stop
hitting my screen, stop hitting my stream!
You gotta stop bumping the stream!
What the fuck are you doing? Relax, sit in your
chair normally, like
this, don't move! Oh, isn't Twitch
having a bunch of problems? Like
yeah, my, I got no drop
frames. Right when I start talking about
this, that's so stupid. Well, Twitch is having
problems, whatever, it's all good. I've heard about that.
Alright, let's keep going. Are we good?
Everybody good for me? Everybody, is it good
everybody good for me? Like everyone's like
waiting for me? Are you good for me to
begin? Are you good for me to start?
Does it skip? There it was,
see the bars? Nothing unleashes
it. Get out of
the phone? Get out of the phone?
Wait, hold on.
I gotta start this again.
Who is selling
the car to who?
It was
alright, whatever, neither.
Hold on.
He's doing,
Arnold is doing the thing,
the YouTuber thing,
where he goes to switch
the camera off to cut,
to do a different take. Watch
him.
What do you think of anyone who doesn't see this movie?
Big mistake.
But it's old. But look
at what he's doing. It's like he's saying
his line and then he's like, oh, let me have that one
turned out. Let me try it again. Think of anyone who
doesn't see this movie. Big mistake.
Everybody knows when you do that though. That's why you
gotta do it in post. There's no way
to like go, nope, you
can't move. Different people will know.
I think it's the biggest movie of the
summer.
Burger King and order a flame broiled whopper with
large fries and a medium drink. You get this last
action hero. Whoa, that's actually
sick. Like him, you can be large
and in charge. So see the movie and
collect all four cups. It's your way right
away. I love this place and I'm
going to see the movie.
Have you ever opened doors?
With the sound of your
voice. Carried your medical
history in your wallet.
Your wife's gonna be just fine.
So this is where we
attended a meeting.
Your bare feet.
Company that'll bring it to you.
AT&T. Wait.
Did the internet exist?
It'll bring it to you.
When in the 90s is this?
How early in the 90s?
This is showing very, very detailed
video conferencing. You couldn't
do that.
Look at this.
This is
a detailed video broadcasting
software. I don't think you could do
this.
Also, there's no way anyone could hear what he's saying.
He's just going off and just talking to himself.
Hold on. By the way, I've got
a few other ideas. Let me go over here and talk out
the window so nobody hears
what I'm saying.
He just skipped that guy.
He's calling it like
Omegle. He just skipped
him.
Your bare feet.
Company that'll bring it to you.
AT&T.
In this quiet neighborhood, there lives
a menace named Dennis.
Feels warm.
You need an ashtray.
This summer, watch out
for the kid who's causing all the
excitement.
What the fuck?
What?
In a classic comedy,
Dennis the Menace.
Rated PG.
I remember Dennis the Menace.
He was actively trying to kill
Mr. Wilson?
What?
In this quiet neighborhood,
there lives a menace named
Dennis.
Feels warm. You need an ashtray.
This summer.
But he's
he sees him do that.
This summer.
Like, hey, what are you doing with my aspirin?
Watch out for the kid
who's causing all the excitement.
What is happening?
What's
going on?
America's classic
kid in a classic comedy.
Dennis the Menace.
Rated PG. Starts Friday,
June 25th at a theater near you.
Running.
Where's the fun?
Introducing the fun way to run.
When he said YouTuber thumbnail face.
Rated classic excitement.
America's classic
kid in a classic comedy.
You can take these.
You could
take at least three or four of these
and they would be for different subjects.
Like, oh, he's talking about something
really like weird here in this
one. I mean, you have to take out the fact that you just
got flaming, like
whatever this is. Marshmallow
grenade
thrown at his head.
Excitement.
It's his third eye opening.
Holy shit.
Dude, the title of this video is
Nintendo Switch Price
Drop 2023
and have hands holding the switch up.
America's
classic kid in a classic comedy.
Dennis the Menace.
Rated PG.
Starts Friday, June 25th at a
theater near you.
Running. Where's the fun?
Introducing the fun way to run, jump
and condition your body. Exciting
new Exerlopers from Exerscience.
The new idea division of Nordic Track.
Exerlopers give you a more intense
workout than ordinary jogs with
extraordinary fun. Because unlike
running or jogging, Exerlopers patented
carbonite spring soles take the
shock out so your muscles do the work.
Not your joints. You'll jump
higher, jump faster, jump
safer. So put some fun in your run
with the all new Exerlopers. Because
for about the same price you'd pay to be
rolling on the ground, you could be jumping through
the air. Call our to- Okay, you know what it's
like to walk around with ice skates
on? They made that
feeling and encouraged it.
I feel like you stepped the wrong way
on one of these. You are
snapping your ankle. If they were
wider, maybe. I don't know.
They kind of look cool though.
I feel like I'd want to
They're kind of cool. I would just
run around and just bounce around
with them. I wouldn't use them to run.
These are too expensive?
Whoa! I thought it
was forty bucks. It's four
forty bucks. Four A-12s.
This is a hundred and sixty bucks.
I thought they were forty dollars.
A hundred and sixty bucks back in like the early
nineties. That's like
at least two
three hundred bucks at this point. Three four hundred?
Three hundred? Four hundred?
More than that? Like three fifty? Jesus.
I hope they worked.
Cool name.
You gotta show somebody Duncan.
Show somebody-
This was a good take, but it's very clear
that he has lost control when he lands.
And he's running into the people
that are also extras or in the
commercial.
He gets air here.
He's kind of like, oh shit
you're right here man.
They already showed somebody Duncan? No they didn't.
Jump and condition your body.
Exciting new Exerlopers from
Exerscience, the new idea division
of Nordic Track. Exerlopers give
you a more intense workout than ordinary
jogging with extra ordinary fun.
Because unlike running or jogging,
Exerlopers patented carbonite spring
soles take the shock out. So your
muscles do the work, not your joints.
You'll jump higher, jump faster,
jump safer. So put some
fun in your run with the all new
Exerlopers. Because for about the same price
you'd pay to be rolling on the ground, you could be
jumping through the air.
Call our toll free number now and we'll send you
your very own. Okay, if you
show up with these, you're like, alright, we're gonna
do blue shirts
versus red shirts. Okay, here we go.
If you wear those, it's just like a pick up basketball
game. Are you gonna get, are they gonna allow
you to wear those? Is it like, hey
bro, you gotta take those off. They're my shoes.
I didn't bring any other shoes.
These are the only things I have. You didn't bring any
other shoes? No.
Well, I guess we're gonna have to let you play.
Break them off? No, break them off.
These were $350
USD, 2023
upscaling. The, I actually
think, I wanna try these.
They actually kinda look like they would be fun.
Right away.
And with our 30 day trial period, you've got
nothing to lose.
Maybe not. I don't know.
You won't believe how it feels
to be Exerloping. Order now
and we'll include our electronic pedometer
absolutely free. They should have shown
somebody like him landing
that and then doing
ten back handsprings
right after it. Just one, two,
three, four, five,
six and then fade into this. That would have been
so much cooler. 1995
value. Order now.
You're in comedy
When you're thirsty, you need
a diet squirt. What the fuck was that? What's going on?
Because there's nothing like our refreshing
blend of citrus flavors.
Give your thirst
a diet squirt.
Alright, that was kinda, that was cool.
That was like, whatever.
I mean, it was, like all the
fountain is there and it's like
When you're thirsty,
you need a diet squirt.
It's horrible. Okay, hold on. Diet squirt.
Give your
thirst a diet squirt.
You are on the air.
You called the radio station? Sam Baldwin
isn't looking for anyone special.
Some kid calls a phone in radio show and
says that his dad needs a new wife.
And now 2,000 women want his number.
But someone special. What if this man is my destiny
and I never meet him? He's looking for him.
Didn't you see Fatal Attraction?
You wouldn't let me. Tom Hanks.
This is really fun. Meg Ryan.
Is this crazy? Sleepless in Seattle.
Think Cary Grant. Rated PG.
I'd like to play you something that I
recorded literally yesterday.
Those of you that have, this is
a great, great segue. So those of you that have been
on the channel for a long time, you know
that whenever
I get a lot of food in my throat, I get
the Tom Hanks voice. And let me tell you
what I recorded is
unbelievable. I caught
it super perfectly.
Super good. So the Tom Hanks
voice thing I'm talking about, yeah.
If you eat and you get food kind of stuck a little bit there,
like milk voice a little bit, for some reason
it makes me sound just like him.
So I recorded this. This was literally last night.
Then I won't sound like Tom Hanks anymore.
And when you get, when you finally get the
Tom Hanks voice, that's when you really
can shine as an actor.
And be a part of, I was in Forrest Gump
and I was
you know, I was Woody in Toy Story
remember? It's me, Woody,
and you buzz are gonna get us
in trouble with Andy. It's gone.
Fuck. There you go.
That lasted a very long time.
That lasted so long.
Holly said to me last night,
she's like, Dad, that was really good, but
what are you talking about? Buzz, you're
gonna get us in trouble with Andy.
Was, yeah, they don't
Andy's not like their
like dad. Andy doesn't even know
they exist. It was just filler,
filler, filler. I had to get it quick. It was
quick, quick, quick. I gotta get it quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Although that's the point though.
I couldn't do that right
now if I tried. No, you
can't. He's got a very distinct voice.
Special sneak preview Saturday night.
You're 37, supposedly.
And scandal.
Who is this lady supposed to be?
You know, all those things,
all those things that you hear about the Kennedys
eyes in it.
It was me.
But they don't explain who that lady is?
I am the person
who started the rumors about the Kennedys
and Marilyn Monroe.
It was me.
It's so
stupid.
Why is she evil?
VH1's new show that makes
Gotham a king where no
star is sacred. The men share
married, dated, or had sex with.
And scandal scores.
Watch Rumor Has It every Monday
through Thursday at 7 and 11
Eastern on VH1.
Jack, Bobby, Norma Jean,
I'm so sorry.
The first part and the end part
of that commercial don't
need to be there.
I guess it's funny.
Is it funny?
They could have just done the commercial
of the show, but they had to have
this old lady.
It was me. I spread those rumors.
I'm so sorry for what I've done.
The controversial new series
from Time Life Books had a few choice
words to share with us.
It was clear
that true crime digs deeper than
Somebody just dropped
like a big steel pot
down a flight of stairs with us.
It's just a long
hotel stairwell or something.
People who've read true crime,
the controversial new series from
Time Life Books had a few choice words
to share with us.
Watch out, watch out.
I'm making a video.
True crime digs deeper than the headline news.
Complete stories of criminals like Ted Bundy,
John Wayne Gacy, John Gotti,
and the men and women who brought them to justice.
All told with the kind of
responsible objective reporting
you've come to expect from Time Life.
Call now for your first book,
Unsolved Crimes, yours for only
$14.99. Use your credit
card and get this high decibel alarm
keychain free. Other books will
follow, yours to preview without
risk, like Serial Killers,
Most Wanted, and Mafia.
Get true crime and find out for
yourself what thousands already
know. Call
1-800-257-3100 to order
Unsolved Crimes for just $14.99.
Use your credit card and you'll also get this high decibel alarm
keychain free.
Open your code please. Take that thing out
slowly and open it.
Some kind of device. We have a possible
situation.
Not a situation.
Don't touch the button. Quiet please.
It's just a car
stereo. Pioneer car
stereos offer you a detachable face
for the... Why do you have a car
stereo in your pocket? Isn't that
the ultimate insecurity?
You see it's a detachable face for the
car stereo.
Why would you bring it through
the...
Open your code please. Take that thing out
slowly
and open it.
Some kind of device. We have a possible situation.
We've got some kind of device.
It's the JFK
lady?
No it's not.
7-11 Eastern on VH1
Jack, Bobby,
Norma Jean, I'm so
sorry.
No it's not.
It's not.
It's just
an old lady.
It's just an old lady.
Don't touch the button. Quiet please.
It's just a car stereo.
Wait, he's touching the buttons?
Don't touch the button. Dude, don't
do that. Like come on.
If you go through... You're going through security
and it's like
dee dee dee... Hold on a second there.
What's in your pocket there sir?
Oh well you see. We've got a device
and you start going... What?
No it's not.
Not a situation.
Don't touch the button. Quiet please.
He wasn't doing that.
Yes ma'am.
Not a situation.
That's his finger right here. This is somebody else's hand.
That's somebody else's hand touching
the buttons. The old lady sounds like
Lois.
Quiet please. It's just a car
stereo.
We've got some kind of device.
Not a situation.
Quiet please.
It's just a car stereo.
Pioneer car stereo.
It's all for you Adi.
I know we've been on this one for a little while
but this is the type of reaction that characters
in Hitman have to you.
This is like AI. Like you walked over
to an AI and all of a sudden it's like
they're going through their few routines
that they have.
Like this guy
just kind of bumped into
that guy. And this whole thing
unfolded. He got like a little
GTA. He got a little too close.
Or the AI just all of a sudden now
there's something that needs to be taken care of now.
Yes ma'am. Not a situation.
Don't touch the buttons. Quiet please.
It's just a car
stereo.
Pioneer car stereos offer you a detachable
face for the ultimate in security.
You see it's a detachable
face for the car stereo.
I have no idea what you just said.
Hey, you know what it takes to get
ahead. Performance.
You know what it takes to stay
on track. Control.
You know what it takes
to lead the way.
So do we. The Grand Am
Sport Coupe. V6
Performance. The control
of anti-lock brakes.
Excitement.
The only reason you would have a drive like this
in these commercials is if you thought you were going to shit
your pants and you had to make it to a bathroom
as soon as possible. They saw
you flying around these little roads.
Look at that
back. Toastitos restaurant
style tortilla chips.
You've never had it this good.
It's too tall.
This is the taste
that takes you there.
It's cool that they did
this commercial, but you know I don't appreciate the
multi-boxing.
This is the
taste that takes you there.
A plus.
That was an A plus.
That was to the point.
That was very much just to the point.
It was just, hey, Tabasco is fucking awesome.
When that first little drop comes out
it's like, this is cool.
It's like, yeah. Tabasco
is gross?
That's just
no. I don't
trust anybody that says that
Tabasco is gross. If you say
that Tabasco is not your favorite.
You say that Tabasco is something you don't choose.
I don't prefer Tabasco, but
saying Tabasco is gross.
I don't trust you. Mods, can we get a poll
real quick? Is Tabasco
gross? And remember, gross
does not mean I don't really like
it. Gross means like you taste it and you're like
ugh. Just regular, just Tabasco.
The default Tabasco. Tabasco on eggs
is amazing. Yes it is. It's also amazing
on pizza. Is it gross?
If this is more than 10 to 20 percent, then that's
no way. I want to do one more thing
after this before we keep going.
20 percent so far.
Gross? Why do you think it's gross?
Enjoy your vinegar water.
Don't ever have salad dressing ever again for the rest of your life.
Alright, alright, close that
poll. 21 percent said it was gross.
I have a new poll I'd like to run.
Because this is going to determine how I feel.
Okay. So remember, is it gross?
Is Sriracha
gross? New poll. Yes or no?
Is Sriracha gross?
Let's see. I'm curious.
I want to see how this lines up.
It's almost the exact same.
It's actually almost identical.
Do 20 percent of you just
don't like, you just hate hot sauce?
It's the exact same.
I think that 20 percent of you just don't
like hot stuff. So
it's good. Alright. I probably should
have worded this better. If you like
hot sauce, it's
whatever. I got what I wanted out of
this. I prefer Tabasco.
You know what I mean? You know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying? I prefer Tabasco.
You know what I mean? No, we're not doing a
no. No new poll. No new poll.
I like Cholula. Yeah.
But, very
important thing about Cholula. See, to
me, Cholula is
good on different
foods. I prefer Cholula
in a taco. I prefer
Cholula in, you know,
with like avocado and
not, I can't say which
one's better because I prefer
Cholula on very specific
foods, right? Tapatio is also
great. I would put it in the same category as Cholula.
Yeah, they're not exactly the same
kind of sauce, but I actually
really don't like Sriracha. I don't,
I don't know. I don't like it. I don't think
it's gross. I just don't
really like it.
I don't vacation
in the South of- What is it?
This is a pretty, this is going to be a hard one. I'm going to
say coffee. Either coffee
or, I'm going to say life insurance.
A vacation planner.
I'm going to say it's, it's, it's
consumable. It's a coffee. It's a beverage.
An airline. That's a good one.
Insurance?
Okay. Okay. Let's see who's right.
Simple, I go
easy.
I go Greyhound. This
summer, go Greyhound anywhere, anytime
for $149 or less.
No restrictions or advance purchase.
I go simple, easy.
Greyhound bus.
And leave the driving to us.
This program is brought to you by
Kodak Gold Film.
Okay, what's this one?
For your brand new baby, a
brand new film.
Ah, the Kodak Gold.
Moncruise?
Introducing Kodak Gold Ultra
400. Why is this so chaotic?
A new film so versatile, it can catch rich,
accurate colors in almost any light.
Day
and night.
New Kodak Gold Ultra 400.
Would you trust your moment to anything less?
Holy shit!
This one, I can't even process this one.
All I know is I thought that was Tom Cruise.
Introducing Kodak Gold
Ultra 400.
A new film so versatile.
Dad, you did it wrong.
You don't blblblbl. After you take the picture
you blblblbl. Then you take the
photo. What a fucking amateur move that
was, huh?
Kodak Gold Ultra 400.
A new film so versatile, it can catch rich,
accurate colors in almost any light.
Day
and night.
New Kodak Gold Ultra 400.
Would you trust your moment to anything
less?
Why are you giving baby photography advice
to a person
like 20 years ago?
If you found a way to save America millions of
dollars a year, how would you tell
them? Introducing
1-800-Collect. Now
America's least expensive way to call
someone collect.
I thought it was going to be
how do we save?
To make the long distance charges easier for your friends and
family to accept.
I thought they were talking about
the government budget or something.
It's a number that
belongs to everyone. Everywhere
in the US.
Every time they need to make a
collect call.
1-800-Collect.
How does this sound?
Now you can have all the
crisp, refreshing taste of a
great beer without all the alcohol.
Miller Sharps.
Great beer taste
anytime.
Success in life is the result of
preparation and having the right tools.
To become the person you've always
wanted to be, select Nordic
Flex Gold. You provide the effort
and Nordic Flex Gold provides the
means to your personal success.
You want to develop the poise,
confidence, and energy that come from
a strong toned body.
Just like these people, you can have
that body in just 12 weeks with
Nordic Flex Gold. Some people
spend a lifetime wishing for a great body.
Now with Nordic Flex Gold, you
can unlock your potential in as little
as 12 weeks.
The only thing that happened here was the guy shaved his chest.
You can have that body
in just 12 weeks with Nordic Flex Gold.
Some people spend a
lifetime wishing for a great body.
Now with Nordic Flex Gold, you can unlock
your potential in as little as 12 weeks.
Nordic Flex Gold features
linear motion and patented
isokinetic resistance, providing results
fast, up to 70% faster
than with rubber band machines or even
free weights. Now is
the time to act. Great muscle
tone, three times faster fat
loss, increased energy, as well
as poise and confidence can all be
yours in just 12 weeks with Nordic
Flex Gold. To order
or for more information, call now.
Look at my big fat
gun. He got
gun checked. He really did.
He got gun checked.
Everybody now.
You know what's so funny though?
I know I've been pausing a lot today,
but this is ridiculous.
You have to try
to do this. This like hurts.
Nobody actually
looks like that. Just sitting around.
They really don't. You have
to like, you have to like,
ah, that hurts.
I want to try it.
Is this weird? Is this
weird what I'm doing here?
Is this weird? This is weird.
This is kind of weird. I'll do it with the shirt on.
No, never mind.
This lady.
Just the, you know, the sunglasses
down like, I don't know
about what I see over there.
I want to like slow it down.
God damn it. It's so funny.
We need to make this slower. It's almost like he's
doing it on purpose.
How does he know what she is
looking at here? He does
it before he even looks down, right?
It's like, how did he know?
Why?
Why would you just
sit there just looking at
a group of people doing like
hey, look at how fat I am.
I'm reading too far into it.
It's doing it for me.
I don't know. It's fucking weird.
This guy actually like, he's
like, he's bent.
He's sucking it in.
He's doing it for you. What are
you talking about?
We're moving on.
It's a diaper commercial.
We're just gonna move on.
I can't get over that guy.
He's stuck.
He's stuck up here.
I can't get him out.
What the?
Oh, it's a joke.
It even slices and dices, makes thousands of
julienne fries. But wait, you can
play it too. This free Sonic 2
is a $54.99 value. You get two
Sonics for the price of one. Sonic 2 fits
easily into any tackle box. Made from a
space age polymer plastic for years of family
fun. And pets love it too. Buy the Sega
Genesis that comes with Sonic 1 and get
Sonic 2 free. Act now. Weiner dog
sweater sold separately. That was cute.
That was cute. I liked that one.
Three episodes for $4.95 including
the first episode ever aired.
Where is your bathroom?
Next to my bedroom.
Enjoy Cheers anytime you like.
I'm thinking about proposing.
Three episodes?
Excuse me, fella. I left a package in your mailbox
that belongs next door. That's the one.
Thanks.
Three episodes?
Keeping everybody?
Don't say adios to the good people at Cheers.
Keep the laughs coming with your Cheers video
cassettes. Deliver it right to your door
by five million women in uniform.
Use your credit card.
It's because it's a VHS
guys.
VHS's were at maximum
they were what? 90 minutes?
Yeah. Cause there was two
recording versions of VHS.
You could do 60
or 120 or 60 or 90, right?
What was the difference?
Was it the size of the
tape or something?
It was 120 max.
It was a lower resolution on 90.
It was the quality difference.
So weird. Hearing this now
this is so strange to see this.
Three episodes.
And guess what? Back
I know a lot of people might not be used to this
it used to take sometimes
two plus months
for you to get something that you ordered.
Like from one of these
hotline numbers. Sometimes it would take months.
Two or three months. Which is crazy.
Wow.
Read that fine print.
And call now for your first three episodes.
Cheers video cassette for
$4.95. Call.
Subscription is subject to review.
Sales tax added with subscription.
Wait, hold on.
Use your credit card and call.
Future three
episode videos sent every four to six weeks
and are $19.95
each.
Wait a minute. So it's $5 plus shipping
they give you three episodes
and then every two
months they send you three more
episodes but now it's $20.
How many episodes are in Cheers?
Can somebody look this up really quick? I guess I could right here.
The whole series. There are hundreds of them.
There's like 200.
There are 273 episodes
of Cheers. Oh my god.
Hold on.
$20
for three episodes.
We need some math here.
So you'd get 91
tapes. It would cost
$2,000.
$2,000 for the whole
thing. And how long would it
take for you to get it? Like over
the course of like seven years?
It would take
years. They probably wouldn't
even be in circulation anymore by the time you got the
last episode. Weirdly enough.
This is very weirdly enough.
By the time that you are on
episode 200 or so,
DVDs I think have come out
by now. So you don't need this
subscription anymore. What were they thinking?
Maybe they thought that VHS
was just, this is it. It's VHS's.
That's it. You would need an
entire room for your Cheers VHS
collection. Yeah, it would be almost a hundred tapes.
And I think that would be kind of weird.
I felt like if I went over somebody's house
and they had a wall
just a huge bookcase
with a hundred tapes on it,
all of it was Cheers, you would
walk into that room and go, oh, nice, I got a
bookshelf. I wonder, what do you got? The Great Gatsby
on there? Oh, whatever. Every
single thing here is a Cheers VHS tape.
Every single thing on the shelf.
Everything. All right. I mean, that's
I wonder what these are worth now.
It's almost $4,000 today.
Wow. And right now you could probably go
watch Cheers on a ton of different
services and not have to spend like
five grand. You could probably just go watch it
right now. Even if you bought the whole thing
from like iTunes, it probably wouldn't cost
you even close to what, like
a couple hundred bucks total, maybe
if you bought every single episode
on like iTunes. But you don't understand, you're
saving on the first one.
$4.95 is a steal.
It would take ten and a half
years. Now, for your first three
episodes, Cheers Video Cassette for $4.95.
Call now.
This is the number one
eight hundred crook's least expensive way to call
someone collected.
We need to talk about the first one that we just saw.
That's perfect.
Okay.
Yes. I'm so happy
right now. Forget everything.
Everybody freeze. Don't move.
Nobody move. This is really important.
I don't want anyone to move.
Freeze. Okay.
I'm telling you right now, it's
impossible not to be, not to enjoy this
picture.
I genuinely don't think
you could not enjoy
the photo you're about to see. Do you know what I'm saying?
Do you see what I'm
saying? You can't
not enjoy this
in some fashion. Even if you don't think it's funny,
like this is an enjoyable image to me.
It kind of is.
And the best part is you
blurred, you blurred the
price. Because what is that
price? What?
It's cheaper now by how much?
What? I can't see through that blur.
I wonder what percentage
point is going down. Oh my
god. And yeah, it's just question
marks. God, the internet.
The internet is like so
what a fucking insane place.
What a wild place this
really is. There's so much funny
things to see. So many crazy
things to look at.
This is insane. The internet is a
cool place. You should be careful.
Careful. Make it the stream
thumbnail? Okay, grandpa.
Should I do one too?
No, this is no dick. But this is me
reacting
to the video of the
person reacting to the price cut.
Okay. Here we go. Ready?
So I'm watching a video.
Was that good? That was pretty good, right?
Go on to the switch screen. No.
All right. We got to break down
these last ones we just saw. These are important.
These are very important.
The last one was weird because
it was just three, it was what? Three
ladies just chugging
iced tea?
Was it a contest? I don't know.
All right. But here's the next part, right?
We have
What is this a commercial for? He's
blowing his breath in this other guy's
face. Is this for
gum? Mint?
You think it's gum? What if it's for like
a steak and cheese
or something? Or like a sandwich or something? Yeah.
I actually don't know. I don't know if it's going to be
mints. This is a tricky one.
I actually really don't know what this could be.
It's probably for mints, right?
There's no way they would do an ad where he blows
gross hamburger meat breath in this guy's face,
right? I don't think so.
I get a whiff of this. What? What?
Oh, that's very nice.
It's like a
petunia.
Breath savers with its cool minty core
gives you the ultimate fresh breath.
Breath savers. It's not going to be hamburger.
We're here asking kids how clear stick from clear cells
is working to prevent their pimples.
Look at this face. Yeah, it's the stuff
that feels like it gets under your skin to help stop pimples
before they stop. Clear cell clear stick and clear
stick. Those things were intense though.
You gotta just use it.
Do you find that life just takes
your breath away?
You better get on track.
Get on track with NordicTrack, the world's best
aerobic exerciser.
NordicTrack strengthens your heart and lungs,
increases your energy, and gets you in shape
for life's challenges in only 20 minutes,
three times a week.
Does daily stress sometimes get to be too much?
Then get on track with
NordicTrack. Its patented flywheel
most accurately simulates
cross-country skiing for a smooth
total body workout that's non-join
and easy on your joints.
Are you finding it harder and harder to make ends meet?
Your blood pressure is still too high.
You need to lose some weight.
You better get on track.
Get on track with NordicTrack.
Research shows NordicTrack burns more calories
and fat than ordinary exercisers
and helps control your...
Is it NPC walking?
NordicTrack strengthens
your heart and lungs,
increases your energy, and gets you in shape
for life's challenges in only 20 minutes,
three times a week.
Does daily stress sometimes get to be too much?
Then get on track with NordicTrack.
Its patented flywheel most accurately simulates
cross-country skiing for a smooth
total body workout that's non-join
and easy on your joints.
Are you finding it harder to make ends meet?
Stressful job. Stressful.
The doctor then tells this guy
you need to lose weight
to reduce your blood pressure.
It's not the stressful job that might be doing this.
You need to lose some weight. That's what's wrong.
Get on track with
total body workout that's non-jarring
and easy on your joints.
Are you finding it harder to make ends meet?
Sometimes get to be too much.
Then get on track with Nordic Track.
It's patented flywheel
most accurately simulates cross-country skiing
for a smooth total body workout
that's non-jarring and easy on your joints.
Are you finding it harder to make ends meet?
Still, your blood pressure's still too high.
You need to lose some weight.
You better get on track.
Get on track with Nordic Track.
Research...
This motherfucker has a referral code.
That's what's going on.
Nordic Track burns more calories and fat
than ordinary exercisers
and helps control your cholesterol and blood pressure
to keep your heart healthy.
To get on track, call for a free video at Rochure.
Meet your fitness goals at home with Nordic Track.
Nobody looks cool doing any of this though.
Just exercise however you want.
That probably would do alright.
This summer,
guess who's coming to dinner?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Son-in-law.
PG-13.
Review Sunday, June 20th.
Favorite for showtimes.
That's a good trailer for the movie
because, like, that's...
Oh, whatever.
This father's day, give him the
sensor, best a dad can get.
Kid buying that?
Respect.
Now the active ingredient has a higher concentration
of what keeps you drier. Secret's still pH balanced.
Just works harder.
Hangs in there, like you.
Strong enough for a man.
Now keeps a woman even drier.
Jimmy Hendrix.
Make music.
It's the whole history of rock in one collection.
He's dominated
late 90's.
We get 21 classic rock hits from
1968 on your choice of
compact disc or cassette for the special price
of $9.99. Here's how to order.
To order call
1-800-258-9800 or
$9.99.
That's cool. That'd be awesome.
Back before, you know, oh I'm just gonna go to YouTube and type this in or I'm gonna go to Spotify.
This was this was this was sick.
You got everything you needed. Everything.
All the big singles. All the big hits.
This was cool. A-.
$9.99 for one cassette or one CD
plus $3.50 shipping and handling 2.
Classic Rock 68. Fuel box
$18.80. Department Q6
out of...
Alexandria, Virginia.
What is this?
Oh, it's Comedy Central.
Alright, where do we go from here?
Do you guys want 80s? More 90s?
I do have a couple of infomercials.
What do you guys think?
This one is a combo.
This one's Christmas commercials from the 80s and 90s.
This is like a combo.
This one's very long, but we can skip through it.
Alright, let's see what we got.
Queue it up.
Alright, here we go. This is a combo.
This, by the way, again, this is mostly
Christmas commercials.
This is mostly by the
kind of 4-3
thing they got going here.
Alright, let's see.
The Christmas ornaments of Hallmark.
Hallmark ornaments
aren't ordinary decorations.
They're special little presents.
For your family,
your friend, for yourself.
Keepsakes that bring back
warm memories of wonderful people
and wonderful times.
You'll find them only at Hallmark,
and there's more to Christmas than ever before.
That was cute.
Alright.
The young and the restless
will continue.
What are they recording?
What? The fuck?
Why were they driving?
Towards a picnic?
What?
To save a town in trouble.
They're driving towards the
people.
Why are you driving towards a picnic, then?
Why are you not going to the hospital?
One other thing, I know pause, Andy.
Another thing that's important to remember, though,
is a lot of these time slots
were, like,
seven seconds long.
How do you put a movie
trailer in, like,
four and a half seconds?
You can't.
This is C.B.S.
C.B.S.
C.B.S., C.B.S.
Leaving the
I want to see that again.
Wait, what do you mean?
Oh hi, just keeping up with the Christmas rush here at the 50 off store.
Now it's that time of year again when everybody's trying to buy nice and save big on fine clothing
for the family, gift items, and toys. And at the 50 off store, they're saving 50% off everything
in the store every day. Well you know how we do that. We mark each item with the price you'd pay
in other stores, and when you check out, we total your purchase using those prices. Then with the
push of a button, we cut that total right in half. Guys, but they say the price you would pay in
other stores. Doesn't that mean that they're not marking it up?
Even Santa loves the savings and you will too. The 50 off store, where your money buys twice
as much for Christmas. This is ridiculous. This is ridiculous. KDBC TV, Channel 4, El Paso.
That's crazy. I don't know what to say. 50% off store. Your dreams of instant wealth may come
true at American Family next month. Ten million dollars, all yours. Find out on American Family's
Get Rich Night, January 27th. Watch TV for your numbers when I announce the winning numbers for
not just one, but seven big prizes. You get seven chances to win big. So be sure to enter
America's only sweepstakes with my picture. It could make you super rich. Ten million dollars
rich. Don't miss out. Enter today. Butterball made Thanksgiving delicious. So for the holidays,
enjoy another deep-basted butterball turkey. Every slice is juicy. It's very juicy. It's a
butterball. Fresh or frozen, it's been the perfect holiday recipe for over 30 years.
This holiday, save an arm and a leg with Pam. Pam no-stick cooking spray makes baking a whole
lot easier. Pam, because how you cook is as important as what you cook. That's terrifying.
What's this? Bunny slippers? Of all the last-minute gifts you can buy,
one's appreciated more than all the rest. Wow. McDonald's gift certificates.
It's not at all, actually. No, it's not. A gift certificate gift card to McDonald's for Christmas
is like, that's cool. That's all right. But like, I mean, the slippers were kind of cool.
They were coupons. Jeremy, you're the McDonald's guy. Yeah, but I mean, it actually is kind of
cool if you think about it. But I don't know. I'd rather have the slippers. You're a walking
McDonald's ad. It doesn't mean I'm going to buy McDonald's coupons for somebody for Christmas.
Maybe like a stocking stuffer. Okay, hold on. This is important. I would not wrap this
in a big box. That's my issue here. This was wrapped in a big box.
Making a whole lot easier. Pam, because how you cook is as important as what you cook.
Hold on here. What's this? Bunny slippers? Of all the last-minute gifts you can buy,
ones appreciated more than all the rest. That came out of a big box. Cards always go
on the tree. That's right. Or in the stocking. That's right. You don't wrap in a big box a
gift card. McDonald's gift certificates. That's my issue. On the tree? That's cute. Like, oh,
whoa, there it is. Yeah, that's cute. The cold that pains you most at night isn't yours. It's
your child's. Introducing children's Nyquil with no aspirin, no alcohol. It's the nighttime
sniffling, sneezing, stuffy head, coughing so your child can rest medicine.
What was that? Night light will return right after this.
This tastes awful. Well, at least the videos are pretty good.
Are you going to bring me my lemon? Well, at least the video-
I cannot fucking believe. I cannot fucking believe that the Xbox Series S is getting a
price decrease. This is in no way- Those are pretty good.
Are you going to bring me my lemon or do I have to squeeze it from my hat?
From riches, to rags, to romance, to Goldie Hawn, to Russell, Overboard,
Radio PG. Merry Christmas from MGM. It's a Radio Shack Merry Christmas.
Wait, mom, everybody wants to say goodbye. My family loves this cordless phone from Radio Shack.
I got it on sale for just $69.95. I saved $30. It's really convenient. No cord in the way,
and you can dial out or answer from anywhere in the house. Even redial a last number call with
one touch. Merry Christmas, mom. Oh, and thanks for the tie.
The ET-395 cordless phone- Really wanted a cordless coupon.
Sale price for Christmas only at Radio Shack. You better next Christmas, ma.
Intelligence has identified a substantial buildup of hostile forces right here in our own backyard,
and I'm giving you the green light to clean them out. Gentlemen, you're the man.
You used a light gun? It's a Radio Shack at Radio Shack.
I saved $60 on this VHS remote-controlled VCR. These two-way bass reflex speakers were half
price at Radio Shack. This dual-powered calculator with memory was only $8.88,
and I saved $30 on a cordless phone for the family. Harry, I'm home.
Just finished our Christmas shopping at Radio Shack.
The Christmas electronics sale only at Radio Shack.
This is Bobby the Brain Heenan, and if you people out there have any brains, which I doubt you do,
you'll watch All American Wrestling on the USA Network, the best in professional wrestling
with the brain. That kind of reminded me of like a lot of sponsored deliverables.
It's like, Bobby, Bobby, we got to get you talking about the, you know, the network we're on and
we're going to go and it's going to be one take. It's just like, here we are,
this is what we're doing. All right, get me out of here. Bobby the Brain Heenan. I remember all
those guys. Mom, man, let's go. It's definitely for a video game and it's not going to look
anything like this. Harold, Harold, can we talk? Harold and I got a beautiful sale at $1.99 a month.
You know what that means? That means with a normal down payment, I've got a 21 foot hourglass fishing
boat. You guys want to go fishing. If you guys want a cabin cruiser, look at this cabin cruiser.
That's a Chris Craft cabin cruiser. There's the phone number, 432-9000. Whether you want a Chris
Craft cabin cruiser or the hourglass fishing boat, $1.99 a month is the sale, and we take trades.
We're open every day, seven days for your shopping convenience. It's Harold's Marine in Escondido.
I mean, that was, I like that one. That was, hold on, I'm getting overstimulated. Why was that,
like, why was that guy playing laser tag in a prison, a maximum security prison complex against
a bunch of like 13 year olds? That was what it was implying, that they're at this maximum security
prison. You'll watch all American wrestling. Where is this? This is, okay, this is not a prison.
He's late for the game and he's walking, now he's in the arena.
Scary guy prisoner in a maximum security cage.
Mom, man, let's go.
So they fight against, like, prisoners? How come some of them get cars?
The cars has an incredible advantage. Yeah, I've played laser tag before, but
you don't get to have a car. Oh, it's because the commercial cuts off, okay.
Harold, Harold, can we talk? Harold and I got a beautiful sale at $1.99 a month. You know what
that means? That means we're at a normal down payment. I've got a 21 foot arrow. You guys want
to go fishing. If you guys want a cabin cruiser, look at this cabin cruiser. That's a Chris Craft
cabin cruiser. There's the phone number, four three two nine thousand. I love this one. Whether
you want a Chris Craft cabin cruiser or the Hourglass fishing boat, $1.99 a month is the sale
and we take trades. We're open every day, seven days for your shopping convenience.
It's Harold's Marine in Escondido. That was a great one. Steve Martin and John Candy just met.
The next 72 hours. Stick with me. Do you feel this vehicle is safe for highway traffic? Yes,
I do. Steve Martin, where's your other hand? John Candy, between two pillows, planes, trains,
and automobiles. Those aren't pillows. Now playing at a theater near you. Radio Shack sale price
Tandy 1000 TX brings the gift of a true high speed business computer to your home affordably.
PC compatible, easy to use. Hold on, go back, go back, go back. Keep a budget. She didn't know
it was a computer until she took the bow off. Radio Shack sale price Tandy 1000 TX brings the
gift of a true high speed business computer to your home affordably. PC compatible, easy to use
with seven ready to run programs. Keep a budget. Write term papers. Even create graphics or learn
music. Save $250 on the high speed Tandy 1000 TX color monitor included. Only 1249 Tandy computers
because there is no better gift value only at Radio Shack. That's not that bad. Two,
three grand. It's a Radio Shack. Computers were not normal. Kevin is ready for a radio
control car this year. I can see him now as his Radio Shack off-road wild chap takes to the hills
or maybe the Malibu four by four off-roader. It's got both two or four wheel drive or I could get
him that Radio Shack turbo racer. It sure kicks up the dirt. Little Kevin would really like that.
Remote radio controlled toys 59.95. That was a cute one. That was like the the old guy likes
the toy more than the kid. That's a cute one. I like that one. You're quiet. Well I want you guys
to be able to hear. We gotta get these all in full stereo sound. Only at Radio Shack. Mr. Magoo is
back on Broadway and Ebenezer Scrooge lives again. Was the night before Christmas all through the
Christmas spirits teach Scrooge the spirit of Christmas.
It's Mr. Magoo's Christmas carol. Sunday at 11 10.
On my way to a very classy tv awards dinner. Yeah I know they have a new one every year
but this one's at the private home for legendary mcs of groovy movies. That's right the flam award.
That's nothing to sneeze at. Yeah they give it out each year to the highest bidder. I've even got my
acceptance speech ready. I stole a few lines from Joe Biden but heck I don't think he'll mind.
Whoops gotta go. Did you just say what did he say? Legendary mcs of groovy movies. That's right the
flam award. That's nothing to sneeze at. Yeah they give it out each year to the highest bidder. I've
even got my acceptance speech ready. I stole a few lines from Joe Biden but heck I don't think he'll
mind. Whoops gotta go. Commander USA's groovy movies. Today at two on USA. An exquisite fragrance
for a man here. You'll love it. He'll hate it. He'll hate it. He'll hate it. It's perfumey. This
Christmas give him what he really wants. Clean fresh old spice. America's favorites with the
classic masculine scent men love. Why would you want to drink this? Is it a drink? I love it. You
love it? I love it. I love it. And I love you. This Christmas give him old spice and if he likes
the scent of leather. Oh it's a cologne. I thought it was a coffee drink or something. Make your
Christmas. Each selection of fragrances and this week purchase any featured men's or women's
fragrance for $15 or more and receive a free gift that's perfect for the holidays. It's a Knott's
Berry Farm gift box. Great idea for the family or a great gift for someone special.
When you're holiday shopping for the people you love, Grossmont Center has the gifts you'll love
to give at the stores where you love to shop. This Christmas is something comfy and fun from
what's up. We've got bear feet, pig feet, goofy feet, trendy feet, married feet, family feet,
just part of the excitement this Christmas at what's up contemporary paper and gift wear.
The perfect gifts are waiting for you at 140 specialty shops and four major department stores
at Grossmont Center. The stop motion. Hey cookie more pecani sauce. This ain't paste pecani sauce.
What's the difference? Cookie paste pecani sauce is made in San Antonio with fresh vegetables and
spices by people who know what the pecani sauce is supposed to taste like. This stuff's made in
New York City. New York City. Get a rope. Pick up the original pecani sauce. Pick up the pace.
They're gonna kill this guy. It's Santa's. Wait, I remember this commercial. New York City. I don't
remember them killing him because he didn't bring, by the way, why do they have jars of salsa?
They're like cowboys out in the wilderness. Pick up the pace.
Trendy feet are waiting for you at 140 specialty shops and four major department stores at Grossmont
Center. You wouldn't have this. Hey cookie more pecani sauce. This ain't paste pecani sauce.
What's the difference? Cookie. Yeah, but even he doesn't care.
Yeah, why are you so offended about this different brand? The guy that handed it to you goes,
yeah, I mean, whatever. Like, I don't care about this that much. This is, I don't like this brand,
but this is what we have. Paste pecani sauce is made in San Antonio with fresh vegetables and
spices by people who know what the pecani sauce is supposed to taste like. This stuff's made in
New York City. New York City. By the way, I want to make a very clear point here.
This stuff's made in New York City. New York. Not a single one of these motherfuckers is helping.
He's doing everything. Not a single one of them with a ladle chopping any onions. No,
not a single helper. This guy's cooking all the food and they're, this is some extraordinary
bullshit. Get a rope. Pick up the original pecani sauce. Pick up the paste.
A Christmas secret is finally revealed. From the creator of the Wizard of Oz,
a one hour special. We did just have like a hot sauce argument in here, didn't we?
So, I mean. Adventures of Santa Claus, Saturday at eight.
Well, the people at Skaggs have done it again. The Christmas section is totally well stocked.
It's got everything for your Christmas needs. Wrapping paper, Christmas trees, decorations,
lights. In fact, the works. Which is why everyone's shopping here, basically.
Because they know this is the place. Yeah, excuse me.
Gee Santa, I guess you're in a hurry to pick up Skaggs brand eggs. Just 39 cents a dozen. Go
ahead. Put all your eggs in one basket and you'll need your sleigh to hold these delicious shank
hams for all the boys and girls. Just 98 cents a pound. Well, here's Barbie. That's right. I
think I got you one when you were a kid. I thought it was a mistake, but no, you wanted Barbie. Your
mother said. That's right. Well, the people at Skaggs have done it again. The Christmas section
is totally well stocked. It's got everything for your Christmas needs. Wrapping paper, Christmas
trees, decorations, lights. In fact, the works. Which is why everyone's shopping here, basically.
Because they know this is the place. Yeah, excuse me. Gee Santa, I guess you're in a hurry to pick
up Skaggs brand eggs. Just 39 cents a dozen. Go ahead. Put all your eggs in one basket and
you'll need your sleigh to hold these delicious shank hams for all the boys and girls. Just 98
cents a pound. Well, here's Barbie. That's right. I think I got you one when you were a kid. I thought
it was a mistake, but no, you wanted Barbie. Your mother said. That's right. All the blessings of
this joyous holiday season are wished for you and yours by David Chan and Georgie of El Paso's one
and only moon garden located at 3125 Litrovino. TV for El Paso. This is Katie BC. My goodness.
As the gingerbread mama. Oh, mama, I've been out Christmas shopping, says the gingerbread man.
Well, I don't see your Christmas shopping bags as the gingerbread mama suspiciously.
And you're a little peppermint schnapps. No, mama, no, that's the smell of candy cane.
I don't believe you. Well, then I'll just have to bite your head off.
If you could fast forward to the future. Did the adults make these? This looks a little scuffed.
Did the adults do this? That's the smell of candy cane. I don't believe you.
These people are shit faced. Well, then I'll just have to bite your head off.
If you could fast forward to the future, you'd see the cordless dustbuster plus
power brush make vacuuming quicker and easier than the big back day after day,
week after week, child after child. So this holiday, give a present with a future from
Black and Decker. I want a million. You wouldn't tell the kid to stop.
If you could fast forward to the future, you'd see the cordless dustbuster plus
power brush make vacuuming quicker and easier than the big back day after day.
He's dumping all the cereal. Child after child. So this holiday,
give a present with a future from Black and Decker.
I want a million dollars in Publishers Clearinghouse. We want even bigger.
Ten million dollars. The biggest Publishers Clearinghouse sweepstakes ever.
Ten million dollars could be yours if you hurry. We're announcing more winning numbers,
more prizes than ever before right on TV. One entry now is good for five giant prizes,
even ten million dollars January 31st. You can win ten million dollars too.
Just look for this house and enter the Publishers Clearinghouse sweepstakes.
Come on, send it in. How did this even work? I don't get it.
Alan Funt and an all-star cast of helpers are coming to town.
The Candid Camera Christmas Special tonight at 8, 7 Central and Mountain.
Rick Lancy for CalTV suggesting you make this season's gift a special one,
like a beautiful five-piece bedroom set with CalTV's low price of $498.
Or for those holiday season get-togethers, a subtracted three-piece living room set for
only $298. And to enjoy that beautiful holiday music, how about a powerful sound design stereo
with double cassette recorder equalizer and record player for only $348. Weekly payment
starting as low as $6, plus a free gift with every purchase. This is the perfect second camera,
Fuji QuickSnap. QuickSnap comes preloaded with 35-millimeter Fuji Super HR film.
I take QuickSnap everywhere. I wouldn't take my expensive camera. Hey, kids!
It's a special one, like a beautiful five-piece.
Is that what he said? Somebody said porn intro.
Bedroom set with CalTV's low price of $498. Or for those holiday season get-togethers,
a subtracted three-piece living room set for only $298.
He's coming out of the chimney.
Oh my god, this is stupid. And to enjoy that beautiful holiday music, how about a powerful
sound design stereo with double cassette recorder equalizer and record player for only $348.
Weekly payment starting as low as $6, plus a free gift with every purchase.
This is the perfect second camera, Fuji QuickSnap. QuickSnap comes preloaded with 35-millimeter
Fuji Super HR film. I take QuickSnap everywhere. I wouldn't take my expensive camera. Hey, kids!
After 24 pictures, I take the whole thing to where I have pictures made. Then I buy another
QuickSnap or a new QuickSnap flash. It has a built-in battery and flash to take pictures at night
or indoors. Smile! Now get this cute holiday stocking free. See QuickSnap dealer for details.
Watch the dog. Yeah.
When you're hungry for TV and so much more, just reach for Naked Night and the cover door.
Be yummy yums, you just gotta try. Crunchy Munchy Naked Night, Sunday's Naked Night.
Indulge starting at 8, 7 Central with Mr. Ed's Oatmeal Horse Dirt. Then try a twin pack of
Patty Duke's Fudge Squares. Join my three sons for some chips, dips, and flips and wash it down with
a clean crisp taste of Donna Reed. It's the Crunchy Munchy Naked Night. Yum! Sunday's Naked Night.
It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas.
Time Life Music presents the Treasury of Christmas. Over one million sold.
Hot the head. Chestnuts roasting open fire.
Oh, another music compilation. For the first time, music brings you all these Christmas stars.
Go back, go back. It was you. Go back, go back. What, what, what, what?
What are you talking about? When you're hungry for TV and so much more,
just reach for Naked Night and the cover. This guy? That doesn't look like me.
The door. Be yummy yums, you just gotta Crunchy Naked Night.
Indulge starting at 8, 7 Central with Mr. Ed's Oatmeal Horse Dirt.
I don't, what do you think I look like, this guy? Then try a twin pack of Patty Duke's Fudge
Squares. Join my three sons for some chips, dips, and flips and wash it down with a clean
crisp taste of Donna Reed. It's the Crunchy Munchy Naked Night. Yum! What are you talking about?
Sunday's Naked Night. The guy, but wait, the shelf, the guy, the shelf, the shelf.
For some chips, dips, and flips and wash it down with. And so much more,
just reach for Naked Night and the cover door. Be yummy yums, you just gotta
Crunchy Munchy Naked Night. Okay, I mean, you can't even see like 70% of that guy's face.
Indulge starting at 8, 7 Central with Mr. Ed's Oatmeal Horse Dirt. Then try a twin pack of
Patty Duke's Fudge Squares. Join my three sons for some chips, dips, and flips and wash it down
with a clean crisp taste of Donna Reed. It's the Crunchy Munchy Naked Night. Yum!
Sunday's Naked Night. Let's get the same thing.
It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas. Time Life Music presents the
treasury of Christmas. Over one million sold. Chestnuts roasting on open fire.
Now, Time Life Music brings you all these great stars together in one Christmas collection.
50 timeless classics on three records, two long play cassettes, and now on two compact discs.
To order, call the number on your screen.
Only Time Life Music brings you Bing Crosby's White Christmas, the most popular recording of
all time. The Treasury of Christmas, the perfect way to celebrate the joy of this holiday season.
50 songs on three records, two long play cassettes, just $19.99. And now for the first time on two
compact discs, just $26.99. Write or call now.
It's punch time.
No, it wasn't. It wasn't a fantasy. You had a clear, you could have taken a shot at least
five seconds. That was a lot of wasted time. No reason to do that. That was a risky move.
And you're benched next game. What is, what is this? Oh, it's okay. The laundry.
This is a lot of people in this house. This, how many people are in this house?
This is a small area.
And there's a shit load of people here too. This is like being on the subway.
There's 40 to 50 fucking people in this room. And there's, here are your walls,
one here and one here. This probably hurts to be in this room.
You can hear this in the whole neighborhood.
We now return to Play It Again Sam starring Woody Allen, Diane Keaton and Tony Roberts.
Holiday helper time is savings time at Neiman's. Delicious for breakfast,
side dishes and hors d'oeuvres. Oscar Mayer bacon is a $1.88 for one pound.
That bacon looked a little sad. And stock up on plenty of northern bath tissue.
Four rolls are only 98 cents. Holiday helper time at Neiman's.
This is NBC News Digest sponsored by Federal Express. Here is Tom Brokaw, NBC News at the Geneva Summit.
Good evening from Geneva where in a few hours an American president will meet face to face
with his Soviet counterpart for the first time in six years. Today was Mikhail Gorbachev's day as he
was welcomed at the Soviet mission here. He said the two sides had to do everything to ensure that
the situation improves. His wife Reza wanted some improvements in the weather complaining how cold
it was in Geneva. U.S. officials said that President Reagan was upbeat but as the two leaders go into
their historic meeting no one is promising any breakthrough on the main issues of arms control
and Star Wars. I'm Tom Brokaw, NBC News in Geneva. We'll have more news later on this NBC station.
Wait what?
Come with me to a place. You'll be glad that you did.
And so much more I'll want to store with Toys R Us kids.
Guess what we want Jeffrey? You want a Toys R Us kids sweatshirt? We've got them three.
I know I took me a second. From 397. Why would you care about like talking about Star Wars?
The dolls are just 997 and you can only find them here.
And look it's me a real stuff Jeffrey the giraffe only 997.
It was yeah it was like a defense program right? It's not not Star Wars the movie.
An action credit wants there to be plenty of oh my god I'm such an idiot.
From now till Thanksgiving action credit is offering a 20% discount on obtaining a guaranteed
visa or master card in time for holiday shopping when you bring in a toy for the Toys for Tots
program. Join action credit help others as you help yourself. If you file bankruptcy have charge
offs collections repossessions or even have a judgment against you action credit will help
clean it up. Call 560-7131 that's action credit 560-7131.
Where can you find beautiful holiday sweaters and blouses in chermouse and crepe de chine with
sequins and beads these and more are just 24.99 now only at Sears. This holiday season give the
people you love more to read than just a card give them a book and at B Dalton there are a lot
of books to choose from. War and Remembrance and the Winds of War by Herman Wook. Daniel Steele's
Palomino Fine Things and Once in a Lifetime. The Chronicles of Narnia seven volumes set by C.S.
Lewis. The Hobbit and the Lord of the Rings trilogy by J.I.R. Tolkien. The North and South trilogy by
John Jakes and Anne of Green Gables by Lucy Maud Montgomery at B Dalton Bookseller. Fucking jaw.
You can call me books. Why was that so exciting though? Damn it don't show that to me. If I don't
get my money out I am over I am finished. Do you understand that? Charlie Babb had thought he knew
everything. What is the source of this guy? Raymond is your brother. My brother? I don't have a brother.
Guess how maybe you'd like to go Los Angeles with me. I found out a few days ago that I have a
brother and I want to be with him and I'm supposed to give him up. Dustin Hoffman, Tom Cruise, Rain Man
made it all. Starts Friday December 16th at Theaters Everywhere. If you saw the first cocoon you
must find out what happens in Cocoon the Return. I think it's gonna be like like old times. It's a
magical adventure a total 10 says Susan Granger. It delivers oxygen rich blood to the pleasure
centers of the brain. The Los Angeles Times says Cocoon the Return sends you home happy. Hello
darling and Joel Siegel says I loved it. Cocoon the Return rated PG. What is this movie?
There's only one place you'll find a sale this big for appliances and electronics.
15 different movies and tv shows and commercials baked into one. TV and more is 5 to 30 percent off
now only at Sears. Another holiday season in California and many of us will attend
festive celebrations. Spend more time in malls and spend more period. Of course millions of
us will get a holiday bonus. The lottery's new scratcher with a $25,000 top instant prize.
A lot of lottery ads. Now wouldn't that make a jolly gift? And you know like hey win 10 million.
A lot of hey you could be rich.
60% off this week only at M-M-Music Mart. That's a wrap.
What? What are you doing? No disasters it's the next best thing to China. Excuse me?
Hold on what are you doing? That was an entire plate of food you dumped on somebody's head.
That's a wrap. Yeah she did that on purpose. You're holding it directly over her head.
These eyes right here no fuck that. These are I'm about to do something and I'm gonna try
to laser focus over here so people don't think what I'm about to know what I'm about to do.
Those are eyes they have intent that's going down.
The best part about this commercial is let's be honest with everybody here there's way too
much macaroni and cheese on this plate. Way too much. Like this is like five servings of mac and
cheese and a fucking apple. What are you doing? This person is shit faced. Why is she not moving?
Why are you not moving? She didn't even react.
No disasters it's the next best thing to China. If somebody puts an entire plate of food on your head
you're gonna fucking freak out. You're setting me up Nick. I probably have to bust my friend if I'm
gonna do my job and I hate you. It's the exact same voice. Close your eyes. I want everyone to
close your eyes right now. Don't open your eyes. Close them and listen. This forever. Close your
eyes. All of love's languages is forever. You're setting me up Nick. I probably have to bust my
friend if I'm gonna do my job and I hate that. A risky friendship. A shared attraction.
Dating is not a criminal activity. A dangerous mix. You are in the wrong place at the wrong time.
It's the same commercial. Michelle Pfeiffer, Kurt Russell, Tequila Sunrise written and directed by
Robert Towne. It's like diamonds are forever. You set me up. Like this is still the same commercial
and he has to fight and it's explosions. Oh can we do this one more time? I want to see it again.
I want to close my eyes through the whole two commercials. Can I do that? I know I'm like rewind
pause Andy. I know but like one more please. No one more. I promise. I want to close my eyes through
the whole commercial. No you know I don't we can just I'll turn the video off.
We'll watch it from here. All of love. All of life's celebrations. Just bear with me please.
Let's try let's see what happens. You're setting me up Nick. I probably have to bust my friend
if I'm gonna do my job and I hate that. A risky friendship. A shared attraction. So if I asked you
how maybe you'd accept. Dating is not a criminal activity. A dangerous mix. You are in the wrong
place at the wrong time. Gibson. Michelle Pfeiffer. Kurt Russell. Tequila Sunrise. Written and
directed by Robert Towne. Rated R. Oh that's so stupid. That would be an unbelievable commercial
though wouldn't it? It's like oh it's a diamond ad. No it's not. It's something else completely.
You look wicked ugly today. Okay that's so fucking mean. Starts Friday December 2nd at a theater near
you. There's only one place you'll find a furniture sale this big. All bedding and bedrooms.
All dining rooms. All living rooms. All carpeting. It's all 10 to 50 percent off. Now only at Sears.
Need help? Yeah and I've got 10 minutes to get to the radio station. Ah here's the problem.
Stetson cologne. Easy to wear, hard to resist. And for that great smelling guy who started my car,
I get off at six.
Bring home this Jet Links car just ten dollars from Target. This backgammon set is also ten dollars.
They're both great gifts.
Buying holiday gifts at department stores could be a waste of money
because smart shoppers save money at marshals for the same. Dude hold on that was not a hundred.
That was like a child's drawing of a hundred. This backgammon set is also ten dollars.
They're both great gifts. That wasn't even close. Buying holiday gifts at department stores
could be a waste of money. That's not even close. You can't do that to real money? I know but at
least I mean why is he doing this? I see this shit. I see this shit on like like YouTube videos and
like TikToks. Why is he doing this? Like because smart shoppers save money at marshals for the
same brand names. This mock turtleneck sweater is just 17.99 at marshals. This silk blouse 17.99.
These earrings just 7.99 and this cardigan 22.99. That's a total savings of over 40%
off department store regular prices. So goodbye department stores and hello marshals. Well that
was under a hundred dollars right? Like you don't why would you burn that?
You know we're gonna be there. Don't think twice. Service is part of us. He got in.
Now we've seen it already. That's a wrap. The teacher was murdered at the high school.
They teach 60% off this week only at the music mart. That's a wrap. Things out there. It has a
mind that can reason. Something out of control but it's insane. The teacher was murdered at the high
school to destroy it. Why does the dog look interested in that too? As long as he's with
the dog his life is in danger. And I say we make a stand right here right now. From the best selling
novel by Dean R. Coons. Watchers rated R. Starts tomorrow at theaters everywhere. The dog was like
yeah I can't believe it happened. One place you'll find Winnie the Pooh learning toys and the Disney
talking magic kingdom. You are right. It makes learning numbers and letters and counting fun.
It's only 40 dollars only at Sears. Towns in Europe had their own way of knowing the holidays
were near. It wasn't the decorations of the first magic snowfall. It was the appearance of special
holiday lockers in every pub and beer hall. Today that tradition lives in America at Coors introducing
Winterfest. Sucks that this works. So bold, so extravagant. We brew it only for the holidays
and when the new year comes the Winterfest will be gone but not the memories. It's I hate how this
works. I want one of these right now. It's just like uh I don't even like beer. When you uh seeing
the glasses like boom I really don't drink it. Which is I want to drink one of those out of that
mug. Only that mug. I don't want it out of anything else. It works every time on me. It sucks.
Jerome's Furniture and Pinery Tree Farms have a special Christmas offer. Right now at Jerome's
buy this Daybetter Entertainment Center for only 99 dollars and receive a Pinery Gift Certificate
for a free Christmas tree. Buy this Curio or recliner for only 199 and receive a Christmas
Tree Gift Certificate. In fact with any purchase from Jerome's you receive a Pinery Gift Certificate
Anything? And from all the people at Jerome's we wish you a Merry Christmas.
There's one place you'll find this Craftsman Cordless Drill for only 26.99 on sale
and all these other cordless gifts on sale. They're America's first choice in tools.
Craftsman. Only at Sears. Now at the warehouse you can rent the hit movie you want when you want it.
The warehouse? What's the warehouse?
The Darth Vader? No.
Visions by Corning actually tough enough to cook another pot has big news smaller sizes
no heat and eat see-through cookware perfect for microwaving heating and eating you'll eat it up
no Visions heat and eat cookware it's a visibly superior gift to cook another pan up your holidays
with a gift box of Reunity premium classics or a gift box of delicious Reunity natural fruits
top off the season with sparkling Reunity Spumati and may all your holidays be bright
you can search but there's only one place you'll find all these perfect Kenmore gifts all under
oh I thought they were cooking the food with the iron only at Sears
$20 just choose $19.99 each find these and a whole lot more only at Sears
then is over does this happen I guess not then I need to play Santa on day by day the stores
are open late tonight on the size four it's all new fun Sunday Saturday on the network of the
Super Bowl the New England Patriots battle the Denver Broncos before your team takes the field
our team hits the air NFL live
those times you relied on them give them something they can rely on the dependable and affordable
excel what's this bunny slip we've seen it already you know we haven't heard from Mark in weeks
so let's get him a Panasonic phone answering machine we haven't heard from this person in
weeks let's buy them a phone as a POV commercial it's on sale at Kmart for $124.88 yeah think you'll
get the message why did that have to be 10 Memorex cassette tapes are only $4.77 after
rebate and this tefal royale fried pan set is only $13.77 I know football but I don't know this stuff
hey let me tell you ace is a place for me wow Miami vice will continue
this is crystal gale join me and my guests John Davidson David Hasselhoff
let's go Christmas in Sweden it's beautiful very quick as a matter of fact
why are they inside they're in the car wash
luxury carpet dude these guys are inside the car wash is allowed oh fuck I'm trying to turn down
these guys are in the car wash cleaning it while the car wash is running
by the inside the machine thing while others describe the luxury performance with words of
the actual legend coop tend to be a little less technical it's a ho ho ho Dolly Parton Don
Johnson and Olympic medalist Florence Griffith joiners it's like getting a Christmas present
Bob Hope's jolly Christmas show then Marcus Welby returns to television on a special assignment
that leads to love come back to the States and marry me don't tease us like that Monday
that Bob what are you doing time for bed darling five more two three no one and then time for bed
Santa Claus is coming very early look at that this grandpa this this is this tree is kind of
a mess this tree is a mess right this is kind of a complete mess the nutcracker
two three one and then time for bed Santa Claus is coming very early it looks like somebody was
from across the room took all the ornaments and all the spring and tinsel and just threw it as
hard as they could against free i'll show you how it works you open it up from here you put a nut
in there and you all right somebody get this and let's get a switch is 20 off youtube thumbnail
video uh thumbnail close it up and it breaks the nut and you can eat it right okay you broke it
oh darling it'll be okay it won't ever of course it will there's a story about how it gets all
fixed up you'll have to use glue not a story come on over here sit down on grandpa's lap and
i'll tell you a story all right now suppose i tell you that this isn't really a doll it's an enchanted
magic prince you'll have to say once upon a time i'll say it once upon a time there was a little
girl called uh what's her name's clara clara just like yours what a coincidence of course
that's what was her name and it was christmas and it was a party a christmas party and it was getting
late it always gets late when there's a party and she needed to fill her car with oil because the
next day was christmas clara was very tired i think a little bit like you are but she was happy
she had all those toys and the nutcracker doll was that her favorite doll oh of course it was
did her grandpa break it no her grandpa wasn't quite as clumsy as yours
all right now clara's parents wave goodbye to the guests and they went off to bed
you're watching a saturday night live christmas special at comedy central
at two watch stewardess school comedy central christmas is brought to you by blockbuster
driving up onto the lawn remember to stock up on the absolute necessities
and also want to pick up some food remember blockbuster video will be open christmas day
we at comedy central would like to wish all of you out there the very best of holidays and remind
you that christmas is a time to be with the ones you love and to give to those who are less
fortunate this is often difficult to remember when christmas is more often used as a marketing gimmick
santas use a liquor salesman and angels sing 50% off everything in the store this is pendulum
celebrate the spirit of the season and was the voice the narrator voice of comedy central from
or don't spend another decade at least instead hang out and hang over this is the best comedy
central era with pendulums on television then if you wake up on new year's day kick off the
cobbits bowl with don orera and a morning lineup of offsides and then hang over to an afternoon
filled with mind-boggling movies to ease you with the 1996 it's comedy central's new year's blowup
starting new year's eve at 8 p.m and new year's day at 8 a.m
you're in the middle of a comedy central christmas he's going deep he's good shot nice play nice
follow-through you know jack knees guard it's a beautiful day why don't you kids do something
different for a change okay mom introducing the great taste of new taco supreme flavor
doritos tortilla chips that was a good idea but spoiled rotten little shits you each get your own
bag and by the way you each have two full bags it spoiled rotten if you don't you share out of you
share one bag two full bags per kid good idea bud and doyle are trapped in the biodome just
because we're stuck in a bubble doesn't mean we can't cause any trouble on january 12
paulie shore i feel like a duck bear platypus and steven baldwin what's who is this kibble
are the boys in the bubble they are a symbol of everything that is wrong
oh what do you think you're some rocket scientist yes sorry rated bg-13 starts
Friday January 12 at theaters everywhere oh grasshopper walks into a bar why would i like
that movie i would probably love that movie grasshopper says really you got a drink called
murray ah everybody's a santa happy holidays i would love that movie yes it's coming to me
just so hold on oh happy psychic helpers oh yeah i see a lot in your future lady have you called
those other psychic lines only to be left with an empty feeling will you deserve better call the
psychic readers network and speak to a psychic who really cares we believe our psyche for the
best and to prove it we want you to try us for free that's right call now and you'll get a free
sample reading with one of our gifted it's like i don't care if somebody gets mad
bud and doyle are trapped in the biodome just because we're stuck in a bubble doesn't mean
it can cost any trouble on january 12 i won't laugh at the rock
and stephen baldwin what is this are the boys in the bubble they are a symbol of everything
that is wrong what do you think you're some rocket scientist yes sorry ready bg-13
one more i'll get it i'll get it i'll try as hard as i can
kibble feel part of you on january 12 holly shore i feel like a duck bill
and stephen baldwin what is this kibble are the boys in the bubble they are a symbol of everything
that is wrong fire dough what do you think you're some rocket scientist
starts fighting january 12th at theaters everywhere
oh why that whole trailer was so just like why like oh this is we're eating dog food
i'm gonna throw a rock at you in the head oh i'm gonna run into a door hit my head on the door it's
just such dog shit it is a four percent on rotten tomatoes holy shit that's worse that might be the
worst movie ever away you have caveman humor uh it's the sound effect that does it for me
it's just like throwing a rock at somebody in that cartoon like
whack it's just so dumb we should watch it fuck all right let's go i'm not i'm moving on a bar
bartender says you know a little fella we got a drink named after you grasshopper says really
you got a drink called murray everybody's a santa happy holidays from comedy central
yes it's coming to me just a moment hello happy psychic helpers oh yeah i see a lot in your future
have you called those other psychic lines only to be left with an empty feeling will you deserve
better call the psychic jack daniels speak to a psychic who really cares we believe our psychics
are the best and to prove it we want you to try us for free that's right call now and you'll get
a free sample reading with one of our gifted psychics when i heard about the free reading i
just had to call my psychic clued right into me it was the best reading i ever had it was remarkably
accurate and very helpful for answers to your questions about love money and your future speak
to a true psychic call now for your free sample reading you get a free reading why wouldn't you
call my psychic was very good she led me right into promotion at work that i didn't even know about
hello this is the leo oh the aquarium oh yeah i knew that hang on why call one of those other
psychics when you can try us for free call now for your free reading call now 1-800-218-7379
what kind of crazy place takes brand new product and gives it all the way mtv that's what with our
super special year-end giveaway mtv's best of 95 league a brand new season of singled out a brand
new best of mtv unplugged a brand new hour-long vivas and butthead christmas special a brand new
year in rock and a brand new house of style featuring cindy's farewell appearance and all
the biggest best coolest mtv shows the year crammed into your tv like so much stuffing and a holiday
mtv's best of 95 week all this week on mtv
i'm getting killed out there the elves are on my ass about health care i got black lung from
all the chimneys and these animal rights people are driving me crazy about the reindeer you know
it was a time when you gave the guns to the boys and the dolls to the girls now i got this gender
bias gift floor yeah and you could forget about any little children sitting on my lap
yeah well maybe next year happy holidays comedy central what's with these video games my elves
what is going on customers can receive two day packages from fedex
what is happening for an extra ten dollars what is happening on saturday santa whoa
santa what the fuck is going on there's no extra charge on saturdays your customers
cannot receive two day packages from ups sorry jesus santa for the holidays what's your priority
when i make someone a holiday bouquet i think of the look on their face when they receive it
the smiles like the ftd holiday celebrations bouquet it's just the thing to make spirits
uh an elegant gift that guarantees every holiday memory will be
a little warmer a little brighter some of life's best moments come ftd call your local ftd florist
or 1 800 cents ftd you hear that is it still the holidays yeah where you've been pal i'm not
too late i can still get present but where office max they've got loads of great gifts
that has jay's pens software intelligent land at guaranteed low prices night for
land hurry to office max and start my shopping couldn't we just charge it and don't forget about
copy max for great holidays pens printer ink personalize calendars office max we go to the
mac computer paper what does christmas mean to me it's the music of the holidays the family
coming together the memories and if i could give the perfect gift it would be the songs
i love the best join me for a very special christmas here on a&e when i perform your
holiday favorites and mine judy collins christmas at the buildmore estate next on a&e
this is wild it's a&e's 29.95 on direct ticket the world's greatest concert attraction is back
the rolling stones bridges the pavillon world tour and there's only one company that can get
three million people into the concert for free it's direct tv the stones like you've never seen
the stones like you've never heard them before see the rolling stones on direct tv for free
rolling stones all over your living room our way of saying happy holidays to our family
of customers from direct tv oh they don't show the part where springtime comes along and he
melts and he's fucking dead introducing eagle brand creamy chocolate for easy to make desserts
that are rich creamy and incredibly chocolatey sure beats visions of sugar plums recipes on top
new eagle brand creamy chocolate now from a&e home video you can own a judy collins christmas at the
buildmore for 29.95 plus shipping and handling call 1-800-423-1212 and receive the companion cd
free with your order whoa 3d reivac renewal is the first alkaline battery that can be recharged
and that could save you hundreds of dollars so this holiday season give the gift that gives
something back all year long whoa reivac those things they like moved around right and these
other great gifts at the reivac gift center in a store near you it's the ultimate new year's
eve party on direct ticket wednesday december 31st six hours of ultimate action six hours of
the ultimate fighting championship see the best matches and the toughest fighters from ufc one
through 15 plus four matches never before seen make this new year's eve the ultimate new year's
don't miss the ultimate fighting championships ultimate new year's eve party on direct ticket
22 bucks 250 years into the future we have been watching this one for almost a full hour holy
smokes 46 minutes we've been watching this oh my god it's a juicy one survivors need to watch
bio don't the only way to save this movie's crazy playing this month on direct ticket only
on direct so those have you ever heard me say i know a lot of people i see question marks all
the time in chat whenever i do this and that's what this is from anytime you've ever heard me go
stones oh yeah i'll get stones i do that i've probably done that probably two or three hundred
times in the last 10 years it's from that movie stones yeah and people are just like what are you
doing why you keep doing that tv watch that movie and you'll understand yeah a and d special
presentation of judy collins christmas at the five more minutes on this one and we'll move on
the taste of gift to give those are good the bustle of the season can wear a bottom down
you need a place an oasis to bring yourself a shopper survival days at mcdonald's take a break
where the welcome's warm the food's hot and the service is fast
it's holiday shopper survival days at mcdonald's true seriously oh i yeah oh yeah
going going mcdonald's sitting down eating like a big mac and fries like two double cheeseburgers
stuff i love mcdonald's i really do it's like it's you know something i'm about to pop off
i'm popping the heck off right now you want to know something about mcdonald's that i don't like
have you noticed that every mcdonald's is starting to turn into a generic cafe ronald mcdonald's has
been removed there's no more grimace there's no more they just turned they just made it it said
that they're just making it a just generic cafe like come on it's just oh everything's like clean
and modern there's no goofy shit out back it's yeah it's just like a black white gray and yellow
cube where's the weird shit i want to i want to sit next to ronald mcdonald on the bench
i mean who cares you can batches me all you want batches me all you want if you grew up in the 90s
and in the 80s and you're like early 80s to late 90s you mcdonald's was a place to be it was just
like comfortable that batches me i want to i only want to see bad chests it was like it was fun it
was like there was things to do it was like things to play with i oh okay child targeted advertisement
but i it was i liked it it was cool yeah like the escape the escapism has been removed it's now like
a coffee shop no i want to i want like grimace to go like with like magical hands they do it to
refranchised closed restaurants it went from chuck e cheese to starbucks yeah everything just
became a starbucks every single store that sells anything that you eat has just been like almost
we're gonna do starbucks we'll just do starbucks on and just just put them everywhere and just turn
them into starbucks's where's the magic at christmas time when i was a kid i always loved the story
about the three wise men i used to always picture them as being like dr thomas he was the only doctor
that we had up here in these hills and he used to ride the ridges on horseback taking care of the
sick he was a well-educated man and he could have made a fine living somewhere else but he loved
these people and he loved the mountains most of the folks up here just paid him with a live chicken
or a sack of cornmeal he delivered me he was a preacher too so years later he tried to deliver
me from sin of course that was a much harder job for him he's gone now but what he brought to these
mountains was a much greater gift than gold offering consents i'm sorry when dolly talks
yeah you you quiet down catch the true colors of the season on coda color gold films
catch the true colors of the season on coda color gold films
i'm sorry 25 years the natural consistency and dependability of cure 81 ham has taken the worry
out of christmas dinners for thousands of people this year we're taking the worry out for thousands
more by contributing cure 81 hams to local charities because everyone deserves the very
best for the holidays that looks good cure 81 from hormel our very best to you that looks really good
sunday eddie murphy i would i would eat that the world i can see you busy right now you see a little
hari krishna midget eddie murphy and the golden child sunday it's the walt disney world very merry
christmas parade with jone london alan thicke teenage mutant ninja turtles lee greenwood
regis philbin jaleel white and amy grant live christmas day on abc the ninja turtles were here
wait i said five minutes how long has it been okay we gotta go all right we gotta we're gonna
change different video one more odwiser anheuser bush the horse was anheuser bush
wait what i thought the whole thing was anheuser bush it was the horse the big horse the clidesdale
all right oh well all right last one this is our isn't a ring that's adds so much to our lives
oh that's i like this and alpo adds so much to theirs santa's favorite singer dolly parton will
be right back that's a good that's a good one to change on thursday bring the whole family to the
ice cafes the simpsons characters join michael feinstein and he is adora make way here comes
trouble peter scolari hosts the ice cafes 50th anniversary special thursday the 90s were insane
that was like three or four different shows and movies that they put on the same thing on ice
like the simpsons and these two celebrities and i don't know people dressed up in costumes
and doing a play it was it was very strange it was i i miss it i don't want to grow up
don't want to grow up i don't want to grow up don't want to grow up hey holiday toy shoppers
it's not how you play that game biggest clearance ever 30 to 75 off on thousands of
hold on to it that dude that would hurt so much what is this kid doing that would hurt so those
of you should do that a funny follow-up to dollhouse dollhouse on ice oh no don't say that
that would be a disaster oh my goodness what a disaster that would be it would be unbearable
makes sense what happened why i lose my place what happened oh because it would be like how
how would you do a sequel to dollhouse of course like it's being on ice on thousands pretend you
didn't hear anything the toys that toys are us remember we've got the most toys all at low low
prices but hurry they're going fast i don't want to grow up don't want to grow up i want to be a
toy to us kid the buckle of the season we already saw this one repeat
there i was about to make my theatrical debut my appearance waited crowded my sister pointed
then this christmas no flash photography
to celebrate the holidays this is the time the christmas album this is so much cleaner audio
holiday favorites plus duets with placido domingo and winona it sounded unbelievable
next video all right one more one more one more one more you said one more four ads ago
teacher's wife rated pg now playing at a theater near you
we already saw this one shit i thought it was a different version and you wanted me to skip that
one you wanted me to switch it did you see what was just on the screen for a quarter of a second
it's gifts for her on sale this week at caldor our entire stock of sweaters 33 percent off
bath and body gift sets 30 percent off lady stirrups or leggings two for 12
dollars timex watches 30 percent off now through saturday gifts for her on sale at caldor the more
gifts you need to buy the more you'll appreciate you want two million boom boxes and you'll deliver
them yourself that's right hey love the hat oh thanks that was an awesome walk yeah he was
hitting the yoinky swanky caldor the more gifts you need to buy the more you really is
the more gifts you need what the fuck now through saturday gifts for her on sale at caldor the more
gifts you need to buy the more you'll appreciate you want two million boom boxes and you'll deliver
them yourself that's right hey love the hat uh thanks your sunglasses were a great idea
yeah we would have been blinded it's also sparkly came what's got it all on sale even the diamonds
diamonds the rubies the gold all 60 percent off okay all right we're gonna pick we're gonna pick
a different one uh let's take a quick break it's been and i need to take a quick break
i am very overstimulated this has been very funny but we'll take a quick break come back we'll
watch we'll do a little bit more the thing about watching these is they just they just infiltrate
your brain and just over stimulate the absolute hell out of you this is a commercial break yeah
technically all right i'll be right back couple months so we have a few options we could do some
more recent infomercials we could do a little bit more 90s into early 2000s let's wait let's do one
more good compilation and probably call it there what do you guys think do a little bit more modern
2000s all right let me see what we got here all right this is gonna be loud on mic hold on
okay so uh what do we have here we have yeah i have a ton of things up you probably you saw the
tabs earlier um uh 90s okay so this is late nine 1990s to late 2000s is this one we'll give this
one a go let me just scan it let's give it a go ready i was alive then yeah here we go
information from betty crocker it's the most exciting i think we've seen this one inside of
a cake introducing bacon why would you put a bacon fill a delightful new ham bacon in the middle of
all kinds of delicious fillings imagine the look on your child's face when you cut into the cake
and there's his favorite flavor and fill her favorite gelatin not bacon filled with delicious
fresh fruit the secret is these three separate sections just pour your favorite betty crocker
cake mix i wasn't looking i was looking over here and lock on this special inner chamber now pour
more cake mix into this base pan and put them both into bake when they're done remove the insert
add your filling to the center cavity and cover it with a base in no time you'll have the greatest
cake you ever made making an exciting cake with my betty crocker bacon fill is so easy
and everything's non-stick so there's no messy cleanup these are the kind of desserts you'll
find this actually is pretty cool ice cream cakes i love ice cream even baked alaska or you can
simply fill your cake with a different saw this one cake mix just fill the inner chamber instead
of the base now make all your cakes extra special make them betty crocker bacon fill cakes
you'll get the bacon fill pan the inner chamber and the base pan complete with instructions and
betty crocker recipes oh for only 1995 guaranteed to delight you or your no i'm doing this now we
will also include this special dome pan that lets you make holiday cakes like this or give your young
baseball hero a celebration he'll never forget it's yours free just pay shipping and handling
plus we'll give you over five dollars worth of coupons over five dollars products so don't
delay order your betty crocker bacon fill now to order your betty crocker bacon fill for 1995
plus i think it's kind of cool call 1-800-7 does it work who knows 564 or send check or money order
to betty crocker bacon fill to morgan avenue norwalk connecticut call now okay hey kids
follow the bouncing plate oink oink zoo pals buz buz zoo pals quack quack zoo pals
zoo pals make eating fun i remember this when you clean your plate then you see their face
zoo pals ribbit ribbit zoo pals woo woo zoo pals zoo pals make eating fun
zoo pals
does anybody else feel like that's something that would be on shark tank now that's given me
shark tank vibes those are great but kids can lose two and a half months worth of what they
learned in school don't let them fall behind call sylvan at 1-800-7 losing iq lasting skills habits
and attitudes for lifelong success in just three hours a week over 12 weeks you will see results
in your child's reading or math performance improving one grade level guaranteed still learn
how sylvan helps your child succeed in school and in life call now for this free introductory dvd
call sylvan at 1-800-Educate what's squishy stretchy and transforms almost anything
i was talking about this the other day floam look now you can turn anything into a fabulous
floam creation transform this wooden fossil into a fierce floam t-rex oh these things i love this
stuff it had this texture that will never be replicated
it was squishy it was it had like a texture to it
probably awful for the environment if we're honest
floam critters or building an erupting volcano of floam
with hundreds of millions of microplastics baked into every single one a stylish jewelry case
or a funky floam base foam your pencil so they're cool or show some spirit at school
make costume masks even floam rainbow glass take floam outside and make a floam landfill
and put your floam inside of your shoes it will never decompose just ask anyone who
from parents to tots floam it's fun you can feel tired of looking like a fool when your
cakes aren't cool and why do tiny cupcakes take so long to make get in the spotlight with big
we saw a couple of these already an easy way to make colossal same guy same guy 25 times bigger
everyone's face will light up when you make somebody said it's this youtube voice guy grab
your camera to remember those giant cupcakes your family makes together it's so easy just
it is youtube voice bake and decorate wow that jumbo cupcake looks amazing big tops quick
release silicone is flexible and virtually nothing sticks so a perfect cupcake pops out
every time making it the ultimate party activity mix and match delicious flavors like strawberry
and chocolate the man-sized cakes look nothing's more thrilling than a chocolate filling made easy
with our optional magic center insert fill big tops with pudding mousse gelatin even your favorite
ice cream tiny cupcakes won't do but 25 times bigger feeds the whole crew that's so bad one
cupcake is enough it's dishwasher safe i don't get cupcakes are so expensive metal cake mold stick
and cost over 35 but you can join the show with big top cupcake for 1995 we'll even include this
idea book free use the tips to make a silly clown face that's sure to get a laugh but we're not done
we'll give you these awesome animal cookie cutters to bake three-dimensional cookies
make yummy lions or tasty elephants a $20 value free but call right now and as a bonus
we'll double your order just pay processing and handling you get two big top cupcakes two idea
books and two 3d cookie cutters a whopping $100 value for 1995 call or log on to get hurting me
all right so what i was gonna say was i don't understand cupcake the cupcake thing i get it
but i don't know cupcakes to me after i like i split cupcakes splitting cupcakes you know right
in half that's fine i don't like cake i'm not a cake person it's like two you get you know what
i'm talking about it's like it's this weird feeling i hate it it's like frosting and then
like dry like well it's just like i don't know i don't like it give me ice cream instead put it
in the fridge first with spaghettios pasta your mouth will really rock once you get your lips
around us you know you'll be whoa i remember this one
whoa campbell spaghettios oh yeah oh your child can visit steamy jungles grassy plains and the
dark depths of the ocean what the holy shit animals that live the depths of the oceans
do meet and learn to dude jungles grassy plains and the dark depths of the ocean what and learn
surprising facts about the magnificent what a horrendous way to die all through the captivating
colorful pages of zoo books the publication is specially created for young readers each
monthly issue of zoo books is packed with breathtaking full-color photos monkey was
in the room illustrations plus games and puzzles there are animals in the living room with them
you can get 12 fascinating issues of zoo books for the special price of 1995 when you call and
use your credit card will include the elephants issue as a gift plus you'll also get the colorful
collection of animal stickers and the tiger poster so order zoo books today and send learning and
fun to a child you love to order 12 fascinating issues of zoo books for 1995 call 1-800-441-2400
when you call will include the bonus elephant issue stickers and tiger poster with your order
1-800-441-2400 you must be 18 years or older to call oh not tonight you had chef 10 times this week
the thing i took from the cart and didn't tell you rd boy this stuff is good the thing that
i took from the shelf and didn't tell you and now i'm gonna be in big trouble that's classic
one though oh shit i remember this wage didn't do great more cash
i will make a bigger salary so which college is right for me i went on the internet and
went education connection to find out my direction i'm taking my classes online getting my degree on
my own time education connection for free i have no idea what this was i have no idea what it was
for what the product was no clue they nailed it with this commercial i mean that was just great
all around whatever ad agency was responsible for this they have to be swimming in like a liquid
gold pool because they probably went on to make even more absolute bangers the song won a grammy
by the way really you didn't know it's about colleges i mean i knew what i but i didn't know
what it was for it was like you go on it and it's like oh here these are the colleges that
you should go to because like we're matching majors or something i don't i don't know wait
did you just lie to me is it oh you oh i was lying okay i thought it was i thought you were
being for real i believed it because it made sense say hello to the yeah but they're oh yeah why would
i not immediately say what are you talking about they're the grammy for tv commercial songs that
doesn't exist hello pets you have one of these are cute huggable pets that pop open into full-size
pillows they're soft they're cuddly and they make perfect pillows moms your kids will absolutely
love their pillow pets you simply undo the hook and loop strap and the pack pops open into a
full-size pillow just fold it up reattach the hook and loop and it's back to a cuddly animal
it's fun and easy playtime sleep time anytime kids of all ages love these are cute a minus
a ladybug a frog a dog a unicorn a dolphin a bumblebee a monkey and so many more everyone
needs a pillow why not have a fun pillow pillow pets are great for travel look pj's fit right
inside perfect for the overnight trips to grandma's house this is more than just another stuffed animal
this is a pillow that your child or grandchild will use every night i really want one if i'm
being for real is made of ultra soft high quality they probably still make them the
heavy duty stitching ensures years of enjoyment in their i would pick the frog for sure are so
soft and huggable all it takes is one hug and your child or grandchild will fall in i'm not
gonna buy one of these but i'm just saying over a million kids are already enjoying their very own
pillow pets every pillow is so cute and unique the hardest part is choosing which one to get
go online to www.pillowpets.com to see oh my god there's a lot of these i thought there was
only two or three never mind i changed my mind i want the duck choosing which one to get go online
to www.pillowpets.com to see the full selection of pillow pets if you have a birthday holiday or
special occasion coming up pillow pets make the perfect 20 gift imagine your child or grandchild's
face when they get their pillow pet pillow pets come with a full 60 day money back guarantee
so go online right now to www.pillowpets.com that's www.pillowpets.com adopt your pillow pet today
here they come screaming across the sky it's lots and lots of jets and planes lots and lots
of jets and planes DVDs we've ever offered and through this special what is this you can get two
DVDs for the price of one you'll get to see big planes little planes soaring stunts and passenger
planes even planes that fly real low old planes new planes fast planes slow planes smoking planes
even planes in supersonic speeds plus much much more when you order lots and lots of jets and planes
each DVD is jam-packed with lots of high flying close-up action this special tv offer is not
available in stores remember you can get two dvds over two hours of non-stop aviation action
for the price of one it's lots and lots of jets and planes you can order now and receive a free
bonus dad buys this he's really excited and after the first i want to say probably 10 minutes of
the first dvd every single person in the whole room has moved on besides dad and and he's kind
of upset about it right because everyone's like oh yeah that's fun oh yeah what about this one
this jet look at this one and i think the whole room might kind of be like um this is cool but
how how long is this these could be hours long and i'll be very honest planes jets they're awesome
they're really cool that's really awesome i don't think i could watch like planes flying around for
like three four five hours straight what what is this is it just like hey look there's planes flying
around it's for kids there's a train one they're dad sensory videos am i just completely getting
this wrong or is this actually just like little kids would be like look an airplane dad did i
get the whole thing wrong that's what i think the cd of jet plane songs you must be 18 years
or older to call 888-334-55 parents call 888-334-55 satisfaction guaranteed that's wait a minute is
that before 55 parents call 888-334-55 isn't that like a stealth bomber i've satisfaction
guaranteed that's 888-334-55 for lots of jets and planes all right i would watch an hour
scooby-doo haunted house game spin the spinner and move through the house with secret booby traps
shaggy's been trapped watch out daphne good job scooby let's see who the ghost really is the
scooby-doo haunted house game i would have wanted to play this historic past and the limitless
future comes robo raptor fluid biomechanical motion and three programmable behavior modes
make an interactive responsive or unpredictable touch sensors in his head and tail making
powerfully interactive he's doing the yankees blanking sound vision sensors see you take
control of robo raptor with a multi-function remote or let him roam free sensory awareness lets him
feel and react with his environment friend or predator you decide robo raptor a fusion
it can bite you battery's not included for wowie it can bite your finger fiercely autonomous robo
reptile claims his territory stalking his prey with biomorphic bursts of speed while his highly
evolved vision system alerts him to danger part reptile part technology all added to
robo reptile trigger his sound sensors to lure him in and take command with the remote control
feeding robo reptile will tame him but not for long robo reptile a fusion of technology
battery's not included from wowie the eagle screeching
oh i thought it was toilet paper
new from nerf the end strike recon cs6 the blaster you can customize for any mission
for night missions equip the red spy light to spot in targets for multi-target missions the
six dark quick fire clip gives you extra firepower and for long range missions
flip up the site to nail your target the end strike recon cs6 only from nerfs blaster comes
to show another blaster sold separately battery's not included yeah well i'm the doodle bear i come
i remember this
notes and names and games friends sharing pass me on when they ask me which tattoo i love the best
i throw over my arms it's rosy on my chest because i'm the doodle bear this commercial is on all the
time there's no room for something new washing machine and come out nice and clean because i'm
the doodle bear doodle bear what a great idea four different colors with washable doodle pens
and tattoos each pair sold separately
wait wait wait wait
here we go show me dance
with new that's not what they fucking sound like you never know what's gonna happen
you just gotta say hey new furby eats sold separately batteries not included you can
that is not what that was dubbed over that's not what they sound like it's a rebrand from uh you're
thinking i'm thinking the old ones okay well you know what i meant find more fun at hasbro.com ask
a parrot first i gotta read this hold on so belly mouth in mod chat i had one of those but never
no no i had a furby but it talked too much and my brother put it in the freezer and it went eeeee
for three days and died that's fucked good good that's so sad that's actually sad
pokemon sapphire only for gameboy advance rated e for every that's what that was for
muzzy muzzy is the number one language course for children in the world
there's never been a better time than right now to try muzzy i this is he goes
right there's a there's a version of this right he goes right i'm telling i'm serious some i just
i hit that some of you guys went yep it was one of the muzzy commercials wait you've got it right
here hold on dude i'm telling you when i say something and i remember something i remember
pretty accurately i gotta get my credit for that one that was pretty it's pretty good
to celebrate our anniversary we'll send you that was pretty good original muzzy languages in one
program and you can try muzzy free for the first time ever five wrong spanish french italian
german and english in one program at no extra cost this is the biggest most powerful muzzy ever
remember kids are open to languages it comes naturally they don't see it as work it's fun
and it all i wish i learned a different language kids love muzzy and with five languages in one
try muzzy free what are you waiting for and then no that is true though learning a different
language or you know learning two or three languages when you're younger it's so much
your brain is developing and you can just take it in so much easier than right now and i can't do
it i i just cannot do it i always you know what it's interesting because i've always heard people
kind of talk you know by talking two different languages or you're like oh yeah i know this i
know that i know how to speak french and i speak spanish or whatever like and they can just go back
and forth like that i the way the brain works i'm trying to imagine like do you think in the other
language or do you translate it first and then say it right like do you think in english and then
translate it and say that just phonetically say the words or can you actually think in spanish
think in french think in swedish whatever what i feel like that's hard it depends both i think
in my native language and say it in icelandic really depends on a lot of context because i'm
trying to imagine a world where i would be thinking in a different language and like saying it reversing
it into english or vice versa like do you actually start to think in that language pretty cool it's
a 50 50 split okay let's go the fortune for beautiful decorated cakes like these
now you can decorate them yourself with a little help from betty crocker introducing the betty
crocker 100 piece cake decorating it's everything you need to create beautifully decorated cakes
and desserts just like a professional this secret is this unique multi-directional applicator all
you do is point and squeeze simply insert a disposable bag fill it with icing and attach
the nozzle then apparently bilingual people have different personalities in different languages
with beautiful flowers like this the star tip to make striking shell borders or braided ropes
or the petal tip to create elegant roses imagine that was pretty cool looking create gorgeous
accents like this it's so easy you can make these accents with one hand there's even a
grass hair tip for unusual novelty cakes the three-profile icing knife can be used to sculpt
somebody's made that up just go one guy and your complete decorating kit even includes
letter stencils for that special message and a set of pattern presses for heartfelt designs
imagine creating boring snooze on this one where's the rock music where's the person
taking a bite out of a burrito like this and the camera zooms wicked close and then comes
right back out during the bite of the burrito it's every single one what the
fuck this is like educational and explaining stuff i want the guy with the backwards hat
the skateboard electric guitar these one-of-a-kind homemade cakes all by yourself you can order and
receive the betty crocker 100 piece decorating kit with everything it's a cake add plus an easy
to use instruction guide and a handy storage yeah it's all right all for ten dollars plus
nice attention span i'm good 18 or older to order guaranteed to delight you or your money back
that's right this offer from betty crocker turns ordinary baking into an extraordinary love to
bake dollars plus six percent new nor you must be not anymore introducing the original chocolate
factory the fun easy way to turn ordinary into extraordinary desserts just place in store-bought
chocolate select your favorite treat then with adult supervision oh my god fill it or pour it
look marshmallow right there but chocolate factories double boiler is two pans in one
the bottom simmers water while the top quickly melts chocolate into a smooth and creamy sensation
perfect for dipping nuts strawberries and bananas and look fill the designer mold for snowmen
during the holidays create teddy bears seashells lollipops and fondue pots are really cool but it's
one of those items at the store that you see a commercial for it or you have it at a restaurant
or something you go wow this is cool is awesome i want to do i want to eat that right now and then
you walk by like a fondue kit at the store and you go that thing's stupid i'm not buying that
what a dumb product and then six months later i'll see another one and i'll go oh man i would
love a fondue night hey hey let's do fondue night and then we again you know you forget about it
you go to the store you go that product's dumb i don't want it takes up too much space it's just
a double boiler yeah but it comes with the sticks and the tools there's little tools you can use and
i mean i don't know it's probably made the sticks are proprietary or you can even make a gift
basket at a fraction of the price the complete chocolate yeah that's not a stick this is look
at this is proprietary tools see it's not worth buying this factory kit comes with everything
you need including this dipping dessert guide that's over 90 pieces all for 1995 here's how to
order call 1-800-592 look at how cool that is and order the chocolate factory for 1995
but here's the thing i know people how much is a double boiler if you were to go get a double
boiler from the store this is 20 bucks would a double boiler be like 50 100 200 20 bucks
why are you calling sticks proprietary they're not sticks they're these like little thin prongs
they're like thin they're little metal thin and they got two sticks and it's like a proprietary
stick treat your family to chocolate creations you must be 18 or older to call all right uh let's
let's do a few a couple more i have a few little ones here that i want to do how about this one
what is this one oh yeah i want to see this one did we see this one already we may have seen this
one this one's called yolk magic yolk magic egg yolk did we see this already when it comes to
egg whites separating the yolk is no joke messy shells are you aiming out of the pan that are
slow pokes not anymore introducing yolk magic the fast easy way to separate yolks from egg whites
watch just squeeze the vacuum force bulb touch it to the top of the yolk and release presto just
like that you're left with high protein low calorie egg white skill issue yeah
pancakes belgian waffles or a delicious egg is actually a day the healthier way egg yolks
are loaded with cholesterol and high cholesterol oh i'm gonna go i'm gonna don't get me started again
i'm about to do almost spend 10 minutes talking about this again this is this is horseshit egg
yolks are not bad of yeah they have cholesterol if you just eat a shitload of egg yolks every
single day of your life eggs egg yolks have all the stuff most of the stuff that you want from
an egg is from the yolk and there was this thing that happened back in like the late 90s early
2000s where it was like don't eat the egg yolk don't eat the egg yolk it's disgusting it's
terrible for you it's awful for you can be heart disease and shit what eat the egg being it's the
egg eat it now don't eat a hundred of them mr all diets are at an all-time high notice notice how
high cholesterol diets at an all-time high causing health risks where's the part about the eggs
high cholesterol diets today the healthier way egg yolks are loaded with cholesterol
and high cholesterol diets are at an all-time high you know that says high cholesterol all the
fucking hamburgers you eat all the shit you eat every day all the all the steak that you eat every
day i don't like the hell the whole egg yolks got a really bad rap for a long time what does
the omelet look like a tortilla what belgian waffles or a delicious egg white omelet and
steak every day i don't know people eat all kinds of shit start your day the healthier way egg yolks
are loaded with cholesterol and high cholesterol diets are at an all-time high but with yolk magic
removing them has never been faster and easier even from inside a frypan plate mixing if it made
that sound i think it'd be cool fit and lean by enjoying a yolk-free veggie scramble energizing
breakfast burritos or savory quiche lorraine fast and easy yolk magic is a baker's dream easily
remove the yolk not your ingredients perfect for wholesome muffins the fluffiest meringues
or scrumptious souffls and look you can save the yolks for other recipes what i thought we were
why are we doing that why are you not eating them save the yolks for later i thought we're
supposed to not eat these or not use them ever like homemade chocolate pudding or creamy fettuccine
sauce best of all yolk magic is bpa free and easy enough for kids so instead of leaning into the
like eggs are awful terrible for you don't eat egg yolks they're awful this product is actually
pretty cool i mean you could very easily separate there are a lot of recipes that call for just
simply egg yolks just simply egg whites that it's a it's a yolk separator and it works very
well look at how good this thing works this is a cool product it's of all ages plus it's dishwasher
safe stop removing yolks the old way and enjoy your meals the yolk magic way during this special
tv offer you'll get yolk magic and our fast and easy recipe book that thing actually works pretty
well that thing click i'm impressed will double your order free just pay separate processing and
handling and here's even more magic you'll also get this vegetable chopper to chop mince slice
and dice just tap down for a delicious egg white western omelet in no time the perfect partner to
yolk magic yours free this incredible 40 value is all yours for just ten dollars ten bucks you get
that's all right ten bucks looks like it's pretty cool all right there's another one here no
spoilers okay this is this i actually am looking forward to this one i want to see this one
this is the one touch jar opener find out jar lid stuck again you tap you heat you struggle
uh-oh there must be an easier way to open that jar introducing using the one touch jar opener
the fast easy way to open jars just place on the jar on touch the button and your jar
an easy you heat you struggle uh-oh there must be an you heat you struggle this is a prop there's
no juice or anything in this they made a prop to break there's no pickle juice these dry ass
pickles it's not a pickle jar oh there must be an easier way to open television is real
yeah but i mean what why make a fake pickle jar when you can just do a pick what why go through
all the other you just don't want it to be wet but that jar introducing the one touch jar opener
the fast easy way to open jars just place on the jar touch the button and your jar opens in seconds
the one touch jar opener is totally automatic amazing look other jar openers are hard to use
they take up too much counter space they do all require too much force they do with the one touch
jar opener you just touch and go it's so easy anyone can use it best of all it works on any
size jar small medium or large nothing is easier or more powerful than the one touch jar opener
the i mean at 60 horsepower like in what mustang has got more power dude what are you talking about
one touch jar opener automatically grips the jar firmly and clamps itself onto the lid then the
powerful high torque motor exerts up to 25 foot pounds of pressure to unlock the lid releasing
this how much each up to 25 foot pounds of pressure to under the lid then the powerful high torque motor
exerts up to 25 foot pounds of pressure 25 foot pounds of what does that mean to the lid then the
powerful high torque motor exerts up to 25 foot pounds of pressure to can anybody calculate that
what's that mean 25 foot pounds 25 pounds per foot strength of it has the what is it i don't
know what that means the unit of force but how but what give it to me in like like how would you
explain that to a nine-year-old pounds per foot 25 square it's strong it's 12 and a half people's
feet none of you know what it is look at it's almost 25 000 people none of you know maybe like
three of you put the right answer 25 feet per pound 25 pounds there's no point you're not going
to even see it whatever to unlock the lid releasing the seal with ease even the toughest seal is no
match for the one touch jar opener the one touch jar opener fits in any drawer so it's always ready
to use on almost any jar no matter what shape or size just touch and go the one touch and if you put
it in reverse tighten this fucking thing so no one will ever open it again seal away all your
delicious foods that you don't want your your husband or your wife to eat it really will be
the last jar opener you'll ever have to buy my arthritis hurts when i open jars now i just push
a button and the jar opens for me get the one touch jar opener for the breakthrough price of
just 1995 with a money-back guarantee if the one touch isn't the easiest jar opener you've ever used
just return it for a full refund call right now and we'll give you i want to i want to like arm
wrestle this thing i mean like attach it to like a thing that has an arm on it and like let's
fucking let's go what if it kicked my ass be the one touch bottle pourer it makes heavy awkward
bottles easy to handle what eliminate messy spills a ten dollar value yours free just pay
shipping and handling it's a huge job thing is way cooler tapping no more your turn it for a full
refund call right now and we'll give you the one touch bottle pourer it makes heavy awkward bottles
easy to handle helping eliminate messy spills a ten dollar value yours free just pay shipping
and handling it's a huge offer no more tapping no more hot water no more frustrating moments and no
more struggling with other jar openers get the one touch jar opener and touch and go forever don't
wait call now i know a lot of people are going just use two hands do you i i don't know um have
you ever seen uh a child pick up a two liter of something the whole room holds their breath it's
like okay here i go and it's like oh that's safer so do it for them i'm gonna learn sometime all
right i think i'm done maybe one more one more what about what's this one we'll try this one
one more this one's the spinning cool cafe love the taste of iced coffee but hate paying expensive
coffee shop prices brew it hot and that's the wrong way brew it cold and you've discovered the
right way with the amazing spinning cool cafe the fast easy way to spend delicious cold brew
look hot brewing just increases acidity and makes coffee taste bitter but the spinning cool cafe
uses crisp cold water and a unique spinning system to draw out the perfect natural flavors from the
coffee without the bitterness or acidity with just a spin you'll create the best iced mochas
or fantastic frappes that are always silky rich and smooth plus cold brewing cuts acidity by up
to 70 percent it's so smooth you won't even need sugar or cream but simply fill the carafe
with water add your favorite coffee and spin why do you need to spin it the fastest 60 ounces
of fresh cold i've used a cold brew baker a handful of times you don't you just put the
grounds in you seal it up why does it spin does that do anything brewed coffee in the world
and because it's cold brewed it won't get watered down with ice thanks to this press system coffee
grounds are easily filtered and held on the bottom cold brew light medium or dark using any
coffee you choose the best part your coffee stays fresh and full flavored in the fridge for up to
14 days ice drinks at the coffee shop cost about six i like cold brew but the same but what they
don't show you in this commercial in a quarter call now what they don't show you in this commercial
is how much kind of a pain in the ass it is because you'll do this it takes like wait what
did they say 14 days that's a long time cold brew makers are great but yeah you guys saying
already the issue with it is you do it you brew it and you make the amount of coffee you want
and then the thing is sitting on the counter and you you drink it and you kind of just go oh this
is a fucking mess and then you have to untake the thing apart clean it throw the grounds away wash
the thing grounds are everywhere it's kind of annoying it's really good though it's worth it
if you really like cold brew but col a lot of cold brew machines are cold brew makers i wish
there was just a better way right you're lazy yeah do you understand welcome welcome to the future
here every single product you have ever touched has been born out of laziness almost every consumer
product you've ever used everything is born out of human laziness so yeah i don't feel like spending
the the like 18 minutes it requires to clean the coffee machine no i don't want to i'm a lazy
modern human i want it done for me and i want it to be less than a minute for me to do get the
amazing spinning cool cafe for only 29.99 yeah 30 bucks guaranteed to cold brew the best iced
coffee you've ever had or your money back but wait we'll even include i mean it's a cold
brew maker ice recipe book free you get it all the world's fastest cold brew i mean the
spinning thing is a gimmick but it's a cold brew maker and guarantee an incredible 100 value all
yours for just 29.99 it probably works it i mean it's a it's it's you all cold brew is you just
put coffee grounds into cold water put it in the fridge for eight to 15 hours or so 10 hours 14
hours that's all it is i mean it separates the grounds it makes it i don't know whatever
a hundred dollar value 14 days i don't know if i'm one to talk because i feel like i've
put cold brew in the fridge and drank it like a week or two later i feel like i have done that
like oh yeah this is still fine i've been like i don't know it's fine it's coffee it's enough
poison that explains a lot not two weeks but i don't know four or five six days few days five
days how long i've probably done it before coffee literally never goes bad no matter how you make it
well i don't know does it mold brew yeah it strengthens the gut biome
all right that's it that's all for today that was fun there's only four and a half hours i think is
my limit watching watching like two lord of the rings movies worth of old ads is i think is enough
for my brain that was really fun that was very very very wild yeah all right so what do you guys
think you guys want more of this i don't want to overdo it though because i feel like it loses the
magic i think it's a lot of fun it's cool to look at kind of the way the world functioned and the
technology at the time and what people thought was interesting and it's cool please watch biodome
i mean i i don't think i can do that but i'll ask do mobile game ads i've actually wanted to
do that for a while but all right um so the plan was i was going to play driver tomorrow
but i do have some very bad news i'm not going to be playing driver tomorrow and he's a little i
need to set it up he's a little more time to set up but that's not what's happening we're not doing
that sorry so that's shocking do british ads i would i'll do that is it just as simple as looking
up uh 90s british ads and the same amount of compilations i'm imagining two canadian ones
you want me to be a commercial react andy i could do that the uk is so boring i mean i i don't think
there's probably tons of interesting stuff that came out in the uk for ads
yeah all right so here's the plan um i'm kind of doing this like one day off one day on one day
off one day on thing so the next time you see me i'll be here on sunday with hopefully driver and
probably something else i'm not i am not gonna beat driver i don't think so i'll be lucky to
get 30 40 minutes out of that game yeah frog detective makes sense depends on if i get obsessed
with driver i doubt it but you know weirder things have happened on this stream yeah same deal uh i
sus is going to be set for two don't be surprised if it happens earlier
2023 i'm trying to keep myself more honest on when i start so if it says two it could be two
it might also be 130 one could be it is 2023 yeah that was a lot of fun that was really funny
it always is have been this is so much wacky wacky stuff yeah thanks everybody thanks for the subs
there's a lot tonight appreciate it see you guys soon see in a couple days see you sunday have a
wonderful rest of your night and i'll see you sunday take care goodbye call your mother call
your mother see you later