Hey, very dark in here. I know. Play with chopsticks for an hour? I'm not gonna do that.
I want to make sure this is not loud. Let's turn it down for you because I don't blow your ears out.
Okay, I have to install it. Okay, the bitrate's gonna drop like a shitload because it's gonna
take over all my internet, so I don't have it downloaded. Okay. Revolt? Animal Revolt Battle
Simulator. Is this gonna be funny? I don't know, we'll find out. I'm gonna get it. Well, I already
have it. That's a lie. Use coconut oil? Alright, internet's gonna go- the stream's gonna like die
for a second. Alright, done. Downloaded. Yeah, that was literally- do you understand the power
of fiber optics? That was- that was a 1.1 gigabyte game and it downloaded in three seconds.
Just the power of fucking absolute gigabyte. Alright, let's go. I need to update the title
too because the title makes no sense. What's this game called? Animal Revolt Battle Simulator. Okay.
Loud. Good thing I turned it down. Alright, yeah. Early access. Wait, you can do dinosaurs versus
like- hold on a minute. This might be cool. This could be pretty cool. Why can't- I can't
capture the game for some reason. Come on, capture the game. It's right here. Capture.
Psycho energy? Yeah. Let me try capturing it again. Oh, there it is. Alright, good. Alright,
so this game- should I do campaign? Tutorial? Big announcement? Alright. This game looks like dog
shit but it's fun. Alright, well you- I was kind of rude right off the bat. Can I do the tutorial?
Sandbox basics. Welcome to the sandbox basics tutorial. Sandbox basics. Click on the unit
groups button to open the unit groups menu. Okay. Select units here. You can choose different groups
of animals, weapons, buildings, and landscape items. You can even create weaponized animals
by attaching various weapons, armor, and gear on them. Okay. Once you have selected a unit group,
the icons for the units belong to that group will appear in the bottom panel.
Alright. Click on one of the unit icons and start placing units on the map. You can change
the initial rotation of the unit using the mouse scroll. Okay. Eight bucks. Modify various proportions
of the animals like detection distance, HP, multiplier, etc. Click on the J key to see the
properties of the animals. Click on H to see the animal health bars. Units we have created so far
belong to team one which is your team. You can see the total cost of your army is 16 dollars.
Okay. Place units for other teams. Click on the team button and select another team number. You
can also use the number keys on your keyboard blah blah blah. Clear buttons allow you to clear all
the units. We are placing units for team two now. Note team two units are marked by red circles.
Click on the start button to begin the battle. You can end the battle at any point by clicking
the escape button. Okay. Click on the options menu to set the map properties. You can change
the landscape, time of day, etc. Click on the question mark to access the tutorial. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. Edit stuff. If you make a mistake when the building, yeah, yeah, yeah. Click undo. Control Z
works too. You can save all your maps for later use there. Sounds cool. This concludes the tutorial.
You're ready to start playing around. Alright. Alright. We do just campaign. Let's start with
the campaign. First person shooter maps. Alright. Tutorial. Okay. Double click to make the gorilla
run. Click on the escape key to exit the battle. Okay. Select animals. Go begin. Oh, okay. Okay,
that was stupid. You can make your own creations. Okay. Well, we're gonna give me a second. Select
all those fine looking men by holding the left mouse button. Drag. Okay. This is a good RTS.
One man will struggle to move past a heavy wood plank, but together they should be able to make
their way to the flag. Can I get a better view? Alright. I got it. It's Warcraft 3. All those
poor dinosaurs are blind and immobile. Select all your archers and right click on the dinosaurs
to shoot them down. Hold the middle mouse button to activate slow mode. Oh shit. Okay. So this is how
you fight. I want to zoom in. Okay. Cool. How do I move the camera? Q-W-E-A-S-M-D to move the camera
around. Alright. Camera rotation. Oh shit. Alright. I get it. Tab rotates. There's a cute little pig
hiding around here somewhere. Where is it? Where are you? Inside of one of these things?
Last. Really? Okay. God damn it. Alright. Pig in there. Got it.
Instruct your rocket man to destroy it. That's kind of sad. Why? Okay. I don't like this.
Okay. Create animals with a budget of a thousand dollars and an animal count of 25. Okay.
Animals. Ancient humans. About, uh, a knight? Okay. That was kind of unfair. That was really
unfair. Okay. This white character is your FPS avatar. Left mouse click on it and press F to
take control. What? Are you serious? Why can I do this? Okay. That's actually pretty cool.
That's funny. Defoe letter grade? Almost. There's a car. You got it. Okay. Reach the goal. Okay.
Almost done. Take control of FPS. I can reach one of them. You can destroy the tower with a grenade
launcher. Whoa. Are you serious? I actually get to use this stuff? Alright. I got it. It's tabs,
but FPS. Mom, I want to play tabs. We have tabs at home. Alright. Stop. Take control of the FPS
avatar and then go to the enemy spawner to disable it. Okay. Let's go. Let's move. Wait. Why are the
enemies pigs? Alright. Destroy the enemy spawner. How do I destroy the spawner? I feel like I'm
playing Dusk. Alright. Tutorial is almost over and then I can play. Final tutorial.
This poor little hippo has no chance against a bunch of angry humans with baseball bats. Attach
some weapons to the hippo. Missile launcher? Okay. Oh, a limit one. Shit. Okay. Well, that's fine.
Okay. Why does it not hurt the hippo? Okay. This game actually can be really fun. Alright. Tutorial
done. Let's go. Human salvation. Okay. This is humans. Remember that you can control the movement
of your units using your mouse. Alright. So I have to be, I have to win. What do you got? You've got
people with axes and shields and shit. Okay. Ancient humans. I'm going to go with Archie the
archer. It's 10 bucks. I'm going to put concentrated in one spot so that it's like one
giant arrow landing down on their heads. I'm going to put them in what I call a bowling formation.
This should be good. Okay. Bowling formation done. Any pins? Alright. I think we're ready.
Start. Oh, they have shields. This didn't work the way that I thought it was going to work.
Absolutely obliterated. Is there anybody left? You guys suck. Use the RTS commands. Wait, I can?
Oh shit. I can. Alright. Did I win? I almost won. Oh god damn it. Okay. I forgot about that.
Let us gamble. That's not a bad idea. But let me get the swing of the things first.
Let me get the swing of things first before you lose all your money. How much am I? 15?
Cost them a 250. Alright. Alright. Okay. Okay. This one will work. I'm going to control these
guys. Alright. Here we go. And three. Don't get, what a bad camera angle. Alright. Lock it in.
Start. Shoot that one person. Good. That's guy right here. Good. This guy right here.
Again. In the head. Again. Okay. Good. Again. Again. Nice job. Alright. Round two is these
animals. I can't wait to make my own shit. This is going to be awesome. I'm going to do a dinosaur
fight like you've never seen before. Alright. It's versus, how many of us, what is it? Elephants,
hippos, giraffes. I kind of feel like the night would be well good here. Or just a shitload of
these guys with the axes. 400 limit. Or just like 40 archers. Okay. Let's see what happens.
And three. Two. One. Go. Okay. Shoot. That way. Wait. What? Alright. Stop breaking up formation.
Get over here. How the fuck are you supposed to do this? This is impossible for humans to beat this.
This is actually impossible. Can I do weapons? Alright. I'm going to scatter around. We're going
to do the knights. We'll do like, okay, knights. One. Two. Like some over here. We'll do some
Spartan warriors over here. Right at the front. Okay. Archers are going to go back here. And then
I'm going to get some of these guys just to be right here. Just to get attacked. Okay. Let's try
that. It's kind of working. Fucking hippo. What happened to the hippo? This is so stupid. Okay.
That was dumb. But I got it. This one is aliens. Why did I say that so weird? Aliens? Bugs. Alright.
We're just going to load up a shitload of these. Watch out for these mutants. The mutant like
sucker things. Get them. Mom, we have tabs at home. I like this. This is cool. I think we're
going to do a phalanx or riot. Alright. I'll do a phalanx. There are dinosaurs. Alright. You know
what? You know what? I'm ready. I'm ready. Where should we go? Is it just green? Just small green.
Grassland. Time of day. It's going to be noon. Looks good. Victory condition is death match.
Uh, player army limits. Holy shit, dude. That's a lot. Pathfinding. Animals will move in a straight
line. Yeah, we'll do gambling. You guys can gamble on these. Wind effect. Amuro. Animal weapons and
armor. Alright. Alright. Let's go for it. This is the battle. Okay. Animal base. Holy shit, dude.
This just got so much more interesting. Alright. Unicreator. Let's do animal base. How about a
modern mammal? Alright. A rhinosaur. A rhinosaur body. What side are they on, by the way? Team one.
Okay. I want, I want it to be big. How do I make it big? AI mode. Detection distance multiplier. How
do I make it bigger? Can I make this thing bigger? Can I scale it up? How do I make it bigger?
Robotic base. Okay. A head. Wheel. It's the wheel. Wheel for scale. It doesn't work. Wheel? Wheel
just spins. Alt scroll wheel for scale. There we go. Okay. Thank you. Okay. Wonderful. Okay.
Now let's go back to body. Uh, how do I just select this guy? Or so. No, I don't need to
torso limbs. Alright. How about arms? These are huge. These are way too big. Okay. Shit, it's
backwards. Okay. Well, it's backwards, but whatever. Weapons. Decorations. Armor. Gear. Okay. That looks
alright. And this one looks good. Okay. That's team one. Now I want team two. Team two is going
to be animal base. This weird like frog thing. Animal scaling not recommended. Don't tell me what
to do. It's a giant alligator. Okay. And you need a head. Uh, okay. Head. Just messing around. Okay.
Plasma beam T-Rex. Okay. So that's, those are the two captains. So this, you're, on the right side,
we're going to have two brontosaurus and three tiny triceratops. That's team captain right there.
So now over here, let's do spiders and shit. Yeah. Alright. Two huge scorpions. It's got to be fair.
And then three polar bears. No. One moderately sized polar bear. I think that's good for now.
Alright. So you guys ready? Here's the first fight I want to do. See what happens. Team one or team
two. Give the big guys more HP. Oh, that's a good idea. That's true. How do I do that? Can I select
a unit? How do I select? Oh, let me just select the unit. Where are the bugs? Where are the bugs?
Okay. Emperor scorpion. Okay. So, but how do I, is this going to do it for the whole team?
Cancel bet. Why? What? AI mode default. HP multiplier. I don't think I can do anything
about it. It's before you place it. Oh, okay. So we'll do HP multiplier five for the big ones.
Okay. HP multiplier five, attack multiplier three. The big guys. I, I'm not, I'm not remaking these
guys. So that's too bad. We're just going to make a polar bear. HP multiplier five. All right.
Modern mammals. Okay. Polar bear. All right. It was a moderately size. It was, what was it? 1.1,
right? Doing two. It was 1.1. It was 1.1. What was it? 1.1 or 1.2? It was 1.1. That's fine.
All right. Now let's go over here. Let's change these guys. Five, three. Okay. Now I need the
three little triceratopsis. What were they? 0.3? 0.2 or 0.3? And these guys are going to be two
with attack multiplier one. Cause there's more of them. That's fair. It was 0.3. Okay. Oh,
fuck. This is the wrong team. Okay. Who will win? No refunds. You know what I'm doing. I'll get it
right. Team two. Team, I got team two. All right. Team two, team two, team two, team two. Five,
three. All right. Are you ready? All right. Team one. I want to show, I want to see team one.
Team two, team one. All right. Are you guys ready? In three, two, one. Action. Team one kind of
got, wait, hold on a minute. It's still a fight. Shit. This is so stupid. The polar bear died
instantly. Why? Oh wait, it's anybody's game right now. It's the scorpions versus the broncos
versus. Oh, team two wins. It wasn't even close. All right. How about this one? A tetrazyrus,
a gigantic tetrazyrus with attack multiplier of 10 and health multiplier of 10 versus
fucking 5,000 snakes. It's going to do one stomp. I don't think it's going to be one stomp.
Can I actually even fit 5,000 snakes on here? All right. It's starting to lag. Oh man. It's lagging.
3090 omega low. Oh fuck. I can't do anymore. We'll say three. I can't do that much more.
How about, how does 300 sound? I'm going to overheat the 3090. Okay. 300 snakes is enough.
Okay. I got to get the camera somewhere where I don't have to move it because I'm not going
to be able to. Okay. Here we go. Are you ready? Up there attack so it's fair. No, up there attack.
Why? One, two, three. Where are they going? Is he just stepping on them?
I can't tell who's winning. Are these all snake bodies? Some snakes are dead. I can't tell.
They're just like a plate of ramen. A potato computer. No, I don't have a potato computer.
My CPU. Oh God. My poor CPU. I see blood. He's too big for them to hit.
Oh, what an epic battle. Listen to this big drop incoming. I think he killed them.
I don't think this is going to, this is going to, yeah, this is going to take a long time.
He's not even attacking anything. Is nothing dying? Is there a fast forward? I smell smoke.
That's funny. They're pushing it towards the edge. Wait, no, they're running away.
I don't know what to do about this. Should we just call this one a draw?
No? What do you mean no? It's obviously not a draw. Yeah, well, no one's really winning either.
Although there is a big mess of snakes over there. They all died in the same spot.
But there's a shitload of movement though. Are those dead or alive? I think those are dead.
It's just a mat of hair from like the barber shop. Press H. H for health. Oh my fucking God.
This is going to take forever. They can't even like, it can't even hurt each other guys.
Refund. Refund. They can't even hurt each other. They can't hurt each other. It's refund. Refunded.
I can't end the battle. There we go. Okay. Good. Holy shit. All right. Delete all this crap.
Clear it. Clear it all. Okay. Wow. All right. That's better. Okay. Let's do another one.
How about, let's do something easy, right? Something simple. I'm thinking saltwater
crocodile. A little bit bigger than that. One, let's do 2.0 scale. HP, crocodile would have a
little bit more HP, I think. Let's go with five and then attack multiplier two. Slow. Versus Komodo
dragon. Komodo dragon would be a little bit less HP. I think it would hurt a little bit. Then we
hit a little harder. Okay. Who wins? Komodo dragon or alligator? You didn't apply the multipliers?
I thought I did. Didn't I? I didn't change the alligator. Alligator was five HP, but two attack.
2.0. Yeah. All right. Which one is which? Team two is the Komodo dragon. Rock one was one attack.
All right. Here we go. Three, two. Let's get a good view of this. I want like a fucking
national geographic view. Three, two, one. Go. Oh shit. Oh, the Komodo dragon's done for.
What? He won. Damn. Okay. All right. All right. Let's do, how about this? All right. How about,
okay. I'm going to make two different animals. Let's do humanoid. Okay. I want like human legs.
By the way, HP multiplier of three, attack multiplier of five. No, HP multiplier of 10.
Is it going to be kind of a human character? Big legs, strong, very quick, fast moving. Then
we need some torsos here. All right. Humanoid, humanoid torso. It's like plate armor. All right.
Carnivore plate armor. Okay. Uh, limbs. Let's go with wings. Yeah. Like these like big ass bat
wings. Okay. Oh, attack multiplier of one, three. Okay. Now let's do a tail. Tail's a little bit
weak. Attack multiplier of one is fine. Okay. Now let's do, uh, arms. Limbs. Let's do like a sword
hand. This one. Attack multiplier, by the way, this attack multiplier of five. And then I need
a shield hand. All right. Fine. I'll just take a little random like weird claw. Attack multiplier,
by the way, of zero. How are we going? Weapons. Isn't there a handgun? FPS weapons. Okay. Is it
going to be a handgun? Oh, a shotgun. That's, that's available over here, by the way. Two
shotguns are available to use. Fix the wings? What's wrong with the wings? Okay. This is,
okay. This is literally one of the monsters from Power Rangers. Big head. No, I don't want it to be
too big. Attack multiplier for the head is going to be two because there's going to be a bite. All
right. You're kind of a skexy. That's all right. I think this one's ready to go. Any other accessories
or armor? Oh my, can I put this on your head? No, I don't think I can. All right. I can give you this.
I have a trash can and you can have little knee pads too. Okay. Not bad. You look good. How about
gear? Decorations? Absolutely. Sunglasses? I don't think these are going to stay on. Okay.
What about hats? This is like a teen dinosaur and like a kid's cartoon. All right. That's it
for you. Good luck. I wish you the best of luck. Now we're going to go over here. Team two. Animal
base. Arnivorous dinosaur. Okay. Spin neuron. I'm going to do, I'm going to say two of these,
which then we'll give a torso. Okay. Let's do humanoid torso. Does this count as two people?
Or can I fuse them together? Okay. I can't, I can't fuse them together. All right. Hold on. Weapons
one. Okay. Better idea. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Stand back up. Stand up. Oh God. All right. I'm
going to redo it. I just want a torso with like a thousand like murder tentacles. Animal base. All
right. Here we go. This is what I want. Okay. Good. Now we want torso. Humanoid. Back multiplier
of one. Okay. That looks good. Don't fall over. Is it going to fall over? Back multiplier of four
for these. Okay. This is fucking deranged. Why? Okay. All right. The head's going to be like a two.
That looks, it does not look good. That does not look okay. I definitely can't put the head here.
That's for sure. Cause I was thinking about that too. That was the place I was going to put it.
You can't do a snake. Okay. That's fine. I was the, is the elephant going to look just as bad?
You're so immature. I didn't do it. I just stated it was possible. That's fine. Okay. Now what about
weapons and shit? Decorations? Sparkles? We just have LEDs. Okay. God damn it. I'm fine. This got
so mad for no reason. Now he's going to go in the back. Are you ready to place your bets? Let's
remind everybody what team everybody's on. Team one is, I don't remember. I actually don't remember.
Team two is the cool radical dinosaur, I think. I don't remember. Nice third grade arts and crafts
project. Team one is left. Are you sure? That's wrong. What? Wait, wait, wait, wait. Team one is
the rad dino. Let me just make sure. All right. Yeah. Team one is rad dino. Team two is a serious
Sam torso guy. They both pretty evenly matched, I think. Team one is over here. Team two is over
here. All right. Are you guys ready? Get a good view. Pull it back a little. In three, two, one.
Let's go. Oh Jesus Christ. Oh, he got him down. He got him down. He got him down. He got him down.
He's got him down. Him on his back is bad. That's real bad. He's just stabbing him in the chest.
Oh no. One. Team two is the winner. That's close. Nobody picked up the shotguns. I mean he did get
stabbed with every spear tentacle in the head. Every single one landed in his head. It was over
from the very beginning. Okay. So you know how this works, right? Team two moves on. Team one is
eliminated. Now we bring in a new character. All right. How do you guys feel about... Let's
just see if we can... How about lava golem? What do you think? You think he's got what it takes
versus a fucking giant lava golem? What do you think? How confident are you in this?
HP at 10, attack multiplier five. That works. I wonder. He deserves upgrades if he wins? No,
I don't think so. Upgrade the winner. I don't think that's fair. That's J. Starting HP 20,000.
Holy shit. That's a lot. Okay. His HP multiplier has to be like eight. That's unfair. Okay. HP
multiplier of six, five. All right. It's a little bit of a challenge. What do you think?
Give the lava monster a gun. I would love to. I can't hand it to him. I can just put it in front
of him. The lava monster with a gun? All right. So you got team one. Lava monster with a weapon
available. Or you've got the one that won last time. Patch it? I don't think I can. Oh, they're
only for your FPS character. Yeah, we'll have the health bars on this whole time. Lava monster needs
a hat. That's true. Okay. All right. Good luck. In three. Hold on. Let me get a good view. I'm
going to keep the health bars on so it's not a mystery. Three, two, one, action. Oh shit. Not
looking good. He's got him up in the air though. Oh, he's on the ground. Bad. Oh, he tripped. He
tripped over him. He tripped over him. He's got him by the leg. He's got him by his leg. He's going
to get him up just because of the leg only. He's stuck in his foot. Oh shit. He's going to win.
That's going to be close. Oh, he actually beat him. No way. That was close. He got the tendril
stuck in his foot. I did not think he was going to win that. You're eliminated. You're out. Okay.
How about the knockout artist? Okay. How about King? King Kung? Okay. King? King? Uh, we know
we need an attack multiplier of HP multiplier of seven, attack multiplier of six. Okay. He needs
upgrades. The winner gets the loser's hat. That's a great idea. Add weapons. I can't for these guys.
No, I want sunglasses. I want a different hat too. Give me a crown. I like the Santa hat.
You already have a Santa hat. What a crown for the king. After this, if he wins three in a row,
he gets the crown. All right. It's time. You guys ready? Team one is the gorilla. Team two is uh,
I don't know. What do we name them? Guns and unit creator weapons too. Can they use these? Oh man.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Um, not for this one. I'm not going to throw a flame throw on the chest right
now. No, not happening. Okay. You ready? Three, two, one, go. Well, that's a bad start. He can't
even walk. Holy shit. Oh no, he's going to drop him out of the arena. Wait a minute. Does that
count as a tie? Oh, I don't know who wins. Who won? Who won? Does that count as a tie?
It says I lost. So technically that's team two wins. It's a ring out. Oh God. Team one lost.
Yeah, it's a ring out. The monkey fell out first. That's uh, that we watched. It's a rematch.
All right, we'll do a rematch and I'll give it to you this way. Ready? This is what we'll do.
We'll prevent that from happening again. How confident are you now still
that the gorilla can take him on? Do you have confidence still? I'm not, I don't know. I'm
not so sure. You think these walls can hold them? Yeah, I do. What does it look like so far?
This is very skewed to team two. Do a cage match. We'll leave this for now. I'll do a cage match
later. Who will win? It's insanely skewed. This, look at the, look at how you, no confidence in
the gorilla at all. Even with the wall back there. This is, some of you guys have a chance to win
big right now and I mean big. Like really big. Because if this happens, holy shit,
some of you guys are going to get a major payout. Let's go. Three, two, wait, hold on,
it's still going. The gorilla sucks. I don't know. All it takes is one big punch to the face and
it's over. One, two, um. No, it's gonna happen again. He's gonna, no, he's gonna just fall out.
He's still in, he's still in. He's still in it. Oh my god, he sucks. Holy shit, he's bad.
He was really bad. Why is he, why can he not walk? Why does he have so much trouble moving? He was
trying to go for this double axe handle move and he couldn't even do it to anything. All right,
goodbye. He moves on again and this time he gets glasses. I don't know if anyone's gonna be able
to beat him. He seems like, it seems too good. I can't put these on. This looks like I'm at the
beach with my grandpa. They're just lying back in the lounge chair. We got here 10 minutes ago.
Just asleep already. And they wake up when it's time to leave. Those are team one glasses? Oh,
okay. Does that matter? All right, it's time for another, all right, this time I'm gonna create
something. We gotta, we have to rival this because he can't stick around this whole time.
This one's gonna have a weapon, but I'm gonna make it fair. How's, I don't know how this works.
Wrong team? Oh shit, okay. Attack multiplier, machine gun, attack power two, okay. Oh shit,
I needed to, whoops. Oh fuck it, it's gonna be just static on the ground. Anything else I wanna do?
Limbs? Okay, maybe he can fly. This can fly motherfucker, here let's go. So it doesn't do
that much damage but has a huge advantage. It can't walk, important to know. Press J.
Some attached weapons have attack multiplier not set to one. That's fine. Only a thousand starting
HP though? Oh, this is really, okay. Okay, so this thing has a thousand health, but will it just blow
this guy away in five seconds? Raises HP. I, can I even at this point? I don't know, I don't know.
I can't, it's too late. I already bet, that's where we're already in. Look, he, okay, this is
one of those scenarios where he's gonna surprise you and he's gonna die immediately. Or he has a
thousand health, he's gonna shoot in and miss like five times and he's gonna stab in the head
and die. Here we go, ready? Three, two, one, let's get a good view. Action. Oh my god! Wow,
did the Tesla coil even do anything? Look at the wings. He's gone and he gets to have his,
he had a funny hat on. Damn, I didn't, okay. All right, so he gets his hat. More guns?
All right, we need to, we need to, oh, that's team one, god damn it. Okay, how about,
we have to dethrone this guy. All right, animal base, liven. We're gonna do attack,
let's see, what is the attack multiplier? Starting HP 2000. Okay, we're gonna do,
this is gonna be tricky. HP multiplier, so he's gonna have, he's got 7,000 HP. Okay, no, you know
what? We'll have him have more HP. 8,000. Well, hold on, don't, who will win? You don't even know
who it is yet. Oh, wait, team two, okay. Why you, you don't even know who it is? Why are you voting?
Okay, wyvern body, we're gonna do with the intelligence of a fucking man. And I mean,
this is tricky, this is where it gets weird for you guys. This is gonna have human intelligence.
Take that off, it's too heavy. Okay, I don't know about this guy. Okay, oh, and what's that? Two
plasma beam T-Rexes on his, on his front that do two attack multiplier times two. And he's got a
flamethrower on his forehead. This thing, by the way, this shit does fucking 10 attack multiplier,
but it is really small. You gotta get in real fucking close for that one. And then we're gonna
give him, that's it, that's it. Team one is wyvern, team two is our champion. Tail? No, no tail.
I think you guys seriously underestimate the fact that he has a flamethrower on his head.
That is a times 10 attack multiplier. If he gets in close, it's over. Where's his hat? I can't put
that on him. Okay, that's the flamethrower. Yeah, that is the flamethrower. That's a good call. All
right, we ready? Good view. See all the action. Let's do it. Three, two, one, go. Okay, those are
strong. Those are really strong. Those are very strong. I don't even know where he's flying.
It's a victory lap. Okay, well, that was, here's your new hero. Down goes the giraffe. All right,
let's get another contender. Say goodbye. All right, team two. Let's see if he can handle one
of the, one of these. For instance, how about like gore hammer? Gore hammer. Attack HP multiplier of
10, attack multiplier of five. You think you can handle gore hammer? Team two is gore hammer,
team one. Let's take a look. That's pretty evenly matched. Gore hammer does not look that sturdy.
I will make sure that everybody watching is aware of this. Gore hammer may not actually be able to
move. Okay, gore needs ranged weapons, but we don't, you don't know that. I'm taking the odds
on this one. Good luck. Look, I hope he runs in there and just hits the hammer down and just kills
him with a headshot. All right, here we go. Actually, a lot of people are voting for it.
Not really though. All right, remember team two is the gorilla. Oh, that's the previous one. Oh,
okay. Ready? Three, two, one, go. He can only shoot those once. All he has to do is get the
hammer over there and hit him one time. He's flying away. He's flying away. I have to nerf this guy.
All right, well, it's not over yet. Okay, that was fucking pathetic. That was pathetic. That was
pathetic, but here we go. I'm going to do, I'm going to do you, uh, I'm going to, this is going
to make this really hard for you guys because I don't know what's going to happen. So I'm going
to make it really hard for you. Team two, HP multiplier of 10, attack multiplier of 10, two,
two 3.0 for the hammer with 10, 10 times 10. What do you think? If they can walk, it's going to be
very interesting. The two, the hammer brothers make a 1.0 hammer so he can actually move. I think
they'll be able to move 3.0. They were like 5.0 before. That's asking for a lot. We'll see. I
don't know what's going to happen if they can actually walk around this tall or this small.
And yeah, Wyvern has a problem. They're already shaking. I'm not telling you how to bet. I didn't
tell you what to bet on. I'm just here. I'm just them seeing this. I didn't tell you what was going
to happen. Imagine voting gorilla. I mean, if it ends up happening, somebody's going to, you guys
are going to, you're going to get a huge payday. Those are, those are more than 10 to one odds.
All right. Here we go. Good luck. 20 to one, three, two, one, go. He can fucking walk.
Interesting. Interesting. Oh my God. It's over. He literally fell down. Wow.
Wow. That's a payout. Team two wins. It took two hammer hits. 8.2 million versus 1.3 million.
All right. So this is going to be, uh, now we're going to do, so the two, these two are champions
with 10, 10 at 3.0. We know that, right? But let's make it a little harder. Let's do an actual like
battle sequence, right? We're going to do, uh, what's the, what's the default for these guys?
Just one, right? Werewolves. Let's do, what's this? What are the stats on you? Six 50, one, one. Okay.
Let's go like this. Werewolves. Let's do one, two, three. Actually, you know what? Let's do HP
multiplier times 10. 10 werewolves versus, oh shit, look at that. 10 werewolves, werewolves versus
most dangerous fucking animal in the world. Hippopotamus. What's their scaling? Okay. Look at
that. Versus five hippopotamus. Five hippopotamus versus 10 werewolves. Make it six. Five is too
much? I don't know, man. I don't think so. I think five is fair. Do three team to make it wacky. I
don't think you can do channel points that way. Do one horse sized duck versus one duck sized horse.
Isn't it a hundred duck sized horses? Team one is a werewolves. Team two is hippopotamus.
You just do a poll. Yeah, but people, there's no stakes. Okay. That was a quick vote. Here we go.
One, two, three. Oh shit. Oh, he took two with them though. They're dumping them. They're just
dumping off the edge. These werewolves, they're, they're smart. They're intelligent. Oh God.
Got a fight going on over there. No, they just dumped them. This is going to be close. This is
going to be close. He's taking three V1 and one V1 over there. What the fuck is he doing?
He just jumped off the cliff on his own. What a fucking moron. All right. Well, he's gone.
These two have to beat this hippo. Okay. Oh no. Fighting for his life on the edge.
One mistake though, when the hippo goes off. This is going to be anybody's game.
No, don't do it. Don't do it. Nice lunge. Oh, could the tables turn? Is he too heavy? I think he's
too heavy. I think the werewolves are doing more damage. Oh, so long King Bowser. Okay. This is
bad news for the werewolves. Oh no. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Don't get cocky. Don't get cocky
hippos. Bad move. Get away from the edge. I'm telling you, he does more damage. They have to
throw him off. That was why they were doing that. The AI was like, we can't win. We got to throw
him off. He's just clinging, holding onto his leg and just biting his arm. Oh shit. This is bad.
Shit. Oh, he's going off. Yeah. He's getting gnawed on both arms and legs. It's over. It's not. He
can't come back from this. It's over. Wait, we've got some friendly fire here. Friendly fire. This
is so stupid. Last ditch effort. Oh, he's gone. Hippos win. Yeah. If the wolves did not just jump
off the edge for no reason, this would have ended a lot differently. Hippos win. All right. We need
to do, we got to put them in a, like we got to block, we got to lock them in. Okay. We got to
lock them in. Fences. Wait, I can make houses? I can make a castle? Wait, what? I put a hippo in a
castle and then have like a bunch of people try to conquer it? Oh, that's not going to work.
I think the team's tiny. Actually, I could probably do it. Do a tower. Okay. Yeah. So,
okay. We're going to put a hippo up here. All right. Hippo is going to go up here.
Okay. One single hippo. Oh yeah. Easy. Easy. Two hippos versus, how about like, I don't know, like
humans? Commando bow. Okay. Versus a bunch of commandos. There's a bunch of tiny commandos.
How about like 500 little tiny commandos? What about your CPU? I'll be all right. Okay. Nevermind.
Two, 250 tiny commandos. Okay. Just kidding. 200 tiny commandos. Okay. Around 200 tiny commandos.
Okay. They have 1500 HP. Their attack multiplier is one. All right. They have to storm the castle.
Good luck. PowerPoint Andy. Give the castle a mortar. No, no. I don't think so. Teams are
backwards. Oh shit. Team one is, oh shit. Team two of the commandos, by the way. Yeah. Team two of
commandos. Team one of hippos. Give the hippos crowns. Absolutely. Okay. And then I want my FPS
avatar up here too. No, actually that's not going to work because I have to die. All right. Let's
do it. Are we ready? Are we good? Are we ready? All right. Three, two, one. The commandos,
it's, it wasn't attached. They're not going to be able to get in here.
They alive? They're in there. Yeah. They're stuck in here. They're slowly getting in. They're slowly
getting out. They're getting out. They're getting out. They're getting out. Oh my god. Well, that
didn't work. Commandos win. Okay. Well, I think I screwed that up a little bit, but whatever.
Now I got to clear this whole thing. Clear it. Clear it. How do I clear this? Clear it. Set wind.
Hold on. New landscape. Okay. Yeah. All right. Coward coal. Can 10 coward coals beat one angry
Joe? We're doing defaults. Team one. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Just one single angry Joe on team two. What do you think? Four hours? Four hours. What do you mean
four hours? Oh, and by the way, did I mention angry Joe has a fucking helmet on? Um, never mind.
All right. It worked. Angry Joe versus 10 cowards. I don't think the cowards even fight, if I'm honest.
Cowards have a shield wall though. That's, you're right. They do. Yes. Left team. The coward is team
one. Joe with the bad is team two. They could push him off. That's true. He's in a really
vulnerable position. All right. Here we go. Three, two, one, go. Uh, the cowards don't even fight.
Although, very important, he might walk him off the cliff. He fucking fell. You're really
hoping for. He falls off the edge here. Uh, it's still possible. Uh oh. Big trip incoming.
He has to do this 10 times. I know. Oh shit. No, not enough. It wasn't enough. One slip up though
and that's it. Nobody can, they can't even attack with their umbrellas. This is an easy win. Hold on.
Don't just say that. It's still time. It's still time for a monumental mistake. This is a real
tragedy for the coward crew. Hold on. No, it's over. This is just slaughter. This is just
slaughter. What was the point of this fight? Uh, it was to see if 10 people could fight this guy and
win, but they don't even fight. And I can't stop it because money is on the line. Channel point money
is on the line. And if there was even a 1% chance that he trips and falls over the edge, I can't
stop it. Oh, nope. There was your, that's the last opportunity. Go wins. All right, new fight.
This time let's do, let's do another hard one. We're going to do berserker gorillas. How about,
you know, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, eight berserkers, 1.5 scaled knockout
artist gorillas. Two of them. 2.0, Wolver, Wolver, Wolverilla, and Goro the Giant. By the way, at,
at 3.0. Can you not stand up? Okay. Wait. And you're going to be 10, you're going to be 5 HP,
two multiplier. Holy shit. He is fucking insane. Nevermind. That's too much. Okay. That's better.
Uh, we lost Wolverilla was 2.0, right? At default 2.0 Wolverilla. You stand over here. All right.
That's team gorilla, team one. So team two. Um, I'm going to throw you a curve ball here.
Bugs versus a bunch of bugs. Way more bugs. Giant praying mantis and a shitload of spiders.
Okay. Praying mantis at 2.0. I'm going to have to give you more multiplier there. Let's go to
one more. Let's do three. The two attack multiplier. And yeah, we'll do, no, no, no.
You know what? Fuck that. How about one, five, five, giant enemy spider. No, 20. Good luck.
And then a shitload of little praying mantises at default. Two, three, four, five, six.
Why are they moving? Why are you moving? Stop moving. What are they moving for?
Why are they moving? Stop moving. Okay. Well, whatever. Six praying mantises and are they
attacking? And then a bunch of little ants. I don't know why they, why are they attacking?
Are they, they're too small? Oh, okay. Hold on. Let me fix this. All right. One medium size
giant praying mantis and then wrong team. Shit. Did I say one? I meant two. And then a shitload
of ants. Tiny. We're talking like 0.2. We're talking like 50 of them. 30 is fine. All right.
The spider is insane. No, they're on the right team. Although look at this guy though. I don't
know. And one worm all the way back. The one giant worm, two giant worms and an extra gorilla. Get
ready. I'm excited for this one. I don't know. I don't want to influence the vote, but I have
what I would pick. I think we have to stay high up for this one. I don't think I can do very much
camera work on this. Wow. All right. I was going to say gorilla because we don't know if he throws
things or not. He might like throw rocks. I don't know. Three, two, one, begin.
What the fuck are you doing? What was he attacking that guy? All right. I don't understand.
They're too big. I think the spiders won, but what happened? Was he on the wrong team?
Was he on the wrong team? No, he's on the right team. He just started swinging at him and slashing
at him. Scimitar guy pulled an ant up. Oh, okay. All right. We're going to try this again with a
more dialed back gorilla or the giant. 2.0. 2.0. Giant enemy, giant enemy spider is going to go to
also to 2.0. No huge shit. It's impossible. No, 3.0. I can do 3.5. 4.0. 3.5. Wait, wait, wait,
wait. Wait, wait, wait. Okay. Good. That means I got a team. God damn one. 2.0. Spin him around
and I want him 10, 10. No, he's got 42 fucking thousand HP. No, let's do four, four. Still way
too much. Two, 84. Okay. Two attack multiplier of two. All right. Now we can actually do it for real
this time. Ready? You guys ready to vote? Show stats. I think it's pretty evenly matched considering
that the bugs do more damage, but the giant enemy spider is way less powerful than Goro.
Let's see. The answer on the right team. Look at the circles. Three, two, one, action.
It is a pull. Okay. Now I understand what happened. All right. Looking good. Just the little bugs.
Don't walk off the edge. Giant enemy spider is currently attacking two gorillas. We still,
look, it's still plenty of game left. Scimitar is still alive. So is Goro the giant. I, this is
Goro's game to win right here, I think. No, they instantly killed him. The bugs win. Fuck. That
wasn't even close. Oh, he's doing like the Peter Griffin family guy thing when a family guy character
falls down. Okay. That was, that was embarrassing how bad that was. They lost very, very, very, very
badly. Can you last versus two? 10, 10. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. How's that?
Good luck. Two, 10, 10. They're Resinosaurus. 12,000? Yeah. It says 12,000, doesn't it?
I don't know if the bird sounds. I, I can't, oh, I just realized what you're talking about.
Oh, and by the way, did you notice? It's really fucking windy out. It's rigged. All right. Wait,
wait, wait. I'll turn, all right. Not, not for this one. For the next one. You're right. That's,
that's just like, you're right. You're right. You're right. Okay. Here we go. One, two, oh,
not yet. I can't turn the bird sounds off. One, two, two and a half. And you guys were concerned
about that. One of them's already dead. Okay. Bugs win. I would be shocked if they won again.
I'm just going to be very clear. And 250 angry Joes, which by the way, by the way, one of them,
captain, he's covered in fucking armor, surrounded with armor and he's going to have guns and weapons
all over him. He's getting into the hockey pads. It was like, he can play with like his big brother.
The Legion of angry Joes with one angry Joe dialed up to a thousand or a couple of bugs.
Oh, we are the gal here in friend tree. We're the ones that stomp on those bugs and camaraderie.
Captain needs a hat. We're ready. That's in three, two, one. Oh shit. One of them went flying.
Holy shit. What? I don't even know what they're attacking. One of them is getting shot with the
machine gun multiple fucking times. He's lighting up. Yeah. That's what I'm talking about. Yeah.
It's a fucking rave. What are they fighting? There's nothing even fighting each other.
Are they trying to hit the bugs on the ground? Oh shit. They're going to make it. Oh fuck. Here
they come. All right. This is there. There's a guy right now going like this, like way in the back.
There's a guy. She's like fucking freaking out over there. Wait, what happened? They won. There's
something. The doors like bending down too. You know, like it's always just like, it's like
their hair is like going fucking crazy. That person's having a good time. A really good time.
Fire the cameraman. All right. Here we go. All right. We'll do.
You got instantly overcrowded. This is too many. All right. Let's get rid of the dance guy angry
Joe's versus commandos. All right. Oh yeah. That's a good, that's a good one. Or how about
like just a, okay. 15 commandos versus 250 Joe's. Wrong team. God damn it.
Okay. And we'll give them a, like a fence or something to hide behind. Attic. Wait,
are these turnstiles? Hold on. I can make them have to go through turnstiles? No. Wind on.
Enough of this one. Hold on. It's fucking good enough. Whatever. Okay. Now we're going to put
mines where the mines missile launcher. Are there mines? Yeah. Then land mines. Okay.
This is quite a bet I would be making. I don't know if I don't know if I would make any of these
bets. I would, I'm going to say right now that I don't, I would not vote for the angry Joe's.
Okay. I'll make it a little better. Okay. There I would not vote for the angry Joe's. This is a
tough one. Let me make it easier for you. Let me make it harder. Actually. Now it's actually a hard
decision and we're going to remove this wall here. Go easy. All right. Let's see. Put your money where
your mouth is then. Team two is commando. Team one is angry Joe. There's way too many Joe's.
I don't know, man. We've seen countless things so far. We've seen things that looked impossible to
fight die instantly. This is a toss up for me. I don't know. On one hand, are they going to get
overwhelmed by the Joe's or on the second hand are all the mines going to blow up and kill everybody
and there's going to be one commando left just sniping all the Joe's running around.
In three, two, one, go. Oh no. They're going to hit the other one. The bodies are in the way.
This is fucking heinous. They can't move because there's too many bodies. Holy shit.
What's with the gas? That was fucking horrible. They just started turning into cement. Human cement.
Oh yeah. Okay. Well, there were too many Joe's. If they weren't that many Joe's, it probably would
have been a little bit closer. Wall of flesh. All right. We're going to get rid of the fucking
landmines are not fair. Let's just be real. We're going to get rid of the landmines. We're going to
keep one landmine right here. We're going to get rid of a bunch of the Joe's and we're going to make
one big Joe. One large Joe who has a two and a two. You ready? No, he needs way more help than that.
Times 20 fucking health multiplier. Times 50 health multiplier. Let's put him far away though.
All right. He's got 10 fucking thousand health. All right. Let's go. Team one is Joe's. Team two
are the commandos. This is too easy now. Well, we'll find out. I have removed a bunch of the Joe's.
Team one Joe, team two commandos. I believe in big Joe. I believe in mega Joe. All right. Here we go.
What happens? Three, two, one. Lock the camera. Go. Well, he slipped. There's an extra mine over
there, but it's okay. It wasn't that bad. Oh, they're reloading. What's with the gas? What the fuck
just happened? What? Wait, what? What happened? What was the gas? They can't get through. Dude,
I'm telling you, if that angry Joe gets over here, it's over. Are they even hitting anybody?
How did they get out? Do not spread out. Are you stupid? Oh, gosh. They're all stuck.
There's too many Joe's again. There's too many dead bodies. He is flopping over here
very slowly. He gets over here, man. It's going to be trouble. Well, they're all dead. Okay. Well,
whatever. Sorry for all the Joe believers. There was an extra landmine. I'm going to delete that
one and delete that one. And we're going to get rid of the fence there. But to make up for it,
they get one of these. That's not going to work. Let's make it fair. Wrong team. It's going to
disaster. They're very vulnerable, but they have a ton of firepower. And we're also going to,
I'm going to remove another like 10 to 20 of them. They stopped getting all bunched up. All right.
Begin the vote. Team two versus team one. You've seen how it plays out. I think we're ready to go.
There's no way that big Joe is going to be able to move. I think he can.
Does it look like pretty even actually. If I had a vote right now, I'm putting it on the commandos.
I'm just going to give you honesty here. They have machine guns and they have blisters on their head.
Three, two, one, go. Uh-oh. Oh, shit. Oh, the gas. The flamethrower instantly killed them.
Damn. I would have lost. Fire is OP. Yeah. I was sleeping. I think the commandos just do the gas.
Oh shit. Big Joe, big Joe almost out. Stupid as shit ever. All right. One, I'll do one more.
One duck sized Joe versus one horse sized, a hundred horse sized ducks, whatever it is.
One duck sized tiger versus a hundred horse sized. I don't know. Get this turned off.
Okay. One duck sized, one horse sized boar versus a hundred duck sized buffalo.
Worst noise runner up. That's fine. I was trying to do a 56K modem. That's what it
started. That sounded like that for a couple of seconds and I was like, well,
fuck it. I'm just going to just really commit to this. All right. Here we go.
Can they wait? Can they walk? Okay. Well, that was fun. All right. I'm done. I'm done. I'll see you
guys tomorrow. We're going to play the pawn shop game tomorrow. We're going to play, uh,
no umbrellas allowed. It's a game where you have to like haggle, sell things, buy things.
It looks really fun. I'll do one more. One more climactic one. Sure. This is going to be the final
time for you to bet as well. Drop sticks. I know. I'll get them. Wrong fucking team. No, it's not.
Right team. Okay. Who do you think went to increase their health? Oh, whatever. Hippo is
two OP. I'll change that. Here we go. Yeah. One more vote. I'm sitting there like, all right,
let's go. It's just a sci-fi channel original. But what if, what if the polar bear had a missile
launcher? It's like, uh, like Pixar movies from like 2001. But what if we made the claws of the
polar bear three inches longer? Then it would kill the hippo. Yeah. Isn't that weird? Not really.
Three, two, one, go. It's not even a contest. Oh my God. Sci-fi channel original.
Oh, that was my biggest bet of the night. Oh, I'm sorry. Okay. I'm going to go. Okay. That's it.
I'm done. But what if we do this? But what if we give the same exact machine gun that we gave the
hippo to the polar bear? Would the polar bear's aerodynamic way of moving prevent the hippo's
slow and coordinated movement from being shot? Let's put it inside of our simulator.
Stay tuned for Kathy Mitchell's copper pan infomercial because this is absolutely airing
at 3 a.m. Are we betting on this one? Keep stalling. I got to get more points.
Don't call Aaron at 3 a.m. No, it would be, we don't call Armin at 3 a.m. That's Armin saying
Aaron. So like it would be you call Armin and Armin thinks it's Aaron calling and it gets it
like really concerned. You've got that bit wrong. All right. Three, two, one, go. It's not even
fucking close. It was close. It was actually kind of close. All right. I'm out of here. Goodbye.
I'm going to get chopsticks in a second. I mean, what the fuck? Wait, why did he win that one?
Why did he win that one? What? Holy shit. He's winning them now. I didn't do anything different.
I just pressed the button. No, no, there's no more betting. There's no more. Maybe too late.
What? No, we're not betting anymore. Too late. Already did it. Already bet. What? I'm leaving.
I'm done. You guys were betting? No, no more betting. No, refund, refund, refund, refund.
I'm not even playing. All right. I'm going to beer up. I'm going to go pee. I'm going to get
the chopsticks, prove that I can use them, give them times 5,000 HP. I can't even do that right
now. We're going to make this fair. We're going to make this absolutely completely fair. We are
going to do hippopotamus. This is the last bet of the night. I make it fucking count. We're going
to do a 4.0 hippopotamus at times 100 multiplier health, more times a thousand multiplier health,
which would give this 900,000 health. And then our polar bear is also going to be the same size.
Was it 4.0? Same distance. Exactly. Different team. Let me redo this because people are going
to get confused. 4.0 polar bear. 500,000 HP. We have to do a little bit more than that.
So he has a million health in the hippopotamus. Team two, 4.0. Although that's not fair. 3.5.
Same distance. Separate team. You've got 1.8 million health. That's not fair. We're going to do
1100. Now they both have just about, there's a small disadvantage. They're just about a million
health each. Plasma. We're going to do missile launchers. You like that strategy? Okay. So that's
mega, mega, mega. That's mega. Mega what? I don't think that's just so powerful just yet.
Fence him in. It's a good boy. Barnacles. Team fucking one for the love of God. Okay. And then
rockets. A ton of them. I gotta redo it. Shit. The hippo looks actually stronger.
Okay. Fence. I need fences. So our mechanical gigantic monster fight. Let's do with a fence.
Okay. Fence. Static. Can't be moved. It has to be fucking huge. Okay. Team one. You know who it is.
Polar bear. More missile and plasma oriented. Team two is the hippo. Heavy machine gun fire
and light cruise missiles. Get a good view. I think right here looks about good. Right about
there. Looks good to me. So this is it. Hippo is two. Right. Hippo is two. Polar bear is one.
And three, two, one. He didn't fall out. He's still in. Oh my God. He's done. It's over.
He's done. He's not getting out of that. They didn't even scratch each other. Oh my God. Well,
that was insane. That was crazy. I'm gonna go get chopsticks. That's the end of the stream pretty
much. I will close the stream out. We'll see you tomorrow for the pawn shop game. Seems like a chill
fun game to experience. So see you tomorrow. Same time. 2 p.m. Pacific. I'll be right back.
I've got my bowl. By the way, this is going to be difficult because I got little carrots that are
wet and slippery. So if I can pick these up, then you know I know what I'm doing. Let me just exit
the game and quit the game. They're little baby carrots and they're wet and they're very slippery.
So let me come back. I'm gonna turn the exposure up. Okay, there we go. Okay, hi. Let's move you
over here. So just wanted to show everybody I've got a bowl with carrots in it and I've got
chopsticks. So as you can see, let's just go ahead and get one of these carrots. It's very simple.
It's very easy as you see. And these are slip. Oh, there's probably hair on it. There's probably
hair on it. They're slippery. There's probably hair on that because like I have like Otto has hair.
They're really slippery. But you get the idea. If this was a piece of sushi, I'd be fine.
I win. What do you mean fraud? What are you talking about? See you tomorrow. Off camera
chopstick double. I told you I could use them. What do you think I am? These are good. They were
a shitload of subs today and I missed a bunch of them. I missed almost all of them. Carrots are
really hard to eat. They take forever. But pawn shop game tomorrow. See you tomorrow. Next week,
we're going to do Sims 3 Mod Hell and Delta Rune. I'm not going to play it tomorrow. I'm going to
play chapter one on my own time to refresh my brain. But we'll see you tomorrow maybe.
Carrots take, oh no, carrots take so fucking long to eat. There we go. I got through them.
Yeah. I want to, how long is it? Okay. So now that it's out, I have a question. So now that
Delta Rune is out, it came out like three or four hours ago. Has anybody beaten it? How long is it?
Do we know? Like have people completed it? I know it just came out like three or four hours ago. But
I'm just kind of, I'm trying to figure out how long the chapter is. Is it less than six hours?
I have not yet. I'm not sure. Probably like four hours based off the last one. Okay. Four to five
hours. Okay. Cool. All right. Yeah. Let's raid somebody. Let's throw a raid out there. I haven't
raided somebody in like three weeks. So let's raid. Who's live? Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Vinny playing Cyberpunk 2077. Do people still play that game? Vinny, Vinny, Vinny. Let's go
say hi to Vinny. What, people still play Cyberpunk? Did they update it? I played Cyberpunk today.
I did not play Cyberpunk today. All right. Well, I'll see you guys tomorrow. Go say hi to Vinny.
Take care of yourselves. Goodbye. Good night. See you later.