Hi, welcome back to another day, another stream. Today, as you know, we're gonna be playing Tiny
Toons Wacky Sports, one of my favorite Super Nintendo games. I probably have as many hours
in Tiny Toons Wacky Sports for the course of my life as I do in Team Fortress. We're talking
thousands of hours from the ages of like 13 to 17. This is like one of the only games I own
for the Super Nintendo, owned when I was younger. Oh no, he referenced it again.
Tiny. Oh, funny. What about the Mickey game? Yeah, the Mickey game's good too. I'm sorry,
excuse me. The magical quest starring Mickey Mouse. He's just in that game. It's the magical quest
starring Mickey Mouse. He better be so fucking good at this game. Oh, I'm gonna be real good
at this game because it's about hitting a button as fast as you can. And we all know I've come
close to that record. And when I beat that guy live on stream, that guy was like number 10 in
the world. I became number nine. Is this where it all began? No, maybe not. Here's some personal
lore for you guys. Friends of mine used to hand me the controller when you needed to press a button
really fast. In Metal Gear Solid 1, there's a point in the game where you have to press the
button as fast as possible. And it is insanely difficult. And in fact, I mean, spoilers,
you have to press a button real fast. That could mean anything. But I used to get handed the
controller. Dude, I need you to do this. And I'd be like, hold on, don't worry, I got this. And I
crack my knuckles and just go. And then I would give it back. Because I'm a one trick pony.
I don't have any I don't have any other tricks. I have one if I was like a MOBA character,
I'd have one move. It would be unload entire clip in three seconds. And it would just do like 6000
damage. And then it would be like a two hour cooldown. You'd only be able to use it once a
game. That's just tracer. I wouldn't even have an auto attack. Oh, you just have to I just have to
walk around. And that one team fight that is really, really important. Just get me in there
and give me the controller and I'll just spam that button. But then I need like a fucking two
hour break, dude. I'm going to bed. I can't walk. That's a second move. What movement is not a move.
Anyways, let's play. This is a game about it's a mini game game. And say this is going to be a
long stream. I'm going to adhere to what we're supposed to be doing. Not eight hour streams
like last night. Play this for a little while. See what happens. This game fucking sucks. You
can't just use that when you want to. You can't just say this game sucks. All right, here we go.
I'm looking forward to this. Hopefully I have my button spam capabilities ready because you have
there are so many cases where you have to spam the button. I'm probably going to get exhausted
in the first 40 minutes. I'm not going to lie to you. Here we go. Is everybody ready? Oh,
I hear the music. Oh my God. We're tiny. We're toony. We're all a little loony. And in this
cartoony, we're invading your TV. We've got all the questions, the questions and expectations
and tiny tune adventures. It's invading your TV. So here at me acres, we're enjoying your TV.
We've been learning farts since 1933. Expect the unexpected. Expect the unexpected. It's tiny
tune adventures. Please enjoy the fun. And now let's keep going. You guys ready? God damn it.
We're tiny. We're toony. I'm not going to fucking do that. Ladies and gentlemen, Montana Max's
sports festival opens grand prize of $1 million. I told you, remember I said Montana Max.
I'm gonna prove that I'm the best athlete in Acme Acres. I'm going to build my own
theater with this prize money with $1 million. I can become a presidential candidate.
What? I can party every day with lots of food. All right. I gotta be Flucky. Flucky's my guy.
That's just a million dollars. No, that's not Taz. That's Dizzy Devil. These are all their kids.
Buster. These are all their children. Flucky Duck. This is Daffy Duck's son. Dizzy Devil. This is
Tasmanian Devil's son. Babs Bunny. No, they're not. They were supposed to be the new generation
of... Here's what happened. Let me explain. Looney Tunes came out and then they said, fuck,
we need a new generation of cartoon Looney Tunes. It's been like 75 years. Let's have like young...
Oh, here's like the new generation. Flucky Duck instead of Daffy Duck. Dizzy Devil.
And then they did it again, which you don't know in the last probably five years with the Teen
Titans. Teen Titans are now the Looney Tunes of the current generation.
That's Robin is Flucky Duck's son. That is Mike. The games are about to begin. Let's go. I'm ready
to spam. I'm ready to fucking spam. The first event is Ice Cream Throw at Wacky Land. Wait,
this is not a spam one. Instant loss. Throw the ice cream at the targets as they come out. If you hit
them in a row without missing, you'll get the big points. Okay. Throw, throw ice cream, move.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm ready. I got to get 250 points to qualify. I'm ready. And then it goes...
The best song. Where's the OST for this shit? Not this one. I mean,
how many of the X's? I just have to beat these fucking losers. That's all that matters. See,
what an idiot. Hit all the irons. 20 points. No! Sorry. That's why I screamed.
Oh my god. Okay, this is fucking hard. I forgot how hard this was.
I need 250, right? All right. I smoked them all. I'm good. There we go. I just had to get... Look
at this. Are you kidding me? This is like what happens when like... I'm like a 16-year-old
playing in the Little League. Like my parents lied about my age. Oh, he has 60 home runs this year?
Yeah, he's 12. Oh, are you sure he's not like 15? No, that's my son. He's good.
Wow. Zero points. Bad. Come on. Usually I'm the one over there in that next ranking.
You know what I mean? Usually I have to look at the guy next to me that has a thousand points.
Not this time. I think this is... If I remember, this is like a Mario Party where they give out
points at the end for like how many times you got hit in the head or something. Chicken Race
at Acne Canyon. Good luck. Use the power gauge to set the strength of the rubber band and run
towards the cliff. Try to stop as close to the edge of the cliff as you possibly can.
You can only use your brakes once. Be careful. You fall to fouls. Imagine a game where they
launched you at a cliff and you had to stop. Here we go. All right. Stop. Okay. Be cautious
this time. Second try. Okay. It's 250 to qualify. I have to get 250. I'm not going to go that fast.
That was the problem. I went into red. How did I take that? 290. I'm good. Chicken Dash. 290.
Speed bonus. Boopy prize. Okay. Wait. Buster's getting up kind of close. I don't like where he
is. Third event is weightlifting at the TV station. Good luck. All right. I got to listen up to this
one. It's all about saving that power gauge. You lift the barrel before the others. You make three
lifts. You get the top points. If you're too slow, you're out of the competition. Save up a lot of
strength or you'll drop the barbell. Yeah. You just have to power. Just lift. It's not about
getting the little ones. It's about getting one huge one. Fuck. Out of here. I went. Oh, hand me
the controller, Jeremy. Look at how fucking huge. That's how huge I am. He's just the Hulk. 110.
Oh, wow. Buster failed. Buster couldn't even do it. 750 subs. Wait. What? We have to do it twice?
Okay. Well, it doesn't even matter. I destroyed it. Let me see if I can get it in one go.
Shit. It doesn't matter. You got to get it right on that needle. Buster didn't even try. Can we do
it again? Should I just not even pick it up? I've already qualified for the playoffs. Oh,
it's just me and her. Wait a minute. I went. One try. First fucking try. I just threw that
thing into the ceiling. That's guaranteed that I win. Oh, no. Just challenge. What do you mean
challenge? My arms are already tired. How did I do this when I was a kid for like fucking six
straight hours? How did I do this when I was a kid? How? My arms. I already need to be relieved
already. Stretch it out. Okay. I've won. I did so well in the first few competitions that
saucer throw. Okay. Then I can just literally throw this one in the ground and I just still win.
Power gauge and go around the circle. Decide the angle and let it go.
Don't throw it out of bounds. Go to the bathroom. I'm good. All right. They have all 321.
Here we go. How much time do I have?
There we go. That's not coming back. That thing's going to get picked up by gravity.
Okay. I don't want it. Second try. Oh my God. Why did I think I still had a 14-year-old body?
I was like growing up. I was growing. My bones were strong. I was drinking milk every day.
I was like 15. I was strong. 16. I could pick up a fucking car. Midlife crisis.
No, there's no such thing as a midlife crisis for me. All right. This is...
I win. Fifth event is obstacle course at Acme Acres. Good luck, everyone.
Thing is though, I have to destroy this because it keeps getting up. It keeps ramping up in
difficulty and the events change to be way harder. Run collect as many items as you can.
Pump your opponents. Avoid Elmyra and hit by jumping. Oh, how do you jump? Wait, how do I
control it? How do you control? Just run? I don't understand. I don't know how you run.
Why do I keep falling back? Is it A? Why do I keep just falling backwards? What do I have to press?
It's X. It's fucking X. Okay. No. Come back at the sentry right here. Give me this shit.
I just have to beat the fat guy. That's all I care about. I have to beat this fat guy.
Did I win? Oh, I can't brawl. Whatever. It's okay. It don't matter. I can cure it.
If I didn't get a jump bonus, trip bonus. Oh, I fell down the most time. Okay, boss. So you
can't even sniff my score. That's how far away I am. Last competition. Birdman contest
in the tropics. Good luck. Fly as fast as you can. If you get a certain number of targets,
you can climb a wire and then aim for Montana Max's mansion. Speed, brake. Okay. It's just speed
and brake. That's it. There's only two things. Do I have to spam first? No. Okay. Just apply.
Okay. How does any other character fly in this game? Take the brakes. Oh, it's time. I have a
time limit. Wait, can I do it? I'm trying to land it up. Cut it. Cut it. Cut the wheel.
Why didn't I take the parachute off? Why wouldn't I take the... Wait, was I just going to...
I would just die. What was I expecting to happen there? Smash into his ceiling and instantly die?
I got to figure... I mean, I don't... What would have happened? It's not like you lost because you
lived. All right. Number one. Maybe. Because he doesn't even get a place on the board. Password.
Okay. Somebody remember that. Write that down. It's Wile E. Coyote Jr., Road Runner Jr., and
Montana Max. All right. Somebody remember that. Next, try the normal course. Do your best.
We keep upgrading. The first event is Ski Race. Let's do our best. Ski down the hill and grab as
many point flags as you can. You can jump and land on the others to slow them down.
If you turn into a snowball, you'll be out of control. It's just move and jump. That's it.
No, it's just move around and collect the flags. Get out of here. Don't fall off the edge.
That's 30 points, but what? All right. Now just be conservative with this.
Destroying them. Dude, I'm fucking liking this song. Put your hand down. I can't.
I put your fucking... I can't fucking put my hand down. This is a generic face sign. Yeah.
I mean, it's... It is because you can always tell when there's a really generic face line
when the bass guitar is just counting to seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Well, this is... I'm doing...
I need the points because you know I'm going to fuck something up eventually. Eventually,
it can't be this good the whole time. I remember the log cutting one. There's a wood cutting
composition eventually in it. It always fucked me up and I always get so angry. Give me like a
thousand points. What the fuck? I want 500 points. 500 points or I'm going to uninstall the game.
It's not like on Steam. I'm going to get a Steam refund. Come on, speed it up a little bit. Let's
get that bass line. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. You can count to eight. Am I?
What does the booby bonus mean? Booby prize. No one gets it. What is it? Chicken race. Oh, no.
Okay, so it's 300 to qualify. This is the run killer. This is the run killer. I need 300.
Yeah, we got it. Max is 400. Hey, super frog. Thank you Burnout for that. I don't know why I
even said that. I'm so used to just doing that. Thanks for the five community subs, Burnout.
I don't know why I did that. Thank you Burnout for the five subs. 350, good. That's not super
good. Zero and zero for Dizzy. I feel bad for Dizzy. All right, still in the lead by a lot.
I can really easily lose this if I fuck up a whole entire event. Ice cream throw. Uh-oh.
Okay, just be good. 350 to qualify for this ice cream throw. It's not all there. He's fine.
Did they give me a head start? That's a risky move over there. Fuck, I was going for that one.
Nice. They all fucked up. I got it. I qualified. The fuck? Hey. Hey, don't have a fuck with the
guy whose main weapon in Team Fortress was the Huntsman. Bleeding targets. Blue plate special.
Oh, and there he is. Super frog. Thank you Super Bruce for the five community subs.
Super Bruce five subs. Use the Luxman. What? You guys want to give me shit for being the guy that
every time that cough nucleus showed up. I just played Huntsman the whole time and just aimed at
that area where you could shoot down that long winding hallway into where the people spawned out
the door. Just get a headshot every eight seconds. But am I the bad, am I a bad guy for that?
Apparently. Bull vault. Gather your speed by hitting the buttons and plant the pole and decide the
angle and you're off. Try to catch as many stars as you can. If you miss a jump, it's a foul. Hold on.
I wear one, power two. Do I have to alternate? Shit. I don't know what to do.
To alternate or do I just spam? Whoa! I missed. Oh shit. I didn't go for the pole.
Does it matter? I can't move over this way. I landed. Oh shit, don't even matter. I went under
the pole. I got to land on the squishy thing. All right, it's fine. I can lose this. I don't care.
Wait, what's the qualify? 300? Holy shit. Wait, get these pink ones. Get a pink one. Yes. 410.
All right, just land on the thing. Where's the thing? Where's the thing? I don't know what the
thing is. I win. I like this song. Landing bonus. Boobie prize. Hey, Duke. Thanks for the five
community subs. You're good. Thank you. Five subs. Rolling in. Fifth event is weightlifting.
Do our best. All right. I'm usually really good at this shit. I want to blow this thing.
Do weightlifting. Got to get three lifts. Not on easy mode. It's on normal mode.
Oh, lost her pretty good. I want to see Dizzy's evolution. We never get to see it. We just get
to see the germ of Pluto face. I did this three times. Wait. Oh, he's out forever. I feel bad.
All right. I have to win. How did I get gifted if I'm not watching? How does that work?
What are you trying to prove by playing this game? Do I have to be in a constant state of proving
myself? What? Why? Don't you know every single second of every day is a constant?
You need to prove something to someone else. I can't let him fucking beat me. Oh, that was bad.
Oh. Okay. He's trying to prove. What would I want to prove with this? Hey, guys, you know,
I just want to tell you this. Super Nintendo, I can hit the button real fast. I mean,
I've already proved that. You already know that. What else do I have to prove? You're seeing it.
Literally ban that person. I said that. Look at that. Am I trying to prove that?
What are you trying to prove? That's so funny. Here we go. Saucer throw. I really got to you, huh?
What do you want? What? We will just be like, oh, I'm trying to do that. I want everyone to like me.
Can everybody like me now? Look at how fast I can press the button. Do you like me?
Oh, fuck. Tasmanian Devil Spinner. Go home. No. No. You don't as a 35 year old man,
try to gain respect by playing Tiny Toon Adventures for the Super Nintendo. What are
you talking about? Shit. Don't go out of bounds. Don't go out of bounds. Don't go out of bounds.
Right on the line. Oh, what are you talking about? It's not a foul ball that's in the poll. That's
inside. I lost. What was it? 250. Oh shit. What happened? Oh, you can't. I got to continue. I'm
fine. I'm good. All right. Saucer throw. Let's go. You get three chances. I'm losing respect.
I get that respect back, please. When I cross 400 points,
I'm about to. That's got to be a little bit right in the middle.
Right there. Right there. Wine drive. Inbound. Yeah. More respect. Give it to me. Oh yeah.
Hot box my room with respect. Feed off of it. I live off of it. I need it. Obstacle course.
This is the one I fucked up last time. Run. Collect the items. Don't get grabbed by Elmira.
Move. Yeah. Run. Jump. Okay. I'm like, what do I need to qualify? 300.
I can't even fucking see where I am. Give me that coin. What the fuck keeps happening?
How am I losing points? Dude, this competition is a fucking mess. Don't let Elmira touch you.
Die if she touches you. Whatever it is. Come on. Give me another piece of meat.
Come on. One more. All right. Just don't. I did it. Just barely. Holy shit. None of them qualified.
That's not even fair. Look at how badly tuned that qualification is. Half your participants
don't qualify. Come on. Here we go. Last is bungee jump at Montana Max's mansion.
Do our best. Okay. I need 550 points to qualify. Wrap a bungee rope around your body.
Aim for the targets in Geronimo. How many bonus panels can you touch? The time limit.
Elmira or Montana Max grab you. They'll slow you down. Be careful. Power and run. Power and jump.
I remember this shit. Hey, you gotta... I'm gonna go right here.
Don't touch Elmira. Extend. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points.
Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points. Points.
All right. We're good. How much time do I have? I'm gonna go right side.
Don't go too fast. Don't touch that. Double speed. Don't touch it. Oh, shit. Okay. I guess
stop being conservative over here. Right here. Right back down. Right back down. Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go. The whole line of 30s right here. In there. Hens. Oh, I almost just
touched the lost... All right. What do I need? Extend that time.
Okay. I got how much do I need? The fuck up? I need 20 points. Where... Just drop, drop, drop,
drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop,
drop, drop, drop, drop, drop in there. I see the right there. In the corner. Top left corner.
Holy shit. Thank God. Wait a minute. Was it 500 or 500? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
wait give me something oh my god thank goodness it's 550 i almost just lost my mind thank
god oh i got all these bonds i'm fine get it on normal now where where it gets to be
uncompletable the events coming up now it's not they're not completed uh uh daisy duck
duck the tweety bird and lucky i don't i don't know them all duke nukem another five community
subs thank you for the five subs here we go ah this is the one this is the one i remember
this one i remember hating this use the power gauge and cut as many logs as you can you are
very strong you can cut through more than one in one stroke it's like a huge swing it hurts
it hurts okay i need to go i hate this one oh i can't i've been doing it for too long
thank you he killed me they didn't tell us that in the beginning of this saw movie
make your choice unbelievable i might still qualify for like no missing holy fuck i win
speed bonus over 30 pounds oh hell yeah i'm not i gotta be on the ball okay it's the chicken
race chicken race this is 350 to qualify that's it's getting higher this is a rogue light
i'm gonna stop at 30 oh way before that especially going that fast like 40 i just think 350
this liquid all over my controller i think i spit all over the controller
oh no all right i got three continues there was a little sneeze character what's the sneeze
character what's that character's name you just save scum this we have to save some already
okay
my hands all right my middle ring and pinky finger are out we're we're only index now
i've lost a few steps oh yeah this dude has wicked calloused hands
oh i'm from spamming all right i'm currently in the last place swimming race i don't remember
this one at all swim skillfully and grab as many items as you can be careful or you'll run out of
breath you won't be able to swim you catch the big air bubbles you can get a whole breath of air
while still underwater oh that's your breath oh my god why are you guys not getting the points
buster is dying do you actually get by the shark on the bottom of the screen
give me that ammo pearl oh god too much water oh my god i'm winning by so much it's not even
cares holy shit you dropped everything i was down to win it was perfect i'm gonna have
all the points i'm gonna win by a landslide i'm trying did i look at everything what happened
oh i drowned wait i had like 500 points
get it all pick it all up who's can't even has anything left
i tried again how do you drop twice freeze freeze bucky go for air quick bucky you need air
okay i don't think any of us won i mean i had the most points but who fucking cares it's 300
it's 400 what happens if nobody wins speed bonus iron man bonus bogart bonus no okay let's do this
again why won't you say booby prize because no one ever gets it it's at zero every time
all right so here's the plan the plan is just they're they're going to die multiple times
just be there to get the scraps when they come back because it dumps out of their body so just
stay alive and just sit at the bottom like a fucking lobster bc algae i mean they're gonna be
getting this thing 400 right see see all right just stay stay back and now stay back i don't
have any points to lose how am i supposed to get money from them if they don't have any money
i have all the money i have to lose so then i can collect my own money i have everything
i own everything i have i own everything okay now i don't give me give me that
give me that money get it out i want them all at zero
come on all those points get deleted they get deleted that's not how it works
oh shit i still win okay don't get hit by anything what if you lose if you get caught by the if you
die somebody just burns all your money in a backyard doesn't make any sense good i'm gonna
be honest with you uh the blue numbers that's like air water that's not a point number yellow
red orange point number like that's an oxygen number you know what i mean like the the that's
a the blue is an that's an oxygen number for me just right thank you one person that apparently
doesn't think i'm insane for saying that thank you one person for agreeing that the color blue
is synonymous with water just thank you for agreeing with that apparently we have
a bunch of people to think water is orange all right saucer throw it's a power gauge okay 350
it's got to be good this is going to be real good do a taz impression now no
what is the color that i say it is water wait what hold on i gotta pay attention
so that's going to be damn good it's right on target straight ahead good angle too
couldn't have been much better 350 i don't care if i have second place overall not one event
so
look at that high angle too tons of power a little bit higher angle last time it's going to be over
400 what the fuck they do that better i'm still qualified i'm still in first place that's all the
matter what's the rankings the actual rankings yeah i'm still good that's one full event ahead
weight lifting i'm good i'm good i usually i i i smash this shit 550 is the qualification
let's go i gotta get a good one this has got to be good it's gonna be worth it i gotta pee what do i
do he sneezed on me what are you fucking kidding me get away from me all right i'm the only guy
that gets sneezed on i'm the guy that gets sneezed on he comes and sneezes on me doesn't he know and
doesn't he sneeze on anybody else because i'm in first place he's gotta go for the guy in first
right of course you do okay now who's paying that guy i don't i don't got anymore
come on no continues left i there's like four more events i can't mess it up keep an eye
sneeze character fuck that sneeze character how come that didn't affect buster pretended to
sneeze let's see what's watch watch no he's faking it he's pretending to sneeze
just like you pretend to see i don't last okay i promise the last two times i've sneezed i've
not been pretending to sneeze what the fuck get away from me oh is he doesn't even get
fucked he's just already fucked you have to go against dizzy again see if i can get it in one go
honey let's get it up dude my arm is so sore
i still qualify and i'm still in first how the fuck did i do this all day
all right still about 400 points ahead of everybody
bungee jump at montana max's mansion here we go i gotta get 600 points let's go right in the
middle i'm see look at all these points right below me i'm gonna go in that v all right no
no let's do it again do again again again i'm gonna go v and then i'm gonna go up to the
that right the left side here holy shit i must have touched the loss all right we're gonna go
top right look i need some 30s that fucking idiot 30s up here too fucking fast man too fast
that's okay this is 30 right here i need do i get enough what's the qualification five something
five what five what no five what five i did it yes oh thank god it was 600 holy shit
okay i made it and i'm in first place i just barely beat dizzy awesome step event is hammer
bash in the courtyard do our best for hammer bash store up power with power gauge and hit the
seesaw the rocket that goes the highest wins push the buttons consecutively to make your
rocket go even higher i didn't even see the control i was gonna hit x wait what was it
you gotta be fucking that's the best thing that's that's the number one how do i get
it how do i what do i do what's up get away from me i just got i just got killed
you don't want to get killed right what's wrong with you what's going on what
what
okay i did so mine's red see how it tries to fuck me every time just tries to screw
me over every time you see that pick up the asteroid i'm supposed to still be pressing the
outer space soar continue i remain more all the way to the sun don't you need 700 points to
qualify oh i got it there it is i win on hard mode the eighth event is oh well
shit just 400 points i'm so far ahead just don't fail is that too high okay i have 400 points just
win just oh i'm holding right i just needed one of those i'm just holding the right button
wait why does it tell me to go this way what that was if that was a genuine screaming what
the arrow didn't tell me to move anymore the arrow didn't tell me to i stopped blinking
what the fuck i did no it didn't give me just one of those pick ones okay pick one give me pick
one oh shit i have to actually play no i have to actually play i need 400 points okay i'm good
okay just right here just land on that there i went okay thank god we're just trying to qualify i'm
not trying to win i'm already ahead by like 700 points and i still got the most points
because i went the highest what an overactor the ninth event is the obstacle course oh this is bad
oh no this is the worst one 400 to qualify this is the worst one this is this throw a coin who wins
this might be this yeah this might be the end i gotta play it well you this is so messy
watch me just live needed 400 that was the wall right there that's because that could have gone
either way all right what are the points standings look like now because we're just going for
qualifications we're not going for trying to get as many points to call it i am ahead by almost a
thousand points i just have to qualify the last competition is birdman right this is the one where
you have to fly break collect 450 okay here we go just have to get 450 and i have to try to hit
the mansion don't miss how am i losing points why oh my god what are you doing what why am i
burning points i did it give me a bonus give me a bonus give me a bonus please oh no one time
for your favorite negative game it's shit it's the last competition i was that was the end of the
game i was gonna win that was the last competition of the whole game don't act me at gurys it's a
whole wide world of hearts spends alone and contrary work of art it's the unexpected it's
tiny dune adventures now it's time to fucking delete it