Relax. What? No, I don't want you to see, like, I don't want you to see my, like, pores. Yeah, I know, I know.
Screen cam, screen cam, he's gonna sit. I'm a per- I'm a human being, okay? I'm just a fucking emote. How did I even do this?
Let's get it stretched out.
Is it still stre- it is a little stretched out.
Right there, right?
Right there? That-
That works. Okay. Look like fucking Adam Driver. Yeah, well, he's a handsome guy, so we do that guy give a shit.
That's like a handsome- that's a handsome guy.
All right. Uh, this is community- I gotta change. Hold on, get off. I don't want to be on camera. I'm never going on camera again.
Let me change the, uh, title.
To...
Uh, this is not gonna take that long because it's a lot less than it was last time. We're just catching up to...
This is as of...
Of last week? So as of, like, this past week.
So from, like, the 18th or something.
Or, like, the 19th, whatever it was.
Just for us to catch up on all the stuff that we missed. Adam Driver is ugly.
Okay, and- and- oh, and- and- and- and- and now you're gonna tell me- and- and Brad Pitt is fucking ugly, too, apparently, huh?
You know, I can- I could have an opinion about somebody's that I- that- that's completely an unpopular opinion.
Except I actually- I do think that Brad Pitt is very handsome.
Uh, community.
Content.
Uh, snippets. Because this is not gonna be as long. Community content snippets.
It's a bad name. Community content snacks.
Oh, that doesn't make any sense.
Community con- just community content. Nah, you- whatever. Who cares?
That's what we're doing.
So as you see, we're- we're on the art section.
Art. There is a ton of art.
Art is actually one of the things that is the most, uh, submitted.
That's why we- we have so many- we have so many talented artists here that put up a ton of awesome shit.
But there are hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of art submissions.
There's a lot.
You guys- you guys do
a lot of this shit, and it's great.
I'm back.
All right, we got a giant rat.
Uh, no watermark though, but I don't know whoever it was. I'm too big. I gotta- cause I'm like, huge.
Put on some music?
Yeah, what we got? Uh, we have Skype hang up sound. That's not really good OST. Skype OST.
Oh, yeah, let's take a break. Right. We didn't- we can take a pee break. Right. That's probably gonna-
Yeah, I have to go to the bathroom. You're right.
I'll get some songs. We'll go take a piss break. Be right back. Hi guys.
All right, what about- what should we do for music?
How about
something chill?
Not doom, not doom, not doom.
Do I like okra? A vegetable?
The fried okra is awesome. Yeah.
Odd question, but yeah.
Uh, Animal Crossing. Yeah, that's a good-
Which one though?
Three hours of relaxing and beautiful Animal Crossing music.
When's a new one coming out? Isn't there one coming up with Switch? Eventually? March? Holy shit, really?
All right, let's do some artwork.
So we have- it's a giant rat we saw for a little bit.
Thank you, whoever this was.
Good shit.
We have, uh,
me as the king.
LOL boomer king.
Thanks for the watermark. This is really well done.
Hey, we both rule. We both rule together.
It's important.
Boomer king. What's boomer king? I don't get it.
Me. Yeah, but I don't get it. What is a boomer king? Am I the king of all old people? I don't understand.
That's a restaurant.
Oh, okay. I get it.
I mean, I- I still don't. I'm 34.
I still am trying to catch on to that.
If you don't get it, then that means you're a boomer. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, this is awesome. Thank you.
Good shit.
This one's wild.
This one is fireman here.
I like this down here.
Hey!
My- my- one of my seven shirts I wear.
Cute little fireman in the middle. You're gonna be flashed.
Not in that way that you're thinking.
You got the teeth right.
Got the teeth right.
I love it.
SCP-985.
Very- very toothy. He's a very toothy guy.
Rat down here, too. That's cool.
Is there a watermark that I'm missing? Ooh, this is fucking high fidelity.
Oh, right here. There it is. Good shit.
This one's really cute. Yeah.
It is.
This one on the other hand, uh,
referencing jump king.
But I don't- I'm never gonna get this shit. I'm never gonna understand what this is.
This is horrible.
Fuck the king FTK. That's coming back fairly soon, by the way.
We have some new rules implemented.
And the new FTK server
is gonna be-
Uh, it's not ready yet, but we took all that data from the last mess of a stream with the thousands of people connecting.
And we got it down for real.
Uh, there's gonna be a lot of fun stuff to do on that server.
Soon.
Soon, soon, soon.
Fuck the king.
Uh, this is a pretty good, uh, and this is a pretty good depiction of what happened on that stream.
Uh, chat was just freaking the fuck out because nobody could do anything and nobody could eat and I was just killing people.
Um, surrounded by
mods and devs that can fly around.
So yeah, I-
We took the criticism. Don't worry. We're implementing a lot of changes.
That's a Spongebob movie?
This is great. FTK will be coming back soon.
Soon, soon, soon.
Oh, right. We have, um,
we have these uh, the new
Soul Calibur VI created characters. Let's actually get close to this.
I can just do that. So these are new Soul Calibur characters.
Here's, uh, by the resident Soul Calibur VI character creator.
Dick Dastardly Richard. This is good. Uh, here's Bugleberry.
Everybody's favorite character.
Some of these are really fucking good, by the way.
Look at this one. This is the J.
The J. Janitor. I don't even know how you do this.
It's perfect, though.
Here's, uh, Dr. Schmeichsen. A good doctor.
Is this music not loud enough?
You guys know? Oh, there you go. It's Ivy.
Look at this one. This is a Jupiter.
This one's scary because
it's just, it's the same idea with making characters in the wrestling games.
You just have to make this gigantic torso human and it's scary.
Uh, here's King Germa from the FTK stream.
Pretty accurate. I don't know who any of these fighters are, but still.
Uh, here's the Joker.
Or the, the Germa Joker. Everybody always makes me the Joker. I don't get it.
I told you I'm more of a Riddler than I am Joker.
Make me as the Riddler and stuff. That's like what I want. That's what I like.
Oh, there's Grill Master. Why is he huge?
Why is he like seven feet tall? He's stacked. Does it? That's not accurate.
There's the Grady Grinner. He's got those barbecue shoes on.
Huge Santa.
Germario? What is, who's, what is Germario?
Just me, but Mario.
Dr. Germario? Why, what?
Oh, it's the mustache hair. Okay, I get it.
I didn't know what this was until right now.
This character is, wait, what?
The subsound from the Hearthstone card.
Holy shit, that's, that's a reference.
It's Monk, Monka S.
Oh, here's the wine guy.
Here is the Trine Wizard. Trine Wizard?
He killed my, what is this?
Character name, he killed my what?
He killed my mom.
My father was fairly well. Oh, that, right.
Here's Parappa the Rapper.
This one's awesome.
You gotta take this in and like fight with Parappa.
People would be so like impressed by this one.
Here's Gino.
How the fuck?
Oh, in the name of God.
Look, he's in Soul Calibur.
Look, he finally got to do something.
Instead of collect dust in a box at Square Enix.
Frank West.
Holy shit, here's the dentist.
Here's the Outer Worlds dentist.
That's so, it's surprising every time we get a batch of these
because I would, I wish you could have like 10 people
fight at the same time in Soul Calibur.
We would just do one of Rumble there somehow.
But you can't.
Here's the Jump King.
These are, this is awesome. Perfect.
And he's got the boots, he's got the boots on.
Soul Calibur Rumble.
Character name, Brian Johnson.
Is that, that's the ace, the lead singer from ACDC.
And here's me, Gnarly62.
Hope you enjoyed the third batch.
This may be the final batch
because a hundred character slots is not enough, I guess.
This community's wonderful.
They cook up some seriously amazing stuff.
Have a great community content night.
Thank you, Gnarly.
Again, you, you make some great characters.
These are great.
Even if we don't get another one,
you've done three batches of very, very accurate,
detailed character stuff.
So thank you.
You're awesome.
I'll get this back to normal.
Scary, pretty scary stuff.
Germagreed, Money Machine Germa, yep.
Looking good.
The duality of, of Germa, maybe.
Greed changes a man.
This one is the Blockbuster 1995 store champion.
That's me.
I actually own that.
I've shown it on stream before.
That is a legitimate document.
Is the ornaments on the tree for, for Grill Master?
There's Grandpa appearing in.
That's a, that's a very, that's one of those videos
that's on my main channel from like almost a decade ago now.
I don't think very many of you guys have watched.
There's a full Grandpa poetry animation
on that main channel for Christmas.
I think, I think a lot of people may have missed that one.
Main channel.
Archive channel.
There you go.
I fixed it.
This is good stuff though.
Down here.
You can't see because I'm in the way.
Let's fix that.
Can you see now?
No, you can't.
Can you see it now?
There you go.
Thanks a lot for the image.
It's very, very good work.
As always.
Keep moving.
The incredible frogman.
Live for one night only in Viva Las Vegas.
Presto Majesto.
7 p.m. Friday.
Wait, isn't today Friday?
Well, I don't even know what day it is.
No, it's Sunday.
Do you mean live?
Oh, live for one.
No, live for one night only.
Live for one night only.
Let's correct that record there.
This is cute though.
Good shit.
Flip it.
Oh yeah, this is cool.
We have some cookies.
This is cookie number one.
And then here's cookie number two.
Here they are.
You know how hard it is to make cookies that are custom?
It's actually hard to do.
It's such a pain in the ass.
Real human teeth on this?
I didn't even see that.
Looks like...
No, those are cranberry crunchies.
What are they called?
Candy cane crunchies.
This is good though.
Thank you for these.
This is Dura.
This is Thunder.
I don't know who I'm supposed to be here, but I'm trying.
Cranberry crunchies.
Pog.
Pog?
I don't know.
Should I be Pog into that?
Is this a legitimate...
I don't know.
Let me see.
Let me see what you guys think.
Enable Pog.
No.
I like seeing it spelled out.
I don't like seeing.
I want to see it spelled out.
To me, it's spelled out.
It's not an emote.
It's just you saying it.
Thunder.
I'm fine, guys.
I was.
I was fine.
We got a GIF of the planets, which looks good.
You know, Earth still has a hat on.
Am I ever going to take the hat off?
This is really good, Delia.
I wonder if I should ever take the hat off.
No, please.
You better not.
He went on vacation three years ago, and he's still wearing his vacation hat.
You know what?
I got into this idea that my emotes were going to be sentient things that did stuff.
And every six months or so, they would all change because they all did something.
And then I did it once with Earth and never did it ever again, and he never took it off.
Like, the sun would go somewhere cold and it would get, like, chilly or something.
I don't know.
And then I got lazy and never did it ever again.
But at least one of them did something fun.
This is during the Jump King stream.
This is supposed to be you guys, I don't know, comforting me.
That was a hard game.
Earth had a really good time.
I love it's on this old-ass TV, too.
Put a scarf on Venus.
Look at this dude.
Let's get up close.
Dermba.
It's Alex, Kim, Otto.
Who loves Fireman?
Fireman is just, it's just everything, it's just the energy that Fireman gives off.
It's just what, it's how I want to live every day.
You know what I mean?
Oh, no PP.
It's Alex and Otto don't have a PP.
What?
Paul Don.
PP like the fucking mana, I know.
Nancy Drew.
Drew Crew, where you at?
I know you're in here somewhere.
No, no, no, don't worry.
I don't have to say, they'll make themselves known very quickly.
I don't have to, do I really have to say anything?
Hey, how can you tell if somebody's in the Drew Crew?
Oh, don't worry, they'll tell you.
That was long and loud.
There are dozens of us.
All 30 of them.
This is funny though, thank you.
We got this boomer, let us handle it.
Twitch plays Dermba.
I thought these were sweat stains for a second.
I was like, yep.
Wait, they are.
Oh, they are.
They are actually, it's sweat.
It's just these gross, sweaty stains.
All right, cool.
Nice work.
That's very clever.
False start.
Look at this dude.
We're gross.
You belong to us, old man.
Happy New Year 2020.
This guy's fucked.
There's the one guy having some drinks.
That's good, that's all right.
Just don't go too far.
Don't drink too much.
You're in the legal age of alcohol,
able to divide into your county,
and you're legally of age to do it.
Then have some, don't have too much,
and just be safe and take care of yourself.
That's it.
How old is one guy?
30.
We have to show them.
We showed these on stream already.
What was that?
We showed these already on stream.
But this, they're too good to not just have up
for like a minute.
And there are a few of these.
I love these so much.
This is so fucking stupid.
This one actually is scary
because they didn't do any doctoring.
They just kind of, it looked like a parrot.
It looked like a parakeet.
Some kind of fucking bird.
Silent Hill.
There's Dr. Schmeichsen.
I think we've shown this already,
but it was good enough to show again.
This was edited.
I mean, it was.
That's such a great image.
That like, what a great guy.
Everybody loves the doc.
Dr. Schmeichsen.
What about clown lady fan art?
Excuse me.
You mean Miss Polly Polite?
Doesn't sound like you're a real fan.
Happy birthday to whoever's birthday it is.
This is really cute.
I like this.
What kind of cake is that though?
I wonder.
I love this one.
I love it.
I just love the teeth.
The little like, the little teeth sticking out.
It's adorable.
I love it.
Fuck you Joel.
Yeah, this is when I was going to leave without paying.
Fuck you Joel again.
Hope you have enough money lol.
This looks like a movie poster for a Zoomer horror movie.
The Great Canadian FK Club.
20 community subs.
You what?
You gave six earlier too.
26 community subs, Canadian.
That's a lot of money.
Thank you.
20 community subs.
From fucking Great Canadian.
Thanks a lot man.
Yeah, this would be like a movie called like,
Don't Download This or something, right?
I get like infected through like a virus in my computer
and I turn into a murderer or something.
I don't know.
Dude, hype train.
Jerm, stop talking.
No!
Sorry, I couldn't look at that one.
Teeth posing.
This is a, this is a real curtain, right?
From that fucking website that I'm not going to say the name of anymore.
This would scare the shit out of me all the time.
I would be, I'd wake up a couple times a week,
really groggy, open the door to my bathroom and go,
Ah!
Gonna kill me?
No, it's okay.
It's just that fucking dumb thing I wasted money on.
The Jerm Lane.
Oh yeah, this is like a character in some RPG or something.
I don't know.
That has like a rat and it looks like me.
This is real.
Frequency on common.
Armor class.
Move.
Hip dice.
One to four points.
Occasionally getting visions of games to good boys and girls.
Jerm Lane or Jermy.
Something that's known as Bain Mejiz.
Well and elaborate tunnel and den.
Is this real?
Somebody fuck this up.
This is like a joke, right?
I don't understand.
Like yeah, somebody, yeah, this has to be fake.
This is like, it's that fucking, it's that face.
This is not real.
There's like a lore with it.
I don't know.
I can't tell from the pixelization.
Hold on.
This is a lot of info for it to be fake.
This is a ton, this is like a ton of info for it to be fake.
Jerm Lane are very fast, moving with scuttling, gay, very quiet.
And a master's remaining unseen.
Now where's like the one line that says like,
Oh and he's like compact and look at me, right?
This has to be somewhere.
Can I speak their own tongue?
And your fans are dedicated.
No, this is, this is definitely not real.
They like, look at this.
I see the editing.
Look at that.
Busted.
Yep.
Oh, get absolutely busted.
Look at how different that looks.
Look at it.
You didn't smooth it out.
Busted.
It is real.
J-E-P-G artifacts.
Oh, this is, this is a real character in a game.
Or in a Dungeons and Dragons thing.
All right, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
They, this, this is not, this is fake.
This is that, this is the, that's the face has to be edited.
You know, look at the floor.
It's not, it doesn't match up.
It's compression.
Oh, the face is shopped.
Yeah, whatever.
Is that, that's real though?
That's strange.
Oh, in motion for 3,000 minutes?
How is this a book?
I don't understand the book.
This is, this, I think the tagline was this,
fireman got into the makeup cabinet.
Wink got redeemed.
All right.
Look at that, look at that.
Don't wink over the image.
Well, I, I, I'm, I'm, I can only be in here.
I can't be outside of this box.
I can't go over here.
I'm stuck in here.
Full screen?
I just did.
Full screen the camera.
No, that's not part of the deal.
If you get a wink, you get a wink.
It doesn't say full screen wink.
How's it?
It doesn't.
Plus like, subscribe for more.
Plus like if you did.
All right, these fucking hurt my head.
I don't want to look at this.
Is it the smile that does it?
Is it my like, it has to be right?
Did people paint my hair green and do the makeup on me?
Because I go like this.
And then I got a fucking long ass chin.
I get it.
I'm, I'm the Riddler though.
I'm not the Joker.
I am the Riddler.
No, I'm the, I'm not going to say that.
I'm, I was going to say I was a combination of the penguin and the Riddler.
That doesn't, I don't want to say those words together.
But I, I like the peng, like, I don't know.
Danny DeVito is fucking crazy.
Too late.
Scary.
That's a scary image.
Otto.
We've shown this image before, but it's so nice.
He's so, look at how cute he is.
Wearing his little jacket too.
He has this jacket.
It was exactly what he looks like.
Uh, the lovely classic sensible haircut germa.
Whatever this is versus whatever this is.
Eyes aren't that fucking close together.
Okay.
Like, my nose might be that big, but I'm not.
This is, this is like the kind of shit like I get.
Okay.
This is like a, I opened up like, this is a caricature artist did this.
And I feel like I'm like, I'm some like a politician or something.
You know what I mean?
Like I'm like, this is like a politician caricature.
That's like, I got fucking more hair than that.
I got more hair than that.
That's funny though.
That's actually pretty good work too.
Who is this supposed to be?
Is this supposed to be me?
No, I'll tell you what this is.
The lovely classic sensible 26 year old Jeremy versus what happens when you get to 35.
There's aging.
People get older and they look a little different.
You get older and things change.
35.
Yeah, I, you guys already know this shit.
Do I have to say this out loud over and over?
I'm turning 35 this year.
That sucks.
35.
It's so, I'm like a hundred.
I'm not, if you think I'm turning 35, you're fucking crazy.
This is a German noir and I'm being haunted apparently from my old self.
I fucking hate this image.
I hate this image so much.
Oh, I hate it.
This is like the worst image ever.
It just like, it just looks so bad and shitty.
Not even like funny shitty.
It just looks bad.
Sour please broken for anybody else.
Let's find out.
No, it works.
Thank you, Germa.
Cares makes me happy.
It's very sweet.
He's farming sour please.
How do you farm sour please?
Just put any, put any song on.
You'll get it forever.
He's no friend of mine.
No, no, I'm talking about that person that's, no, no.
No, I'm talking about the person that just said that.
I'm saying, I'm not your friend now.
Well, you're not invited to my fucking birthday party.
There's going to be 50,000 people there.
I love the sleepy rat.
Relationship with Germa over.
Who the fuck is your new best friend?
Who?
You got to finish that.
You can't just say the first part.
Who?
Joel.
This is really nice though.
I'm in 50 years.
That doesn't even look that bad.
If I look like this when I'm 60.
Am I really going to care?
That looks okay.
I'll be, that's fine.
Nice eye.
This is not a real image.
People, oh wow, dude.
Look at your eye.
Your eye looks like it's fucked up.
Yeah, this is not a real image.
What are we, are we dead?
We're good.
Just hang tight.
2020 year of the rat.
This is true.
Actually is year of the rat.
A lot of them.
I like the eyes on this one.
They're very sheeny, shiny.
Looks really good.
We better get a new rat emote this year.
I mean you kind of have to.
Eventually.
Whenever I decide to do it.
Hopefully soon.
I'd put this on the wall.
I gotta have some cool shit on the wall.
Don't I?
I gotta have like, I gotta,
I gotta make like a streamer room.
Don't I?
Right?
I gotta have a streamer room.
Yeah, I want, I want,
I want a blue light.
And a pink light.
And a red light.
And they just,
that's how you can tell it's a streamer room.
I need like a blue light back here.
Streamer cave, yeah.
That actually would hurt my head.
You know, I see a lot of people have lights.
Like bright orange, purple, pink lights back here.
Like in their room.
I feel like it'd be like, it would hurt me.
It would be like UV raised in my head.
I wouldn't want to do that.
What is this?
Did you go too fast?
I can't clear it.
This is actually pretty funny.
This is pretty funny.
Yeah, this is funny.
It's funny.
Oh, okay, I will, I will allow this one.
I allow this one.
It's like, it's, it could be real.
It's, I feel like, this is like,
I feel like this is the type of image that you actually have
when you go so overboard
and you're trying so hard to like,
have a good Tinder profile picture
that it ends up looking like this
because you've taken a hundred fucking pictures.
And finally you get this one.
You're like, you've seen the same image of you
trying to do a good picture a thousand times.
And it's like, I guess that's that one.
And then people scroll through this and like, holy shit.
Like, why, why is Jerma using Tinder?
I used to use Tinder.
I used to use Tinder before Kim.
You guys knew that.
I used to talk about it all the time.
He's talking about like all the fucked up shit that happened.
You guys don't remember that?
What do the old viewers do?
That's how he met Kim.
I did not meet Kim on Tinder.
That's not what happened.
No, I don't have like a story like,
oh, I super liked her.
She super liked me back.
Rats, we're rats.
We're the rats.
We pray at night.
We stalk at night.
We're the rats.
I'm the giant rat who makes all the rules.
These are not even rats.
These are dogs or something.
What is this?
What the fuck is this?
These are dogs.
Although I do like this one so much.
Why can't this animal exist?
I want one.
Don't you want one of these?
10 seconds.
I want one of those.
It's a doge.
I know what it is, but this is not, that's not a doge.
That's, this is a rat dog gerbil thing.
The wizard in the boulder.
What's on the ATM?
It's me, the wizard.
I telepathically downloaded my soul into this ATM.
From AI dungeon.
Otto is literally a rat dog.
Yes, I know.
He's a rat terrier.
Noxon.
We've confirmed that with genetic DNA.
This is good shit though, thank you.
Oh, the banana milk in the bag.
What is this?
Oh, I thought this was liquid.
I thought this was like Gatorade.
Oh, that's the bread.
That's the bread.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You always gotta bring enough bread and cheese and oatmeal and shit.
This is another picture that I like wish I could delete.
It's just fucking scary.
You look like you have encouraged the cowardly dog.
Was this your Tinder pic?
No, it wasn't.
No.
Okay, I just like laugh internally a little bit.
Like my chest just kind of popped.
Imagine this was your profile picture on Tinder.
You get reported.
Hey, look at that.
Okay, add a five and then add a one and then add another one.
Then you'd be correct.
Add a five, turn this into a five and then make this, turn this into an eight.
Now you're basing that on that one image of that white thing and it was a joke.
Come on, you guys can't take a joke.
Four, five, four, what?
Six, and then five, eight, five, eight, whatever.
Good shit.
Say the line.
What line?
What do you mean line?
Got the coffee right though.
I love coffee.
I'm a big coffee fan.
I get it from my mother.
My mother drinks coffee a lot and I drink coffee a lot now too.
Chicken.
I actually did buy chicken and I bought Cheetos.
Yes, say the line.
Say the line, say the line.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken, everybody.
This is from PeacefulHaley.
I was during the FTK stream.
How did you get it up there?
How did you even do this?
How did you get that up there?
Wait, did you build this and then jump off?
Afterwards.
Oh, this is like the crowning achievement.
And then it was like, I got to get down.
The scaffolding.
There's no scaffolding though.
How did you do this?
How did you get down?
You're bad at Minecraft.
You can't be bad at Minecraft.
You can't.
It doesn't, there's no such thing.
No, you cannot be bad at Minecraft.
You can't.
You cannot be bad at Minecraft.
How can you be bad at Minecraft?
You forgot to wear armor.
But that's like saying you're bad at LEGOs.
You can't, can you be bad at LEGOs?
Oh, actually, it's like, hold on.
That's a little different.
It's like if you were making LEGOs
and people were trying to like break your door down
and like kill you.
Actually, you never mind.
Like while you're doing LEGOs,
there's just like monsters outside.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
That's right.
You can be bad at Minecraft.
You can't be bad at creative mode.
You can't die with LEGOs.
I'm saying Minecraft is sort of just like digital LEGOs,
but there's monsters trying to kill you.
So I was wrong.
I misspoke when I said that LEGOs,
if you went, if you had, you know, I misspoke.
It's not.
How is it not?
What?
How is Minecraft not like digital LEGOs?
You can absolutely die with LEGOs.
You ever stepped on one?
Stop stalling.
You can't.
You're backtracking now.
What?
Hey, look at this dude.
Literally, my grandpa has said that.
What did somebody just say?
Minus two funny Facebook, Instagram humor.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh, really?
Funny Facebook, Instagram humor.
I don't have an Instagram,
and I don't have a Facebook, Instagram humor.
I don't have a Facebook, Instagram humor.
And I don't have a Facebook.
So I would just call that shitty humor.
Get it right.
Oh, really?
We struck a nerve on that one.
I already have a Facebook.
I don't have a Facebook account.
I don't have an, well, there is an Instagram account.
It's not mine.
Somebody made a fucking fake Instagram account,
and it's just been there for like 10 years.
I don't fucking even know.
I'm not connected to it at all.
Oh, Cheeto.
I really like these ones, actually.
You're licking my, yeah, I posted on there like in 2012.
Is this paint?
This is on a canvas.
This is actually on a canvas, right?
I mean, it looks, this looks great.
I love that smile.
Canvas effect.
This again?
What do you mean this again?
Click the link, click the link, click the link.
This is when, when chat hears Jerma go on a rant.
Damn it.
No, no.
I'm just going to start talking in like
fucking nutritional labels.
I'm not going to talk about,
I'm not going off on any more like weird,
like reaching and talking about rant.
No, I'm just going to read like the nutritional facts
and that's it.
No more talking.
God damn it.
Oh, dude, Royal Rumble.
It's tonight?
Oh my God.
I'm going to, I'm going to only tell you guys
fucking jokes like from popsicle sticks from now on.
This is great though.
It's beautiful.
You're a cartoon character.
I've been called worse.
Yo dude, I noticed that you're alone.
Do you need a spot or anything?
Just talk to me if you need anything.
This guy's fucking huge.
The farting is screaming.
Yeah.
This dude's focused.
This is really funny.
Good work.
What's wrong with this guy?
There's nothing wrong with me.
Okay.
This is in the background.
I can't say what this one's called.
Apologize.
Doesn't count.
I don't have to apologize unless I say it.
This is a fucking E3 awards.
Nice sound.
Very good.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Cool.
Excellent art.
Yeah, this is good.
This is really good.
The streams are always so strange.
Those E3 streams.
There's always something wrong with them.
Look at this.
Can you fucking even imagine?
This is a photo.
This is a photograph.
Picture of my face.
Like this.
That's so well done.
It's incredible.
Incredible.
Nice fucking work.
Nice Arthus Menethil hair.
Nice.
That's a new one.
That's a new-
I like that one.
That's a new one.
That's cool.
You guys should say that now.
Instead of goblin.
Or peasant hair.
Or Farquaad.
I like that one.
Arthus Menethil.
That's what it is in canon.
A fantastic work.
Let's get in real close.
You can get like the bump too.
You got the bump correct.
Let's look at this.
It's crazy.
Some of you guys are so fucking talented.
It's ridiculous.
Awesome job.
I love it.
There is Drew Carey.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Sorry, what I meant to say was
it's a picture of Nightwing.
Could be anybody.
He said some, not all.
He hates us.
You're all right.
What song is playing?
I have no idea.
Uh, this is our number.
This is 51 minutes into the three hours
of Animal Crossing music.
I don't know if there's a...
All right, hold on.
Uh, this, that song was just called
New Leaf.
Wait.
Okay, that's New Leaf, 7 p.m.
Yeah, let's hear it twice.
Look at how just fucked up this is too.
Look at this image.
It's like, all right, you started here.
You're like, all right, let me get
like a nice clean line.
And then you're like, at some point
you're like, fuck it.
I'm putting the Nightwing symbol
on Drew Carey.
Fuck it, Friday.
I love this though.
Thank you.
It's fucking hilarious.
Uh, is that Omega symbol?
I don't get it.
Omega.
Click this link.
I will in a minute.
We're doing community content part two night.
What is it?
Yeah, I mean, yeah, we showed
the credit card already a couple times.
We already showed the credit card.
We've shown, we've shown the credit card.
And it's weird to say that I've shown
a viewer's credit card on camera.
You know, that's weird to say that.
Wrong link.
Oh shit.
Oh my God.
This is all right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ready?
Check this out.
No, no, spoiler.
That's insane.
How long did this take?
Oh, I didn't even realize it was digital.
That's even more impressive, right?
That's insanity.
I wonder how long that took.
You here?
You still here?
Are you here?
12 hours?
Flowers.
Is Apple shift here?
Oh, that's a Omega fireman.
Omega fireman.
Observe the individual.
Yeah, I didn't know what this was.
And what do you want me to say?
I also, you know what?
It's more embarrassing to not know
the half-life symbol.
When you're locked in
and someone's yelling instructions at you,
you just forget, forget.
Another rap?
Lambda, I know.
He doesn't know.
Omega low.
Blaming Joel.
No, Joel had really great instructions.
Those instructions were actually very, very good.
I think we turned into a solid team there
and halfway through into the end.
Cute rap?
Little tail?
Speaking of which,
here's one of the times we played it.
Think.
How does Joel get armor?
I don't have armor.
I guess I do have armor.
He's got like, he's got like,
because he's diffusing.
I need armor too.
I want to be in armor.
Where am I?
All right, from the way that I see this,
I guess no, never mind.
I'm not in the same room, is it?
Well, I guess I could be sitting there.
We could both be looking at the bomb.
So I'm definitely not in the same room.
So why would I be?
Yeah, I wouldn't be in armor.
You're right.
Leon Kennedy.
Not strong enough to wear clothes.
All right.
I don't know what, I don't know what that means,
but I'm kind of scared that I just said,
uh, I don't know what that is.
Get good.
Here we go.
Here's another one.
Two plus two equals what?
With the bomb.
This is really cute.
It means you eat poop.
Well, that's hysterical.
Why doesn't this work?
I'm going to get that to work.
The ninja get good ultimate guide to gaming.
Doesn't he have one of those?
Does ninja actually have like a game manual?
How do we go to video games?
Yes.
Wait, what do you mean?
Really?
I should probably read this.
Ultra gaming one.
Ninja get good ultimate gaming.
This is real.
Wait a minute.
What does he say in the book?
Hold on.
Get good ultimate.
Okay.
How many pages is this?
Is this more than 20 pages?
Get good.
Invest in a gaming mouse.
What makes a good mouse?
Get a good mouse.
Developing game sense.
My biggest win.
My biggest win ever?
Like money?
Pillars, the four pillars of improvement.
I can't believe this is real.
This is wild.
Imagine a regular win.
My biggest win ever.
Read it on stream.
Make your own book.
I can't.
How to lead.
There's like leadership skills in here.
Suppressing and covering fire.
Suppressive fire, sometimes called covering fire,
is both tactical and psychological.
Not only does it scare opponents and potentially...
Is this like a military handbook?
Team Tactics 101.
I'm going to read this book.
I have to.
It probably won't take me very long.
I'm going to read that book.
Remember, you don't need that.
You beat Dark Souls 3 on stream.
Yeah, but I didn't know about suppressing fire.
I didn't know what that was.
Covering fire?
What the fuck is that?
You beat...
I can't believe that's real.
That's fucking crazy.
Well, good for you, Ninja.
Got a fucking book.
I tried to do that once.
And I wrote like seven pages
and then gave up because it was too hard.
So, good on you.
You beat the Sekiro final boss.
What is this?
This is not an ammo crossing.
Is it?
facade.
I don't want to show this on stream
for more than five seconds.
All right.
This is weird and scary and creepy
and it's a scary face.
For these, this person posted...
At first, I wasn't going to include these
because I was like,
what the fuck is this person doing?
There's like three of these.
They just put this.
And they say, oh, there was some weird images
during the green screen.
But I'm like, all right, what does that have to do with anything?
And then they did this.
So I was like, okay, I guess I understand.
That's a person's face.
I don't know.
Don't get too close.
All right.
I feel like I've woken up a bunch of times
and like that's where Otto's face is.
This is like if you have a dog
that's like ever been in bed with you
and you're like snuggling your dog.
It's just like, oh, there you are.
I don't know what this is,
but it's pretty detailed, whatever it is.
Zoom back out.
10K.
I don't know if you're referring to.
Look at that fireman.
It's a beautiful fireman.
Beautiful Shido.
This channel is over 10,000 subs.
I can tell you the exact number right now.
It hasn't moved in a long time.
It hasn't moved since this January 1st.
There are 10,773 subscribers on this channel.
It's fucking ludicrous.
Uh, yes.
They're still here.
Good shit.
That's a lot of spendies.
New tax bracket hype.
That means a lot.
And speaking of subs,
I said the word subs.
So here we go.
Thank you, fly for shy for the 10 community subs.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
More on a ton of them are community subs, by the way.
There's like 5,000 community subs on the channel.
Something like that.
Something fucking crazy.
Thanks guys.
Keep going.
What's the cakes?
Minecraft cake?
Forced subs.
What?
No, community sub means you just get a sub.
Oh, that's actually...
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Are these stickers on the notepad?
Oh, all right.
That's cool.
I always have to be...
I'm always crying.
I cry a lot.
If you're a new viewer, I fucking cry all the time.
I was a for...
I was...
I was forced into subbing.
No, what?
A community sub just means you got a sub for free.
Every other stream.
I don't cry every other stream.
Only if there's like fucking loud sounds in my ears.
This is really good art.
All right.
We need to talk about like images that will come back to haunt me.
This is like...
This is one of them, right?
This is always here.
And even when like 10 years from now,
people will be making like photoshops of this image, right?
That's kind of how that works.
You need to make that an emote.
VenomGermo.
What?
The hand?
The hand...
Wait, the hand is not art?
It's not like drawn art?
Wait, is it...
It's like pumped in?
Oh, it's still cool though.
I like this.
I don't know how you do this type of stuff,
but like you're watching this on like a TV.
Like an old...
You know what I'm saying?
Like these...
The weird...
Like kind of chroma...
Whatever it is.
You know what I'm saying?
It looks like electricity.
Like it's like a chromatic abrasion.
Yeah, chromatic abrasion filter.
I said half of it.
I said cro...
This is really nice.
Thank you.
This one's gonna take a minute.
Okay.
Internet dependent is up here.
Sane is on the left.
Insane on the right.
And then internet independent at the bottom.
So what's the...
Okay, the extreme up here is...
Internet dependent.
Twitch TV transhumanist bionic boomer AI.
But sane.
Eternal pre-streamer TF2 time loop.
Immortal meme god of the century.
Complete user controlled vessel.
All right, now moving more towards sane,
but still internet dependent.
Colitis immune superclone.
Derma 987.
Yeah, cool.
Savvy vet tech substitute teacher.
Omega insane aquarium neo tuber.
Psychopathic egotistical monstrosity.
Is over in insane.
All right, now we're insane and little...
And less internet dependent.
Old age Kim and Jeremy Albertson family lineage.
That sounds kind of good to me.
This is just like...
Yeah, you just have...
You just got like a normal life with a dog.
It's all right.
Extremely confident older sounding man.
Yeah, yeah, go ahead.
There's a misspelling on that page too.
Worldwide wrestling resurgence.
And then...
Internet independent but insane.
Sewer dwelling gross goblin rat lord.
So now we're completely insane
but completely independent from the internet.
Austonian psych ward sob story.
Transnational global comedic powerhouse.
Presidential celebrity elect Anthony Banthony.
And then box office record breaking director.
Interesting group of potential people here.
Thanks for the sub.
Thanks for the community subs, Liz the squirrel.
Thanks for the five community subs.
This is great though, thank you.
I can't say it.
Just...
I'm sorry for thinking it.
Oh, it's Murius.
Point.
I miss Murius.
Anybody else miss Murius?
I can't wait till we get to see Murius again.
I love Murius.
It's like my favorite character.
Such a cool...
What a great little friend.
Black and White 2.
Is the cow in Black and White 2?
Otherwise I refuse to play it.
Even though I own it, it's right behind me.
Black and White 2 has Murius as a cow.
That's all I needed to hear.
That was so much fun.
This makes me happy.
It just does.
Thank you.
Oh, this is a depiction of the transitions.
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is important.
You watch this stream on a cell phone vertical.
That's not enough room.
Sometimes the chat...
Yeah, that's not enough room though.
Is that enough room?
I'd do that.
I feel like I wouldn't be able to see anything.
That's what I'm doing right now.
Oh, shit.
You have to have chat on...
Oh, all right.
Don't they have a thing where you can touch the thing
and it transparently comes out as chat?
But I guess that's kind of annoying.
If you can see then, yeah.
I can imagine if I'm at the gym or if I'm on the toilet.
Yeah.
I don't think this person's at the gym or on the toilet though.
We already saw this.
Fox office record-breaking director.
Is this a joke from something?
I don't know this is from exactly.
Somebody cropped my meme.
That way somebody cropped this image from your submission
and then blew it up and then submitted it.
That's what happened?
Well, this is nice.
This is very nice.
But they didn't watermark it.
Well, we don't know who it was.
It could be anybody.
It's little Jeremy.
Plant Jeremy.
What's with the bottom right?
What?
Oh, it's just...
It's the signature.
The signature.
Signature.
What do you mean that link?
What are you linking me right now?
This is not even real.
Wait, wait.
What happened?
Wait, what?
Hold on.
Wait, this is a dextero article about when I fell back in the chair on New Year's Eve.
There's an entire article written about this.
Hold on a second.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to read this.
Let's read this.
Let's read this article.
Okay, here we go.
This says,
Twitch streamer forgets how chairs work with a musing fall.
Twitch streamer Jeremy, Jerma985Elbertson,
struggled with his chair during his last broadcast of 2019 resulting in an amusing fall.
I don't get it.
God!
Wait, did I just...
This is the ad.
This is an ad.
This is...
Okay.
All right.
Jerma is a popular variety streamer that covers just about any category of game
and occasionally dips into IRL in real life content.
He was streaming a personal best and worst of 2019 on New Year's Eve
when one moment left him retreating into his chair
and then hilariously tumbling into the floor.
Why this image?
This is like the Jeremy loves money image.
Jerma is a variety Twitch streamer known for his entertaining...
God, dang, that's a nice thing to say.
The American.
I just reached the worst sound of 2009.
Am I getting to...
This is a real article.
I didn't get like fucking edited.
Somebody fucked me up and gave me a fake website, right?
Hey guys, I'm not seeing enough movement.
Why did it go over here?
They want me to watch this video so bad.
All right.
The American just reached the worst sound of 2019 category
and was not enjoying the winner,
which was the popular anime Ayaya's song,
something he claims he apologized about for over an hour.
Jeremy tried to get as far away from the song as possible,
sinking into his chair.
However, he quickly realized he'd gone a little too far
as the chair slid away from him
and he hilariously tumbled to the floor.
Oh shit, he screamed,
which was followed by a loud thud and a short silence
as he picked himself up off the floor.
Muted.
Okay.
Jeremy tried to be cool about it
and played it off as a real life fall joke,
but his chat was saw right through him,
enjoying the hilarious moment
while poking a little bit of fun at him.
And of course, spamming the classic L-U-L-E mode.
Fall joke.
However, he recovered after a short break
to regain his composure
and continued with his personal awards,
finally moving on to best noise,
which very well may have been his scream as he fell.
At least this happened at the end of the year
so he might be able to forget about it
and get a fresh start in 2020
as long as he remembers to be more careful.
What the fuck happened?
Classic Surgeon says,
doing this every morning can snap sagging skin back.
Or plastic surgeon takes picture
of two different people's hands.
I can't, this is fucking crazy.
This is crazy.
The best part is this Jeremy Albertson.
That's, I love it.
And this part, a real life fall joke.
Imagine writing this article and going,
they use the word hilariously six times.
It wouldn't be a bathwater of one.
No, no, I'm not reading any more articles.
What the fuck?
Hold on, this is all news to me.
Twitch streamer discovers a surprising true origin
of gamer girl bathwater.
What?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, let's look.
I want to look at this first.
Hold on.
This is a great image.
This is of the black and white.
This is black and white.
There's a not safe for worst picture in the article.
Yeah, it's all right.
We just need the first part.
All right, hold on.
This is so funny.
This is really funny.
It's really funny for one reason.
Twitch streamer discovers surprising true origin
of gamer girl bathwater.
While the bathwater trend went viral thanks to Belfdelphine,
Twitch streamer Jeremy German985 Harrington.
Okay, we've got different last names now.
May have found the first reference to the stunt
in popular culture.
All right.
What was it?
Oh, I am fine.
I'm fine.
It's not the most flattering statement.
And it was, oh, yeah.
We didn't, didn't, didn't you say the Coke gaming?
Tyler one roast loser donator.
What?
What is this?
I can't do ads on websites.
I fucking, they get me.
All right.
It's not the most flattering statement.
It didn't work.
What's her with girl?
And the German was cackling in the background.
Twitch chat instantly exploded with references to Belfdelphine
in the gamer girl bathwater stunt too.
With many saying how topical and relevant this rent.
This is fucking freaking me out.
What took most people by surprise is now there's...
How many of these exist?
They're studying you.
MonkaS, they're studying you.
Well, Jerma Elbertson.
Jerma, I gotta have like, you know what?
That's how you can tell when somebody fucking doesn't even know
who the fuck you are.
It's like, you know, but let's throw out some more last names.
See if anybody actually fucking can even get it right.
You know what I mean?
Like, let's have like, Elbertson obviously is like my real name.
But let's give some other fake ones like Smith or something, right?
Smith.
I'm going to start referring to myself as like, as like Jeremy Smith.
Or like Jeremy O'Leary.
Jeremy O'Leary is another one.
Jeremy O'Leary.
That's my actual last name is actually O'Leary.
So I just fucking...
Whoopsie.
Dick Dastley Richard.
I've seen the Kotaku one.
I've already seen it.
This is great.
I have like, I have like the images over here.
I gotta get rid of these.
Dick Dastley Richard.
Looks good.
I love the finger smoke.
Gregory Hamilton.
Ooh, you got the treasure.
That's the best part about this image.
You actually got it.
I love that shirt.
This art's really good too.
Good shit.
The gamer?
Yeah, I saw the carnival one too.
Look at the glossiness of the eye.
Oh, I saw...
Somebody said something about me.
And I looked at it and I got self-conscious for a minute.
Somebody said that I look like just sweaty all the time.
They said I look like...
They said specifically that I look like the girl from Get Out.
They said he looks just...
He looks really like shiny and sweaty all the time.
He looks like the girl from Get Out.
And I was like, okay.
But I'm just like, do I have like...
Sludge coating.
Yeah.
I just dumped Dewey who said that it was a fucking thread.
I read it.
Your head is constantly rim-lit.
It's because I got a huge ass eyebrow bone.
Look, I have a big fucking eyebrow bone.
It comes out like this wide.
But this is fantastic.
This is very, very, very well done.
Which concludes the art portion.
We're going to move on to the video portion now.
It's Brow Ridge.
Get your eyebrows threaded.
No, Kim does my eyebrows.
She helps.
She does like the middle and she cleans up a little bit.
But I don't want to do too much craziness.
It's video time.
We're going to move on to videos.
Which now we have to turn off the relaxing Animal Crossing music.
So this first one is titled Jerma's True Shortness Revealed.
We're going to go off cam for these like always.
Jerma's True Shortness has been revealed.
He is exactly like you in every way.
Except one-eighth your size.
Oh my god.
Hi guys.
My spirit is leaving my body.
He is exactly like you.
Except one-eighth your size.
Oh my god.
Hi guys.
My spirit is leaving my body.
That right there.
It's so stupid.
It's so fucking dumb.
All right.
No spoilers.
Well, I change the next one.
This next one is called World of Warcraft.
World of JermaCraft episode one.
My son.
The day you were born.
What am I doing up here?
Is this just the please help I'm lost.
My child.
I watched with pride as you grew into a weapon.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, please don't do it, please don't do it.
What?
Hey.
You will show.
Was I getting an ad?
Who has ruled wisdom and strength.
It's time for you to pay.
Exercising your great power.
You're going down.
What?
The whole trailer.
Absolutely terrible.
Nothing about this.
I tell you this.
For when my days have come to an end.
You shall be.
What the fuck?
He was hearthing.
Wait, was I actually hearthing?
What was victory, my son?
Absolutely terrible.
Nothing about this is good.
Not one thing.
I don't understand what I was doing.
I don't know what that was.
Oh, that was fucking good.
Teleporting.
It was an electro dealt.
This next one is called Stand Eye Catch.
Whatever that means.
Here it is.
I'm pissing cat off.
What? I didn't even do anything.
This is cool art.
Oh, it's Joe.
It's Jojo.
I see.
All right.
Well, this is fucking cool.
It still looks good.
I got like power in some of these categories.
Really cool.
Coming up next is I'm something of a scientist myself.
Can't wait.
Hi, Harry.
Harry.
Been needing this?
Yes, sir.
Peter, may I introduce my father, Norman Osborn.
Heard so much about you.
Great honor to meet you, sir.
Harry tells me you're quite the science whiz.
You know, I'm something of a scientist myself.
I read all your research on nanotechnology.
Really brilliant.
And you understood it.
Yes, I wrote a paper on it.
Impressive.
Your parents must be very proud.
I live with my animals.
They are proud.
Hey, you two.
Let's move.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
Hope to see you again.
You don't seem so bad.
Yeah, not if you're a genius.
I think he wants to adopt you.
Yes, I wrote a paper on it.
Deepfaking is so crazy because it even gets the emotion correct.
Eventually, this technology is going to get so fucked up.
Look at the guys.
That's somebody actually focusing their eyes in different directions.
But I didn't do.
I live with my aunt and uncle.
They are proud.
Hey, you two.
Right there.
Even look at that.
Let's move.
That's a real emotion somebody's having.
Nice to meet you.
See you again.
This is going to be scary in like 30 fucking years.
We got another one of those coming up.
It's from the same movie, if you could guess.
It's called Out Am I.
Out Am I.
As of today, Oscorp Industries has surpassed Quest Aerospace.
That's a little Voldemorty.
As the principal supplier to the United States military.
In short, ladies and gentlemen of the board, costs are down, revenues are up,
and our stock has never been higher.
Wonderful news, Norman.
Lost it for a second.
Matter of fact, it's the reason we're selling the company.
What?
Yes, Quest Aerospace is recapitalizing in the wake of the bombing.
Expanding.
They made a tender offer we can't ignore.
Why wasn't I told?
The last thing they want is a power struggle with entrenched management.
The deal is off if you come with it.
The board expects your resignation in 30 days.
But you can't do this to me.
I started this company.
You know how much I sacrificed?
Please, Norman.
The board is unanimous.
We're announcing the sale after the World Unity Festival.
I'm sorry.
You're out, Norman.
This is actually scary.
Am I?
Welcome to O-
Come with it.
Scariest part is for this, right?
Like, when it gets close, you can kind of see through the cracks a little.
But right here, it's-
Please.
That guy could be standing there doing this.
Norman.
It's still a little fucked up.
The board is-
The unanimous.
We're an out.
Oh, Max.
Please, Norman.
How long does it take to render this shit?
The anger part is good, too.
It takes like 50 hours to render this, doesn't it?
It takes like a week to render this.
About weeks to render.
Jesus.
That's insane.
I started this company.
You know how much I sacrificed?
Pretty good work.
Pretty good-
Actually, no.
Pretty good computer.
I don't know what you're running this on.
Coming up next is when you show your friend your favorite streamer.
Dude, get that crap off my computer, bro.
I wonder how many of you guys have gone through the same scenario here.
That's so fucking funny.
Even the look on his face, too, is like, oh, fuck.
He doesn't think this is funny.
He thinks this guy sucks.
And I can tell.
Oh, look.
Hey, what do you know?
More.
I'm not even going to introduce it.
Just here.
Except one eighth your size.
You motherfucker.
Breathtaking.
I shall call him Mini-Me.
Come, Mr. Bigglesworth.
Mini-Me, are you hungry?
Something to eat.
Not even a hot pocket.
Jesus, that's too good.
No, no, we don't gnaw on our kitty.
Leave Mi-
No.
Leave Mini-Mr. Bigglesworth alone.
Just love him.
Stroke him.
As you know, every diabolical scheme that I've hatched has been thwarted by Austin Powers.
And why is that, ladies and gentlemen?
My mother watches this stream.
She's probably like freaking out right now.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Down.
Down, Mini-Me.
Good computer.
You got a great computer.
The part that slayed me right here is this part where he takes like the bite.
It's just so fucking stupid.
Mini-Me, are you hungry?
Something to eat.
Not even a hot pocket.
An Eggo.
No, no, we don't gnaw on our kitty.
This face.
No, no, no, no.
Well, good thing we haven't done a community content night in a while,
considering that it took you two months to make these.
This movie's fucking hilarious, too.
This one's called Kira985.
This is Jojo.
This is Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.
Is Jojo reference?
This is called Howling at the Moon.
We don't need to see that one again.
We don't need to see that one anymore.
This is just a quick little two second video, but I thought the rats were cute, so.
Rats, rats, we are the rats.
It's infinitely loopable.
I thought it was cute.
It's a draft, I guess, of coming up with some stuff.
Maybe an animation or something.
You look suspiciously like a furry.
What are you talking about?
Now, this is a Who's That Shitty Germa character.
Who's that Pokemon?
It's the giant spider that tries to eat and kill you.
Tricked you.
It's Germacraft, the series where I play Minecraft.
Hold on.
This is going to be a single player Let's Play.
What's going on?
Did you hear what they just said?
I like the anime.
Oh, God.
All right, honest opinions.
What did you guys think?
Why is that?
Wait, why did this happen twice?
That was all over the place.
All right, honest opinions.
What did you guys think?
Minus two.
I mean, that's for you guys to decide, not for me.
Link, link.
I need this link, link, link, link, link.
All right, all right, all right.
Holy shit.
This one is called Patrick Warburton reviews Germa's impressions of his voice.
I don't want to watch this one.
Hello, my name is Patrick Warburton.
I do cartoon voices.
I do voiceover.
I do cartoon characters.
Yo, I'm Family Guy Joe's, you know, he's a professional.
Peter, I'm a cop.
So people like to do impressions.
What the fuck?
Why does this keep happening?
Peter, I'm a cop.
So people like to do impressions.
And so we're going to look at some today and critique them.
Hello, Peter.
Peter.
Hey, Peter.
Hello, Peter.
Or should I say, Peter?
His approach there, I think, is right in tune because he is physicalizing.
He knows that it's his face that's informing his voice.
I feel so fancy.
This is my wheelchair.
There are many like it, but this one is mine.
I hate this video.
You guys are in.
This is the end game.
Peter, Peter.
We're at the end game now, Peter.
But we're in the end game, Peter.
My kids always make fun of me.
I think he does a very good job.
He's got the timber.
He brings it down.
Joe is, Joe's very officious.
That's where Joe comes from.
Because he's a police officer.
So, you know, everything that he says, he's got a little bit of that attitude.
There's so much more in this video.
I know what I'm talking about.
I'm a cop, a good cop, but very fine.
What the fuck was that?
Oh, I can't do it.
What just happened?
I'm so full.
What was that?
No facial hair.
Peter, it's Stewie Griffin.
Okay, I like what he does there with the physicality.
When you do that, that instructs your voice.
Guys have their tricks.
You know, my friend Tom Kenny does this thing.
Ah, it's me, SpongeBob.
You know how to do the SpongeBob laugh?
Take your finger, put it on like the bottom of your throat and shake up and down.
And go, ah, the hand technique.
Ah, ow, ow, fuck, that hurt.
Don't do that.
Nobody do that.
Don't do, I just hurt myself.
This poor fella.
Dr. Schmoinson?
I believe that is Beater.
Who is Beater?
What is Beater?
That's Joe on acid right there.
Can I poison him?
I'm sorry.
Smooth it out a little bit, but he's got a really nice style and tone there.
I think he's doing a very fine job.
That's the only critique I give him.
And here are some impressions of me.
What?
Hey, it's me, Patrick Warburton.
Cronk, you know, I'm Joe from Family Guy 2 and Beater.
Hey, Beater, let me tell you something, Beater.
Is that what we're talking about?
Cronk?
Beater.
That's what he does.
Problem is when you look at impressions of yourself, you're like,
oh my god, am I really like that?
I mean, I don't know who I look like anymore.
So that could be me right there.
Well, I'm Patrick Warburton and that was my critique of some fantastic work.
I'm so appreciating that.
God damn it.
That was fucking disgusting.
And the next time you see me, you can just kick me right in the nards.
Peter.
What?
Beater.
Hello?
And the next time you see me, you can just kick me right in the nards.
Peter.
Hello?
I'm losing my mind tonight.
All right, we got like the real meme ones today.
This is ultimate trickery.
Why is it a fucking Egypt?
What? No, no, no.
Trick you, it's-
Super frog.
Perhaps you don't like it.
It's got games.
So much better.
Well, you have like editing capabilities.
You know, you can do it if you want.
Well, I guess I could edit anything there.
Classic game of jewel wizardry.
If you think you're powerful enough to take on my challenge,
I'm wearing a fucking red dress and a bathrobe with a Diablo 2 Paladin Scepter.
Hey, you guys talked about this today.
Are you kidding me?
That isn't what happened.
That is not what happened.
That's exactly what happened.
What are you talking about?
No, it's not.
You- that was bullshit.
This is what really happened.
Oh, hold on a minute.
I'm wearing a super frog.
Let's quick zoom in.
Okay, you're not-
I didn't- hold on.
Okay, you're not liking it.
It's got candy.
I'm losing my mind tonight.
Reference.
That's the line that-
That made me famous.
That's not what happened.
That's not even close to what happened.
Every little dog fight.
What a beautiful working day.
Your first mission is to destroy a nearby factory.
Okay.
No, no, no.
There was no truck.
There was no- look.
The one thing that's been in common of this whole thing is
it's over.
Yeah.
That's been a part of all of our flashbacks.
It has to do with something about it's over.
I don't know what.
I'll tell you right now.
No, I'm gonna put my foot down.
It's-
Why is it a fucking Egypt?
What?
No, no, no.
I tricked you.
It's over.
What drugs are you on today?
I can't.
I can't with these today.
This is the crack stream.
This is like the community crack night.
A fresh slap meets an old classic.
Oh, you want to fight?
You want to fight?
Don't fucking come at me.
Don't-
Ow, my butthole.
For what?
I've said a lot of words in my life.
Oh, spoilers.
This one's called a real statement.
A real statement.
It's a statement.
And if you want to hear what I'm talking about here,
I'm talking about a real statement.
A see-through gold play-
Why is it a fucking Egypt?
What?
No, no, no.
I tricked you.
It's Egypt and we're both flog pyros.
These are all different videos, by the way.
Derma slap best quality 2020 edition.
I can do that better.
Oh, you want to fight?
You want to fight?
Don't fucking come at me.
Don't-
No.
I tricked you.
It's Egypt and we're both flog pyros.
Okay, this one's called flash bang out.
Fucking goddamn spoilers.
Whatever.
I don't care.
On the ground now!
We're in trouble now, asshole!
Flash out!
Derma fights against the secret undertale boss.
Secret undertale boss.
I wonder what it's going to be.
Not true.
Is true.
Two out of three.
Three out of four.
The giant enemy spider.
This whole thing, the whole-
Three donations until the end of the stream.
Okay, okay.
Video games suck.
All video games.
None of them were fun.
All of them suck.
All video games suck.
I'm never playing a video game ever again.
That was really good.
That was very, very well done.
Even have the actual fight too.
No.
My turn.
Oh, get Matador!
Did you really just get him?
Community crack night going strong.
Spoilers.
Whatever.
Yoda got a message from Derma.
Fuck you.
That's the whole message.
Crazy J.
What's going on?
360 feet.
There's a quick little-
I told you we should have named it like Bites.
Or Snacks.
Community content snacks.
What's going on?
These are snacks.
Oh, this is-
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
A snake in the clouds, read by the actual author.
Look at this.
A snake in the clouds, written by Jeremy Albertson.
There once was a snake that did not care.
Got up on a cloud.
Who's that?
How did he get there?
To his friends and family, he did say goodbye.
On a whim, he wanted to try for the sky.
Soaring and slithering, how high can he go?
Oh, it was empty.
Yeah.
This is the point where the streamer gave up.
Turns out you can't-
But you can do it if you want to, otherwise just fly to the sky.
Was this the whole story?
Is it?
No, there was more story, wasn't there?
I swear to God, there was like a-
There was a whole story.
About how he-
As friends, he like left all his friends and family and stuff,
and he became like a-
Like a super capitalist or something,
but it was something crazy, right?
What happened?
Remember when there was like-
He like-
Remember when we were talking about how he had made like
fucking 500 trillion dollars or something?
No, I swear to God.
He's on crack tonight.
No, no, no, it was like-
Yeah, look at the key.
It was all like a gold bar and shit.
Yeah, no, no, no, they got it.
Was this like friends looking for him and stuff?
Go, go, go read that stream.
You'll see.
I'm not, I'm not on crack tonight.
This is community crack snacks.
Not, not streamer does crack on stream.
Giant enemy Muffet.
The giant enemy spider.
All right, you guys gotta film me in.
What happened with the giant enemy spider?
Why, why does everybody-
What happened?
Why did it come back?
It came back so strong.
It was just a random thing I did in a video from like 2013.
And it's been around for a long time.
It just kind of happened, I guess.
You are trending on Instagram.
How do you trend on Instagram?
You can, you can, that's a thing?
You can do that?
That's not right.
It's not right at all.
Giant enemy tree.
Activate windows?
What do you mean?
Do I not have an activated copy of windows?
What are you talking about?
Why did somebody just say that?
Well, activate windows.
Dudes run on a, dudes run on a fucking pirated windows copy.
All right, what's next?
All right, this is McDonald, McDerma?
McDerma, do I eat ass?
Of course I do.
Piss in my face.
Immunity crack night.
Community, community smoke crack snacks.
Do I eat ass?
Of course I do.
Piss in my face.
I mean, this is just, this is the, this is the drug stream.
Shut the fuck up, I'm listening to I Feel Fine.
Didn't we see this already?
It's sped up or something?
That's one of those streams where I, when I watch that back, eventually if I ever do,
there's going to be a lot of weird clips of me fucking moving around with my eyes closed
and shit.
I'm certain of it.
I'm absolutely certain of it.
What do you care about spoilers?
This one's called Morbus, Morbius, It's Your Birthday Today.
Michael.
This one's called, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah.
That's actually the title.
Oh, smoke crack, smoke crack, crack stream.
Why is it not here?
What the fuck?
Don't smoke crack, it's fucking bad for you.
Okay, all right, all right.
I got to get on cam for this because I have to do this.
I have to do this because I made sure that these were going to be together.
I know I make, when I saw the titles, I'm like, I got to put them in the right spot.
There's only ones that I really looked at beforehand to know what the fuck they were.
I am sorry about the next four to five videos.
I'm sorry I'm apologizing because people are going to make me do it anyways.
I'm sorry and I'm not going to say it again.
I'm sorry.
Oh shit.
Ow, my butthole.
What?
Okay, that was funny.
All right, that was good, too.
What's the next?
Why is it a fucking Egypt?
What?
No, no, no.
I tricked you.
It's Egypt and we're both flog.
Jerma's guilty pleasure.
I think that's it.
I think that's over.
I think I don't think this anymore.
I think we just had to get through them.
We had to get through them.
All right.
I already apologized already.
I said I'm sorry.
This one is the giant enemy spider, but on Mario Paint.
I think we've seen this before.
This is remade.
It's just Pokemon.
Yeah, I know, right?
It is.
It is just Pokemon.
So what's what?
Okay, so it's not the giant enemy spider theme song.
It's just one of the Pokemon battle themes.
Yeah.
So what what's going on?
Don't talk about me.
I thought I'm just doing the Pokemon song.
That's not the giant enemy spider theme song.
I stole that from Pokemon.
I stole it.
This actually is really good, though.
Make an original right now.
I did.
It was the giant enemy tree.
I did that already.
Second one is never as good.
This is really good, though.
Nice work.
Let's link this one.
How do I remember it?
Because it's three notes.
It's not hard for me to remember the three notes.
All right.
This one's called, you know, I'm just going to let you figure it out.
Yes, we sense.
The giant enemy spider.
We must stop him now.
Yes, now we have no choice.
Okay, for a second, the reason why I scrolled over here
is because I thought it was another unactivated windows.
I was like, damn, you guys don't have windows.
This one's called waste of 14 seconds.
At least they're honest about it, I guess.
Yeah.
See, a lot of people didn't know that there was a boss battle in this.
The giant.
Oh, oh, farting monkey.
Oh, I hate dog.
All right.
You wait.
Well, that was a waste of time.
That was a waste of time.
That was a waste.
All right.
Get it off.
I mean, Nintendo is here.
What do you mean?
Nintendo is here.
Nintendo is in.
Nintendo is hanging out in the stream.
No, they're not.
Where's the viewer list?
That's a lie.
Nintendo is not here.
Give me the link now.
All right.
They actually were.
No, they were not.
They were not.
The official at Nintendo Twitch channel guys only logs in to stream directs.
They don't hang out and people stream and like gift a thousand subs.
You know what I mean?
It's not like here comes Nintendo with like a huge.
I got like millions of dollars.
They were not.
They were.
They were not here.
No way.
I don't believe it.
When were they here?
What did you say?
You idiot.
What are you talking about?
They were here.
They were actually here.
Somebody prove it like three minutes ago.
Hold on.
You mean to tell me that Nintendo actually Nintendo account was here.
And when I write, when I clicked this button.
See, a lot of people didn't know that there was a boss battle of this.
The giant farting monkey.
They left because of that.
Oh my fucking God.
What do you mean?
His proof.
This could be doctored.
You could have you could have doctored this up.
It could be doctored.
It's real.
Hi, Nintendo.
German985 here.
Hope you're not browsing around channels to sue.
Why else would you be here?
He stole the team that the.
Oh, actually, this is kind of fucking cool.
Take a look at this.
The giant enemy spider.
That's pretty sick.
That was really good.
The giant enemy spider.
Just want to make this really clear.
Huge Nintendo fan.
Like absolutely massive Nintendo.
I'm the only person that streamed the Nintendo Labo.
All of them.
I'm the number one Nintendo Labo streamer on Twitch.
That's naughty.
That's not a joke.
That is a fact.
That is an actual fact.
So I mean, I love this company.
That was awesome.
All right.
We're getting close to the end here.
We have more.
I knew we were going to get these.
So here we go.
This is called German when nobody's looking.
We saw a couple of these already during the.
You look pissed off.
What?
We already saw this one.
Yeah, it's worth a second look.
Psycho.
What a fucking psycho.
It's like that's murderer vibes.
You know what I mean?
This one's called German encounters.
A something, something, something.
The giant enemy spider.
Enemy spider.
Fricked you.
It's Egypt.
We're both flogged pyros.
I'm waiting for it.
I think it's just a good song.
What a way.
But here I'm saying dude, John Nintendo.
No way.
Really good.
Check the gifted subs.
Yeah, but you can give you can give some anybody.
Anything I can give some anybody right now.
They just type in their name.
Can I?
This one's called German and star symphony.
Star.
Let's put cigarettes out on my dick.
I told you I was fucking pumped up.
So like, yo, I'm pumped up right now.
We're both pumped.
Pump brothers.
I'm going to teach you how to pull it off.
Okay.
No, no, no.
Nope.
Star, are you ready for this?
I want to
Nope.
No.
You watch it.
You can watch it on your own time and your own non non.
Suspend me from twitch web browser.
Nope.
I just linked it.
Where I am fucking watching that one. I'll be back. I just need to get a parking ticket
Please don't break the window. The AC is on he has water and is listening to his favorite music
It's the it is the it's the epoch from Chrono Trigger. Don't break the window
Fuck is this this is ridiculous the driver's seat. Yeah, I shouldn't why am I the driver's seat?
I do appreciate the editing on this one the outside ambience and the fact that the song is muffled. Oh
That's fucking wild. This one's called DJ Jerma again another one from the rhythm heaven stream
Thing is this so much what did this shit?
It's so much nice. There's so much footage of this
How long did I play rhythm heaven for?
Like seven hours, we're gonna see this stuff crop up for a long time eight hours
This next one is a song. We have a couple songs after this. This one's called Kirby 64
Aqua star crystal beers aqua stir
What do you want me to say this is the crackhead cracks next
Why is Kirby's mouth pasted on
Why is that?
Auto he needs to be watched. I need to take care of him right back. He actually many to go outside. You okay?
You good?
Well, no, he's just he's just popping down. Okay
You want to go tight?
Yeah, he wants to go outside
I'll be right back. Let me just take him out
All right chats in crack mode
No, you guys are good
All right. We have we have an apology song here
You should know what that is. Hold on. Let me just come back over here
Coming up as an apology song
Oh
You enabled this I said it I know and I know what happened I said it once
And that just opened up the floodgates, but just just dump in and now it's we're gonna hear
I'm gonna have to apologize every day. You're gonna get apology every single day a bigger. There we go
This one's called giant enemy spider
That there was a boss battle of this the giant enemy spider
Stop apologizing fuck them
At Nintendo copyright, whoa, whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Hold on. I don't talk over this part
Stop ignoring me. You're a fake name. You're a fake lawyer. You're not a real lawyer. You're a fake lawyer
Not a real lawyer. It was good. And
finally finally
last thing of the night we have
Jermis spider undertale joke dot wave
Question these kind of I guess they go they go together, right like giant enemy spider and
Spider boss from undertale because this is this is like undertale crossover number like four or five with giant enemy spider. Thanks
That makes sense
Fuck yeah, fuck. Yeah
Good stuff good stuff
All right, there we go
Good cider give us the link you want the link to that one. Yeah, they're all available in the in that discord channel
What's what people what's going on?
year of the rat
What did I not?
When was this uploaded? Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's why. Yeah, so
The reason why I didn't put this one in is because this is as of last week
And I figured that we can have obviously we'll do this again in February
Watch it now. Well that this is not fair skipping
30 other videos. That's not fair now now now now now now now now now now
Now the next community content night is not gonna be three months from now. Don't worry
The really the reasoning to do this up until about like the sick 15 16 to 18th or so
Is in the first or second week of February, I can actually do another one on time
Make an exception. It's the year of the rat. I think an exception is the year of the rat. It's a year of the rat
All right. All right. Fine. Fine. If ever ever. All right. All right. All right
All right, you're gonna be shut down buddy
There's also another video that I want to show too that we'll put in the next one as well
That was longer than five minutes, but
We're gonna make an exception for it. So
But yeah, remember that if people are like, whoa, what happened? What about I uploaded something to january 23rd?
That's because it's as of like a week ago or so. So all these things are as of like the weekend of the 18th
17 18
Hey, what are you doing? What are you doing under here?
Just like skid the shit out of it. Hey, you just like ran under my legs
You're not supposed to be doing that. You're not supposed to be doing that
He's like, hey pay attention to me. You are so hyper right now
He's like a million miles per hour. What are you doing? What are you with you?
Are you hungry? I think he's hungry
You just went outside and now you're hungry
Hold on. I gotta feed him
We're pretty much at the end of the stream. So
He's starving or something. You just ate like you what do you want? He's like please I need you to do something
What do you want? He's like, please I need you to do this. It's like glassy. What happened?
Somebody fall down the well
All right. Hold on. I'll be right back
Hold on. I'll be right back
Hopefully shit. He's back and he started playing the video without us
No, here we go. This is year of the rat and this will be the end of the stream
What are you doing? What are you linking?
I'm gonna click on a google drive
Oh, no, no, no, it's the card. Okay. I thought you I thought it was somebody's like personal google drive
No, wait, what?
What is this my favorite show? What the hell is this?
It's like somebody's slideshow
Wait, what is this? Is this correct? This feels like why is this somebody's fucking why is it?
This is somebody's desktop
That's not that's not it. That's not it. That's that's incorrect
We were I know I know I know but that's not the right one
You guys just I just got linked somebody's desktop
Oh, here we go. All right
That's the wrong one. All right, let's hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait one thing at a time
You're the rat
I love the top right rat
That's just
Giant enemy spider
Of course I do ladies and gentlemen best joke of the decade
Yeah, 30 percent of the vote there was a lot of votes
the rats
Year of the rats. That was fucking awesome
That was so it was so just cute on every level
Thank you. You want the link? I'll give you the link for that one
That's some good 2d animation. Yeah, it was
all right now
without further ado
We are going to
Uh, look at this card
Look at this card. So I went when I got it linked originally it was like somebody's desktop
But I was like, wait, why am I on someone's deck?
I was like sharing somebody's computer screen and it freaked me out. All right, let me uh, let's get this in the right spot
So anti-spoiler slide
Wait, wait, wait, wait. I gotta go back
Anti-spoiler slide
This card is 250 slides long
Holy shit. That's a lot of slides
It's huge
Holy fuck. Oh my god. I'm gonna need a whole stream just for this
Holy shit
We started this in november and you kept pushing ccn back. So it got really really long. You'll have to cancel nancy drew tonight
You'll have to cancel nancy drew
For real read it on tuesday do it tuesday. It's it's gonna all right. All right. I'm gonna tell you this
for the purpose of not
Just blowing through something. That's this
This fucking nice for a community to do to somebody I don't just want to blow through this
So what we're gonna do
Is I have a plan to finish
Well, uh, let's let's go over some, uh
Some stuff here really briefly
So as of tomorrow i'm not streaming tomorrow because i'm doing some medical shit. I got some stuff to do
I have a doctor's appointment that is very very important. We have a lot of stuff to talk about
but on tuesday
I have a five day plan
One of those days
I'm going to try to kill diablo in hardcore. So whatever day that is
That stream that that playing d2 against diablo hardcore might be like 20 minutes long
If I in the for some reason beat diablo, I it's going to be tricky
But one of those nights over the five days in a row that i'm going to stream we will do this
I just want to give it um
I want to give it time that it deserves. I don't just want to skip it and be like, oh, yeah
It's been six and a half hours. All right
Next next next. Thank you. Next. Thank you. Cool. Cool. Cool. I'd like to put time into it
So we'll do it one of those days
Uh in the upcoming five days in a row
Just read my slide. Why would I do that?
Yeah, well I have to link now
So i'll just i'll have this bookmarked
But to think that somebody made me a card with almost 300 slides on it
That's I that's I don't even know what to say. Uh, we'll touch upon it when we go over it, but
There's 282 slides
Oh my goodness
Am I doing fine health wise?
Yes
Yes, it's just been a pain in the ass
And I will have every answer that i'm looking for as of tomorrow because I had a
very very very extensive mri
Of my entire chest and abdomen and shit. So it
They know that I I don't know. I tomorrow i'm getting the results and i'm going to figure out what the hell is going on
And then from there, I might have to get an injection into my rib cage. I don't know. We'll see
You're all right. Well, then give us the card back. Hey
No, it's my card now
It's mine. Holy shit
But that'll conclude the uh kind of double feature here. We did some community content stuff wanted to catch up more into january
And we did
Thank you everybody again for
Intributing to community content night
I mean this was community crack night. I know but like it's still fucking hilarious. You guys are still talented and funny
Regardless of what you come up with
We'll do that again somewhere in the probably end of february middle of february
and then we'll be
Pretty much 100 caught up completely
But I will see you guys on tuesday
We've got a lot of shit to do for that week
We still have
Hmm. What am I what would do on tuesday? What am I gonna come back?
tuesday tuesday tuesday tony hawks underground
Maybe black and white too
maybe
We'll see
No more heroes, too
It's all on the table
But let's do the bits and go up the subs and everything
Outer wilds that's on there, too
Well, i'm streaming five days in a row
There's plenty of plenty of content plenty of games to play
Yes, there's a chance
Yeah, there is
Bring back salmon max. I'm not sure that'll happen. I'm sorry to say
But let's uh go back to earlier
We had thousand bits from lime liquor
It says mmm beans
Uh, I hope you enjoyed the beans. They're good
Sounds good
Lm man, thanks for the 500 bits germa. If you were a meal, I would be your gluten
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, I would be your glutton
What?
I got that wrong
Oh the breakfast beans. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they're good. They're really good
I would be the gluten. I thought it was like oh, I would be the one I would be like hold us together
You know what I mean? Like i'm the gluten of uh, I don't know
Not a wolf man. Thanks for 400 bits
Germa haven't been able to catch a stream in a while and I wanted to ask if you played majesty yet
I bugged you a bunch about it during the sleeping dog streams and I wanted an update keep being cool. I did
I played the majesty hd version
Did a whole stream on it. Yeah
It was fun
I did play it though go search through the archives through the archives. You're fine. It's a good game
Moving on we had 300 bits from ozals. They said dear jeremy
My boyfriend broke up with me after a one year of dating my weekend's been shit and i've been depressed like never before
My streams have been helping me cope so I can at least thank you for that
This has come with the worst time considering. I have my act coming up in a month and some of the hardest classes this semester
Do you have any advice?
Thanks for being awesome
Well, uh in relationship well relationship wise
I don't have very much good advice to be honest
Because I I didn't I haven't really been part of too many relationships
And my tinder was kind of a joke. So I don't really have very many
much in good relationship advice to be honest with you
but
I'm, not sure how young you are. But if you're taking your act i'm assuming that you're fairly young
So don't worry. There's still plenty of people to meet
how many people to talk to
and
Hope you do well on that test
Wrap it up jeremy. What?
What?
Hey
Wrap it up
I just started
But anyways
uh
I wish your luck on your on your act's
It's not a joke. Those things are hard
And in my opinion, they're kind of stupid
Because why would we put so much on?
one test
It's just like come on like this. Give me a break
sat's act's it's just like come on it would really have to do that
Really have to make everybody's entire college and high school careers alive is based around one exam
Tests of bullshit in the first place. Can I just say it's not an indicator of how fucking much you know
Here comes another school rant. No, no, that's all I gotta say. That's it. That's all I gotta say
But I wish you luck and i'm really sorry to hear that you've uh had some relationship
issues here
Good luck on the test
I'm sure you'll do fine
Hey black bear, thanks for the 300 bits. I'm glad to see you streaming this game. The devs are really nice
I met them in a stream. I was moderating when this game sequel came out and it's an all ages game. Not a baby game
I don't I I thought it was very good too. It was very charming. It was really fun. The characters are really cute
It's good. I just was asking in the very beginning if it was like a putt putt game. I didn't know
I just was asking the question. That's it
I just wanted to know
But it wasn't it was just fun. It was cute
Become as god thanks for the five community subs god
Goal becoming god. Good luck with that
Uh sparkle quest. Thanks for 300 bits
German, my name is illa. I've been a huge fan of yours for years. I love this game frogs are the best
I found out I have costochondritis and heard from a friend that you do too. Hope you feel better
That's the theory we have not
stamped
The actual diagnosis on that we'll probably figure that out tomorrow
Tomorrow is the day when I find out if that's what really is going on
But it seems like that's probably what it is and it's a pain in the ass
Thanks for the 300 bits. Thanks for watching frogs are the best
Yes
Rock writing thanks for the 500 bits. Your first bernie sanders voice was veering into dan ackroyd crystal skull vodka promo video territory
I need to hear this. I'm dan ackroyd since childhood
I have been fascinated with the invisible world a world which can help us get through life if we know how to draw upon its power
a world serving positive projections wherein you use your own personal mental and spiritual abilities to believe
And subsequently make true the things that you want to happen for yourself
Some landscape painter john alexander whose most recent exhibitions include showings at the american wing
I've had the crystal skull vodka before I actually kind of like it
I thought it was pretty good. I've had it before then it's in a crystal. What what i've had it. It's good
What's wrong with it?
Just because it's in a crystal skull doesn't mean it's not good
I've heard it's good vodka. It I mean it tastes good. It tastes fine. It's okay
It's a scam
But how can it how can how can vodka be a scam if it's just vodka it was filtered through
No vodka tastes good
Well, you start to like vodka when it's one of the only things you can drink
Because it's the most basic benign alcohol you could possibly consume
So yeah, I have i've drank it
Alcohol is a scam
I mean, that's a
Whatever. I also stay happy stay healthy. Happy new year. Happy new year to you ruck
Goiki, thanks for the 1500 bits. Your voices are actually fucking gold
Uh, sometimes I can have some fun sometimes I just felt like doing it today, but it was fun. I had a good time
This guy's wasted
Who that person or me not me?
But thank you for the 15 dollars. I appreciate that
Uh freak out freak eight out. Thanks for the 2500 bits 25 dollars
Hey germa, i've been watching you for a couple years now, but being from southern texas
Being from southern texas. My dad wasn't too keen on me getting my yankee influence
I was able to convince him that you're nothing more than a northern sympathizer, but he was still suspicious
Somehow my dad found out and went to the nearby saloon trying to drink the disappointment out. He came home drunk and started. All right
Thanks for the 2500 bits. Appreciate it
the music on oh fuck
All right
Thanks for the that's a lot of money. Thank you
I like how he doesn't care about these bits
Um, all right. There's got you got to give me a little bit of slack here when somebody like rp monologues being like
attacked by their father
And I what do you want me to do? Wow, this is let me read this
Let me just talk about this
Hey, thank you
He doesn't care. It struck a nerve. No, i'm just saying what how much am I supposed to react to that?
It's like what the fuck
They also gave they gave 50 dollars 5000 bits
After a while he passed out in front of the tv while watching football
I'm typing things i'm typing this after taking his 1984 ford f-150
and driving to
Under under a bridge
I just want to say even though you're a yankee and even though we're both guys. I love you. That's fine
That's all good, man
I didn't skip. I just read it
I love you, too. You know
Yeah, I skipped the last part of it because i'm not reading that is shit
That's why
We could be five grand
What? Oh, okay
Anyways, but that's a lot of money. Thank you freak out
Have a wonderful night. Thank you
Um, okay freak out gave
a shitload more money
I don't I don't know what all this is
This is like a bunch of a bunch of okay. Let's freak out gave it gave another
5,000 bits
and it's
a bunch of numbers and letters
Ap app avr ap pa ap what does all this
These are codes but codes for what these are nuclear codes. What are these codes for?
b b d c bug
What the fuck is all this?
I don't I don't understand what this is for
codes for crystal skull vodka
Are they game codes? These are not game codes
I don't know
If you know they're not steam codes
Uh freak out. Thank you for the
Um the codes to whatever it is
Thank you for the thank you for the hundred dollars freak out
Codes or cards one one two three. Thanks for the 5,000 bits. I missed it early, but thanks for 50 dollars frog squad, baby
frog squad
Yeah, got a frog. It's got a frog in it. I'm gonna play it eventually
Thanks for the 5,000 bits dude. Seriously 50 dollars is a lot of money, right? There was a lot of money that came in during this
Uh, go icky gave 30 dollars 3,000 bits for the voice actor fee
Thank you pass it along
ready the frog
frankie the frog
frankie the frog appreciate it. Thanks for the 30 dollars
Uh tinker taylor soldier batman. Thanks for the thousand bits
I remember yesterday. We had to put my 16 year old dog down. Thanks for streaming and making me laugh
Even though i'm still crying about it
It sucks. It always sucks when something like that happens
It's a big part of your life
Really? Sorry to hear that
I hope it's a good dog. I think most people have been there before. Yeah, it just sucks
but
What i've done over the last
For almost three decades having animals in the house
Is when one passes you spend some time?
And then you know, you take care of another one you you get a rescue a dog that needs a house needs a home
Take a cat in that needs a family
You know and the the cycle kind of continues, you know, that's how it's happened at least in my family is
Not immediately after but you know, you still want to take care of something and that's kind of how it happened with auto
we had a
Dog that passed away and we had another dog in the family and it was like, you know
We always have two dogs and we're gonna have another
That's how it's worked
Sorry to hear that though
Uh, may they rest in peace?
Thank you for the thousand bits
Noodle is bad at gaming. Thanks for 500 bits. It's not imaginary. He's an astral american. I don't know what that means
astral american
like stars like
astronomical
frog va
Oh, oh, yeah
Thanks for the five dollars
Great the color. Thanks for three hundred dollars three hundred bits. Yep. That's not correct. Three hundred bits three dollars
Easy contender for the next awards and sad that larry david bernie voice didn't really materialize so far
But the whole stream is amazing
Uh bugle bros, where you at?
Anyway, favorite curb your enthusiasm moment
Uh, there's a lot
But probably uh the pie in the restaurant with uh, dead dancing
If I if I wanted to order it, sir
I would have ordered it get that fucking pie out of here. You eat that fucking pie larry
No, you get to take this fucking pie and shove it up your fucking head. That's
The the eat the pie in the restaurant bit was hilarious
Larry you make me look like a fucking asshole
Yeah, there's so many good episodes. This is such a funny show
dark soul, thanks for 250
I finally escaped the virtual world for enough time to catch a stream
Please don't let todd find me and drag me back in well todd leave me alone
And dark soul again for 250. Hey you you're finally awake
You were trying to cross the border right walked into that imperial ambush same as us that thief over there
Loki damn you stormcloaks skyrim was fine until you came along empire was nice and lazy if they hadn't been looking for you
Could have stolen that horse and been away to hammer fell you there you and me
We should be might reading like a huge spoiler or something
It's these storm cloaks the empire ones. This is like at the end of the game
We're all brothers and sisters and vines now. Am I reading the end of the game?
Thanks. Thanks with the 250 appreciate it dark soul
It's the opening
That's literally the opening
Whatever we had a shitload of community subs from great canadian fk club
30 40 45 community subs from great canadian. Thank you. It's a ton of fucking money
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Seriously great canadian
pulling fucking 50 goddamn subs
All in a row, too
Lm man. Thanks for the thousand bits germa. Your strength can make people cry
I am pretty strong. I'm very strong probably than you think lift up a whole king-size bed
Yes with two hands
Not the frame though. Just the bed just the mattress part
Hard to do that shit, you know, floppy and sloppy those things are
Uh 25 dr. Pepper. Thanks for the 250. Congratulations. Mr. Albertson
It's with our pleasure to announce you are now a new featured gamer of the month for dr
Pepper. I can't say this shit out loud before someone's gonna actually fucking come get me
Dr. Pepper gaming, please accept this 250 as a token of our appreciation. Thank you. Thank you pretend 25. Dr. Pepper. Appreciate that
Yeah
Michael smells. Thanks for the 275
Uh, leo, you are yeet
Thanks for saying that for me. It's uh for an amazing friend. You're very welcome. Anyway, you're the best
Thanks for being there and stuff. So our chat rails on you so much. We all love you so fucking much
No, it's all good. We're just fucking around
We're just messing around
What just happened?
Thank you. Michael. Why did somebody donate a hundred different porn names? Is that what that was? I don't i've no idea
That's why like I get like scared sometimes if random donations come in hey click this link. Hey say this word. It's like I
I can't
You're gonna get me in trouble
Anyway, peaceful hailey. Thanks for the 250 jeremy. Glad you liked my courage meme
Makes me happy that I can make others laugh missed most of the stream, but I hope you had a good one
I did it was fucking funny
That was a really funny ass
Serial
What that's so why
Why would you give fifty dollars to me?
And put porn serial numbers in that's five. It's fifty dollars you spent
That's fifty dollars
Fifty that's a lot of money. You could have done it with
250 man
No, no, don't do that. Don't do that. If you're gonna do that, you may as well give 50 because that's a lot
No, no, no, no, no, no
Don't do that. Don't fucking do that shit
Read read the codes
Hey smarty. Thanks for the 1500 bits
Fifteen dollars. Thanks a lot smarty. Hey jeremy. It's been a while since I've donated. I just need to remind you
You still haven't played the claire b on resident evil 2
I know. Thank you. Thank you for the uh, the
Bye monthly reminder that I haven't played the second half of my favorite game from 2019 appreciate. Yep. Thank you
Yep, yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
Or the codes doesn't matter who cared. Uh, but thank you smarty
I think about it every night before I go to bed. That's passive aggressive. What no
All right, all right
I I will admit that I think about it every night before I go to bed may have been a small
A small little bit passive aggressive. It may have been
I admit that okay. Everyone's just keeping those codes for himself
You guys look crazy
Fly for shy. Thanks for the 10 community subs
Liz the squirrel five your boy 10 community subs. Thank you guys
I'll be back to back there
Really appreciate it. It's a lot of money 10 community subs is a fucking lot of money. It's a lot of money
It's a lot of fucking money
Apple ship. Thanks for the 250. Hey, i'm glad you liked my drawing. I didn't expect the speed paint to be shown, too
Took me 10 to 12 hours to complete
As in is incredible
Happy to show the process too. That was really really cool
Thank you great work
How would you use those codes? I don't know stop asking those questions
Stop asking and talking about that
What are you guys doing?
Wembley ttv. Thanks for the 250 if ads get to you
You do sound like a guy who would download fake pc security programs and getting a hundred toolbars on ie
You must have downloaded bonzi buddy in your life as well
did
Bonzi buddy was fun. At least that was a fun virus
I'm, okay with that one
Moo means moo. Thanks for 500 bits
Character specialist witty drive humor. My voice can be changed to sound extremely elderly kind old man senile old man
I'm extremely confident with my older sounding men
My voice can also be used for intelligent but flawed deep sounding characters listen to my demo for a better understanding
Bilactery lich. Thanks for the fuck me bilactery lich. Thanks for the 5000 bits
50 from bilactery again like every stream
That austin powers deep fake was just germa's family dinner part two
something like that
Thank you bilactery for your like seven thousand dollars you've given this stream over the last four months
And I mean that like unironically. That's like probably how much it's been more than that probably
Brick built. Thanks for the 500 bits
Here's some funds for your upcoming legal battle with nintendo. Keep up the good work. I'm the number one labo streamer on twitch
At least 30 people bought a labo because of me
Right. It was it was a 9 000 people that were concurrently watching the labo stream
Okay, but like at least 20 at least 24 people bought a labo because of me
Come on, they're not gonna come out
They have to pay me to buy a labo
Don't don't say that say I bought one and it was fucking fun
Hey moo means moo. Thanks for another 500 bits
Those wipe effects you be you have between the different screens look clean as hell
Which is surprising is the concept of a clean wipe must be foreign to you
This joke wasn't worth 10
bucks
I don't know. What is that? What's that saying? I don't wipe my ass. I don't get it
Seven layer wario. Thanks for the thousand bits ten dollars. Here's some bits for you medical troubles
I know how hard that it can be and I hope it goes well best of wishes. Hope you're doing great. Have a good night you two
Thanks for the consideration. Thanks for the support
Anybody that's ever had mystery medical problems that you don't know what the hell's wrong with you
I've had him too and it sucks. This is this is round two. It's really annoying
Back when I first had the colitis and Crohn's you've Crohn's you've colitis you have proctitis
When all that bullshit that went on five six seven straight years
And I finally figured it out and I've been all right with that. Here we go again round two
Oh now you have like chest and back pain like it's like
Internal pain. All right, who fucking knows what the hell it is. Good luck. See in three years when you find out
It's a pain in the ass
But you do what you gotta do
You do what you gotta do and you just try to figure it out. That's all you can do
I didn't realize you were having medical problems recently when I donated that no, it's all good. Don't worry
I'm fine. I'm doing just fine. If I wasn't fine, I wouldn't stream
If I was seriously in pain or if I was uncomfortable right now, I would not be live and you guys all know that
I hope that I've made that really clear
If I was not in if I was not having a good time and I'm not like forcing myself to turn a stream on trust me
Absolutely, not if it ever got there
I would take time off and you know, I would so don't worry about me. I'm gonna be just fine
I was under the impression that you shit your pants every single stream
Yeah, but that's completely unrelated
E word toward E word toward thanks for the 250. You better play halo 1 when it's released or you're getting banned
Halo. All right. All right. I'm gonna I have to play halo just by myself silently
Like maybe with on stream. I'm not gonna play it on legendary. I'm just gonna be silent and play it
I'm gonna bump you for a second here. Sorry about that. You all right
Let's see the credits going to come all the subs
There was a lot of community subs as you see there's a shitload of subs on this channel almost 11 000
There are almost 11 000 subs on the channel 11 fucking thousand subs, right?
that's
Bunkers, that's crazy
still
Hopefully I spent it. Well, I hope to still climb
We good. We good. We good
Maybe don't let us down by promising a reach stream. I streamed halo reach. I did. No, no, no
Hold on. I have to get this has to be corrected
I promised a halo reach stream and I played halo 2. I played halo reach with joe
It was one of the worst streams I ever did. I did I did play it and that was on one of the worst streams of 2019
That's what was voted. It was voted as one of the worst streams 2019. I liked that stream
But i'm sure the ceo of burger king thinks the chicken fries are good
So, I mean
Do you I my does my you know, what do I?
More community stuff
But who were they?
Who were they?
They were they're coming up right here
20 community subs from cyclops parker. Thank you for the 20 subs
Adam add them to the group
Of 11 000 of you guys. Holy shit. I can't believe saying that out loud
This channel has gone has gotten so much more
It's grown like four times in the last year and a half
It's like quadrupled in size in two years
Jesus
I hope you still like it
i'm trying
but
Another five community subs from witty username on top of the 20 from cyclops parker. Thank you both of you
300 bits from gooberry juice. Hello. Mr. 985. Uh, love you and your fan base. Just kidding
It's egypt and they are both and they were both
Pyro pyros. Yes. Yes pogchamp germavine is pogchamp
It was me gooberry juice all this time idiot. I sent the anonymous bits and wanted to do a joke, but it didn't work
So here's more I guess
Oh, we have 300 bits from an anonymous cheerer with no message
Thank you. Appreciate it
Crack donation message. Yeah, that's a crack message
Very nice. Thanks for the 250 do you ever play dead island?
It's a buggy piece of crap sometimes but it'd be cool to watch you smash some zombies. No, I didn't
No, still to play dead rising 3
More zombie games and then dying light 2 comes out eventually. So
Maybe we'll do that, too
Maybe we'll do them all
Uh right now. Oh muffin gave 300 bits. Stop apologizing for I ya ya germa. You don't have to apologize about art
Uh avery dropped dead. Thanks for the 500 bits. Hey germa
I just got off of my shift at taco bell and i'm elated to see my favorite streamer
And having dreams of us just hanging out and being friends probably because I fall asleep listening to you
well, I wonder how many people just like
Have these have dreams of me like hanging out with them because we're i'm in your ear talking while you're asleep
Well, this stream is probably not one you wanted to go to bed to
uh because
I was you know, I was like fucking bernie sanders and shit
Like donald trump and like obama there was a lot going on in that first like two hours
What kind of dream you had?
I'll have to say help the medical stuff goes. Well, thank you me too
Me too
And with that i'll see you guys on tuesday
Thanks for hanging out
As always thanks for spending time
That's not I clicked the wrong thing
That's also the wrong thing
That's the correct one
Figured it out. It only took three tries
I'll see you guys on tuesday
I'm gonna get some shit done and then as of tuesday, we're starting early on tuesday. We're starting at
Probably somewhere around
12 p.m pacific on tuesday i'm gonna start pretty very early
Because I got some stuff to do in the evening tuesday, but I do want to get a stream in
So we'll see you tuesday morning afternoonish. I'm around like 12 p.m pacific
See you then
Be on tuesday, uh gooberry juice right at the end gave 300 bits. Hola, senor
Nine eight five ignore my last donation. I fucked up twice. I promise i'll be funny next time
I'm sorry. I fucked up so bad pepe hands. It's all real. It's all right. You're gonna be fine. It's okay. Don't worry
Don't worry. It's all good. You're good. You're fine
Don't worry. Everything's good
You did you you're doing you're fine
You're doing just all right. I'll see you guys
Good night. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. I'm on the front page right now
I'm on the front page of twitch right now. Well, thank you whoever did that. That's very kind of you
Was it when I was talking about like?
Cool. All right. I'll see you guys tuesday. Good night. Goodbye. Take care
See you later