Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here, and today, gonna be playing some League of Legends.
It's supposed to be really fun, and really awesome. I don't know how to play the game, I have no idea what's happening, I just installed it.
And those of you asking to see my face, I'm gonna show my fucking face, just wait a few days, okay? It takes me a while to get on camera.
Where am I going? What are you even doing this game? Is this like a puzzle game? I have no idea. I'm just gonna go this way, I have no clue.
Oh, there it is, there's the action, there's the action, right there, baby. Yes, this camera sucks, get over here, okay, right in the middle.
The character I picked was a Mew Mew Mew. He's a mummy, and he's a cool-looking guy. Actually, he was one of the only free characters I could pick.
Am I dying right now? What the fuck is going on, am I getting killed? That's fucking bullshit. How am I supposed to know you could die in this game? I thought that guy was on my fucking team.
Okay, I gotta help protect this lane. These two guys look like they're in some trouble. Don't worry, Grandpa's here to help protect the left lane.
Just stay behind me. Don't be a hero, don't get yourself killed. I'll take care of this, there's only three people here. Just stay back and get yourself some help.
There's a guy in the top left corner, gotta be careful of that guy. Let's see if I can sneak by. Alright, I'm going for it. I'm going for the tower! I'm going for the fucking tower!
There it is, come on! Come on, get there, Grandpa! Get there, this is you! It's all you, baby!
What? Seriously, where am I? I have no idea where I am, I'm completely lost. What the fuck? I need a teammate to save me. Oh, you're not a teammate! You're not a red, red!
Wait a second, oh god!
This is the song we sing, called You Can't Get Me Up Next To The Tower. Hey, what are you doing? Get out of here! Get the fuck out of here, dude! Come on!
I did it! I actually just killed somebody! I killed that guy, I murdered that guy! Wow! I am the master of League of Legends!
Can we seriously get this lady to stop talking? That's all she does is talk! Your ally has been slain, your minions are under attack, you're under attack...
Listen, I know how to play the game! If I needed your help, I would ask for it! Now shut the fuck up!
What the hell is this? What is this? Are these items? I don't know what the hell any of this shit even does.
I'm just gonna buy it, okay, buy that, I'll take this thing, I'll take one of these, I'll take one of these, and shit, I don't know, one of these.
I don't know, that's done, done, done! Oh jeez, these are skill points! I can't believe I didn't put any points in them, like level 7 or something, I'll put these in.
Oh, what an idiot. Grandpa, you can be a real idiot sometimes. I gotta see what these even do, hold on, just go over there.
Um, Tantrum. Amumu takes 6, reduce damage from physical attacks, and when I turn it on, what they have, it deals 125...
You have been slain.
Okay, you know what, I'm done. I'm done with this game, it's over. I'm not playing this game anymore, it's way too complicated.
And that's it, so thanks for watching and see you later.
You play that, I mean, you need a PhD. You need a fucking PhD to play that game, you seriously do.
You better go to law school. You need to get a doctorate in law, if that's even possible, I'm not even sure.