Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with some Special Forces Team X.
Kind of a weird name, I know, but bear with me here, just in the first minute or so.
I'm gonna do an introduction. This is a live commentary with my buddy Ari.
Just got this game last week. It just came out last week, actually, just about seven or eight days ago.
And there's not a whole lot of press on this game, which is very odd,
because it's made by the same people, Zombie Studios, that created Blacklight.
If you play Blacklight Retribution, a lot of this is gonna be very familiar to you.
A lot of the gun sounds, a lot of the menu screens are pretty much identical to Blacklight.
But anyway, this is not a free-to-play game. This is a $15 game on Steam right now.
And I highly suggest you play it, because it's a third-person shooter, mash-up,
kind of like TF2 and Gears of War had a baby, and they brought the dogs over from Black Ops.
Like, that's what you're going to get when you play this game, as weird as that sounds.
But just wanted to give a quick introduction. The live commentary is going to kick in here now.
So I'll see you guys all next time, and of course, take care, everybody.
Alright, I'm gonna sneak up.
I think he's up top.
I don't know where he is.
Got him.
Nice job.
Can't go down.
Let's get this cap.
Nice.
Beautiful.
Perfect.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, my hard drive failed last week.
Really?
My main 1TB hard drive. I lost absolutely everything.
Couldn't recover a single thing from it.
Oh my god!
I lost a shit ton of music.
That's the worst.
Yeah.
Doggy!
I'm sorry.
I love dogs.
The weird thing is, it kind of looks like Otto.
I know.
You know what?
I'll say this right here, right now.
I don't like games where you like...
For instance, if I don't shoot the hell out of that dog, I'm gonna die.
I don't know.
I hate shooting animals in games.
Oh, airstrike inbound.
Shit.
What the hell?
That guy's not dead?
He got assassinated.
He's now.
Give me a sec.
It's alright.
Changing mags.
What do we need?
A, getting captured?
Oh, we got all three, huh?
Oh, B.
Let's B it up.
Sorry.
That hard drive just came back from...
I had it under warranty, thankfully.
That's a good thing, at least.
Oh, beautiful teamwork.
Beautiful.
That was beautiful.
Can you tell the difference?
You can't tell we're halfway across the world from each other?
I don't know, really.
It's like we're in the same room.
Yeah, there's a guy right here.
I think he's wrapping around.
Nice job.
Beautiful.
One guy at the back as well, behind the truck.
Oh, little dogs.
Oh, I'd have gotten murdered.
How did he...
Wow.
How the hell did he kill me from back there?
That guy just annihilated me.
Oh, he's dead.
Oh, it's alright.
I'm right here with you.
Can I climb over that?
Oh, there's a guy coming over here.
I'll gas him around the side.
He's gonna blow...
Oh, no.
Did I...
No, you need health.
Did I just...
No, I didn't kill him.
Dude, I just blew my own teammate up.
Oh, I'm such an idiot.
I just blew my own teammate straight to hell.
Killed the guy with the minigun.
What?
What the hell was that?
That guy teleport-slided.
What a bastard.
A bunch at A.
There's a ton of them at A.
Oh, you're in trouble.
Is that you right there?
Oh, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Oh, lord.
Wow.
I tried to get on you, but...
There's a...
There's a lot over here.
...because you're in action.
Oh, give me that headshot.
Come on.
Oh, what are you using, by the way, guns-wise?
Just, I think, the default.
Whatever the default was.
Are they still at A?
I see one guy.
Ace.
Boink.
I'm gonna win this one, I think.
Oh, too easy.
Oh, yeah.
Guy on the roof.
Yeah.
He's over here.
Oh, he's got a face.
Samuel.
There he is.
Come on, show yourself again.
Show yourself again.
Come on.
No.
You know you want to pop out of there.
I double dare you.
Oh, this guy.
Oh, a bunch coming.
Bunch coming.
Whoa.
I'm, like, doing flips.
Yikes.
There are a couple of A.
There's a couple coming to C.
There's a lot coming to C.
See, I was too busy, like, aiming at the guy across the map, and two guys came, like,
underneath the stairs today.
It's a pretty open situation.
Like, I quite...
Yeah.
I like how the maps are designed.
There are multiple entry points.
No one can complain about getting camped.
Yeah, it's definitely fun.
A lot of fun.
You can get a team of, like...
Anything between, like, two and, like, five people is incredible.
What's the cap?
What's the cap of people playing?
What do you mean?
Like, how many people per...
Can you have in each game?
Like, 10 out of 10?
I think 16.
Seven.
Ah, 16.
Okay.
Eight.
Yeah, eight on each.
God.
Maths.
I don't want to go over here.
I gave that up a while ago.
Oh, boy.
Dog.
Oh, sit down.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Dude, I just threw that behind my head.
Nice, like, nice toss, bro.
Guy right across.
Right in the corner.
Two of them.
Nice.
Careful.
I think there's still one over there.
Did we win?
Yep.
Hey, look at that.
The big victory sign will probably be an indication of that.
Nice.
Keep fueling.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Rank seven.