Sorry dude, I forgot to press the button that says to talk.
No, I know. I can't even have two minutes. I can't even have two minutes to myself.
Oh, I can't have two minutes to myself. I turn the stream on and I'm just sitting here,
just looking at Spongebob. This is our time. You had a whole day to yourself.
You're ours now. His mic is wicked fucked up. I tried to fix it. I tried to make it louder.
Did I not succeed in making the mic louder? Am I loud now?
You had two months to yourself, Omega Lul.
And do that again. That's how you know I'm at 61%.
Oh, we shouldn't do that though. We have to take another fucking three months off.
That's your- that's how you prove it. That's how you tell people that you're feeling a little
better. It's the amount of times that you can- how many octaves and you can go up or down.
Fucking idiot. All right, we're gonna play Spongebob Battle for Bikini Bottom Rehydrated.
I was gonna play the original on the PS3, PS2, but months and months and months ago,
I was told, don't do that. They're making a new one. They're redoing the whole game. Just wait.
So I just waited and here it is. I've never played this. I'm a huge fan of Spongebob. I've seen
like the first 12 episodes and then I just stopped. I'm a huge fan. That's not even fucking true.
I think I've seen all the Spongebob episodes up until, I don't know, like maybe after the fourth,
sixth season? Season seven? How many actual new episodes- hit the thing about Spongebob
that's hard for me to understand. So does Spongebob keep having new episodes or do they keep
replaying old ones? Sometimes it's hard to tell. There's 13 seasons. Seasons one through three are
the good ones. Yeah, I know, but I can't- I'm not gonna lie to you. I've definitely laughed.
Like giggled at like probably like season eight, like episode 10, you know? I have.
Yeah, they made a movie too. All right, let me tweet this. Give me one second.
I'm just- hold on. Just on my Twitter. This is the first thing that's on my list.
Okay, this is- this is a render of me singing this song in the game. Why is this the first
thing in my feed? All right, well that was cool. All right, let me tweet this. This is freaking me
out. Why is it such- why is it so good? That's me doing that, but it's a render of me on another
character. Was I deepfaked onto a video game character? You can do that? You can be deepfaked
onto a new- a video game? I thought it had to be like a human face, like a photo or something,
or like an actual video of a person. Holy sh- all right, hit this star. Let me tweet this.
In the meantime, you guys can take a look at Spongebob doing the fucking gerbil walk.
That's what he's doing, right? All right, give me one second. Spongebob. People probably think
I'm watching Spongebob. What if I wrote, watching favorite Spongebob episodes? And then like,
he doesn't know. I'm gonna wake it fucked up mood today. This is gonna be a weird one.
I can already tell. No, not Jerma975. Who the fuck is that? All right, can I- why would you make that
name? Are you gonna start a streaming career as like Jerma785? Like, I'm Jerma985. Are you gonna be
Jerma895? What do you think's gonna happen? I'm the only Jerma985. I'm the only Jerma with any
three series of numbers after his name. All right, let's go. Do we even have a controller? Yeah,
I do. So is this game any good? Is this actually like a fun game? Here's where I'm concerned. Is
this a Simpsons hit and run kind of game? No. Okay, well, let's check it out. I'm ready.
It's like its own episode.
I think he's gonna do it this time.
With my brand-new
I'm available.
One last review of the checklist. Let's see. Item number one is Plankton, a genius.
And sir, yes, okay checklist complete. Throwing the switch. I think that's just a game.
Welcome my perfectly obedient robot army. Hang on. I want to get a photo for my scrap.
What do you mean no? Hey, hello. What do you think you're doing?
I'm seeing that in real time too. Wait, I'm your manager.
That's not you seeing that on stream. I'm seeing that too. Another perfect day playing robots
and racehorses. Yeah, only I keep getting the racehorses and the robots mixed up.
Wait, do I have like the Spanish animation and the English dub? Do I have this wrong?
These unreal robots are getting boring. Hey, what if we put robots in here?
No, this is right. Oh, how shellfish of you.
I won't do it. I'm not gonna do it.
Great, Patrick. So we put the toy robots in here.
Yeah, it's fine. I didn't even do it. Why is everybody minus? I didn't do anything.
I told you I wasn't going to do it because I didn't want to offend everybody in this room.
It's quite a big room. Shut up. All right. Oh my god.
Patrick, are you going to say the magic wishing words?
You already did. Magic wishing word?
It used to be, but I kept forgetting it. Are you sure this will work?
Sure. Last week, I only had one big cookie crumb and I was really hungry. So I put my
cookie crumb in the magic wishing shell. Is this like Patrick accidentally makes meth?
What is this episode? Patrick, I proclaim that tomorrow is going to be the best day ever.
Good night, SpongeBob. Good night, Patrick.
The next melding.
Is this blood? The bikini bottom stinks.
Yeah, Gary. It sure looks like we're in a doozy of a pickle.
What in the world is going on? Did Patrick breathe in the shit in the shell and go in
like a drug craze and destroy the place? That is what happened. Is that actually what happened?
Why are people saying that's what happened? Yes, Jeremy, that's what happened.
That's not what happened. I think I can't just read this normally.
I can't. All right. Everybody fucking leave if you don't like it. Whatever. I don't care.
I think I'm going to have to learn a lot in order to fix this mess.
What a fantastic idea. Oh, he already read it.
These signs will provide important tips to help me out.
He already read it. Why did I read it after?
Why did I not process that he's the whole thing is voice acted? What am I stupid?
OK. How do I read the signs? Press this to read the signs.
Right bumper to read the signs. You got it.
So if I want to come back and talk to you again, just walk up to you and press this button.
I'd better get started now, Gary. I think that this is going to be a very long day.
OK, so you talk with Arby, explore the kitchen with all this stuff,
explore the bedroom and explore the attic. Explore the closet.
Pretty fluid. This actually looks really good.
This is really, really nice looking, isn't it? OK, let's explore.
We need 50 whatever those are. These are shiny objects.
Shiny objects are very valuable and may be traded to help SpongeBob a lot.
This is a currency. SpongeBob will need to collect as many shiny objects in order to complete his
quest to defeat the robot menace. There are five different hundred.
There are a hundred different community subs that just came in from Freddy Dredd.
Another of like added to the thousands that Freddy Dredd has given.
It's a fucking insane. Thank you for the hundred community stuff.
He's ready there. Thank you, Freddy. Jesus.
Ready again. Ready every day. Ready every moment.
I need to open up my like Twitch analytics and look at like total amount of money
contributions and just see, oh, here's the percent from Freddy.
It's like probably like it's probably like 13 percent by now, 20 percent.
Thank you, dude. Seriously.
Anyways, there are five colors. It's him.
Ready. Yeah, Freddy Dredd. I don't know who the fuck that is.
Hey, go look them up. There are five different colors.
Red, yellow, green, blue and purple. There are five different colors.
OK, red, yellow, green, camera TV. You know, I need to do it again.
Red is the most common and the least valuable.
Purple is the most rare and therefore the most valuable.
We'll value the shiny objects on her. OK, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, get over it. I was what? What's wrong?
You know, I can't do that.
And it even smells sweaty.
Just like I said, I said the words camera and TV.
All right. What? I can't say camera and TV in the same sentence.
But there's five things to remember.
I know from Mr. Krabs, it even smells sweaty.
That's gross. How the fuck does that happen?
Ahoy there, SpongeBob.
That's disgusting.
As a faithful crew member of the Krusty Krab, you've been promoted to head shiny object collector.
Yeah, that's a different actor.
Is it wasn't available?
That's right. A promotion.
So what this here new job entails is you collecting all these shiny objects.
He's probably leaving behind and bringing them to me.
Now, stop seahorsing around and get busy collecting.
That's right. No, I'm not going to try.
I need like another year to figure that out.
The robots of the area.
I love this. This is so fun.
I haven't done anything.
All right. So let me see the rarity.
Red, yellow, green, blue, purple.
Red is the most common.
Purple is the most valuable.
So that's what I'm looking for is purple.
You better do SpongeBob voices.
Do you really think you were going to come to the screen
and you're not going to hear at least four times?
It's already happened twice.
I don't know.
I thought that you said SpongeBob can see through walls.
SpongeBob, we see through walls.
I was like, wait, how is Hitman?
All right.
SpongeBob, I see how well he's doing.
But pressing RT, Zixie, a hundred community subs.
You guys, it took two fucking streams.
With like 3000 subs to get just jumped, dumped back on here.
I can't even fucking believe it.
Thank you. It's insane to me.
It's insane that you guys would even remotely
like have that many people come back and sub it
or community sub.
It's crazy.
I can't even believe it.
SpongeBob, we see how well he's doing by pressing RT.
Thank you, Zixie.
Seriously, so many people gave money last time.
I was just kind of overwhelmed and trying to ease back into it.
And if you don't know, I'm no longer doing bit readings.
It's a whole thing.
I'll go over it again later on.
We'll talk about it again if you don't know.
The upright is how many shiny objects you have.
Is it like a currency?
Don't say that.
That's an easy joke.
Golden spatulas.
Is this kind of like puzzle pieces in Banjo?
Like Stars in Mario?
Patrick's Lost Socks.
Here's an underwear SpongeBob has.
Cool. All right.
Okay.
I make myself a snack.
SpongeBob, there's snacks.
All right.
What's the last room I have to go into?
I need more shiny objects.
Oh, I can put the camera in this bathroom.
The attic.
How do I get to the attic?
I'm blind.
Hold on.
I got to get all the shiny objects.
There's a double jump.
This game just became 10 times more cool.
I don't want to miss these.
This is a classic collectathon.
Oh, don't get me in this one.
I don't think I'll ever get out.
Wait, what is this?
Oh, whoa.
Oh, I see.
All right.
This is the bedroom.
I thought of.
All right.
Here's underwear.
How do I pick it up?
What is underwear health?
Can I open this?
It is.
Wow.
AA.
Double jump for extra height.
SpongeBob can only double jump once per jump.
Is there any?
I was going to call them crusties.
Oh, shit.
There's a lot of tutorials in here.
See how well SpongeBob is doing in every level of the game.
Press.
No, I got.
What the fuck, Xbox?
Like, what ever happened to the original start?
What's with the fucking menu button thing?
Like, I always forget where that is.
I always forget if it's selector start.
It's been the same thing for like 20, 30 straight years.
And you had to just put the weird like top left.
iPad friendly menu button.
That's on every website.
Like, just make it the start button.
Well, who?
Why change that?
I don't understand.
I don't get it.
I always forget if that's selector start.
When a level is selected, press A to view its details.
So, okay, you can see how much you've collected.
Yeah.
There's a hint on each golden spatula.
Hmm.
SpongeBob can take a taxi directly to the area of that spatula
from anywhere in the game.
Holy shit.
That's so good.
How many areas are in this game?
SpongeBob's.
Wait, did I just take a taxi to my closet?
Press Y when the ground, when on the ground,
and SpongeBob will do a bubble bash.
The bubble bash can smash tiki's or robots
or push buttons that are directly above SpongeBob.
When you see this icon, SpongeBob can stand on it
and do the bubble bash to break this directly above him.
Okay, cool.
I was going to say, what the hell does that mean?
I, I get a beach ball.
Oh, cool.
I haven't even played the game yet and it just happened fun.
This is fun.
Can I run on it?
I've got to believe I can run on it.
What do the tiki's do?
Just extra, uh, I got to think of something to call these
because I'll, I'll forget it every time.
Press B and he'll do a bubble bounce attack.
Okay, that's just like a grandpa.
Yeah, B.
Rampoline.
Okay, cool.
So what does the attack button do?
Can I just catch stuff?
This is going to turn into like Luigi's Mansion
where I told you I couldn't play Luigi's Mansion 3 on stream.
You guys know why, right?
Oh, here's the bubble spin.
Okay.
It was asking me why because I couldn't,
I had to suck up every single object in every room.
I just, I couldn't even play it.
I had to stop playing it.
I got to like the first little boss encounter
and it was like three or four hours had gone by
and I'm just like, I have to stop this.
I have to stop playing this.
It's driving me crazy.
Oh, let me see.
Okay, right.
Oh, you can push buttons on walls.
Why was I pretending that I, that was new information?
Okay, you can jump, do an emitter.
All right, cool.
But yeah, if I have to just collect every single item.
Wait, now I, oh man, this is not going to,
this is not going to go well.
I'm going to be stuck here for the life.
Shit.
Okay, I got to get that dirty sock.
Give me that beach ball.
Hey, what the hell was that?
I need to get that.
Wait, can I just push it?
Why am I trying to?
Oh, here comes some hustle platforming.
25 seconds left.
23 seconds left.
22, 21.
No, do they get a head start?
What the fuck?
I thought I was looking at, yeah.
I hate that I wasn't going to get there.
And that's one dirty sock.
Room complete.
Yeah, you can take a 10 second head start.
That's fine.
All right, now it's 50 to go in there.
I have 50, right?
Yeah.
All right, let's go.
This room is expensive.
Ooh, there's a golden spatula.
What about the legendary chest?
Hold on.
This is a golden spatula.
They're needed to unlock new areas of Bikini Bottom.
SpongeBob will need to collect many golden spatulas.
Okay.
Ooh, go back and look at the chest somebody said.
Maybe a little bounce on the old bed.
Read the sign next to the chest.
Wait, what?
This is underwear.
To lose a pair of underwear every time he gets hit by a robot or touches dangerous objects.
Like this.
When he's lost all of his underwear, he must start that area back over again.
Yes.
SpongeBob may get back underwear he has lost by collecting additional pairs along the way.
SpongeBob starts out wearing three pairs of underwear,
but there are special pairs of golden underwear hidden in Bikini Bottom.
Which if you find them, they'll allow SpongeBob to wear more than three pairs of underwear at a time.
Ugh.
SpongeBob can check how many pairs of underwear he has on.
Pressing right trigger.
SpongeBob has no underwear on.
All right, let's go.
I got the spatula.
Look, I'm not looking for 100%.
I'm just looking for like somewhere around 80.
TV.
Quietly.
Yeah.
Oh no.
I'm in big trouble.
This is a plus two game.
Yeah, it's SpongeBob.
There's nothing like the sounds of your own neighborhood.
Oh shit.
Open world.
Go away, SpongeBob.
You're polluting my thinking space.
Trying to steal the Krabby Patty formula again, eh, Plankton?
Well, you won't get away with it.
I've got bigger fish to fry.
I've got to figure out how to regain control of the chum bucket from those robots.
Crush him.
Not for me, though.
That's for sure.
They just showed up out of nowhere and started calling me rude names
and throwing things.
They even bent all my spoons.
I love those spoons like they were my children.
He's a liar.
He did it.
That's terrible.
It was him.
I know it.
It's him in every episode.
Oh, won't you help me stop them before they bend all my forks?
But wait, I'm supposed to collect a whole lot of golden spatulas.
Golden spatulas, SpongeBob?
That sounds like something I'd be interested in.
Golden spatulas, eh?
SpongeBob, if you could get me back into the chum bucket,
I'll give you a bucket full of golden spatulas in your dreams.
You've got a deal.
Stop it!
Oh, god, that was fucking so funny, Jerma.
I laughed wicked fucking hard.
I love opening presents.
All right, so taxi.
So let's, can I just go anywhere?
Any five to go this way.
Need more golden spatulas to unlock downtown Bikini Bottom.
All right, should I just do what happens in every SpongeBob episode?
Like throw rocks at Squidward's house?
Where are they?
SpongeBob, this flapping robot crisis is making
the Krusty Krab lose money like a sinking ship.
No money means no more Krusty Krab.
No more Krusty Krab means no more fry cooking for you.
It's imitation crabs.
Imitation crab.
Ah, that was pretty good.
That was pretty good.
But because you're gullible, I'm going to help you out.
And of course, make a small profit in return.
I've got a few golden spatulas that I'll be willing to trade to you
for some of those shiny objects.
But because you're gullible, I'm going to help you out, boy.
And of course, make a small profit.
It's, his voice is un, you can't mimic it.
You can't.
Alex Jones.
I got a few golden spatulas that will be willing to trade you
for some of those shiny objects and...
Ah, Spongebob, I just, where's the problem?
The problem is you just...
I'm not getting any more money on this,
and I got to make money to make money, you know what I mean?
I mean, but don't you think that Alex Jones
would be able to do a better Mr. Krabs?
Like if it was just Alex Jones talking,
it would be closer, wouldn't it?
Hey, Spongebob, I just dropped by to give you a bubble hand.
No.
If Alex Jones, yes, somebody said it.
If Alex Jones did his best pirate impression,
it might be kind of close.
It could be.
Wait, what you've never heard, Alex Jones, is Mr. Krabs impression?
Neither have I.
You see, you're going to need to learn some new bubble blowing moves
if you're going to journey to the ninth dimension
and defeat the giant monkey man.
You see, you're going to need to learn some new bubble blowing moves.
But, uh, all I need to do is figure out how to get rid of these robots.
You really want...
Oh, what the fuck?
I'm, all right, now you're throwing me off.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
I've been in the soap bottle a little too long.
Where were we?
That's something about new bubble moves.
I'm not on crack.
All right.
Right.
Press this button.
I'm on a different, I'm on a different drug.
That defeats anything that is directly above you.
Try it out.
I already know.
The sign told me this already.
It shines.
Mega combo?
Wait, why is this attacking me?
It's on absent.
Don't forget to defeat robots or tiggies that are directly above you.
Press this button.
Did I try this one?
No.
What about the robot parts?
Anything with those?
Hey, hey.
Oh, that just, okay, that freaked me the fuck out.
That was so out of place that I thought something was wrong.
I don't know why.
That was so out of place that I felt like somebody was in the room with me here
and did that from behind the monitor.
All right, so where do I go?
Where should I go?
Should I go to Squidward's house?
Ooh, golden undies.
Shit, what did that do?
How do I get there?
On this side?
Wait, no.
Hurry up.
Oh, got one.
Two spatulas.
All right, so I need five to go that way.
So let's go to, let's go to Squidward's house.
Those stupid robots ruined a perfectly relaxing mud bath this morning.
And now you show up.
Can my day get any more dreary?
Yeah, let's like annoy Squidward.
I am so sorry, Squidward.
Patrick and I were just playing a game and-
I correct myself.
Oh, I correct myself.
That whole robot problem involved both of you.
This whole stream is going to be that.
And I'm sorry, there's like 8,000 people here.
And I think a lot of you might not have been to the stream maybe before.
That's what this is.
That's the whole thing.
I don't know either.
I know what you just said out loud.
I don't know how I got here either.
I don't.
Let's move on.
Squidward, I don't know what to do.
How can I fix everything?
One picture on the wall.
That should help out more than enough to another town.
Guys, what are you talking about?
That's just every iPhone selfie when you turn the forward-facing camera to you.
I didn't know Squidward had a lamp.
Let's get all this stuff.
Old joke.
No, old joke is fine.
I didn't know-
I'm lucky.
Okay, okay, okay.
Just stop jumping, will you?
If you take this golden spatula, will you please go away?
Wait, I get it.
See, Squidward?
I knew that you could help me out.
You're the best.
Don't touch me.
Wait, he's gonna-
I just came in here and-
This is like mob protection money.
I just came in here and trashed all of his stuff to get the currency.
That's wicked fucked up.
All right, can I-
The Squidward or what?
His name's not Squidward.
It's Squidward.
He only has one room?
I thought he has a bathtub upstairs.
He can't go in his upstairs bathtub thing?
Go kill the painting.
Come on.
What?
What do you mean?
Break all this stuff.
I did.
Didn't I break it all?
I didn't know Squidward had a lamp.
Oh, he turns into-
Squaliam.
Oh, Jerma pretends to like this show.
Does he?
How would I have fucking known that?
Hey, Patrick.
What sock?
Oh, right.
What are the socks for?
The one you're standing on.
Oh, that one.
It's lost.
Well, if that one's lost, where are your other socks?
Well, they're more lost.
A bunch of robots came through here and stole my whole sock collection.
I could use some help getting them back.
What do I get?
Sure thing, Patrick.
What are best friends for?
Okay, then.
For every 10 socks you bring back to me,
I'll give you a golden turkey baster.
You mean spatula?
Bless you.
Oh, so this is the red coins of SpongeBob.
Living under a rock.
Does he have anything?
And that's the life.
Love opening presents.
Too pretty.
Holy shit, SpongeBob.
Really?
Are you going to first of all-
Are you going to break into your buddy's house
who owns a sofa and not even a carpet or anything?
And that's what you're going to do?
You take his stuff?
This?
Wait.
Oh, man.
And I'm going to destroy his sofa.
That's good.
You're the one controlling him.
So?
What?
Why is everybody freaking out about that?
That's part of the video game.
All right, so I have-
How many do I have?
I need two more.
Okay, let's go this way.
Let's do some platforming.
What?
Am I getting invisible wall?
Shit, I am getting-
I'm getting invisible wall.
That's-
What the heck?
I have 240 of these.
All right, so go to jellyfish fields.
Okay, I'll go to jellyfish fields.
Is there a dash or a run?
Or am I already running?
Hey, I can't.
You can't walk there.
You have to go through the taxi thing.
Oh, this is where we get to start.
Jellyfish fields.
A place to experience nature at its most raw.
I can't walk there?
And sometimes a bit tender from the stings.
Horrible scream.
That's the kind of scream that I feel like Squidward
was lying on like the medieval stretcher.
That was fucking nuts.
Squidward, are you okay?
Hey, you barnacle.
I mean, bigger than usual because it's usually pretty-
I mean, that thing's gigantic.
And you look clammy and-
I mean, Santa.
That's my favorite thing.
That's my favorite line.
When Squidward's pretending to be Santa Claus
and SpongeBob keeps talking about how big his nose is,
it's like just-
It's total cartoon comedy.
Always been bald, but now I'm stung all over.
Well, according to the jellyfisher field manual,
severe jellyfish stings can be treated effectively
by applying a thick layer of king jellyfish jelly
to the affected areas.
King j-j-j-jellyfish!
I'm not bald?
Yeah, neither am I.
Good, we got something in common, you and I.
Well, I guess you're on the scale-
We gotta go kill the king jellyfish?
...sport mountain and die off the vicious tentacles
of king jellyfish.
I'll stay here, bald up here in excruciating pain.
You do that!
Don't worry, Squidward.
I'll bring back that king jellyfish jelly
for you to rub all over yourself.
Real voice.
He's just pretending the whole time.
All right, let's go.
What did I do that for?
I didn't get every single crusties.
All right, that's okay.
I'm gonna have to call them crusties.
That's how I can't call them anything else.
Ooh, what's this?
Can I catch the jellyfish?
Like, what does it do?
Nothing.
This is goo.
SpongeBob and Patrick can't swim,
so don't let them fall in the goo.
So how much currency is a lot?
This is a teleport box.
When you have both of the teleport boxes
in the area open,
you may teleport between them by jumping inside.
I don't have both, I don't think.
I think I have to touch both, probably.
Yeah.
All right, let's go.
Collect everything.
Do I have full underwear?
Just said that.
Yeah, I'm just processing information.
You have your way to process info, and I have mine.
Mine happens to be I say something out loud
and then go over it.
I know, I already know what it is.
I have to just activate my audio processor.
Ow, that hurt.
Does it want to kill him?
All right, I don't want to die in SpongeBob
Battle for Bikini Bottom.
Hold on, does this bounce?
Wow.
All right, that's fun.
Yeah.
Wait, I probably can get pretty far from there.
Hold on.
This is great.
This is fun.
I like this game.
Am I allowed to say this is better than Mario Odyssey?
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
It's not, okay?
It's not.
It's called a joke.
I, that Mario Odyssey's fan.
Oh, fuck.
What am I supposed to do?
I can't go back.
I'm not supposed to step on the gas.
It was 125.
Oh, checkpoint.
Step on the gas.
Step on the brakes.
Step on the brake.
Now step on the, well, you're saying it wrong.
It's, step gas, step on brake, step on, step on, step gas.
I would have understood what you were talking about
if you said it that way.
Wait, I don't want to go over there yet.
Okay, where do I want to go?
There are green shamrocks over there.
I want them.
I got to check, I'll get his underwear over there.
That's a secret.
Yeah, but I know.
Look, I'm, hey, you play your Super Mario Odyssey games
the way you play, the way you like,
and I play my Super Mario Odyssey games
the way that I like.
Holy shit.
Look at this.
Am I going to die if I go down here?
This is goo, right?
Can I land on it, though?
What if I just land on it?
If I land on it, does it, okay, I have a question.
So if I touch this, does it go like,
and we get a silhouette close around the character?
Yeah, and then we go back to the beginning.
I didn't touch it.
How?
Is there a penalty for losing?
What?
There's no way I didn't touch that.
I don't know how that's, I touched it.
I touched it.
I slow that down.
I can't touch it.
You don't get it this way.
You can't get it that way.
Well, look, there's no penalty for dying.
As a whole joke.
No, I'm touching it.
You're wasting underwear.
What do you mean wasting underwear?
Does SpongeBob piss his pants or shit his pants every time he fucking dies?
Wow.
Shit.
Yeah, you do.
Okay.
That makes sense.
Never mind.
Yeah, I forgot.
What does that happen to you?
Everybody.
The question I should be asking is why does he come back to life?
That's plain.
All right.
How do I get that sock?
Hmm.
I'm going to use the bracelet.
It's a video game.
Yeah, I, what?
I was just talking.
Okay.
If you are defeated after activating a checkpoint,
you restart at the checkpoint instead of at the beginning of the area.
So how do I get this?
It shines.
Oh, is it like a floating thing I can use eventually?
Doctor.
He thinks he's screaming again.
Yes, he does.
He does.
Because he is.
Tell the story.
I'm just going to thousand of these things.
Whoops.
What was that?
Fear?
This is a freezing fruit.
Only Patrick can use the freezing fruit.
Why?
I can't have like a nice ice cold fucking draft beer.
Ah.
SpongeBob not old enough.
Minus two.
Oh, I missed this.
I missed this.
This is like my favorite thing on earth.
I'm so glad I'm here again.
I missed this shit so much.
Ultra combo.
I think I needed those.
Can I make this?
What's this do?
It's going to be timed, isn't it?
Well, what is it?
A big one?
Whoa, what the?
Hey, what?
This dude's addicted to streaming.
I thought I had it.
Apparently not.
Half life.
It is.
It is half life.
All right.
You need to do it.
Okay.
It's kind of hard because usually you just watch the shadow in these 3D platformers.
Kind of hot.
Ooh, purple.
What's how much purple?
842.
8.
Okay.
872.
892.
Oh, that's like a Sonic the Hedgehog thing.
Oh, all right.
That was a thousand.
Bro, please watch the shadows.
And do you guys remember when Mario Odyssey came out with the two player mode?
That was not even a two player mode.
It was just like a like a holy shit.
Like your little brother gets to at least do something.
I stopped talking shit about Mario.
Like what am I doing?
What am I thinking?
What's wrong with me?
I love that franchise.
Like what am I doing?
I feel like a new sponge.
He's breaking his conditioning.
Hey, Gary.
What's shaking?
Was someone shooting the cannonballs?
He won.
Wow.
Don't touch that.
A bungee jump for a guttula.
Hang jellyfish.
Oh, that's the first boss.
But I want to see what this does.
This is a bungee jump.
SpongeBob can bungee from it.
Bungee from the bungee hook.
Just jump up and touch it.
Dive, press A.
To exit the hook, press B.
Oh, that's how you do it.
Got it.
That's how you get it.
Okay, cool.
Nice.
All right, that's how you do it.
Let's go kill King Jellyfish.
Get four.
I promise.
I know there's a lot of people probably waiting for me to do
like the Quentin Central classic.
Dive when you move your finger up and down your throat.
It's going to be crazed.
I'm going to do it at one point.
I'm not going to tell you when.
But that's the only reason why you're here.
It's going to happen fucking crazed at one point.
I don't know.
It could happen like four hours.
I have no idea.
Just my size.
You've just met the Sponginator.
Hey, are you guys minus doing SpongeBob?
I'm pretty sure that's illegal.
Hey, what?
Can I reverse it?
I just, how do I talk?
I need underwear.
If I'm going to fight King Jellyfish,
how the hell am I going to do this?
I'm going to wait until after he swings down the hand.
You know how, you know when there's a game mechanic
that is just stuck in your brain forever
and you'll never get rid of it.
I was just thinking to myself,
like, oh, I wish there was like a dodge roll.
It doesn't have to be in every single game.
But it kind of does now, doesn't it?
FromSoftware has ruined all video games.
Because if there's not like a, like what have they done?
Oh, no.
What?
I thought I could get the edge.
Okay.
Friends of Persia did it first?
Yeah, when I'm talking about who did it first,
I'm talking about who did it best.
Yeah, back in like the fucking 1700s,
a guy made up toothpaste.
He was brushing his teeth with like cream.
He did it first.
It wasn't until fucking Dave Colgate came along.
He did it best.
Yeah, the guy that made the toothbrush is cool
when the guy that was brushing his teeth was sand.
You're a corporate shill.
A corporate shill.
Okay.
All right.
You ready?
Ready?
Three, two, one.
Name any other brand of toothpaste right now.
Go.
Name a single brand of toothpaste that's not Colgate.
Fuck.
Crest.
All right.
Not Crest.
Something else is not Crest.
This is like three, okay?
There's like one.
There's two on Earth.
Oral-B.
Oh, but that's only if you want to brush like a dentist.
Fuck.
Aquafresh?
Yeah, Aquafresh.
Why can I not say this word?
Aquafresh is the best by far.
Without a doubt in my mind.
Like everybody just buys Colgate and Crest.
Like what the fuck?
It's just the easiest thing to get.
But Aquafresh.
Holy shit.
Especially that like orange like shower cream like one.
You know what I'm talking about?
The one that said it was a shower for your mouth.
It was like an ad campaign.
It was just marketing bullshit.
That was the best one by far.
It was the orange.
It had the orange line.
It was the Aquafresh like shower for your mouth clean.
It was the best one.
Show the ad.
I don't think there was an ad.
I don't think it.
I don't think they just.
The ad was just it was on the shelf.
And that's what they said.
Let's see.
Aquafresh shower for your mouth.
What the fuck?
There's this.
Wait a minute.
The first thing that pops up is a shower for your mouth.
What is this thing?
Can we go over?
Can we examine this for just a minute?
Okay.
What is this?
I don't want to put that image up.
Okay.
It's this one.
What is this?
Do you put your mouth up around the edges of that and just turn it on?
How does this work?
I like it.
I'm intrigued by this.
This actually is.
I kind of want to see how this works.
Do you like wrapping your mouth around?
It's the hose.
So wait, you put.
Okay.
So hold on a minute.
This is it.
I love this.
I don't know why.
I like this.
So the red cap is like the toothpaste or something.
And then you like you turn the hose on with this in your mouth and you just like.
It does not go.
No, it does not go.
I'm not even going to say it.
It's as seen on TV.
It's a water flosser for your shower head.
I think I want this.
Do you know how hard it is to floss every day?
Imagine you can just like put a tube in your mouth and just turn the water on full blast.
Does this work?
It's got four stars.
I'm not even fucking around with you right now.
This is the this has four stars on Amazon with like 2000 fucking reviews.
This thing is probably cool.
I got to look into this after the stream.
All right, let's go.
You guys are so fucked up and I'm the fucking weird guy, right?
That's the thing.
I'm the weird guy.
This is very dangerous for just one health pack.
Oh, yeah.
Try this new water flosser.
It goes.
I can't say it.
I can't even.
I can't do it.
You connect it to your bidet and do put it in.
But all right, I'm moving on.
And what you as you're on the toilet, you put it in the
and then what spit down between your legs into the toilet.
Yeah, I got.
Oh, I got the teleport that machine huffing and puffing over.
There is a duplicate duplicate OTRON.
I'm going to call it the duplicator, duplicator, the duplicator.
I'll call the D 1000 that will continue to create robots until it's destroyed.
Be careful, though.
It goes out with a big bang.
Oh, you can.
That's cool.
All right, we got to kill this thing.
That was a big bang, wasn't it?
All right.
Well, there's a button.
Coked out streamer flosses his teeth in the bidet.
All right.
You know, as well as I do, that there is there is a 90s comedy or an early 2000s comedy
where like Will Ferrell has to really get something out of his mouth and rinse his mouth.
And oh, what's this up a day?
And he leans down like fucking cartoon three stooges style
and turns it on and starts like rinsing his mouth out and like
spitting into the toilet with a bidet.
You know, it existed.
It's in a movie somewhere.
I don't know which one and I don't know when, but it happened.
Let me look it up.
Nobody look up.
Will Ferrell rinses mouth with a bidet.
I feel like that's that sounds like where's the king jellyfish already?
Is he up there?
All right, I got I have five that is it's in a movie.
It's a life hack.
Mr. Bean did it.
No, he didn't.
He's too clean for that.
I want to go up.
Is there anything else I missed up there?
I mean, he's not.
Go back.
Wrong way.
Mr. Bean is is too clean to do that.
He's he's like PG clean, fun humor.
He's not.
It's like a cave in the trees.
Germa, the trees.
I mean, these the bouncy trees.
Oh, look at those bouncy trees.
Literally, no.
Look, I can get up there with the bouncy tree.
Watch.
There's a sock over here.
Get up there.
Yeah, this is what I want.
There's another bouncy right here.
Somebody just say you're a dick.
I'm a dick.
What happened?
Sorry, I had to I had to give Kim some information that was sensitive.
So I had to say it very quietly without the mic on.
I could sensitive info was crying.
I'm going.
I'm sitting there just crying like a second day back.
I'm just going to the caves.
Let's go go caves.
He lost in a kid's game.
It's only been like six months since he's done.
Miss Piggy.
What?
It's that sponge kid and now what was I supposed to tell you?
Oh, it's that SpongeBob kid.
Now, what was I supposed to tell you?
I think it has something to do with massaging my feet.
What do you want to say it?
I think we need to get into the Batmobile and get over there and destroy it.
What should I say it?
I should say it.
Fuck.
It's an old man.
I just did that.
Whoops.
And my fingers slipped and it was an X button working quickly.
This is a slide.
When SpongeBob, Patrick, or Sandy jump onto a slide,
they will zip down the slope at hydrodynamic speed.
Didn't think I knew about the secret spot, did you?
I was going so well, too.
I was going so well.
Oh, so by the way, I didn't tell this story because there's too many over the last few months.
Okay, seriously.
Don't tell any stories.
Get the fucking secret song.
Play Half-Life.
No, I don't want to play Half-Life.
It's a fantastic series and it's one of my favorites.
I've already done it a bunch of times.
No, no, I want to do something else.
But I'm on my tongue.
That's fine.
All right, so I don't know why.
So you guys know I've been doing a lot of doctor's appointments, right?
And at every single doctor's appointment, most of them check your vitals, right?
So they'll check your temperature.
They'll say, okay, let's do your blood pressure.
Let's sit down for a second.
Let's check your weight and all that, right?
So I don't know why, but I've had my blood pressure checked
like dozens of times, like probably 20 fucking times in the last six months, right?
For this, for some reason now,
like the last doctor's appointment I went to,
I was getting the, it was an automatic machine.
And while it was going on, while she came out, she put it on, she pressed the button.
I started laughing so hard.
I couldn't help it.
I couldn't stop because it was crushing me.
It was really, really uncomfortable.
And the reason why I was laughing so hard is because
you guys have seen the Beavis and Butthead episode
where Beavis and Butthead are at like CVS or something.
Beavis puts his arm in that thing and they think it's a ride.
And he's trying, he's, it starts going on his arm and crushing him.
And he starts freaking the fuck out because he doesn't know what it is.
I was sitting there just thinking about Beavis and how I was like
acting, kind of thinking that way.
I was like, oh my God, I'm getting the fuck out of this.
And I just, and they're laughing and I, I can't tell like the nurse why I'm laughing.
Like, oh, what's, what's, is that funny?
Yeah.
Everyone Beavis like freaks out and his like face starts turning purple
because he had this thing put on his arm.
Remember that?
Oh yeah.
You, okay.
Let me write that down.
I was, I don't know why I just started thinking about it.
I couldn't stop.
It was really tight though.
Like Beavis and Butthead comedy type.
I hit all three of these buttons, right?
You're a loon.
Bro, I don't think I am.
Do you, hey, hey, hey.
You think I'm a loon?
One in chat, if yes.
Two in chat, if no.
You think I'm a loon?
Can I buy costumes?
Okay.
Where's the last one?
Oh, there it is.
Bart, Bart.
I have a question.
Is like the Bart thing going to turn into like Johnny Depp?
Is just Johnny Depp being a parody of himself as Captain Jack Sparrow
because he's done it so many times?
Is that going to happen to me?
Like, is that happening to me?
Like, like it's no longer Johnny Depp doing Captain Jack Sparrow.
It's just Johnny Depp pretending to be Captain Jack Sparrow.
It's not actually Captain Jack Sparrow.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about when I mean that?
When I say that?
You know, like it feels real.
It feels like it's, it feels like just acting.
Somebody knows what I mean by that, right?
Like it's, it's like Johnny Depp is like doing a parody
almost of himself when he's doing it now.
Does that make any sense?
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Thank you one guy.
All right.
So what did that do for me?
Oh, Patrick.
Nobody said that.
Yeah.
At least 10 people did.
Germa Johnny Depp.
Germa what?
Hey, SpongeBob.
Your cherry picking responses.
Thank goodness you're safe, Patrick.
Well, of course, SpongeBob.
Why wouldn't I be?
Only pull out the ones that agree with you and don't
and just ignore the sea of people that disagree.
Did you guys think I'm right?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, yes.
No, no.
Oh, you think I'm right.
Thanks.
Cool.
Thank you.
I know I am.
Patrick, I tell you what.
All that running around has left me pooped.
Why don't you continue on for a bit?
You literally do that.
You have an emote about it.
Where's.
I'm Patrick now.
can he fly? I feel like he can fly. No. Don't you think he can lie down flat like a starfish
and glide or spin and glide? This is a throw fruit. Patrick can pick up a throw fruit and throw
them. Press the B button to pick up a nearby throw fruit. Okay. Use it quickly. It wilts after a few
seconds. How far can you throw it? That was a bad example. Oh, there's a lock on. Patrick can also
pick up and throw tiki's, but only tiki's that don't have other tiki's stacked on top of them.
How do I throw to that guy? So shiny. Patrick can throw fruit up steps. What's happening?
And climb the steps, pick up the fruit and throw it again. But he better hurt before it wilts.
Real voice. No, it wasn't. Morty. Real Morty. Oh, fuck. I didn't read. Okay. You can throw stuff.
Read. This is a thunder tiki. When Patrick touches it, it will begin to storm and after a few
seconds it will go boom. Don't be near it when it goes boom. How many pairs of underwear does
Patrick have? The same. I feel like these are here for a reason. Oh, whoops. Okay. Anything else over
her? Oh, I can read it. This is a special Patrick teeter totter that only Patrick can use. Okay.
That's a really important point. SpongeBob can't use this shit. He didn't notice. Why is everybody
jabbing? Patrick, keepo. Keepo happy. Okay. Who's your, who, are you ready? Who's your favorite
SpongeBob character? I'll tell you mine after you tell me yours. Okay. Okay.
Okay. I'm seeing a lot of, yeah, I'm seeing a lot of things that I would do.
Oh, hi there, Mr. Plankton. Are you going to vaporize me today?
So very tempting. Unfortunately, I found myself in the undesirable position of having to assist you.
The guy that screams, yeah. I was in an undesirable position yesterday and now my neck hurts.
Which Looney Tune Daffy Duck would I be? That's easy. Which Looney Tune character would you be
Daffy Duck? Or the Road Runner because I'm really fast and explosive. Either one. Combine them.
Not anymore. No, maybe not. Go into Jellyfish Cave, follow the instructions and sign.
At the end of the caves, you'll still be a big idiot, but you'll know enough to help
defeat the robots. Well, then will you vaporize me? I might spare your life so I can force you
to work in my sweatshop, making low quality design and knock off wallets. Oh, thank you.
The intel is his favorite character. Road Runner. Oh, for SpongeBob. Right. Have you guys ever seen
a Road Runner in real life? They are the most, they're the best favorite bird on earth. They're
the most cute little funny little guys. They're amazing. They're so cool. The way they run,
they got those funny little mohawks. They're little, they're not huge. They're fast. They
go like 25 miles per hour. They're fast. Oh, stalling, stalling. Oh, right, right. Favorite
SpongeBob character. It's free season five. It's going to be Patrick. Post season six,
it's going to be Mr. Krabs. That's a, that's, that's a really hot take, dude. What the
fuck is he saying? I'm talking about my favorite SpongeBob characters. The four seasons,
whatever the early one I said, Patrick's my favorite character. And then after season five,
after season five, it's Mr. Krabs. I just think he's funny. Don't watch past season four. See,
I don't agree with that. I know, I know that like the first four or five seasons were like just way
better. I know they were. And then like after like season 10, it was like, okay, I do this twice.
This joke is as salvageable as the Titanic. Talking about who my favorite
character in SpongeBob is. That's, wait, what? That's, that's a, what do you mean joke?
Season one came out when you were like 20. I don't know. I mean, just do the math. Yeah.
Something like that. I thought it was great. I can't jump. I can't jump. Hold on. Can I throw
this? How far can I throw this? Give it to me. Come on. Dan here. He just fell. This dude's
fucking ancient. Sorry, I'm over 30. Fuck. What's happening? I, what, so what happens when I turn?
Like, all right, you get out of here. Like I'm paying attention. I don't care about anything
right now. Hold on. That's what I wanted to do. Here we are. Thank you. That's much better.
When are you going to do new emotes? No, I don't think I'm ever going to give a date for that
because I keep saying I'm going to make new emotes and then a year goes by and nothing happens.
I just like massive spam went through a bunch of stuff on a better Twitch because I was like,
yeah, let's just add like 10 of them. We're so lonely. There will be.
I don't know. The way to throw fruit will also activate pressure plates. Okay, cool.
Now I can run through, but wait. Yeah, whatever. Patrick can also jump up on a throw fruit to get
to higher places. You may stack throw fruits as well by throwing a throw fruit on top of another
throw fruit to allow Patrick to get to even higher places. Well, don't they, don't they have to wait
respond? Does that not matter right now? This is kind of how, it's just kind of how I feel
like 40% of every day. Can I tell you that? Not like that. Not like that. Not like that. Not like
that. Not like that. Okay, let's play. Let's throw them this way. No, the lock. I can still do it.
Good work. Oh, I didn't know this is a slide. I'm lost. I want to spend some of this. Oh wait,
Patrick can drink this, right? This is a freeze fruit. Patrick's favorite. They can throw it.
Freeze goo. You can slide on it until it thaws. Let's take a look. Well, that's interesting.
Do it again in a minute. I'm gonna go up there first. Oh, spatula.
Patrick's belly flops into your robots. He can damage or stun them. That's awesome.
It's the same sound effects as Spyro. It was the same team. Maybe it was the same team.
Powered. That is pretty well powered actually. That's much better. It was the same death team.
That's pretty cool. Patrick may even pick up robots he has stunned and throw them into other
robots. Oh, well, I crushed him. Almost happened. I want to try it. All right, well, that's you.
You're too close. All right, that thing was small. That's cool, but when am I ever going to
use that besides rolling into a bucket? Oh, well, that didn't even do what I thought it was going
to do. And spatula. This game sucks. It doesn't. It really doesn't. It's fine. This game does not
suck. Wait, I want to do the ice thing. This may in fact be the last great licensed video game. Is
that true? Could be. That accurate? No. What was the last great licensed video game based on like
a cartoon or a TV show or a movie? I'm not sure I count comic books right now.
It's like Batman, Spider-Man. I'm talking about like TV show. Just based on a TV show.
Not on like an iconic character that's been around in like comic books and shit for like 50 years.
Batman's been around for a very long time. I'm talking like solely like a licensed movie
video game or a licensed TV show video game. You don't count it because it answers it. No,
because I gave separate criteria like TV show only. Spider-Man wasn't a TV show for like 30 years
before. Wait, what? What did Spider-Man get invented? Probably South Park. I mean,
it's a signed Seinfeld Samurai Jack game. Is that good? What? Okay, why so many people just said it
and then now so many people are saying no. There's a purple one over there. These guys talk.
I'm good. Got what I wanted. South Park games have been good and weirdly enough I never gave
either one of them a chance and I always knew that they were good. Don't ask me why. I don't know.
Ahoy there. Squidward tells me you're looking for the king jellyfish. Here we are. Yes. Good thing
too. That monster has been stinging all my good customers in their poop decks. I hear that you
can find him up top of Old Sport Mountain here. Shark Tank? Go hook that beast, sailor. Dude,
I would love a Shark Tank video game even if it was dog shit. You know how much fun that would be?
Why didn't they make that for the Wii? Imagine with the Wii mode and shit you make like a product
and it would be like shitty 3D rendered Mark Cuban. I wanted that. I want that for the Wii,
like a 2005 version of that game. Shark Tank didn't exist in 2005. Why not? Oh boy, Mr. Krabs,
I'll see what I can do. Like I'm talking about I want Mark Cuban to be rendered in the terrain
editor. Not even like the model. You know I want like a pure just like old fucking shitty 3D video
game. Boss fight. This whole body was chattering but not his tongue. You're not going to take all
my 3882 coins are you? No you just killed. That was he was not even a big deal. Oh it's this guy.
This guy's my favorite character in Spongebob. I remember this. Yeah this guy's my favorite. You
know why? Because this guy always reminded me of those little aliens from the Jim Henson Muffet
shit. The guys that go like yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep that's my favorite
character. I just didn't know what his name was. It was guy with huge folding down mouth.
Hello Mrs. Puff. Hello Patrick. I've got a job for you to do. Oh boy. Actually it could be it could
be Mrs. Puff. I found a golden spatula. Yeah it might be Mrs. Puff. I stole it and threw it into
the lake. Yeah no I changed my answer. It's Mrs. Puff. That's my favorite character. You're welcome
to it. I remember she's so fun. Showing off Mrs. Puff. She doesn't do anything. She's actually one
of the only characters in the entire series that is very concerned with how fucking how Spongebob
like breaks shit and hurts people. The only character in the whole series. This farm? What
about Squidward? I think Squidward's just irritated that he exists and like hates him because he
exists. I'm not sure Squidward's ever concerned about anything he does. I think he just hates
him. It's never like ah Spongebob why did you do that? Let me tell you some ways that you could
do that differently instead of throwing my fluid into the dumpster. No he's just like you're an idiot
I hate you. Mrs. Puff is like Spongebob did you hit the break? Just slowly my friend. Like he
Mrs. Puff tries to help him. Oh um well uh no. What am I supposed to do? Did you get the golden
spatula back from the robots on the island? Okay robots on the island get the spatula from the
robots on the island. You got it. I have to get I have to kill that. Oh I know what to do. Throw the
nuke. Get double tapped? Fun. I don't think Spongebob's underwear fits Squidward right.
Wait should I? Hmm I haven't thought of that. Farming. Can I not reach from there?
Do I have to just just destroy all the buildings? I can't reach from here. Use the guard breaker.
Dude you're killing me. Oh just kill me right because these are robots that are they just
just kill me like organic or just kill kill me into a robot too. I made a whole game about this.
I played it. How do I get over this? Can I not throw them? Wait a minute should I? Throwing.
Should I just walk around and throw it at that? I can't reach from there. I oh I can get them on
the bridge. Children's game. Children's game. Children's game. Children's game. Children's game.
Children's game. Children's game. Children's game. Lost in children's game. Sorry children's game.
It's still there. The Simpsons hit and run all over again. No it's not. This is gonna be like
have I ever played a game like this before? I don't think I have. Wait what was that game
that was Yooka-Laylee? Yooka-Laylee. Oh Mario Sunshine. Yeah yeah I didn't play Mario Odyssey
on stream. Played it a little bit off stream and by the way let me tell you oh perfect don't listen
to what that guy said to you like two hours ago. No. That's much better. I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna go this way. Well done Patrick. You're a real star.
Can I get a cookie? No. Swap characters. Oh I guess I don't feel like playing with um Patrick
anymore. This is a shticky. SpongeBob will have to sneak up on it in order to destroy it.
Ah okay. Patrick may throw things at it from a distance. Well let's change back to SpongeBob.
It's a sneak.
That's what they see. You know what I mean? Like I bite him. Bite him. He's coming. SpongeBob's
a little less strong. Dude you're unhinged. Shit. Wait there's something up there. There are
underwear up there. I yeah I'm gonna go get that stuff. Put on Doom OST. You want me to
replace SpongeBob music with Doom OST? Now here comes a real fight in the chat.
This is gonna get interesting I think. I feel like a new sponge. That would be funny. Put it
though. Oh I'm not sure that would be very funny. Absolutely funny. SpongeBob should come back here
later when he knows the crew's bubble move. Oh I don't know the crew's bubble move. What the hell am
I supposed to do? He's vetoing it. Oh that already did. That already happened. That was vetoed when I
read the D in Doom OST. It's very relaxing. Okay I want to get that sock. It goes all the way around.
Okay let's ask you to keep moving. It kind of worked. This is not relaxing at all.
You don't think this is relaxing? You don't think so? Did I go on the wall? Where did I go?
You've never been like sitting on the beach and this is just kind of playing?
Stuff like this is just like that's like that's what they're playing on the beach.
No no no. But you've never gone to any restaurant or a little bar on the beach?
They all play this music. Everyone just looks around and goes like yeah yeah. You get a big
like sip of the drink. Yeah. You just nod your head the whole time that you're in there.
No they don't. Yeah they do. I've been in the same room when this happened. You take the sip of your
big drink with the umbrella in it. You know the big like big shoe drink. It's a huge glass like
shoe thing. This is a stone Tiki. That's what you know. Can I tell you? Stone is one of my favorite
words. Cannot be destroyed with ordinary moves. It can be blown up by thunder Tiki. Beach in Vegas.
Guys I'm I'm 34 years old. You don't think I've ever been to a beach before with a drink in my
like on the on like the beach waterfront or like a beach restaurant before up when I'm in my like
early 20s. As long as these pants are square and this sponge is bob I will not let Bikini Bottom
down. You don't think I've ever been to a beach restaurant where it's like oh we have this like
little beach drink. Oh I'll take one. And the person that you're across from you go try this.
Try. And both of you take a sip of each other's like drinks. You go like oh whoa this is what he
got. And then you never go back ever for the rest of your fucking life. You never go back
to this restaurant or bar ever again. Get him. We got that one wrong. Holy shit that's a lot of
stone in there. That's a lot of stone in there. I want to see it. Yes. 150 bucks open this.
Is that worth doing? I only have 6,700. Do I watch Veggie Tales? No I never did.
Veggie Tales for me was just Alvin and the Chipmunks but scary. And this is somebody that's an avid
listener of Alvin and the Chipmunks. And by avid listener I mean that every time an Alvin and the
Chipmunk song ever came on the radio it was immediately being turned down four or five
notches on the volume. That's how you know an Alvin and the Chipmunk song has come on the radio.
You immediately drop the button. I'm dead. You're not a Christian. Aren't you a Christian?
What do you think? Who told you that? Oh this is Patrick. Okay there's never been one time on
stream where I've been like and guys I want to make sure everyone knows I'm a I'm a Christian.
I don't whatever. I don't give a shit who you are. He said it. You're deranged. Okay hold on.
Oh I want the facts. I want the facts out here. So me just saying you know guys no I've never
mentioned that before. I'm not a Christian. I've never said that. He's fucking deranged.
Somebody wrap him up quick. Where's this uh thing spawning? Oh over there. He's getting political.
Cut the mic. Get my mic off. It's on forever. You know unless there's a power outage.
I told you that today was a weird one. I told you I was in a weird mood and I knew something.
I told you. I prepared you guys two hours ago. I did. I told you two hours ago. Right? I did.
I warned you. I can go to one of the new areas now. I can go downtown right? Holy shit. This is
such a random lol stream. He's so random. Thanks for saying that dude. I try so hard to be like
random. Does it work? Is it working? I need 10 of these right? I want to get up here. I gotta go
all the way around and there's another sock over there. Hulk burger nom nom. Oh boy. Now he's just
pandering. Oh you know what pandering looks like on this channel. I think that's what's happening
right now. I know what that's like. I know what that is. There's that sock all the way across.
Oh this is gonna be annoying. What the fuck? I knocked him to the other side.
Wait freeze this stuff. Shit I hate I hate when I have to come back as other characters.
There's so much content to do. What a fun game. What a great amount of content they've given me.
No. That's what happened to Donkey Kong 64. You know I'll be honest I really didn't play Donkey
Kong 64 really at all. I really didn't. How did I miss that? Remember hearing the emergency
broadcast thing? Like this is a test of the emergency broadcasting system. Did you just hear
that? I did. It's weird. I know that they do that all the time to test it and everything but holy
shit it doesn't scare the absolute hell out of you. I've been in the car before with like the radio on
and all of a sudden you're just like kind of oh the radio's just on this and
it's like what the fuck happened? And then you're sitting there waiting. You're waiting. You're
sitting. You're in the car and you're out of red light and you hear that like and you're sitting
there going uh oh okay what happened? And you're just kind of looking around waiting to see a
bunch of other cars just start fucking driving. That's how you know that they like got it first
or something. They like they're hearing it too. You're at a red light. You see like four cars just
start speeding away. It's like uh oh what's this what's this gonna say?
I think that they should really before doing that they should go like
excuse me just want to let you know that there's about to be a test of the emergency broadcast
system. Here it comes. Like I know here it comes right? I'm kind of going the wrong way aren't I?
They do it every time. No no no they make the loud noise first and then the guy comes on.
They make the and then the guy goes hey just letting you know. Here comes the test.
Where is the box? Back box idiot idiot. Where's it? Where is it though? I don't I don't remember
where it is. Where's it from here? You're going the wrong way. I know I'm trying to figure it out.
Play the actual sound. No no no I'm not doing that. I I think remember before like I don't think you
could do that. No no no I'm not doing it. No now I'm not gonna why am I gonna do that? I'm
not gonna play the emergency broadcast sound. Somebody will be in their bathroom and somebody
like went to go take a dump like fucking 30 minutes ago and they left the stream and now
they turn it back on and they hear that. Yeah I don't want to do that. No that's no that's
fucked up. I don't want to do that. Did I pick Patrick? How did I miss this? I'm also disappointed
that this is not. Hold on. Me not you. I'm disappointed that this is not. No why would
I be disappointed? I'm not gonna say what I was gonna say. Imagine only imagine only needing 30
minutes to dump. I'm not gonna be known as the guy that just talks about like going to the bathroom
every stream. We need at least one in between where I don't do that. Oh super monster combo.
I'm not gonna do the Diablo 3 thing where it just does that every time right?
Remember that? Remember Diablo 3? How cool that was the first like 2000 times it said
wow plus 200 experience bonus super ultra kill and how badly you just wanted to fucking turn
that off and never say that ever again. They never let you turn it off. Diablo 3 by the way
I'm not talking about Diablo 2. SpongeBob can jump up walls well then why would I be Patrick?
Sound like a broken man. Still been thinking about that setting I couldn't undo and I don't
know why I was supposed to say Mario 3. Yes I know SpongeBob can do it. All right SpongeBob let's go.
Cool. Care about the game he's playing. What are you talking about? I'm having a blast. I'm having a
great time. And look I got now I have 10 nine spatulas. There it was again. Who makes that noise?
It's the robots that do it? Oh shit this is King Jellyfish. His first major major encounter
of the game. Gosh everyone is trying to help out today. Look at that I know what he's doing.
Step quietly there that King Jellyfish is just up at the top of this path. Good luck you'll need it.
Thanks Bubble Buddy. I feel like a new sponge. All right here we go. Get on top of Bubba Mountain.
Actually it's huge.
I knew the King Jellyfish was big but who knew he had such a beautiful voice.
Slap him. Is any of this based on an episode or something that he's based on?
And you got to slap him in the head. Wait open this. I can't open that. There it is. Slap him again.
Like a spring breeze. He's gonna lose the King Jellyfish. No I will not.
I feel like a new sponge. Desperate grab. But how many Wiimotes does the jellyfish have too?
Who cares about the ads? Just kill the guy. Why is he getting so close?
Fast. Oh that was fast.
Peanut butter. I could go for some peanut butter right now. Peanut butter and flop sandwich.
Or a deconstructed peanut butter and flop sandwich.
Will you just take a spoon and you take a big spoonful of peanut butter put it in your mouth
and a big spoonful of fluff put it in your mouth. I did that. I still do that all the time.
You're 35 years old. What's wrong with eating peanut butter? Peanut butter is perfect.
I feel like a new sponge. All right so what does that thing do? Oh that's the jelly I needed.
Don't you don't say deconstructed.
Oh deconstructed. That makes me so happy. You're such a hipster. Wait this is like a
we're gonna get like a goodbye from the level. We're gonna be ready. Wait give me that one.
I got it. What the fuck is that? Hey there it looks like you'll have to make a huge
jump at the end of that ramp in order to reach that golden spatula.
Cowabunga. Wow that's a mighty big leap. I think I can do it. I can make it. A jump at the end of
that. At the end I can. Yep that's how he dies. SpongeBob's on like drugs. Oh no look where I am.
Run saved. Get the box. Get the box. Get the box. I got it. Okay I'm good. Open the box. I got it.
The stream is delayed. The stream is delayed. All right should I go at the end of
should I'm gonna see what happens at the very end of the whole thing. Turn somewhere. I mean look
at that. Where does this go? Does this wrap around? This wraps around. Okay here we go.
Thank you. Back to the main menu. Here you go Squidward.
Oh yeah I feel so much better. Can I rub some on? What if I just gave you this?
How many spatulas are in the game? 120? This is why I don't go outside ever. Is it 100?
That's kind of a lot. That's cool. Okay hold on. No no I'm gonna go check out the other zones. I
stick in one area the whole time. Please stop the music. But what if the music changes in a new area?
See the music. Look the music's already changed. Please stop. No I'm not going to turn the music
off. It's it's classic SpongeBob music. Okay this is all right. I have a question. Does it consume
them or do you just have to have them? I don't answer that. My question was already answered.
Goo Lagoon? Downtown or Goo Lagoon? Which one? That sounds more interesting.
Downtown? There's a lot of downtowns. Somebody said this is a concerning amount of missiles.
Okay we're at the bottom of the ocean right? Something really fucked up is going on up there.
This is some World War 3 type shit.
Downtown Bikini Bottom. Once a bustling metropolis. Now a debris covered crater.
Oh it's just debris? SpongeBob the robots are destroying Downtown Bikini Bottom. We have to
evacuate. Definitely favorite character for sure. All right but it's gonna take a while to get all
this dust. Not vacuum. Evacuate. We have to get everyone to safety. Evacue? Can we just load them
up in the boats? That won't do any good. Why not? Because the robots have taken all the steering
wheels. Couldn't we just drive in a straight line? No there are too many turns. Those fiends,
they thought of everything. Never fear Mrs Puff. I'll get those steering wheels back. True.
Why are we seeing? Why did I see even one true? SpongeBob if you're involved I always fear.
But I tell you what if you can pull this off I'll give you a golden spatula. Get all the wheels.
How about a driver's license instead? Nice try.
There's one and it's 11. I need 11 steering wheels. What else is over here?
By the way 15 spatulas gets me to the... This place takes place in Texas.
Oh wait. Explode. Blow up. Who's throwing trash cans at me? Who's throwing garbage cans at me?
Oh you. That was weird. That was kind of like... I didn't like that. That made me feel uncomfortable.
That was strange. Blow up. Oh wait I can get a sock from Patrick right?
Me too. I love opening presents too. Secret? Yep. Good call. Oop-wine sock.
Get that person out of here. Get that person out of here. Nobody said that? Yes they did.
Scroll up. Scroll up. I mean there's like over 9,000 people here. You're gonna have to scroll up a
little bit. Don't ever tell me I can't do anything. Because I can. I thought I could hit it back.
Why did I think I could hit it back? That's what I want to know.
Please. All right. Can I jump on the lamps? What happened? Oh he did it for me. Wait a minute.
Oh well that's neat. I'm gonna do that to all of them. One, two, three. Do it. Over here. Nice.
Do it again. Nice. Bachelor. I love it. I love it. I'm gonna die. Put on some pants.
I'll get them. They're all over the place. I'll collect them. Is there a drivable car?
Can I go over here? I already went over here.
SpongeBob doesn't have a license. We see him driving around every episode.
He's always driving around and like crashing and stuff isn't he? And doesn't Mrs. Puff sitting
there going like, SpongeBob you need to do me a quick favor and hit the brake. Right? That happens
all the time. This looks like cheese puff SpongeBob. You can roll but you can't do anything else.
Being hurt or pressing any button will change you back. What the hell?
Let's try that again. What? What are they doing? Thank god for Gary. No I want to be the SpongeBob.
Can I read? This robot is called G. Love. The best way to deal with him is to bubble bounce him from
above. Stop. I want to roll around. Whatever. I saved your life. Wait, did it again? That was
awesome. That was such an awesome move. All right. Don't touch the red stuff. Okay. Is it hot sauce?
Volcano sauce. Oh, there's a wheel. Wait. How would I press this? Brew. Cool. All right. Cool.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. What do I do? Let's roll around. Let them blow up. I think. Yeah.
I don't want to be the little ball anymore. Stop hitting them, Jeremy.
I know. I'm trying to listen. That was pretty sick. Oh, this bubble buddy. This door is locked
from the inside. Who would do such a thing? Psycho? SpongeBob ice cream from the ice cream truck
is the best ice cream. I agree. And that's not even what you said. I just said that after you.
I want to get up there. Watch this. Watch this. Ready? Are you guys watching?
Oh, wait. Don't watch this part. I go higher on the trampoline.
I get that from here. Hey, vaude watchers. Why don't you skip forward? Don't do that. You're
going to miss the best joke of the whole night. How does this go? What was the joke? I didn't do
it yet. I just said, if you skip. Most people, when they skip, they go like 20 minutes. They go
forward, forward, forward. And they go 10, 15, 20 minutes forward. You don't just go like 10
seconds forward. Who skips 10 seconds on like a more than three, four, five, six hour vaude?
I actually do. All right. I've got 10 K of these things. Can I dump them with the bag upside down
at the bank? What do I do with these? Buy weapons. Oh, that's cool. I'll give it to Mr. Krabs. I guess
I really haven't explored completely the hub world, have I? Give them to Mr. Krabs. I will in a minute.
I just like jumping around. It's fun. You can open up areas with them. Oh, that's cool.
I know how to get this open. Just make him angry. Oh, all right. Now what do I go from here? Kill
this guy. I'm at the joke waiting room. Oh shit. All right. Uh, okay. Let's think here. Think quick.
So, um, somebody said something about toothpaste, right? It's quick. Somebody said like a toothbrush.
The guy from like 1700s having a toothpaste with sand in his mouth. Somebody say, somebody do
something like that. Quick. I'm in a lot of trouble here. You'll have to open this door.
How do I get up there? Open this door from the inside. How do I do that? What? That's all it did is
close the door. It closed the... No bag. It just closes the door. It closed the window.
I thought that was it. I thought I was ready. I'm gonna be the ball. Let's go be the ball. Okay. I am
ball. That's 2100 fucking points. That's worth it, right? 2100? That's a lot that I get. There's
nothing in here. There was nothing in there. Oh, it opened the gate. Fod watchers skip. No, no, no,
no, no. I'll know if you skip. I'll know if you skip it. I'll draw it down. I'll know. I'll know
who did it. Fod watchers run. That's like the equivalent of, okay, how many times per minute
do you guys think that somebody types into Google? Does somebody know if I unfollow them?
Does somebody know if they see your... Does somebody know if you see their tweet? How many
times a second do you think that's typed into Google? If I have read receipts off,
will people still know I saw their text? Quick rewind.
Oh, that gap looks big. Okay. I'm definitely not making that jump. How is anyone going to get
across there? New character? Oh, more robots. Looks impossible. Okay. Okay. I'll go get Sandy
to help me out. Where's Sandy? I don't know where Sandy lives. Oh shit. I need to have watched the
show. No, I actually don't know. I know that Spongebob, Patrick, and Squidward are neighbors.
I don't know where Sandy lives. I know that she's in a dome somewhere. Did she just get off the
bus? She just gets off the bus. Okay. Well, that makes it way easier. All right. Let's go jump to
the top of these steps. Sandy can glide across the gap to the next rooftop by double jumping
and holding A. Nice. I don't think I'll ever not play with Sandy. Double jump and a glide? Oh wait.
I love it. I love the jump too. Jump looks exactly like those... There's a toy. There's a toy. I don't
know what it is. What toy is this? It's like a little string and you pull the string up from the
top of the head and it goes... All the legs and arms come up and down. What am I talking about?
What is it? An old wooden toy. It's a toy that's like wood. It's a depression era toy. Yes. What
is it called? Called a barrel man. Are you lying? No, this is not... What the... This is not it. No.
It's a wooden toy that has string and legs and arms move up. What is this thing? Jumping jack.
There it is. Thank you. It's like a... Yeah. Okay. Yeah. It goes like this. Don't leave.
You're hovering over the X. Just stay. It's okay. All right. You're just like... You were about to
click and I stopped you. Just wait. Skip 10 seconds. Hey, what's up? Just want to make sure
that you actually did what I told you to do. Now, if you want to be cool and we can be like,
you know, but like a big community here, I'd like for you to skip an hour and 10 minutes
and I'll see you there for a sacred surprise. Skip an hour and 10 minutes. It's going to be fun.
What's that exact time though? It'll be 3... It'll be 3.42. 3.42. All right. Where am I going?
We can't skip when it's live. This isn't for you. This is for the Vod Watchers.
Right. Does she have something? Sandy can do a chop attack by pressing X. If you chop while in
the air, you will perform a karate kick. Okay. Cool. Wait, what? Sandy can lasso the object by
pressing B. So, tutorial, what you're telling me is Sandy is the best character in the game.
She just has every awesome move. Sandy can swing from a swing hook by pressing B.
I don't like it. It didn't say hold B. It said press B. It said press B, not hold B.
B. Press B, not, hey, hold it. It didn't say that. Now, what do I do now?
And she turned into a ball. Shit. Wait. Blow this up. That makes me so mad. I want to like
leave the level. Fuck. No, I can't leave the level. I think I just fucking glitched the game
out to get that one. It's right over there, you baby. Is it? What? Dude, you just call me baby?
What else can I get with this? It is right here. I need to get back up there. You enjoy halo.
Yeah. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. All right. I'm paying attention now.
Everyone's yelling at me. Where's the trampoline? Remember, you're just crying. You're crying.
Oddwatches, skip whole stream. How would you do that? The stream is sick. All right. We're back.
Which way is correct? Which is the right way? The stream is infected. So again, hold it. That's
actually kind of fun. He's got it under control. Sandy can lasso a rope up at pressing B. Sandy's
the best. Watch out, explodes. Good point now. Where do I go from here is the question.
We've got the whole area. Oh boy. There we are. Yes. This is a fake Sandy. I don't think it is.
I think this is real. I will destroy this though. Just get out of here and I'll get one of these.
Five. Well, anything else I can do from here? I go into the tuba. Holy shit, you can.
No, you can't. Oh, damn it. I thought you could. Honestly, that was cool. And Sandy's best
character in the whole game. So I've unlocked Sandy. You have to press R. I thought you'd win.
I need to have someone replace my old antenna with this shiny new one. So call cable company.
Yes, sir. That fair antenna is shinier than a three dollar bill. Well, why don't you replace
it yourself? I'm not really much of a jumper. So what's jumping got to do with it? Because the
old antenna is up there.
Which is gross, by the way. I just want to make sure I make my opinion on that very well heard.
The robots have blocked off that building and I can't do all those fancy moves you and Spongebob
do to get across these gaps. All I can do is flex. Want to see? Great. So what are you going to do
with the old antenna? I fucking hate ice tea with tons of sugar. I hate it.
There's a lot of sweet tea can get to a point where it's like syrup. It's not even a drink.
Like you could pour sweet tea over pancakes and that would be OK. That's a lot.
Sandy may cross the large gas by double jumping and holding a. Yeah, I know.
Or the candy bottom motor company. But I like ice tea. I like ice tea that should sweet with
sugar in it. Sweet tea is at a whole nother level. It's just it's just too much.
It's just killed that person. Swing. Hey, I can't. I'm trying to read swing from swing from sweet.
I know. I stopped saying that. I know how to do this. It's a funny cartoon.
Oh, what? Hold on. You're putting on Spongebob's underwear.
I don't know about that. Why does everything explode? Oh, almost fucked it up. But I'm there.
I like that guy. That's my favorite character in Spongebob. I think so.
Twenty one hundred dollars. That seems like a lot. What is going to open? Rebuild the bridge.
Oh, I have no. Holy shit, I almost missed it. Oh, what the fuck happened?
That guy just grabbed me. That was. Maybe there's no reason for that.
See those baits right there? That's bullshit. Just do it. Just kill me. How did I miss that?
I don't know. I just picture somebody sitting at their computer right now like
like just laughing at me. Give me the fucking thing. What did I win? Did I get what I needed
to get? I didn't. I need to get the antenna. I get the box though, right? That was just for
the bonus. Oh, well, did I miss a box? I don't think I did. Back where you started. Well,
at least I got a spatula. Oh, you can get hit in the air and you lose your jump.
They are laughing. I picture with like any of you in the same room. You're all just
fracking the fuck up after when I get hit by even when I get hit by an enemy.
I don't know why, but for some reason you guys are playing some like old fucked up stupid game
like trouble. I'm just on in the background and you catch it every now and then you guys just all
fucking start laughing your asses off and when it's a bad happens to me. Let's not screw this
up. Please. No, don't I don't need to do that. I just do it. You just go a different way.
I'm going to wait. I'm going to wait. No, no, no, no. I know I'm at the crosswalk right now and I
I'm not taking that chance. No, I'm not going to win the hand. I got nine seconds. When the
hand starts popping up, I'm not fucking running. I'm just going to wait till the next cycle where
I can cross the crosswalk. Not going to happen. Then you start to go like, oh fuck, I got to get
over there quick as fast as I fucking can. See now I got a full time here. Man, I did it again.
What are you just fucking?
Better. The fuck am I? You're going to hit by a train. You were. I know I was here before,
but where's this bridge? I was getting rid of a bridge. Where's this? I got to get the antenna.
I got to go up higher than this. Exactly. I'm pretty good at it. I've got, I've got like 10
years of experience pretending to be bad at video games. So come on. Yeah, but I wanted to see what
was over there. I want to see what was over there. Wait, can I get your ass? I can. I don't think I
can make that one though. So what? Just get your own underwear. I don't, I don't get that thing.
I don't understand that. This is really weird. Where is SpongeBob's underwear? Get, put on your
own underwear. That just tried to tell me. Get across large gaps, lasso, and then glide.
The hell is it trying to say? Oh, I did it. Any more? Nope. Defeated. Sorry, I had to do it.
What does this do? What's the trampoline down? Is he going to jump on it? Come on, jump on it.
And Sandy sneak? Checkpoint. That's going to be an issue then. I can't even. That was the checkpoint
from Cruisin' USA. Yeah, it was. You're incredibly perceptive. And just because you got that, I'll
give you my best intro. Cruisin' USA. Not very good, but I tried. Come on, better make good use
all these. That was wicked cringy. Don't talk shit to me. You can lasso the red ones. Can I?
Jerma cringe compilation. I, you know what? I wonder what that would actually look like.
You know what I really have to say about that? Here's what I actually have to say about that.
I think you'd probably get to like Jerma cringe compilation 60 before you ran out of clips. I'm
being honest. And I have to be honest. Watch. Come back. Yeah. They would be scraping the barrel by
10. You know, thank you. That means a lot. That means that this, you don't think, wasn't prepared
for that. That means that there's only like six hours worth of cringe. Stop going on this trampoline.
What would that even look like? I really want to know. Part of me wants to know what that looks
like. There's a lot to go through though. Go have people make cringe compilation videos of me and
watch them. I feel like that's levels of self-deprecation. I'm not sure I want to
cross. Do you know what I mean? Like that's like, oh, hey guys, let's watch. Let's watch like the
most cringy shitty things I've ever done. Isn't that funny? Maybe. So what is this box?
Oh, I'm going to be cringe night. Don't do that to yourself. No, I'm not going to do that to myself.
I don't want to know. Travel to the lighthouse, but to anything else I can do here. That's easy.
Just play the whole wow stream. Are you ready? Kids set. Oh, what? You can't say, are you ready?
Kids and not have the next thing be, I can't hear you that go shit. So this must be how you open up
the door. Isn't that hard? No fun. Game gets, or hits a huge difficulty spike after the real first
block. Didn't I fight the first boss already? I'm the first boss, the squid, but that was a mini
boss. Oh, out of here. How many more of these do I need? I need two more.
You on the other hand, I want you to explode, but I got a purple one in there too. I don't forget
the button. I just make it sure that I get this. I don't want to hit this button and teleport out
the button. Dude doesn't do anything. I feel like a new sponge. It was a sock.
Let's wait. What was there? Did I miss a sock? It was a trampoline. Oh shit. I hit it and then I
didn't notice anything immediately. And I looked over chat and somebody said nothing. Two people
said like nothing, nothing. LOL. And I'm like, okay, it must be nothing. Two people said it out of
9,000. Uh, let's go back to Sandy. How many, uh, I've got 16. I think I want to check out the other
area. There's two other areas I can go to now. Or should I go get the antenna for Larry the antenna?
I like jumping around. It's a lot of fun. It makes me feel happy. I would have just jumped into the
box. All right, Larry, SpongeBob dream levels are pog. I hope you get that far. All right. I
get Larry to the top, right? I can finally watch those reruns of the, but I already fixed it.
Nevermind. I already did it. Yeah. I'm going to let me try one of the other areas.
Dream levels are awesome. Okay. Kini bottom. Oh, look at that. You get, this is
SpongeBob's closet. Let's just go to SpongeBob's closet and go to sea needle. What's the one with
15? It's over here. Travel to the Poseidon. Okay. Cool. Lagoon or Poseidon. Oh yeah. Turn in the socks.
Here's your golden back scratcher. I don't speak Italian. Oh yeah. I got, I got lots of money.
This isn't money. So do you want to trade shiny objects for a golden spatula? Yeah. That's quality
craftsmanship. I do it again. So do you want to trade? Yes. I have less than a thousand bucks.
I wonder how many times you can do that. I'm going to the Poseidon. 126,000 for all those. Holy
shit. This is the real first boss. Oh shit. I got to sit up then. Whoa. Wait for the bounce.
Like that. And then in the head. I get it. I know what to do.
I don't, I don't get it. I don't know what to do. I don't understand. Oh, that's the bounce.
But will he get the drop on the robot? That's the bounce. That's the bounce.
Get off my screen. Get off my screen you fucking like 10 sub stream labs notification. Get out of
here. Oh, that was a good job. Bad execution. Cause I was trying to pay attention to the boss.
That was slowly slow to come out. Get out of here. You bad 10 sub notification. Oh, watch out for
Sandy. I did get the drop. Do it again. I get it now. It's like the robots left itself vulnerable.
That's taking a beating out there. I wasn't even doing this thing.
Oh, phase two. Do I tag him in? Bounce and throw the head. What does that mean? Bounce and throw
the head. So I have to like just wait. Everybody's wearing his underwear.
Throw the head into, uh, into the electricity.
Right back on her head. Just give it back.
And there we go. Nice flying, uh, head thing move by Patrick.
There's a swole spongebob in the background. Where? Shit, there is. Oh wow.
That's losing its head. Now it's Sandy's turn. This is the last phase coming up.
I've never seen such an electrifying match. How does Jerma manage to read some comments?
That's how Jerma manages to not know, uh, where he's standing half the time.
So Jerma gets to the same spot he's been to three times and doesn't remember he was there.
Wait. Oh, I got to hit you right in the chin. He's talking in third person again.
Mom, he's talking in third person again. Not the top bro. Not the top bro. Finally did it.
Boss defeated. What does it do? That's pretty pogchamp. He still says the whole thing.
He still says the whole thing.
Where are the subtitles? They're on. They're right here.
No, not really. I was waiting for someone to say it. Exactly. And as your non-friend,
I dropped like a few, I dropped 300 frames just real quick and I was waiting for a fiber,
like F fiber high. He's got fiber lab out loud. Tell you what I'm going to do for you. This way
you won't hurt yourself and you can just keep working on getting me into the jump bucket.
I already said, don't stop using a VPN. It's snake oil. You're the best non-friend,
don't you understand? I've committed to a point where it has to be real.
I've committed to a point where it needs to be real. Very cool. So that was just a single boss
fight, huh? Oh, wait, I, wait, I, this is where she lives. She's that close. I thought she lived
like in another city. Wait, this is blowing my mind. Sandy lived right here, like right down
the street. I thought she lived like 10 to 20 miles away. Holy shit. This isn't cannon.
Are you ready kids? Let's go. Oh no. He turned it from SpongeBob. Hold on. I don't want to lose.
I only have, that's a long time. Nevermind. I think as many jokes as you want, Jeremy.
Talking in third person again. Things he's talking to himself somehow. I don't know what
he's doing. It's been pretty long. Go for an oh, tartar sauce cloud.
Maybe when I get, maybe later. That was the easiest spatula of the whole game.
Wait, isn't this where the, I don't need it. Don't need it. I definitely don't need it.
He's sitting right here, right? He's like, I don't need it. I don't need it.
He freaks out. I don't know what happens after that. All I know is I've seen the GIF
like a thousand times. I don't know what happens after that. I've never seen the episode.
SpongeBob's a cool little guy, Annie. Can I do anything else in here? Of course I've seen the
episode. Can I go actually in the tree? Let me teach you how to bowl a bubble. Press this button
and you'll bowl a bubble that can knock down robots from a safe distance. Wow. Really? Remember
though, the bubble ball only works on things that are close to the ground. Got it.
From a joke, it's 342, guys. I, I know what it was. 342. That's in like 30 minutes. Nice. That's
cool. Charging it goes, but yeah, it goes faster. 40 to go over here. I'm assuming that's probably
end game. Golden factuals to enter, to unlock. 30. Go to goo lagoon. It's cool.
All right. I'll go to goo lagoon. Well, wait, I want to, let me go,
let me go inside of this building. What is this? Oh shit. There's nothing like the smell of bubbles
in the morning. What did that do? There's a timer. Oh shit. Let's go. You're going to catch me with
that one. Didn't you? Yep. You almost did. Yeah. That's sunshine flashbacks for sure.
Let's go in the police station. Okay. Now give me, there's gotta be a spatula in every single
building. All right. It has to be. I think bottom most wanted it. Oh, it's, it's just, it's a,
it's a bestiary. Oh, these things. We'll get the golden underpants. I'll get it. Ready?
Why is every spamming a link? First link spam. We're coming back. First actual link spam. What
is it? This is, I'm intrigued. Hold on a second. This is first purple, like just huge wave of purple
links. That's pretty good. That's, that's worth showing. I think. Nice. Okay. Come on, let's get
this. Get this mouse off the screen. Okay. So like where's this golden underpants is up here.
Yeah, it is right here. Extra health slot. Can I get up there?
I just was able to break the game and go past that without 40. Oh, I got an extra health pot.
Why does it want me to turn into a ball here? I can't figure this part out.
I'm a quick show staking. I could go for one right now. Actually, not kidding for real.
We don't do that stuff anymore, kid. We're retired. Is that the TV repairman?
No, it's that excited sponge kid again. Oh, are you sure he can't fix the TV?
Fake voice. Not real voice. Twidby, my greatest honor to come fix the TV.
I would have done that for 50 bucks. Hey, sponge kid, you really want to help out?
Okay, then. But lighten up a bit on the enthusiasm, huh? You're making my bowels act up.
We've got a link. Only one link for 10 minutes. Are you sure you're up to this task? Absolutely,
barnacle boy. Well, go to the couch to access the Mermalair. Wait, there's a whole Mermalair?
You're a fake fan. 10 minutes have not passed. No, it has not.
Go over to the couch and we'll go to the mermaid lair. Wait, we can watch TV?
Oh, I thought we could watch an episode of Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy.
What's his shoe size? 13.
What the fuck are you watching, man? Enter the Mermalair. Yeah, it's everybody's dream to go to
the Mermalair. Wait, what's going on down here? This looks corrupting. All right, I'm gonna die.
I've already done it like twice. I don't need to do it again. Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy.
You shouldn't sneak up on Mermaid Man like that. His heart's not so good.
Come to think of it, nothing on him is that good anymore. Sorry, Mermaid Man.
It's just that I'm always so excited to see you two. Standing in your awesome presence gives me
the chills of justice. See, I've got goosebumps on my goosebumps on my goosebumps on my goosebumps on
my. All right, kid, knock it off. Just tell us what you want. What a great character. Well,
I really want a new pair of sunglasses. Patrick sat on my old ones. That's not what I meant.
Actually, it's a good thing you showed up, young sponge of goodness. It is. It is. A bunch of
evil robots have taken over the Mermalair security system. It's up to you to shut it down and stop
them. Well, why him? We're perfectly capable superheroes. Because it's Thursday and we have
a whole bunch of doctor's appointments. Fish sticks. I forgot. Go talk to the Mermalair computer
in the next room. She'll tell you what you need to do. Accept this awesome responsibility, Mermaid
Man. You won't be disappointed. To the doctor's office. Away. Did somebody just say LOL Bernie
Sanders? Why is every voice Bernie? That wasn't Bernie Sanders. That wasn't even close.
Oh, there's another Bernie. Everybody's not Bernie. Oh, I'm going to die. Bernie, LOL, you normie
loser. What the fuck is going on here? Wait, don't let me read this. Don't step on the red squares
off the disco floor. Why not? Wait, hold on. Let me process. Let me just let me process.
Did you say that Bernie was normie? What? What? I'm trying to figure out what that means.
Get out of here. Got him back. You missed that one.
You're in such a shitty spot. Just get out of here. So bad. Why am I trying? No, you're right. I'm
going to let that one stick here because I'm trying to knock them back at him. Bounce them,
throw them back at him. And it worked a couple of times. So I was like, Oh, that's just what I'm
supposed to do. So yeah, I don't, I don't. Yeah. Can I spin this? You can use bubble ball to turn
paddle wheels. Ball one side of this paddle to make a turn. So I'm making that up. Okay. He wants
me to go this way. Can I turn this on? Your chair is about to break. 15 minutes until it's funny.
This is going to be like a, oh, damn it. Shit. It's still possible. Is it though? No, it's not.
Fuck. Fuck. Important. This is very important. Seriously. This is the most important thing in
the whole stream. We only have a few minutes to do this. I need somebody to go back to like,
uh, I need somebody to go back to the first like fucking 40 minutes of the screen.
And I need something. I need to, I need to, I need something that I said that I can use this
like a puzzle for the Vaude watchers. When I say, Hey, welcome. You're paid Vaude watchers. Here you
are. Okay. I need you to go back and we need to get the secret code from one hour and 41 minutes.
Right. If you can decipher the code, meet me at four hours and 22 seconds. You know what I mean?
Let's make like a fucking stupid game for the Vaude watchers. I need like a, a one line that
we can, I can refer back to it. 342. I need an exact time period for this as well. I'm not clicking
that. It has to be something that was like at least two hours ago. Colgate thing. What was the
exact time for Colgate? Okay. Like if you can, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like go, go. Hey guys,
go back, go back to one hour in 42 minutes. And if you can find me a C a certain name
that will decipher that. No, it's gotta be, okay. Dave Colgate, right?
D is ABC. That's three. A is would be one. That's three, one shit. It doesn't work out.
I need something like a, something that, uh, damn it. ABC D is four. D is four. D is not three.
Okay. That works. That's four, one. So V would be 20. So that's 22, four, four hours and 12
minutes. E, A, B, C, D, E, four hours, 10, 12 minutes and five seconds. Cause then four hours
and 12 minutes. It's like, Hey, you solve the puzzle. How can you say so much without saying
anything? Somebody, all right, let me pause this. I want the Dave Colgate to be the, I, what I tell
them to go back to. And then when they get the Dave, I, they need to figure out the secret code
to find the timeframe to skip to. Cause the Dave would be the code would be the time in the Vaude.
That's what I'm saying. Yes. Dave equals the time like for the Vaude and like ABC D would be for
the fourth letter of the alphabet. So that's our four. You understand what I'm saying? Oh, wait,
the A would be one. How are you not getting the corresponding? What are you talking about?
Yeah. Four, somebody got it. Four, one, two, two, five, four hours.
Okay. So in minutes and seconds, that's four, 12, 25. Yes. All right. Okay. Here's what was the
exact timeframe that I started talking about Dave Colgate. One, 14, 32. I need an exact time.
What is he doing here? What would have been worst joke 2020? It didn't even happen yet.
Can I blow this? I have to be Patrick for this. Where's the bus?
Actually really isn't that good.
No, I'm not doing it.
It was still putting in a fucking image. Hey, what the fuck? Oh, the 10 minute
cool down ended. Right. Right. Right. Right. Dave Colgate bit starts at 58 minutes in the Vaude.
Okay. Hold on. I have to beat this part. What the hell? It's not on a timer, right?
No. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. 5740 is exactly where it starts. All right. Steakums. This is okay. I'm going to show this
just because I want, I, why do I have to, why would I show this? I'm going to, but like,
why would I do this? By the way, good luck getting your Steakums to look like that and be like that.
It's very hard to do. Okay. Let's do it again. This one's going to be the hard one.
It's not that hard. That wasn't that hard. It's when you just walk. All right. Mermaid man. Now what?
Well, for a joke that sucks so bad, it seems like a whole lot of you can't wait for it to happen.
Give me that spec. Incoming worst joke of the year. You, no, stop. You're getting in my head.
Holy shit. This is a huge, this goes way up. I'm going to stick with SpongeBob.
There's nothing like the smell of bubbles in the morning. It smells like victory.
Just don't get knocked off. Should I've, I couldn't have stayed in Patrick. That
isn't how that works. Wait, is there a dog? Why is it a dog? That guy was making dog sounds.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What the hell was that slide?
It is a slide. I got it. Got the purple one. Oh, whoa. Bridge activated. Nice.
I got the bridge active. I can destroy this. Whoa. Shit.
Move, move, move, move. Don't watch out for that. I don't want to get hit by that.
I don't want to, I got to stand here for a second. I don't want to get the,
the dude's going to come over here and he's going to, Hey, what's going on? Vod watcher.
Welcome. You made it to the third step of the puzzle. Now the trickiest part of the entire game
so far is you're going to have to go back, back to the beginning, at least somewhere in the first
hour. And you're going to need to find the name that was said. It was a first and last name that
was said. And once you figure that out, you're going to have to go to the timestamp that you
can decipher the code for the timestamp from that name. And if you can figure it out, you're going
to find yourself a prize. Good luck. Not going to give them the, you think I'm going to give them
the time? No. Telling them, Hey, go to, go to fifth. They might still be here. Get out of here.
Go do the puzzle. Don't stick around here. Don't go do the puzzle. Get the fuck out of here.
Oh, all right. If I say the exact time, then it defeats the purpose of the puzzle.
All right. So what if they're still here? I can't even say the time. I can't say the actual,
okay. I, wait, there's no more VODs, right? There's no more VOD chat anymore, right? There is.
Shit. Oh fuck. How do I, can I turn the chat off from VODs? VOD chat stopped a year ago. Wait,
but did it? I missed a button. Shit. No, it didn't. You just can't type in it anymore.
Delete the VOD. You can't even do anything. I just can the whole thing. Fuck it. It didn't work out.
Hey, by the way, the prize, I'm just going to scream in my room at the exact second.
I know the exact time. I'm going to just stand it back there. I'm just going to scream like into
the wall at the exact second that it happened. Okay. I didn't hit that. I thought I could make it
play copyrighted music. So the VOD gets me. Um, I can't go back to the stream from like an hour
ago and play copyrighted music. Oh, that was such a huge brain thing to do when we were talking
about it. God damn it. What a huge brain thing. I could have put on, I could have put on
that copyrighted music while we were talking about it. Oh well. The first one is here.
When you have pressed them all, you should return here to press the master shutdown button.
Just redo it.
Return here. Got it. Are you listening to me?
Listening. Got it. Well, at least the people in the archive channel can have fun.
Right. Really should have been paying attention to that. What that said. Can you say it again?
Press all of the security override buttons throughout the murmur. Okay.
Press all of them. Is there another one that I didn't get?
Press the master shutdown button to lower the bridge to the villain containment system.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. What is it? Give me the good one. Give me the one that everybody
wants me to click on. Give me the good one. I don't know. I don't think this is it.
I don't. I just clicked on one that I don't. I think that is wrong.
Jerma Patrick.
Okay. This is good. This is worth it. This is actually worth keeping on, by the way, for a while.
This is the wrong one. How could that be wrong? It's great. He's a both good.
Oh, did I see Jerma Patrick deep fake? You can't deep fake my face onto Patrick's face. That's
not how it works. You can't do that. Can somebody do it? Can somebody deep fake me onto Patrick?
Somebody has to try. Even if it looks like shit. You guys are just like adding people.
Do not underestimate the power of the chat. Yeah, that's right. Anytime you underestimate
chat, it comes back to bite you. Click on the actual Imgur link. Why am I Patrick?
I wonder. Patrick's a moron. That's what it is, right? Let's continue. Patrick is a fan favorite.
He's my fan favorite. Yes, I know. I love Patrick. He's my favorite character.
Before season four. After season four, it was Mrs. Puffs. No, that's not true. It was Mrs. Puffs
always. Mrs. Puffs always. Electrical grid? What's this?
It's like a spring breeze.
You know what I thought of recently? You know what was the greatest job on earth?
It had to have been the greatest job on earth. Is being the guy that played the rock and roll piano
way back in the day. Because you just had to mash like four keys at the same time over and over
again. Just go while somebody else went. I would have loved to do that job. And you get to stand
up and you can just be like, you're like, everyone's cheering you on. And then you move a little bit to
the right. You got a big jacket on. There's like a bunch of flare all over it and shit. You look
awesome. I would have hammed that up like crazy. Did somebody just say that? I'm trying to read
fast and play. Let me say the DMT is kicking in. Oh, don't die. Wait this. Okay. Hold on.
He's shooting missiles. It's not fair. Did it hit me? Oh, whoa. Whoa. Oh, they knew I was going
for the underwear. Just get this. Wait, open it. Oh, I get to go up. Did I get the other
teleport box? Penis is showing. That's okay. The camera's not on. Whatever. I don't know why.
I want to go up there. Oh, there's spatula at the end of this. That better be.
I think that's the last of our friend's SpongeBob. By the way, don't fucking run or anything.
Sorry. Fuck. This is why I have my mic turned down. For those of you that are asking, why is
the stream always so low? Because anyways, before I had that little problem there,
I was going to say the last two streams have been like monster stream. There was like 15,
fucking thousand people at the other one. There was like at the peak here, there was like 9,
9,400, 9,500. That's crazy. This is just a huge amount of people have been hanging out
the last few streams. All right. Let me get this. Let me get this. Wait for the cycle.
That cycle. I just damage hit damage. No, I can't. It's all this for a sock. Oh, there we go.
Ooh, this is called rolling. Finally. All right. Okay. Okay. Spatula is right there.
Uh, I mean, let's go get that first.
Boy, there's, I see my eyes. Am I going to play chess? That's not going to happen ever.
I, I think the only time I've ever really played, I don't even know where the, how the characters
move. I know the pawns can move one or two spaces forward. I know that the horse can move in an L.
I don't even know how many spaces. I just know it's an L. I know that the,
the Bishop with the thing with the crown on it can move in all the way diagonally. And then I
know that they're the king and the queen. They can move any direction. I always just get the
queen out there and just get the queen killed. So I get, I lose every time. I just get so impatient
that I just know that the queen's like a super assassin, like really cool character to come out
with. And like, I just take the queen out all the time just to go like on like assassin missions.
And she just dies. I'm like, I'm sick of this. I don't want to move in an L. Where's the queen?
With a great big ball. Impatient. Yeah. I can't play chess. No way.
Here's how to win at chess. Call everyone who beats you a cheater. How do you cheat at chess?
You're like extra pieces in your pocket.
So this is like mouse trap, huh? Move the pieces of machinery along the track.
Well, this is going to be horrible. I can already tell. Let's see what happens.
Oh no. All right. So then it has to go. Okay. And then come on. Hurry up. How do I make this move?
He's smarter than a fifth grader. Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Just wait a minute.
I didn't even get a look at it all. This, I don't even know why these things all happen.
How do I get the hammer to move down? Wait, wait, hey, hey, how did that happen?
Did I just throw a ball at it? Oh, what the hell? Okay. And what does that do?
Oh, this thing's set up. All right. Let's go. Have you missed? How are you missing?
Get it! Blaming SpongeBob. Ready. Here it comes. Okay. Then it's going to get scooped up and then
it's going to get placed up there and then it wraps around. Okay. Scoop successful.
Now it's going to go around here and then end up down here. It's going to get scooped up there
and then it's going up here. Okay. Then it goes that way. That's going fast.
It's exhausting pretending. Scoop it already. Come on, man. Oh, I'm going to have to do this again.
Come on. There's timing on. Where'd he go? Shit. I think I fucked it up again. Hey!
What the fuck?
Way too early. All right. It's to go around the whole damn thing.
What is it? Oh, that was dumb. What the hell happened? Yeah. What happened there? Whatever.
This is the one. I agree. I think this actually is the one.
Yeah, this is the one. Got it. Fuck. Okay. I thought the arrows were talking about like,
I like you like tilt this, tilt it. Well, look, you got to tilt it around and get it in the middle.
Those old stupid toys. I thought it was like tilt, tilt, tilt it around. You get it in the
middle. I didn't. Okay. Shit. I thought it was just like, oh, get it in the hole.
Didn't he say get it in that hole too? Can he say something like that? Like, oh,
make sure you get it in the hole. Can he say that? Congratulations. You've solved the puzzle.
It took a ton. Oh, no, wait for 12 or one, two to five. Right. All right.
Four, one, two, two, five. I thought it was four, one, one, two, five.
Imagine not solving it. Congratulations. You solved the puzzle. You did it. You did everything
possible and your prize. Congratulations. By the way, I just did that into my chair
and I've been sitting on this for four hours. I was like, I don't want to scream because that's
way too loud. I'm like, I got to muffle it somehow. Okay. I can't laugh this hard.
All right. I got to relax. Like hairs in my mouth. Ow. I have a dog.
I was thinking, do it into my hand. That won't muffle it enough. There's no pillow in here.
There's nothing in here. I have to like scream. There's like a cushion here. Oh my goodness.
What the fuck is wrong with me? I can't even talk about it.
Congratulations. You ate your own ass. Okay. We're going to pull this back. I'm going to,
I'm going to get control of the stream again. Where's the ball? I got to get, I got to get
under control. Come on. Have it not be, is that too early? Oh God. My whole body hurts right now.
That was just stupid. No, knock on this way. Come on. Did I do it? Blow air in it. I was holding,
I was trying to throw, I was trying to throw it in the air. I was trying to throw it in the air.
Hold on. I got to, I have to let go. I got to go like brush my teeth. I'm freaking out.
What happened? Dave Colgate. Come on, do it. You should use your brand new mouth shower.
Oh man. That was too early. That was too early. It was too early, right? Oh no.
I don't think he needs a hand. All right. All right. In the back here. Okay. Let it up.
Drop that fan. I swear to fucking God. I thought that was the I did it cut scene.
That wasn't the you did it cut scene. Chat's going to leave if you don't stop pretending.
What do you, did it go over? Hey, and some of you VOD watchers, I'll see you four hours and 24
minutes for an extra special surprise. I can't even fucking believe it. I can't believe it. I
can't believe it. What am I going to do? I can't fucking believe it. I can't believe it. It's not
hard. It's not hard. It's fucking easy. It's why did I say fucking like that? It's fucking easy.
No, it's easy. Just do it. It's not even hard. It's a simple puzzle. It's just a simple thing.
You just have to time it right. Like that's a lot of you guys right now. Just like, I'm just
going to sit down. Yep. He'll get it eventually. Oh, he did it. Now how's about giving old Mr.
Krabs that shiny gold. I'll give you a promotion. A promotion. Sure. You'll get a whole extra 10
seconds added to your break time. Oh, a whole extra 10 seconds added to your break time.
No, I'm sorry Mr. Krabs. As enticing as that sounds, I can't give this to you. I need every
golden spatula I can get. Mine was worse probably. I understand boy. I'll just dock 30 seconds from
your break time instead. That means I have a negative break. Thanks Mr. Krabs. That was just
for one spatula by the way. Oh, I'm so defeated. Mine is 20. What's going on here? Why are you guys
fucking with the algorithm? Why are you guys fucking with the algorithm? Why are you guys
welcome? You made it Vaude Watcher. Your secret prize is to go back to exactly
61 minutes and if you can tell me the name of the first letter that comes up at the first moment
that you hear the sound of me talking, you're gonna... I don't care. Just watch the rest of the
stream. Just watch the rest of the stream. I don't care anymore. It was fun until like
10 words into that sentence. Hope you had fun.
Where's my prize? Oh no, he hates us. Stop doing minus 20 you fucking with the algorithm.
Uh, what am I missing? What are you guys doing? Stop doing that. You're gonna break my computer.
Did I talk to the computer again? It was a joke in the game. Oh, well the joke in the game is
affecting me in real life. Press all of the security override buttons throughout the murmur layer,
then return here. So what the heck? What am I missing over that way? I missed a button. What?
Where? Probably up. All right, if you see a button, let me know. Please tell me. All right,
get all that and then over there. It's right there. Press that one. Whoa, there's an oyster.
I didn't have enough money to open this one. How many do I have? Oh, what did I spend all the money
on? It was on another clam. All right, let's just farm. We're gonna farm just for a minute.
Just for a minute. Just for a minute. Hey, VOD watchers, go watch Vine Compilations instead.
Why would you say that? You're putting my stream under Vine Compilations? Come on.
What the heck are you? Come on. Wow. Can I get up that? I feel like I can get up there.
How do I make that jump? I just said that the VOD watcher probably wouldn't see it unless you...
Yeah. Uh-oh, they started counting. This is extreme scenario. This is an extreme scenario.
Uh-oh, I might have to pull out. I might have to pull out fucking big guns here.
I might have to pull out the big guns. Wait, how do I get this? How do I make this jump? Like over
there? Damn. Do I have to be like Patrick or something? Somebody fatter or bigger?
I'm pulling like the light post or something? Or is that all the way up? Come on. I'm down that way.
Oh, happy new year guys. Yeah. I mean, that was a long time ago, but yeah, sure. Can Patrick do
anything here? That's not bad. Ooh. Oh shit. Okay. I want to get over there. Do I really need 2300
clams? I think I really actually need 2300 clams. And I like just somebody says skillshot the
bowling ball. Would I do that from all the way up here? Use the box? There's nothing like the smell
of bubbles in the morning. Smells like victory. Hold on. Hold on. What is this? New Lincoln chat.
That it's a video. Oh, you wanna fight? You wanna fuck? God damn, don't fuck him up.
Oh, you, you really wanna fight. You wanna fuck, well you wanna fight. You wanna fuck?
Don't fuck him down. So you wanna fight? You wanna fuck. Don't get up.
this is the creepiest face I've ever seen you know what I love the most about
what would happen what's going on right now who wants to take a guess that it
took the whole time since I asked that to right now to have that rendered which
was what two and a half hours ago an hour at least but this why can pictures
be turned into real life why can you tip you know how many times I've seen that
image of my face that I love so much and somebody just puts like fucking like
Ronald Reagan talking or like me singing and shit it's it's insane pictures can
come to life now deepfakes are one thing man but like like when pictures can
start to come alive that's where you've got to really kind of figure out what
you want to do with that technology you don't want to just have that I know our
technology says technology's bad he hates it he hates technology he hates us
can I go up another level oh this hold on I have to reload the area hold on wait
wait wait wait wait oh that's a look at me a moment right there
holy shit I did it hi act oh what the fuck I made it I did it guys I made it
I jumped it cool I'll take the box thank you now I can just get her I need to be
Patrick though there's no evidence that happened oh there is
all right I was just doing my best German I had five impression from 40
minutes ago with that ball bullshit it was that way doesn't do anything all
right well I got them skip all right hold on let me let me cheat for a second
okay nice now I go turn into Patrick I go back in there wait I can't be Patrick
I can't get up here with belt is there a bus stop here jump across it as Patrick
I can't well it don't matter but what is the thumbnail of my stream yeah I could
have guessed wait I went all the way back I'm just whatever I'm gonna get
enough of the coins you have to click that you watch the video what did
somebody else do it and and everyone's renders are all ending at the same time
is that what's happening we get to see who had better computers
it kind of like I always freak out a little bit whenever that video shows up
and like a joke or if I ever showed it but I could kind of show that on twitch
this is bad I've lost audio on spongebob hey you want to see you know what an old
an old YouTube video on stream was like forget about the webcam but you'll always
you can never get this part out of your head it was like as if that the
controller was the microphone like they were using a microphone built into the
controller I don't know how you make those sounds all right oh I had to click
inside of the window I need more clams 2300 right
Super Combo Ultra Combo
Super Combo ready ready I'll get it ready I used to be able to do I used to
be able to get close to an ultra combo in killer instinct with oh what was the
what was like a water guy who's like the waters like goo what was his name yeah
glacius yeah there it is and I used to get so pissed off when I what's the
skeletons name with the sword in the shield easiest character in the whole
game play you just have to fucking he just he had like one or two moves that
were great and it was just his basic attacks it would piss me off because I
would be like hyper combo super combo ultra and then all of a sudden I get
hit by two fucking sword swings by that skeleton I would get I would get all the
combo damage I did to the person it's horrible what was his name not sans come
on use the bungee got it it's finally yes thank you there it is
can't reach it yeah hyper combo laughs like spinal I'm not sure I could I don't
remember what he sounded like you want me to try and then see if it worked see
if it matched up let me see spinal spinals laughs finals laugh was like all
right I don't know why I'm leaning more towards this but I'm this is where I'm
leaning like a
something like that was close how many points do I have all right I need
literally a hundred I need literally a hundred grunty no grunties like it's
not a happy yeah Ernie laugh does Bernie laugh I don't know I love Adam Sandler
he's my favorite this is my favorite movie is and then I'm like Adam Sandler
like it's in the fight with like Bob Barker and he's just like no he doesn't
laugh like that he laughs he's not Barney it's not like
Fred and Barney holy shit there's the last one what does this want me to do
why do I what do I do with this well it's supposed to be invisible oh it's
an Easter egg all right now let's go open the clam so I can get out of here
remember where that is over there where I go for that one wait a minute that did
something it's this way you're careful when you talk about a clam
what smells like victory you've just met the sponge in a time no I wanted to
go through the other skip thing where's the um ah here we are all right nice I
have enough money get in the box actually do it the right way because I
can't just break it hey with the way we're supposed to do it by the damn
thing be done with it all right that do anything for me oh I need a watermelon I
need one of these I'm up top with Patrick now listen up there are eight
cylinders over there eight if you throw something at the cylinders it'll turn
around to the power side throw it cylinder power side turn all eight
cylinders around to the power side and I'll give you a mall on sorry what was
that I was watching Squidward just start turning those cylinders got annoying
puzzle it's gonna take me like 40 minutes to do a fun slide oh it's one of
these these things where you have to turn them all yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
reset it all right it does it three at a time thank you how we get to take the
slide 29 let's go 30 spatula's now I can take the fun slide and I did the final
override oh all right so I go in that box I get over there I'm gonna do with
all right computer the end of the screen voice probably soon yes not at this
exact moment not right now but probably soon but I pressed them on all the
security buttons now press the master shutdown button if you hurt yourself
screaming um I didn't scream that loud I like pushed it into the chair and I
went like I'm fine I did it what the hell does that mean it was the after
that is what the problem was was all the how that played out afterwards the
villain containment system is probably a boss
does mermaid man smell like sour milk yes yes I do oh no it looks like one of
the villains is broken yes
worse than that he's your arch enemy prawn did someone call oh I thought maybe
I was looking at superheroes but now I see it's just a couple of pieces of now
I do this shit all the time I don't get it I just throw a Kim used to go crazy
she used to hate when I did this I would just put all my clothes in the washing
that would just that didn't matter if they were I didn't care jeans like red
shirts I just did it she'd be like don't do that I'm like what's happening we're
gonna watch them now I separate all my the bright although you know you do your
whites oh he's I thought he was huge but he was really big I tried the five
year old way to play the game now let's try the actual smart person old adult
person way to play this game because the six-year-old me would have done that and
would have turned it off this shield went down I think I thought I could go
in there and hit him oh man that's a shit spawn be honest
we're good
he's gonna spawn a shit load right no this game's pretty this is a fun game
you know what I think I might beat this game
you got to give me more than one can't just give me one thank you here you go
Frank ugly 30 very cool so have I is this this area done this mermaid man and
barnacle boys a quest will line complete that was cool I like that area that was
fun purity tunnel I can just leave right all right let's go to go back to the hub
this is a good spot to stop is there is there like more than four or five hours
worth of stuff to do after as of right now yeah oh no I like it it's it's fun
it's fun just to hang out and just do the shit and just play it right here at
the halfway point yeah all right well I'll complete it next time there's also
multiplayer how do you have multiplayer in this game I hold on I'm not done I
want to go look these things I want to look at I know face cam I don't really
do face cam only sometimes when I'm feeling really cocky and confident
that's when you'll see it turned on fields this is blue lagoon right
somebody wanted me to all right we'll do that next I have 30 now when there's
something else yeah over here when naming a character Dave Colgate leads to
you leading dog ass hair weird yeah Sand Mountain all right he's look this
okay this is the one I want to do okay all right so here's the plan I'm gonna
give you guys the kind of next streaming days as you know I'm still trying to
ease back into streaming sitting here for more than four or five hours fuck me
up uncomfortable but there's some other things I'm gonna do too to help with
that I just got this desk like not even a year and a half ago and it's
unfortunate that I have to say this but sitting down sucks so I'm probably going
to just invest in a really really just good standing desk so that's something
I'm gonna do too eventually I can find something else somewhere else to put
this one I like this desk a lot and one that goes up and down yeah that's the
idea is like maybe I could have one that is I could sit down at it for a few
hours and then all right let's get them I got to get the fuck up and stand up
for like another couple hours stand-up comedy yeah so if you don't know I'll go
over this again just because I've only talked about it once so I as well talk
about it again I'm going back to the pre Vegas streams which is I'm only gonna be
live like three days a week and those streams are gonna be somewhere like this
around like five hours five ish four to six ish hours the end of the stream
wind down is going away we're not gonna do any bit readings at the end of the
streams anymore and it was a hard thing to do it was a hard thing to remove but
it means that I can sit here for as long as I can and long as I really want to
comfortably without needing to potentially add another hour or so to
stream to go over the bits and talk and hang out and stuff but that's sort of
the thought process there and it's probably going to be pretty permanent
because I've been gone for two months trying to get this figured out and this
could just be a longer term scenario where I have to just manage whatever is
going on I'm optimistic still though but there's something just random and stupid
that it's gonna be oh wow that's real fucking dumb huh it was that the whole
time here's how you fix it I'm still pretty optimistic about it so we'll see
but with that being said I'm going back to the kind of pre Vegas I almost said
pre Vegas arc a lot of you guys say that no going back to pre Vegas stream times
and lengths so I'll see you guys I will be back I'll see you guys on probably
probably the middle of next week either on Tuesday or Wednesday and at that point
I'm gonna try to do two days in a row I'm gonna try to do Wednesday and
Thursday in a row see how that plays out how to do maybe Wednesday Thursday
Saturday one day Thursday Sunday they'll see then I'll update the sus tomorrow
the next day I figure out which one's gonna be wins movie night yeah we'll
talk for a little bit streams are not just gonna turn off obviously they still
have the credits to do I don't do my mom gonna be reading bits or anything but
we are gonna hang out for about ten minutes or so don't worry so do that now
oh where's the music I got it there it is movie night is gonna end up being I
gotta come up like there's a lot of streams that are on the way here that I
really have to set hard dates for the DLC movie night is on Wednesday I'll
give you a hard date it's gonna be within the next ten days that's pretty
much a guarantee that it within the next like 10 to 15 days and then there's the
webcam stream there's FTK August is gonna be there's a lot of stuff going on
it'd be fun we're probably gonna have to break it down into more than
potentially two or even three nights because you guys have had months and
months and months to work on projects we're probably gonna have to put some
criteria in maybe some changes on like the second or third night maybe I don't
know well I'll have to figure it out I want to try to get as many things seen
as possible but yeah let's run the credits these are all the subs today
there was a lot of major sub drops thank you I when I went when I left back in
the end of May another end of May yeah wait was it May when did I leave yeah
holy shit it was it was May wasn't it it's been almost two and a half months
well I'll just tell you just for full just just transparency here you guys in
the last two three days have brought the sub count of the stream back to where it
was before I left that's fucking crazy in three days it's like all like all of
you came back and decided to resub like I can't even fucking comprehend that and
people that were still subbed to the channel for the months that there was
nothing here that's even harder to believe so thanks that's it's incredible
to think about that that like I I I'm gonna try to use the money as best I can
because obviously that that's a concern right like when anytime you if I you go
away for a little while I go is but people gonna remember who I am am I
gonna I'm gonna come back and people are gonna how many people are gonna be there
will that be will I lose a shitload of people if I go away for three four
months or something I'm gonna my channels gonna die but it didn't even
it didn't even fucking happen there are more people watching now than before
I can't believe it who is this guy who is this guy who are you who who who are
you omega low who are you what who omega low wait am I getting hooded in my own
stream that's so funny now I long story short I'm forever grateful that you
guessed all all of you pretty much came back and then something because it was a
concern to have and you you smashed it thanks guys we'll see you gonna we'll
see you on probably Tuesday Wednesday we run the credits we're gonna do
spongebob again I'm gonna beat it and then on Thursday I have the Riddick
games I really want to play but I also mmm I wonder if I want to just do the
webcam streams if I can get that see if I can get it to work where are my
credits make it better this whole streamer thing do the webcam one yeah I
did look into after stream from two days ago I did look into it more I think it's
a little more elaborate than I think I'm gonna have to add some peripherals but
here comes credits these are all people that subbed today it's doing the Star
Wars thing again so this is very obviously broken this one is not gonna
okay so let me get the other one because the other one actually works is it the
same ten people from last time I think it's the same people yeah it has to be
only those people sub yeah all right let me pull up the other one right it's
okay okay you know what I really really desperately need I have to set up I have
to set up like a new button to press get like a window it's killing me it's like
half the time it doesn't capture my window and like I sit here trying to do
browser source and then capture a window and shit really annoying I should just
be able to do this I think my computer just sucks I think I've come to the
tournament yeah come to the realization I think this computer just sucks hi not
what I wanted don't get that off hey get out of here oh shit they can see
everything oh they can see everything look at this window look at brother
source three oh no oh no you can see all my fucking look at this you can see all
my shitty command center image one image three germs sandwich
yeah you're my and Jax top bits top bits too I don't even know what these are
what is sandwich you all know the honest-to-god stupid truth about this
whole thing that was probably the image name and file of a fucking picture that
somebody gave me to show on stream seven months ago and it's just still down here
that's so embarrassing this is so embarrassing it's not doesn't exist
anymore it like has to exist in the folder I can't it doesn't it won't show
up on stream it's the Mick chicken picture yeah now that does it's not
attached to anything it's not all it's not in the same spot where it was six
seven months ago it's been moved okay anyways let's go ahead and do this oh we
could see his command center oh you guys got to see behind the curtain and how
shitty my actual streamers set up is an image three how many people were here
today here we go let's do it here come the credits I gotta get this fixed for
next time here they come and they're in alphabetical order we finally get to see
his command center my eyes hurt when is the rumble the rumble really kind of got
just thrown it just in a total total just dizzy the original plan for the
rumble was it was gonna be a charity stream to sponsor my buddies run in the
Boston somebody hold on a minute that person it was Jerma seven seven five
when the dudes talk with it was Jerma seven eight five what was that
Jerma seven nine five all right well if that person starts streaming you know you
know we talked about it anyways the it was supposed to be a
charity stream for the Boston Marathon it was gonna sponsor my buddies run in
the Boston Marathon it was a whole charity set up there was a whole page
that was ready and they canceled the marathon the Boston Marathon is has
been just canceled so it really was like oh I now like I'm gonna do another one
I do it maybe two of them just don't know it's all this was before obviously
COVID-19 you had this plan for a little while before that but that's kind of
what happened to that it was supposed to happen in September and that stream
was supposed to happen months ago but there will be another rumble promise
it's not like I don't think about it all the time so there are tons of ideas and
tons of things I want to do yeah I oh I yeah I pinky promise absolutely there's
other fun stuff to do as well though all right I'll see you guys on probably
Wednesday I had a lot of fun spongebob's it's I love this game I think it's
really good I'm glad you guys made me play it cuz I wasn't gonna play it
unless you told me to wait until WWE 2k 21 I don't think I want to do it in one
of those games I think I really would go back painfully somehow they're like 2k
14 or maybe even stay on the current year that I'm on now where this a lot
of the characters already are as manned I refuse to buy that new 2k 20 whatever
the one that just came out this past year now I refuse to buy it shit no it
is it is shit 2k 14 is the best yeah now I know and the problem with 2k 14 is
just it takes so fucking long to do anything 2k 14 it just you'll make a
character you'll load up a character and you'll put a layer on them you'll put
two layers on them three layers on them and then the game starts to go for you
load a piece of clothing it's the worst I wish and this is so horrible that they
didn't do this it was so close 2k 14 just didn't make it to the ps4 they
waited to make that new 2k 15 right was the first one and if they had I wish
they just made 2k 14 the one for ps4 because it was really close right it was
like not even a year right it's Alex yeah a little right it's Alex what's he
doing see what he's up to let's see let's see what he's doing
they have slowed down but the battle for Texas is just the toughest on two mobile
teams in here for a second I was like wait what was it how is this italics
a stream I think pub G he's playing he's playing total war warhammer 2 not subbed
no I'm not logged in I'm not logged in on Chrome I go say hello he's in his uh
he's in his new place now I love you won a full room tour and I'll see you guys
at Wednesday take care guys have a good one see you soon