Hello. How are you doing? It's good to hear. I'm doing pretty good too. Just hanging out. Loving
up PS4. Gonna do something I've wanted to do for a while, and that's play Days Gone. I know the
reviews aren't that great. It's not a 10 out of 10 experience, but we're gonna just throw a whole
day away. Pretty good title, I think. But hope you're doing good. We're gonna get started.
I'll give you the rundown for this week. Yes, we are very early today. That's because we're
gonna be very early tomorrow too. Back-to-back days starting somewhere before one or two o'clock.
EU stream. Stop being so early. I can't help it. Sometimes I have to. But yeah, so what's
gonna happen here is I wanted to play Days Gone. It's a new game. It's got motorcycles
in it, so that's an automatic plus one ladder grid. It's open world zombies. This might be
terrible. This might be fun. I don't know. This could be the worst game I've ever played.
I'm willing to give it a try. So we're gonna go today and tomorrow. If Days Gone is fun,
then tomorrow we're gonna keep going. If Days Gone, we actually just wasted a whole day.
Then I won't play it tomorrow, and we'll do something else tomorrow. Then Saturday and Sunday
is gonna be Sam and Max Season 2, Episode 3 and 4, and MS-DOS Night 2. Told you I was gonna
make that a weekly thing. That is the plan for this week. Porn 2. It sucks, but you may enjoy it.
I'm going in with an open mind. I doubt it would be the worst game you've ever played.
I don't think it will either. It's very bland. So this is what, like, the tasteless sponge
of video games. Isn't this like 50 hours long? It's very playable. Alright. It's a coin flip
if it's gonna be enjoyable or not. Okay. Well, let's take that chance. Days Gone.
Yeah, like, you ain't getting this one back. I really hope at the end of this stream,
I don't say, I wish I could get this day back. But let's go. Days Gone, we're gonna start
it. And here it comes. Days Gone. Here comes the opening cut scene. Days Gone, more like eat ass.
Yeah, I know, right? Alright. Wait, wait, wait. Why is there no sound? Should there be sound
right now? There should be, right? What a waste of a day. I already know. It's a waste.
Is this a loading screen? Why do we have, like, the Witcher 2 base game level of loading
screen? No, this is, like, the original Witcher. Do you guys remember that shit?
What is going on right now? It can't be this long. This is, that's the initial load time,
right? I got, I have nothing, I have nothing to say. I have nothing to say. I don't have anything.
It's just a long loading screen. That's it. That's all. I don't have anything else to say.
This better be good. No, I already put a warning in the title. You've been pre-warned.
This is kind of, uh, is unbelievable though. I have class soon. You may as well just go,
you know what? If you got class soon, you may as well just go study, like,
extra study time. I can't hear anything. All right, brightness. This doesn't need to be
brightened. Set your brightness so that days gone is barely visible. Now, I always hate that
shit. It's never correct. I'm gonna go with, like, seven. I'm gonna turn HDR on or off.
Can I not turn it on? I can't even turn it on. I cannot hear anything. Is it because
this is too low? Playing on seven brightness. What do you mean? I need to be able to see.
Nobody plays these games at, like, two brightness. You can't see anything.
Is it possible to play? All right, let me turn this up on my end because this is, like, this is
bait. You know what I mean? This is bait. Okay, now I can hear it. Press any button.
Days gone. Welcome. Here's the options menu. Controls. Display. Oh, all right. I'm staying
at seven brightness. Audio. I mean, I don't know. Who cares? Dialogue. Sound effects.
They'll just keep everything normal. I don't like the music being the same. Gameplay.
Difficulty. Put it on. Just keep it on. Wait, there is no hard. Guys, there's no hard,
so you can't make fun of me this time. You can't make fun of me. Normal is hard.
Vibration off. This ain't 1995. We're just gonna keep it like that. What else is there?
User interface. XP indicators are off. Well, we're gonna get an entire huge tutorial.
We're gonna get, like, a four to five hour tutorial. This is my last chance here. This is
it. This is my final chance to, like, do something else. I've done to skip. No, I'm, I locked it in.
Hope that wasn't a mistake. It's a good game. I know. Why am I, like, sitting here going,
like, oh, no, this is my last chance. This is it. After this, it's a video game.
Relax. This is not my audition for American Idol. I'm gonna be okay. Like, it's a game.
We're just gonna enjoy it. Now, this is my one shot.
Knife.
That's, yeah, what did he say?
We need subtitles.
Hold on, I can't do this yet. Wait.
Wait, we need help. She's been wounded. What? What's wrong with her? Well, she's not.
Whatever the hell's going on out there, she's been stabbed.
Come on, man. You're an astronaut. You should know what to do.
If we don't get her to a hospital, she's going to die. There are no more hospitals.
Hospitals. You got, uh, doctors. You got tri-i's. You got a mass unit.
Oh, look, I'm just a grad student, okay? I, I got volunteered to do this.
Just an astronaut. That's the, that's the party store astronaut costume.
That's the guy that comes to the party in the astronaut costume that was like
$14 at the party store. He's smoking a joint and he like takes the helmet off and he's like,
Oh, I'm ready to hit the moon. All right. I'm going to play.
Chopper's coming down. Big ring.
This man coming.
25 captain crunch box top to get this. Make sure you bring it back in one piece.
Okay. Let me put the subtitles on.
It was plenty of space in the helicopter. Hello? Anytime a game spends this, I think the
game's hung up. Like it's hanging. It's pretty much what I was going for in dreams the other
day. Did they did a kind of a better job than I did, but you know, he can't be perfect.
Freaker is all dead. Zombies are called Freakers. Sounds like he's YouTube sub
community. Uh, plus one letter grade.
Can't be far. Wait, hold on. Cut your engine.
Shit, she's alive. Alvarez. Alvarez. Hey, Alvarez. What happened here? I mean,
who did this? Was it, was it Rippers? No, his community is really nice. It wasn't
Rip Van Winkle 22. It was Freaker. Freaker HD 1080p. Here we go. Gameplay.
Chase down Leon. How do I, how do I drive? They didn't tell me how to drive. X to
boost. It's actually kind of hard to drive this. How many boosts do I get? Oh,
it's the rumors versus the zoomers. Just drive through the fire. It doesn't even matter.
Look, I'm going too slow. Subtitles, subtitles, subtitles. All right. All right.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Display. Why can I not turn this on? Why would you have
this setting here? This is probably PS4 Pro only. Language. Subtitles. There,
I turned them on. Derma, come to Brazil.
65 mile per hour on this road. He lays his bike down. When landing, you can
reduce bike damage by using L to angle your tires parallel to the ground. Give me the
next tip. If you drift while turning, you can slide through corners and even do donuts.
Give the next one while on the bike. Watch the gas tank right behind you.
How do you cover somebody with a shotgun from that far away? You may as well just
shoot it in the air. We'll make it quick. Tracking. Press R3 to activate survival vision,
which will reveal clues and other information about your surroundings.
Does every game have to have this? I'm sorry. Like I'm going to have to take a
second here to explain. What? Why does every fucking AAA game have a spider sense? Why?
What is causing this guy to have this? Every game is Batman. Yeah, but like why?
What's like the story purpose for him to be able to see through walls?
Tracking. While using survival vision, your DualShock 4 wireless controller will vibrate.
I turned off vibrate. When your camera is facing a clue, depending on your distance to
it, vibrations will increase or decrease. But I turned them off.
Okay. Do I seriously have to turn on the vibration? No. What? They're behind us.
I don't need the vibration. I'll just look. Wait, wait, wait. Here. Down this way. Wait,
I can see into the past? Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. I touched the blood. Therefore,
now I can see the past. Wait, there's a Dark Souls blood stain here. Let me see what
happened. Watch out. Watch out. He died by something over here. What did he die by?
I have no idea. He fell and died. I think he was doing the meme where he jumped off
the top to die and made sure he had the blood. This blips on the map. Can I like investigate?
How do I take out the gun? No, it doesn't say boomer.
Balls. He's losing a lot of blood. Press X to hop over parkour style.
I mean, the environments look pretty cool. Who shot him? Did I shoot him?
Leading out. That's a hell of a way to go. It's slow. A lot of pain,
but I suppose you know him about that. She was still breathing when we found her,
you piece of shit. I wasn't going to waste a bullet not on her.
I don't know for a second. I don't know for a second now. Where's the stash?
Boss, don't look like you've been sleeping for too long. Leon, he got a little problem.
Why would you do that? I can smell your blood. Now they'll smell me because I'm stupid enough
to put my hands on it. No, wait. All right. All right. I got it right here. Take it.
He smears blood all over it with his hands.
Is he a bad guy? We're the bad guy in this story.
Do it. Do it. Do it. Fulfill your destiny.
Holy fall. Oh my God, he actually did it. Welcome to the dark side. Hey, uh.
Tuck's going to need something for the bounty.
I didn't even have time to make him a mask. Oh, no. Oh, God. I'm not putting the pressure.
I had six months to come up with Darth Vader. You are, uh,
Hey, hold up. I want to search this camp. See if I can't find something.
That's terrible. Make something out of this. Oh, scraps. Fine materials to craft. Crafting.
What? Are you telling me that there's a whole entire fucking crafting system?
Let me use my boomer vision. Come on. I can't like fail to pick stuff up off the ground
tutorial. We'll make it quick. Um, will you? Are you sure? Where? I seriously need to turn
on vibrations, don't I? God damn it. I hate vibrations. It makes me feel like ill.
I didn't even help. Um, are you like, are you my dog? Are you pointing in the right
direction here? It vibrates like you're on a hog. There's a dead guy in there.
Sleeping bag? No, it's not the sleeping bag. All right. Where is this?
Uh, so I'm serious. Where the fuck is this? That shit? What? There wasn't even an indicator.
All right. Why was there an indicator for the first one and no indicator for the second one?
There was no square on the screen. All right. He's R to expand the medical category.
Hold R1 to craft a bandage. How many can I make? He's gone. No, that didn't. What?
All right. Let's use the bandage. So you can go on the wheel. Just hold R2.
Okay, it's got a fucking wheel. We're really ticking all the AAA video game boxes, aren't we?
Sprinting and rolling depletes your stamina. If you run out, you need to wait for it to
recover. At first I thought that said you need to drink water. I was about to say no,
don't make me do that. Died to loot wheel.
Son of a bitch. Step back, step back. Just piss yourself. Fuel pump. Yeah,
shot out my damn fuel pump. Can we get anything out of Leon? Get away from that.
It's done. Let's just go back to O'Leary Mountain. All it takes is a guy with a
cigar in his mouth and you're done. Fight this? Far from here. Let's just head over there.
What are you thinking? We were going out hunting tonight anyway.
What's it really like? It's as good a place as any.
Okay. Oh, we're doing. Oh, we're doing bunk beds. Nice. Hey, what did Leon give you?
Map of some kind. Once we get my bike back, let's head up to the cemetery. Look around.
Yeah, I have no control. I just have to hold on. So tomorrow get the drugs, take him to Tucker,
collect on Leon's bounty. Then I say we head north. Do you think shit's any different?
I say we head south. So we have a little bit. That just scared the fuck out of me.
What the fuck would you do? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why did this just come up? What's going on? Hold on. You went too fast here.
Swipe left. Did I press that? I mean, maybe I pressed it. Swipe left. Can I go back?
Swipe left or press R1 to view inventory and get info on gear,
crafting supplies. Okay. Storylines menu. Swipe up or press R1 to view. Swipe up.
So it's swiping. So we got skills. Okay. Did I level up or something? No, it requires a skill
point. Jesus Christ. What's happening? This is scaring me. Oh, it's all. Oh, that's what's
happening. If you touch the, if you touch the pad here on the PS4, it opens the menu.
Oh, I'm going to scream about this later. I'm going to be in the middle of a fight and I'm
going to fucking like move my thumb and touch it and it's going to open and I'm going to
scream. Move the truck with our bare hands? Pushing vehicles. Some vehicles can be moved to
clear a block pass. Hold. Swear to push them. Put tape on your controller. I thought someone
was driving. I don't know how this happened. I got stuck in the snow. Hey. What? Oh,
he wanted to punch him. He wanted to punch that guy. He didn't, he wasn't even aiming for me.
What? Why? Why? Hold L in any enemy's direction and press R2.
Choose direction and then tap R1 to roll.
I just slit everybody's throats. Oh, okay. Anybody have any loot on them? Wow. Jake,
you're a real psycho. I don't know what it is, man. I have to slit their throats.
No loot? Yeah, what's up with that? Coming up on the old Nero checkpoint.
Dude, the best trope in all of media is definitely you punched a guy in the face you
weren't supposed to punch in the face. Imagine like you punched your friend directly in his face
as hard as you could because somebody ducked slowly.
That would cause, that would be ripple effects for what that happened there
for 10 years. You would never trust each other. There'd be a falling out
months and weeks later. It would never, it would change your friendship forever.
Yeah. Okay, go through the tunnel.
Can we siphon some of the gas from these cars? That would be a real survival game.
No, we just walked 10 feet for another cutscene. Why not just have the cutscene go through here?
Clip this. Somebody show the clip. Do it. I know somebody has that one. Do it. No,
not the slap. I'm talking about the puke. Why? Why would you do this?
Two fucking enemies. What is this game? Can I play? I got to shoot twice.
They could have done all this in one cutscene and then like just teach me how to shoot
in two minutes. Oh, you're never going to get this day back. You're never getting these days back,
Jeremy. These guys are on the map. I'm being too harsh. They need to like teach people how to
play. Do I have to get on his bike? I can't like, there's no more enemies or anything. I'd
have to get on the bike. He's just following me. Okay, if there's another cutscene here,
I'm going to be very, very, no, wait, are you actually just following me on the bike?
I can't get on the bike. Oh god. Why don't we just ride through? Oh, there is loot. Oh shit,
we can turn this off. I've played Left 4 Dead before. Can we steal something from her?
You know anything about cars? Plus one scrap. Oh no, you unplugged the car from the outlet.
How many bolts do I have?
You're not getting your bike through there. Try that service tunnel. See if you can clear us a
path from the other side. I got it. Just keep your headlight pointed that way.
Keep your head, please keep your headlight pointed at the objective because I,
I would have missed it and I actually would have. I went too far up. Wait,
hold on. This game probably has like secrets. I shouldn't just be running through as fast
as I can. Whoa, scary. Am I gonna have a fist fight with a zombie? Oh, that would have been
so fucking funny. You redeem this entire first like 30-40 minutes of the game if me and that
zombie have a fist fight. He like punches me in the face like three or four times because
he hands up like a boxer. Where's the flashlight coming from? Um, I think my eyes.
Where's the flashlight coming from? No, it's just a spotlight. Oh fuck, I was talking a
lot of shit. He does have superpowers. I'm sorry. I retract everything I said. Never mind.
Every biker has, has what? Light eyes? Oops. Come on, get in here quick. We're gonna get
out of here. Let's go. No, let me shoot him. Shoot. Shoot him. He doesn't give a shit. He
doesn't care if I live or die. He was pretending to help. That backwards side gun hold was just
like, ah, whatever. I'll find another friend. There's a double. Is there a zoom in feature?
They're blocking the bullets? He wasn't actually trying to block the bullets,
was he? His hands? I don't have any bullets left. Did I fail this tutorial?
Another nest. Knife. Yeah, that's right. I have a knife. How many molotovs you got left?
Oh, we're gonna teach men to throw molotovs. Just use the last one. You got any shit to make
more? Burn the freaker nest. Okay, well, give them to me. You got any shit to make more.
This will just take a sec. All right, throwables category. There's rocks. Okay, so, I mean,
there are rocks. With the molotov equipped, hold L2 and aim, tap R2 to throw. All right,
there's the nest right there. I don't have any bullets. I don't have any bullets.
No, I want to like, what are they doing? Oh, he got him. It's like more fun to dodge
around than it is to do anything else. Round one of zombies. All right, get us out of here.
Yeah, I'm collecting their ears for some crazy reason.
25. From 65 to 25. Sounds about right.
Got any more molotovs? Oh, I have an idea. Hey, you just scream as loud as you can over
here off the bike and wait till they all run over to you and then I'll leave.
Wow.
That's actually what we're doing. That's the real plan.
All right. He didn't leave the bike though. He's gonna pull them and I have to get to the
garage. I would laugh if he just crashed and flew up. I don't have any bullets though.
I'm gonna have to really play tactically. You got a death wish. Find crazy Willy's garage.
Newts. Newts are skittish and usually stick to out of reach places like rooftops. They will
attack if they sense you are low on health or if you invade their turf.
Oh, I'm invading their turf. Get away from me! What? What? They're like zombies. They're
like aliens. All right, hold on. So what on the screen here is... I didn't even hurt anybody.
All right, so we have to get into the garage. Bushes. Provide cover for stealth if you haven't
been spotted. Remain crouched with circle to stay hidden and use rocks to create distractions.
I didn't even need to use the... He didn't see me. I technically did it in stealth.
Oh, shit! All right, you got a guy right there. I'm gonna actually do the rest in
stealth. I'm gonna play this like a true video game. Watch this. Ready? Well, it takes the
gun out immediately. I just want rocks. Did you see me? Can you see me? This is actually fun.
This is a fun game. No ammo. What? Oh, you have... I gotta stop fucking around.
There's ammo in the game. Nice dodge. Holy shit. Okay, so there's a guy in here. Wait.
All right, no more fucking around. Let's actually do this correctly.
Would the buddy go? Yeah, that's true. Where is he? He was riding around out here.
Gas can? Gas cans can be used to refuel your bike and generator. Is it...
Wait, I can throw? Can I just pour it out? Holy shit! Drink the gas. Spark plug?
Silence your guns by attaching a suppressor. Select a compatible gun of the survival
weapon. Press R1 to attach it. Did I get a suppressor from the car? That's a little odd.
It was R1, right? R1? R1. Is that not... Am I not doing this right? Yeah, R1. R1. I don't
know. I'm gonna blow that up. You know I'm gonna. Oh! Yes! I need to try. No, no. I want to hit...
I want to swing at it. I got a sick... a stick. Wait, hold on. I want to look around. What's in
here? A spark plug? Maybe I don't have enough materials. All right, there's something over here.
Explosive objects will blow up and damage by bullets or other explosives.
So I can't, like, do anything with this. This... No, that's gonna explode. This is an
explosive. I'm holding an explosive. If I throw an explosive at an explosive, it's at explosives.
So I'm not gonna do that. All right, let's just get in here. What do you mean? Yes, you can.
Not real. Okay, see? It's plastic versus metal. It's not explosive. It's what's inside that
matters. Break it with a knife. Okay, we gotta get in there somehow. Up on the roof.
Let's use our boomer vision. Shoot it. I don't have any bullets. I'm out of bullets. Baseball
bat. Damage and durability. Oh, I want the bat. I love baseball bats. Can I throw stuff?
Can I throw the bat? Imagine if it went through the can and exploded. All right,
we got any more freakers? I don't think so. I need to bring this with me, though.
I might need it. I don't see any more freakers. No more trunks. This is just open.
Oh, another gas. No, I don't want that. Battery, though. Battery. Take the battery.
I'm not gonna drink the gas. It'll be a sidearm suppressor. It'll give you energy. I don't think
I... Why am I carrying? Do I need to take this somewhere? Can I have... Can I hold two? No.
Which one has more in it? I'll take this one. Well, there's just a bunch of shit in here.
Rag. Drink the bat. No, I gotta do something cool with this. I'm not drinking the gasoline.
I'm gonna blow the gasoline. I wish I could just dump the gasoline. All right, that's fine.
Let's just get out of here and head into the back way of the garage. Here we go.
Board it up. Well, oh, never mind. We're going this way. I can't jump. Is there a way to go all the
way around? Like, up there? I can't go... Wait. Am I maybe, like... Can I jump on these? Well,
I have to go across there. So how do I get up there? Is it the tree? Do I have to jump from
the tree? I don't see a ladder. You'd think there would be a ladder out here. I don't see
a ladder. Well, do I push the car over here? Can I, like, shove the car over?
Can I just go into edit mode? Well, it looks like I'm going over here. Can I, like... No,
don't go in the dumpster. I want to, like, climb the dumpster. Well, okay. Can I go up?
Compelling climb to trash gameplay. Do I just need to shoot the lock? No, I don't. Look,
they're making me go, like, all the way. Do I have to shoot the lock? No, no, no, no, no, no.
They wouldn't do that. They wouldn't make me do that. I don't have any bullets. I need a
different gun. I have no bullets. I can't even, like, attempt to do that. Pour gas on the lock.
All right. Well, I'm... Let's try, I guess, go to the left and climb up. But from where?
Like, over here? There's, like, nothing over here. Is it up this? Do I actually have to just jump on
this thing? All right. I didn't... That was... I had to do that. They were coming after me.
All right, so let me get in here now. Is there, like, a hatch I can pull? Can I, like, move,
break something, move something? I mean, all right, yeah. So, I'm sorry I didn't know
that. I'm looking for a ladder. This one, like, little gray shed that's sitting on the side.
That's the only place you can get up. All right, let's get some cash out of the ATM,
I think. Fucking money's worthless. Don't worry. I still got plenty of gold. All right,
what else is in here? Nothing. Nothing. Let's unlock the... First of all, let's get the
shortcut open. That's important. Anything in the toilets? No. Yes, there is. Elevator next
to Firelink. No, what? Find the fuel pump. Was it in this room right here?
No, I found the fuel pump. Dude, how long have you been in there for?
There's 400 chasing me. I'm out of gas. You've been in there for an hour and a half, man.
Hey, Boozman, I'm sorry. There was one shed that I had to climb up and I couldn't figure
it out. I needed a bunch of friends to help me find it. What are you fucking stupid? A couple
thousand friends. Wait, what did I just do? Max. All right, I have too many of these. I gotta
craft some stuff. Hold on. Can I craft ammo? It's refined metal. All right, let's go find
Boomer. Hold on. Hang on, Boozman. I'm coming. What was my gas tank? Oh, he's up there.
He's just doing donuts up there. Is he really just like spinning around in circles?
You took way too long. Blind. Streamers blind. He did this to me.
What the hell? How? Get low. Get low. Is that a song?
I've been singing a song. You can enter cover by crouching next to it. Press circle to toggle
crouch. So those are rippers. Shoulder swapping. While aiming L2, press X to shoulder swap.
Let me make a couple things here. Let me just start crafting.
Sons of bitches, get off of them!
I was trying to hit him in the head with a rock. That may have been a mistake.
I was trying to throw a rock at my friend's head.
What's with the crowd?
It's us.
Yeah, there they are. I needed like three or four thousand of them to figure out what to do.
Streamer sucks, game sucks. Idiot blind. That's what they're all screaming.
He can't possibly be this bad. Next. He can't reach it. He's not pretending.
Hey dude, you all right? You okay? All right, here we go. Welcome to the game.
Don't you wait out here. Make sure it's all clear. Screw that. There's a bunk calling my name.
This guy's all fucked up. Like there's much to steal. I'm just gonna reintroduce myself.
This is ride to hell retribution with zombies in place of the so bad it's good factor.
I mean, I can't make that assessment yet.
Oh, it's still light up. Hey, I've got some ammo if you need it in the footlocker by the door.
Thanks. Can we just dump hydrogen peroxide all over you? You're making me itch.
Thanks brother. Just feel kind of naked without it.
All right, so director is on the mountain. Six percent he's my brother.
I'm six percent of the way through the story. New items.
Primary. Sidearms. Special. Primary. Nothing. Sidearms. Nine millimeter with the can on it.
Okay. Crossbow. Good in stealth situations. Its versatility goes up. The more bolts you can
craft, the crossbow has a longer reload time. All right, let's put it on. Drifters on the
mountain. Return to your bike. Hold on. So this is where I store my weapons and items and
stuff. What else is in here? A bunch of ammo. Why do I even have the shot? I want to like
reload that. It's one of those things where I have to walk out and then reload.
No, it's locked. See, there we go. Okay, now reload the damn gun. Reload them all.
And now take the ammo because I can take more ammo, right? Or no. Well, whatever.
I thought I was going to be able to load the gun and take more ammo.
Pick this one. Now what's this?
Maneuver quickly through the safe house gate to avoid letting enemies in.
People can just come in. Heal. Oh, you actually, okay. Thankfully you can just press this
button. So that's fully heal. Anything else in here I need to do or can see?
It's just ammo, all right. Crafting bench or something. That's a bat. I'll take it. All
right. Well, let's go. I can't just drive my bike. I can't drive his bike to my bike and somebody
will get it. You can now create a new crossbow boat by crafting them. Cedar saplings provide
the wood and scrap makes the tip. Combine the two in the survival wheel. All right, so I need
saplings and scrap to make bolts. Makes sense. I can't even
do that. Follow mission. Crossbow bolts are affected by gravity and will drop as they
travel to the target. When shooting at something far away, aim higher. I gotta follow this guy.
We just have to run behind him. All right, he's in the base. He made it to like the
fallout base. Clear the Marauder camp. You got it. Target the binoculars with up and press
R2 to mark. Marking enemies makes it easier to follow their movements.
Tracked human enemies will display their awareness levels. All right, let's just do it.
How do I zoom in? L3 is zoom. Well, L3 is zoom. Okay, I'm walking towards them with
binoculars. I saw L3. Technically, this is zooming in. It's just walking forward.
Where are the others? That guy's alive? All right, where's the rest of them?
I think I saw something. Yeah, well, you may have. Stool leg? No, my, the weapon I had was
better. Pistol ammo. Do they have an indicator over here? Wait, is some?
That's a bird. Speaking of a head. Well, neither are you.
Regaining stealth. If you've been spotted by an enemy, get out of their line of sight
and hide. They'll eventually give up the search. Really. I'm trying to backstab her.
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me check around.
She was walking up backwards.
Nothing else.
Free shit. It's fucked up that you're killing their entire family for no reason.
Well, it's not for no reason. It's to survive. I missed a rifle. Wait, there's a rifle? Am I
getting baited? I don't know if I believe that. Bad weather can affect enemy's ability
to see and hear. It can also affect the conditions of trails and roads. All right,
damn freakers. Swimmers are sensitive to light, feeding mostly at night or during heavy storms.
Taking on more than one is death or something. It's not worth it. Will they have anything
good? I might be able to get a stealth hold on. Got him! There's only one more.
He's telling me to run. Why would I run? There's only one.
It's raining all the time. All the rain, rain, rain, rain, rain.
Oh shit. Somebody's right here. Oh fuck, there is somebody right there. What about the rock?
Go to the rock first. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! What the hell just happened? That was
weird. Does he know I'm here? What is he doing? Oh my god, he's doing the golem. This
is bad. I think I have to... durability meter, melee weapons found on the field, break easily.
Pay attention to the durability meter. If there's a blinking red icon, there are only a few hits left
before it breaks. Oh, I still got a knife. Okay, slide. Stay down. Give me my bike back
so we can continue playing the game. All right, there's still two here. Give me the rock.
You know, you go that way. Melee stealth kill you?
Car. Always check the cars. There's a camp right here. Nothing in the boomer vision.
I need to stop calling it that. Somebody see me? You want to hear me? Rifle over here,
rifle over here. What's this clip? Why is everybody clipping this? Oh wait, I can't watch
that. Did I? Who cares about the rifle? Turn around. You and then you. Am I getting
experience for this? There's exp in this game, right? Wow! He just dodged it.
No. Melee in this game feels very good. To the point where you could just melee everybody.
Everyone. You can just melee anyone. Maybe that's just the initial enemy.
This is it. This is where we left it. All right, so give me my bike and let's move on.
Somebody stole the bike. I have to keep going. My bike's gone. What a waste of 500 million
dollars. I don't think it cost that much to make this game. I think it was more like,
it was probably like 40 million. What?
You can't shoot him. It was aiming around him. Let's see if I can get one rock throw.
Why would this guy be over here? There's no reason for this guy to be hiding here.
Just waiting for me to come know that my bike is stolen. He's standing behind the car.
That was a huge underhanded throw. Nobody can throw that far underhand. No overhead throws?
That's kind of ridiculous. It's me! Open up! He's here! He's here! That's right I am.
Fuck no! I didn't mean to do that. They don't really care. Now he throws it overhand.
Should I just shoot this guy? Let me like make the- hold on. Let's- can I craft- to
craft bullets, right? I don't think I can craft anything. Bolt. They don't have enough.
I need cedar sapling. Well we're just gonna have to shoot people.
This is- I just- we just go walk in. Yeah that's where I'm headed.
So it's just a town. Okay. I thought this was a
bandit camp. I was supposed to go in here and just start shooting people.
All right here's the kitchen. I'm like trying to plan how to go in
and kill people. Meeting plans can be collected and turned into encampment
kitchens for trust and credits. Different types of meat and plants provide different rewards.
Why does somebody always call me at the worst possible moment? Why do you have to call me?
Okay. Are there animals in this game? I mean I guess I saw the elk but there's tigers and
like bears and shit. Okay. Bounties. Freaker ears can be collected and turned into encampment
bounty clicks for trust and credits. Different freakers have different rewards. All right so
I can just turn these in for money. Swarmer ear, newt ear. I guess we can just sell them right?
Is there any reason to not do that?
Merchant.
You ever read it? No. That book doesn't exist man.
Ran a shop. Farewell. Made all the grease monkeys read it. Being a mechanic requires great peace
of mind. That's it. If I'm working on an empty stomach, that'll focus your mind. Man,
I'm looking for a bike. But yeah. Oh, hold on. I want that one. It just came off the truck.
Some dumb son of a bitch left it out in the shit. Busted up good.
It was me that did that. Okay. Fooled the road. It didn't be shit about bikes.
Is that right? Yeah, that's right. Shot the hell out of this one. Partyed it out. It didn't even
have a fuel pump. We could have used that man. Fuel pump like this one. Okay. Like this one
man. Okay. Okay. See now when I said fool, what I meant was the fools that brought that
bike in. See they didn't even tie that shit down properly. So they were like rattling around
back then. You were right about not getting this day back. It's all right. We're just
enjoying a new game. All right. What's with the big explosion meter?
Is this guy flammable? Oh no, I think that that's just the indicator for the quest.
I thought this guy was flammable. I can't skip the optional dialogue because when I touch
the, when I touch the thing. Yes, I can. No, I'm not skipping it. Is that people? Come on.
I'm not bored. I'm not bored yet. I'm not bored.
Tell you what. You find yourself bored. Bring it to me. Just wait till I get on the car.
We'll see what we can do for you. I want one of your chapsticks. The bike. You have two of them.
That your men stole. Salvage. Salvage. Oh wait, nice hat. What? Oh this one. Don't you ever
touch it. Hold on. Leon wore a hat like this, didn't he? I swear to god. Don't. Do business in
my camp. Is it weird that I feel like somebody sneezed this story into my head last night?
That's all I like. The only way I can describe it is there was a storyline that somebody just
like fucking opened up my head just with a buzz saw pulled back my skull and like took
and just covered it up and then shook my head and woke me back up. And I was like, oh,
okay. I think I know. I mean, I'm not really paying too much attention. I mean, I am,
but I guess there's only so much you can. Can we talk? Can't even talk? Why can I not talk?
I can't believe there's no talk button. All right, let me go to the, hold on. Before
I let go anywhere. Where's that merchant? I'll let you buy shit. Yeah, they sell guns,
ammo, and supplies. If you have enough credits of trust, you can buy shit. So,
ammo, pistol ammo. How much do I have? 143? Let me buy ammo. Upgrades, presser, health,
med kit. Oh, grenades. I can't get them though. Locker. Oh, you can go into your locker.
Okay. All right, look.
Hold up. I just want to say how sorry I am. I didn't know. I swear. You have any idea
how much time I put into that bike. It was a drifter bike, Manny. I know. I know.
I'll make it up. I put together a new one. Oh, this piece of shit, a bike.
I know it's not. Look, I'll keep an eye out for more parts. I'll hook you up. I swear.
Okay. What about my custom gas tank, Manny? You know, the one that I got for my dead wife.
You're going to keep an eye out for that one too? Jesus. I'm sorry. Let's get the fuck out
of my way. I did it. 100% of the game. Plus a thousand trust gear. There we go. I can't
wait to be doing that. Me and Boozer can't ride north till I fix up this bike. Get some better
gear. Give me this bike. Finally. Ride to the Nero checkpoint. Let's go. Let's go.
It's a bad game. I mean, we can't, we can't, I can't bump into somebody like that.
Drift. All right. So R2 and then circle.
Can you fall off the bike?
Whatever. No third degree burns. You stay there. You rest. Okay. I'll be there as soon as I can.
I'm here. I don't know what way to find out. I guess I made it. I guess, I guess I'll see what
I can find. This is it. The Nero checkpoint. I got to find some shit for boosers.
Oh, you can't. All right. Games, not the games. All right.
Why even fight them? Just run into them. Quick save. T-pad. Do I have the code? I gotta
find the code. Okay. Uh, restore power to the Nero mobile medical unit.
No, I was trying to, what? I was trying to, never mind. You know what I was trying to do.
That's, oh, that's, I told you I was gonna hate it. I told you I was gonna not like
that mechanic. I was gonna, my thumb was gonna touch it. It won't start. It needs gas.
I can get gas. I know where gas is. Just find a can. Saving game at the bike. Yes.
I know about saving the game at the bike. I figured it out. Can. I just need a gas can.
Dude, I just love scavenging. This gives me flashbacks to when I played The Surge.
Well, I'm gonna have to disagree with you there for one reason. Because when I played
The Surge, I was insufferably angry at the game. I hated every second of that game. So, I mean,
I'm not like angry right now. I'm just kind of bewilderment to try to figure out if I like
it or not, you know. Bewilderment is the good way to describe this. Give me this stuff.
Beer bottle rag. Can I make this jump? You don't like it. Just get over it. That's not
true yet. Hold on. You gotta give me like a... What did I just do that for? Just give me like
another 30 minutes to tell you about my initial assessment of the game. All right,
we're gonna get gas. Probably over there. Can I just take it out of the bike?
Can I put a hose in and just like suck the back of it? Found it. That's as far as you
can throw. I need 20 hours for my initial thoughts. No, no. I just need like a few.
We haven't even seen anything yet. All we've seen is... Who's this?
That's gonna bring them all down on me. But where are they? Right when I get out, really.
Oh god. I need bandages. Can I stealth by? I probably can. Okay. I gotta like get in there.
I don't want to go in the front door. Speakers! Where the hell are the speakers?
I don't feel in danger right now. There's two people. How would they keep their shit?
If there were like a hundred people chasing me right now, I'd be like, oh no!
It's two people. Toilet paper and a drill. Neuro injectors can be found inside neuro medical
units at neuro checkpoints. Use them to permanently increase your health, stamina, or focus.
How would you inject yourself? Health, stamina, or focused shot skill? I don't know.
This is a tough decision. Probably stamina. All right, ready? I'm gonna press them all at
the same time and when everyone happens, happens. Ready? One, two, three! Health.
There's a bed in here. Why would there be a gun locker here? This is weird. Speakers!
Why? Speakers!
All right. I'm trying. Don't even use a weapon. Just swing. Speaker!
This game really likes to say son of a bitch. You missed. Oh god damn it. Just get out of my
way. I don't have nitrous. Booster god damn it. Answer me. Booster god damn it. You son of a
bitch. Come on. That was cool. When landing, you can reduce the damage. Angle your tires
parallel to the ground. Did I have to freeze the game every time I want to tell you anything?
You're just tired of listening to your paranoid truth, your bullshit.
Everything you say is fucking absolute. I thought it was a... I don't know what I...
I just panicked. I panicked. I didn't really mean... I just panicked. I thought it was like
an infected zoomer or whatever they are. Sometimes the best strategy is to run away.
If you have stamina available, press L for you to sprint. Thanks for the tip on my bike
at the checkpoint here. Thank you. Appreciate it. Come on. Get up there. Get up. Oh fine. Don't
let me have any fun. I was just gonna start shooting it and blow it up. That was a bad
idea. He's turning into a freaker as we speak. He's turning into a freaker as we speaker.
He's dead.
And then you play him as a playable character now.
Actually, I do need help. I can't do this.
Yeah, why would you leave the door wide open? This is Firewatch. It's the same thing in
Firewatch. Bug the hell out.
300 nanometers that way. I can't even jump off this either. I can't like jump off that and
land. No, hold on. Let me... Okay, let's go. I love freedom in environments. No, you go the
right way. I would call this game in a trend of closed world games. All right, let's go.
Oh my god. What? I can't believe you hit that thing. I can't believe you hit the dog.
That's it. All right. I don't know. I want my open world freedom. I'm going this way.
Something's wrong. Where's my bike? Oh, it does sound... That sound is so... It really
is like waking up your grandfather instead of I fell off my bike and it crushed me.
Grandpa. Grandpa. Grandpa.
Stop pausing the game. Use scrap to repair your bike. Approach the bike and hold circle
to begin repairing it. I thought this was a town that I was supposed to go to.
All right, sounds good. Oh my god, I'm dead. Get off the bike. Okay, so I have $200 if
anyone wants to sell me something. Sorry about all that. Oh, rifle. Get rifle. Get rifle. Get
rifle. Get rifle. Okay, all right, man. All right, so clear the ambush camp. Sure thing.
So there's a couple more people here. Let me upgrade this.
Video games. Oh, wait, I need to repair the bike. No, give me the... Do I have it?
Do I have the rifle? It's on your back. Is it repaired? No, I'm using scrap metal to fix it.
All right, cool. I need to see. You know what I mean? I have to test and see if this works.
This is more important than anything else in the whole game. Am I going to sneak up on
somebody and we have to do the cool thing, the desperate thing to have five million of these
lying around? Because they want you to do this and I'm gonna do it. Well, he did it. It works.
By the way, that wouldn't even happen. Where am I? Am I all the way back here?
Of course it works. What did I end up? Oh, I have to do that again. That's what I want you
to do. Yeah, it is. I'm gonna turn off the headlights. This time I'm not just gonna drive
straight in. I'm gonna leave the bike at the door. All right, all right, all right, all right.
Now we're gonna just clear the camp. I'm gonna do this nice and slow and skillfully.
What? What am I holding? Is this a cocktail?
Something's out here, you asshole. Someone's hit. He's hiding. Look for him.
Where's that coming from? I don't know. He's dead. Uh, yeah.
I didn't think you could actually hit them with the frog. Damn it. Where is he? Um,
he's covering fire. A squirrel dropped an acorn on me. Shoot to kill. Dude,
I just felt this lady with rocks. Uh-oh. Who? Who found me? Is he shooting at her?
Are you the one throwing rocks? Are they even shooting at me? He's flanking me. Oh,
all right. Well, I had my fun. I'm supposed to do this stealthily. Hold on. Let me search
their bodies. All right. This is what I'm talking about here, man. Get them both. I
need ammo for this. I don't have any ammo. Can I even replace the uh, I don't think I
can even replace the crossbow. It's primary. Get rifle. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Check this out. All right. We're fine. There we go. Let's just take them out. Nice and slow.
Do it right. They're throwing rocks at us. How many are them? I don't know. They might be
200. Where did you come from? They shoot when I'm... You guys are really stupid.
He's pretending to be dead. They're playing a gigantic game of telephone.
Hey, he shot me and then distance. He's been shot. Somebody shot him. Somebody shot him.
Boom. Oh, God. What happened here? Kill me. All right. I think I just alerted the horde.
Did I really? Oh, fuck. Hold on. Where is he? He's not here. Where's this guy?
You got him. What do you mean, got him? Oh, fuck. All right. Hold on. This is my opportunity
to do this. Watch this. Ready? I gotta get this right. Go that way. Go that way so I can
throw it in the fire. Who killed who there? I don't know. Did the eye die there? Who's
got the... Who killed... Who killed who? Hey, where is he? Have we got some tail? You know,
we got... Moonshine! I stabbed myself in the stomach. He's gonna get the same spiel.
He tricked me. He tricked me. Wait, I'm gonna go get another one. Just stay there.
He's dumb. I'll be fine. Is somebody in this building? He's gonna come in here, isn't he?
What's head level right here? Right. Whoa! I thought the gun... I thought the rock was
a fucking explosive bullet rock for a second. Where'd he go? Get in here. Yeah, I'm in there.
Come on in. Just step in the door. Step inside of here. Okay, he's gonna get covered.
Don't fall back. Get in. Did they seriously run away? All right, that's enough.
I'm pissed off. Let's go. Let's heal and let's get out of here. Exclusive. This is an exclusive
game. This is a Sony PlayStation exclusive. You can only get this on the PlayStation 4.
Turn up the difficulty. I feel like that would make the game harder, though.
You know, that makes the game difficult. I don't do that. You gotta get a PS4. Get one. Oh.
Hey. If you had bullets, I wouldn't be breathing now, would I? You've been the one
throwing rocks. Please, mister. Don't shoot women if I have a choice. I have a choice.
I ain't got nothing. I got nowhere to go. You got it that way. What is your opportunity?
There's always some way. All right, let's see if they got an underground bunker around here.
Investigate the bunker. I got nowhere to go. We all got nowhere to go. Yes. I mean,
here it is. I can't even slide down. I can't fast go down. I can't really. Nothing in here besides
the storyline. Stupid. Stupid. There it is. I had to get it right, sorry. Looks like they
marked it up good. 91% that's an A-. Gear up for the ride. Me and Boozer can't ride north
until I fix up this bike. Get some better gear. Craft unlocked. Ambush camp hunter.
I can make people. Spiked bat. Yes, yes, yes. Newly discovered craft recipes are shown in the
survival wheel. Yes, yes, yes. It sounded like bike engines riding somewhere on the mountain.
I just finished clearing it. Use a bunk at safe locations like bunkers or the safe houses
to leave in advance time. Some challenges like infestations can be approached differently
depending on the time of day. Additionally, progress can be saved when you're a bunk.
The radio tower for Copeland. Climb the tower. See if I can see.
We're gonna climb the tower. I'm just gonna close my eyes for a little bit.
I'm still on the phone. You know, you say some real fucked up shit and you sleep.
I don't think I've ever heard somebody say they want to shove an ice cream up their ass.
Cold side first. All right, let's go. Get up. Oh, it's X. What the fuck?
That sounds like a one guy comment. Don't sound like yourself. It's nothing. You know,
I just let this drifter get the drop on me. Lucky for me, she was out of ammo.
You know, the game's boring and the streamer is always too ass jokes.
Yes, yes, I let her go. It's a climbable tower.
Yeah, well, something's gonna do it, right? Does it matter what Deacon out?
Jesus, what a climb. All right, let's see what the hell was just talking about.
All right, look at the O'Leary Mountain safe house. It's doing it for me, so don't worry.
We're right. Someone's on the mountain. I see smoke from their campfire.
Son of a bitch. I knew I heard something. Where are they? I'm gonna head out there.
No, god damn it. Boozer, gotta get your arm healed up so we can ride the hell out of here.
I'll take care of him. Mark, it's just, I'm going a little stir crazy here, Deacon.
Just try to stay awake in case they head your way. Deacon out.
There's no, I can't jump. Do I actually have to climb down this?
I don't want to do the whole climb again. I can't slide.
Leap of faith. No, but I mean, there's no, I can like, no.
I guess this is how you actually would do it.
I just had to go up and down the ladder. That's it.
Locate the camp. All right, can I call my bike and I whistle from my bike?
Now you can fall off. Now you fall off and take damage when you fall.
Took us this far to figure that out. All right, there's a...
Encore. Encore. Encore. I could do that. That's bullshit.
I swear to god I could fall down this. I could go down that. I know I could.
Look, that was the difference. That's not much of a difference.
That's amazing. Yeah, I do need some. Deacon out.
I need my bike. Oh, fuck. There's my bike behind me the whole time.
No, I'm not doing it again. It's not gonna be the third encore.
No, it was right here. Okay. All right, we're good. Let's move on.
Wow, what the hell? Can I climb this?
You wouldn't put a tree bent over like this if I couldn't just tightrope on it, right?
I guess so. Gunfire. Does that mean anything?
Who's shooting? Oh, that's the motorcycle doing that.
I'm out of gas. Mechanics can repair or refuel your bike for a fee.
The price adds up, so take care of your bike when you can.
While your bike is idle, you can walk it backward or forward.
If you're trying to be quiet or you're out of gas,
you can walk your bike around as long as the path isn't too steep.
How do I walk it? No, I have to walk the bike.
No, I'm sorry. I have to... Just leave me alone. I don't want anything...
They're still fucking chasing me. I'm out of stamina.
All right, I have to... desperate.
Please, just leave me alone. I don't want to kill anybody. I don't want to kill you.
I have to. Unfortunately, I have to.
My god, he's faster than I can aim.
You leaving? The stick aiming is slower than he can move.
How many... What the fuck?
No way, dude! Oh my god!
All right, let me walk the bike. How do I walk the bike?
Did it tell me a button combination?
No, I'm out in front of the coin-operated toy in front of Walmart.
It's too steep.
No, it's not.
No, I'm good. I'm on my tricycle.
I see a gas station. I'm fine.
On the road, where it's safe.
And then I can just glide. Yeah, now I can just glide.
Cool gameplay.
I'll get there eventually.
What happens if I leave the bike?
Can I get the bike back eventually?
Or is it one of those scenarios where I have to keep it with me?
St. John to Copeland's camp is done.
The radio tower's locked down and I've restored your radio buffling.
Not see the value in St. John.
But radio-free Oregon is the only thing keeping us from turning into savages.
A wheelchair would be faster.
Savages is about nine square meals.
Try going hungry for three days.
There's no such thing as a starving patriot.
Well, sir, booze man, I have your word.
They set up all the railroad tracks.
There's got to be gas in here.
There's going to be gas.
Kill every one of the sons of bitches.
Gas? Come on.
Ooh, fire axe.
Can I craft gas?
I'm not sure I can craft.
Can I craft?
That's just a tractor.
Pipe bombs.
Pipe bomb, huh?
Where did I get these?
By holding L2 and aim to press to throw.
Well.
Is that going to explode?
Hey, somebody's hit.
It had nothing to do with the pipe bomb.
I'm not unkillable.
See, I can still play on normal.
Do I have gas?
Hey, hey, wait, wait.
Why am I already in combat?
I can't die on the bike.
That was a fucking marionette on my leg.
All right, here we go.
Maybe you should stop screaming shit and attracting people.
Yeah, you just heard gunshots.
I think they're shooting at me.
I'm not good.
I might be mistaken though.
Brax.
No, no, no, stop, stop, stop.
You're getting stuck.
Stop getting stuck.
Okay, can I please just get out of here?
He shot me.
Why did he shoot me?
I'm about to roll up in there and just start swinging.
All right, let me search.
I gotta, just go, go, go, go.
Just walk it this way.
Who cares?
I don't care.
I have to go down here.
All right, I'm not fucking around.
Not anymore.
Come on.
He has one of those too.
Like a bear trap.
What?
Can he go in this?
Put it under him.
Hey, how did he not go on the ground and catch my leg?
Heel, heel, heel, heel, heel.
Oh my god.
How do I have another one?
Plus three bear trap.
Plus four bear trap.
Plus five, six, seven, eight.
I just get infinite bear trap.
I could sell these too.
He's duping.
He's resorted to duping.
All right, I'll do it with 50.
50 is like, it's gonna be like five grand.
Okay.
Where's bear trap?
So I don't have any.
How do I not have any?
It says plus 50.
Waiting to jump me.
Step in it.
Oh, no.
You're not gonna roll.
Oh fuck, I have no ammo.
Oh, you dick.
Pick it up.
Mother fucker.
You talking to me?
Yeah, nice job, man.
Kill him.
That guy sucked you out of me 20 bucks.
All right, there's only one guy left, all right?
This guy right here is two.
We're gonna kill the guy with the handgun.
Okay, give me the fucking bear trap.
I have to do this.
This is so important.
Where'd he go?
Is he behind?
Where is he?
Oh fuck, he's right there.
Come on, do it.
Just come over here.
I need to see this, if it's possible.
If not, then who cares, right?
If I'm hidden for long and I feel he comes out,
because he can't see me.
Come on, come out.
Oh fuck, he's going, he's wrapping the other way.
Give me, hold on.
Don't take this.
Where is he?
It's right there.
I don't think he knows where I am.
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
Okay, here we go, ready?
Oh my god, which way is he going?
I haven't moved from this spot.
How would you not know where I was?
This is our opportunity.
Here it comes.
Should I just sneak up behind him?
Okay, here's the plan, ready?
The plan is throw a rock, sneak up behind him.
He's not listening to the rock.
I can't, I can't tell if he's,
what's he doing?
He's so erratic right now.
He's not listening anymore.
Okay, I'm gonna try something.
One, two, three.
I don't know where he went.
Where'd he go?
Where the fuck did he go?
Where did he go?
Is he behind me?
Is he behind the tent?
God damn it.
All right, I tried, I tried.
Oh fuck, I don't want to do this again.
Okay, I'm just gonna do this as fast as possible now.
Hold on, I'll get it.
Just wait, I'm gonna do it really fast.
I'm gonna make sure I get this done like right now.
Oh, I can't even go back.
Bitches.
You have a shotgun.
There's no way.
No, fuck, what?
No, take it seriously, please.
Heal, heal, heal, heal, heal.
Wait, I just like froze him in time.
He's still, oh no.
No, no, no, no, no.
I put it in the trap.
What trap?
I put the other one down to my left.
I picked, didn't I pick that?
Here we go, this is for real this time.
I was stupid to pay attention to the guy that was on the cliff.
I know I put the one down to my left,
but I didn't pick the one up to my right.
No, I want to go up here.
What's with every game nowadays?
Your hitbox is like five people wide.
I want to like go over here.
It's like, you didn't want to like run out here
all the way over here and then stop.
All right, here we go.
Fucking mad because bad.
Mad because bad.
Thank God I slid through it.
What the hell?
What is this thing over here?
There's no trap, don't worry.
Oh my fucking god damn.
Now you have shotguns.
Now you're shooting the shotgun with ease.
No, give me the...
They just always appear behind me.
Okay, so I need to stop fucking around.
They're still alive.
Oh, you motherfucker.
No, I have one bullet left.
Dude, how many people are in this camp?
How many bullets do I have?
Is the ammo in here?
What am I doing?
No, I want that.
I want...
I don't want this.
I can't...
I don't have ammo.
What happened?
Did I...
All right, I'm about sick of my incompetence here.
What is...
Yes, they set up on the railroad tracks.
Okay, kill everyone and I...
Give me my binoculars.
I want to like mark them.
Why can't I not use my binoculars to mark people?
They've made such a big deal of that.
I want the rock.
All right, what the fuck are you doing?
Category distraction.
Put the...
What the fuck are you doing?
Put the rock on.
I want the rock.
What the hell is going on?
Do I not have any more rocks?
All right, somebody's gotta explain to me why I can't select the rock.
It doesn't like me.
I think I'm just gonna go...
I'm just killing them.
Like, we're just gonna kill them.
I'm just gonna kill them.
I just have to make this...
They're all right here.
Watch this.
Ready?
I'm gonna get one shot here.
Kill.
Dead.
No, I hit him right in the head though.
Oh my god.
If I just could put my fucking rocks on.
I'm gonna make these count.
Almost out.
I'm gonna get closer.
Wait for me?
Huh?
My god!
I've seen that coming.
That's the last of them.
Let's take the hell off of Leery Mountain.
You sound like you're having fun.
I am, actually.
I have to keep Boozer alive.
I'm gonna have to go back and walk my car.
Boozer, he's done.
Squad of camp.
They won't be doing any more killing on O'Leery Mountain.
Hank, I should have been there.
Another bear trap joke.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Rest up, booze man.
Rest up before we ride north as soon as your army heals.
You got that?
Jerem's fuming, dude.
He's fuming, he's fuming.
Let's go.
Yeah, I'm gonna ride up to the cemetery.
See if I can find the hot stash.
Sorry.
There's no gas down there.
Rest up, Boozer.
We're heading north as soon as you can ride.
Out of nowhere map.
Where are we going?
Storylines.
View story progress, view gameplay rewards, and activate missions.
So, crazy Willy's infestation.
World's end.
Or out of chasing Leon.
Out of nowhere.
Search the pioneer cemetery for Leon's drug stash.
That's the one we're gonna do.
God damn it.
786 meters this way.
Deke, you there?
Just give me some forward momentum.
Did you say you were heading north?
Booze man, no.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I just kind of...
There's no gas down here.
Third degree burns will do that to you.
So, take care of Alvarez, you know?
Let me just check.
Deke, there's a lot to do.
Better get walking.
Yeah, I know.
I better start moving.
Take care of her, Boozer.
Just get some rest.
Deke, get out.
I can't like dump that in the tank.
Imagine unironically thinking you were a GTA character.
Biggest vroom ever.
Maybe.
Nah, I don't think so, Cope.
Not today.
All right, I need to go...
Here we go.
I see a car.
I see a gas station.
We just have to coast our way into it.
Gas station right there.
Cars.
What the fuck?
What was that?
Why?
What?
I needed that gas.
Who has a sniper?
What in the fucking name of God is happening?
Give me that thing.
Oh, fuck.
I have no more...
Please, please, please, please, please, please heal.
I don't understand why somebody just drove a flaming car down at me.
Where was the car?
What was the set?
They just came out of nowhere.
Some guns are so powerful,
their shots can pierce through multiple enemies with one round.
Trying lining up multiple enemies.
Okay.
Shot the place up.
Then he just took off.
And he said his box got erected.
He was wearing some kind of motocross helmet.
Silver.
Okay, if I go now, I might be able to catch up to him.
I want him alive, Deke.
Alive.
I needed that gas that was in this car.
You catch this guy, then radio me.
Fetch him and hang the bastard right from this time we start showing these drifters,
sons of bitches, that we have law and order in this kingdom.
One bullet in this.
No offence meant to yourself.
I better be ready.
All right, let's get it up.
I'll take it.
I'll find him.
How's this thing doing?
You can't boost without equipping your bike with nitrous.
Thanks.
All right, let's go.
I can't believe there's no gas over here.
I'm gonna check down there.
There has to be gas over here.
Has to be. Look it.
It's like a bunch of big gas tanks right there.
Gas?
Gas.
Give me something to gas.
Anything.
Please.
Gas.
No, no gas.
Are you serious?
It's just like a lighter fluid.
It's not gas.
Oh, found it.
Thank god.
Fill it up and get me out of here.
Fill it up.
All right, repair the bike because I just got run over.
Finally, it's gonna feel so good to actually be able to ride this thing again.
Feels so different.
Let's go.
The boos are...
No, no.
You're gonna get yourself killed.
You're gonna wait till you're whole, brother.
Nitrous, too.
I'm over here anyway, so I'll take care of that mess.
Right up here.
All right, clear the logging camp infestation zone.
You just ran two stopsides.
That's fine.
There's nobody here.
I feel like it's just...
Yeah, let's just...
I'm cutting through here.
I'm not gonna follow the road.
The GPS in this game is dumb.
It's a post-apocalyptic world.
You don't have to follow the roads.
Shit.
Can I jump it?
This is Radio Free Oregon.
The truth shall set you free.
This earth is a gift for us all.
Okay, I'm good.
To use as we see fit.
To provide for ourselves and our families.
I'm not saying this.
It's the Lord that gave us dominion over it.
But that wasn't enough for some men.
They wanted more.
When our fuel down, they jacked up the prices
so they could consolidate power into their own hands.
So we wanted to build dams for electricity.
But they're precious runs of salmon.
Coke, Coke, Coke.
Shut the hell up.
Return...
What do you mean?
Return to shore.
What?
You can't be in water for more than three seconds
so you drown.
Closed world game.
Coin it.
That's a new phrase, man.
Why can't you go in the water?
I mean, very clearly I could go in the water.
There's even a swimming animation.
That's really odd.
If you're gonna have a swimming animation in the game
and what's the point of making it
so you can swim for three seconds and die?
Is this gonna happen again?
Is it gonna trigger the random event if I go over here?
No, they're dead.
That's weird.
That's very weird.
But all right, good to know.
So don't go in...
What about the bike?
I need...
I want to test something here.
Hold on.
So the bike can swim, but I can't.
What if I go in a little deeper?
I'm just testing.
Can't get back on the bike.
Okay.
I'm sure I'm not getting dragged under by something.
You can retrieve the bike.
Oh, that's good to know.
Taken by the ground demon.
I would believe that at this point.
That's so odd.
But why?
Is this clear?
Okay.
Back in the day, when you went into water,
you just instantly died.
You sunk through the earth and it instantly killed you.
I'm treading water.
Is it a weight thing?
I'm gonna make...
What the fuck, man?
I'm not sure I want to listen.
I'm gonna go around.
In the site here instead of over at site 13.
How do I turn this off?
This is the weirdest, longest voicemail I've ever received.
What audio book did I download?
What is going on over here?
Is this a random encounter?
You gotta take a closer look.
Water can?
What is it?
Upgrade?
No, it's tracks.
Let's take a look around.
Oh, look.
He dropped something.
Let's see.
Drug vent.
Whatever they're called.
Survival hint.
Plants can be easily...
Yeah.
Well, where is it now?
We lost the trail.
Over here?
What is it?
Is that him?
Should I be sneaking?
What exactly am I looking for here?
Am I looking for this person?
But what am I looking for you for?
Found you.
Another bounty.
Oh, it was a bounty.
Okay, I get it.
Use this.
Don't die from this, please.
Okay, well.
Got the bounty.
I would take point and click Batman over this.
Come on.
Like, let...
Just give it a little bit.
We're only gonna do this for like a stream
or maybe another one.
No, we're not.
We'll do this...
This is day gone.
One day gone.
We gotta burn them out.
Make it safer to ride.
What does that mean?
We gotta burn them out?
What am I burning out?
Oh, I missed the...
There was three, that...
Three, whatever.
I don't want to do that.
Water!
It's water!
No, it's not.
It's a road.
Okay.
Pulling the camera all the way out here
so we can wait till nighttime.
Enter Pioneer Cemetery.
Find the statue.
I can't open that.
I think it's gonna alert the horde.
Don't blink.
Scrap.
Yeah.
Angel statue.
Anybody see an angel?
Angel, angel, angel.
I don't see an angel, but I see this.
Just you.
Oh, hey, thanks.
You're such a sweetie.
No angel here.
No band.
Why would I ban you for saying that?
That was such a sweet thing to say.
Leaving the mission zone.
Leave the zone.
No, I'm not gonna leave the zone.
I'm enjoying my closed world game, okay?
Can I go in here?
Could it be over this way or something?
I don't know where it would be.
I have 15 minutes to switch the game.
There it is.
Is that an angel?
I'm not switching the game.
Weeping angel.
This has got to be it.
I'm not...
I'm playing this one.
Where'd you hide the stash, Leon?
I'm enjoying my time.
It's just a fun experience to check it out.
Oh, it...
Oh, I thought that was a person.
I was about to go up and sneak and kill this person.
Take the cooler.
What, do I got a guy's kidneys?
Can't climb that.
A chopper?
What are you talking about?
You can't climb this.
A neurochopper?
It just buzzed right over me and acted like I wasn't even there.
All this time and a fed chopper shows up out of nowhere.
I'm gonna chase them down and I'm gonna see what the hell they're doing.
Get off of me.
Oh no, I dropped a beer.
I gotta get this to the tailgate party.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
What?
Get it back to the bike?
To tie stash to bike.
I...
God damn it.
Wait, what?
Whose bike is that?
Why?
I'm not leaving the mission zone.
Okay?
I promise you.
No, if it failed me I would have changed games.
We were so close.
No, come on.
Let me just investigate the helicopter.
Uh, what...
What helicopter?
They're slowing down.
Looks like they're stopping.
You're talking to me?
Who's keeping you hostage to play this?
We all know you're a comedy genius, but I feel like maybe you've tapped this game for all it's worth.
You guys don't have very much confidence at all.
Now that the military's involved, let me...
Hold on, let me at least just...
Come on, this game's 60 bucks.
Dude, I bought the digital deluxe version, too.
This was like 90 bucks.
They're immune to attacks.
Okay.
Now I'm getting where you're coming from, guys.
Now I see what you're getting.
I see what you're talking about here.
I didn't see it before, now I do.
I get it now.
No, I didn't buy the digital deluxe.
Why would I ever do that?
No, I get...
I know what you mean.
I didn't...
For a sec...
Okay, I'm gonna line this up and get a collateral here.
Let's try to get like...
Let me try to get like four people in one shot.
Don't look over.
What the hell are you doing?
Go investigate the rock.
I want to line up like a quad.
You can't use any weapons.
Okay.
I...
I can't kill anyone.
I can't attack anyone.
Not even stealth kill.
I just...
Oh, no.
It's one of these fucking clothes goddamn.
All right.
Okay.
Listen.
All right.
Just everybody relax.
I know.
I understand.
Just hold on.
I...
I've seen the light.
I've seen it.
Yes, I can't even...
I thought it meant like melee attack.
But what is this shit?
Why would you show me that thumbnail
of a guy being stabbed in the neck for this mission?
What the...
Why?
I thought I saw the knife.
All right.
So...
Oh, man.
Is this hidden?
This counts as grass, right?
Are you getting hungry?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
Fucking dump.
My flashlight is on.
The hell am I doing?
Why am I reading this?
Where'd like the researcher go up there?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
In the helicopter?
Do I have to take the helicopter?
I don't know.
Just throw...
Do I have to go in the helicopter?
Where is he?
I don't...
I don't know where...
This way?
In the helicopter.
Are you sure?
I don't know if you're sure about that.
Hold on.
Wait.
One.
Two.
I'm luring him.
I'm luring him to me.
Anybody hear any sound?
Helicopter.
Go.
You guys lied.
Other side of the helicopter?
Oh, fuck.
I'm just waiting for it to be like...
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Well, I just tried.
Other side.
Stop.
It's not gonna...
There's no alarm in there.
It's at the back.
It's not at the back.
That's a tail.
I have to find the guy in the white suit.
It's this way.
You guys lied.
I have to just go this way.
Here we go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Go.
Wait.
Where'd the doctor go?
This way.
Somewhere, right?
Oh my god damn it.
If I swear to god, if I have to go to the tail...
Is it that guy right there?
Down that way.
There were people talking right next to the helicopter.
Yeah, that's...
I know, but I feel like...
Can I just go down that way?
Please stay low.
Stay low.
Okay, stay low.
What are you talking about?
I am.
Do I...
I feel like I have to...
Hold on.
Let me see if everyone's lying to me.
You have to enter the helicopter from the top.
It's not the helicopter.
They went uphill on that west side.
Yeah, like up here, right?
Hold on.
Up like this way?
No, that's right.
West, not north.
Okay, I'm gonna go...
Just go west.
I'm just gonna go west.
I'm just gonna be tactical about this and just go...
What?
We need something to move.
Hide this bunch quick!
Up here.
Go north-south.
And god damn force stealth game.
Oh, there is nothing worse.
I'm gonna...
I gotta send them that way.
You, like, go over there.
I was going the right way.
I was.
Everybody just got in my head.
I was going the right way.
I was going past the helicopter.
I was doing it correct.
And everyone says, no, you're doing it wrong.
I was going...
And then we're at all...
I went all the way back around the circle.
It's over here.
It's up there.
Please don't turn around!
Don't turn around!
I made it.
Okay, now it's up here.
They went this way.
Oh!
Get the fuck out of here!
Leave me alone!
They went right here.
Oh my god!
Where do I go?
No!
What?
I...
There's nobody here.
Where is this guy?
I already went to the helicopter, like, three times.
Is it over...
There's a car over here.
Is it this way?
I think I was supposed to be tailing somebody.
Oh my god!
This fucking cave!
No, there's no cave!
I'm one of those who'll fucking distract you.
In the water?
Like, down there?
I went over there.
It was nothing.
Is it like a little spot I can go in here?
Okay, hold on.
But this just goes back up!
Somebody open up a goddamn game, Janie.
The map has a quest point.
But what?
No.
This is out of the mission zone!
This is out of bounds!
The mission ends if I walk out here!
Hold on.
For start the mission, don't throw any rocks.
Just follow the guy in the white suit.
I just follow the guy in the white suit.
Quit the game.
No, no, no.
I can't let it be me.
I have to win.
Throw rocks at the guy with the suit.
All right, where...
Hold on, wait, wait.
But where...
Where's the guy in the suit?
It keeps spawning me.
It's soft locking me here.
Where is this person?
The whole game is gray.
I can't see anything.
Go west?
Like, that's...
Okay, here I go.
This is gonna lead back up to the spawn.
Up the hill with the fence.
No, that's bullshit because look!
This is the start of the game!
This is the beginning of the game!
Go north.
You went everywhere but the right direction.
Why do I have to follow the straight line path
in an open world game?
I can go left from here.
The other fence.
Look...
I mean, like, you're talking about over here.
Let me get the fucking binoculars here.
Like, he marked this guy.
Like, you're talking about this way.
What do you mean the other left?
This is left!
This way.
Like, just go straight this way.
Okay, where that little pixel is pointing
is where you want me to go, right?
All right, okay, hold on, wait.
I'm looking at the helicopter right now.
To the left of this helicopter
or to the right of this helicopter?
Hard left.
So this way.
I don't know.
Yes, no, left, the back.
Left, left of the back.
There's a cave right next to you.
Where is there a cave?
There's a cave.
Wait, the cave.
I don't see a cave.
I'm going for the...
I'm going this way.
Everyone said this way.
Hard left.
Give me, give me, give me!
There's nobody in here!
There's nobody inside the cave!
There is!
There's a scientist!
Going too far from the researchers!
What are you talking about?
He's from...
I've been...
I've been far away from the researchers.
Be careful!
Wait, now it wants me to clear the camp?
I have to sit here and listen.
No, stop it.
Just let it in.
I spent a whole day on this mission.
A whole day going...
Follow the researcher to continue eavesdropping.
Stay close and out of sight.
Oh, come on!
I really don't think anyone,
and I mean anyone,
that has ever played a video game
in their whole life thinks that...
No!
Thinks this is fun!
Following...
Forced stealth follow and listen to somebody talk.
Nobody thinks...
I don't want to listen to this!
We have like decades of video game research
and knowledge.
They made whole games...
Some of the Assassin's Creed games
were this mission's the whole game.
And everyone was like,
all right, I'm going to go to the escort,
walk behind them and listen to the mission.
Now, I can stomach this,
but I can't...
They have to have forced stealth
because you have to listen to this.
You can't just throw an axe at somebody's head.
We have to hear this!
We got to go right here.
Dude, I'm going to throw a rock as hard as I can
to make sure it's in space.
Quit, quit, no!
No quitting!
Hurry up, go back to DOS.
No, he's not seeing me.
That light is really close.
Please don't see me.
Okay, return to your bike.
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
Get me to buy a bike.
What's the fastest way to get over there?
I didn't mark anybody.
Um, shit.
No, con!
Con!
Why is this guy just here?
Don't make me do it all again.
Don't make me do it again.
Thank you.
You saw that.
You saw me do it.
Give me back my bike.
Give me back to the bike.
Oops!
Oh no.
Okay, come on.
Give me to the bike.
No, he's going to come over here too, isn't he?
You stay all the fucking way over there.
For God's sakes.
Thank God, get me out.
Oh my God, it only took like 40 minutes.
Holy shit.
You better switch to a better game or no dessert for you.
Oh, fuck all the quitters.
All right, you know what?
That one guy, you're right.
Why is he still playing?
He admitted it's not.
I never said it wasn't fun.
I just said why would they do missions like this?
Unlocked.
Crafting recipe.
Residue bolt.
All right, get me out of here.
Turn on each other.
Cool.
All right, let's go back in the game.
I got to deliver my...
I got to deliver this.
New skill.
Finally, we got a skill point.
Check this out.
Probably didn't even think it was...
You're going to see this.
Ability to activate focused aim.
Move and aim a ranged weapon with more precision.
Ability to follow a melee attack with a ranged attack for massive damage.
Increase the time that icons display in survival vision.
Plants are displayed on the minimap.
Provides a chance to retrieve some bolts that have been...
I mean, I guess this one.
Oh yeah.
This one.
It's sponsored.
This is not a sponsored stream.
I would have...
My contract would have been ripped in half.
Sarah.
That phone call in the beginning of the stream would have been from the sponsor.
We're just calling to let you know that the contract's terminated.
You said, fuck this dumb stealth mission.
And you laughed at something.
Hello.
You should play Photoshop.
What do you mean Photoshop?
I don't know how to use Photoshop that well.
He doesn't come off the bike.
Fuck you, buddy.
I got something for you.
Smile!
No!
Please!
Do not Bioshock!
We're good.
Microsoft Office.
I'm always just writing paper.
No, come on.
Come on, just give it a chance.
Clear?
Is there a hostage?
Okay.
No!
I can't do it.
I can't.
It doesn't work.
What the hell?
No, I want you to throw the pipe bomb.
Great.
No, I can't quit.
I can't quit.
We have like three and a half hours in.
Come on.
This stream's only going to be like another three hours long.
Four hours.
We got to stick with this.
It's the only time you're ever going to see this game.
Don't you want to know if you want to buy it?
I went right through that log.
Shit.
I already know.
Do you though?
But what if like something happens and you go,
oh shit, that sounds like fun.
Yeah, let me just...
This is what we're doing.
Don't worry.
I'll be live tomorrow.
If you don't want to see it then it's all good.
We're just having fun.
What is on the other side?
I'm having a fun time.
I'm doing fine.
I'm having fun.
Raider camp.
What you mean sons of bitches, aren't you?
As you said this week.
I mean guys, I'm being real.
It's either this...
Or...
No, I can't even say that.
Because we're doing that on Sunday.
Or what?
Say it to everyone.
It's freaking out.
I was going to say Mario Yahtzee, but that's...
Shouldn't have said it.
Don't quit.
No, we'll play Mario Yahtzee on Sunday.
Well, like, let me...
Hold on, let me like...
Move the car.
Finally, some decent food.
One guy said don't quit.
That's true.
And plus this was what I wanted to do today.
Look, I'll think about it, okay?
Here's what's going to happen.
We're going to play this a little bit more.
And I'm going to go pee.
It's three and a half hours.
I haven't peed yet.
It's a world record.
Nobody said that?
Yes, they did.
Scroll back.
Just go up on your mouse.
Drive five feet.
Move another car.
Line it up, line it up, line it up, line it up.
Fuck!
I had it too.
Oh!
I'm angry about that.
What?
All right, bye.
I guess.
Pee stream?
Oh, you're going to get a pee here.
No, not on stream, but I'm going to go.
No, get off, get off, get off, get off, get off.
Can I not move this car?
I can't move this car.
No, that's not true.
No, I definitely can.
I was going to say no.
Obstructed five bike.
No shit, huh?
At least let us play with smart click.
I'll think about it after I pee.
Think faster.
Okay, if there's another roadblock, I'm going to quit again.
Good, good.
I'm out of gas.
No roadblock.
We get to stay.
Let me at least turn this shit in.
Gas?
Camp was wiped out.
No, I know that, but I heard.
Okay, look.
What's what are you doing?
Why is it doing that?
Wait, wait, you're into their LZ?
What the?
Just listen.
How do I call the bike?
Recover.
Bike is too far to recover.
Oh, we're losing internet here.
Hey, get some sleep.
D, get out.
This is Radio Free Oregon.
Walking.
Check the nerd camp for fuel.
It's too far now.
It's too far.
Look at the gas back there.
Just turn around, I can coast.
Uh-oh, boring, boring, boring streamer.
No, just wait, wait, just wait.
Something funny could happen.
Right here, ready?
Oh shit, not even the funny music will make them laugh.
What?
I just want gas.
I don't care about anything else here.
One of these days I'm going to need to turn the stream on during this.
And I'm just going to be making balloon animals.
Hey, the game sucks.
Like boring.
Come on, play something else.
Oh shit, I'm going to turn the camera on.
Just start making fucking dogs and stuff.
Find the fuse.
I just want gas.
I don't even know how to make balloon animals.
Thank God.
All right, the stream can go on.
It's right there, just give it to me.
I can see it.
It's right here.
That's gas, right?
That's gas, gasoline.
I'll take it.
You guys actually have pretty good patience.
I will give you that.
We're going for about four hours.
But it's been fun.
You guys are really patient.
What do you mean?
How?
How are they patient?
No, we're not.
No, we don't.
I'm trying to give you a compliment.
Now my turn.
Give me one.
What do you think?
Your turn.
Your infestation zone.
Jump!
A cool jump.
How did you get down here?
God damn it.
My frame rate dropped to like 20 frames a second.
I didn't make the jump.
Okay, I'm holding right trigger right now.
If I don't make it this time.
See this like slow down.
Is it not catching my frames or something?
No, I'm going to make it this time.
Why would?
Why?
No way.
You tell me I can't make that jump.
It's like 15 feet.
It's not even 10 feet.
I'm hitting that jump.
I'll show you how.
You think I give a fuck right now?
We're hitting that jump and I'm going over it.
This nesting zone.
Get it.
Oh, a freakery infestation.
Did you know that the freakery infestation
are highly dangerous areas where freakers can congregate
to build their nest to hibernate during the day?
Clear all nests to be careful about that.
By the way, if you need anything else, just let me know.
I smell a nest.
Oh, I got a freakers way to check these houses, man.
Grab me and then I got his eyes out.
All right, supplies.
We're looking for ammo, snacks, bandages,
anything of that sort, guys.
If you see anything, make sure you holler at me.
And if you see anything in the comments below,
let me know if you find if you see something.
So yeah, guys, I was just chilling the other day
and I went to the ice cream store
and I got a chocolate ice cream and I really liked it.
What's your favorite ice cream?
Let me know in the comments while I game engagements.
Oh, okay, let's start the video now.
So hey, welcome to another video.
Where's the, where's my bike?
Oh, what?
I still have this stupid kidney here.
Your old videos were that exactly.
I'm not able to look back and say I've grown.
All right, that was weird
because right when the internet died, this popped up.
The second the internet tanked, I got like,
hey, make sure you just grab on your bike.
What the fuck was that?
What is happening?
I don't know.
Get off of me.
Get your eyes out.
Why did I fly off the bike?
I got clothes lined.
Oh, I could repair the engine.
This thing's fucked.
Get on, get on.
Drive the location price on your head.
It was a trip wire.
Oh, that's pretty clever.
It is fucked, dude.
Yeah, I don't know.
I pulled over though when I fixed it.
It's like a dirt bike path
that I'm riding with a giant Harley motorcycle.
Well, what the hell?
That's worth checking out.
There's just a fight here?
Who's fighting?
Will these guys be my friends?
I wonder if like, are these guys friendly?
All right, let's fight them together.
There you go.
Nice work.
You and me are now a team.
I think that was his fault.
He dove into my bike.
Three pointer.
Did he?
Wait, did he turn into?
I don't know.
Where do these people come from?
I wonder, there's this thing on the mini map.
I want to read it.
What does this say?
Three finger jack viewpoint.
Old hot fingers.
There's another person up there.
Who is that?
All right, I'm getting the fuck out of this.
Give me my bike.
My guy landed on the crown of his head.
Oh my God.
Get away from me.
I died.
Now, now you die.
Stay down.
Okay, I'm going to go look up here.
Because this stuff up here,
people were up here hanging out.
So what was even up here?
Nothing?
Nothing at all.
Why was that guy standing up here?
All right, I'm out.
Let's go.
We're not almost there.
We're close.
Shut the hell up.
I was supposed to save the guy.
Well, I mean, he just walked off a cliff.
I would love to pick those up.
Yes, this is exclusive to PS4.
We cannot get this anywhere else.
And speaking of cannot do anything else,
I don't think I can go anywhere else.
Maybe I can go this way.
Can I go over this?
No.
It's like maybe a jump or something.
All right, well, I have to go this way.
I have to do it the right way.
That's what I'm talking about.
Deer crossing.
No, I don't.
Can you do a wheelie?
I don't think you can.
Not that I've been able to do.
Cave.
Oh, it's not a cave.
Shit.
I can't go over this, I don't think.
I can't go over that.
I can't just break through that and fly off.
God, that would be so cool.
Wouldn't it?
How cool would that be if I could just fly over that?
I'd be like...
It'd be cool.
It would be cool.
There's no way for me to jump over that.
I'm going the wrong way, but can I not wrap...
No, it's a tunnel.
Turn around.
I'm not doing another tunnel.
I'm not getting off the bike three times to push cars.
We're just gonna go this way then.
I feel like the bike doesn't go that fast either.
Perfect.
Just perfect.
You know when you play GTA with your friends in multiplayer
and they do this thing where they cover the whole street in cars
to try to block the road and fuck everybody?
Why did somebody do this?
Because, you know, what about blocking the zombies?
They can just walk around.
Just let the engine explode.
If the engine explodes, then that's the end of this game for me.
Because then it'll be so humiliating.
I'll have to stop playing.
That's...
No, that's not it.
I have the binoculars.
Put the binoculars away if you could.
That would be fantastic.
Okay, Terminator.
God damn it.
Bulletproof down jackets.
That's not embarrassing.
That's...
I got ambushed.
Made it.
Give me the cutscene.
No.
I thought it was gonna go into a cutscene like it usually does.
Here we go.
Jump to fire.
Nice.
Let me in.
Don't fun-aloud.
All right, I'm gonna turn this in.
I'm gonna take a piss.
Here, we'll come back and figure out what we're gonna do.
If anybody touches this or anything on it...
We won?
What do you mean we won?
I have not made a decision yet.
You can't preemptively say you win while you hold the ball.
While it's seven to seven.
And you're running into the end zone.
You're ten yards away.
There's two or three people behind you about to tackle you.
You can't say we win.
Because what if you get tackled?
They're not gonna look good.
I keep telling you.
Everywhere you look, it's all one giant lava field.
25 feet solid rock.
It'll take jackhammers to...
I don't need a lecture, god damn it.
I get it.
I know you don't.
These people are hungry.
I don't...
Well, don't we have to at least see like the 500 zombies?
Remember E3?
I don't give a shit.
When are we gonna get the E3 moment when there's like 500 of them chasing us from behind?
Wouldn't that happen?
But this job's gotta get done, whether it takes all goddamn year.
It's not like we got somewhere else to be now, do we?
Wait, I'm not finished.
We'll make it quick, will ya, Al?
I got things to do.
Rippers, this morning one of my men spotted a large group of them coming over the pass.
And no one stopped them.
How the...
Tucker, you know we're already spread thin.
Are they headed north?
That's five hours in.
Are they headed towards us?
Yes or no?
I don't know.
E3 isn't real.
Maybe he knows.
Yeah, it is.
What the fuck are you up to now, huh?
What's this about, huh?
It's not his job to know.
It's your goddamn job to know.
I can't be in two places at one time.
You're the one me here running your dig.
You want me out there in the shit chasing the Rippers.
Go check the store.
See how much ammo we got left.
I'll tell Wheeler to watch the dig.
What are you looking at?
I don't know, I'm just waiting for you to smarten the fuck up.
Don't.
No, I'm just waiting for you to smarten the fuck up.
I can do that.
I don't know, man, I'm just waiting for you to smarten the fuck up.
I thought that was a person's head for a second.
I was like, why would you be handing me a person's head to this prison?
Ride with me.
Oh, we're going to get a double mission here.
All right, this is going to be good.
We're in a golf cart, guys.
Now you want me to quit?
You want me to quit the game?
We're in a golf cart.
Is there a potential here?
It's not my problem.
You want our food.
I'm making it your problem.
Fine, the game is good.
Two runs for you, but we're not joining your goddamn camp.
Remind me again, my old woman's memory.
Why is that?
Because it's a waste of time, Tuck.
Well, aren't you the optimist?
Rockstar added poker to Red Dead and you're playing this?
I had to uninstall Red Dead Redemption 2 to install this game.
It's not closer or further.
Look, I'm not Boozer's old lady.
He goes where he wants.
It's like 40 gigs.
Shit's burning all day and night.
I had to uninstall Red Dead.
It's piling up out here with men like you doing your jobs.
It's a big game.
It's a damn bright game.
Try using more gasoline.
It burns faster, less fumes.
Why is this waving?
Like we got so much to spare?
When it's all gone, what are you going to put in that bike of yours?
Spit and sweat?
Now what the hell is going on here?
The count's off.
Storage is missing food and some ammo.
Jesus, who was on watch last night?
Give me control of the golf cart.
Tonight, double the watch.
This shit's starting to piss me off.
You got it.
Trouble in paradise.
It's like I was saying.
Camp's like a prison.
Bunch of goddamn lazy liars, thieves, rapists, and murderers.
You know why that is?
No idea.
Cause that's who we are.
Oh, now it is.
A freak show.
Only folks who survive are those mean enough and nasty enough to out-freak the freaks.
The rest are here.
Hope and I feed them, protect them, keep them nice and cozy and warm
so they can sit on their asses and watch the world end.
You, get your ass back to work.
Don't make me go get Cyrus.
We could've walked.
We could've just taken my motorcycle.
It's cooler.
Daytime is my time.
Running this camp is no different than running a prison.
I can't remember what you said.
You were, you were what?
You were a warden or something?
Nothing so high and mighty.
I was matron of the women's ward.
You look like the sort who might've spent some time in the pan a day.
Do we really have to do, I think, follow Cadgar around in Shadrath City?
Larson was on a run yesterday.
Passed through Marion Forks.
Every time we meet a new character.
Young woman with pants.
He stopped to look around but he never found her.
Is he sure?
Larson's been doing this as you.
He knows a person from a freak.
You can skip this?
How?
I'll see what I can do.
He's getting beat up.
Look, I want the rest of my credits for Leon.
You bring me warm bodies, I'll give you all the credits you can spend.
I gotta go find Wheeler.
Someone's looking at a knight in the shack.
Let me get in.
Let me on that.
Come on.
Let me on my bike.
All right, I'm gonna go pee after we turn this in.
I'm gonna, we'll figure it out.
Alcott, what do you want, Drifter?
What's your problem?
One of my men escaped a ripper camp over by Iron Butte.
That tortured him, like they always do.
But this time, they kept asking him if he knew about it.
Two bikers, two men, asking if he'd ever seen them or heard of them.
A lot of bikes around here.
What's it got to do with me?
He's never gonna go pee.
The ripper called a mongrel.
How do you know I didn't already?
How many drifters still flying colors around here?
Is it that shit matters?
Can you ask me?
You got a price on your head.
Did have a coffee cup in here.
How's it feel to be on the other side?
Now why don't you just show me what you got because I don't have time.
Here's why you should never pee into a bottle or pee into a cup.
No matter what.
Because you'll run into a scenario like I did.
One time, I was in a long road trip.
I was in the passenger side.
What?
I'm talking about going pee into a bottle.
You can buy guns.
I see how it is.
Well, you guys must really be bored.
You don't want to hear my, like,
when I was sitting in the passenger seat, I peed into a bottle story?
Holy shit.
Oh my goodness.
You guys ever just test to see if it's possible?
Oh.
Choices.
Bring the drugs to Tucker.
Bring the drugs to Copeland.
Manny promised to help restore your piece of shit bike.
Weapons for sale.
I want the bike.
So I'm on a long road trip.
Couple of buddies.
There's no story.
Now you see, the story is,
if you want, this is the truth.
Here's like a little tip for you guys.
Anytime you tell a story that is not true,
it's still true,
but you're just making up a whole bunch of scenarios in the middle of it.
So, the real story is,
in a Gatorade bottle,
I don't know, maybe like seven years ago,
I just had a full piss and pissed into the Gatorade bottle to see if it was possible.
And I filled the whole Gatorade bottle up with pee
and still had to go and had to like waddle to the bathroom
to pee the rest into the toilet.
So don't bring a bottle of Gatorade,
the 32-ounce bottle of Gatorade, by the way, big one.
Uh-oh, I think he's getting bored.
Because now he's like, he's telling made-up stories
about peeing into bottles.
Uh-oh, I think we've crossed the line here.
Hey, let me tell you,
one time I like peed into a bottle.
I was passenger's peeing.
I'm out of gas again.
I'm gonna throw piss into the gas can.
No.
If you think I'm gonna actually answer the question
that's being put into chat right now,
you don't, you must not understand
that this is a family-friendly streamer.
Pee's dirty.
What if I peed?
You see, what I was trying to do there
is I was trying to make them jump off.
I didn't think it was that far.
That's not, no, the stream, that's not the stream.
The stream's still going.
What does it cost me to stop playing this fo-
No.
All right, I'm gonna go pee.
Let me pee and then contemplate my entire life.
I'll be back in like two minutes.
Can I just say something?
Let me say something.
Can we, I got something to say.
The fact that there's,
there are 3,200 people here right now, right?
And even if you don't like the game
and think this is, you know,
game's not great or, you know, whatever,
you're still here.
Thank you.
That's like, well, let's keep playing.
See, I'm like,
I'm like pulling your heartstrings here
to make it so you are like,
oh, yeah, yeah, this is good.
Thanks, man, it's a good game.
No, here's what's gonna happen.
All right, here's, no,
but I really do mean that though.
You know, people could just leave,
but you have,
you're like having your fun,
however you have it, right?
We're going to, what's going on?
Are you having fun?
I actually am.
I mean, it's not,
doesn't even matter what the game is.
It's just fun just to
dick around and have fun.
Doesn't have to be the game any good.
So we've been going for about four
and a half hours or so,
just about another like 10 minutes or so.
We are going to,
hear me out, okay?
Are you hearing me out?
Back to work.
What's back?
What is back to work?
See if it was possible.
See if what was possible.
What is this?
I'm laughing.
Back to work.
We had to listen to that.
I forgot to mute the mic.
Who is fucking hurting me?
Show us.
Yeah, it's just the BRB screen.
It's just this.
All right, guys, I'll see you.
Be right back.
Okay, see you soon.
Don't go anywhere.
Okay, bye.
That's so stupid.
Okay, so hear me out.
My fucking stomach hurts.
I'm going to listen.
Are you going to hear me out now?
I'm going to play this for like another...
Everyone's...
No, please.
Listen, don't hear me out.
Hey, hey, hold on.
Wait.
I'm going to play this for a little bit longer
and then I will end the stream
with a best out of three
Yahtzee Mario Tournament.
Okay.
Let me just do like another mission or two
and we'll...
I mean, like another 30 minutes or so.
We'll move on to Mario POG.
Mario Yacht.
You know what I'm saying.
That doesn't matter.
All right, where's my bike?
Where's my bike?
Back to work.
No, no, wait, wait.
I'm going back to work.
What's in here?
Yeah, this is a Mario Yahtzee waiting room
at this point.
That's so fucking stupid.
I'm never going to be able to repair this.
Check out a site called Talk to Transformer.
What is that?
I did have...
Yeah, I did have a bounty.
Hold on.
I got to get my bike out of there though.
Can I just call...
Okay, recover bike.
Recover bike to your location.
There it is.
Just everything about that is fucking hilarious to me
because everyone's like,
dude, why are you like playing this game?
Like, stop.
Like, do something else.
We can play Mario.
No, no, I'm not.
I need to play this.
I got to play this game.
I'm having a great time.
Back to work.
Ah, can you move out of the way?
That's what I said.
All right, what is like the mechanic?
All right, can't mechanics for fuel repair,
customize and upgrade your bike parts.
Is the game muted?
Oh shit, I'm sorry.
It is.
All right, let's put $284 to repair the bike.
226 free fuel.
Get out of here.
Your bike could use some work.
Check back.
I have like money.
See you later.
I like, I have like,
I like have like money.
I like have like,
like I have like like money.
Hey, I haven't seen Boozer around much lately.
Yeah, he's around.
I guess he's just been doing more for Copeland lately.
Didn't I turn him on?
You tell him I said get off his ass.
Turn in.
Am I messing something here?
Yeah, I'll let him know.
Sell one.
Did I already do it?
Am I insane?
Maybe next time.
Stop by soon.
That's just something.
I've got the courage to take.
All right, let's go.
I can get a weapon.
Sell all the bear traps.
I don't actually have any ammunition over here.
Let me see if I can get a gun.
Merchant, all right.
How you doing?
Hi.
Hey, what's up?
All right, weapons.
22 repeater.
I can buy the repeater.
I can buy a sidearm.
I can, I already have this.
22 repeater.
Very low stopping car requires a lot of headshots.
This is somewhat offset by ammo availability and quick fire rate.
Repeater.
Thousand bucks.
Sure.
That right there?
Good piece.
Thank you.
All right, supplies.
Ammo full.
Pistol ammo.
Let's get some fillet ammo up.
Upgrade.
Sidearm suppressor.
Primary suppressor.
Miasmo.
Good as new.
And okay, what about, I can't do grenades.
Locker.
Cool.
All right, all right, all right.
Let's do one more mission and then I want to see the trail of zombies.
And then we can move on.
Okay.
And then tomorrow, what do you guys want to do tomorrow?
What do you want to do tomorrow?
Let's make our friend hangout plan for tomorrow.
What do you guys want to do tomorrow?
Because here, I'll tell you, I'll tell you.
We've got Salmon Max Season 2 Episode 3 is going to be on probably Saturday or Sunday.
And then MS DOS Part 2 is going to be either Saturday or Sunday.
What is the best way to make it out of here?
I got to get the heck out of here.
Locate the drifter.
I guess just get me out of here.
This is really far away.
Like really far away.
Rage 2.
I feel like two AAA back-to-back games like this in a row probably aren't very good to do.
Can I get out of this time?
I don't know, we'll figure it out.
This is AAA.
This is as AAA as they come.
This is a Sony first party game.
Exclusive.
Why are they guys naked?
Why are these guys naked?
Were they swimming?
I guess they just, they're just naked.
All right, can I get out this way?
Or do I have to, I can't just go up the mountain.
I can't cross this.
The bike's going to get destroyed if I cross this.
No, I'm not going to ford the river.
That would be the last time you see this guy.
We need to just get out.
All right, out.
Finally.
Are we out?
We're making our way out.
I think.
No, we're not.
I need to get back to this road.
I guess we're just going to go over here.
Time for Mario.
No, it's not Mario time.
It's not Mario time.
It will be very soon.
I'm going to do one more.
Oh, why?
What didn't, wasn't this just taking me over here?
Wait, what is it doing to me now?
It's up ahead, wait, sorry.
What, what's this transformer thing?
Talk to the transformers?
This is Radio Free Oregon.
The truth shall set you free.
Oh, not in the mood.
Start the story prompt.
It fills the rest of the story up automatically.
Shit, that's right.
I got to finish burning out these nests.
Well, I don't have to finish anything.
I don't have to do anything.
You can just go.
All right, mission time.
Then we're moving on.
That sounds pretty cool.
All right, now we're going to go here.
Well, I mean, the fuel is at half already.
It's because I was driving around the circle
trying to leave through the one opening
that I could leave through.
The one four foot square
I was allowed to go through to leave the camp.
Uh, you seriously just did that to me.
What a sniper.
This is seriously driving me fucking crazy.
Should have gone back to work.
Get in there.
Come on.
Days gone by legendary game designer Clyde Barker.
Who made this game?
More bounties.
Use this.
Bob Barker.
Dude, that's seriously the worst thing ever.
I'm talking like even a tap, like a little touch.
If you touch this fucking thing, your map will come up.
This is guys that made Zoo Tycoon made this.
That's a kind of long way away from with Zoo Tycoon.
I got sniped again.
I know you missed it because the internet sucks.
But somebody jumped again and did the same thing.
I don't know if anybody saw it, but it happened.
Yes, pick up the gas.
That FPS drop and the lights come on.
Yeah, unfortunately, we're stuck with the
internet being bad very recently here.
We usually hit this string of like a couple hours in a row.
We dropped like 20,000, 30,000 frames.
No more.
My getting more phone calls.
More phone calls.
Hello.
Who is it?
Yes, it's happening again.
Problems are still here.
Thanks.
Oh, that's not good.
I can land that.
I know I can.
God damn engine.
I can land it.
I thought I could minimize damage if I land flat.
I guess not a terminal velocity.
I think I still can.
I just imagine like a fucking five-year-old
that just doesn't understand that I'm driving.
It just keeps flying off the cliff.
You should probably change to easy.
And you know, easy, I guess.
What's that?
I just want to drive your motorcycle.
I can't believe there's a you should change to easy mode.
Get off the car.
I can't make it.
I have to accept it.
Uh-oh.
My stomach hurts.
Hold on.
Where's my health?
Heal.
I'm gonna push you off the edge.
Come on, off the edge.
Oh, the one opportunity.
There it is.
Back.
Do it.
Go off the edge.
Why is there an invisible wall here?
Go off.
Oh, come on.
That's such bullshit.
That would have been so...
We could have stir...
Ah, that would have been so cool.
Can I get this?
And back up is the question.
Yes, I can.
Oh, yes, I can.
Bullshit.
I should be able to get down this.
I need to go that way.
Now it's like a fucking YouTuber joke.
I'm moving on.
I tried to back up.
I better thought I was gonna back it up.
Fucking wily coyote over here, yeah.
It was that simple.
I didn't know there was gonna be a place to go up here.
It was that easy.
It was so easy.
The bike is slow, but I think it's because it's not upgraded.
I'm pretty sure you can upgrade the bike and make it better and faster.
Better, stronger, faster, faster.
Snower, faster.
I'm sitting there looking at my internet.
I'm looking over on the right side because it went down again
and I took my eyes off the fucking screen to look over here.
I thought it was at zero.
It was at zero.
All right, we're gonna have to have another angry phone call to cox.
Great.
Every like three months I gotta call some internet company and be like,
hey, I'm a customer and I deserve to be treated right.
Oh my goodness.
We're almost there.
We'll get there this time.
Wait, what?
There's no fast travel.
Fast travel from map.
Summon Solary makes it way easier.
Nobody told me I could fast travel.
The game spent so long pausing the game to tell me I can repair my bike,
but it never told me I could fast travel.
Here we go.
This is it.
Then we can move on.
I found some stuff.
Found him.
He's dead.
Reloaded the bike.
Resistant coma.
Should be it.
That I hit it.
I really did.
Which way?
Back on track.
There he is.
Biker Bounty.
Some bounty targets will stand and fight.
Others will flee.
Chase your target out and capture them alive to complete the job.
Ramming into and shooting their bike are the best options.
Keep your target alive.
Silver helmet.
Red gas tank.
That's him.
Where are you going?
Oh shit.
Get away.
So you thought you'd ride into Copeland's camp.
I shoot the place up.
That about right.
Kill a few folks.
Take some shit.
Just ride out.
Take a shit.
How do I shoot from the bike?
I don't know.
But I'm going to wait.
Nobody taught me that.
I think he was waiting for me.
Bike combat.
While on the bike, tap L1 to acquire a target and tap R1 to fire your sidearm.
There it is.
The size of your target displays how accurate you are.
The smaller the rectangle, the better your accuracy.
I would say, ow, my bike.
Did he shoot himself?
Wait, who is talking now?
Why did he fly off like that?
I think he blew himself up.
How am I supposed to keep him alive?
Is he alive?
I don't think he's alive after that.
Oh, god.
Give drifters a bad name.
He has a little bit of dirt on his face.
What if you had shot me?
Like on his face.
He has like a smudge.
Stupid piece of shit.
Screw you.
Does it pick him up?
You want a Copeland Stonys?
You little bitch.
That's what you are.
I'm...
Okay, mission complete.
All right.
Unlocked.
Gear up for the ride.
Copeland's encampment custom accent.
Cope, it's done.
Got him.
Mark down these coordinates and send your man out here.
Is he alive?
Hey, hey, drifter.
Yeah, he's alive.
But I won't promise you how long he's going to stay that way.
Deacon out.
You tell him, drifter.
You tell him that's such a good...
That's what I'm doing.
Oh, knocked his helmet off.
What?
I talked to Al-Kai the other day, some of the other men.
You've been doing runs for the camp.
I just wanted to say thank you.
That's...
I'm hitting him right in the face.
St. John.
This is Copeland.
I haven't seen Boozer in a few days.
He used to do runs for me, is all.
I know you ride with him.
Tried to radio him.
Can't seem to reach him.
Well, you see him, you tell him to swing by and say hello to Cope.
Hi.
Oh, no, no, no.
Okay.
Well, he tried.
He's just made of stone.
Oh, no.
Stone men.
I don't know why I got up.
There's no bullets in the gun.
Stop smoking weed.
What do you mean stop smoking weed?
It's illegal in Las Vegas.
It's legal in Las Vegas.
What are you talking about?
I mean, like, what are you...
Somebody thought I was going to do it.
Thing that I do all the time.
One of the camps can use this.
I don't think so.
Somebody knows what I was going to do.
He smokes way too much weed.
That's why he's like so dumb, you know?
He smokes too much weed.
It makes him dumb.
Fast travel, but hold on.
Just needed to get some speed, that's all.
I just needed some speed to hit the stone men.
That's it.
Just need to go fast.
Fast travel?
Nah, we don't fast travel.
We fucking slow travel in these parts.
Just naturally dumb.
Hey, I'd rather be naturally dumb
than unnaturally dumb.
I don't need performance enhancing drugs to be dumb.
I'll check up on you.
Hang in there, buddy.
Soon as we get that arm patched up,
we'll ride to the north.
Just like you said.
Just work.
Perfect.
That's what falls off the back.
And it's a red explosive.
I still got some work to do on the bike
and we got to stock up on some gear.
But once you're passed up,
we're out of here, peeking out.
Okay, this is it.
Yeah, this camp is gonna be crawling.
Oh, yeah, yeah, going in nice slow, nice ammo.
Nice and quiet.
I'll give you quiet.
I gave up a heck in the middle of that.
I was gonna do really hard
and then I just got bored halfway through
and I was like, I can't.
I'm doing, I'm done.
That was thunderstruck.
It was the beginning.
It was, I was trying for it.
Let's make some noise.
Give me the first line.
Can somebody give me the first line to thunderstruck?
Okay.
I don't even hear it.
No, no, not thunder.
What does he say?
The first line.
Yeah, I know it's like...
Oh my God, what does he actually say though?
Oh my God, I'm still alive.
I gotta get on the bikes.
I'm gonna die.
Wait, rags.
They won't let me die.
Oh, finally we got a train.
We got our first train.
How many is it?
One, two, three, four, five.
Ready?
Get out of the way.
I'm trying to...
Why am I still alive?
Did it switch on easy mode?
I'm done.
Hey, just kidding.
Son of a...
What am I looking for here?
Uh, clearly an infestation logging camp of infestations.
You got it.
One, two, three...
That just didn't do anything.
Like I said, I ain't this old lady, Deacon Alba.
Can they get up here?
Pretty good spot.
Two.
Finally.
Jesus.
Bounty.
Where's Mario?
Fuck.
Hold on, just wait.
Just wait.
Just have a little bit of patience.
Have, you know, have five hours of patience.
You know, I have to have a little bit of patience.
Where are you at?
Where's the final two or three?
Dermot lied about Mario.
Dermot did not lie about Mario because Mario is going to come on the screen
very, very shortly.
In no time at all.
You don't even believe how quickly it's going to be on the screen.
I'm going to title the stream, Mario Yahtzee Rematch.
Zero does much clearer than nests.
I don't think I even have any molotovs to do that with.
Do I?
I think I threw them all being a dumbass.
I can only, how many can I craft?
Just a few?
Okay.
I need more stuff.
Hurry, hurry.
Monster.
I got double capped right there.
Be brave.
Pile of shit.
Be brave, assholes.
Why are you saying that?
There's another one probably over here.
Oh, there's got to be a nest in this shack.
Boys, just keep that out of sleep.
Don't pay no attention.
Did he say, oh, no, I missed?
Oh, no, I missed.
Come on, boys and girls.
Let's do this.
He's like way too pumped up.
I need more bolts.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I'm going to die because I'm going to die.