Uh, I have a question. How do you, um, how do you do, like, the pointing emoji on PC?
Like, if I wanted to do, what, can somebody just do it so I can just copy it?
What's the, like, pointing, pointing, like a finger pointing? Yes. Yeah, there you go.
Thank you. All right, I'll be back. I, I apparently didn't copy it. How come I didn't copy it?
It's, oh, that's, it's a, well, hold on. It's because of BTTV emote. That's a middle finger.
I need, like, a, the pointing finger that's not from BTTV because I need to put it in the,
I'm gonna put it in the title. Do Windows plus, I'm not gonna have to do that. Windows plus
for an emoji. How do I, does anybody, can somebody just write it so I can do it?
Oh, there you go. Thank you. There you go. There, there it is. That's what I want. Thank you.
All right. Appreciate it. This title is so bad. Actually, I like it. I actually like this title.
See, okay. Wait, why did you, you already put the, what, did you put the pointing thing in already?
What do you mean Neopets? What are you talking about? Why are you guys saying Neopets?
This has nothing to do with what I'm doing. All right. I'll be back. I'll be right back.
All right. I'm actually going BRB. Okay. I had to get my tweet ready. I forgot about it.
Are we all ready? Getting there. Very cool. I'm going to do my tweet. There it is. All right.
Let me just capture the game. That's important. Oh, I got to do my, hold on. This is important too.
Let me get this out of the way because I need to make sure my webcam is not going to freak out.
All right. So we're going to do co-op. Let's see. Talk to the people here. All right. I'm going to
say, all right. That's how you know it's about to start when I say, all right. But seriously though.
All right. The switch is not available right now. Turn that off. Turn this off. Okay. I'm ready to
play Gotham Knights. I had to pee. Okay. Your title still says Zelda. That's changing. Now I
got to plug this in. That is changing very shortly. No, it doesn't. You just gaslit me so bad,
didn't you? All righty. All righty. All righty. All righty. Jesus Christ, man. All right. I got
to think some more filler words than just, okay. All right. All right. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Yeah.
The last thing I was playing is Batgirl, but I was, I was hit up by a one son. He said, hey,
I think, I think we need to do some co-op stuff with the campaign. I was like, huh? Oh, let's call
him. See if he's available. Hey, what's up? Oh, I can't hear you. Hold on.
I don't know what he's saying. I can't hear him. Have you played this game at all?
Oh yeah. I've been playing for like three days. Have you done the tutorial? You might
have to do the tutorial. Yeah, I'll carry it. Just once you can do multiplayer, we'll uh,
just give me, give me a ping. This is like, this is a classic. Another,
yet another classic goof and gaff session where John carries me through. Hey dude,
are you ready to goof off? It's going to be so fun. I'm going to goof off. I'm goofy. I'm
goofy with it. Okay. I'm going to finish this video first. All right. Get, get, get out of here
and do the tutorial for God's sake. Okay. I got to put him through a different, yeah. Hold on.
Uh, hold on. All right. I'm muted there. Let me, uh, I could have changed this. We'll play as a
backer for a little bit and then he's ready. We'll go from there. We're going to goof off.
It's going to be goofy. All right. So my input is fine, but the output is the problem, the output,
because he's come through the wrong thing. I wonder if that's going to be better. We'll test it when
he gets back. And yeah, I know my webcam is freaking out. There's nothing I can do about it.
So, but I, it does, wait, it says, it says I'm playing as Robin. Oh, that's bad. I am, this is
not Robin. Wait a minute. We're not even on the same, we're not even on the same mission. They're
not even close. Is he going to be level one? Hey, can we ride the car together? But anyways,
we're about, we're about to start. At least I am. Welcome everybody. This is a sponsored stream.
Gotham Knights is currently out now. It's for the Xbox Series S, the Xbox X, the PC, the,
what did I just say? The PlayStation 5. It's got co-op. We're going to show that today. This is
Batgirl. You're going to see Robin. Open world, Batman like game. All right. So let me do this
mission. Dude, you got to really lean into it. Turn around. How would I turn around? You need
your overlay. You guys are just on point. You really are. Where am I going to go? Down here,
right? Yeah. Yeah. I got an image panel. There's a panel down below. If you click it, it will take
you to the opportunity for you to buy Gotham Knights. Why does it want me to turn around?
It's over here. Yeah. Thanks Warner Brothers for sponsoring this segment of today's stream.
I'm going to switch to Robin. I promise. Batgirl, I'm leaving. What? What did that person say?
All right. Did I actually have to go the other way? Shut up. What are they talking about? All
right. Hold on. I need to go. Who is he talking to? Somebody did something that exploded. Um,
excuse me. What's with that fucking in menu BM bullshit? All right. I'm out of here. Batgirl,
I'm leaving because I'm not playing as Robin. What is going on here? Is that her? What was it?
What? No, I'm locked into the mission. I'm already locked into the mission. Don't throw stuff into
cars. Idiot. Did I go on that bridge this way and I'm coming back on this bridge that way?
I'm doing it my way. Okay. So there he is. Let's see what's going on here. Colonel Kane. Who's that?
Sergeant Pennyworth. Why are you wearing? Why is he wearing a Catwoman suit? I'm not. I had to
push our meeting so late. Work never seems to stop in this city. Oh, I can certainly relate.
The paperwork hasn't let up since Bruce's passing. I still can't believe it. Burying Bruce was the
hardest thing I've ever done. Yeah. Do you remember what I mean? I'm just Robin after Tommy. I was
just close to it. So I want to get it done. You said life matters when death matters. We take the
living for granted until they're gone. What settings am I on? What the Wayne Foundation will
do without Bruce? I'm on so I'm gonna have a 3090 and I have a 1440p resolution. Master Grayson. 60
fps frame rate I think. Yeah. Dick had his first investor call the other day. I'm surprised. I do
get a little bit of stuttering. I find you geezers escape from the old folks. Don't you know what's
going on? Every day I find new reasons to be proud. Empty your pockets or empty the gun.
We're gonna get like an Alfred moment here where he's like, you know what? Never mind. Oh, um,
quite the about face. That punk didn't know who he was messing with. Wow. Holy shit. Have a drink.
Catch up. Don't have to twist my arm. Let's not be long though. Isn't that girl supposed to be in
this cut scene? Oh, I was observing the cut scene from up. I actually think Batgirl might be.
Well, I can't say that until I play Robin. Let's change to Robin.
Robin time. Do you have concealer on? No, I don't have concealer on. It's a face smoothing filter
that I have turned on. Robin, you guys ready? I'm the only person on Twitch playing this game
with Robin, I think. Here we go. The title is now accurate. Stealth specialist, tactical genius,
bow staff prodigy. All right. What does Robin got for moves? We're gonna do the gears first.
All right. I got my suit. I actually cool. Whoa. This is Robin's suit in and beyond. I mean,
this thing, I kind of want to, I kind of want to be in this because I, when I look at this picture,
it's like, okay, that's, that's Robin. I guess that's so I love it. Ooh, he's got a slingshot.
Are you shitting me? All right. I, I'm very curious now. I'm the only person on Twitch
playing with Robin. Slugger, shadow or tinkering. Robin produces no sound while running and moves
faster. Okay. Uh, perfectly timed dodge. That's kind of good. 20% more damage when attacking from
behind. 20% more crit damage. Robin's decoy inflicts a large amount of, is it decoy? What's
this thing? Should I be stealth? Stealth, Steven? Don't do the ghost pepper challenge. Uh, I think
I'm going for slugger. I like doing damage. You know what I mean? 10% crit chance. Yeah.
Decoy. Yeah. I'm just going full slugger. All right. Let's check out his move set.
Jerma chat is unhinged. Uh, they'll be all right. They'll settle down. They'll be all right. They
settle after a little while. I'm actually kind of looking forward to, uh, getting in a game with
Hassan and him kind of his reaction to this character. He's going to be like, who are you
playing as? I'm going to be like, oh, of course that's bald boy. You know, Hassan, you don't know
who fucking bald boy is. Do you even watch the TV shows or movies? Ooh, what is this? Like little
throws rocks. All right. Let's give it a try. I need to make the fast travel thing. Don't I?
Honestly, I feel like this is, I feel like I'm traversing more ground than I do with the bike.
You can just fly around the city like this. Okay. So it's over here.
So this is the powers club. This is the culmination of the last thing we did last night.
Let's go. Let's kick some ass. Wait, I have a stealth specialist, aren't I? I'm inside. Good.
Be careful and let us know what you find spotted a patrol. Level seven. Oh, I might be too love with
this. Nobody can see. Oh God. Maybe you can. You look over at us in this. Holy shit. That'd be
terrifying. You know what? Why don't, why doesn't everybody just wear a superhero costume? If I
lived in this universe, I feel like less people would fuck with you. If I lived in any of these
superhero universes and I didn't have powers, I would put a costume on and just walk around and
shit. Did I go to the grocery store? I feel like people would be like, Oh, you're not like a regular
guy. You might, you're like fucking burp man or something. Right. Who knows? Like I feel like that
you'd, I feel like I'd be less inclined to like, Oh, I'm going to sneak up behind this guy and
stealth kill him. If this guy was in like a bright green spandex suit with like a pair of goggles on,
I'd be like, Oh fuck, I got to be careful. Right. Why don't they just wear costumes?
Okay. Let's scan the area. Oh, blood. AR shows a clear trail of blood. Wonder if there's anything
else to see. There's something hidden under the floor. The hatch is wired to a network.
There must be some way to activate it through the lamp. Okay. This way, but the light switch on the
lamp. Yeah. You could just make up what your powers were. Right. Okay. Somebody was like,
who the heck are you, man? I've never seen you around here. You're the superhero. I'd be like,
that's right. By the way, if I look at you and I decide you'll instantly die, I feel like people
would be like, Holy fuck me and get away from me. I'm instant die Reno. Right. No one would fuck with
you. And I would hire actors to like come and come after me and I would look at them and they would
just drop down. So people wouldn't be able to prove I couldn't do it. They said we'd be working
at a club. This isn't exactly what I had. Remain undetected. Just saying. I was hoping for something
a little more clubby and a little less creepy. Shut up. It's easy money. We barely have to see
the snobs anyway. Yeah. What the hell is that about? Who cares? The less we know, the better.
Looks like shit. I haven't been detected yet. I haven't been detected yet. Get out. Okay. I'm good.
This one right here. You're aiming at a wall, dude. Don't have a fuck with bug boy. Robin school's
character in the fucking game. I'm the only one playing him. No, Robin's my character. Oh shit.
Right in the head. Hey, dude. Oh, right in the eye. Is this dangerous or am I just annoying?
I think everyone right now is not doing anything because they're like, holy shit. Wait a minute.
This might, I don't think this is like a grown up. This is like a kid in this awesome outfit.
Ooh, that's cool. Bo staff. Okay. This is not just a Bo staff. This is an extendable Bo staff.
It's a telescopic telescopic Bo staff. Find a way. Okay. Flip the switch. Let's go. All right.
Well, it's right there. Okay. Hidden in plain sight. Press the button. Oh, I can press it.
Can I get in there? How do I get down there? Oh, there it is. Cool. I'm just, I just want
all of a sudden to turn the corner and you just hear. Ranger. Oh Robin, you think you're such a
smarty. Well, I don't think you're going to be so smart after you deal with me. Okay. Follow the
wires now. Where do they go now? Oh shit. I was too busy like talking. I missed it. I missed it. I
was talking. I'm an idiot. Find a way to follow the activated wires. I mean, was it part of the
bust? Where was it? It's not that thing down there, right? Connected to electric. No. Back of the
bust. I just was in my own world. Where are they going? Oh, come on. All right. Follow the wire.
The wire goes here and then it stops though. I mean, the activated wire is going down there.
Should I try to go down? No. Uh, is he for real? Oh, I thought, okay. I'm sorry. That's my bad. I
thought I had to like follow it. It's not like, oh, I thought it was, you know what I mean? Whatever.
Nice brain. Yeah. What, what did you get in science? Probably a C. I got a D. So I don't care.
You got a B. What's this weird labyrinth?
What's down here? Okay. All the blood trail. Where am I? The blood stops at the wall.
Weird. That's weird. Well, obvious way through here. There has to be more to this. Yep. Right
there. Nope. That's a light spotlight. All right. Turn it on. Okay. That did something.
Oh shit. God damn it. The shadow puzzle. Uh, what am I trying to make? Probably the fountain,
right? Am I trying to make the thing that's on the wall? Is that an eagle? That looks correct.
So now I got to do the body, which is down here. One more. That should be it. All right. That's not
it. That's not it. Almost. Was it this wing here? I feel like this could be accurate any way this
could be, right? Depends. It's like that different angle. Why did they not do that before? Let's get
the shit out of me. Oh, it's the owls. You are. Yep. What was that? Holy shit. You do like a,
you do a decoy. That's cool. That's what I'm saying. If you're the penguin and you talk,
you're tell, your penguin tells the truth. If you say you're the penguin, you are being serious.
By the way, for people that can do this in real life, how, how do you do that? It doesn't even
make any fucking sense that a human being can do that. People can do this shit. People can do that.
All right. Look at the blood trail. I can because I'm not a weak ass motherfucker.
Let's see how deep this goes. All right. Guess I just follow the blood then. Not gross at all.
So many things we could have done. His death has cleared the way for our new acquisition.
Good. However, do try to be careful where you're looking.
We've already brought the senators. I've been assured your bill will pass in the next month.
What is going on with that dog? I'm sorry. Turn it up. I can't move the camera. I want to get
a close up of the dog's face. I can't zoom in. No, you can't. Hold on. Can I just, what about if
I didn't crop everybody out in a frame? Okay. That's pretty good. I like that. I should let
a film grain do it. I can't change the lighting. That's all I can do. Okay. I got it. I guess I
have no other choice but to go through them. No one gets through. The ceremony can't be delayed.
You don't need to tell me that twice. This is our chance to impress the voice.
He'll be intruders first. Then you can think about the rewards. Oops.
Wrong fucking way. Whatever. I guess I technically could run away and then hide.
Resilient takedowns. It counts. That was fucking awful. Oh my God. What a horrible way to go.
I don't even feel like there should be something like the mask sound effects whenever you move
around like this. Like, I need one more silent takedown. Don't ever do that again. I mean,
I saw a lot of plus twos on that one. I don't know. Should I do it again? See ya.
Oh, watch this. We're gonna take this guy out like this. I'm gonna meat grind this motherfucker.
I missed this backswing with it. That's good. Oh, right in the head. Really? There's more?
Shit. So bad. Oh, I like that move. It bent the staff. I hit them so hard in the head.
I bent the staff around that person's head. This is a lot of blood. More than most people can spare.
He's easy, Robin. Jeez, Robin. I mean, I know you took out like 10 people, but
pull back a little here. Oh, I hear someone. He's still alive. Who's this?
Come on. Look out. We're hit me. I'm in the enemy's back. It won't happen again.
Death to the traitor. And death to also that guy.
The guy, the metal bald guy too, I guess. The voice of the court comes. He will dictate the
punishment. I don't know who that is, but death to you. Who is this?
The court cannot forgive your failure. You will atone with blood. Owl man?
And you, Vernon, do not belong here. The last time an intruder set foot here was more than a
century ago. The punishment for this insult remains the same.
You didn't save that guy. I missed the QTE. No, I didn't. Oh my God. It was like a fucking
death room. I was trying to jump through it. It's not the time to like show off.
Oh my God. All right. Stop it. Look at all these bones. How do you, I'm trying to slide.
Oh, it's just walk through it. Oh my dude. Hey, what that wouldn't be.
I'm made out of fucking solid steel. It would scrape my chest.
Shit. No, this is hard. This is actually fucking hard. Oh my goodness. Jesus. Okay.
I was just going to say what, what is this doing down here? Oh dude. What? Oh my God, man.
Get away from me. Holy shit. That was impossible. I accidentally just did that. Sticking that
landing makes the whole thing, you know, everything's good. Everyone's dead.
Game's loud. I turned it on. That should be better. It's like a thousand people down here.
That was insane. Hey, Jerma, are you there? Oh my God. I thought that was in the game.
I thought that was in the game. Oh my God. That scared the shit out of me. Jerma. It's me.
Snake. Solid snake. I have a question. What's up? I finished the first mission,
but it's still not unlocking multiplayer. How do I unlock multiplayer?
Hmm. So I, my multiplayer is unlocked. Let me see. I wonder if I can just pull you in
because did anybody know what, what mission you have to do? Cause I didn't pay attention
to that yesterday the day before. Which one did you pick by the way? Cause I'm,
I'm, I'm double gatted up. What, what are you playing as a red hood? Yeah, I got the gat.
Okay. That's fine. I'm playing as the much superior Robin. Uh, no shot. You picked Robin.
You need to do mission 1.2. Let me see if somebody got the answer here. Mission 1.2,
where you investigate Langstrom's corpse. That's the mission you have to complete.
I did that already. I just investigated that. Did you complete it? Or wait, no. Uh, I don't think
I did. Wait, maybe I didn't do it. Oh, people are saying, oh, you didn't do it. Okay. Um, okay. F1
Batman's last case, the Langstrom drive, right? The Belfry is being brought back online until
then patrol the streets of Gotham and fight criminals. That sounds like it is. It should
be 1.2. You have to, uh, did you do the part where you investigate the corpse? There's like a,
you look at the corpse and it's like a little detective mini game. I don't think I did that.
Yeah. Um, no, I have not seen a corpse yet. I'm just investigating criminals. I'm investigating
crimes right now or not crimes. I'm just waiting for crimes to happen so I can deliver some swift
vigilante justice in the form of red hood with my guns. Yeah. The game is that you have to,
you do crime, you solve crimes and stuff in the kind of in between
of the main mission. I don't do crime. I solve a long story. Can I be the one that says that's
kind of stuff? Cause I'm Robin. I'll tell you more when I get back. Wait, okay. Wait, what's,
what are the vibes? What would my vibes be as I'm solving the way, did you say you were solving
crimes? Or did you say, what did you say? Wait, hold on. I'm hearing machine gun fire.
Oh no, I don't do crime. No. Yeah. I'm supposed to be like the smart one that can
finagle engineering and stuff and get us out of sticky situations we might get ourselves into.
Oh my God. I'm so good at shooting. It's not even funny. Yeah. You just, you're the muscle.
As long as you're the muscle and on the brains, we'll be fine. As I almost get by a train.
What did you say, Jeremiah? I couldn't hear you. I'm sorry. Oh, I just said I'll be the brains.
You'd be the muscle. Okay, good. I have no brain. So that works perfectly for me. I think I just
stopped the crime. It should be the other way around. How? No, definitely not. Well,
actually I've seen old photos of you and you are a thought. So. Okay. I question for you.
What's up? If you were to pick a Batman rogues gallery villain that you would identify with it,
like, oh, that's me. Who would it be? I have no idea. I mean, I don't know. I don't have a good,
I don't have a good enough. Oh my God. This is wonderful. You think you're like the Joker or?
No, that's too cliche. I feel like everyone always picks that.
Okay. What about the Redler? I like Bane, not Riddler. I think Bane is more my speed. He was
a bit of a, he was a bit of a lefty too. Okay. All right. That's a good answer. He was just
not ideologically pure, but he was close to being a lefty. Like he had the motivation.
Let's see if master Bruce left us anymore. Okay. Like that's um,
Margie. I can respect that. Okay. What would you be the Riddler?
Um, I would be the person that is selling all the equipment. I would want to, I would want
to be the one that was like just part of the company, but nothing concrete. I can't authenticate
any of these. Someone said German would be the mad hatter. I'm in the same universe. I love the
sound. You are talking over my cut scene. What would have made a wonderful addition to the library?
Am I loud? I'm just, I'm trying to see what's happening. I am trying to literally unlock the
mission, but it's not unlocking it. I think I need to solve more crime. There were a lot of bodies.
Yeah. You should have a thing like a case file thing and it'll tell you like, oh, there's this
you can do. There's this you can do. Go solve some stuff in Gotham. Yeah. No, that's what I did,
but it was like, wait, hold on. Now it's loud. Okay. I did that, but then it was like,
I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to lower the audio of the game first because
games these days are so loud. I feel like an old man saying that young whippersnapper.
All right. Out of the four here, who do you think is the coolest? Nightwing, Red Hood,
Robin or Batgirl? No, Red Hood. 100. Ah, Nightwing, Nightwing. Good answer. I wasn't
going to leave the call if you said, uh, Red Hood. Why? What's up with this anti-Red Hood
sentiment that I'm hearing from so many people? Nightwing is like my favorite.
I mean, Nightwing is pretty good. Nightwing is the original. I wonder if I can just like
suck you into my game. It might be possible. All right. Let me read my emails. Oh, right
direction. Belfry. Did you get it? No, I think this is the crime I need to solve though.
I'm sending you the coordinates now. Did I get any new stuff? Let me see. Nice.
Oh, I like that one. That looks cool. By the way, as you play, make sure you check on your gear too.
Uh, this, you got suits, you unlock suits, you unlock weapons. Oh yeah. I want to change out of
the sleeveless hoodie as quickly as possible. I have a point I can put in. Oh, I have to go to
the GCPD morgue now. There it is. That's the one I can't steal cars though, which is no,
you do have access to the bicycle though. I really do wonder what this game is going to be like in
co-op. Are we going to, you haven't done it yet. So you played the game already. You did one.
Yeah. I played the last couple of days. Okay. Okay. Because I think we can be anywhere. I,
um, this might be incorrect. I'm curious, but I don't think it's like, oh, you have to be within
like 10 feet of each other or something. I wonder maybe you do. Is there a camera? Can you turn on
camera tracking while you're, uh, while you're driving or is that just a product of me playing
keyboard? Are you playing keyboard and mouse or are you playing controller? Uh, I would say
keyboard and mouse would be an, a not ideal way to play this game. Are you on keyboard mouse?
I am. Were you playing multiverses on keyboard and mouse too? No, no, no, you weren't. I was
just bad at multiverses. I was just bad at it. Uh, where's my car? Wait, what? Everyone's asking
you to hit the Luddie. Have you hit the Luddie yet? I have not. Have you? Yeah. Oh yeah. I nailed
it. I'll hit it after this. Wait, what? Weird. What? So I'm, I'm going to, I'm not going to start
a new story mission. Wait, I'm just, I'm almost done. I'm almost done. Yeah. I'm just going to do
some, uh, let's do some crime investigation. I got here. I'm a GCPD. There you go. All right.
So you're probably like 10 minutes away. 15 minutes. Maybe I'll solve a couple of, uh,
city crimes while I wait for you. All right. Are there any, there's one here. What's this?
Good thing I don't need to walk in from the front door.
One of the, wonder why the cops would be on alert. Oh yeah. You, if you, if you cause like,
like chaos and mayhem, like they're like, they get annoyed with you, but they don't,
they don't like vigilante justice. No, you only, it's a, it's a dish best served cold.
Can you do it a little deeper? It's a dish best served cold. Can you go even just a little bit
more? It's a dish best served cold. Very good, but less cookie monster, more like scary.
It's a dish best served cold. That was close. That's as far as it goes, man.
Why am I walking? I have a car. Why am I walking to this? Oh, you upgraded from the, from the,
Oh, well, a bicycle from the bicycle. Okay. Oh wait, upstairs door. There you go. Oh,
no, it doesn't work. German. How do I get into the GCPD? Um, unfortunately that, that was three
days ago. So it's gone from my memory and nothing goes into long-term memory. I actually, I really
have no idea. I don't remember what I had for breakfast yesterday. You know what I mean?
It's that literal. All right, give me the car or the motorcycle. Oh no, I went the wrong way.
I think he's just literally saying, go through the front door. You know who I am?
One of my chats said, ask him for money. He won't remember. They really got it out for you.
I would remember that. You say you don't remember what you have for breakfast. I like that he said,
what am I going to do? Go through the front door. And I went into the back door. I would definitely
put a sticky note on like, oh, hey, like Hassan owes me 50 grand or whatever. Right?
I wouldn't sticky note what I had for breakfast yesterday. Oh, German. I'm, I'm beating cops
pretty aggressively and violently. I don't know what's going on.
Oh, the game, the game gets a little nuts. I don't know if I'm supposed to be doing that,
but I'm kind of cops. I want to do the, uh, I want to do the like prison mission with you with like
the, you guys chat, you guys know with the song. I w I kind of want to be pulled into your game.
It's pretty clear how to go to places and yet I'm still failing.
I already failed the mission. No, no, no, no, not at all. I just went the wrong way.
I just went the wrong way. It's okay. That's not a bad, that's not a bad guy.
Okay. I was checking tactically, giving an ocular pat down to the other side of the car.
Oh, wait, the bomb's going to detonate in a minute. What? Oh, oh, this is bad. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
A citizen's injured here. Medics are inbound to your location. Oh no. That was bad.
I really could have used some, uh, muscle there. I know. Well, luckily you and everyone else who
gets this game by clicking on either of our panels could potentially play cooperative and get all the
help that they need. Pretty good. Pretty good. Right? Dude, I'm, I'm pretty cracked with it.
Did you, uh, I saw if you happen to tell anybody what platforms this could be on,
couldn't be on, you know, uh, I did not. They're on, uh, PlayStation five, Xbox series S X and
the PC. Got it. This has been an injury. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Well, there's another one over
here. So they didn't stop doing that. Oh, wait, I am in prison. Did you say prison break or no,
it's the bullpen. Uh, there's a mission after and like another 30, 40 minutes from where you are.
That's just, um, it's a little, it's a little wild. Okay. Let me try to do this again and not
mess this whole thing up. This seems kind of hard. No, you don't. Cause you're the downed officer.
I'll meet myself.
Is he seeing me? I don't think, I think he thinks of a statue.
That's awesome. Why does he got Fortnite dancing? That's a literal Fortnite dance.
He's hanging with a pretty rough. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
All right. This mission is kind of hard. Oh shit.
Are the freaks gentrifying?
Robin trouble. I'm not failing this the second time.
Thank you. There we go.
Have you heard any reports of the freaks actively recruiting suburban types like
soccer moms or guys really into their public bites?
I wish. So wait, why are they?
So some of these people are, they're not, I don't know.
All right, cool. So that I prevented a crime there. Good. Oh shit. I am not muted. I'm just
talking through Hassan's stream right now. I think. Oh my God. I'm sorry. Let me fix that.
I'm just like streaming at Hassan's stream. Get me out of here. So something going on right here.
It's okay. Jeremiah, you're making the stream, but the wrong call,
you're the wrong discord bit. I'm not going to do the wrong discord routine.
It's not possible. And this is more than two or three people in a call together.
It just being me and Hassan on a call, my indicator is just going to light up.
Oh shit. What's going on? What are they chasing? What are they doing? Where are they going? I'm
very, I need to see, I need to investigate this. Okay. Ooh, new move. Oh, that was good.
I feel like a bowstaff would be fun to just like, that would be a good weapon. Right.
So what's going on here? What's the actual crime? What? Somebody's trimming hedges
where they shouldn't be. What is that song? Okay. So I, did I do it?
I think it was those two people that I was chasing. I think that's what it was.
Well, I'll take whatever that is. How do I get that? There it is. Cool. All right. There's a,
there's an Omega crime going on over here. I'll try to do the, the red Omega crime.
It's actually going to, you know, it's going to be probably kind of funny watching the song,
like try to do this because he's, he's just trying to get to the co-op part, right?
Doesn't have the kind of experience that we have here. So what is the issue? What's happening?
What does it say on the map? You see PD report. Uh, okay. So we'll have to go report to
stolen goods being moved. Robin is silent. All right. So I got to scan the, what is all that?
Okay. Camera control panel. All right. Disable those cameras. This is a Batgirl mission.
Oh, come on. He's bugging out. Oh, wait. Where's it? Where's the organ? Where's the organ?
Yes. Get out of the way. All right. What do I deliver this to? Right there. All right. Turn
around. Where's the song? Uh, he's currently, uh, getting to the point where he can play the
multiplayer. What are you doing over here? Wait, what? This is bad. I got to turn it in to here.
I have 17 seconds. Make it count. Robin, don't do a flourish. Oh my God.
Had to do the flourish. You got an expiring organ in your pocket and you got to do the,
the spin jump swing. Oh, I may have gotten stuck under the, the, uh, sign. How did I do this to
myself? I must've gotten into the perfect. Okay. I can just fast travel. Well, I hook what I'm
playing is Robin. Yeah. Gotham Knights. There was more to that sense. Oh, we have a cut scene.
This is a Robin cut scene. Let's check it out. I was surprised. There's no way the penguin does
not double cross. Like, I mean, zero percent chance. All right. Let's see what this, uh,
cut scene is. Playing with a ghost, Alfred. You might say that I'm finishing my last game with
Bruce. This is kind of sad. I couldn't save our board from the manor, but I do have our notes.
We tracked each move. All right. I think I'm in, I'm in, uh, Belfry tutorial ending patrol.
I think night one crime stop zero citizens rescue too. I feel like that's more important. You know
what I mean? What good is stopping crime if you're not saving citizens? Oh, there's another mini,
another cut scene. Yeah. Uh, watch that cut scene and we'll, we'll, okay. Are you winning playing
as Bruce? I can't see how he loses. Bruce is dead. Maybe he wins your game, but without him,
I'm not so sure about that. Not so sure he's dead. Not so sure we've lost. Bruce played an important
role, but he never saw himself as the only piece in play. I mean, take a little bit of credit,
Robin. Like you, you are, you are just as good. You are a good superhero and you got your own
shit going on. And let's, you know, let's watch another cut scene because this is another one
here. This is bike one. That green slime hurt Jason. When I fell from heaven, when you came
back to life, he just screwed that in with his bare hands. He didn't even need a wrench. It changed
me. Hey, Lazarus isn't going to bring Bruce back to who's to say he doesn't want us to try.
Oh, he wants to break. Okay. I see what's happening here. Okay. Bruce isn't this bike. You
can't just change everything out and expect things to work like they did.
Then what am I supposed to do? Try grieving. What? He's locked. I want that one. I want this one.
I want this one bad. I want this one. I want this one bad. I want this one real bad. I want this one.
How do I buy these? I want this one. Oh my God. I want this one so bad. They're all locked. All
right. Do I? What's next? What's the main story mission that I have? I have this. The Penguin.
Penguin is available. This Court of Owls thing is available. Dr. Jada Tompkins is available.
I wonder how close the sound is. I want to start something major. Hey, what's your,
what do you got for an ETA? You think you're pretty close? Yeah. I'm talking, I'm having a
moment with Alfred right now. Okay. I'll shut up. He's crying about Bruce dying. Did you know Bruce
Wayne is Batman? I mean, I heard that. Did I spoil? Did I spoil everything? I'm sorry.
I don't know. Do you mean like the billionaire of Bruce Wayne? What? Yeah. Billionaire Bruce
Wayne is Batman. Oh, okay. Oh no. Chat's saying major spoilers, dude. Damn it. I thought,
it's time to craft. Okay. I need to complete, prepare for patrol and complete interrogation
training. And I think after that, I suspect I will be able to, I guess like I have to complete
interrogation training. And then after that, maybe. I think that's it. I think that's the one.
Dude, I'm making a legendary slingshot. I'm trying to upgrade my guns, man. Yeah. You get a crap.
You can go to the workbench when you have a chance. You might have something you can make.
Yeah. It's just gun level one though. Oh, you can switch right here.
I think it's time to switch to Nightwing. Pick somebody else. Pick a different character.
Okay. Yeah. Nightwing's like dumb. That's not even like a fun. It's like, I play as Nightwing
sometimes, but like, usually I'm the Nightwing guy. I'm like the Nightwing streamer. Oh, you're
the Nightwing guy. Okay. I'll just keep, I'll stay with Red Hood. It's fine. No, you don't,
you don't have to. No, no, no. It's cool, man. No, you don't do, you don't have to. It's my
first time playing the game. I guess. No, I don't know. Okay. No. Yeah. All right. Yeah. If you
insist, I'll just stay with the Jarhead haircut. It's fine. Okay. This is advanced training,
ability training and basic training. It says learn interrogation training, but I don't know where
that would be. Is that in advanced? Okay. And I had, okay, let me show you. So if you go over
to the training dummy, go to the training dummy. I found it. There it is. It takes about two minutes
and be ready because it's cool. Here it comes. You're going to go. Holy shit. Physical and mental
preservation go hand in hand. Oh, Batman's alive. As a young child, I didn't want to say it. They
were behind his parents. Okay. It must not be Bruce Wayne then because Bruce Wayne is dead.
Spoilers. I think this on is very close. I think I have enough time to do one more small crime.
I mean, prevent one more small crime. It's better. Wait, that's it. I just said,
tell me what I want to know. And he said, cat don't got this tongue. I'll tell you what you
want to know. Then we'll be free to fly to and from this neighborhood as much as we want.
That's a surveillance drone. Scan each one in the sector and send me the data.
Then we'll be free to fly to and from this neighborhood as much as we want.
Once I reprogram them to look the other way. Yes. In the drone. Where's this drone that he's
talking about? Oh my God. Batman said I've come so far. Okay. So when I exit, oh no,
now I can play multiplayer. Let's go. Hold on. Let's switch over to multiplayer. Oh,
is this quick math? Main story, heroic assault, main story, right? I would assume. Yeah.
I think that's a waiting to join. Are you just joining me? I don't know. Are you? Did you host
me? No. It said joining host. Did you just join a random game? I don't know. Who, man? Wait, what?
I've joined a random person. Random person's game. I don't know how that happened. Oh,
because I think you did quick play. Did I? I think. Hold on. Let me, let me investigate this.
Let me do some investigation here. Oh, I should go to social, game invites, friends. There it is.
Theme friends. There it is. And then you. Yes, can. Wait, did I actually accept your friend
request? I thought I did. Did you not? Awkward. But you didn't accept my friend request. I just,
I just accepted it. Yeah, because you were forced to on stream. Oh, that's awkward, man. That's
kind of whatever. I guess I'll just join you right now. I might as well. Sorry about that.
Oh, there you are. Oh, hold on. Hold up. Did it not work? Oh, I'm here. There you are.
Gas can has joined the chat. OK, I got to come find you. Yeah, you are really far away.
Wait, really? We can look, look at, look at how far away we can be. I don't think it's going to
ever. No, I'm Robin. Oh, OK, that is way drippier. You look like Legend of Zelda, Robin. I look cool.
You hold on. The other Robin looked so, you know, about the other character in the game.
This is like there's a bunch of characters here. I'll show you one.
Um, is, uh, what's his name? Watch out. Who's that? What's his name? Um,
bald boy. Right. I forgot. Wait, what? What is this? It's bald boy. It's another Batman.
How did you change your character so swiftly? You would, you know, you don't know bald boy is.
No, you wait. You, you know who Batman is, but you don't know who bald boy is.
Oh, who's bald? That's all right. You're trolling. Does the train ever come?
Like, I feel like we'd get cooked if a train just decided to.
Wait, where are you going? All right. We don't. Whose mission are we on? Are we on mine or yours?
No, it would be yours, I think. All right. So let's go. Let's let me mark something.
Let's do. Wait, I can change my suits, uh, dial in in many. No, I can't. I think I'm about to spoil
like the first third of the game for you, by the way. It's OK. Because we're about to go talk to
a certain character. I'm down to do the mission with you. All right, let's go. Let's do we both
have like, it seems like you need the help. Oh, or wait, do I get on your back? I don't know.
Let's find out. It won't let me. Do you have to have your own? Oh, you have your own bike.
I wish I could just like, yeah, I wish I could mount your bike with you.
All right, let's go. You got to ride a wheelie the whole time. That's part of it.
OK, we're like the. Whoa. This is the reason why Eric Adams said no more motorbikes in New York
City, by the way, because of this kind of behavior that we're engaging in.
You're doing pretty good. The little political joke, a little political.
Was that a political joke? Yeah. One of the.
I don't know where you're going. Oh, excuse me.
You just used me as a jump. That was pretty cool. I did that on purpose.
Actually, that was sick. All right. Let's get on.
You might have thought that I was actually scared, but really, I was just doing it as a joke.
I love how you're in character. Oh, yeah. Wait, hold on, hold on.
I think I'm going to turn you up. Let me I'm going to go to gear.
I'm going to go to gear. Oh, my God, I can change my suit.
You got a better suit. Beyond.
We both look like henchmen of.
What is the red hood beyond suit look like?
Pretty cool. I think I've seen it.
All right, so we're going to go over here, so hop off the bikes.
We're going up there and we're going to visit a particular character.
I don't know what I did. Where are you?
We got to go in the ceiling. Oh, God.
What? I can't get to you. I don't know why.
No, you're right here. You're right here.
I know, but won't let me jump up there for some reason.
So yeah, jump right down here. There you are.
All right. Just duck and roll, baby.
Oh, he's just right here. Get him.
Oh, what? Dude, spoilers.
Watch out. He's got grenades and shit. Watch out.
Wait, really? No.
Are you seeing this cut scene?
No, I'm just hearing him talk to you.
Can you walk behind me? Like, get behind me.
What do you want? Straight to the point.
Like, will you just appear in the cut scene?
So how's about a little part? I'm behind you.
I'm too young to run about. No, you're not there.
And I don't have a fake ID either.
You misunderstand me, friend. As the owner of a respected establishment,
I have an interest in keeping the streets safe.
You could help. What's your angle?
Are you hoping I'll take out some of your competitors?
Speaking of angles, you should probably angle the umbrella up.
I'm not in the crime business anymore. So you don't get rained on.
So if I can't cross any unusual gear, I'd be obliged to turn it over.
Upstanding citizen that I am.
You're lucky they're criminals, or I wouldn't even consider it.
Well, that's the spirit. You're working with crimers?
Sometimes you have to work with information.
That's my response to you. You see that?
What about my response? Wait, do you see my emotes?
Wait, I don't... What are you, rock, paper, scissoring?
I don't get it.
Yeah. All right. Let's rock, paper, scissors.
So if you select the emotes and then do...
Good job. Good job.
Wait, I can't do another emote?
I don't think I have rock, paper, scissors.
No. All right. So now we have to go from here.
And... Okay.
They're kind of rude of Mr. Penguin not to even acknowledge my existence,
but that's okay, I guess.
Oh, his name is Mr. Penguin.
That actually makes him way less intimidating to me.
Oh, Mr. Penguin. Mr. Penguin to me is like an actual penguin
that's like the animal with the stripe on his stomach and stuff.
Mr. Penguin. That's not the penguin. Penguin is scary.
Wait, this guy's not the penguin?
No, he is. But like, you called him Mr. Penguin.
Yeah. Mr. Penguin was my father's name.
I'm just the regular old penguin.
All right. Where are we going?
We're going to go this way. We're going to do the owl stuff.
I'm not going to lie. This is giving Spider-Man a little bit.
With our suits. I don't know if I'm allowed to say that.
That's a different franchise entirely.
This is Gotham Knights. This is the DC Universe's Gotham Knights
starring Batman, Robin, Batgirl, and of course, who could forget Red Hood?
All right. We should get on a bike.
All right. Get on a bike.
So we're going to go through here.
I'm curious how the gameplay is.
So what difficulty are you playing?
I was on hard, but I was kind of getting my ass kicked, so I put it to normal.
Oh, yeah. I'm on medium.
The big enemies are horrible.
If you play the game on hard, the huge enemies, they're just so tanky.
They're really difficult to kill.
All right. We're going right in this building up here.
So we're going to find a secret door.
Do you have this on the map?
I think I found the secret door.
Hammer right here.
Oh my God. I think you actually found it.
We can just take out the cameras.
How do you take them out?
If you hold left trigger, you can aim and then you can use right trigger to shoot.
Good to know.
All right. I'm turning this off.
Wait, crime resolved, secret identity compromised?
What?
That might have been a side mission.
Thanks for helping me complete my side mission, Hasan.
That's crazy.
I just compromised someone's secret identity.
He's kind of messed up.
He just doxxed.
I think we have to go down the front door.
Wait, no way.
Hey.
Oh, no, I'm falling.
Look what I found.
This looks pretty secret, doesn't it?
This is a secret door, I think.
Open this.
I suggest it to you, the host.
I mean, I am Robin.
I'm an engineer.
Wait, who did you say that to?
Why are you speaking to yourself in the third person?
Whoa, chill.
PvP, let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Fucking double agent for the owls.
I mean, I'm shooting the heck out of you right now.
So all right, let's go.
You have other suits in the styles tab.
Wait, hold on.
But let me look at it real quick.
Oh, there's different colorways.
Stop playing with me.
You have points to put in, too.
If you look through the skill tree.
Nice.
Oh, the shinobi one.
But transmog suit is locked.
Strange location for it.
I'll see what I can find.
Okay, these suits are sick, but it won't let me.
I can only get I can only apply a transmog
to the new guard.
I don't know what that means, but I can't get
I can't get night ops or shinobi.
I think I need to craft different gear.
This one's fine.
All right, you're good.
All right.
I'm good, gas can.
I think we have to solve there's probably a puzzle in here.
Oh, this isn't this isn't the mission.
Yeah.
Oh, it is the mission.
Okay, letter box.
We should probably look for to scan some documents here.
Moreno.
I feel like I know that name.
Me too.
Belfry, we have an open case file on the Moreno murder.
Can you look it up?
Case files.
The brother of Elena Moreno, a local judge.
She took a leave of absence from the bench
directly afterward for family reasons.
That's what would happen if you gave a camera to a monkey.
I actually think a monkey would probably turn the camera
and just be like taking pictures in its face.
I'm investigating this.
The West End.
This peg points east towards the hospital.
Okay.
This peg points northeast.
Interesting.
There's a card.
This takes me to be in old English.
AR scan analysis indicates means purge.
The rest of the text says kill all those who trespass.
This image matches the one on the second order.
All right.
So what means threatened?
The rest of the text says, make them fear us.
Well, we need to figure out.
So we need to figure out where the target is
and what the instructions are.
And you have to piece two pieces of evidence together.
Do you think we can handle that?
Okay.
There's another one that says kill the target.
And then there's one that says near way,
which means constrained or confined.
The rest of the text says, take them prisoner.
Okay.
So we're going to try kill the target.
And what do we know so far?
I have no idea what this mission is.
I'm supposed to be the brains.
That's my bad.
You're supposed to be the brains.
What's going on?
There's an owl dagger here.
Maybe we use that to kill the target.
I think they're going to use the order to kill.
They want to kill somebody at Gotham River.
I messed up.
I spilled coffee.
I love my controller for a second.
I didn't mean to do that.
The order is to kill.
Let's see.
Symbols are different from the previous document,
but it seemed to indicate a command and a location.
Okay.
It looks like there is a kill there.
And it looks like that location is possibly.
I would have deduced this.
The order is to purge because the swords line up there.
Purge the river.
Thank you very much.
Brains of the operation.
Okay.
What happened?
Looks like the court gave a purge order to the Chelsea tunnel.
So by the way, I'm not going to fight any enemies.
That's for you to do.
Was declared unsafe.
That seems convenient.
The court of owls must have something hidden down there.
Heading that way now.
It's so funny.
You could have just like walked.
No, I rule in style.
What's your favorite Batman?
Dude, I don't know.
I mean, obviously the dark knight is, you know,
that's got to be up there, right?
I know that I didn't like the last one.
I didn't even see the last one.
That's crazy.
I really probably wanted to.
It's very angsty.
I think the original Batman cartoon.
Bro, you are cooking right now.
I don't know how I'm not able to go as fast as you.
Oh, all right.
So right before you land, it's going to say,
oh, jump.
You essentially want to time it.
So maybe like a half second before you land.
No, I got it.
Yeah.
All right.
So what is down here?
We got something here.
Lower level, maybe.
What are we looking for?
The court went to great lengths to halt construction at the Chelsea tunnel.
Investigate the construction site to uncover what they...
This is like level.
We're kind of under level for this, but whatever we can do it.
Dude, you got me on your side.
I'm the greatest carry.
Don't worry about a thing.
We have to find the entrance in here.
Maybe lower.
I'm going one step further.
Oh, it's a tunnel.
Okay.
I think it's the tunnel.
Yeah.
I want to see your combat prowess.
I want to see how good you are at this.
Oh, no.
Secret entrance?
Easy.
Looks accurate, right?
Here we go.
That was pretty sick.
All right.
Oh, they say we miss you, buddy.
We did?
Oh, here it is.
I've suggested it to you, the host.
I think we...
Yeah, we can teleport in.
Between the two of us, we can figure this out.
I'm in the tunnel.
Looks like they hit some kind of chasm during construction.
Maybe we're going to fight like aliens or something.
Chances are we'll lose comms down there.
I'll check in as soon as I can.
Jerma, they want me to ask if you're the sus guy.
You already knew that.
You're the sus guy, right?
Yeah, you knew that.
All right.
So I think we're probably going to end up fighting a bunch of stuff down here.
Oh, okay.
I'm ready.
I got the Glock and the Rari.
1738.
It's stalking me.
I don't think it's human.
It's the last message this phone received.
Okay, I'm going in.
You stay out there.
You stay safe, soldier.
I hate tight spaces because I'm such a big muscly guy.
I have no idea if I'm going in the right direction.
You are.
I think so.
You're the brains of this operation.
I'm just the brawn.
Okay, cutscene unlocked.
Do you have a cutscene too or is that just me?
Yeah, I'm watching you.
I just saw that weird alien person.
Okay.
Where are you?
Whoa.
Watch out.
You're ugly.
I just got a bloodborne villain.
I thought you were good.
You just got knocked down by a random putty.
That was a cutscene, okay?
You just got knocked down by a putty from the Power Rangers, dude.
Come on, man.
Oh, God.
Okay, I can't even land a hit on him.
Come on, get him.
You got it.
What?
He's dodging everything, Jerma.
I mean, are you pressing X?
Press X and you got to string X together.
Wait, press X?
Yeah, X.
What does X do?
X, X, X, X.
It's just a punch.
No, X on the swing.
Oh, no.
I'm not on a controller.
You almost got him.
Why is he hitting me?
I'm just trying to find an opportunity when I should come in.
I was going to let you fight the first enemy.
I can't get a single hit on him.
It's because I'm on a keyboard, I think.
That's why.
You probably need to plug a controller.
Let me try.
Let me try to hit him.
Okay, so I don't know what was wrong with him, but my game was fine.
I mean...
See?
I'm ranged.
That's just what we were supposed to be doing.
I mean, my game seems to be working fine.
Yeah, yeah.
No, no, no.
It's just what we were...
See?
We did it together.
Like, I just hit ranged attacks and that's how we were supposed to do it.
Yeah, the guns probably are better.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what it was.
That's what we were doing.
We're probably going to have to fight a lot of those.
Wait, that was just a regular creep?
That wasn't the boss?
I don't think so.
Uh-oh.
What, are you behind us?
I look so much less intimidating next to you.
Well, you have guns and I have a slingshot.
Yeah, you have a slingshot, dude.
What is that?
Hey, watch this, you know?
All right, we got to get on the other side somehow.
Is there a way to go up?
Yeah.
In parkour?
Parkour.
Nice.
Okay, we should be able to...
Very nice.
All right, be careful.
I'm never careful.
Oh, also, you're playing keyboard and mouse, right?
Yeah.
In the lower left, you probably already know this,
but there's a button to just do an instant, like 30% heal.
Yeah, Z.
Okay, yeah.
Just want to make sure you...
Oh, no, I've been abusing it.
That's why I'm still alive, even though I...
Are you going to play this again tomorrow?
How many of you are there?
I am not.
I will not be playing this tomorrow.
Oh, no.
Who's going to carry me tomorrow, then?
Bro, I can't even hit him.
I'm not even kidding.
I don't think I can hit him.
I think I might be too low.
Yeah, I'm doing like 22 damage.
Yeah, try holding the heavy attack button.
That should stun them, and then you can hit them.
I wonder if they're combo...
Are they combo moves?
I want to see if I'm cool.
Check this out.
They're very good at dodging my projectiles.
Yeah, the best...
These characters, you got to...
You hold the heavy attack button.
Whatever your range attack button is, hold it.
Oh, God, I'm dead.
I got you, don't worry.
I'm respawning at two.
One.
I can't pick you up.
Why?
No, I have to do it myself.
Wait, what?
Where does I...
Where do I respawn?
Okay.
Come on, we can't lose to the putties.
Oh, I killed one.
Nice job.
Let's go.
All right, so what's your...
Okay, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
That's for me.
All right, let's do...
Can we do a pose?
Let's do a pose together.
On the count of three, let's do your favorite emote on the count of three
because I want a picture.
Okay, let's do it.
I'm ready.
One, two, three.
That's fucking cool.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
I actually look so cool right now.
You do look very cool.
I want a better frame.
There we go.
Perfect.
Nice.
All right, but what's your range attack button?
Right click and then left click
or Q for range attacks or...
That one.
Hold Q for heavy attack.
So that one, you want to...
That's the only way you can hurt these guys.
Oh, really?
Yeah, so you have to hold it, hit somebody with it,
and then they stunned enough for you to do the melee damage to them.
Okay, got it.
They are also level nine and I'm level three.
That's also true.
Yeah, you are kind of under levels for this.
So am I.
What am I, seven, six?
People are yelling at me saying it was on my screen.
Need my attention.
All right, almost up there.
These guys got nothing on us.
That's actually not a bad impression.
That actually sounds pretty good.
All right, we're going to find research items.
It's my job.
Very good at finding research items.
Sample.
I think these are the research items.
This is some giant slim gyms.
This is a spectrographic analyzer.
Spectrographic analyzer.
I got a chest over here.
I've never even seen a chest yet.
Did you get the item?
Ooh, I think I got some green stuff.
Yeah, it's crafting material.
So eventually you have enough to make new weapons and suits and stuff.
Seems like we need to open up this extraction room.
I think we have to find two more pieces of research.
Which it looks like over here.
Oh, no, it's back here.
What's this stuff?
More x-ray analyzer and more ore samples.
Is this going to be an insanely hard?
This looks like a difficult puzzle.
Where'd you go?
What are you doing?
We opened it.
That's it.
Oh, it's down a level.
There was a thing down there.
It's a rock climbing wall.
Oh, whoops.
Rookie mistake.
It's not a big deal.
I'll keep us grounded.
Oh, I fell.
By grounded, I mean literally in the ground.
Rookie mistake.
What?
I will do Red Hood now.
Where are you off to?
What?
Oh, you're back.
That was pretty sus.
Oh, my God.
I fell again.
All right.
You made it.
I think the game got sick of you falling.
Just put you there.
Computer from a crown to all.
I did some tinkering and went back to some older composite samples.
Turns out what we thought was waste ore just needed a different extraction treatment.
The carbonic acid.
They're just making words up now.
Carbonic acid.
Carbonic.
It's nerd stuff.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, I'm a nerd here.
I've come on.
All right.
So this is samples have got to tell me something about what's going on.
Oh, it's another piece together.
The mystery.
All right.
I'll leave this up to you.
The brains of the operation.
Which sample should be placed in the extractor?
Which chemical will extract material from the sample?
Interesting.
Well, this is composite ore, which the holes in it would indicate that it's already been
extracted.
So I don't think it's this one.
Hmm.
A note on the sample reads reacts poorly to all previous extraction methods.
No sample.
I think it's marble 1063.
Um, what?
I don't know.
I just wanted to say.
Oh, you clicked on this one already.
All right.
So we need to actually figure this out.
So which sample should be placed in the extractor?
This one?
No.
It's already been used.
I hate science.
And can you back away Red Hood a little bit?
Your breath is fucking awful.
Listen, didn't have time to brush my teeth before we ran outside today.
No sample extracted.
Hasn't hasn't been extracted yet.
This one here.
Which chemical will extract material from the sample?
I didn't think you'd be able to smell my breath from under the mask.
How do I find out what the element is?
Which chemical?
Which chemical would it be?
How do I select it?
Okay.
If you can't figure it out, then there was no shot.
I was going to figure it out.
You're the nerd on this team.
Stop, stop, stop it.
Uh, where's the I'm trying to work Red Hood.
Which chemical will extract material from the sample?
Is that a mechanical keyboard?
Seems like a real gamer.
WASD keys are actually highlighted.
I wish Batgirl was here.
I wish Batgirl was here instead of you.
How can't I put any chemicals here?
Is there a list of the chemicals?
I don't see them anywhere.
I think that was a bit mean.
You just said right there.
I mean the breathing is fine, but you know how I feel about Batgirl.
Where's the list of chemicals?
Maybe the email?
Yeah, I can't click the email.
Sulfuric acid worked perfectly.
So where's sulfuric acid?
Is sulfuric acid here somewhere?
Oh, Jesus.
It's all right, Red Hood.
I got this.
We just didn't look one inch to our left.
That's my bad.
I'm supposed to be the brains.
Yeah.
I apologize for everything I just said about telling you to get away from me and everything.
Are you loving this as much as I am?
No, I'm not.
I got it.
Okay, we're good.
I was just about to shoot this nerd thing.
That sounds made up.
I'm not the only one who hasn't heard of it.
We should get another photo.
Everyone wants me to say this.
I don't know why.
Scorn.
You shouldn't have said that.
Why?
Just saying you've infected your channel now.
Wait, what?
With what?
Scorn.
Guys, there's a new Scorn streamer here.
He's in the call right now.
I've never played that.
Well, now you have to.
I'm actually playing Gotham Knights.
A brand new open world third person or action RPG featuring the Batman family.
You can step into the roles of Batgirl, Nightwing, Red Hood, and Robin
and rise up as the new protectors of Gotham City in the wake of Batman's death.
You can also customize your night with new gear and looks as you play through all the
new original story solo or an online co-op with a friend like Jerma.
Like we're doing right now.
Like we're doing right now and come face to face with some of the most infamous
villains in DC's Batman universe such as Mr. Freeze, Harley Quinn,
Spoiler Alert, Clayface, and Mysterious Court of Owls.
Gotham Knights is now available on PlayStation 5, Xbox Series S, X, and the PC.
It really looks like your character is sitting there talking into a camera.
Yeah.
Right there.
Because he is.
But everything you just said was true.
Is there a co-op experience?
Batman is dead and also he's Bruce Wayne.
Uh, there's an absolutely amazing part.
I don't know if you'll see it or whatever, but I forget how far into it it is.
It's absolutely hilarious.
It's probably the best part of the entire game.
So, um, Batman sends an email.
This is a spoiler, by the way, but it's hilarious.
So Batman sends an email out to like all the Gotham Knights.
He's like, oh, hey, I just want to make sure everyone's aware of this.
Um, it seems to me that Bruce Wayne and Batman are Google trending right now.
So I feel like people know who I am.
He actually says that search trending like he's trending as Bruce Wayne and Batman.
He's a bit of a boomer.
Yeah, but that was like my favorite part of the entire game so far.
There's nothing wrong with being a boomer.
All right, let's go.
He looks up his name and Batman and sees that like the trend line for searches has gone up.
So he's like, oh shit, I've been compromised.
That's how he knows.
Suggesting that the ho.
There is everything wrong with being a boomer.
Wait, what do you mean?
Oh, are you saying that?
Wow, they're being ages.
They're being ages.
Oh, it's clear you don't understand your place.
Dog, you're a dude in an owl head.
We are the protectors, not you.
What?
Well, that's a load of shit.
Don't you think you'd want to press that when you leave?
Yeah, doesn't that hurt his own owl guys?
Yeah, and I think I want to be in the cut scene.
I'm not in the cut scene.
I pressed it.
So we're going to get the fuck out of here now.
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm going to do the cute thing now.
All right, we got to do superhero talking to each other like in every movie.
Okay, I'm not able to use the ocean.
Oh, God.
Red Hood 6 o'clock.
Bullseye.
Oh, that was mine, man.
I died.
I can't help you up.
Wait, I can respawn.
I don't know why it just it wouldn't let me know.
Oh, I'm good.
I'm good again.
I respawn.
Oh, God.
Okay, they're spawn camping.
Oh, my God.
These guys are kind of tough, actually.
Oh, God.
I'm going to fall.
There's a button prompt and I don't know what button it is.
It just flashes way too quickly.
It's dodge.
So you see like when their hands kind of light up with a circle around it.
When the circle lights up, that means you can do a perfect evade.
I don't think you can put a point in it.
No, it's not it.
Here we go.
Okay, I have to actually right click because it doesn't auto aim.
Possibly because of the PC.
Probably.
What was that?
What is that?
The Ghost of Nightwing?
What the hell?
What do you got?
A spirit bomb?
What is that?
The Ghost of Nightwing.
Nice job.
Oh, you killed him.
I killed him, actually.
That was me.
Oh, we're going down, man.
We're going down.
We're going down, Goku.
Well, I guess they're going down with us.
No, we're good.
Not in the cutscene, Sag.
I think I'm just about done with Talons, thank you.
The mines are collapsing.
Oh, it is collapsing.
This is not what I was expecting to be for our Saturday afternoon.
Are we running?
I'm running.
I'm not fighting.
Hey, when we get back, promise me you'll do the cooking.
Is that you talking or is that Robin?
What?
I've been saying hi to the chat for a minute or two.
Wait, it just says, when we get back, promise you'll do the cooking.
I was muted.
Wait, is that actually him?
Yeah.
Am I being ghastly right now?
That is pretty sus of you, dude.
Yeah, I was being kind of sus.
Damn, you were sussy.
Wait, can you do that again for real?
Uh, it has to be in the moment.
I'm a method actor.
I hate cave-ins.
Guess we got to go up now.
Okay.
That was a bad line, I'm sorry.
And I didn't even do it.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
All right, let's switch roles now.
You do Robin and I'll do Red Hood.
I can't do Robin.
I think I can probably do a pretty good Red Hood.
I sure hope so.
Okay, that sounds very scorn-like.
Maybe a little.
Why do you sound hungry?
Oh, up here.
I'm up here.
I'm looking forward to chopping those carrots later on.
It's a long ride up.
Shut up, Robin, you fucking idiot.
Listen, Red Hood, just because you're so sexy and muscular
doesn't mean you can bully me like that.
Oh, well, I have to see.
But I like it.
We did a really good job together.
You and I.
You sound a lot like that conspiracy guy, Alex Jones.
I just want to tell you, look,
what you need to understand,
it's not, I'm not, it's not, don't listen to me.
Belfry, can you hear me?
When we get back, when we get back to the Belfry,
I'm going to eat as much meat as I can.
I'm going to eat, and I'm going to have children.
The court is mining the strange element I've never heard of.
Here we are, we have you.
Are you still there?
Belfry.
Oh, no, where's Belfry?
How are we going to go back?
Whatever you do, do not punch this person.
Don't do it.
I'm telling you right now, you better not.
Where?
This guy?
You better not.
Don't do it.
You're under arrest.
All right, stop.
Actually, stop it.
Stop it.
Stop.
I'm getting out of here.
This is not on my stream.
I'm out of here.
I thought you told me to punch the person.
I said, don't.
I misunderstood.
You tell me to punch, I say, how hard?
All right, we're going to go talk to Talia Al Ghul.
I'm a bit of a anti-hero.
You know what?
Let's do, oh, my game's just turned off.
Oops.
What?
Are we still on the call?
Yeah.
What?
I'm going up.
I think I'm going to have to join you.
Wait, are you still in my game?
Wait, I just lost.
Connection to the game session.
Yeah, I think it just booted us, I think.
Wait, why did that happen?
Internet.
OK, well, on that note, I think, I mean, wait, hold on.
When did you start playing?
I don't know, like a couple hours ago.
Oh, OK.
Do you want to keep going?
Because I was just going to end it here.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, I'm going to play for like another 20 minutes, 30 minutes.
If you want, I'll play more with you.
Do you want to keep playing?
Yeah, I'll play 20 more minutes.
Let's do at least a couple of crimes on the street.
Wait, I wonder if it's because I shot the civilians.
No.
Let's do a little bit more.
You come with me this time.
You come with me on a mission.
All right, yeah, that's probably better because then I can actually carry
because I'm going to be like four or five levels higher than you.
OK.
So let me go to social.
Wait, why isn't it showing up on recent?
Oh.
Friends.
In-game friends, it doesn't say.
Are you offline?
No.
Hold on.
I'm just are you offline?
No.
Can you invite me?
You're not you're not showing up on my list.
Oh, no, it says, OK, invite player.
Oh, there you go.
Invite casket to your game.
Let's go.
Did it work?
Can you hear me?
I mean, I invited you.
I wonder if it was it through.
Oh, it's through.
OK, it was through steam.
I see.
Yeah, it's through steam friends.
OK, coming in.
So let's play for like another 25, 30 minutes or so, 20 minutes.
I mean, you know, Warner Brothers is obviously sponsoring the stream.
So let's showcase what we can.
You know what I'm saying?
Hey, there you are.
God, you look like such a freaking nerd.
Little guy.
Wait, can you change your casual gear?
I don't think you can change the casual gear.
So this is your game.
So am I still level?
I'm still level eight.
So.
Oh, my God, the talent gear is soon.
Wait, I have different demon.
I have different ones here.
Yeah.
No, I don't.
Shinobi.
No, no, no.
It's the same ones.
As you level up, you unlock more suits and stuff.
Well, how do I get to this one?
I actually like that.
When I do the decoy, the elemental residue.
That's pretty cool to me.
I'm going to take a look at the workbench here.
You should.
I don't have a suit.
I don't have anything for suit.
I only have stuff for melee.
Like I can craft a stealth pistol and I'm doing all that,
but I want to do it so I can like actually change my suit.
But I can't.
It only says apply transmog.
Does that mean it's unlockable?
All right.
So does it say crafting ready underneath it?
Oh, no.
So you don't have enough materials.
Joe, why are you guys saying you have other gear to equip?
If you get out of this and just go hold down whatever to get to that menu.
Like one and go to gear just like out of the workbench and then go to suit
and then go to melee.
It's the same thing, but you probably have a couple things to switch out.
Okay, suit.
I have the beyond suit on.
You might have other guns too.
Last hurrah.
Yeah, I'll do nightwing last hurrah.
It's my favorite character.
I want to play more bad girl though.
Bad girl is cool.
Oh, your stats are being decreased to match the hose.
They are.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Well, I mean, that makes sense.
But yeah, that makes sense.
Okay, I have a stock suit and a beyond suit.
That's it on gear.
That's the only two things I have.
And I guess I can try this.
Yeah, with different styles.
I've been waiting to do this ability.
This is gonna be awesome.
Hold on.
Okay, Batman's last case, weird science.
Should we do that one?
Is that what you want to do?
Yeah, or we could even just walk around the city
and just do like the kind of random events.
I feel like that would take about 20 minutes or so,
not like 30, 40 minutes.
Okay.
Wait, hold on.
Melee.
We might actually have to be out for you to put new stuff on.
I wonder if I can craft something.
I cannot.
I guess I can't.
Oh, I have the beyond suit now.
I think you were in that before, were you?
Yeah, but it just like it changed it.
Oh, styles.
I can do new guard on the beyond suit.
That's it.
I can do night watch.
I mean, I like night watch.
It's fine.
I want shinobi, but it won't let me.
And night ops, I can't.
Metal is sick, privateer, demon, neon, nor.
Batgirl, he's talking to himself again.
No, I'm talking to you as well, but...
Batgirl, I don't mean...
Who is he talking to?
I'm just talking to you.
Do people say that in your chat?
All the time.
After you go on, like you talk for like 10 straight minutes,
people just go like, who is he talking to?
Who are you talking to?
All right, let's try to do a crime.
You know what I mean?
Shopping again.
That's what he's doing.
That's true.
I am shopping.
I do be shopping a lot.
Did you say let's do a crime?
I meant, yeah, you know what I mean?
You meant let's stop a crime.
Okay, Batman's last case.
You don't want to do that.
You want to do just regular, huh?
Um, I'm down for it.
I think it'd probably be easier.
It'd be less time if we did just the stuff on the street.
Okay, you lead the way then.
Or do I have to lead the way?
I think because you're the host,
I think you might have to lead the way.
Okay, there's a difficulty low.
Let's do a higher difficulty one.
There's only one.
There's only two crimes here.
Difficulty normal.
Faction mob.
Yeah, I like awesome.
And then there's another low difficulty kidnapping and process.
Okay, that's 473 meters.
Maybe we should take our...
Is that that way?
All right.
Okay, never mind.
This was a very easy way to traverse long distances.
There's a shootout happening downstairs.
I think we should cover it.
Coming.
All right, so where's it at?
Right here?
Underneath us?
Yeah, it's down here.
I'm going to engage in an aerial attack.
Let's go for it.
Wait, what?
Oh, these are cops.
What?
I'm beating up cops.
I don't know why.
Wait, wait, wait.
What happened?
Wait, this is not the robbery.
This is a robbery?
Why are we beating up cops?
I don't know.
You came down here.
What's the mission?
They're so strong.
Hold on.
They have stuff over here.
I'm shooting the wrong thing.
Dude, I have ice moves.
Why are we doing this?
I don't know.
Just go with it, I guess.
It's the next street over, Hassan.
Oh, God.
Oh, you killed him.
All right, it's the next street over.
I think we helped the cops out.
I mean, I think we helped the crimers out.
I think that's what may have just happened.
It's possible.
All right, this one is right over here.
Sorry, but when I go to an address,
asses need to be whooped.
All right, so take a look down here.
We've got to get spotted.
Okay, I'm hiding currently behind the mailbox.
Where are you at?
Are we doing an aerial attack?
I'm going to wait for you to go in
and then I'll go into.
And it's, by the way, silent takedowns
and try to be undetected.
Be a little hard.
Okay, you get the mob brawler on the other side
and I'll get the mob brawler down right underneath me.
That way, we'll be able to eliminate both of those.
Wait, there's another mob brawler over here.
I'm thinking you jump in and I, yeah.
Well, because there's only four of them.
So we're not going to be able to do it silently, I'm saying.
Unless you also do an aerial attack.
All right, I feel what you mean.
Coming up there.
All right, so I'm going to do an aerial attack silent kill.
Can I get up here?
They can't see me.
All right, see the one I'm right above?
Okay, that's the one I was going to do, but hold on.
There's one right next to that one.
I'm trying to get to, I'm trying to get to that right now.
Trying to get to a better position, a better perch,
so I can do an aerial attack on the other one.
Just drove by, something just flew by the screen.
Okay, I got a silent takedown.
All right, three, two, one, go.
Good, all right.
Watch out, let's wrap around this way.
Wait, I'm going to get this guy now.
Oh wait, he's not.
Dude, there is a car just driving by.
I swear to God, that's a car.
Slow that down.
There's cops right there,
and they're not even doing anything about it.
That's crazy.
All right, there are three.
All right, they've been beating the shit out of this person
for like five straight minutes.
We need to like act.
Okay, I'm going to get this other back.
Oh, shit.
Oops.
Uh-oh.
Defeat enemies undetected is done.
Not quite.
I haven't been detected yet.
Just keep them distracted.
We'll get it.
It doesn't count.
Nice.
There's one more.
All right, we got it.
Crime solved.
We got it.
Let's make a check on this person.
Make sure they're okay.
Are you all right, sir?
Thanks, Ero.
Might be a good idea to head home.
Yeah, get out of here.
I'm shooting it in his vicinity,
so he's like afraid, you know what I mean?
Wait, yeah, give him a swift kick in the ass.
That's right.
Get out of here.
Teach you something about
trying to meddle in criminal affairs.
All right, I'm ready.
Okay, we solved that crime.
That was pretty easy.
I mean, God damn.
That was pretty soft crime.
Yeah, felt pretty good.
So there's one, 212.
Let's do this hard one.
This one's leaving 263.
How do you, where is it?
So I don't know what it is on yours,
but okay, on the bottom left of your screen,
whatever the rightmost ability is,
is to see what's around you,
like the AR mode.
No, it's not.
If you add, so for me, it's down on the D-pad.
It's on the lower left of your abilities.
We heal and call the bike and emote.
On the map, you mean?
Oh, no, just like the lower left of your screen,
like whatever that button is,
all the way to the right above your health bar.
Oh, I see it 160 meters away.
Purple, is that the one?
Yep.
Oh, well, is it 100?
Where is it?
It's this, I think.
I think I just way pointed it.
Hold on.
It's whatever the one is red.
It's a red one.
Oh, it's a red one, not a purple one.
Okay, I did the wrong thing.
Wonder what the purple one even means.
Red one is 256 meters away.
Does that mean it's hard?
I think that's a difficult one.
Wait, let me look at it real quick
and then try to pinpoint it on the map.
Oh, yeah.
That is his difficulty very low.
Very low.
Yeah, let's go to the purple one.
I know what it means.
We'll do the purple one.
I don't know what that means, though.
But again, thank you, Warner Brothers,
again, for sponsoring this segment of the stream.
It's out now.
Both of our panels down below
should have a image of the link.
The game is currently on PlayStation 5,
Xbox Series S, Series X, PC.
It's out now.
It came out yesterday.
Wait, it's down here?
There is co-op, as you can see.
Oh, my God.
Are these criminals
or are they just trying to get in their car?
I don't know.
But you're having a hard time
whipping that ass, I see.
I did all right.
They were going to break into a car, I think.
Good thing we were here to solve that crime.
I feel like that was kind of overkill.
It's like, oh, they're breaking into a car
and all of a sudden it's like you got us two here
with like our superpowers.
Like just throwing ice at people and shit.
I don't think that was the purple one.
Oh, no.
Yeah, it wasn't.
I was going to say that was not...
There's one over here.
I thought it was.
Right here.
Oh, wait.
It's not.
I'm still going.
We can do this really quickly.
I'll go for a stealth kill
and you go for a silent take down from above.
You just like Mario jumped on his head.
That's right.
That was not a purple one, was it?
That was the purple one.
No, no, I think there's...
No, there's another purple marker on mine.
Difficulty low.
Let's do a hard one.
I don't...
There isn't any...
Like it's not...
I have no hard ones.
Oh, I think...
Yeah, because we're low.
Let's do the one that is bright.
Let's just do this one then.
This is called the Freaks.
I have it marked.
We can call it for this if you want.
Okay.
Lead the way.
A lot of fun playing with you, dude.
Absolutely.
Anytime.
All right.
So I don't know what exactly this is, but we'll find out.
We're about to find out.
I did say it back.
Why is Chad saying it?
Wait, did you not hear me?
No, I did.
Yeah.
I said, absolutely.
Anytime.
I heard it.
I had a lot of fun, too.
All right.
So there's a lot of...
That's why I was begging him.
Literally.
Whoa.
Two stars.
I mean, you can tell that story if you want.
I was like, no, I don't want to play with you.
You suck.
You're bad at the game.
And I was like, please, Yerma.
I need you.
Aerial attack time.
Aerial attack doesn't kill people, which is weird.
Wait, why are cops shooting at me now?
All right.
Let's get them.
Is that...
Did cops shoot you in your game, too?
They did, but I ran somebody over with my car.
So, I mean, it made sense.
Like, I was like running people over.
I was attacking people.
Now I'm hitting these cops and they're not actually doing anything.
I was driving into people and shooting at them.
It was a disaster the first 10 minutes of the stream.
I played it for the first time.
Damn.
Whoa, chill, bro.
Cops are shooting me, too.
Are they still mad at you?
No.
I think they were accidentally shooting me.
Hey, oh, no.
Wait, they're running away.
Run away.
Get out of here.
Get.
That's how I clear an area, though.
That's just like my signature move.
Okay.
All right.
You want to do one more or are you good?
It's up to you.
I'll do one more if you want to do one more.
You need for the guns down.
I will never put my guns down.
America, damn it.
It's Gotham.
I mean, I don't know what this one is, but we can go to it.
Let's do it.
Somebody just called you out.
Yeah, she did.
What?
So this one looks like the previous one that we just did.
I think maybe we didn't get rid of them all.
No, it cleared it for me.
Oh, she's an AK.
Let's go.
This one's a little bit more challenging.
Just kidding.
Whoa.
Watch out.
She's aiming for you.
Yeah.
Look, team attack, team attack, team attack.
Come over here.
Team attack.
Oh, oh, that was sick.
Yeah, that was so again.
Oh, I'm just getting warmed up.
Damn it.
That's pretty cool.
All right.
How are you doing?
Is that you good?
I'm good.
Yeah.
All right, German.
Thank you so much.
Thank you to Warner Brothers for allowing us to play this wonderful game.
Gotham Knights, which is available now on PlayStation 5, Xbox XS, and the PC.
That's right.
Get it by clicking on our respective tabs underneath.
Great.
All right.
Bye.
Yeah.
Thanks for playing, dude.
Well, I'll talk to you soon.
Cool.
Okay.
So that was Gotham Knights.
Oh, I got kicked.
That was Gotham Knights.
That's going to conclude the sponsor segment
and that's going to conclude the sponsored streams for Gotham Knights.
Huge, huge thank you to Warner Brothers.
Like I said before,
WB has been an unbelievable supporter of the stream, so I'm happy to play.
Hope you guys enjoyed it.
Hope it was fun to watch.
The game is available right now.
You like what you saw?
It's available right now.
With that, I'm going to end the stream.
Thanks to Hassan Tupac for playing.
I mean, he was just, you know, check out the co-op.
Why not?
And I will see you guys in a few days.
See you on the 25th.
25th at probably around 4 Pacific, I want to say.
I'm going to start doing Halloween stuff.
I might play, I don't know, I'll figure it out.
I'll be in pre-stream on the 25th.
Maybe a little bit early, maybe like 3 Pacific.
But yeah, thanks for watching.
See you guys later.
We'll just kind of play it out here.
Very cool.
Can we get one scorn?
You want one scorn?
You guys have been good.
I'll give you a scorn.
No, we haven't.
We've been good.
Probably you guys have not been good.
You guys have been, you behaved pretty well today.
Yeah, I'll give you, okay, here it comes.
Prepare yourself.
It's on its way right now in three, two, scorn.
That's so funny that he scorned.
Yeah, good night guys.
See you soon.
Take care of yourselves.
Goodbye.
See you on the 25th around 3 Pacific.
We'll figure it out.
See you soon.