Exit so you get it right, nice and tight.
Hey, what's going on everybody? Jermuck here with a vlog.
It's been a while since I've done one of these face to face one on one.
Me and you are the only people in this conversation.
So see your way out of it, buddy.
There's nobody else here.
Anyways guys, hi, welcome to the vlog. I haven't done one of these in a while.
But I thought I would do one tonight because pretty important reason.
I'm an uncle. You probably saw the title.
The baby was born not tonight.
It didn't like just happen like, oh, did it just happen?
Okay, I'll get off the phone. Hey, it's a video.
I just spilled that everywhere.
But that's not what this is.
This is it. Hold on. I have to clean that up.
But no, my my niece was born exactly two days ago.
It was at 11 a.m. on the calendar on Wednesday, July 31st.
Got a bunch of pictures.
There's probably going to be one like right here in this area right here.
My hands are probably disappearing behind a little baby.
Hello. Yes, baby.
So what's the baby's name?
I talked to my sister to make sure this was all OK.
So I'm not just like uploading pictures of her newborn infant baby on the Internet.
But no, the baby's name is Harper.
It is a girl. Harper Eve is the baby's name.
Very pretty name for a little one different baby right there.
But Harper Eve is the name of the baby.
I'm not going to tell you the last name because I don't want you to go like find her or something.
And she was already scared enough for me to do this video.
She's like, make sure like nobody like harasses me.
I'm like, no one's going to listen.
No one's going to harass you. You're going to be fine.
Just chill out. You just had a goddamn baby for Christ's sake.
Just like go sip on some sangria or whatever.
What do you what do you do when you're not when you're not pregnant?
If you're watching this video and you were pregnant at one point in your life,
What's like the first thing you did?
What's like the first thing you did after you were pregnant?
I'm kind of curious because I mean, I'm a boy.
I'm a man and I can't have babies come out of my body.
So I'd like to know.
And if you're not able to talk, but as you can tell, I'm in a very crazy mood right now.
I just got home from a family reunion where everybody was interested.
We got to do this like iPhone FaceTime thing where it was like I had the iPad set up and she was on the iPhone.
She showed pictures of the baby in real time and it was crazy.
It was amazing.
And it's a really it's really cool feeling if those of you that have not been able to be alive to see a sibling or a niece or a nephew born.
I feel great right now, man.
Like I feel awesome because knowing that like somebody in my family is like continuing the human chain just feels good.
You get to see life.
You get to see death in this crazy world that we live in and you get to see it all.
And I'm glad that I was able to share this with you guys.
I just want to do a quick little thing to tell you where I've been the last couple of days.
I've been freaking out with family just with the family conversing about little babies and how cute they are and how I'm going to like do lots of snuggles and lots of nose nuzzles to this little adorable thing that's in my life now.
But yeah, that's about we're going to wrap it up here.
I just want to do a quick now.
I'll see myself out.
I'll see myself now.
You know, don't don't don't get up.
Has there ever been has there ever ever been a full body German shot ever recorded?
I don't think that has.
I'm pretty sure this is the first ever like full body German shot.
This is my baby.
Well, I already have a baby.
His name is Otto.
Hello.
Hi.
You fucking stink.
Get out of here.
You smell like fucking piss and dog food.
But that wraps it up here, guys.
Just want to throw together this quick little vlog, probably a very chaotic vlog because I'm very excited, as you can probably tell that by now.
So I'll see you guys all next time.
Take care, everybody.
And the meaning of life, guys.