You weren't supposed to be able to see me yet. I'm not supposed to be on here.
But hi. He thinks he's live. Don't turn it off.
No, I'm fucking out of here. Just like listening to like the bibidibid bibidibid bib.
Right back. Okay. That means your mic is hot now.
Okay. My first time. Hey everybody, welcome to the stream.
You know me. Look at your wrist to view your watch.
Don't listen to that lady. She's going to say that over and over again.
You can hear me, right? Oh yeah.
Good. Today we're going to play some fun co-op VR games. Me and my friend Ster here.
Look at your wrist to view your watch. Some of you might have heard of them once.
Very fun games. We picked the most exciting VR games that have ever been made.
Last week we played, what was it? Lethal League Blitz? Last week.
Actually that was only like three days ago.
Something like that. I got the wrong hands on.
So yeah, we don't know how to do any of this. We've been sitting here for a little while.
You say VR stream, but you mean like tech stream.
We've never played, I've never done any VR multiplayer.
And it was just like, let's do it. And we both sat down for a while.
We were like, we picked out some games to do.
And then we sat down to actually try to do that. We have no idea what to do.
So, so far I'm pretty good at buying VR games.
Yeah. I'm really good at like purchasing games on steam at this point.
Look at your wrist to view your watch.
That one will.
All right. Are you, are you going in?
I'm, I'm in the tutorial room.
Yeah, me too. But are you like going in? Are you in?
Oh, I'm in.
Okay. Just I need, I need you to, I need clarification that you're in.
So I can go in too. So then we can, I could be in here.
Look at your wrist to view your watch.
My balls are dangling right now. You're going to have to tell me.
I'm in. Get in.
All right. That's all I needed to hear, man.
This thing's, oh, this is too tight.
Look at your wrist to view your watch.
Wait, technical difficulties.
Okay. It's too big. All right.
Are you in?
I'm in. Oh, I'm in.
I think I just pulled out all the hair in the front of my head.
Look at your wrist to view your watch.
I'm going to look at my wrist. Just relax.
Are you seriously not looking at your wrist right now?
Hold on. Look.
I thought you were in.
I'm in now.
Okay. There you guys are. Hi, guys.
Look at your wrist. I did.
All right. Here's my wrist.
Let's get you into a game.
All right. Let's get into a game.
Press the play button on your watch.
Plus the fucking headphones just came out.
I'm stuffing these in as deep as I can.
I don't even know if this is the right one.
I did buy like the VR, like fucking cocking glue
that you just stuff it in your ear and it's a headphone.
And you need to get like a goddamn surgeon to get it out.
All right. How do I join your video game?
Go to play.
Look at your watch.
All right. There's paintball, paddle ball, paintball, crimson cauldron,
laser tag, golden trophy.
How do I like be your friend?
Look at your watch.
I am in my watch. Where are you?
You look at your watch and it says people.
And I imagine you're people.
People?
Oh, it's like forcing us to press the play button.
What do you see? People.
Right below.
Okay. Hold on.
Go back to the home menu.
And it's making me pick paddle ball.
It's making me pick paddle ball too.
Is this like putting us in the game together?
Let's pick paddle ball.
All right. Just pick paddle ball.
It's going to be easily.
We're the only people queuing a rec room paddle ball tutorial mode right now.
You'll be matched with another player.
It's you. We didn't have to...
Hey, look over here.
To go through the glowing door to practice.
Is it your name is pasty octopus?
And you're coming through twice.
Nice.
How do I delete that?
And when you're ready, one last...
Voices.
Does voices turn that off?
My microphone.
Turn your microphone off in the settings.
Where?
Open up your fucking like Aqua Teen watch.
I'm in the watch.
Why can I still hear you?
Where do I turn it off?
Go into your watch.
Go to settings and then turn up my microphone.
Turn off.
That's off.
Why are you huge?
This is how tall I am.
You're not like six, eight.
What? It maps the VR to where your head is.
No, no, that's ridiculous.
Give me a high five.
That was a good one right there, man.
Oh, yeah.
He's fucking huge, man.
What the fuck are you doing?
Why would you do that?
What? I just wanted to play rock, paper, scissors.
You ready?
What the fuck is wrong with them?
We only have five minutes.
Rock, paper, scissors.
How do you do the thumb?
Whoa.
What?
I just teleported.
How do you do the thumb?
It's different on Vive controllers.
I don't know.
Why do you have like a better VR system than me?
No, I'm just taller.
That's bullshit.
I know what's going on here.
This is exactly what's fucking happening.
You have your Oculus, by the way.
Oculus is like the platform
you shouldn't be on.
You should be on the HTC Vive
just in case you were wondering.
You have, wait.
Press the start button on the scoreboard to plan.
Are you just sad?
It gives you random faces.
Oh, I thought you were like crying or something.
Your character is just doing like a constant
I'm talking, listen to me, I'm important.
Wait, can I get down here to your size?
No, that's bullshit.
You have your two lighthouses on huge like cranes.
I'm honestly sitting on the ground.
Yeah, it's because I have my setup correct
and your setup is fucked up.
You're not this tall.
You're not like 10 feet tall.
Give me a hug.
You're like Andre the giant.
All right, let's go.
Majestic squirrel versus hasty octopus.
Which one's you?
I'm majestic squirrel.
Dude, you are so big.
This is not, I can't do it like this.
Can you move your lighthouses down like five feet?
How do you play?
What?
Why did that just pop up?
How do I like turn this off?
I don't, what?
Hey, just again, one of my mods is playing TF2
in case you were curious.
All right, so we got-
Oh, I think I got, I don't know the rules.
It's just, it's like a just big, it's small tennis.
Small tennis.
Yeah.
I can't get over how fucking huge you are.
That's not.
All right, I wouldn't, why is there no sound?
It's coming over here.
I need like a bit more audio.
It's like just music.
All right.
How do I turn?
I don't have sound.
That's just music.
What the fuck?
See, it's, did you just score off me right now?
I don't know.
Wait.
Jolly green giant over here.
Oh my God.
This game, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
How do I turn it off?
How do I make the sounds better?
Just, can you just wait until we can get out of the tutorial?
Oh, sure.
So we can just play Jeopardy for God's sake.
I'm going to hit this as hard as I fucking can.
I hope you're ready for that.
Can I like grab it first?
Where am I in my room?
Am I near like a wall?
Which wall is back here?
You're okay?
All right.
Let's go.
Match point.
This is too hard.
I hit that.
It's too hard.
All right.
Can we thank congratulations?
We did it.
I got a present.
What is it?
Open.
I need to level up some more to use this item.
You got an exclamation point.
Good for you.
I get another one?
That's pretty satisfying.
That's kind of satisfying.
50 tokens.
What did you get?
I got 50 tokens.
I can't.
How do I do thumbs up?
Violet, why are you dressed like an opera singer?
What?
You got a tank top on.
Yeah, I do.
Do it alone.
How do I leave?
I think we're stuck here opening boxes for another hour.
Are we?
There's a door right there.
Should we leave?
Oh, you have walking on.
You're advanced.
Yeah, I'm going to throw up.
By the way, this makes me throw up.
Stock button.
No, I don't want to do that again.
Does our watch have a thing?
No, there we go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay, challenges.
It wants us to do a challenge now.
But what about this room?
This is a store?
Wait, let me turn this.
I need to have the music down.
The sounds are going to go up.
What happened?
What are you doing?
I sent you a friend request.
You sent me a package.
Oh, that's my package.
That's my box because I completed the challenge to make friends with you.
No one else could do it.
But look, I got another one.
Complete one game in paddle ball daily.
Will you stop spraying the coins on me?
All right.
Who gives a shit?
Press the start button on the scoreboard to play.
Let's go.
Okay, play.
All right, all right, all right.
Can we pick some of the same thing?
Let's put it like bowling or something.
This is just Roblox.
Yeah.
Did you accept my friend request?
I don't know.
Did I?
People?
I have a message from you.
Let's open it.
That's from me.
I accept your friend request.
Yes.
Okay.
We're friends now.
So.
Yay.
All right.
Play.
We're always going to jump into one of these.
How about the streets?
Okay.
I just clicked on something called the streets.
I don't know what this is.
You're gone.
Click on the streets.
It's like the second page.
Okay.
Why is this all screwed up?
No shit.
This is like a fucking PVP room.
We're going to be throwing up on the streets.
How do I?
See, look at how fucking huge you are.
You are way too big.
Everybody else is normal.
This person can hear me talking, right?
Did you mute your mic?
I'm like, why am I spying on what she's writing?
That was so odd.
Okay.
I have a new notification.
What?
Are we kicking me out?
Everybody has boxes and shit.
All right.
Let's just go to the PVP area.
I don't know what this does.
I'm going out.
You coming?
I'm out.
What?
There's people shooting lasers at me.
I got to kill them.
I got them.
We killed each other.
I'm alive.
Power weapon refreshed.
This is Roblox.
That guy has a sword and a shield.
I like handball better.
That's what gamers are being so violent.
Oh, I just heard a scream.
So I got killed.
Where are the weapons?
This is a water fountain?
I think that kid might actually be running around in his house.
This is a big house.
All right.
Good guy.
Come in.
Come in here.
Walk in.
Unlock door.
I'm absolutely lost.
Should I not have done that?
Hey, come into the door.
There's a door over here.
Do you see the door in the building?
There's the buildings everywhere.
I know.
But there's a locked door.
I can't even communicate because you're in the head.
I always die.
Come on.
Am I a prisoner right now?
I've somehow become a prisoner in here.
You have to help me.
They're absolutely ruthless in here.
What color is the house?
It's blue on the inside.
I don't know what it looks like on the outside.
They're fucking torturing me in here.
Come in.
Get in here.
Don't be a threat.
Is that you opening the door?
Yeah, I don't own this PlayStation right now.
It's my friend's.
But I'm playing on a VR.
So they haven't even turned around to look.
At what point is he going to turn around and be like,
what are you doing, man?
I need to hold on a second.
Whoa, what?
Hey, he saw me go off my watch.
He saw me go off my watch and he fucking shot me.
I was going to try to communicate.
New notification.
Where are you?
I just got to the blue house.
No, no, no.
It's called Tony's Gun Store.
Tony's Gun Store.
He went to the wrong place.
Tony's going to Tony's Gun Store.
How have I not been hit?
Are you at Tony's Gun Shop yet?
I'm stuck inside the blue house.
I think I hit like four.
All right, I'm turning voice chat on for a second here.
Hey, let me in, let me in, let me in, man.
Let me in, let me in.
Hey, let me in, man, let me in.
There's wild people here shooting at me, man.
Let me in.
Oh, thank God I made it in.
People out there shooting at us.
What the heck?
I don't want to, I'm just, I'm going to, I'm a prisoner.
I'm a prisoner.
I don't, I'm not going to do anything.
I can't shoot you.
I'm not going to do anything.
What happened?
Oh, shit.
Jesus.
I'm just going to hang out behind the houses and throw up in the grass.
Okay.
Don't, no, no, no, no, don't do it.
All right, can we do something else?
Please.
I'm waiting for you.
Can we do something else?
This is your show.
All right, let's go.
Get out of here.
Go to play.
And, uh, can we, how do we, let's go bowling.
I see bowling.
Let's play bowling.
You and me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can we like, you want to get out of here?
A friend group?
Do, can we?
Ready to start.
I don't think there's anybody here.
Oh shit, there's somebody here.
Oh shit.
All right, I think we have our own lane though.
This is like a general bowling alley.
On the friend page you can click go to.
Sending me to you.
And we can be friends.
I'm right behind you.
Wow, let's me sneak in.
I don't know, man.
I got nothing.
I don't know.
It's a different game mode.
All right.
Um, should we just?
Hey, Jeremy, your pee pee small.
Where's Jeremy?
How the fuck would they even know?
God damn it.
How do I?
Because you've been here for 10 seconds.
We didn't go that way.
And we're doing that one.
Let me show you guys a thing or two in a hole.
Where's Star?
Get over here.
Where are you?
We just ordered a pizza on the scoreboard to play.
I'm going to get a strike.
Oh, he's so lost.
He's so lost that he has no idea what he's doing.
Do we have to be in different lanes?
All right, let's take the one over here.
We maybe maybe we should just do our own private lobby.
That's what I'm figuring.
I'm going to do.
God damn it.
I'm fucking going to get hurt.
Do we can do private.
We're going to do private.
We'll do private.
All right, get out of here.
All right, I think I made a room.
I don't know if it's private.
OK, you made a room.
People.
And then on friends, you can do go to mains.
Oh, yeah, this is private.
OK, hopefully that's not like the password.
I hope that's not the password.
What is this person doing?
Get out of here.
Get away from me.
All right, how do I join?
All right, go to people.
I just subscribe to you.
I've invited you.
No, that's inventions.
Am I stupid?
Yes.
All right, I see.
OK, messages.
Game invite.
Open.
Do you want?
Yes, let's go.
OK, look, God.
Hey, there you are.
Hey, I reserved the entire bowling alley.
So we could be friends.
He's a billionaire.
He's a millionaire.
All right, you ready to bowl for real?
Yeah.
He's trying to pick up the chair.
I'm trying to pick it up.
Can we play pool, too?
Wow, you are really short.
No, have you just noticed that you're a monster in every single lobby?
You're just a gigantic person.
I wouldn't be surprised if you.
He's going to start a VR fight.
We got that coming up later.
Ladies and gentlemen, let me tell you something.
You want to stick around because we've got a fun fighting game.
What did I just do?
Who's turn is it?
Um, I'm not that you're really just making this so hard for me.
Me?
Why?
Why couldn't you have known that you were going to be on my live stream?
You could have brought your lighthouses down two feet.
I don't know what that means.
How do you pick up a ball?
Do you have a ball?
No, I don't know.
I have no idea.
How does anyone figure out this game?
Okay, literal children are playing this right now.
You understand?
We're adults.
We have to figure this out.
But first, I'm going to get a drink.
Paul, there's a bowling shirt.
Hold on.
What's this?
Coffee or something?
Free donuts?
Yay.
What does that mean?
You want a slice?
There's a wall there.
He's like looking in the instructional manual.
How do we play the game?
It says practice.
It says game in progress, but it says practice.
I got to turn this off.
How do I disable notifications?
Personal space.
Ignore bubble.
Okay, that's good.
All right.
Did you figure it out?
I mean, it should be my turn.
There's just no balls.
All right, guys.
What are we doing wrong?
I think we're playing rec room.
Well, let's see.
Maybe somebody says no clue.
We need balls.
We need to do an official game mode.
Just run down and kick the pin.
You can't.
I tried.
Did you like press a button over here?
We both had to press start.
I pressed start.
What's that?
Uh, you're the host.
These two old fucks lost in a kids game.
You have an idea?
Oh, you lost.
Who won?
I found out how to end the game.
Okay, this is FFA sandbox.
That's the problem that we're having here.
We don't want to do sandbox.
Two team, just you versus me.
Not free for all sandbox.
Me, two teams.
Two team sandbox.
Me versus you.
Game starts in three seconds.
Here we go.
Game on.
All right.
Who's up first?
Me.
Like, dude, I bet this is like you need to buy the ball and have it in your inventory.
You definitely don't have to buy the ball.
No, you have to buy the ball.
The balls are in the front?
Balls in the front?
Like in the lockers?
Uh, somebody said under tail front.
Under tail front.
Hey, we're not in the bowling game mode.
We're in the bowling room.
Well, what's the difference?
I don't know.
I guess this is like not the bowling game.
This is like the hang out with your friends in the bowling alley.
But it goes somewhere different.
Take it somewhere.
I don't know.
We're not going to have bowling shoes on.
Whatever.
Just go on our bare feet.
We'll be fine.
To your right.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't do anything yet.
Stop it.
Is that activated?
No, that didn't do it.
No, no, no.
Just go.
Just get the fuck out of here.
No, that was wrong.
Like, like walk through here to activate.
I'm just going to like put your head down in there.
Can I see what you're doing?
No.
I don't know what's going to make these any different.
We're just going to be in a room.
To create a private room, open your watch and press on play.
Then find the room you want to create a private version of.
Afterwards, instead of clicking the icon, click the exclamation button.
Close that.
I missed it.
It looks like an old motherfucker on an iPad.
That's like what my grandfather does when he's on his iPhone.
Like, oh, you're not going to send a text.
We good?
No.
All right, hold on.
Click the, close the name of the room.
Then press on private.
And voila, you now have a private room.
I'm thinking, I'm close.
I'm getting close.
Does somebody just said I'm the most obnoxious streamer on Twitch?
It's, that's not true.
Why?
What did I, what did I do?
You couldn't figure out how to play bowling.
Well, dude, I'm following the instructions and they're.
Let me see what happens when I, let me think of it to try.
I'm a little like, I'm a little younger than you.
So yeah.
Okay.
Let's see here.
You're not, but I got it.
Me and you dodgeball.
Let's go for real.
I'm going to invite you.
I figured it out in 10 seconds.
Oh my God.
If you like, you can practice until more players arrive.
Waiting for the invite.
Come on in.
I would kind of already did this, but with a paddle.
All right.
We're on different teams, right?
But no.
Ready to start.
Why did you just do that?
You and I are on the same side of the court.
What color is your shirt?
I can't see my own shirt.
You're blue.
All right, here we go.
You ready?
Dodgeball.
Put away.
I punched him by.
All right.
Can I get that one?
No.
You don't have legs that went through you.
We don't have any more balls.
Okay.
Here it comes.
You ready?
I'm going to hit something.
How do these go slower than the paddle ball?
I don't know, but how can we not do this?
Why are we so awful at this?
There's no way you could hit me.
Who's doing the move?
You're doing a doggy paddle.
Don't fear.
You can teleport.
That's the BS.
Like that block?
That's too convenient.
All right.
Now you're fucked.
Ready?
Can you not catch?
Here, here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
If I was 11, this would be the most fun I've ever had.
I said wait.
I'm going to toss it up gently and try and catch it.
Okay.
I didn't know that was real.
You can catch it.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, what do you know?
Spin it around a little bit.
It's so loud.
It shouldn't be.
Come on.
Why would I do that?
Hey, under that.
All right.
Are you sick?
This is the worst game of dodgeball you've ever played.
Can you hit yourself in the face?
Oh, fuck.
How many, hey, how many times have you ran into like your desk?
Not once.
Next.
Tell me, check one.
Let's get one more.
Next.
We didn't spend no money to not get out of here in 15 seconds.
I mean different game.
Like, not dodgeball.
Okay.
Uh-huh.
Never have I ever.
Rec room restaurant.
Rec restaurant.
That's what we're doing.
Shit.
I went to the public one.
It's just going to be a hangout.
I got to move this.
I went to a public restaurant.
Big mistake.
You seem actually fucking hanging out in here.
Pretending to be in a cafeteria.
Come over here.
Hold on.
Put your mic on.
It's going to sound terrible, but we need to.
So this is the place I was talking about.
They got pretty good burgers here.
They got an excellent, excellent garlic aioli that goes on top of it, too.
It's pretty great.
Did you do use open table to get us a reservation here?
No.
Okay.
Let's go ahead and just...
That's a snowman.
Excuse me?
Does anybody work here?
Oh.
Hey, you should be his new boss.
He has lots of restaurant experience this guy.
He runs Michelin star restaurants.
Oh, that's great because this place is in a state of disrepair.
It's complete chaos here.
Wait, who needs menus?
Oh, okay.
Let me see.
No, that's okay.
I know it's your first day.
I believe they do.
I need the menus.
Wait, do you work here?
Okay.
Burger minus steak equals pizza.
Can we just throw a brick through the window?
Okay.
Uh, I think...
Can I get just a glass of water?
Can I just get a glass of water?
No, that's okay.
That's okay.
Everything going?
Everything okay back here?
Can you pick a table?
Because you're blocking the way.
I think we need to get seated.
Oh, that's the VIP table.
What do you want, sir?
Let you sit.
Anyone want to sit?
Sit.
Uh, that candle is made for any of the other tables you see here.
Guys, what do you want?
So I heard about this place on Yelp.
I come to New City, and I try to go to Yelp when I go to the top 10 on Yelp,
and this was number two.
So we're, you know, really hoping for big things here.
So I guess, uh, you ready to order?
Because I looked at the extensive menu that you guys have.
Anyone want a candle?
I think I will have...
I got it under control here.
I think I'm going to have the, uh, the hamburger here.
Can I get that medium, please?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Sorry what?
You can order here if you want.
I'm going to, uh, check our stock real quick.
It's okay.
It's, uh, it's all right.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay.
I'm doing okay.
I can't, I don't know how to sit down.
I need you first.
Okay.
You're standing on the seat.
What are you doing?
I'm standing on the seat.
Oh, okay.
Hold me.
Hang on.
Let me...
Can I help you?
I'm not supposed to be doing this at three and a half on Yelp so far.
You ever do a SlavSquad?
Yeah.
Sir, can I help you?
That is one short streamer.
There we go.
That's just SlavSquad.
Who said that?
It's just nice.
Don't bloody throw cards.
Please do not insult our guests.
Don't throw cards.
Do you know what you're going to order?
Because I ordered a hamburger and we got a fucking pizza.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I probably shouldn't have said that.
I want the Bean Eagles pizza.
That employee.
You're going to have to talk about this employee.
Because that was like the mistake number five.
It's okay. I work here.
Well, it's now two.
Can I get some fireman's and chat?
But it's okay.
How are you sitting?
I sat down in my room.
Okay, so...
What happened to my mug?
You know what?
No, no, no.
I want to see the kitchen.
Damn it.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Somebody call the police.
I'm sorry.
I hit the table.
Oh, my God.
Who is sitting this close to me?
What's going on?
You took a photo of me in the restaurant?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I mean, you could have asked permission for it.
Like all these cameras.
Can you believe this?
This is ridiculous.
We're just being followed.
I don't believe it.
We're being robbed.
Give the pizza burger back.
Jesus.
If I don't get a pizza burger back...
I'm trying to enjoy my meal.
Help me get the burger back.
All right.
It's probably time to call the police.
So I'll see you anyway.
Don't say, oh, my God.
Yeah.
Let's go to the police.
Does anyone have a...
I don't know how to...
It's my watch.
Oh, hey, look.
I got a camera.
I can't be in there.
Unbelievable.
Chug, chug, chug.
Did anyone order pizza anyway?
Like I'll have a half-eaten pizza.
Half-eaten slice?
Like...
Half-eaten slice, anyone?
Woo-hoo!
Oh, I just ripped the corner.
All right, can we...
I don't...
Can we...
Is this what I looked like?
Why do I look like Doug Fuddy?
I ordered the hamburger.
It was me.
Sorry.
There's a piece of cheese and two pieces of bread.
Did you even try, mate?
Look at this.
A slice of cheese.
That's all that's in there.
Fucking rubbish.
Did you just take that from me?
Stop swearing!
My voice cracked.
Oh, sorry.
I don't have access.
I paid in...
I paid in photos.
Yeah, I'm out.
You paid in exposure.
Exposure.
How do I get out of here?
All right, are we moving on?
I don't know.
Were there any other actual games?
We can go to featured games.
There's Paintball, Golden Trophy, The Streets, Newtown, Reborn.
We did a couple of these.
Hide and Seek?
You want to play Hide and Seek?
Just me and you?
Oh my god, no.
Lemonade Simulator?
There's Minigolf.
Oh, Minigolf!
I don't want to play that game.
Minigolf is...
I don't think it's very fun.
What do you guys think?
I don't know why you can't make a private one.
Everyone's screaming to do Minigolf.
Do Furry Hangout.
What are you talking about?
No, I ain't doing that.
All right, let's do Slender Eight Pages.
That would be on here.
You're going to do Slender Man Eight Pages?
I'll follow you.
Does somebody get to be Slender Man?
It would be you.
I'm done being tall.
How do we start?
Can't run.
Always watch us.
Don't look.
If I can't join you, it says game full.
Really?
Come up.
I actually think it's only two people get into the woods.
Just me and you.
Yeah, it's just me.
There we go.
All right.
Only two can enter.
Hey.
What's going on?
How does it feel being up there?
Feels pretty good.
Why can I not hit you on the head?
Because this is a non-violent game.
The only thing you can do is...
Okay, that was funny.
Why did that happen?
All right, before you go,
do you want to press this button or what do we do?
What are you doing?
No, we didn't even read the rules.
You didn't even let me read the rules.
I'm in.
Where are you?
Throw me a flashlight.
Get a flashlight.
Throw me one.
I'll throw it to you.
Hold on.
You have to come get it.
I can't throw it to you.
This isn't even doing anything.
This just hurts.
This is just like a filter on the screen.
Here.
All right.
This is bad.
This is...
I kind of don't want the flashlight.
Thanks.
You just put that right in my face.
All right, let's go.
So we can find the first page.
I'm going to welcome that.
I think your voice is still coming through.
Oh, yeah.
I can turn that off.
Yeah, you definitely should.
Okay.
You ready to go find the eight pages?
Yeah.
I wish there was a camera on you right now
because I'd love to know what the hell you're doing.
I'm crawling.
I need you.
Will you stand up and just play?
You are ruining my street.
Let's hit it.
Let's go.
Hey, behind you, there might be a...
Is there a page?
Over there.
Like...
He really is right here.
This is not the Kingdom Hearts version of this character.
As long as the flashlight's on him, we can not move.
Look at how muscular his legs are.
He looks a little inflated.
You know those things on Halloween?
That big display that you walk by and they go...
And they say like a line about eating you.
That's what this thing is.
He's going to get you.
I don't think he will.
He's ignoring you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Go get him.
What is he doing?
Let's follow him.
Alright, yeah, we gotta follow him.
Hey.
Is he collecting the notes now?
Is it his turn?
Yeah, we're the annoying ones.
Okay, that's a little odd.
This is scarier somehow.
Upbeat.
Daddy, upbeat.
Just have him grab you in the face.
I tried to.
I think he killed me.
He killed you.
I was going to say, maybe we get to trap him like a Ghostbusters proton beam.
How long have we been in rec room for?
We've got like four or five other games to play.
Yeah.
What's next?
What do you want to do next?
I don't remember the list.
Neither do I.
We can do Survive.
What do you want to do?
That is the only one that I did not download.
Why didn't you download that?
It wouldn't start and then I just figured, I figured it'd be fine.
You didn't download the game, like the co-op horror shooter game.
It could start.
Well, start downloading now and we'll play.
Alright, guys, I got some really, really interesting news for everybody.
The last thing that we're going to play is Desert Bus VR.
So we're going to try to take the whole eight hour trip at the end of the stream.
Oh, wow.
Star really ruined the stream.
Dude, just go to the furry room.
I'll be done downloading in a second.
Oh my God.
No, dude, I don't want to.
You get 15 seconds, okay?
10 seconds.
It's just three minutes to download.
My mic turned the fuck off.
Three minutes.
I thought I just did that for a second.
That was weird.
Pretty good.
I'm just going to go and look and I'm going to go and look.
I just got pressured.
Alright, you get 15 seconds.
I don't care if you're a furry.
It's not a problem.
I don't give a shit.
I don't care if you're furry.
I just don't want to see you.
How did you know I was going to go there?
Well, the iron giant is really cool.
I'll tell you.
My favorite part about this is the iron giant.
Is that the iron giant?
It is.
Nice.
Okay.
Can I come up here?
No.
Okay.
It is.
Nice.
Okay.
Can I come up here and spin records?
How do I turn this on?
I think I have to have special DJ permission to use this.
That's a pretty cool Spyro the dragon costume.
I want to see it.
That's a pretty awesome Spyro the dragon.
Spyro and then I don't know what that other one is.
What's going on?
Is this stuff going on up here?
That's a VIP area.
You can't go up there unless you're VIP.
I'm going to respect the rules.
Here's the newest costumes.
Okay.
Spyro the dragon.
What did I tell you?
Uh oh.
All right.
Survive is I'm launching it.
Am I stealing a costume?
I think I'm actually, I think I'm taking this.
No, I got to put this back.
It's that.
All right.
You're launching it?
Yeah.
There you go.
There's your 15 seconds.
Okay.
How do I get out?
What's the out button?
Dorm room right here.
This is actually pretty cool.
If you could make something get like in a cool room with your friends hanging out
You know what my favorite thing about your streams is?
Is after you play like a shit game for an hour, you always come out with the positives.
How is this a shit game?
Is Roblox a shit game?
You don't have to answer that.
I didn't even do this.
This is why I look like a default character.
I didn't have any personality for God's sakes.
All right.
Let me just take off my toupee.
Put it on there.
All right.
I'm going to open up Survive.
First I have to like YouTube or funny break something.
It didn't even work.
All right.
Time to change games to Survive.
In fact, let me just pull up for a second.
All right.
There we go.
So you in Survive right now?
Yeah.
I'm a furry and I hated that.
I didn't.
I just went in.
I just, it was all right.
I just put on a spiral dragon caught in uniform.
All right.
Survive.
Why is the rec room still open?
That was weird.
So how self-explanatory is it to get in a room?
I don't know.
It like starts you in this really weird room.
I'm going to change my name.
So we're going to, we're doing a, this is a co-op zombie survival game.
It has like an H1Z1 title that I can't even put it into this.
Yeah.
There we go.
It's H1Z1 with like an extra S and a U.
Oh God.
I'm in.
That was sudden.
Going back in.
Okay.
I exited rec room and like 300 people came back.
It's fun.
Come on.
It was a fun experience.
Going back in.
This game just jumps out at you.
You said?
It gives you some, you're in a room.
It gives you some options for like how you want to turn and move.
I would go through it real quick.
And as soon as you're done, like throws you to a main menu.
Okay.
But I don't see how to join each other.
So I'm looking around.
You can figure it out while I stuff my face in here.
Oh, you have to beat the tutorial for co-op.
God damn it.
I got like face grease all over the shit already.
Come on.
Hold on.
All right.
It's only been like fucking 30 minutes.
How long has it been?
Has it been longer than that?
How fucking long have I been screaming?
Holy shit.
It's been more than an hour.
Never mind.
That's better.
All right.
Welcome to survive.
For the best play experience you're supposed to answer, how do I walk?
What the fuck is happening?
Do I have a glue man shirt on?
For the best play you're supposed to answer a few questions.
You can freely update all options later as well as play this wizard again.
The game has many other options.
You use the sign in main.
Okay.
Use your finger.
To start tiered with touch here with your finger.
How tall are you?
We've automatically set your height, but this will work only if your VR device is correctly set up.
Feel free to override it manually.
This looks right.
This looks correct.
Okay.
That's good.
Who are you?
Who did you pick?
Steve.
Okay.
You picked Steve.
I want to be Steve too though.
I'll be Jason.
Do you want to see your body?
This will not influence how other players will see you.
No.
I like it.
I like seeing me.
I think that's fine.
How do you like to choose pad and stick?
What the fuck is going on there?
Arm swing.
Are they going to do arm swing?
How do you like to turn?
What is HMD?
I have no idea.
I set mine to snap.
Snap turn?
Yeah, so when you thumb stick it just snaps you.
Guns volume.
I'm going to turn guns volume on normal.
And there's only normal and realistic.
What does that mean?
Is it louder on realistic?
Realistic is very loud.
Would recommend.
This is not an arcade game.
You want me to peek my microphone?
Why do you want me to peek my microphone?
I want you to peek your microphone with realistic guns now.
No checkpoints for nightmare.
Okay, what are we doing?
Survivor or no future?
Sissy, can I play daddy?
How about just survivor?
Okay.
Story mode starts at chapter zero prologue.
It's a real tutorial.
Okay, so we just have to...
Alright, story.
And then story will give you a tutorial you have to do.
And I'll wait for you at the end.
Okay.
Can you guys hear this?
Infection day 47, chapter zero prologue tutorial.
Oh, I walk.
Alright, that didn't seem correct.
Okay, okay.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Why is this happening?
Why is it doing this?
Why am I doing this?
Arm swing.
Stop moving.
How do I stop?
Okay, there's a zombie right there.
I hate this.
How do I...
Wait for the button to go to the menu.
Press trackpad in any direction to sprint.
Something's not right here.
Okay.
Press the grip button to grab it.
It's just moving me around.
Okay.
Healing spray is limited so use it carefully.
How do I put it away?
You have bags on your waist.
You can put them in the right one.
Did it tell you how to do that?
No.
It tells you later.
Why?
What?
Just go with the tutorial.
Stop strutting out about this apocalypse.
I have to change the controls.
These are terrible.
Why do I think this is a good idea?
Are you lefty?
Press and hold menu button to change trackpad between locomotion or action mode.
Okay, that's better.
Not really though.
Freaking arm swing.
Duck to get through.
Center, press left touchpad.
This is so fucked up right now.
Like every time I move any direction.
Press left touchpad playing in seated position.
I'm not in a seated position.
How do I fucking move?
I should have just done god damn teleport.
Okay, trigger button to grab.
Oh my god.
Stop moving.
Grab a magazine.
Yeah.
Don't move.
How do I release this?
How do you get rid of the magazine?
You press E or one of the buttons on your hand.
I didn't fucking tell you that.
Under barrel flashlight, touch under barrel flashlight.
I cannot wait to go to a menu and turn the shit off.
Even aiming my gun is making me walk.
Yeah.
Alright, not bad.
Press down on the trackpad.
Down.
Probably almost done here.
It's actually a lot longer.
Is it longer?
Like I don't know when this ends still.
Oh god, you're still in it?
Yeah.
Put objects in your backpack?
No, not yet.
Not yet.
Okay, you just gotta throw it behind you.
Can I have three objects?
That's in my backpack right now.
It's not.
That's how you know.
Okay.
Oh man.
No, I'm trying to.
Fuck.
How can I tell what's in my backpack?
Can I get in my backpack?
I just took the bullets out.
What was I thinking doing this?
I have no idea how to get into your backpack.
Sidearms and weapons and...
What?
Okay, you can keep it in three magazines in your belt.
This guy...
Did that go in my belt?
I think so, yeah.
I don't know if this is the tutorial or the whole game.
Didn't it say once we get to the end of the tutorial we can play together?
I know, but this feels unreasonably long.
Fight together, that's what it says.
Are you sure?
Vive inside.
This looks like a safe house.
Press grip to grab the drill.
Okay.
What the fuck?
Okay, this has...
No, this is definitely it.
Speak, friend, and enter.
This is it.
Right?
It has to be.
Fight together.
How do I invite you?
I don't know.
I assumed that was still in the tutorial.
Is it...
Is it like a start menu?
No, it is not.
Does anybody know...
how to...
I've got to get back to the controls.
Anybody have any idea?
I can't smash the TV.
Zero out of ten.
Arms up to enter the menu.
What a lie.
There was a button to skip...
Hey, there's a button to skip the tutorial at the very beginning.
You want to just reload and press the button?
I think I'm probably at the end.
You can skip and I can explain anything.
I don't know how to leave the game though.
It's always Alt-F4, easy.
I have to turn this shit off.
I'm just fucking going to quit the game.
This actually is a text-to-speech voice.
I'm just going to fucking sprint.
Zen's outside.
Shoot the lock to continue.
Let's go.
Come on.
Just go.
You can keep two melee on your side.
This seems like fun.
It's a checkpoint.
Oh man, come on.
How do I open the door?
What if I drill?
Open it to unlock a...
Got it.
It worked.
All right, Cole.
Do you see how fucking odd this is?
No.
It's so fucking throw-up inducing.
I'm going to keep complaining about it over and over again.
It's my stupid brain.
It's my stupid brain that decided to do it.
What decided to do it?
I just hit my fucking face on the car door.
What is this?
What's this like popsicle bag?
Okay.
I mean, I've gotten to a second safe house now.
I'm just going to skip the tutorial and see where I am.
Turn the gun on yourself.
Oh, fuck.
This is a checkpoint.
I have to complete it.
I think we have to complete this, dude.
Oh, I just quit.
Press the...
Can I just like...
Oh, look.
Star is now playing survive.
You need to run.
All right.
Let's...
Damn it.
I have to like exit.
Do I actually have to go home?
He's mad.
Why can't it just be like some kind of start menu?
Don't you have like a...
VR button to open up that menu and close it?
Where is it?
Screen savers?
What?
No, these are Steam friends.
There it is.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, no.
Skip the tutorial.
I can't.
What do you mean you can't?
Because I reached checkpoints and it saved my game,
so it didn't start me at the beginning.
I clicked story and it just started me back where I was.
Is it like a new profile?
But thank God I can at least turn this shit off.
For the love of God.
Read what that says.
Can anybody fucking read this?
Wait a minute.
How close am I to something?
Pad and stick.
Standing...
So you're telling me that we can't...
Are you sure?
Players.
Two player.
And teleport.
So are you...
Do we actually have to do this anyway?
This is disappointing.
Wait a minute.
I can skip the tutorial.
How?
I just had to start...
I just started it over again.
Never mind.
It's a lie.
Uh-huh.
Why is this...
Why is this still doing this?
I did teleport.
I didn't save the settings?
What?
I thought I...
Ah!
Are you sure?
I thought I hit save settings like twice.
Oh fucking God.
Give me a break.
Are you sure I didn't hit save settings?
Hello?
Just add a start menu.
Like hold this button down for like three seconds for something.
That's like, come on.
What the heck?
Do I have to quit the game to go to the menu?
Or am I insane?
I can save settings.
Two player co-op.
Teleport.
Are you still in the room with me?
What?
There is a start menu.
How did I get to it?
So apparently we hit a tablet at the end of the tutorial to like have a menu.
Are you still doing the tutorial?
I can't figure out anything else to do so I'm doing it.
I'm just running through.
If only we knew we should just press the fucking goddamn big red button.
I don't know what's going to be in the story when the tutorial is showing you every feature in the game.
God fucking damn it.
I'm going to scream.
How am I supposed to reliably just teleport?
And this is even worse.
Where did my gun go?
I get that.
I guess I'm full over here.
I don't have a gun to shoot this.
Do I have a gun?
Where's my gun?
I can't go through there without a gun.
Get me out of this fucking room.
Why didn't I...
I went down here.
Oh my god.
Get me the fuck out of here.
You don't seem too good.
Oh my god.
Okay, just give me an axe.
I'm fucking going as fast as I can.
Is there anything over here?
Do I not hold this with two hands?
Hey, I made it.
Does it matter which way I go here?
Probably not.
It's fun.
It's not a sidearm.
Okay, alright.
You'll be done in about an hour.
No.
I'm still going.
Are you still in the story?
Yeah.
Why didn't we just press the button?
I'm hoping that when I get to the end I can end what you were saying.
I hope so.
What's going on here?
This guy's as a zombie.
You can like dump goo all over yourself.
Grab the stew, okay?
Zombies do not attack you, but stay away from them.
Don't use any gun or object.
Be quiet.
Press C.
Ah!
I pressed it!
I pressed the button!
I think that skipped the tutorial.
I need that flashlight.
Where's the flashlight?
I had one before.
If only we just pressed the fucking red button.
I think I'm at the end.
Oh, thank God.
Please invite me.
Get me out of this hell.
I've got tablets and walkie talkies.
Please.
Roger that.
Is this how I'm supposed to open this door?
I did it!
Oh no.
Why are you oh noing?
Don't oh no right now.
That's not what we need.
We don't need an oh no.
We need like an oh yes.
I think this is part two of the tutorial.
No, it's not.
I mean, it still said chapter zero.
I couldn't open that before.
Why?
Honest to God, what is going on?
It's teleport.
I'm like, I have like a whip in my hand.
I can't go further?
A water bender over here.
Okay.
Figure it out.
No.
What is in my backpack right now?
The spray is really loud.
The hold a button.
So I have, I don't want this shit in there.
Get that out of here.
Give me this.
I don't care.
Let's just go.
We need to get to the, so we can play.
The whole point is this is a co-op video game to play together.
So you're not out of the tutorial.
I'm, I think I'm getting the tutorial to when the game isn't a tutorial.
They gave me the tablet and it has like find a game on it, but it's grayed out.
I don't know how I would invite you.
At this point, it would probably actually be faster if we like uninstalled the game and then reinstalled the game and then skip the story.
Oh, all I know is I'm, I'm feeling sick like having to walk here.
No, no.
That didn't go in my holster.
This is a, this is a monster in here.
I need to drill.
Do a drill.
Is there a gun in here?
I can't open that.
Oh, this is cool.
Go in here.
Why do I have one of these?
Okay.
Give me the, give me this.
I'm turning into the zombie.
Is something going on here?
Where am I in my room?
Am I like, did I like punch a hole in the wall?
Why?
Change fire mode.
He just won't stop talking and telling me what to do.
But he won't tell me what I really want to know, which is how to be friends.
What is going on right now?
That's bad.
This is like good game mechanics too.
Like losing the track on the ground.
Three magazines in your belt pouches.
So you get the front pouches.
So what do you want to do about this?
One of the other games we have.
Do you want to keep playing in a tutorial until we can play with each other?
What is that sound?
Why is there somebody washing dishes?
I'm going to throw up.
Ah, shit.
Somebody hit the zombie with a shopping cart?
Oh, okay.
What are you doing?
God damn it.
Alright, it might be time to make an executive decision and do something else.
Bye.
One second.
If this is not the end of the tutorial.
Chapter one!
I'm so far behind you though.
Tell me, like guide me.
Okay, I just got to be so far.
I'll just see if I can invite you.
Trust me, you're not going to catch up anytime soon.
I'm trying to go as fast as I can.
Numbers, numbers, numbers.
What? Is that you?
This is an all frequency message.
Are you contacting me?
My name is Jeremy Stan.
Are you writing this?
You're almost at the end.
You need to beat this.
This is the only way you get the join session on your story mode.
I'm limited by the teleport.
If you want to keep going, I'm sitting on the ground and I'm going to wait for you.
Okay, I'm going.
I'm going.
So you tell me I just got the assault rifle?
You have to kill like a giant group of things and you might get past this military base and you're done.
Did I walk by something?
Yeah.
Someone in President's sleep was in chat.
I'm sorry.
We didn't know this was going to happen.
Just wake up.
Just wait until we play Desert Bus.
Save your resident sleepers for Desert Bus.
Okay, I made it through another room.
Is it a drill?
Skip that room.
Skip this room.
It's like a safe house, right?
Is it?
I don't know.
Is this like the army wants you or something?
You want the army guy.
Are you sure I don't go in this house with a big red door?
I guess.
No.
I need a drill.
I got the radio.
Hello.
Okay, you just have to follow the instructions.
Don't get distracted.
And as soon as you finish everything.
What do you mean as soon as I finish everything?
You go into a whole other room with a bunch of guns and he gives you like tutorial number two.
I thought you said I was done.
And then you're done.
Just follow instructions.
And then we could play for like 10 minutes.
Mom's calling me for supper.
Put the radio on the left shoulder of your backpack.
It's right there.
Put it on your back.
Wait, what?
What is I'm going to put this like fucking scholastic tablet in my pants on your butt?
Thank you.
Weapons.
I got something to say.
Why not just have this room have all the like tutorials in it?
And it's like you can play around.
Make sure you figure out how you understand how the game works.
I don't know, man.
Because this is tutorial room two.
Why don't I have like a bigger tutorial room zero here?
I don't know, man.
You lied to me.
You said I was done.
I'm begging you to play something else.
No, guys.
Give it a chance.
Just wait.
Just give it a chance.
We've put in so much time.
We're almost there.
Got it.
Do you know how to do it now?
I can't.
It's fine.
You should be able to carry also smaller ones.
Didn't we already do this?
This feels like what should have been the tutorial.
I'm confused.
Testfully complete course to become a thought-becoming mother figure.
407 days later, that's what it feels like.
Yeah.
Chapter one.
Bad Satan.
There you go.
Can we do it?
On your tablet, you should have a find a game.
Find a game.
Search for an available session or join a random session.
Refresh.
Got it.
You did it.
Just wait.
Don't say that yet.
Don't say that.
Instead of new players, join the game.
All right.
Now, how do I change my controls again?
Oh, I can hear you in game.
Don't move.
No.
Trust me.
That's fucking terrifying.
Wow.
Do you want to come join me?
Yeah.
Is there?
Can I?
All right.
Wait, wait, wait.
You ready to go kill some zombies?
Not yet.
Stay there.
You left.
Just wait.
I have to change.
The teleports make me sick too.
We're almost there.
Just another minute.
Just everybody relax.
Calm down.
You've been very patient.
And I appreciate the fact that probably only 600 or 700 people left.
Okay.
I'm doing movement type pad and stick.
Is that what you have?
I don't remember.
Did you pad and stick?
I think so.
All right.
Story.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Get fucking calm down about this.
Turn the audio down.
You got it.
Okay.
All right.
Invite me again.
No, don't invite me.
I got you.
I can't see the viewer count.
How many people are here?
I can't see.
Like 15.
Did everybody fucking leave?
Just about to get crunked.
I am so sorry, guys.
I'm so sorry.
That took way too long.
This game is going to be fun.
We'll make it up for you in Desert Bus.
We're going to make it up to you guys when we play Desert Bus.
Welcome to VR.
That's right.
I'm talking to you.
I know where I am.
There you are.
There he is.
It's me.
Hey, turn around.
Look at me.
What are you doing?
Let me just do this.
What are you talking about?
Okay, get the fuck off me.
Get the fuck off.
Get the fuck away from me.
Get away from me.
Get the fuck out of here.
I ain't going to fucking have that happen.
I'm ready to fight the zombies.
What happened?
How did I make a pretzel?
What is this?
What am I holding?
What?
I don't understand how this happened.
I can't do it.
On my screen, it's some sort of interpretive dance.
Just wait for Desert Bus.
You guys are going to be fucking lit up for it.
Oh shit.
Did I rip it out?
No, I'm good.
Okay, that was fucking out of control.
Alright, let's play this goddamn game.
Stop!
Stop, you dick.
What?
You're going to kill me.
It's killing me.
Do you understand?
Wish I could be so lucky.
Am I going to revive?
Oh no, did it boot us?
I think it booted us.
I'm here.
Okay.
I'm right here.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Alright.
We took so long to get here.
Give me one of these.
What are you doing?
Stop.
Alright.
No!
I need to live!
Kids!
I can't, we have to...
It's not...
You know this is going to be better than the game.
Is it though?
Are you sure about that?
Positive.
Alright.
Where are you?
Soldier.
Why do you have to keep sitting on the ground?
Because otherwise I'm like up here.
You're like eight frames a second by the way.
The game is not like, you are not supposed to be here.
This is going to be very odd.
That's so fucked up.
That's not normal.
Alright, soldier.
Is it fucking huge?
You don't have to look, just cock it.
It's already got bolts in it.
You put that in your ear.
You put that inside of your...
You're storing that like a hamster.
Come on.
You think you can shoot me?
Is that what you think?
Alright, your turn.
Let me see if I can shoot you.
Okay.
Which way is the right way?
Are we ever going to know what happens to Santa?
No.
Oh, you wrecked my face.
Alright, is there a sniper rifle?
Yeah, over here.
This is so awkward.
Alright, so I want a scope on this.
This might be the scope.
No, it's right over here.
Is this the scope?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, there we go.
That's not working.
Catch it, catch it, catch it.
That's not working, you claymation motherfucker.
How does this go on?
How do you put on scopes?
I didn't even get a chance to dodge.
You holding the scope in one hand?
You're a genius.
This got so much more fun.
This is Groundhog Day.
It really is, but it doesn't matter.
We'll get it out of our system in 20 minutes.
Alright, let's...
No, get away from me.
One in each ear.
Oh, my hand.
Day 407.
Alright, we've got to stop.
I think grenades in this game.
I hope so.
Fucking ridiculous.
Find a grenade so we can play with one.
What's over here?
That's not a grenade.
Go look under there for a grenade.
No friendly fire with melee, apparently.
Alright, okay.
We're done.
Drop it.
Right now.
I'm shooting you.
You won't.
Oh, yeah, hey.
What's up?
What's up, right, man?
Huh?
No, no, hold your hand up.
What are you doing?
See?
No, I did the fucking movie thing with the guy with the action leg.
Hey, man.
Hey, man, hey, man.
No, hey, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
Hey, man.
Come on.
One in the chamber.
Okay, 4-0-7.
I am so caught up in this.
It's not even funny.
This is the game.
We have to, okay, it's time to play the game for real.
You have to leave.
I'm not going, I'm going to wait until you leave the room.
Okay, well, we've got to get equipped.
I'm going to get equipped.
Okay, you've got to, wait.
What's your loadout?
I've got to tell you, my favorite gun is, okay?
Okay.
My favorite, what do you think it is?
Nope, wrong, idiot.
I thought we just talked about how we were going to play the game, and now I'm like
injured.
I'm dead.
Stop.
I'm going to shoot you.
Oh, yeah?
Is that what you're going to do?
Hey, man.
Hey.
All right, don't even tell, okay, let me tell you something, guys.
Like, it did, 407 days, okay?
If this is the 407th time you've revived here, at some point, you're going to Bill
Murray.
Don't you do it now.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Quick before, shit.
Hold on, wait, wait.
Can you shoot through you into me?
Is it possible that you can, like, blow a hole through you and me?
Try to shoot yourself in the face.
How do you always like that?
Can you, okay, wait, can you, like, outstretch your hand?
I don't know what's going on with your head.
No, you just shot me.
I need a hand gun.
Wait, I'm smaller than you.
Hold on.
I am much smaller than you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stay there.
No, no, no.
I'm going to die.
Just wait.
Okay, you have to guide me, okay?
I have to what?
You have to guide me.
I'll just get behind you.
I'll line it up.
Okay, line it up.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, that's on me.
It's on you?
Yeah.
Didn't get me.
One of us has to fucking call this quits right now, otherwise we'll never leave.
I'm having a great time.
Never leave.
Just stay in here.
Hey, truce.
It is time for a truce.
Actual truce.
Double high five for a truce.
Double high five.
Oh, that was terrible.
Okay, I actually, like, what are you doing?
Stop.
This is supposed to be...
Yeah, hit me.
Oh, yeah?
What am I doing?
It's his fault.
He keeps doing it every time.
I'm the bigger man here.
No, you got to...
Literally.
I'm not leaving.
No, I am leaving right now.
Fine.
Ow.
Okay.
Stock up.
What's...
Okay.
Like I was saying before, what is my favorite gun?
You have to find it.
If you can find my favorite gun, then nice.
That's a bad gash on you.
You fucking idiot.
You ran out of time.
That's all right.
It's this one.
The default handgun.
Don't make me look like an idiot.
It's...
Where's the deagle?
This is a deagle, right?
Yeah, that's a deagle.
Is this a deagle, Chet?
Which one of these is the deagle?
The bigger one.
This is the big one.
Will you get away from me?
Okay.
That...
This is the one I like the most.
I like to do the dual...
What's his name?
Deadpool?
What is it?
Does Deadpool have two handguns like this?
Do you know?
Come on!
Can you just get some guns and slide them to the door?
Just get a few guns and slide them to the door.
I don't care what they are.
Look, I'm just going to take...
Whoa.
Okay.
No, no, no, no.
Just because I did it to you doesn't mean you should do it to me.
Oh.
You didn't do it to me.
I'm going to quit the game.
I was getting ready.
Oh, yeah.
You were doing the crab shotgun walk.
No, the one before that when you shot me in the head twice.
Yeah, but I couldn't help it.
That's a shit excuse.
No, okay.
I'm getting ready.
Okay?
We're going to go shoot zombies.
Don't even look at each other.
Don't look at me.
I like that.
I'm sorry.
Get first aid.
First aid is over here.
You didn't take that, by the way.
Okay.
You didn't take any of those.
I just want to make sure you're aware of that.
You did not pick up one of those.
I did.
No, you didn't.
I heard the zip.
Why?
They're all on the ground.
Hey, open your eyes for a second.
This is the second time you've done this.
Yeah.
You got it.
Okay, let's go.
Time to go.
Out that door right now.
I don't care if you're ready.
Go.
I don't have a handgun.
After you.
I'll get the fucking door.
Wait.
Flashlight.
Give me the flashlight.
Wait.
I need a flashlight.
Don't move.
I need an attachment.
No.
Who cares?
I'm going.
I got a regular flashlight.
Oh, wait.
Yeah.
Where's the attachment?
Oh, that sucks.
I'm not doing that again.
That's sticky keys?
Here they are.
All right.
Where?
Chapter one.
How do you attach this shit?
Who's saying uh-uh?
Yes.
That has to be done.
How?
Just go.
Everyone in the chat was fucking screaming at me to shoot you.
They would like crouch down here and wait for him to shoot him in the back of the head.
And I was like, guys, we have to play the goddamn game.
I grabbed that.
Huh?
I'm going to get you.
Oh, you should.
All right.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Oh, we have the map.
Yeah.
You get the map?
How do you go to that way?
I don't see.
Can you see it?
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go.
We're going to the white zone.
Okay.
We're going to the white circle.
White circle.
Go.
Shoot him.
He shot me.
I didn't shoot you.
My screen's red.
We've got to go back.
Why do I have to go back?
I didn't bring any health.
Maybe it was just his blood going on me.
I don't know.
I'm waiting for you.
I'm over here.
Can you see me?
Okay.
I'll go first.
That actually looked kind of cool.
How do I run faster?
You have to aim your gun down, then you move faster.
You do?
I think so.
If you have it up and aiming, you move slower.
You have to have your hands down at your side.
Hey, we're going this way.
Okay.
We look like fucking assholes right now, by the way.
Just wanted to make sure you're aware of that.
Double cleave.
Make sure you're aware of that.
Nice work.
What is this?
Oh shit.
Give it, give it, give it a go.
Help, help, help, help me.
Good job.
I don't have a light.
I can do what Leon Kennedy does.
You want this?
Uh, yeah.
Good.
Oh my fucking god.
You were like the most unprepared mercenary.
unprepared mercenary. I see. I'm dropping my guns, there's my flashlight, I'm like wait hold on.
All right, like let's go. I don't even care, we're going. Just shine your light.
You know you left your rifle here. I don't have any more ammo for it. Watch out behind you.
Whoa whoa whoa! That's why. Is there a clip in here? I have any fucking idea. All right,
put your guns down and move. Hold on, cover me. All right, covering you. All right,
I want to look at this map. Yeah, we gotta go left here. Right here? Hey! Hold on. We're even
pretty heavy over there. I know I gotta. How do you aim this? I'm just putting on like cologne,
right? Let's move. Is it down here? Yeah. All right, I'll tell you something. I will tell you.
It is so sweaty in my visor right now. It's like I have goggles on and I'm under water.
I just want to make sure that you're aware of that. Okay. I'm not at 100% right now. I'm
at like 30% vision. Where are we going? We're going the right way, right? Yeah.
There's like a... How many bullets do I have? Behind you. Behind you. Watch out.
I gotta be out of bullets. That's like 10. Yeah. Hey, you know when you go into a pool that...
Stop doing that. You know when you go into a pool and the pool is like a public pool
because a bunch of kids like shit and piss in the pool and stuff? Yeah. And then when you
get out of that pool, all you see is the haze surrounding everything. The lights all have
rainbows on them and shit. You're saying you're the kid that shit in the pool?
Precisely. Pretty much. Like when you go underwater in a public pool and you open
your eyes, shit is flowing into your eyes. It's clean shit. It's been cleaned. Hey. Hey,
Donnie. Bet you can't hit that Zed from here. I bet you I can if you just give me a minute
here. One shot. One shot, Donnie. The new player has joined the game. Oh, no.
How did we get here? It's better not be like a hacker. Hold on. I'll get it. Was the Zed?
All right. Where is it? You're lagging so much now. Which one? Either. Pick one.
But you can't wait till he gets that close. Come on, Donnie. My turn. Watch out behind
you. Don't worry. I'll take care of it. Oops. I'm getting hacked. All right. I see a safe
house. You're doing all right. Are you putting me out here? Is this like the let's play a game
with Jerma and then when his back is turned? Oh, no. We're going to go this way. I don't
have any weapons left. I need to switch this, by the way. I don't like this, by the way. I
don't want to do this, by the way. Oh, inside of there. There's a house. I don't know what
this green arrow is. The green circle. Uh oh. What? No. Got it. Jack's activated. Watch out.
It's the clock tower, girl. Back me up here. Back me up here, please. I am. Uh oh. Back me
up. Back me up. Back me up here. Star. Star. Star, I don't know what to do. I'll shine the
light on you. Shoot him. Where's my guns? All right. Jesus. OK. Why can I not take that?
There we go. All right. I'm helpful. I'm your personal floodlight. You tell me where you want
it to shine. Why don't we check the houses? There might be ammo because they don't have
anything. Can I have your axe? I have a lot of ammo. Dad, can I have your axe? Can I play
the axe? Do you need ammo? Yeah. What is, what guns is for? I don't, I don't have
this kind of gun. Oh, well. It's not the right gun. You can't hit me or no? No. OK,
someone, someone is outside. You have to go with him. But you have a drain? Uh,
let's go, let's go. One, two. There may have been a misunderstanding.
A player has left the game. He was just trying to help. He was trying to help. He was a good
guy. And you just fucking blew him away. He came up behind us. Yeah, but he's, zombies
don't talk. Where am I? Where's my character? Did I like pull a cord out? What? Am I
running around? I covered my headset. Hello, I'm here. Hi. Hi. Did I put like sweat on
the headset? Is it like, doesn't know where I am? Wait a minute. OK, hold on. This is,
hey, kill me. It's a bug. Just shoot me. Just, OK. Oh my God, that was fucking
outrageous. Are you killing me, please? You're dead. Guy comes in to like help.
It's like, hey, we're gonna go this way. It says a full three or four sentences. I thought
he was a zombie, right? He was a zombie. But he got even worse. I can't see anything.
I was trying to protect you. Oh, that was fucking ridiculous. He just wanted to help.
And then he was like, he was like, this guy sucks. And he left. I feel like we've
done this so many times. I'm like, I'm going to work again. You know what I mean?
All right, just get the fucking ammo. Hey, watch out. There's a zombie behind you.
I think this person has full leg tracking, by the way.
You're a zombie. Prove you're not a zombie. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't
do it. Put it down. She's infected. No, no, they're not. Stop. No reason.
Put it down.
Only one of us is making it out of here alive. It's gonna be me.
Okay, I'm done. I'm out of here.
All right. Let's get this show on the road. Day four. Let's get ready. Let's get ready.
Let's go. Let's get ready. Okay. What time is it? All right. Let's go over here.
I just clucked in. I was like fucking goofball clown stream. There it is. Okay,
here we go. Let's go over here. Hey, I pick up the sniper rifle. That's what I do typically
on the first day. You know, grab two of these, three of these. Well, let me load that one.
Okay. Where's where are those sites? You know, the sites are up here, I think.
I don't know how to put them on. I think they go like this somehow.
But they never actually attach. I think it's very different gun
because they keep saying no way. That's the only sniper rifle. Why would like
this big scope isn't going to go on here? It keeps saying whoops. I just put that into my head.
I just like video drone that into my head. Maybe we should do the tutorial.
Maybe we should have done the tutorial. Hey, hold on. Hey, look at me.
Hold on. Let me get a good close look at you. You might need to have a little bit
of skin work done on your pores there. I can't even see you. Well, don't shoot it.
Don't do it yet. Don't do it yet. You're going to do it right here. Right through the
scope. What the fuck am I looking at here? Like what you see. Hold on. This is like upside down.
It is upside down. Am I missing something here? Oh, there we go. Mounting a scope on a scope.
That almost worked. I can't fucking. All right. I want to get something attached here.
What was it? Was it grip? They keep saying no. I feel like with the flashlight on this one,
I just put it near the area and it attaches. I don't even have to press anything.
Somebody help us out here. Read the sign. Read the sign. Read the sign. Read the sign.
Out here. Read the sign. Oh. Anybody see sign? No, the sign's right here. Sign.
You need to find the journal to be able to attach things. What? What do you mean find the
journal? Look right here. Where? Oh, that. Right. All right. So aren't you able to mount
an attachment? Find related in three seconds. Try to shoot each other in the journal. Three,
two, one. I missed that other guy. I know. Yeah, I do too. I would have loved to have another
player here to have fun with and like know what they were doing, know what he was going.
But no, I have to shoot that guy. I have to shoot him. I have to unload a whole
clip on him and then I have to like. To be fair. Do a die hard bit with him.
The second time I shot myself. Yes, you did. Okay. What else? What other games do we have?
Desert bus. Desert bus. We're not doing desert bus yet. That's the 12 hour stream for later.
What's the other one? Tabletop tennis. Nobody wants to see that shit.
No one wants to see that shit. Nobody wants to see that shit. It's fun,
but nobody wants to see that shit. We also got. We got two more. What are the other three games?
I have no idea. What are they? Oh, bar fight. Oh, the bar fight game. Yeah,
we're going to play bar fight. Tabletop tennis. And then desert bus.
We can go do bar fight. You want to do bar fight?
I want to. Hey, let's do one PVP. Do is jet island multiplayer. I actually
brought up jet island to this guy here, but they said, what did you say? You can,
you can explain it. I don't remember what is jet island.
The way you go really fast and you have those tethers.
You said that you were going to throw up if we played. Oh, no, that was gun haven.
I said I would vomit over gun haven. Well, if you're going to throw up,
I don't know what jet island is. Oh, he, guys, he doesn't even know
what jet island is. He can't even play gun haven. All right, you want to do PVP?
PVP outside of here, though. No bullshit. You only get one gun.
Well, no, no, no. We'll get all the, what do you call those guns?
You got a ton of guns on you. Go out that door. I'll go out this door
and like inside the fenced area, PVP. What do you mean? What's the fenced area?
Like right outside this whole area is fenced in.
So you're talking about like out of this room. No, no, no. Get back in here.
I want to examine your shit. Come here. Let me see.
In case you have, you have a large supersized Uzi. You have a regular Uzi.
Okay. Is that all you have? That's it.
Okay. I have a handgun in my pocket.
Okay. I'm going to go with handgun. It was a very stupid way to pick that up.
Okay. Gun safety. Okay. Gun.
I'm also going to go. Are we allowed to have first aid?
No. Okay. Fine. Oops.
What are you doing? Never mind.
All right. I'm going with this. This speaks to me. This is all I need.
Okay. I'm going out there. So we're going to do like,
are we doing a 10 paces thing and then we'll turn around and let go?
No. We're just, as soon as you're out here, if we see each other.
Okay. So we're out like this door here. You mean like out here?
No. The other door. Okay. So I'm going.
You ready? You're not doing it right.
You don't understand. No, you don't understand.
I don't want to hit the wall. I'm like, I'm trying to associate myself.
So I don't hit the wall. Go outside.
I'm just tangled. God damn it.
Hold on. I'm just tangled up here. All right. Let's go. You ready?
What? Oh, shit. It's me.
All right. That's two out of three. Handguns only. No, like no rapid fire bullshit.
We're talking about weapons that were like before like the 1900s.
You know what I'm saying? Only single shot handguns.
Yeah. Weapons that were like used in the civil war.
Only single shot handguns. Weapons that were created back in the 1930s.
None of this bullshit. None of this like rat tat tat bullshit.
We're talking shotgun pistol. I'm just it's pistol time.
No, no, no, no. I went back in the 1950s.
They didn't have flashlights on their guns.
Fine. You will pull that. You only get one handgun by the way.
I don't know. One shotgun. I'm ready.
I'm turning to yell at that to you for some reason.
I'm outside. I'm ready. Wait, wait. Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
I'm just making sure you're ready. Are you ready?
I'm ready. I'm coming.
Trying to get my foot in here.
Coming.
Sitting there entrenched.
I'm trying to like bait you. I've got the flashlight bouncing.
All right. That's two out of three.
Just get a handgun. No shotguns.
Oh no. You know what? Fucking handguns only.
Only handguns. No slappers.
No. No handguns. Only flashlight.
Okay. Hold on a minute here. Let me go.
Okay. Just making sure it works.
You're going to die. I'm right behind you.
I mean, I still have my gun. God, just deal with me.
Oh, you fucking liar. You liar.
Post. Host bullshit. Host bullshit.
Got him.
That was actually fun.
Like I didn't want to play the PVP military VR games because it seemed.
What, Pavlov?
Yeah.
What do you got against Pavlov?
Nothing. Now that we've had the 1v1.
We were going to play Pavlov.
This is a mess underneath me.
All right. Last one. Sniper rifles only.
Okay. You ready?
We've got to count to like 30 seconds, by the way.
Yeah.
What? How? How are you doing that?
What?
How did you? I don't know who you were.
I flanked you.
All right. This game's fun.
We were doing a lot of shit talking at the tutorial.
Because the tutorial isn't good. Everything else.
This is really fun, though.
I could see like getting two, possibly three people in here.
And the third person like kind of knows what they're doing.
It's like trying to give like some advice.
Fun, I think.
All right. I'm going to get some water.
You want to take like a two minute break?
Sure.
Just to get out of the headset. Get some water.
Drunken bar fight or?
Drunken bar fight is next.
Or bus next.
How long have we been going?
That's a good question. Let's find out.
Just about two and a half hours.
We'll do drunken bar fight.
And then from drunken bar fight we'll go to a desert bus.
Okay.
So go grab yourself a water and we'll return.
I'm going to hydrate up.
Don't you need to get drunk for that?
Theoretically, no.
I've been drunk this whole time.
All right. Be right back.
Hello.
We are just waiting for stir.
And then we can continue with the drunken bar fight.
As we'll just get it open now.
Oh, you're here.
Okay.
Yep.
Now let's figure out how we jump into this as a team.
I missed. I missed massive bits, did I?
Let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see.
Yeah, yeah, we did.
Bloody doctor.
Thank you, bloody, if you're bloody doctor, if you're still here.
Is a 50 dollars, 5,000 bits from bloody doctor.
Thank you so much.
Sorry I missed it.
I was immersed in virtual reality.
But they said you should mute stir on discord and use the in game voice.
It's more immersive, but it's not as crisp.
Yeah, we're all about crispness here.
You're not as crispy.
Oh, by the way, I just burped and tasted food.
So I'm going to tell you a little story about a dream I had last night.
You're going to like this one.
So you're, you're aware of the chef Gordon Ramsay, right?
Um, yes.
So I had a dream that I went to one of his kitchen nightmares restaurants.
With him.
Me, Kim and Gordon Ramsay, it went to one of his kitchen nightmares.
I like the idea.
I'm coming back to check on it.
You know, he does that sometimes.
I was there for some reason.
I don't know why.
So we sit down at the table.
We try a bunch of the food.
He's ordering a bunch of shit.
And me and Kim are like, oh, this is delicious.
This is great.
He's like, what do you think about that?
Isn't that much more tender?
We're like, yeah, it's great.
So anyways, we eat like, I don't know, a hundred dollars worth of food
and the check comes.
And I was having like this in dream panic of do I have to pick up this check?
And Gordon Ramsay was like kind of looking at it.
I was looking at it with like, I was like, is the show paying for this?
I didn't say that.
And like, I kind of got up and was moving around this check.
Like that check is laying on the table and neither one of us are touching it.
And then I woke up panicking.
It could be worse.
It could have been way worse.
Yeah.
But like that it was weird.
It was an actual dream.
I had a dream recently that was I told my stream.
I mean, Donald Trump were laying in bed together staring at the ceiling
and he was telling me how bad he felt.
And I was just listening to him and I felt bad for him.
And then I woke up.
Yeah.
He was like, people really don't like me anymore.
It's really weird.
Scott, let me tell you.
I don't know what it is about people.
They don't like me.
I don't know why.
All right.
Are you inviting me?
Yeah.
Okay.
I just clicked a hey German meet me at the bar.
You know, you know, I really wish you'd make TF2 videos again.
It really, I would love that.
All right.
Uh, the first thing he said, hold on.
I can't hear you.
Don't talk.
Oh, but there's a guy that drives.
Yeah.
There's a guy that drives by the house like 15 times a day going like
40, 50 miles per hour in a God damn neighborhood.
Just making an appearance on every stream.
Hold on.
Oh, yeah.
Why are you doing this to me?
Headset.
All right.
One more drink of my officially not sponsored Canada dry ginger ale.
And I mean that for real.
It's not.
Okay.
Can you see me?
You guys can't see anything.
Why?
Oh, that's why.
Ginger ale isn't hydration.
There's plenty of water in that.
Ginger ale just like when you drink ginger ale.
It instantly forms gas.
It shoots out of your system.
It's the worst soft drink because I love it though.
All right.
What's new?
Waiting, waiting for you at the bar.
Said you'd be here looking at my, looking at my watch.
Said you'd be here.
Okay.
So where are you at?
Hold on.
Don't don't don't don't don't.
Nobody move.
Now you can move.
Hey, Jerma, meet at the bar.
How do we do that?
Meet at the bar.
How do you have two hours in this game?
That's how long I've been waiting for you.
If you've already played this.
No, I've been sitting here waiting at the bar.
1.8 hours.
All right.
How do I accept your invite?
I don't know.
No, this is wrong.
Meet me at the bar.
Why did you play drug and bar fight?
I pressed the button.
Help me.
I don't know.
That's all I can do is invite you.
Messages on top.
Top right you see messages.
Show keyboard.
Drug and bar fight.
I don't have anything from you.
How do I?
I have six things from you.
Click.
No, I don't want to join.
It's Alex's Rimworld stream.
All right.
I'm going.
Play game.
I'm trying.
I'm promise.
Did you go off?
I believe you.
No, I'm I'm in the bar.
You accepted an invitation.
Okay.
What the fuck is happening?
Are we here?
Are you in there?
Are you in the bar?
I got a loading screen.
There you are.
That's you.
Hey, what's a good country band to get into to sell my look?
I don't know which one is you.
I'm the one sitting at the laptop.
Hey, behind you.
Anyone got anything that'll wake me up?
You're sitting over here.
That's you.
I'm sitting at the laptop.
You trying to start a fight?
Something fucking weird is happening.
What?
Why?
Okay.
What's going on with my room here?
Why?
What's with my hands?
Come on.
This is such a fucking YouTuber game.
It really is.
It's not like one to one for some reason for me.
Not the napkin dispenser.
Get up.
The bartender won't serve you down there.
Maybe next time you should pick yourself up.
Who's this guy?
Happy New Year.
That was fun.
We did it.
That was it.
You can't just immediately start fights.
He doesn't even know you're doing it.
Let me show you.
All right.
Where are you?
Are you trying to stick his head through?
Are you hitting me?
This is the jankiest game ever.
I'm up.
Oh, he's part of the fight.
Oh, tips.
Oh, I'll take these bits.
I got your back.
No, I got your back.
We're taking out the whole bar.
Get everybody involved.
Get everyone involved.
All right.
Concentrate up.
Strategy, strategy.
We got to start strolling because we got to get everybody before the cops show up.
Okay.
So how do you want to do this?
Get the weapons in the right place.
Everything is a weapon.
This guy's a walking cane.
I'm going in.
I'm going Indiana Jones style.
You ready?
Oh, my God.
Hit him.
Hey, hey, who's whipping me?
I'm trying to get this guy in the fucking teeth.
All right.
Quick, I got to try to get away.
Also, there's another bar.
I don't know how to leave this one now.
No, I didn't mean to do that.
Let's do it.
Where did you get the whip?
Oh, this is my fantasy.
All right.
Come on, come on, come on.
You flew across the whole screen for me.
Get up.
Help me.
Pick me up.
What?
Wow.
This is crap.
What the fuck did we just see?
All those teeth.
Okay.
All right.
This guy's got to go.
What did I just do?
Oh, German.
Hold on.
Emergency.
All right.
I got an idea.
Get a bunch of weapons up there.
We got to fucking push it.
Look at me.
I want to see if this looks...
I was lifting my legs with my own guitar.
Is you going to sit on...
That's so, so fucking stupid.
I'm going to kick you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
How are you doing that?
All right.
We got to...
Hold on.
Whose phone is this?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to do that.
Here.
Open your mouth.
No, no, no.
You.
I'm drunk.
Hey, open up, bro.
Open up, bro.
Devil's Cocktail.
I call this one.
The bartender won't serve you down there.
Maybe next time you should pick yourself up.
Come on, bro.
Yeah, it's...
Cherry sauce, vodka, and a Guinness.
I don't know how to go to the other bar.
I don't know how to do anything.
Can we just walk out the door?
I couldn't walk all the way there.
All right, let's go.
I'm done.
Turn my way.
I can't...
You get stuck here.
You get the fuck out of here.
Get out of here.
Did he just drop kick me?
I think he did.
Oh, boy.
The bartender won't serve you down there.
Maybe next time you should pick yourself up.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I've got the play.
Come here, come here.
Have you seen me?
What's the play?
I want you are going to one-v-one mail him.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, what's going on, bro?
What do you want to do?
I want you...
You can take that guy on.
What's up?
That guy right there?
That guy in the bar.
Yeah.
That fucking piece of shit.
What'd he do?
Did he talk shit to you?
He said I look like Mickey Mouse.
Oh, man, bro.
I'll just...
Wait.
Hold on.
You good?
Man, come on.
Light up.
You good?
All right.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, excuse me.
My buddy over there.
Uh, you tell me he looks like a fucking cartoon character?
Is that what you said?
Mickey Mouse.
Kind of like that fucking Mickey Mouse fucking necklace you got on, right?
Finish him.
All right.
Don't you ever say shit to my friend again.
What are you looking at?
Fucker.
I can't even look.
You don't have to.
Next time, you should pick yourself up.
This is like 0.1% of GTA if it was in VR.
Oh.
Dude, you should have seen.
You're going like this, man.
It's fucking hilarious.
I miss my fucking laptop.
All right.
Can we get out of this bar?
Don't fight me, buddy.
Just wait.
Just walk out here.
Hold on, man.
You sicko.
All right.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Was that fucked up?
You could never leave.
All right.
Just right.
I didn't do anything.
Why are you fighting me?
I didn't do shit.
He's the one guy.
Your character is so fucking lanky.
Maybe next time, you should pick yourself up.
All right.
Exit menu.
Hit menu.
I don't know how.
Oh.
Let's hit menu to get out of this bar.
All right.
Let's go to another bar.
What is the menu?
It's top right button on the bar.
Trigger to play again.
Okay.
No, I left.
Are we together?
No.
I can invite you to the other bar.
I think there's only two.
Let's go to the other bar.
I'm going to fucking puke.
Oh, no.
There's like a...
Okay.
Hold on.
If I get KO'd, you have to pick yourself up.
Can you go in the elevator?
Oh, shit.
You can go in the goddamn elevator.
I don't see you online to invite anymore.
Oh, no.
There's a bar up top, too, man.
Yeah.
That's where I am right now.
I'm at the supply party.
Are you here?
Should I invite you?
No, because we have to actually join each other.
Yeah.
How did you join off the invite?
Uh, I just...
So I went to the...
This is going to be a bad...
It's going to be a problem here.
You go into your, like, SteamVR menu.
Oh, I'm going to, like, mess...
You got me?
Hey, German, meet me at the bar.
Are you coming to me?
I send you an invite.
Okay, I'm coming to you.
When you see this shit, you're going to be, uh...
You're going to be a little, uh...
You're going to be a little shocked by what you see.
How are the cops going to get up here?
I don't know.
Are you...
Did I join you?
I don't think so.
I don't see you.
You accepted an invitation.
Do I have to leave?
You accepted an invitation to play drug and bar fight.
Okay.
So, meet me at the bar.
I might have to leave.
Yeah, I got to be, like, in the...
I got to be, like, in the main venue.
I once cured the shingles, and then I realized I could make more money.
What is this?
Oh.
Man, lots of low-flying planes around here.
Okay, I think it just said, yes.
Sir, please don't speak with me.
My therapist recommends I don't talk to you.
Okay, I have, like, a phone.
Wait, let me just get the fuck out of here.
How do I fight?
Sir, where are you?
Sir?
There we go.
Okay, all right.
All right.
It loaded me in, finally.
I'll go find you.
Watch out.
I'm going to use my new technique.
You got a new technique?
You okay?
I once cured the shingles, and then I realized I could make more money.
Oh, no.
You, uh...
You want a drink?
Here, come here.
Come here.
Have some of this.
Yeah.
This is the most uncomfortable I've done in my life.
You want some?
That's my wall.
Go over here.
Yes.
Can you pop that open?
No.
All right, come on.
Ready?
Oh, they're all coming.
Behind you.
What?
I can't pick myself up.
How do you pick yourself up?
The bartender won't serve you down there.
No, no.
Maybe next time you should pick yourself up.
You still alive.
You're still fine.
Is that a firecracker?
Did you shoot a Roman candle?
There's like...
There's these whole big...
I don't know how these are called, but it blew up.
Whoa!
Wow, that's so funny.
Watch out!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Stop it!
Watch out!
I don't understand.
All right, no more.
I gotta like pick you up?
Yeah, if I go down, you can come over and grab me and pull me up.
All right, hold on.
Sometimes it works.
Come here for a second.
What is this?
I didn't mean to.
Look, I'm drunk.
I want to do something.
Oh my god!
Come over here.
Come over here and uh...
Dad, mom, dad, yes.
You know what I mean? Put your hand here.
Right?
My wall's right there.
Hold on.
Oh shit, my wall's right there too.
Ow!
I can't.
Right?
I'm going for the bombs.
No, don't go for the bombs.
Get that out of here!
No!
Nobody else was even remotely involved.
No one, no one is bothered.
Maybe next time you should pick yourself up.
These two assholes.
Playing with toys over here.
Like killing each other.
All right, okay.
Did you take pictures?
How does this work?
That wasn't very good.
Excuse me.
I'm just looking.
Let's go.
Come over this way.
Nobody's talking anymore.
This is my sister's wedding.
I give it two years.
No, no, wait, wait.
You wait.
I'm waiting.
I'm just joining the conversation with my vase that I brought.
You're trying to like...
Feed Jeff Bezos.
This is fucking terrifying.
It's like up his nose.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to see if I can balance it.
Did you ding him?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's he doing?
Wait, give it a whine.
Oops.
Who are we feeding?
That's fair enough.
All right, he's a little bit boozed up.
Perfect timing.
Easy over there.
Hey, you enjoyed the wedding?
You guys enjoyed the wedding?
Yeah, I love this couple.
They're so fucking friendly.
My favorite thing, if you've had the wine yet, it's fantastic.
Hey, if you don't like the three snooges.
Oh, come on.
Damn it.
Hey, my favorite.
Oh, what's this?
Why can't we just sit here for an hour and behave?
All right, here's the deal.
You ready for the game?
Where are you?
The game is you have to let go of that.
No.
Stop it.
I was just doing fireworks for the party.
No, you're going to piss people off.
I'm down?
I got you, I got you.
Okay, all right.
The goal is stand in the...
What the fuck?
All right, when you settle down, Kylo Ren.
Get away from me.
Get the fuck away from me.
It's a crab.
It's going for your legs.
I'm like the kid in the party.
Yeah, you're like the annoying little shit
that's running around and bumping into people.
Wait, I wonder, can they punch me when I'm down here?
I'm just chapped right now.
They just keep punching this lady in the face.
I'm winning this fight.
This is bizarre, I'll tell you.
What about your fucking animals, you know what I'm saying?
Look at your ankles.
Nice.
Get me, get me, get me up, get me up, get me up.
I'm down.
Oh, turn, quick, quick, quick.
Over here.
They're coming.
How do you win?
Do you win?
I don't think you win.
Wait, hold on a second.
Don't hurt anybody, just give me move people.
I want to throw someone off the roof.
Fuck, help me.
I'm down, I'm down.
I'm down, lift me up.
I won't serve you down there.
Maybe next time you should put yourself out there.
What are you doing?
I thought you of all people would appreciate a double middle finger.
Oh, that's what you were doing?
Yeah.
Hey, what do you got to say about these?
Wait, stop.
DJ plays goodbye horses.
That's my favorite song to dance to.
Hey, hey, excuse me.
He tried to run off the roof.
Hey, hey, I'm down.
Help, get me.
Nice.
I can get myself up?
Why can I not take a single punch to the face?
All right, that's it.
All right, come over here.
Come with me.
Don't hurt anybody.
Get over here.
Okay, here's the deal.
I'm going to go on.
I'm going to get support his body.
You support his legs.
We're going to one, two, three, throw them over the edge.
Hold on, stay there.
Okay, so you don't like that the practical is wrong, but you kneel behind.
Yeah, yeah.
You ready?
Ready?
Here, he's kind of come up with his legs up.
It's like grabbing him.
Where are you?
So, you know there's a Halloween version of this game too, right?
I'm sure it changed the game dramatically.
It's going to be 300k in a month.
I piss 300k daily.
My face is as high as I'm supposed to win.
Is that Gilford Godfrey?
It sounds like him.
Is that Dry Bear?
It does sound like Godfrey.
Gilford Godfrey.
I got him.
No.
What, you got him?
He almost went off.
It's really like this.
All right, I'll take two more of these.
This guy's hanging on for his life.
I'm done.
I'm dead.
I died.
It's just the same shit over and over again.
But it's-
Yeah, so how about that desert buzz?
I know.
How about desert buzz, huh?
Hey, actually, you know what?
We need to do the 1v1.
1v1 here?
Yeah.
All right, fine.
It's all about the intimidation factor, guys.
How do I-
Can I turn my body without turning-
I don't think I can.
No.
Hey, you want to see what I got?
Hey, hey, come at me.
You want to come at me?
Are you scared now?
Intimidated?
How about I do it again, huh?
Hey.
You just brought me back to life.
Big mistake.
Are you down?
Okay, I have a headache.
Yeah, I do too.
I have a fucking bad headache.
All right, we got to get everybody.
You ready?
Oh, I have a headache means we're getting everybody.
Well, then we should be throwing bombs.
All right, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, stop, stop.
Slow down, slow down.
We got to get this slow down.
Easy.
Are these candles?
No, these are the bombs.
Make sure they're not like shaky toys.
I'm sure.
Okay.
Ready?
How about-
What's the fuse time?
Oh, God.
I'm seizing them.
I'm allergic.
The bartender won't serve you down there.
I can't even believe you survived until 40.
And then I realized I can make more money.
What?
I just fell over?
This really quickly went from bar fight to acts of terrorism.
Why am I getting switched?
On my screen, I'm standing on top of you.
I snuck up here and sabotaged this place
since they're stealing all the customers from my-
God damn it.
What are you doing?
I'm fucking sitting down, man.
I'm going to fucking pass out.
Looking up at your face.
So fucking-
It's not like this is not-
I don't know.
My-
Something's-
Okay, where am I?
Guys, I understand something.
I didn't do this.
This was another reason why I was laughing.
What am I doing on your screen?
Your arms are crossed like this.
They shouldn't be.
Are you holding the wrong controller?
No, I got the straps on.
There's no way that my hands came out of the straps,
through the other straps.
No way.
That could not have happened, right?
There's no way on the ground.
I don't-
No, that's impossible.
Don't ask me, I have no idea.
No, that makes no sense,
because look, this is my left hand.
You understand?
This is the left hand.
Are you still alive?
The bartender won't serve you down there.
Maybe next time you should pick yourself up.
I didn't see-
My daddy's on bitcoin.
He's gotta be worth 300,000 dollars in about two months.
All right, how do we get out of here?
How do we get out?
Oh my god.
What if we gotta get the cake?
How do we get the cake?
Real helpful.
Bankrupted.
I honestly don't even know how you're doing that.
Can you grab my hands?
Bring me the candle.
This is how I want to go.
No, you dropped it.
Come here.
I want to eat it, I want to eat it.
Oh, I'm up.
I'm up.
This is what a beat up looks like.
Can we beat one level, please?
I got him.
You don't win.
It's a metaphor.
Give me the knife.
Excuse me?
I'm not doing that.
What?
Why did it do that?
Hey, you want a pickle?
Oh no, there's a wine.
I got you, I got you, I got you.
Will you please get up?
No.
Brother!
Could you?
You're just causing me so much fucking anguish.
Protect me.
I read it one.
I'm exhausted.
Let me help you, let me help you, let me help you, let me help you, let me help you.
Give me the- wait.
You're back.
Slowly taking care of this guy.
Are you still alive?
I'm good.
I find you.
Oh shit.
What, this guy's dancing?
This guy's still getting hit by a lag.
How did you get him down there?
You're a monster.
I think somebody just blew his ass in the game.
I gotta get a bribe.
Just keep him distracted.
What?
Hey.
Hey, um, what do I mean?
It closed the helicopter.
I'm so bad.
What the fuck?
Give me this whole toaster.
I'm so bad.
What the fuck?
Give me this whole toaster.
Oh shit.
Come on.
That's the sound you want to hear in VR.
But where are you?
I can't get out of here.
I can't get out, guys.
I cannot leave.
Somebody just- okay.
All right, it's time to stand up.
It's time to stand up.
You know why?
Somebody just said 33-year-old.
I gotta get up.
I have to stand up.
I gotta delete this VOD.
That's all you need to say.
All right, I'm getting up.
I have to delete the VOD.
I'm gonna delete this VOD, okay?
What are you doing?
Me?
Am I alive?
What?
I thought I was dead.
Oh, now I'm in trouble.
Quick, help.
I'm out.
That's not a real table.
Is he- where are you?
Are you gone?
You here?
Bye.
I left.
Totally wasted.
I think we all hear voices in our heads sometimes.
Subverting expectations!
33-year-old.
The bartender won't serve you down there.
Maybe next time-
All right, you ready to take a bus?
Yeah, let's get on the bus.
Let's get on the bus.
I could use a relaxing 8-hour drive to soothe my headache.
Only drink at rooftop bars.
Even if it's the dead of winter.
Okay, uh, you wanna take-
Oh, I gotta-
What?
You're gonna get on a bus?
Yeah, I'm launching it.
All right, how do I do it from my, like, home?
Studio?
I don't know.
Oh my god.
Oh god, it's so loud.
Click on it?
It's not up here.
Like, library?
No, no, where's my library?
Get out of this shit.
Open the Steam menu and go to the VR?
Yeah, yeah.
How do I get the fuck out of this?
Vive?
No, I don't know how to launch a Vive port.
Oh, my hands.
Oh, I gotta fucking put my face out of this.
Oh my god.
I gotta change the title anyways.
Desert bus-
I'm getting a chair if we're doing desert bus.
You don't stand and drive a bus.
I'm standing.
Are you standing for 8 hours?
You gonna do that?
Yeah.
You sure about that?
8 hours, I'll go back on the ground.
Yeah, stand for 8 hours.
It's a great idea.
Oh man, that's fucking funny.
All right, let's do it.
I'm gonna load into-
Let me get a sip of my not-sponsored can of dry.
Go do this and get prepared.
Go use the bathroom.
We'll switch off.
Funny time when you're on the bus.
Yeah, we'll be fine.
Pee before the trip.
We're gonna be fine.
Okay, opening it up.
This is how easy this is to do.
I have no idea how to do a game.
I have to open the steam VR.
Launch desert bus directly in steam VR mode.
Okay.
I think it's working.
You look like you've been through hell.
Kind of have.
That's what it feels like.
Who knew that a fucking funny YouTuber game was gonna be so funny?
I'm gonna drop this volume.
So, people are saying that we need to go take a pee break,
but I don't believe them.
We can switch off.
I'm good.
I'm in the game.
You want to drive?
You want me to drive?
You can take first shift.
It's so filthy in here.
I don't know how to get together in a game, though.
Dude, hold on.
I gotta clean this.
It is filthy in there.
Filthy.
It's like, okay, somebody like came in my room
and put peanut butter in my vibe headset as a prank.
That's how ridiculous this looks.
This is sweat from sweat.
Yeah, I figured it out.
I'm gonna throw in the fucking laundry.
Oh, man.
Did I buy a face pad yet?
Uh, not yet.
Hey, start.
Let me know when you need me to tell you what to do.
I just wanted you to know.
Oh, God.
It was very fun.
Hope you know that.
Before we get to Vegas.
All right, I got the wrong answer.
All right.
So, Tucson city limits.
So, how do we get this going?
Uh, the top right lever, pull that down,
and the card will come out.
And then you'll search for a game.
Okay, do I have to get any parameters
or can we join each other?
I have no idea.
I'm in a game.
You're in a game-found joining.
Okay, it's definitely mine.
Is it?
Oh, I can hear you.
I'm gonna turn off Discord probably.
Are you in here?
Hello?
Are these other people in here?
Yeah.
Um, can you come to the front?
I can't come to the front.
I'm all the way back here.
You can't stand up?
No, because I, uh, I don't have a driver's license
and I have no idea how to do this.
Uh, we might have to...
Can we make, like, a separate game?
All right, here we go.
How do I...
Okay.
Oh, you can...
I can leave.
Why are you leaving?
Hey, you!
How do I get up there?
Like, go like this?
I can't.
What the hell is this?
Are you driving the car?
Yeah.
He's just throwing something at me.
Teacher!
Teacher, he's throwing stuff at me!
You can't switch drivers.
Oh, I can't even walk back here.
Okay, um, this is it.
Turn on the radio.
Sir, sir, this is not how you drive.
I'm gonna fall down in real life.
There's this thing that keeps making my controllers
vibrate, like, harder than I've ever felt.
It's concerning me.
I don't know what this is.
This is more of a dare than a game.
It's supposed to be terrible.
Oh, no, no, no.
Okay, you know what?
What?
Why do you have the police siren?
Uh, uh, I think we're getting towed.
What?
What do you mean we're getting towed?
You're a...
You're a toad!
You're not driving backwards right now?
I'm not driving...
No, we're getting towed backwards
because I drove off the road.
Oh, my spleen just hurts.
And this is back to the beginning.
This tow truck is going like 90.
Can you at least put on music for us?
I left.
Here, you drive.
Me?
How is that possible?
How do I drive?
You have to get back to the menu.
Okay.
How do I pick drive car?
Uh, tell me when you're there.
Oh, you take the time card out of the green box
and you put it on top of the time card clock box,
the clock in.
You don't draw pictures.
Oh, the other card.
Doofus.
This one?
No, put it in the top of the green box.
This guy has never gone to work one day in his life.
Boo!
Are you coming in?
Wait, wait, wait.
Where are you?
Which one are you?
I'm loading.
I'm three seats back right behind you.
Waving.
Hey!
Okay, guys, be good.
Let's get a bit of radio station on here.
How do I change the radio?
Yeah, good luck with that.
How fast can you go?
About this fast.
Oh, that's you hitting the tires on the side.
What?
That's what that is.
What does this do?
What is this?
Is this the radio?
How do I change the station?
Get down from there, this instant!
Behind the yellow line.
You gotta tell your mother about that.
That's gonna be in my write-up.
Fucking asshole.
Just walk through the window.
All right, I'm out.
Already?
We did it in the last one minute.
No, we didn't.
We didn't last one minute.
I thought we'd at least be able to walk around the bus.
Yeah, it didn't last a minute.
Sign in to restart state.
No, no, no.
That's not what we're doing.
You want to do table tennis?
Or are you like tapped out?
Let's do it because we're only going to do it for like five minutes anyway.
Probably.
I'm not sure how you can group with people.
I guess we'll have to find out.
Eight hour stream.
Oh yeah, that was a good eight hours in there.
Within the last fucking 15 seconds.
Is this game good?
Yeah.
Is it? Okay.
You need an entire dedicated weekend for Desert Bus.
Yeah, I can't believe we finished the whole thing either.
That was ridiculous.
We made it all the way to Vegas.
It's pretty cool.
All right, let's open it.
This is like squishing my eyes.
All right, this should be opening.
Drunken bar fight.
Killed me.
Joel beat Desert Bus?
He's good.
He's made out of steel.
Made out of incredible balls.
Why am I already fighting somebody?
Who is this?
Is this tutorial?
I don't get it.
That's tutorial plot.
Okay.
This looks kind of good.
This looks like it could be a lot of fun.
It is actually very, very well physics simulation.
Very well good.
Okay.
If you press the menu button.
There should be a multiplayer.
I've never done the multiplayer.
You're going to have to go real easy on me, man.
Yeah, well, I'm trying to...
Are you Tommy Pickles?
Yes.
I sent you a challenge that I think shows up on your right.
It does.
How do I say yes?
I'm not sure.
Okay.
All right.
Also, if you want it to, like if you go to your computer.
I'm not that tall.
I am.
Not that tall.
You're almost as tall as the top of the staircase.
This is my life.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is very important.
Okay.
Very important.
So you go back to the menu and go to settings.
Settings.
People are going to throw up if you use first person cam,
but you can like make it.
I don't know what the option is.
In game positioning.
Go to the eyeball, the top middle.
Do you have spectator camera?
Spectator camera.
Yeah.
The eyeball at the top middle.
So enable the spectator camera.
Yeah.
It's already on.
Because if you're in first person mode, people will throw up.
It's like 50 field of view.
Okay.
Well, enable spectator camera is checked.
It's definitely is first person.
Uncheck it?
How does this look?
Uncheck spectator?
All right.
No.
That's fine.
It looks all right.
Wait, how do you get the funny mask?
There's the funny mask option.
What?
Uh, yeah, I don't know how to change it because normally you can like
pull the camera to anywhere you want.
Whoops.
I hit my mic.
Yeah.
You smashed your mic.
All right.
I'm ready to just do a little volley here.
Hold on.
My sound is like zero.
One second.
This does feel really good though.
You don't even need a ping pong table.
Just return the one that you bought.
Oh, yeah.
Ah!
I didn't even tell me I was getting that close.
That was bad.
That was like breaks up.
You can move the table around with the left hand trigger.
You can like adjust where you are.
Is this all right?
Oh, that was the worst one yet.
That was the absolute worst one.
That was like I'm trying to break this controller in half.
Yeah.
How do I kick this?
Look, I'm like, look at how far away from the table I am.
How do I do that?
Uh, I don't know because your controller is different.
Left hand trigger.
You hold and you can move the table.
You can be like a tiny boy.
Because like here, I'm too close.
Right hand trigger.
Left.
Remember what I'm saying?
Right.
There's a dent in the wall.
Shut the fuck up.
Don't tell me that.
It's a fucking like new desk too.
Oh, I can see where I fucking made a problem here.
I like chipped it.
Your controller?
Oh, okay.
I see what you're talking about for Spectator Cam.
Nah, it's not doing that because I have OpenVR.
I see what you mean though.
Do you?
Yeah, because when I take my headset off, I can see it.
But I need to figure out how to get this not the way to set OBS to the game capture.
I could just pull it, can't I?
Yeah.
Let me just do that real quick.
Because it creates, yeah, the screen on your monitor is the drag around camera.
Let's see.
Is that it?
There it is.
But the problem is I need to pull this table closer.
It should be one of your triggers to move the table.
I've done them both.
Do I have to physically grab the table?
No.
Anywhere you push, everything turns white and you can move the table.
For me, it's underneath trigger on the left hand.
See, when I press that, I get the ball and then I have menu.
Oh, do the Vive controllers have two triggers?
I have like the buttons.
But like looking at your hand, what does it say?
Menu ball.
Oh, mine has a hold to reposition thing.
Can you move it for me?
No.
Change back.
Switch back.
What's wrong with this?
It's on the right hand.
Okay, right hand trigger.
Not doing anything.
Right hand grip.
Doesn't do anything.
Right hand button.
Not doing anything.
Grips.
Triggers.
Both triggers.
Pads.
Haptic.
Where is this?
Maybe it's in the settings.
Room.
Challenger.
What does your right hand trigger do?
Uh, anything?
Hold on.
Studio.
In game positioning?
Maybe that's what it is and I don't check it.
Let's just see what happens.
Maybe I have that checked.
Okay, there we go.
So it's this.
There we go.
That's my...
Okay, that's a thousand times better.
I think it wasn't selected somehow.
All right, I'm ready.
How close am I to the fucking...
Okay, I'm good.
Actually, I need...
All right, I'm good.
What is happening with my...
I'm so tangled up.
Look at this bullshit, guys.
I'm just seeing a cat head spinning circles.
I probably shouldn't be doing this,
but I have enough strength to be able to do it, I think.
All right, that made it better?
Or worse?
No clue.
It's a mess down here.
Wait, hold on.
All right, fuck it.
Let's go.
Ready?
I'm ready.
You win.
That was it.
I won.
That's the whole thing.
Oh, boy.
It's really weird without sound.
Why are you not playing with sound?
I don't know.
I can't get it to work.
Yeah.
Damn it.
It's in the game.
I just thought about the drunken fight game.
Damn it.
It's in the game.
Oh my.
Is that from the ceiling like that?
Mine's like fucked up here, too.
All right, let's do a ranked match.
You and me.
Ranked.
How do I ready?
What did you do on the left side?
Ranked.
Let me try one more time to get my sound to work.
Jeremy has a weak backhand.
I've got a weak every hand.
First person.
Put the first person cam back on.
See, everyone wants the first person cam, man.
They don't like this like weird spectator mode.
All right, I'm okay.
All right, fine.
If they want to vomit.
I got you, guys.
Don't worry.
I wasn't even...
I tried to...
Yeah, see, you're gonna...
I keep wanting to touch the table.
That's not how it works, Jeremy.
Everyone's doing vomit emotes.
You asked for this.
All right, I'm ready.
I don't know how to ready.
To the left of the table is a...
It says ranked and unranked.
Oh, okay, I got it.
Game one, ranked.
Here, sir.
Okay.
Thank you.
Here, sir.
God damn it.
Here, here we go.
Whoops.
What?
Oh, that was bullshit.
You know what?
You couldn't get that?
That's a fault?
You can't throw the ball over
the line of the table and you still...
No.
Come on, let me get the 30% on you.
What the fuck did I do?
What?
I can't cross the line, bro.
I can turn that off, actually.
All right, I'm...
I got no awareness here.
Turned it off.
This is gonna be tighter.
You ready?
I'm ready.
This really is the most dangerous game.
I've hit the wall more times.
I've done VR streams like eight times.
Oh, God.
Oh, my chair's behind me.
Hit it.
I fucking ate myself.
That's the worst too.
I didn't mean to.
If you hit anything to the corners
then it's like my wall's right here.
How do you do like the fucking curve?
What do I do?
So you go like...
No.
I got it.
You got it.
You're getting it.
I don't know how to do it, okay?
That was your fault.
Whoops.
No, I see what you're doing.
You're doing like you're pancakeing it.
You got a pancake.
What was it on that?
It never hit your side.
Hey, by the way, your apartment sucks.
White brick, dirty windows.
What does that go?
Why do you have a staircase there?
But what is up there?
Your locker is up there?
No, no, no, no, no.
You got a lot of shit to talk.
You haven't even seen my basement.
Had to come down here
when I have some philosophical quandaries
about how much taller I am than you.
Sometimes I just like to, you know,
just wonder how could one person be that short?
We just surf from up here.
I couldn't get down.
Get a little taller.
A little bit taller.
Every point I get.
Wow.
Rating zero to 16.
Cool.
Dude, I'm going to be ranked 10 million soon.
I tried to watch the replay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Does it record voices too?
I don't think so.
Oh, how do we?
All right, let's go again.
Ready?
All right, surf.
Rank it up.
Here's your surf, I think.
Okay.
Pick out these million dollar pieces.
Where do you get that from?
King touch tomb.
Please don't look at it.
It gets older when you look at it.
Just nice and easy.
Nice and easy.
You don't understand.
He plays.
He plays like professional table tennis.
You know, you just start making things up just so you don't look bad.
Oh, what did that happen?
I think the five controls have these big balloon heads.
You know, just got to start making things up.
Why am I just trying to catch that in my groin?
It was like, what's the fucking like glass I can throw at you?
Nice try, but you didn't get it.
What the hell was that?
Like whipple ball bullshit.
Whipple ball bullshit?
Come over here, table.
That's just the I'm done.
I'm done.
I'm good.
That was my mic.
You got me.
Yeah, that's okay.
VR, when you play with a friend, you're just playing battleship.
Like you bumped into the wall.
Like that's C2.
I get a point.
I got to come into your room and put like chairs and shit in the way.
And you have to do it to my room.
VR battleship.
Take this chair out of the way.
I never have it here.
Why didn't you return it?
Did the people say that was a bad joke?
I'm going to name it what?
How dare you?
Seven to six, I'm still winning.
If we're playing beer hockey, what's it called?
Oh my god, you were.
Air hockey.
If we're playing air hockey, I want to do 11.
Yeah, name of the game.
The name of the game is ping pong, actually.
Actually, name of this game is 11, table tennis.
The name of this game is ping pong.
Double nine.
Come on, you stupid game.
I'm not worried.
Your name here versus stir.
Yeah, they think that's the one.
All right, hold on.
I'm watching something.
Is this?
I got to get out of the way.
Who's who?
This is not the whole replay.
What part of the replay are we watching?
I always do like the pancake.
I got a shit.
Oh, was that when he hit his hand?
When does he hit his hand?
Oh, no.
All right, you know something I'm noticing right now?
Look at how much I'm talking and gesturing with my fucking hands.
You really are a moody Susan.
I'm like, let me tell you something.
Do I do this?
Yeah.
Like, look at over there.
He just is a person.
I'm like a cartoon character.
Hold on, stop, stop.
Oh, don't yell at me.
Look at the amount of movement over here.
I'm going to do this at like time's fucking five speed.
Just look at the movement on this side of the table.
This person's being electrocuted.
This person's just hanging out.
Yeah.
Do you understand?
Like, what the fuck is wrong with me?
Oh, my God.
All right, let's do one more.
How do I get out of here?
Do I have to invite you again?
No, I'm the tallest one.
All right, let me get out of here.
All right, back to main menu.
I'm trying to scratch my nose.
What is minigames?
Um, it has a simulated ping pong robot.
Oh.
And different challenges you can do with it.
There's nothing wrong with being an animated talker man.
All right, you got to throw me an invite.
I'm looking.
Can we go to one of the other expensive rooms in your house?
Yeah, it says you're idle.
Idle?
How about now?
I don't know why I can't invite you.
If you go to multiplayer,
and you should be able to scroll and find my name.
Tommy Pickles uses online.
All right, hold on.
Itchy nose.
All right, loading my roof.
Oh, Jesus.
This is bizarre.
I don't like it, though, because the ball is white,
and so is the background.
There's only two good levels.
The other one's like a winter one,
and it also is like really blue.
Oh, this is nice.
This is like whoever loses, the vultures get you.
Las Vegas.
You're going to have to find like a better friend,
because like I'm like a bad player, a friend player.
Hold on.
Same spot.
Shit.
If you got that, I would have I would have S'd your D.
Wouldn't be as animated as you,
so you don't feel bad afterwards.
Oh, speaking of vultures, there they are.
A lot of them.
This level is kind of laggy.
You getting any laggy here?
No, that's fine.
Little deal.
Actually, I am getting it.
I'm switching.
That was really bad.
You should see the part of the controller here.
I'll show it on camera.
All right, give me some tips.
How do I stop doing like the under pancake?
Every time a ball comes, I go.
It's really hard to tell what you're doing
without seeing your arms.
Just watch my stream.
Just turn on my stream.
Do you really think you're going to learn anything?
Just get like VR window and open up my stream
while you stream.
Oh wait, you're not streaming.
Well, technically you are.
Technically, we're all streaming.
Two to six.
I caught it.
It doesn't count.
Whoops.
Like how do you do that?
That like-
Just hit it.
You're like charging up an EX move.
I can like see you doing it.
You go like-
What?
Cause you gotta, you gotta do it.
I can't explain it to you over the internet.
You have a fighting game tell
when you're going to do that.
I feel like I should parry you.
Like I need to go.
Well, parry this.
That's not going to work.
You know, let me know if you want to think about that.
Oh, here's the edge.
The game sucks.
You know, I could see how two table tennis enthusiasts
could really play this and add love every second of it.
It's, it's really-
The physics are-
It's pretty good.
Surprisingly accurate.
I was pointing out on my stream
there's like two things it does wrong,
but they're not-
That big of a deal.
The biggest way you can tell-
You can actually change how much in your paddle has.
Oh, really?
And the options and everything
and change what kind of paddle it is.
That's cool.
But if you have a really spinning paddle
and you just put the ball on it
and you move the ball around,
it's pretty fully accurate to what it would do
and how it would feel.
The feedback when you hit the ball,
that little like knee.
Yeah.
It's like you can actually feel like-
You actually, you know, you feel like Spider-Man.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I know what you're saying.
Ha ha ha.
Fuck.
Hey, pro tip.
You're not listening.
If I swing down,
the ball's going to drop down.
If I swing up, the ball is going to go up.
When you see me doing these big swings
and your paddle's flat,
it's going to go straight down.
Okay, so when you go like this,
go like this.
And when you go like this,
When I go down,
you need to make your paddle like this.
When it hits here, down is forward.
You get it, down is forward now.
Oh, okay.
So like in one of those mirror puzzle games,
where I have to bend the laser.
Yes, you have to bend the laser.
Move the laser with the mirror into the spot
and you get the key.
Yeah.
Okay.
You did it.
That was good.
Why am I hearing voices?
This is the first time you've asked yourself that.
No, no, no, no.
I'm hearing voices.
I swear.
Got him.
That didn't count?
What?
That's my point.
I had to itch.
I have an inside of my nose itch.
See?
Wait, you're in the closet.
Get out of my way.
I was in the closet the whole time.
All right.
How are you doing?
You good?
Watch replay.
Why would you want me to watch this one?
All right.
I'll watch the replay.
Oh, where's the game?
What?
I have the replay.
It's not playing.
Why do you keep watching the replay?
I don't understand.
You just played.
Because Chad's saying watch replay.
All right.
Anything else you want to do?
I could do this forever, so.
You could do this forever.
I get trapped in the loop.
One guy.
Watch the bot, one person says.
Do you have anything else?
Do you have any other experiences you want to just try?
It would be cool if I could show you the minigame, but I can't.
No.
Because you can't actually multiplayer that.
They don't really know me.
Just see.
Oh, listen to the voices.
Let me see what else we got.
Oh, we can go for like four and a half hours or so.
Turret looks really dirty.
I'm just really sweaty.
Pavlov.
Everybody wants us to play Pavlov.
I would play it, but I think we should do it another day.
You want to do it another day?
To get its own thing, yeah.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Playing Pavlov with you.
You want to play Pavlov tomorrow?
Sure.
I don't think I'm doing anything.
I mean, it's up to you.
Yeah, I'm saying yes.
Okay.
Maybe we'll get like another couple to play.
He's bruised.
Yeah, but I have like actually bruised cheeks.
Are we getting desert bus today?
We completed it.
We did the whole thing.
Yeah, it's over.
I'm like so into VR.
Sorry that I'm like a VR streamer.
Like, no.
We had Pavlov onward.
There was a couple others.
Where was that list?
Show controller?
Oh, here, I'll show you.
I don't know if you can see it in the camera,
but like it's I like chipped off like the front here.
See like that.
Like a little focuses right here.
There's like an indent and like it's white.
I like.
Let me see.
Yeah, this is like a bunch of stuff to play.
Are you still here?
Yeah, I can't find where the thing is in this game.
I also want to play like Mind Show.
There's so much like fucking VR I want to play.
But we can call here if you want.
Take a break because the drunken bar fight game.
I act like sometimes I get in one of these games
and like an after an hour goes by
and I'm just getting constant fucking pain from either laughing
or like fucking wheezing.
There's a multiplayer mod for Beat Saber.
Are you serious?
My understanding is just that it shows your scores at the same time.
So you're competing for a better score on the same level.
If there's something else, I don't know about it.
People saying we should play Minecraft in VR.
Oh, yeah, Minecraft.
God, no.
Yeah, we'll play some more stuff tomorrow.
We'll do Pavlov tomorrow.
We'll give like Pavlov like a real
because that's like a full on multiplayer shooter experience, isn't it?
Pavlov?
Pavlov.
I think so.
All right.
Well, that's probably as good as any time to call it for the day.
I'm going to wake up sore tomorrow.
That's the thing.
When I've been playing so much VR,
I'm like building up my muscular tolerance again.
You should do Mind Show for your own full stream.
Yeah, that's why I'm like Mr. VR.
Oh, my God.
How many times did I slam into a wall today?
Like six?
How many times did he slam into a wall?
Like two?
I think it was two.
You sunk my battleship today.
We love the VR.
It's not a problem.
I mean, it's just so much fun.
It's something I've never had this experience before in my life.
So it's worth having.
All right.
Let me get this off.
And we'll start probably on the same time tomorrow if you want.
So thanks for hanging out, everybody.
Yeah, this will be like just about probably like a four and a half, five hour stream.
It's kind of what they've been.
Just only so long I can do it.
But yeah, I'll be in touch.
We'll figure out what games we're going to play.
Bye, everyone.
Say bye.
And like, he has a Twitch, you know.
And I have a YouTube channel where I'm not allowed to upload videos anymore.
That's true.
It's a court order.
Can we get a stirrer link here?
What are you, what's your number one game in?
Apex?
My other, my what?
What's your number one game in?
Like Apex?
Getting dirty club.
I stream it all.
You've really been into that like press the button with the monster voice today.
I like the monster voice because it really
Then you know I'm for real.
No, I got to like, I'm going to physically like type your name.
Dude, I don't know.
It's stir, right?
I don't know.
You change your name sometimes.
Like four years ago.
Who was this?
I don't even know who he is anymore.
We played Lethal League like a week ago.
Relax.
What is your name?
Like German948?
Yeah, we already talked about the forest.
You didn't want to do the forest because of the, it was going to take too long.
Yeah, I didn't, I didn't want a full stream of a full forest stream.
Oh, man.
All right.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
We'll play some more.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Thanks for our first ever collab we did today.
Maybe we can do more.
Yeah.
Now have a good night.
Good night.
Bye.
Yeah.
We'll see you.
Just putting like weird pressure on my eyes and eyebrows and I feel like my eyebrow.
I look like a different like a different person.
It's like squishing my eyelids.
All right.
Let's get to the bits here.
See you guys tomorrow.
It's taking off.
More multiplayer VR.
I'm going to pad my room.
You look weird when you do that.
I look weird probably every day.
Do Google Earth VR.
Can you do that multiplayer?
That doesn't work multiplayer, does it?
All right.
Let's get out of this and put this up.
No, that's not VRB.
We need to see a later one.
There it goes.
Okay.
Let me get out of here.
Payday 2 has VR.
Yeah, I had a fucking lot of fun though.
Even in like rec room and then that zombie game started out kind of a little bit annoying,
but turned out to be absolutely fucking fun.
I could see how if you get four of your friends,
that would be some of the most fun you could probably have.
But no, that's I love it.
So we'll see you tomorrow.
Here come the bits.
Thanks everyone for sticking around.
See you real soon.
And let's go back about four to four and a half hours ago here.
Stirr hosted you with one viewer.
What?
With what?
Him?
Was it him?
Was it he the only one?
Thanks a lot Stirr for those.
That's so funny.
It was just him.
You probably didn't do it right.
Oh my God.
Thank you Divus for the 250.
Appreciate it.
Let me get the chat out here.
The actual chat.
Let me shut down that VR.
Real quick.
Is there a multiplayer horror game?
No, there really isn't.
That's kind of sad and unfortunate.
I was we've been looking.
There really is not a horror VR multiplayer game.
Unfortunately, raw data is kind of horror.
Jet Island, he won't play it.
He already told me he saw me playing that game.
He's like, I wouldn't be able to do it.
It's hard enough to make a good multiplayer horror game
in general anyway.
Yeah, it is.
But thank you to Divus.
Thank you Bake Me Home for the 250.
Thank you Fitty for the five bucks.
This makes it a hundred thousand dollars.
Can you please release my family now?
Are they even alive still?
Please Jeremy.
Thank you Fitty for the five bucks.
Appreciate it.
Thank you Num Legs for the ten bucks.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
There's a horror game called The Exorcist Legion VR.
Is that?
Didn't acknowledge what?
Oh, oh, oh, you guys are okay.
Is The Exorcist multiplayer?
Or is it just single player?
Exorcist VR is supposed to be legit.
I'm telling you, that Dread Halls was one of the most
nerve-wracking, stressful horror games I've ever played.
And yeah, I'm a little biased here
because it's one of the only VR horror games I've ever played.
But it was horrible.
Still going to do Mind Show?
Yes.
This co-op VR kind of couple of streams here in a row with Star.
They just kind of happened.
So my plan wasn't really part of the plan,
but we were just like, hey, let's do it.
But thank you Zombie Man for the five bucks.
Sorry, Jeremy, for the messages I was trying to send.
Cheers your way.
And they are right next to my friend invite.
No, it's fine.
Don't worry about it, man.
Thank you for the five bucks.
Appreciate it.
Miss Melon T, thanks for the two fifty.
It's really nice to draw some pixel art watching your streams,
Jeremy.
Glad to catch your streams when I'm not working.
Seriously appreciate the company from both you and the Discord chat.
Jeremy Hart, thank you.
If I could just kind of be in the background while you do some work,
that's awesome.
Glad you're hanging out.
Glad you can relax.
And we do have a pretty good Discord community.
You haven't joined it yet.
It is there.
It's available.
Open to the public.
There is one sub only room,
but the whole thing is open to the public.
Just good people there.
Discord.
Not discourse, discord.
But thank you, Miss Melon T.
And then Bloody Doctor gave fifty dollars earlier.
I missed it completely.
I don't have notifications on when I'm in VR.
Because I find it's hard to pull out and see.
So I don't have notifications on.
But if you do end up seeing this, Bloody Doctor,
thank you so much for the fifty fucking dollars.
It's a lot of money.
It means a lot.
The TJ, thanks for the five community subs.
They came in a few hours ago.
Then TJ, right after that, gave fifteen bucks.
Hey Jeremy, back again from overseas.
Showing my love again with the deployment cashola.
Have fun in VR, my dudes.
I'm off to my plane now.
We'll have to catch back up at the VOD.
Peace stream, boys.
Thank you so much.
Welcome back.
Yeah, I really appreciate the five community subs
and the fifteen bucks.
Thank you.
When's this shit start?
Let's party.
Sark.
What's up, Sark?
You want to play VR?
You want to do some VR bullshit?
I'm down.
But my eyes can only take like four to five hours though.
My brain can actually only handle it for like four hours.
It's good to see you again though.
Hope you're doing well, Sark.
Can we turn off the slow mode?
Yeah, we can probably turn it off now.
We're at the end of the stream.
Probably just dump slow mode.
I just puked when he said VR.
Can we turn up slow mode?
Now you don't have to turn it up.
Sports Bar VR has multiplayer games.
Probably check it out.
We have a list.
We picked, over the last day or two,
I've been just doing some research to find some good ones.
And there's a list of like fifteen games we have.
We sort of just kind of threw darts.
And we're like, that one, that one, that one, that one, and that one.
And that's what we'll have time to do, I guess.
So we'll do that again for tomorrow.
But thank you, Combine, for the five, six, seven, eight dollars and eighty-seven cents.
Thank you.
Why can't you do such a simple thing as walking, you absolute donut?
Please actually tell me, you absolute goddamn buffoon.
I love your videos, man.
Cheers.
Well, that was during the survive portion of the stream.
And I had like the arms moving thing set up.
And you saw, on screen, that it was really, really wonky.
It didn't work out as what I thought it was.
I changed and did just fine.
But thank you.
Appreciate it.
You absolute donut.
I'll move those words around.
It's fucking, you fucking absolute you nut.
I'm a unit.
I'm a you nut.
Thanks, man.
Appreciate that.
They also say your face brightens up my dull days whenever I come home from work.
Your presence gives me warmth like no other person
not even your father.
Jerma, I'm so proud of you and all of your brothers.
Jack, Jomi, Garrence, and little Jerma, my lovely boys.
You are my absolute champion of a boy.
You must come visit me sometime.
Sincerely, your loving, proud mother.
Combine.
PS, here's my social security number.
What are you doing?
Thank you.
Peaceful Haley.
Thanks for the 250, Peaceful Haley.
Hey, Jerma, today's stream was a lot of fun.
I couldn't stop laughing the whole time.
Anyways, hope all is well for you.
Have a good night, Jerma, and chat.
Thank you, Haley.
Always a pleasure.
Thank you.
Glad you had fun.
Read it.
Fine.
No.
No, it's a joke.
It's like J9858985.
I read that completely wrong.
I don't want to read that out loud.
What if it's real somehow?
Hey, Freudian Weapon, thanks for the 250.
Mostly lost, thanks for 250.
How are you so bad at Five Finger Filet and Red Dead Redemption
but you're perfect at it in a VR game?
Because that's just real life.
I could do that in real life.
Because I'm not physically lifting my hand up in Red Dead.
I'm doing like X, circle, square, triangle, X, circle, square,
triangle, square, square, square, triangle, X.
I just got a flash of Star doing like the crab walk in the drunk game.
Oh, this is so dumb.
But look, look, okay.
Yeah, that game is like a tuber game.
But sometimes that don't matter.
Sometimes that's all you need.
Just you and a buddy just being just dickheads in a game.
It's so much fun.
Sometimes that's actually all you need.
But thank you to Bloody Doctor again for the five bucks.
For the love of God, Jerma, your fly is down.
And they say Star Genius.
I'm sorry.
I don't have a fly.
I'm wearing jogging pants today.
Tuber, what the fuck?
Stark, it's not Mr. Stark.
Mr. Stark, I don't feel so good.
I don't after VR.
Mr. Stark.
Tuber is just a tuber.
Stark.
I don't know why I added T, I'm sorry.
I was wearing jogging pants, not a pair of jeans.
How could you play VR without a full workout gear on?
Like a hoodie and a pair of jeans.
Sweat would be dripping down my ass.
I would have to, it would be embarrassing.
I would turn around during the stream
and there would be two fucking huge wet handprint marks on my ass.
If I was in a pair of jeans, we'd go right through the jeans.
It'd be horrible.
I'd probably get like suspended.
Who's touching your, like me.
Like I'm grabbing and I'm doing an indentation on my jeans
and I'm going to grab and like move and push.
Thank you Nuke for the five community subs as well.
And then Nuke subscribed themselves.
So six subs there coming in.
Thank you for that.
It means a lot.
Timmy Tim Tam, thanks for the 250.
Hey, I think you could do with some comedy tips to be funnier.
Uh, check out this observational comedy master.
Is this me?
Are you linking a clip of me?
What the hell is this?
Why do, why, why do what a girl said fake mustaches?
What is this?
No, this is not the master of comedy.
This is, this is why do girls wear fake mustaches.
It's like a commentary video.
I don't know.
I show us.
I don't hold on.
No, I don't, I don't, I don't.
This is like somebody's like personal channel.
I don't like, I don't know if this is like, I don't know what you're doing.
Where'd the chat just go?
I lost you.
Where the hell did everybody go?
Oh, there you go.
There we go.
Now I can see why is it doing this?
Oh, it's because of OBI drop.
I see you could learn something.
I don't need to learn anything.
Comedy is just, it's whatever you want it to be.
If you think something's funny and I don't,
that's comedy for you, not for me.
That's not true.
I'm not making a joke.
All right.
All you need to know is I won the junior Massachusetts standup championship when I was 14.
I had an amazing bit about how water,
like why don't people just drink water out of the ocean?
And I got like a standing ovation.
I was 14.
I had like two jokes.
I did a thing where I was in a boat, like pretending to sail around.
It's like, oh my God, what are we?
I can't believe we're, we got no water left.
And again, it's like, you just drink the water in the ocean.
Dumb.
A guy in the front row had to go to the hospital
because he laughed so hard his face turned red and it turned purple.
He was like, and like 15 people had helped him out.
His family sued me after that for comedy negligence.
I had a great lawyer.
There's a rumor that you went to actual clown school.
Let me like hit that right in the,
let me like just cut the head off that snake here.
Um, yes, I went to clown college.
I know all the balloon animals.
I know dog, I know snake, I know cat.
I got the nose.
I graduated top of my class and in my senior project,
I did such an amazing balloon animal.
One of my instructors actually was sitting in the front row.
He was, I don't know if he was eating something,
but he was like, he couldn't believe how fast I did the balloon animal.
And he started fucking choking and laughing and like,
like fucking 10 paramedics had to come in.
I've almost killed him.
His family gets a fucking lawyer.
And that would be the second time that that's happened.
So I think I have a pretty good track record of making people laugh.
I did a balloon dog in like 1.2 seconds.
It was so fast.
He couldn't even handle it.
He was the instructor of the class.
Oh my God, I'm choking.
No, don't get your lawyer.
I got a good one.
Hey, what's the deal with water?
Why did you just drink it out of the ocean?
I was on the front page of Time Magazine.
Up and coming comedians.
That line.
Top text, bottom text.
And it was me going like this.
Like right into the, like here's the cover, right?
This is Time Magazine.
And I was like, and then the text was up here.
Why don't you just drink it out of the ocean?
And I was in a magician's outfit with like a tail and a tie.
Those were some great years.
Oh, he's a sad one.
All right, let's move on.
Thank you, Timmy Tim Tim for the 250.
That is the, what the God, we gotta start it on that.
You look like shit, man.
Yeah, I know.
I know how bad I look right now.
You think I don't know that?
I told you guys before, I gave up like years ago,
giving a shit about like looking good on camera.
No, I'm in the virtual world for four and a half hours.
This is what happens.
Am I gonna like cut the camera off
and go get my hair done and then come back and be like,
why would I be praying?
I don't know.
I don't know what that came.
Why would I have my hands in a prayer?
Gotta take care of your hair.
No, well after this, every post VR stream,
I go into the shower and I condition.
I let some nice warm water run through it for a little while
and then I get some nice conditioner,
let it sit in my hair for about 30 to 45 seconds.
Let it sit there, hang out.
I take the shower attachment off,
get it close and run it through,
pat, dry it, calm it with a brush and let it just sit there.
What's my opinion on taking baths?
I literally took one yesterday
and I put a turtle bath bomb in.
It was like a fizzy bath bomb.
It was wonderful.
It turned the water green.
Have you used the frog soap?
Not yet.
Frog soap is sitting out on a dish next to the bathtub.
I don't want to get rid of it.
I want to keep it there.
It's a set piece.
What's your favorite color?
Blue green.
Decorative soap.
Yes, it is.
You guys don't know what blue green is?
It's like the halfway point between blue and green.
Have I ever shit in a bath?
Yeah, everybody has.
Probably more than 20 or 30 times.
Because when you're between the ages of
three and six months,
you shit in the bathtub all the time.
Your parents just didn't tell you that.
Every single one of you has shit in a bathtub at least 10 times.
At least.
I'm not so sure.
No, of course you did.
Have I ever shit my pants as an adult?
Yes.
Isn't it embarrassing to say that?
People that tell you they don't believe anybody.
People pick their nose, they shit their pants,
they shit in the bathtub, they pee their pants,
they piss on the wall, they miss the toilet.
Everybody does this.
Get rid of the mask.
Take off the fucking facade here.
You pee on the seat sometimes.
You piss in the shower.
Can we stop this bullshit?
I don't want to go to Jerma's house.
It's a very clean house.
I came in a towel except to clean up after.
No.
All jokes aside, I have a very, very nice, well-kept environment.
Somebody just said something that I have to say out loud.
No, I'm not.
It's the one.
It's in all caps.
That's unbelievable.
That's insane.
I've never even thought about that before.
That's insanity.
I'm not going to read it out loud.
Wow.
That's so weird.
What the hell?
What was that?
Somebody just tried to post like a...
What the fuck was that?
It was in all caps.
You could just scroll back.
Thank you.
Mostly lost for the 250.
Mindshow should get its own full stream.
It's VR the movies.
Yeah.
I will give Mindshow the time it deserves.
That's why I haven't really done it yet.
Because I know I'm certain that I'm not going to want to just jump out of it.
Somebody already got it.
But yeah.
Mindshow will get the time it deserves.
Eventually here.
Eventually.
Thank you.
Shadow's One Disciple.
Do not say Shadow's One Discipline.
There is no end.
Shadow's One Disciple.
Thanks for the 250.
Anyway, I found this in the freezer.
What is this that you found?
Grill Master Eight Quarter Pound Patty.
Have you guys learned nothing from Gordon Ramsay?
Don't eat frozen patties.
Grill Master.
Patty Elitist here.
I asked you a question but you didn't reply.
Or other people too.
Don't ever think you're too Hollywood to reply to me or the people in your chat.
Never forget you're just a regular average guy who's just good at a video game.
Get out of your own ass.
I mean you get the first part there, right?
I'm not very good at video games though.
Good at a video game.
What video game?
Get out of your own ass.
I was pretty good in VR.
You put the patties in your fridge to keep the shape.
Are you kidding?
No.
You get fresh cut.
Bring it home.
Immediately cook them.
Not this re-refrigeration shit.
Step into the ground beef.
Can you cook?
Went to culinary school.
I think I know a thing or two.
I mean I'd not like to say that.
It was a double school.
It was a culinary clown school.
The balloon animals we made, we ate them afterwards.
Balloon chicken.
Balloon cows.
Balloon turkeys.
Balloon snakes.
Use every part of the balloon animal.
That's right.
But thank you, shadows.
Discycle for the 250.
Thank you, kimchi.
Kimchi for the 10 bucks.
I was broke, now I'm not.
Here's some money.
You're the only streamer I watch.
Thank you for always doing so much for us
and making the best streams.
Thank you, kimchi.
I just aim to have fun.
Hopefully you guys think the same.
I'm just trying to have a good time.
That's all.
Thank you for the 10 bucks.
I'm honored to be the only person that you watch.
Thank you.
Tingy, thank you.
Tingy to the 250.
So James got a kick out of one of your emotes
after seeing it in his chat.
I think it's safe to say that he liked it.
Oh, wait.
Oh, I see.
Hold on.
Can you guys hear that?
I have to change my desktop audio.
Let's see if we can hear this now.
Can we hear this now?
Yes, we can.
And that was so loud.
I'm so sorry again.
All right, let's see.
What is it?
It's a clip.
What's he playing?
Metro Exodus.
Uh, if you haven't played Metro Exodus,
I might not look at the screen for a little,
for like 30 to 40 seconds.
That was way louder.
He's getting closer.
Let's see.
Let's take a look.
The guy sounds like Willem Dafoe.
The voice actor.
Green Goblin, dude.
Ew, what is that fucking emo, dude?
Is that a fucking Jerma emo,
but it's also Willem Dafoe?
What the fuck is that emo?
I never would have pieced that together
that he looks like,
that he looks like him.
Oh, that's funny.
I'm pretty proud of things.
I'm such a fucking weirdo.
Thank you for that.
Well, you are.
I mean, they're back.
That person better be like spreading magical cheer
like Santa Claus shit out their car.
I will not be upset anymore about this.
If that guy has like a bag of magic sand
that he's throwing out
and it like has good luck charms in it for everybody.
Every day.
Uh, Clueless Sniper,
thanks for the 250.
250.
Thanks.
Uh, thank you also to Strawberry Pulp
for the 10 bucks.
10 dollars from Strawberry Pulp.
This might sound silly,
but I had kind of a crappy week in this room
really helped cheer me up.
Thanks for everything you do.
Sure my heart.
I'm sorry you're not having a good week,
but, uh, as sorry as I am
that you're not having a good week,
I am happy that you can come here
and hang out and have a good time.
That'll make you possibly not think about any bullshit.
You know what I mean?
Thank you for the 10 bucks, Strawberry Pulp.
Take care.
Thank you.
Uh, Growdiv.
Thank you Growdiv for the five bucks.
Check out Wildlands 2.
It has multiplayer and similar vibes to Jet Island,
but more focused on rope swinging.
Is it VR?
I'm assuming it is.
There's so much VR.
I've got such a backlog.
It's, it's overwhelming.
Windlands.
No, did I say wild?
Oh, I said Wildlands.
Windlands.
Uh, there I go,
adding another letter for no reason.
I still have to go back and beat Jet Island.
I was close.
I was only a couple hours away, wasn't I?
But thank you Growdiv for the five dollars and the suggestion.
I want to play it all.
I want to see it all.
Mostly lost thanks to the 250.
The stupid shit you and Stir were doing in these games
reminds me of the shenanigans you two did in TF2
and it made me happy.
Yeah, I mean, like I said, anytime you get,
like, buddy together and you just,
the purpose is just to have fun.
There's nothing else there.
It's just, I want to do something
and just have a good time.
That's it.
It's always, it's always a good time,
you know, when stars are down.
You'll see him tomorrow.
I love beating people at the bar with my buddy.
I love throwing glass at people's faces,
you know, with my friend.
Hitting guitars over people's heads.
Pretending to smoke the same cigarette
30 times and burn it on someone.
Yeah, with a friend.
It's come on.
It's just, it's a blast.
But thank you mostly lost for sure.
Am I going to want other people
to join us in Pavlov tomorrow?
I don't know.
How big are the lobbies?
Is it a big lobby system?
Is it like 12 players?
How many players?
10?
Yeah, maybe we can get something going.
I'll try to get like one of those
chat roulette system things.
Maybe we'll play like a handful of games
with subs or something.
That'll be fun.
I have it.
If you need a sharpshooter.
Really loving the VR streams,
even if I don't chat a lot.
I'm glad you like them.
I'm going to keep doing them.
I'm going to keep doing them
until I am satisfied.
And I'm still interested
and still very satisfied.
So we're going to keep going chat.
No, like a chat,
a roulette based raffle chat system.
Yeah, we'll have,
we'll get something going.
Hey, Novi333.
Thanks for the 333.
Free dolls and 33 songs.
Thank you.
No message.
That's it.
Thank you so much.
Timmy Tim Tim.
Thanks for the 250.
Can you tell the story
where you ate a pack of Oreos
and puked in your mother's bed?
No, isn't there a clip
lying around somewhere
from two years ago of me doing this?
And then didn't I say clip this?
So anytime anybody says this
to just to have it.
I just it's it's somewhere it exists.
How many times have I had that clipped
and said, hey, bring this up
when somebody fucking comes in here
and it says to give the Oreos.
Tell the story when you slapped
yourself in the face live.
Embarrassment.
But thank you.
And I'm going to run the credits.
We have another couple bits to do,
but I'm going to preemptively
get them rolling.
These are all the subs
and the resubs that came in today
during this stream.
Thank you for the continued support, everybody.
Means a lot.
You guys are awesome.
Thank you, everybody.
There are trillions of subscribers now.
I have a game in VR
that might be Resident Sleeper.
I don't know.
It's called Iron Wolf VR.
That's actually was on the list.
We were looking at it.
Sure, but please answer the question.
Just answer the question.
But we don't we don't demand things
from the streamer.
Exquisite.
I honestly only come
for the end of the stream.
Well, welcome.
And also goodbye.
Tingy had 250 here.
You is the immediate reaction
to most emotes on Twitch
that are somewhat distorted.
I love all you emotes
because of that reason
it makes them unique,
just like you.
Hey, thank you.
Now, I'm well aware that my some
at least half of my emotes
are dog shit.
Half those planets
should have been deleted
three years ago.
But no, I'm going to leave them.
Like German mustard
is what I would classify
as a dog shit emo.
It just is.
I write you.
I like it.
I love all my emotes.
I have a personal, loving relationship.
I have a great relationship
with all my emotes.
But some of them are
thrown together, we'll say.
Flustered because mustard.
Like, for instance, OK, hold on.
So for instance,
German one guy is just a
just a little shitty paint drawing.
German nose wipe
is a terrible dab emote.
It's a dab emote.
And it was it was voted
because of that reason,
because it's a dab emote.
German mustard, German moon
is my first emote ever.
And it's like I was intentionally
trying to have an emote
that was awful.
I love it, though.
That's my favorite emote.
This is by far my favorite emote
on the site.
I'm sorry.
It just is.
I don't think anybody has
one that can compare.
And I'll stand on the
eagle maniac hill here.
That's why I love that emo.
God, what a beautiful emo.
I say that because it's my face.
It's me.
I hope you guys don't
take me that seriously.
You definitely don't.
Timmy, Tim, Tim.
Thanks for the 250.
Tell the story so we can clip it.
Was sick one day.
Decided to eat Oreos.
Did the thing where you got up
and tried to move around
while being sick to your stomach.
Got up too fast.
Had too many Oreos.
A whole sleeve.
Wanted to ask my mother
a question or something.
I don't know.
The story is getting hazy
over all these years.
It was very fresh in my mind
when I told it the first time.
So go up to my mother
to ask a question.
Get that closed in.
The world's going to fall down
on top of you.
Blackout feeling.
Lie back in my mother's bed
and throw up all over it.
The whole sleeve.
No, no, no.
Like one of the.
This is like this three sleeves
per Oreo container.
One of those sections.
Probably 12 to 14 cookies.
Why did you eat Oreos
if you were sick?
I don't know.
Why does anybody ever eat Oreos?
For any reason.
Can you guys reliably
think of a scenario
where eating like a bunch of Oreos
is a good idea?
They just taste good.
And they're easy to eat.
Oreos are great.
Fuck you.
I also agree.
I think Oreos are fantastic.
But if like you.
The light bulb goes off like.
I'm going to eat 12 Oreos.
It's never really a great idea.
Oreo serving size is three.
You're eating 30 times
the serving size.
Hey, Kirby Heart.
Thanks for the four dollars.
Thanks for streaming on my birthday.
Love your streams.
Happy birthday.
Kirby, thank you.
Kirby Heart.
Did you ever replace her bed after that?
No, we just sprayed it a shitload with a hose
and then let it dry
and then flipped it over.
And that's my time.
That's going to be it for me.
Cliff both parts.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Have a great night.
Now.
Now half of you go to Nova
and half of you go to Italics.
Those are the only two people
that are streaming right now that I see.
Go say hello.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Bright and early at like 330, 4 p.m. Pacific.
Take care, guys.