Hey, what's up? I don't... am I half hour late? Yep, a few things I had to take care of.
A few things I had to do. A few things I had to take care of. But the one good thing is, uh,
not four. I wanted to make sure I started at least an hour or two early today to avoid
any problems with the internet. I had a, uh, naked on stream dream again last night,
and, uh, this one was... I don't... I'm sorry, I don't remember the whole thing.
I just remember being turned, and the camera was pointed down. I just remember it was... the camera
was down, and it was like a full-body cam. Where the camera is, in the same spot it is now,
just slightly tilted down, and I was turned naked, and like, I mean, actually naked.
And I don't know, my leg was turned up so you couldn't see my... I don't know.
But like, I thought maybe you could. I don't know why I was on... look, I don't know why I keep
having this dream. I keep having this dream. I think it's because my brain is telling me,
dude, one day, one day it's gonna happen. You're gonna be naked on camera. Just, just like this.
Just like this. I'm like, no, no, I don't want to. I don't want to be naked on camera. My brain is
like, I don't know, my brain's essentially just preparing me. Retirement stream. Dude, just face
your fears already. You know, I'm just gonna get it out of the way. I mean, my dreams keep... this
keeps happening in my dream, so I'm just gonna do it. Uh, anyways, welcome to today's stream.
We'll be live today. We'll also be live tomorrow. Should be a fun time. We've got a line up.
Quite the lineup today. Vampire Survivors is in 1.0. Check. Gotham Knights has released.
Sponsored. Check. And then we'll end it with Deadly Night, which I was incorrect.
That's not a puppet combo game. There is a new puppet combo game. We will play that.
Probably closer to Halloween. I want to make sure I correct the record from last night.
When is Breath of the Wild? Breath of the Wild will probably end up being...
Oh, tomorrow. We'll do Breath of the Wild tomorrow. Tomorrow will be a short stream,
though. We're not gonna go... I... this one will go at least six to seven hours, I'm imagining,
because we're playing three different games. But tomorrow we'll do maybe a couple of hours
of Breath of the Wild. Couple of hours of, you know, Gotham Knights. And then I love it. Let me...
I think people might want to make sure I clear this up, too. Like, the sponsored Gotham Knights
stuff is not as over after tomorrow. So it was essentially a mega weekend. What's my favorite
movie? There's quite a few. We play Overwatch on Sunday. Gremlins 2 is up, yeah, it's probably
number one. But there are quite a few movies that are in, like, the top five. I don't know if I'm
gonna play Overwatch. Overwatch is one of those games that I feel like you have to... you have to
play it... I don't just want to jump in and play Overwatch for an hour, because I'm gonna be
terrible, and I'm not gonna even know what any of the heroes fucking do. I'm not gonna know what the
maps are, and I'm gonna look like a total dickhead. And I'm gonna get frustrated, because I've spent
like 40 minutes total in the entire game, playing against people that have been playing probably
for like three weeks. And I'm just gonna be like, well, that was dumb. I'm not doing that ever again.
Overwatch is kind of game like all the other like multiplayer type games that are multiplayer
pretty much only, where you need to be playing it. Like you have to play these games in a semi
frequent kind of way. To be able to, oh yeah, I'm gonna play Overwatch today. But I guess that you
do have to start somewhere. But I'm telling you right now, if I play Overwatch one day,
I will not be playing Overwatch two, three, four, five, six days, 10 days, a month. It's just not
gonna happen. So weighing that, like what I would rather play Overwatch two, or something,
anything else in the bed, that's probably always going to be anything else, because I don't have
the time. I don't want to give the time to Overwatch two to get good enough at it where I can play it
and be like, yeah, this is great. cough cough cough cough. When are you gonna play Splatoon?
I don't know. There's a lot of games. When are you gonna play scorn? I even said it the way that I
It's in my brain forever now. Did you hear that? You heard that, right?
I was talking to Holly last night. And she said that as of right now, she's like, it's fucking me
up. Every time something happens, a major event plays out or a big puzzle is done and anything
she does or anything she sees, she just hears it in her head. Oh, the door is opening.
And here we are. Scorn. She says she hears it. What have I done? I'm sorry. You have scorned.
Well, you have to play it. I'll, I don't. All right. I, I think that I like that. It's, I think it's
really fun, but I don't want to ruin it. Because I feel like if it's too much, it will be ruined.
Right? You don't, I don't want to dilute the joke to a point where it's not funny anymore.
You have to be careful with these things. You guys have to be careful with these things.
Do it, ruin it. One right now is okay. No, because there's no reason to do it right now. All we,
okay. All we are going to do is I'm going to play the sound effect and I'm going to see Omega Lul
in like the background. You know what I mean? I'm just going to look over here and just see Omega
Lul is like just spammed in the background. Well, when I say background, I mean, because you're in,
you're on my monitor right now and I'll be able to see it in my peripheral. So I don't know. I,
why would, there's nothing, there's no reason to play it. We're just all going to go, oh yeah,
scored. And then slowly, very slowly, 10 people are going to go. There's no reason to do that.
That was like funny when you did it before, but it's not funny anymore. And then I'm going to take
a sip out of a drink and it's going to be scorn. And then 200 people are going to go as like, why
did you do that? Like that was kind of funny. The fifth time you did it. Be careful. It's a very
careful thing and I'm not going to ruin it. See, all of you thought I was going to do it right
there. Everybody did, but it's not happening. All right. You guys ready? Vampire survivors.
1.0 is out. I don't even know what I can unlock in this game right now. So yeah,
we'll play this for an hour or two. Gotham Knights for a couple hours and then boom,
deadly night to end it. I want to do it at night because I wanted to be scared. I wanted to be
scary. Okay. Here we go. You're a tactical comedian. I need to move this. This is going
to be in a better spot. There we go. Please stop teasing us. Stop. Okay. Um, what happened to my
screen? Who did that? Did you, did you do that? All right. I got my tea. I've got my phone. I've
got my stuff here. Uh, what am I missing? All right, let's go. Vampire survivors. 1.0. How are
you? I don't know. I watched the, some of the clips from yesterday and watched the stream and
stuff from yesterday. Dude, I just, I had just so much blood in my upper body. There's so much
blood in my, in my face and my hair. I'm very flush all the time. I just am. If you, okay,
if I was naked, I would have like a bright red purple face and then like just pale white.
I just have tons of blood. I think there's so much blood in my, in my brain. I think like,
it's just, I'm just constantly moving around here. I don't know. I always have like a bunch
of blood in my face, but it's not, I don't, I feel fine. You know what I mean? It's old. You're an
old man. Drink more water. I drink a shitload of water. Well, you know, I don't drink a shitload
of water. I drink enough water. It's due if you have too much niacin in your bloodstream.
No, what do you, how do you, what? The other guys have too much niacin. Okay, let's go like this.
Nope. Wrong thing. All right. So what do they add in 1.0? Is, is there a bunch of shit in 1.0
that they added? Why does it keep doing that? I don't like that. There we go. Can you guys hear
it? I can't hear it. Why? There we go. What do they add in 1.0? Looks like there's a lot of stuff
here. Move your cam to the left. They added a, all right. All right, let's do it. So I'm obviously,
let me see what the unlocks I have to do. Level 80 in the gallo tower. Okay. 15 minutes with
consetta and you get shadow pinion. I can do this. 15 minutes with consetta. Hide completed. Yeah,
let's do that. So what do you get? You get shadow pinion. All right, let's do this. 15 minutes. I
can do it. Wait, what does that character do? Do I even have that character? I don't even have that
character. How do I get that character? Oh no, yeah, I do. Gains 1% area every level. All right,
so area. I'm definitely doing damage. Super, a ton of huge area. Cool down projectiles or no?
I haven't played in a long time. I'm not sure what to do here. Is the best character? I just need to
survive 15 minutes. Speed, duration is just good. Movement speed is good. I think I have enough to
do pretty much everything. Do other projectiles because it's good to have. Greed, curse, I don't
want to do that. Reroll, skip, vanish. Get them all. Growth is good. Speed is good. You took a
shower? That's probably why I look. Yeah, I took a shower. This twitch integration now? Um, well,
I don't want to break anything yet. Let's do this first. Stop touching your nose. I am a, I am a
face toucher. I can't stop. I always do. Every two or three minutes I go, I just do it. I just do it.
Can I, I think I can do pretty much everything. Why am I even? I think, yeah, I can do like
everything. Why am I even deciding on choices here? Yeah, I can do almost every single item.
All right, cool. Let's do it. So it doesn't matter where I start, right? Just gotta survive for 15
minutes. Let's go for it. Uh, ooh, doesn't matter where, right? How about the library? Wait, what?
This one has a, where should I go? Do gallo for the quest. Oh, right. Okay. How long do I have to
live, uh, survive for? I don't, what is this shit? Hyper hurry arcana's. Should I do any of this? I
shouldn't do it. I don't, I'm just going to go. All right. What is this? What is this ability?
What is it going on? How do I, how do I, do I have to activate it? It's kind of loud. It's better.
It's a little loud. What is this thing? Um, ooh, okay. It's the area is bigger. So what whip for
area to change your direction sharply. Does the gun get gun is projectile, right? You have to stop
moving to activate it. Whip is, I would feel like the whip would be amazing here. I'm doing whip
because it's area. Oh, okay. I think I get it. Fires one more projectile. Uh, Ooh, I want this
song. A man is amazing. And remember it's area duplicator, more projectiles. I think so. Sorry.
How can I tell what direction it's going to go? Okay. It's whatever direction you start moving
when it spawns. I get it. Cool down. Um, yeah, one more of these. Let's go. It's pretty good.
It's kind of cool. It's the last direction of your input. Thank you so much for saying that
because I actually did not. I've actually been doing it wrong the whole time. Whip. Let's go.
Oh, Oh God. Don't get stuck. I want to make it the project. Um, all right. What Matt,
none of these, um, match, right? Should I do garlic? Garlic is area. Oh, look at all these
crunchies up here. All right. Here we go. Skull. Oh, maniac. Do I really want to do that this early?
That kind of sucks this early. I feel like I don't want that. Maybe later. Well, hopefully
will it come up? Maybe you just get one. Oh, it's just one. It's not more. Oh, I thought it
leveled up. Okay. Banish it. Oh, you know, fuck it. Let's go. I'm not like, I've never played this
game before. I'll be all right. Security. Yep. Did someone say the wings were for, um, shadow
opinion? Is that legit? That last 0.3 seconds longer, which is better. How come it's I'm
confused. I turned to the left and it shot to the right. Oh my God. 15 minutes. That'll be good.
Gallic. Look at that area. Are you so greasy? Um, cause I'm just like a wet, I'm a wet person.
I'm just a moist person. You know, I didn't want to pick that up. People ask, dude, how come you
look so young? You look young, man. Wow. How old are you? Well, you look young. And I, you know,
I'm just, I'm very wet person. My skin is very, it's always moist. It's always moisturized.
If there's another shit, I have a black eye shadow again. I think I do. I, I very like moist,
moisturized skin. So how come it doesn't say it on there? You guys lied to me. Your lighting
setup doesn't do you any favors. I don't, I don't care about it doing me any favors. I'm just,
I'm just a guy sitting here hanging out. I don't need to buy what you want me to have like studio
lighting in here. I'm just a wet person. Did you guys actually lie to me or does that,
wouldn't it usually say it on the tool tip? These things are probably going to be awesome a little
bit later. I need cool down, right? Cause then it will happen to be like,
the odd, these guys take two hits, right? What we got? I'll take the whip. That's fine. Duplicator.
Yep. I guess I could just activate it fast. I'm going to go down and get whatever the item is
more. Okay. Yep. Let's get this thing maxed out. You kind of remind me. Well,
you didn't say who I remind you of. So I don't know who I remind you of.
I can't believe this game is read. Is this game still $3? Is it a little bit more expensive now?
Five now. Okay. Yeah. I mean, it's worth more than three dollars. You know what I'm saying?
Ooh. All right. Lightning ring. Although yeah, let's yes. Garlic again. What does garlic level
up with? It's not the book, right? Bro. You look like liquid Shaggy. Okay. Wait,
I'm not going to look at chat. Do you mean liquid Shaggy as in Shaggy that is made out of liquid?
Cause I talked about how wet I was. Or are you referring to like liquid Shaggy like this?
It's me. Liquid Shaggy. Is that what you mean? Like I'm the evil. Like that's what you mean?
Okay. I didn't know how exactly what you meant by that because both make sense. Liquid Shaggy.
I'm going to get smashed by that. We're good. All right. This is where it starts to get a
little hairy here. This weapon is actually really good. Stop distracting me. You guys are typing.
I see words scrolling up out of my peripheral. I can stop typing. I can see it.
Come on. Thank you. Thank you. I have to go down because it is a thing to collect down there. I
don't know. What even is that? Whip again. I need some more stuff. I haven't seen any garlic in like
feels like two, three years. All right. I got max whip as bit rate. We look good. Can you make out
anything that's going on? I'm going down after this. Shit better. What's new in this patch?
There's a bunch of stuff. I'll be honest though. I can't really tell you what is exactly in this
patch that wasn't in the game before this patch because it's been probably five plus patches
since I've played this game. There you go. There's a lot of stuff though. This seems
like there's been a lot of new content, but they'll put on the chat integration.
Yeah. I'll turn it on once I get a second here. I just want to do like one. I want to warm up.
I want to warm up and play it a couple of times because I don't want you guys to be able to spawn
bosses and I haven't played the game in like a month or two and I just lose. Let me warm up.
What if I, I don't have a, I mean, it's, it's, it's, it's definitely cool down. Both of these
are good. It's definitely this one. Does the spear have a, uh, evolution? I feel like it doesn't.
Ooh, it looks like a gas station employee. What do you mean? Like just a person? I look like a
person. Oh, hey, you look, you look like a guy. Yeah. Okay. Like dude, please turn the fog filter
off. I want something better than that. D minus two. Dump it. I stole that from Seth.
You look like Peter Pan. All right. All right. Yeah. I look like a lot of people, apparently.
Yeah. I look like Peter Pan. I look like, uh, Jim Carrey. I look like Willem Dafoe. I look like
fucking Kramer. I look like everybody, apparently. Yeah. I look, people look similar. So by people
that I look similar to happen to be, I'm sorry. They happen to be incredibly handsome people.
That's all right. Keep, keep telling me. I look like who's wicked handsome out of that group.
Don't forget. I do not look like Jerry fucking Seinfeld, dude. No, you can't just because the
guy. All right. Just because they have, just because they're a brown hair white guy does not
mean they are Jerva nine eight five. Okay. People that was risky. I did it. Yes, it does.
Actually, I don't even want that. You look like my dad. You look like Peter Pan. It's because I'm
okay. And also when I wear like a different colored shirt, it makes me other characters.
Hey, anybody else think he looks like fucking Shaggy today? Yeah. Cause I got a green shirt on
dude. Anybody think he looks like fucking Robin today? I got a red shirt on. You do look like,
all right. I do look, I do look like Shaggy. I do. And I do look like Jim Carrey. I do look like,
I look like all these people. All right. I look like Willem Dafoe. I know I get it. Okay.
I get it. That's fine. That's all right. Peter Pan. Peter Pan might be my favorite one for the
last few weeks. What is that? Bigger, longer, faster, stronger. It's like a blowtorch.
Holy shit. Oh my goodness. Okay. You weren't lying. Don't, don't, don't give me any ideas.
I will rig up a fucking wire system in this room and I'll play a Peter Pan song and start
to fly around the room. You understand? I will do that. If you, if you keep harping on this
and then it'll go to a full cam and I'll just be flying around the room and then I'll sit back down
and give me a re-roll on this. This one's definitely a lock. I might do the whole thing,
actually. Do a Batman cosplay. I would be an awful Batman. I would not make a very good Batman.
Guys, I would look, I would kind of look like a dork in a Batman outfit. I'd look like a dork.
My posture's kind of, my posture sucks. I'm kind of smaller and my posture's bad. My arms are big.
My legs aren't. I would, I would look like, I think I would look like shit in a Batman costume.
I would look weird. I don't think I would look all right. That's the point though. Dude, do you
guys think, and some of you, some of you people, some of you guys in here might be this. I don't
know. If you're huge and jacked and you're just fucking massive, you're like a big muscular dude.
Do you sit around and go like, I'm fucking Batman. I get to be Batman this year.
I'm going to be Superman this year and I'm going to look like Superman.
Like, do you get ready to put the Bane costume on and be like,
I'm fucking Bane. Look at me. You know what I mean? If I was huge,
it would, I would not give a shit about being stronger. I would not care about,
oh, you can reach higher shelves. Oh, you're a lot bigger and stronger. Oh, I can lift boxes.
Nope. Every October 31st, I get to be Superman and I get to really be Superman and I get to look
like Superman. I would, I get to be Superman. That's why I think it was cool. You get to walk
around, you know, like this up with your chest out, like citizen. Like you're huge. You get to
pick every October 31st, a superhero that you get to be. You can just do it. Oh, Wolverine. Done.
Give me the metal claws. I can make that work. Style my hair like his. You know, I get to pick
rum every Halloween. Harry Potter characters. You know, I get, I get to be like the Riddler.
That's it. I get to be Shaggy, the green goblin. I've even the green goblin. Shaggy's cool. Shaggy
is cool. You are Jack though. No, I used to be. Not anymore. Yeah, dude, if I was huge and I'm,
when I say huge, I mean like, like six, four, like 200 fuck, but you're actually old.
Nobody tell them. There we go. Um, well, I definitely don't want to see this ever again.
Oh my God. All right. Um, cool down, right? Yep. Okay. Uh, be Groggy Gary for Halloween.
You could be Santa. No, I couldn't. I would be an elf. The huge guy gets to be Santa. I have to wear
the funny hat and the funny shoes and be like walking around my friend who gets to be Santa Claus.
So you could be whatever you want for Halloween. You could be the Joker.
That's right. I could, I could. Yeah. All right. There's no way I don't make it to 15.
Yeah. Like I've said this before, I'm going to say it again. All you need to do should be a good
Joker. Just put the makeup on and go like this. Every other sentence. See my father, everyone will
go. Oh, what do I want for my last item? The clock. What's this? Oh, it's the super
manna. You know, you know, who's a, an absolutely fucking hilarious motherfucker that needs more
credit for how funny they are myth. If you guys, if you guys don't follow myths, he, he did this
video recently. He did a Joker video where he was doing the Joker as XQC doing the, that famous rant.
I was just laughing my ass off. He's, he like did like a Joker XQC thing. It was just like
with like the music in the background. It was funny. Oh my God. Don't die. Oh, that's super
thunder. Oh, the levels are just rolling in recently. That was 11 months ago. Why did I
just see that in my feet? Do I open Twitter so infrequently that what do you wait? Hold on.
When did he upload that? I saw that literally like one day ago. Somebody must've retweeted it
or something. Why did I just see that a day ago? Why did I just see that? It was a year ago.
Do I seriously? What? Why did I just see this? I don't, I don't know. I genuinely do not know why
I just saw that. Oh, you guys lying to me. Okay. Dude, you got to keep up with like your Twitter.
Dude, I don't keep up with anything. I don't even use the computer. I'm just telling you.
The only time I use the computer is right now with, with you all. I don't use the computer.
I don't use the internet. Oh, nice. Oh my God. Look at this. What the fuck? You see that? How much
damage I'm doing. Oh, what is this? All the way. Oh, that means this is the only thing that shows
up forever. I get it. All right. I don't know. Twitter is weird, right? People, I got messages
from people saying, Hey dude, why did you like a bunch of like tweets you made in like 2014 or
something? And I'm like, what the fuck are you talking about? I didn't do anything. I don't,
apparently I went back and liked a bunch of old tweets. I didn't do that. Does it bug?
All right. Well, Ooh, level up. Oh, that's actually awesome. So it doesn't go to the
screen. That's cool. But anyways, TLDR myth is a really, really funny person. Very good on camera.
Really funny. And that's all. That's what I was trying to say. Watch out boss. This guy, you look
like a wise guy. Okay. We've evolved. We've evolved. It's no longer. Hey dude, you look like Shaggy.
You look like Peter Pan. You look like a wise guy. Gold fever. Oh my goodness. What's happening?
Why is this happening? Holy shit. Just $7,000. Holy shit. Sweating. No, pretty can't even touch me.
I just stand still. That's not fun. We got to get to level a hundred. Gotta get to 80. Oh, I'll get it.
I got 10 more minutes. I'm going to get to like level a hundred. How's the quality look?
Can you see shit? Oh, I'm like, I'm like talking to something. These games are great. I can just do
this. Gold fever. I'm just going to go down. Holy shit. It looks like it hurt. Liars. Liars.
Myth put that video up on Twitter literally yesterday. Liars. I won. I win. Everybody ban
everybody that said no. I want a massive timeout for five seconds. I don't want to. Okay. Is this
game even fun? Yeah, dude. Hey, don't look at what I'm doing here. And she deterred from purchasing
this. I got a little bit of experience in the game. Uh, I have dozens and dozens of hours playing
this game, I think. So, I mean, I am at a level where I've got all the power ups. I've unlocked
tons of stuff. You're going to be starting at nothing. You can be starting at zero and you're
going to be walking around getting your ass kicked by the first enemy of the game. So just,
just know where you are right now. I have a lot of experience in the game. I'm probably one of the
most, uh, one of the most experienced Empire survivors. Um, no, I don't, I don't need to say
it or anything, right? Like, I'm one of like, you guys know, you have those big hands. My God,
just die already. Just die already. Oh my goodness. You still alive? Why are you still alive?
Why are you still alive? Why are you so blushy? There's blood in my face. Lots of it. There's
another one. I haven't even killed the first one. I don't think I'm going to get to 100,
but I got to 80. That's all I wanted, right? That is the first one. I can't believe I've made
almost 10 grand. That first money, um, coined insanity, whatever it was. I don't think I've
ever seen anything like that ever again. I put that down so meanly. Evil German. Dark Uga.
Do you eat Taco Bell? Yeah, I love Taco Bell. Well, I love one item in Taco Bell and it puts,
it puts Taco Bell at S tier. Uh, Cheesy Gordita Crunch is the only thing that puts Taco Bell above
B. The only thing. Don't, don't come at me with this, you know, oh, you're going to get the,
no, don't even come at me with that. Cheesy Gordita's Cheesy Gordita Crunch with a Doritos
Taco inside the Cheesy Gordita Crunch. There will never be a fast food item ever. Yeah,
that will be as good. Never. It's impossible. In fact, I feel like Taco Bell is probably
pissed. It's like, oh shit, we made literally the best fast food item to ever exist and no one will
ever come close ever again for the rest of the entire time we're still alive in humanity.
Like we can't make anything else that people would even care about because we made that already.
And quit and cash in leftover revives. Oh, do I really? I don't really care. All right. I got
some, uh, Capella Magna. I unlocked the Shadow Pinyon. I got 500 gold coins. Cool. All right,
nice. Nice. What else we got? Hold six different weapon evolutions. Find the Grim Grimmuar.
Find the Magic Banger. Find the Ars Guda. Find and buy the Glass Vizard. Gr, what did I say?
Magic Banger. Find the Great Gospel. You get Limit Break. Inverse Mode. There's a lot. Oh,
my goodness. Look at all this shit. The Trumpet. All right, what should I try to get here? What
should I do? Why did you have a Q-tip covered in lip balm in a plastic bag during juiced?
Um, well, that's very simple. I couldn't explain it because we're in the middle of a show, but
so I use this a lot. I do. So I don't, okay, I know that you really shouldn't be using ChapStick
that often, but I live in Nevada. I live in Las Vegas and it gets very dry out here. Incredibly
dry. Um, so this helps. I try not to use it too. I don't usually use this unless I'm talking a lot
because when you're talking a lot, you're essentially drying out your mouth and lips
because the air coming in and out. We're like, blah, blah, blah, blah. So it helps while you're
talking to keep your mouth moistened. If I don't do this, you'll notice I will lick my lips all the
time because if I'm talking a lot, I have to, you know, constantly be licking my lips. I am the
fucking joker. No, don't say you're the joker. Don't do that. Stop that. If you say you're the
joker, you're actually the penguin. Don't do that. Don't, Jeremy, don't do that. Don't ever believe
anybody if they say they're the joker, right? People that say they're the Riddler are actually
the joker. People that say they're the joker, they're actually the penguin. People that say
they're the penguin are telling you the truth. They're telling you the truth. Penguin mains are
based. You already said this before. Yeah, there's like a bunch of new viewers. Come on, I gotta get
my, I just like scraped you. Who are you then? I don't, I don't, I don't know. We're talking
into all of Batman? You'd be the scarecrow. I don't know if I'd be the scarecrow. You'd be
Peter Pan. Oh yeah, Batman's famous rogues gallery. Peter Pan. I wouldn't be Mr. Freeze.
I wouldn't. I don't want that to spill on me. All right, uh, let me do,
I'll do one more with the twitch integration and then we'll move on,
play some Gotham Knights. This is work. Let's see. I think it's on. Is it on?
Hold on, let me do this. All right, yeah, it's on, I think. So what do I want to try to go for here?
Six different weapon evolutions survive 30 minutes with either Gallo or Divano.
All right, so I'm going to try Gallo or Divano. Gallo? I don't have either one of those. Gallo
or Divano? Am I not seeing it? I don't have either one of those people. Why, oh, why the Q-tips? Okay,
so I didn't have any chapstick with me when I was at Juiced and the, um, I was kind of figuring out
where have I, where can I get one of these? I need, I need something to be able to put on. Um,
and there was a, there was a makeup artist that was there and it was like, oh, no, no,
I actually have something. You could use this. It's gonna be kind of weird, but, um, it's like
just a little bit of Vaseline. You can put that there, uh, just a little bit to kind of use that
for what you, you know, needed it for. And I was like, oh, okay, cool. So I used it and I was like,
oh, that worked great. And I put it in the pocket and I just forgot it was there and I got called
out for it. Bro, why was it dirty? I don't, I, that I don't know. I feel like it was because of maybe
like the makeup or something when I did it and I got the makeup on it. I don't know. All right,
so where are these? I don't have these two characters. Survive 30 minutes with either
Gallo or Divano. How do I unlock Gallo or Divano? This, Forbidden Squirrels? This is question mark.
Oh, Sir Ambrojo. No, it's my coffin. Your mic sounds like shit. No, it doesn't. That's fine.
Just pick up stuff you missed on the stages. All right, well, let's just go for it then.
I'm going to go with, what is that, a wheel? Have I ever played with this character? I'm going to
play with the wheel character. More projectiles every 20 levels. Okay, yeah, let's do the wheel.
So I'm assuming the ones with the exclamation points on it are, I need to go and get stuff
there. So let's do Moon Glow. I also have this, a weird filter on this camera. This camera's weird.
Let's go to Moon Glow. Fancy a new, oh, there it is. Look. Merchant is in all stages now.
Golden Egg? What should I do? What should I do? I'm going to keep the wheel. What is this move?
Okay, so this is a projectile character. Why do I only have one? What's going on?
Oh, you guys have to vote. I can't pick anything. What did you just give me?
Thanks. Look at all these things out here. All right, this is going to be a fucking disaster.
I'm not going to pick up anything yet because I don't know what I want to do.
And I'm not going to touch anything. Twitch, what is...
Yeah, oh, why didn't you start with this? I wonder why. Is it showing all of your names?
That's, okay, that's weird. What am I going to get? I wonder how long it lasts.
Oh, thanks for the luck boost. Thanks, guys. All right, you only have like
five seconds to choose, so be ready if you want to participate because I can't do any of this.
It's all up to you. Move your cam so we can see. You can see. Okay, here we go.
Lights. What is light sources? I keep trying to pick and I can't. He's melting again. All right,
what is it? How am I supposed to deal with this? I'm level four. This isn't fair. Ah,
it disappears after a minute. Sorry, guys. Get wrecked. Not quite. Is the Twitch integration
for 1.0? I feel like that was not here a month or two ago when I played the last.
Oh, I can't. I forgot. I can't ask questions because all. Okay, I can ask a question if the
answer is one, two, three, four or A, B or C. Guys, what number is the month for April? Oh,
never mind. What just happened? You guys just gave me like a power up or something. I don't know.
Give me the double guns. Don't. Why don't. Why would you give me the wand? You picked. Why would
you pick the wand? You just screwed everything up. Give me double guns, not wand. Great.
So what happens now? Did you guys? You're in the middle of voting by the way.
Thank you. A clueless machine for your support of the stream. Appreciate it.
Definitely keep making these bigger. This thing. These things are great. Actually carts. Well,
what month is March? What number is March? What month is March? What number month is March? Thank
you. A lot of food. Are there any coffins? Okay. Give me the gun. Do the gun. I demand. I command
you to pick one ghost swarm. Uh, I don't know what to pick. Oh, it's ghost swarm times 10.
There's 10 of them at, uh, at Corello. I've been pretty good, but it certainly looked like a
different person. Every stream. Um, sometimes you, your hair is done a different way. You're
if you have facial hair, do you not have facial hair? I will tell you guys that I do get, I do
have a lot of different looks. I sometimes would be clean shaved and then randomly like you'll see
me four days later and I have like a beard. It's just like, where'd the other guy go? Well,
if my hair will be different, I get it. I do base damage up by 30 cool down. I want to,
does this thing have an evolution? Cause I want to see it. It's just a huge car that drives around.
I really hope that once I get to like level 30, 40, 50, that you guys don't have to pick every
single time when it gets to the, do you want the box or do you want, I gotta make sure I make it
always around the whole circle, 20% more area. Go get all the items on the floor. But you didn't
vote for that. I guess I could, right? Could I just go pick up every single item? Done. Done.
Should I pick up every item on the floor? I don't know. I can't even ask a question because
nobody can answer it. Only do that after you fill every slot. Okay. Three more luck. I didn't want
to pick that up. I wanted to save that. I'm shaking my head, dude. I mean, I would say it's probably
two, right? Be dumb. All right. I'm going to get the magnet. There's a lot of stuff on the floor.
Good luck. You're going to have to level up like three times. Thank you. Interesting. Now what?
I feel, okay, this is going to be so messed up here because there are a lot of people that are
on more than a five to 10 second delay on the stream thing on your internet connection and
where you are in the world or whatever. So tons of you guys I think are voting for the like third
level. And that was like the fifth level. I don't, I think this is going to be a little messed up.
Oh shit. All right. I'm making it hard. Okay. Can I even kill these things? Thank God for the
mine carts. Done. This is actually, I thought you guys were going to make like a ha ha killed
the streamer build. Um, but this is actually pretty good. Nice job. Nice work. Thanks, Peter.
I don't know what I did. Oh, I said good job. You're right. Oh, yep. Why do you have such a
crooked face? Um, because I have a crooked face. Mean chat member. Ooh, yep. Get it. Get that. Get
that. That's the big one. That's one of the best items in the whole game. That is the best evolution
in the whole game in my personal. Yes. Hell yeah. Um, I'm not picking up all the items yet. I still
have plenty of time. It seems like it's going to be pretty good. These things explode. Okay. Well,
yeah, I'm dead. I get to come back, but I'm dead. Dude, how the fuck am I supposed to beat that?
I can revive one more time. That lasts literally forever. Kill them. Oh, I got the merchant and
everything. Okay. That's impossible. I mean, it wasn't impossible. It was just improbable.
Wow. You did it. All right. Um, anything. One more. One more and we move to Gotham Knights.
We'll do one more. This time. Don't press the button. That's going to end the run instantly.
Give me the free shit. Who should I play with? I'll let you guys decide this. Who should I
play with? Play with the dog? Dog? Why do you look like Shaggy and Fred at the same time?
I'll do dog. And where should I go? Just probably the library stage two. Yeah. Anything with an
exclamation point. Oh yeah. They have relics. All right. I'm going to do the library. Uh,
should I turn any of these on or who cares? This dude's got wicked extraterrestrial eyes today.
Okay. Put our con is on hyper and hurry. No, I don't want to hurry. That's annoying to me.
I don't know what I don't know what to do here. Feeling. All right. What's this feeling is doubled
recovering HP damages nearby enemies for the same amount listed weapon projectiles gain up to three
bounces. That's insane. Overall area continuously changes between minus 25 and plus 25% over 10
seconds. Overall duration continuously changes between minus 50 and plus 50%. Enables critical
hits for listed weapons doubles overall critical damage. That sounds incredible. Um, what does this
character start with? The flowers, right? Those are, is that technically a projectile? The ones
that bounce. It's not a projectile. It's not listed at all. Do the healing one. Oh, that is listed.
All right. We're going to do that. Why did I pick that up? Give me something good. How often do you
get a sunburn all the time, all the time? Uh, I am Irish and Polish. So, I mean, I burn pretty quickly.
My, my, like I very kind of light, um, skin. So like I, it burns very, very quickly. There's also
like other, I mean, I, I could give you my entire, I don't, I don't, I've literally done kind of
no, there's no kind of what I've been told. It's like a Eastern, you know, Eastern European,
Irish, I don't know, Polish. Stop doing this to me. The stream is getting angry. Hey guys,
what the, what the fuck would you guys do? I like the dog's basket. Maybe if there wasn't
a inescapable jelly wall, I would be able to get out of here. The heel is so good on this character.
It really is. The song is really good too. This game is just really good. This thing's three dollars.
I hope whoever made this made a really good amount of money. I mean, you deserve it. What the fuck
was that? All right. I kind of like just, um, can you guys give me a weapon that can fucking kill
something? They probably made, they made bank. Don't the cats hurt you? The cats attack you.
I see you're going with the animal build. Okay. I see. Go get the item or I forget
and I will forget. Nevermind. Light sources. You like it because it's retro. No, I like it because
it's a really great idea. Guys, how many, we didn't do that. Then who did? You tell me you didn't do
this? Shit. I might die. Just got to get out of there. All right. I need food. Actually good
because I can heal, right? The flowers healed. You know what to do. Give me some health here.
Last 1.5 seconds. More projectiles or armor. School. Eventually when I have a bunch of speed
and I have a ton of this thing's leveled up all the way, I will heal to full health in one second.
Just get me there. What's this? I have to kill that, um, Grim Reaper guy. Need the other gun.
Yeah, you need the other gun. Don't forget that. Without the other gun, I'm in trouble.
How do you kill this guy? How do I get rid of this guy? Just evade. Okay. There we are. Stalker?
Dude, how? Cat ate the chicken. Yeah, the cats eat the food and they hurt you. A fully leveled
up cat though I think is pretty good, right? Give me the hell out of there. This guy can't
be killed either? No. Sorry. Don't have to worry about that. How far away am I? All right. I can
get there. Let's get a run. I like how a lot of the songs in this game go like, they all have that
same, uh, like bass drum that just goes, what? You skipped the passive? What do you mean I skipped
the passive? I missed a gift from chat. I did? I'll go back up and get it. Do I want that though?
I feel like I, I thought I'm not supposed to pick up passives until I get what I want.
Or do I want that one? I'm just saying if you jelly well me, I'm uninstalling the game and I'm
going to uninstall the fucking twitch stream. You give me a jelly while I'm uninstalling the game.
I'm just telling you, I'm just being completely honest with you. Yeah.
Actually that thing you just picked is probably worse. There it is.
Ars guda permanently allows to access the list of defeated enemies from the main menu.
What does this do? Oh my God. It's a, oh, okay. It's like a database. All right. Now I'll go back
up and get the nice gift that you gave me. I appreciate it. Almost got me. Didn't get me.
So I, should I pick, do we need any of this stuff? Should I pick the, um, these passives up? I
shouldn't. No, I'm not gonna. It's not worth it. I got to level up. I get the free one from chat.
Does that, doesn't it just take a slot? I got to level up. I'm very underleveled. I'm level 18
and there's 10 minutes. Get the orb. Actually a good idea. Whoever said that, that was a great
idea. And that person for an hour. Tell me what to do on my screen. Oh my God. I'm going to die.
I'm going to, you're going to kill me. Stupid fucking jelly. Well, I swear to God,
what did I, did a cat just eat that? Why did I not get it? Why did I not get that? I think
the cat destroyed that. Oh, where's it? Where's an orb? Wait, this is okay. There's a chest down.
There's an orb. All right. Get the chest first. I'll take it. Now there's an orb up. There's a
chest up. There's a lot of crunchies here to get exactly what I needed. Tons more luck and more
projectiles. Keep it up. It does suck that the cats eat the food though. I gotta get out of this.
We go up. Yep. Okay. There's a turkey and then there's up. Where's that chest? Right here.
I don't know. What does a pet even do? One more projectile. Cool. All right. Now give me the orb.
Does it heal maybe? I wonder. Oh shit. All right. I'm in trouble here. It's my brother's birthday.
Say happy birthday. Happy birthday to that person's brother. Happy birthday. No, seriously. What's that?
Oh, I get another one. I don't want that one. Enables critical hits for listed weapons,
which I only have. I don't have any of these. That's pretty big though. Although I only have
one of these. Which one? I could reroll it. Although I think this is probably the one.
It is. It's the only thing that's going to save me right now. Well, now definitely get the cross
upgrade when you can. It's a lot of experience here. I'm not going anywhere for a few minutes.
Yep. I'm going to soak all this up. Oh, I thought you were going to do pentagram. Okay.
Cats are going to kill you. Well, I didn't pick them. You should blame your fellow chatter.
I was going to go with side. Cross is doing so much. Play Peggle 2. No, I don't like Peggle 2.
It kind of sucks. It's okay. It was all right. I think Peggle 1 I had the most fun with.
I didn't. Peggle 2 was all right. You guys have to remember I'm older. So the first one that came
out, I'm always going to have a better opinion of because it's Peggle 1. You know, okay. I do
Peggle 2. I liked the second area. I liked that. I like that character because the song goes like
I don't like the first but the horse. What's the horse's name? Yorn or something, right?
The horse creeped me out. The way the horse does like the facial expressions the horse makes. It's
kind of like creepy. I don't know. The horse is, the horse freaks me out. This dude's scared of a
cartoon. Okay. Don't ever, don't ever jump back in your seat at a horror game when they try to scare
you. It's a fucking 3D CGI cartoon dude. Peggle is a horror game. I win. No, I win. I'm the streamer.
I win. Did you see how many people said true, true, true, true, true, true, true, true, true, true,
true. No, I win. I'm the streamer. So I win. Oh my what the hell's happening?
Understand the streamer can never be wrong. Streamer can never be wrong. This is real fun.
Do you mean that sarcastically? It actually is. I've never seen anything like that before. The
crosses are just, uh, this is definitely secure at this point. Good. Ooh. Yep. There it is. So now
this is going to be wild. I need more projectile speed. I need more projectiles. I give me what I
need. Wait, did you guys just do the attractor? Oh, for the, okay. Or, um, the water, right? It's
true. I meant it honestly. Oh, you're good. Don't worry. You're good. Let me look strange because
my camera is flipped horizontally. You are not used to seeing me from this angle. I am though.
So from the other angle, it's weird for me because that's correct. This is how I see myself
when I look in the mirror. So this looks normal to me. It looks weird to you.
The reason why a lot of people think they look weird in pictures is because that's a flipped
version of your face. Well, no, no, no. Yeah. Like the mirror is a flipped version of your face.
So you are, when you look in the mirror, you are not seeing what your face looks like.
That's always why if you look at a picture of yourself and you're like, wait, what's wrong with
my face? Chad is throwing right now. Yeah. What are you guys doing? Are you guys throwing on
purpose? What are you guys even selecting here? No, no. Why'd you get the axe? Why did you pick
the axe? What is going on with this build? It was going so well until like 30 seconds ago.
What happened? It's definitely because there's too many happening in a row and everyone that's
like, everyone that's from, okay, to all the EU viewers, you are voting for stuff that probably
happened 10 seconds ago. The EU viewers get the short end of the stick again. There's a 30 second
delay. So there's a, I have low latency mode on. So there's probably like a four, three to five
second delay. Yeah. So hold on a minute. I don't think anybody's voting for the right thing.
There's a three to five second delay with low latency. Also you have a delay to me
watching through the Twitch server. So it has to compress through and the bit rate has to
send it to you. So it's probably 10 plus seconds. So you guys are just pressing random numbers. I
think at this point it's working pretty well. My delay says 0.75 seconds, but might be one of my
neighbors. 0.75. That's no way. I mean, that person, that person's like on the Las Vegas
script right now. Just like watching. No, that would, no, not even 0.75 seconds means you are
like in the house. My delay is three seconds. Well, okay. So one second, correct me if I'm
wrong. Cause I, I mean, I know a little bit about networking, right? 1000 ping means one full second
delay, correct? Thanks for ruining the whole game by the way. Can't wait. Maybe not. That's correct.
1000 ping means one second is how long it takes to go from the server to you guys. My bit rate
sucks right now. I don't know what the hell yours looks like. Like my game's bit rate is actually
bad right now. I don't know what it could possibly be for you. How long does the panic thing last?
This feels like it's been a long time. All right, now I'm going to go start picking up everything.
Dude, forget about like, oh, if we went back in time and showed a caveman this, what would they say?
If you went back like 15 years or 20 years and showed a person this, they'd be like, what the
fuck is going on and why? What is that? I don't think you have to go back that far. Go back to like
the early 2000s or like if people would be like, what are you, what's happening to you?
What's going on? Can you explain this to me? That's wicked funny. Somebody said this looks
like a bath bomb. Wow. That's best chat of the best chatter of the entire evening.
It looks like a bath bomb. Dude, I can't move because of the panic.
Is that what it looks like? All right, hold on. Open the chest. I got it. It's this. Oh, yes. It's
the side. My favorite. It's fucked up. All right. You have to vote for three, vote for three. So we
don't have to keep doing this. Vote for three. All right. Bring it on. Give me everything. Give me
all you got. I'm talking jelly walls. I'm talking swarms. I'm talking monsters. I'm talking fast
extra speed for all monsters. Give me, give me everything you got. All right. There's a,
there's an orb right over here. I'm going to get it. A fucking bath bomb. Up. Oh, here we go.
I didn't do anything. Oh, yeah, I did. It was traveling. How many times do I level up? I leveled
up like 15 times. All right. If you did go back to like back in like the fucking 1500s and you had,
you know, you were surrounded by, you know, people with like muskets
and they saw this and you had to explain this to them or you were dead. You know what I mean?
Like you were a fucking warlock. What would you do? Like if you were to explain what's going on
right now? What is this? You have 10 seconds. What would you do? Be like, um, what would you say?
Would you blame it on like the devil or something? I think I would be on their side. I'd be like,
I have no idea. You have no idea. I don't know what that is either. It's the devil's work. We
must get rid of it. Right. Cause you, there's no way you're going to, it's not going to happen.
There's no way you have to like be on their team. Yeah. I don't know what that is,
but it needs to be banished and cast from our village. Oh, I finally got it. Say God made it.
No, no, I don't think so. No, I'm not saying that. Uh, the citizens would start to like recreate
this stuff. They would try to like make this real. Uh-uh. Like they would think this is, oh,
oh, we needed to make giant sides. That's what he wants. He wants us to make giant sides and
throw flowers at each other. Society would crumble. All right. How does my face look right now?
Should I go with some, how do you explain electricity? You don't. That's why I would
just be, you would just be on their team. You would just be like, I don't know. Where did you
come from? The woods. I've been in the woods. Yeah. I'll be in the woods this whole time. I've been in
the woods. Who's your parents? They died in the great battle that we had. All right. That checks
out was this one. Uh, oh yeah. Crits. How old are you? Uh, uh, uh, I don't know. 15. Oh, okay.
It's like, I don't know how long people live, right? I don't think people look like if I said
like 40, they'd be like, you mean 40, 40. What do you mean? How come you don't have gray hair?
You're not old. No. Yes. Oh, uh, Brian Michael is, is, is 38. He looks like this old ass guy.
It's not possible. Get rid of him. Kill him. All right. Um, so I'm just going to like stand here
because I need to reply to, uh, somebody in my agency. We're going to talk about the incoming,
the sponsor stuff for a second. So, um, I think I'm all right. I'm just going to take a second here.
What is, um, look at how, do you see how I'm, my game is running slow. Why am I going so slow?
Dude, it's actually, it's not, it's, it's slow motion. There's too many cats. Why am I? Look at
how slow this is. Okay. This has to stop. I'm just waiting for my Jeep, like, like CPU fan to go.
You know what I mean? You know, when you, you know, your computer is working real hard when
all of a sudden you just start hearing,
you're like, Oh, dude, you got to push the limits of the 30 90s. Somebody just asked me to go get
the armor up here. And it's like, I mean, I don't think I really need it. Can you even die? I don't
think so. I actually want to try to get to a hundred. So I'm just gonna stick around here.
I don't even need it. 104. What's the highest I think I've ever been. I'll be like close to here.
One five, one on 10. This is, this is definitely the most ridiculous, uh, like character I think
I've ever seen. Probably could have been crazier too. Okay. Give me the ultra wave. This five more
minutes. I got, I'm going to get to like 130. I'm going to get to like 150. Holy shit. My God.
Hey, I just realized that this is going to take 10 minutes because it's at like half speed.
It's counting at half speed, 30, 31, 32. It's almost three seconds for every one second.
This is going to take 15 minutes. This is going to be insane. It's at like 0.2 speed. So it's
count. Yeah. It's gonna be like 12 minutes. You're in slow mo as well. I am not. This is what Adderall
is doing to your brain. What dude, this shit is flavor blasted. You guys are on point today.
Really? You guys are on point this afternoon. 119. This is the highest I've ever been for sure.
There's still so much time left. I might get to 150 to be absurd. 17,000 gold too.
All right. I'm going to try to go this way to collect everything that died over here. Oh,
I picked up a, I picked up one of those things. Didn't I? Yep. The kind of stuff that they,
it's the kind of stuff they market to babies. Do we need, we need some like,
we need, we need the Muppets back. You know what I mean? Where are the fuck, where are the Muppets?
Where are the Muppets? We need, we need the Muppets. We need them back. Dude, this
Muppets level threat, but it is though you're, it is I'm at one, two, three. Should I just quit
the game right now? Four more minutes. Resident sleeper. I'm really sorry to that person, but
it's probably like seven or eight more minutes. This seems to be counting at two. It's like two
and a half seconds for every one second. Sometimes a little longer. Somebody just came in here and
said, what the fuck am I looking at? Um, demonic power. I agree. We should get rid of this. We
should, we should banish this. I'm on your side. I don't know what this is. It appeared in my,
it appeared next to my outhouse. Showed up in a portal that came from hell. And you know,
hold on. I just, I just saw a bunch of new enemies and I was like, wait, I have to pay attention.
You're from some crazy time in the future. What is happening? What are we looking at?
You could also become like wicked cool. Oh, well, this is what you're watching. It is the great war,
the great war of humanity. Explain to them that this is all, like all of this really happened.
What a ramble stream. They'd be like, it was me. I did this. Then point, point to somebody.
Oh, I want to be the first person to get their milk delivered forever. Okay. Okay.
This game is hurting my head. Um, I think it's hurting everybody's head right now.
Who delivers milk? Um, I don't know all the back in like the fucking 13, 1400s.
It was not, there was no grocery store back in like the 1400s.
It was like a butcher. It was a milkman. Okay. I think I gotta go forward a little bit. I gotta
go forward a little bit because the milkman was not back in like 1300s. It was like in the 20s.
The milkman drove a truck. Okay. Okay. If in the 1400s, there was a milkman that got teleported
back in the milkman uniform with milk in a thing and had the milkman truck, would he also be like
killed and banished? Would they, you know, like the, like I'm delivering the milk today. Like,
hello, good morning, Mrs. Stevenson. Like would they get, would that guy be like scary?
I want level 134. They would a hundred percent kill him. Oh, good day. How are you? Oh, Mrs.
Stevenson. Here it is. Fresh milk. Get him. Like what would they, I feel like they, I don't think
they would. It was like dancing around and like moving, moving his arms, like really happily.
How many times can I revive? Clown, not a milkman. He's different. Get him. He's different.
Hello, Mrs. Stevenson. How are you? Oh, yep. Fresh milk. Get him. He's,
this thing, they grab him. We need muffins. All right. I locked some stuff, but that's enough.
The third coming of Jesus. It's a milkman. The 1500s needed the muffins. Those muffins
would have been disposed of quicker than you could have blinked your eyes. If they, if Kermit the
Frog was playing the banjo on a rock, like throw a fucking javelin at him. You know what I mean?
They would, I don't think that back in like the 1400s, 1300s, I don't think so. Wait,
they did puppet shows, didn't they? There were puppets. They did like shows and plays. Yes,
they would. That would be fine. That would be fine. They did like plays and shows and stuff.
Theater. Why would they go after, why would they do that? How far back do you have to go before,
okay, how far back do you have to go before Kermit the Frog playing a banjo on a rock would be like
terrifying and like, oh my God, what is going on over there? You have to go to 200 BC?
You'd have to go like back 2000 years ago? I don't think, I think it's a little further. I
think the cavemen, the cavemen would be scared of anything. But what was right after cavemen?
They had frogs back then, but they didn't have like muppets and puppets and like, oh hey, it's me.
They didn't do that. Ancient Greece had shadow puppets. They would do puppets. What about before
ancient Greece? When would a javelin get thrown at Kermit, like a puppet? I don't know why I care
about this. All right, I'll be right back. We're gonna, we gotta get this out of our system.
It would have to have been tens of thousands of years ago. Puppets are older than javelins, dude.
Well, like a bug of rock, like a huge boulder, like somebody would run over and just smash one
of the puppet's heads. I guess you'd have to go, yeah, yeah, it'd have to be like 200 BC or something.
But do, all right, hold on though. Wait, this is important. Do you guys don't think that a caveman
one day would be funny, like jokey and be like, and they would all be around the campfire like,
yes. I think that would be, I think that would probably happen. Like this is supposed to be you.
And the two of them were like, that definitely happened. I think that, I think it would be fine.
Who cares? All right, I'll be back in like two minutes. Gotham Knights coming up.
I'm gonna play a different character this time. After Gotham Knights, we're gonna do the deadly
night game. It's gonna be scary. I'll be right back.