Yeah, Half-Life Alex. Half-Life Alex. I've been waiting about a year, waiting a while to play Half-Life Alex.
I told you, everybody thought I was gonna take a day off today. No, I'm here. After yesterday, I was a little tight, yes.
But I'm not taking a day off. I got VR to play. Though in an hour and ten minutes when this stream has to turn off,
we can both be right. How does that sound?
How you guys doing? Hope you're doing well. How drunk is he?
Ugh. On a scale of one to ten? Maybe like, like seven?
Yeah, it's like, it's like two fifteen, guys. I'm obviously a seven right now. No, I'm drunk. I've got a coffee in my hands.
You're always a seven. Don't play the, don't play Alex on the Vive. Well, this is, what, I'm sorry.
I'm the sorry bastard that got the Wii
and have to play the shitty version of the AAA games. They're called Call of Duty 3 on the Xbox.
Call of Duty 3 on the Wii was like an N64 game. I have the Wii version of all these AAA games.
Or they just make a party game. And they do, oh, Assassin's Creed for the Xbox 360.
Hi, 1080p graphics. And then they make the one for the Wii. Assassin's Creed, where's the party?
And there's bowling. I, I had to play that one. And they all have like big heads.
They all, they all got like big avat, like Wii avatar heads.
But me, sorry, me, sorry. Please play Assassin's Creed Wii bowling.
Oh, big head tennis. Don't make fun of my weird mannerisms. I'm aware of them.
Remember, anytime I'm about to say something, I say, oh, oh, and, and, oh, oh, I know that.
Like it's been made, people have told me that a thousand times. I know. Oh, oh, it even bleeds
into other characters. Dick Bugleberry. It's just like, oh, and, oh, oh, I can't help it.
I just, it's, it's a filler word. When are you going to play Chubby Bunny? I'm not playing
Chubby Bunny right now. I'm doing Half-Life Alex, the most anticipated virtual game
since the second one came out. Now, a lot of people were like hyped up for this game.
I kind of wasn't. So I'm going in with completely just basic expectations.
I'm really not hyped up about this at all. So I'm not a liar. I swear to God. I, I, I,
I have to be completely honest with you guys. I kind of don't even care that I'm playing this
right now. I've made sure to not give a shit because I want to be either blown away or not.
Like, I don't want it to, I got to have my expectations. Like, I don't care, right? I've
been telling myself, no, you don't fucking care. Who cares? It's a dumb game. Who cares?
You're going to get blown to hell. Get the other controllers. I got the Wii controllers,
all right? What's wrong with you? What do you mean what's wrong? What's wrong with you?
Why are you saying that? Here we are. And just in case you didn't know,
just in case you didn't know, I'm on Twitch. Do you ever think, I've, no, I've already talked
about this. I already went over, like, if the doctor went to the drive-through with his doctor's
coat on. Like, I don't like to wear this shit anywhere besides, like, in front of the camera
here. Because people see the shirt and they go, you Twitch? Twitch, huh? And I'm just like, oh,
yeah, I'm a fan. I don't even, I like, I stole this. I stole this shirt. It's like, if a doctor
goes to like a drive-through at Dunkin' Donuts and he wears his lab coat, they're going to be like,
you're a doctor? Yeah, yeah, fuck, I forgot I had this on. No, no, I'm an engineer. I don't do that.
Somebody said nice bulge. Oh, that's funny. That you can literally not see below my waist right now.
And that guy for 20 minutes. Like, you mean this? Is that what you mean? Is that the thing
you're describing? Because, I mean, that's there. That's what we mean. Right, okay. He's got a dad
bod? I'm not 20. I'm not even 25. I'm not even 30. I look good for 35, okay? You can see the outline
of my breasticles. Don't you know that means that's a good thing for a 35-year-old? I can do this.
And I can do this. That actually kind of hurt. I know I shouldn't do that. You know, if you tell
yourself that you look good in the mirror over and over again at some point, hey, guess what?
What's that? Oh, wow, that's the wart finger. No, it's not. It's covered up today. Sorry about that,
guys. No wart jokes today. All right, I'm ready. No more stalling. Wait, one more, one more sip
of coffee. I don't want the thing to fly off. Oh, let me put it down on my coaster.
I like the bedroom of like an 11-year-old boy. You guys ready for Half-Life Alex or should I
continue? I'm going in. Close to going. Am I gonna get this shit good? Look, you get to stall
on a game like this. This is the plan for today. I'm not changing games. Like, I'm playing Half-Life
Alex until I can't breathe anymore, which would probably be in about an hour, two hours, three,
I don't know, maybe four. You're a doomer. How would I be a doomer? Ready. God, it's been so
long since I've gone into the world of Half-Life. I forgot the whole story because it was seriously
like fucking 15 years ago. I can't wait to not even know fucking basic characters' names. Why is this
so tight? This hurts. Ow. This fucking hurts. I think I broke it from last night. I didn't even
care. Okay, I'm ready. You guys ready? Here we are. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Didn't I fuck with this
last night? 64, right? Show the settings. I'll show the settings in a second. Hold on. I can't
even hear myself talk. Okay. Not quit. Show the settings. Sure. Okay. You wanna see? There. There
you go. There you go. Okay. Yeah, it's on low. I got a 1080. I can't even put that on medium,
I don't think. Here we go. Difficulty normal. Challenging combat. Very challenging. Easy. Wait,
there's a mode below easy? There's a story mode? Do you even play the game or do you just sit and
watch? That's actually kind of cool. All right, I'm doing normal. No, we're not doing hard.
That's not happening. Movement. Blink. Teleport to destinations with fast linear movement.
Move continuously based on your head orientation. Move continuously based on your hand orientation
or blink. It's no audio. What the fuck? Oh, sorry. Where the fuck is the mouse? There you go. Got it.
Okay, good. Wait, which one of these is better? Blink with head orientation. Is that the best one?
Blink sucks. Continuous hand. Continuous hand. Can I change this? Continuous head.
Can I stop moving? Continuous head. Okay. Aim slot. S.O. 50. All right. Quiet. Here comes the
cutscene. Gotta go. Hello. That was not a good intro. Right. Do I get visited? Do I get visited
by a Gorgonaut? It's five years before the collapse of the Citadel and the death of Eli Vance.
Oh yeah. Object. Alex Vance. Age 19. Female. Affiliation. Human resistance. Current assignment.
A connoissance. Why are you here? This is like the third game they've made. Why? What are you
doing here? You don't jump. You don't watch like fucking Return of the Jedi first and then go,
wait, hold on. Darth Vader is just dead? Holy shit. Okay, low fidelity graphics. My ass. This
looks fantastic. What station does it have to be on? Push to move. Push. Whoa. Push snap. Turn left or
right? Oh, that's okay. Pretty good fidelity, I think. You hit somebody. All of a sudden you
hear like. What's saying? Why am I acting like a caveman? That was just handed this. Who was this?
Oh, this make me angry. Oh, dude, sick. You got a fucking GTX 3090. What do I have to do?
What do I do? Crush the can. Oh, you can't. Isn't there like a fucking alien invasion?
Oh, incoming call. How do I turn on device? Oh, I hate that already. Metricot movement is normal.
Same for the combine patrols. How's it going in the stockyard?
One combine. Oh, I don't like that subtitle. They're never going to miss it. Here, see for yourself.
Someone's taken the combine construction network. Don't get greedy guys. We're not made of time here.
One minute and I'm out. Guaranteed. Oh, also I spotted the combine supplies into the quarantine
zone. That place has been deserted for years. That is all. Well, we'll look into it. Oh,
let's pay attention. Eat back at the safe house baby. Eat back at the safe house. What is it,
Russell? Is the game blinking? Is my character blinking? I keep seeing like a little like black
flash. Like flash. Like I'm blinking. And no, no, no, no, no. It's not me blinking in the headset.
Right? That's me. No, it's not. I'm telling you. All right. Let's go. Of course, you can.
What is he drawing? Me. Me. Me. Son. Explode. Wait, what's this? B 456 B pilon seven B.
I don't know. Do I need that information? I don't know. All right. Let's go meet in the safe house.
I'm telling you, the shit's blanking.
How do I get out of here?
Enable spectator mode.
It's too jerky.
Enable spectator.
I think it's already on.
Medium?
Turn on spectator.
Yeah, it's already on.
What button do I press?
Capture the game window.
Capture the game.
Isn't that what I'm doing?
We're capturing the wrong thing.
Capture game window.
Wait a minute.
I'm coming out.
I'm capping the VR view.
Should I not be doing that?
Capture the actual game engine.
Spectator mode shows us your ammo and shit.
Oh.
Wait a minute.
Turn off the subtitles.
Wait, hold on.
This is like a lot to take in right now.
I'm doing the steam mirror thing.
So I just cap the actual game?
Like that.
So this is like the actual game being captured, not the VR window.
Okay.
The game is now being captured.
How do you actually get into the settings of the game?
What's the pause menu?
Left grip?
Oh, fuck yeah.
All right, let's go.
All right, now help me out here.
Options menu.
Spectator.
Yeah, spectator camera.
Okay.
Spectator HUD.
Medium.
Spectator smoothing low.
Spectator medium.
On high.
Is that going to work?
Can my computer do this?
And turn off the subtitles.
Is that good?
All right.
Subtitles for spectator only.
Subtitles in closed captions.
Subtitles for spectator.
Subtitles on.
Subtitles spectator window only.
Okay.
I didn't...
Well, there are a lot of settings in this fucking game.
I gotta check these cables.
Why am I getting a black light?
Everything's good.
Oh, because I dropped the headset on the ground last night.
What am I stupid?
All right, I'm ready.
Let's go.
It's playable.
All right, let's get out of here.
Is that better?
Out of the door.
Much better?
Okay.
Well, I didn't...
Every VR game I've ever played was just like plug it in and turn it on.
I didn't know there was like all these settings.
All right, let's go.
You can't see the chat?
Oh, the fucking chat is now not viewable.
Okay, well, we'll deal with that later.
Oh, toggle game mode.
Right.
I would have said to walk down the stairs.
Okay, here we go.
Hey, it doesn't even matter.
Like, you guys...
What do you mean?
You guys can see the chat.
I just...
You guys are...
You guys are there.
Because every time I go like this, you just know that I'm looking at you.
All right, let's move.
Do my part!
All right, I'm going back in.
Well, that was fucking crazy.
I need the full audio experience.
Oh.
Oh, there's an alien in there.
Let him out?
Oh, let the alien out.
What are we looking at?
Are we filming this?
Feed him.
Feed the baby.
Feed him with what?
This?
Oh!
I don't overfeed the fish.
Don't overfeed...
Some people just sit there and they just dump.
Over and over and over and over and over and over again.
Fuck it.
My stream is on.
Why is my video feed...
I just caught that.
Barely.
Right there, I saw, like, my stream playing.
All right, let's go.
Oh, shit.
I think it just hit you.
See?
Can I pull this down?
All right, whatever.
It wants me to aim it right there.
Is he standing there?
I think there's a person standing there.
Let me in!
He's got, like, a little finger.
All right, let's move.
Wait, wait, wait, where are we going?
Uh, I don't know.
This one?
This one.
That one.
The only one that works.
What?
Nobody can do more wire but him.
Alex!
Hey!
Are we good?
Yep, they got the reactor.
Easy peasy.
I'm headed back to the safe house right now to meet Dad.
The dinosaur DNA is in here.
Stay safe.
Hey!
Whoa!
Ow!
My hand!
Too much strength.
What's in here?
Documents.
All right, go.
We're under attack.
I have to, like, move my butt.
Alex, over here.
Hey!
What is it?
This doesn't seem like a routine sweep.
Are you sure?
I don't know.
I have to, like, move my butt.
Alex, over here.
Hey!
What is it?
This doesn't seem like a routine sweep.
Are you sure everything went okay?
100 percent.
Okay, let's do a funny thing.
Get a camera.
I'll be like, hey, let me out of here.
Yoo-hoo!
Oh, yeah!
Here we go.
Didn't work.
How do I run?
How do you run?
He's so slow.
What?
There we go.
Oh, my God.
I didn't see him.
Oh, shit.
Cargo.
Oh.
In there?
Door.
Store.
What?
Door.
Hey!
I won't!
No, no, no, no, no!
I just...
Ow!
Come on!
Fred.
Eat this?
Hey, I feel like something just popped up on my HUD.
What?
Oh, I eat cookies.
Oh, yeah.
Thumbs up.
I ate it.
This is fucking...
OK, I'm going to fall.
And that's, ladies and gentlemen, what it would look like if bugs ruled the world.
If bugs were even 20% larger than they are now, that's the kind of shit we'd be dealing
with.
I would never leave my house, ever.
Should I bring this with me?
I need it.
All right.
It's just like Hitman.
It's just like fucking Hitman.
I got, like, my guns in here, and they're going to pat me down.
I just got a delivery!
I just live here!
Shoot!
Pat me down.
I got a delivery for the mafia boss!
I didn't steal anything.
This just flowers for fuck's sake!
No one!
I didn't see anyone!
Quick, run!
Dear.
Nice posture.
Shut up.
Give me a break.
I got, like, a 12-pound thing on my head.
Where are you taking me?
This posture.
Where's my father?
Hello?
Damn it!
Where's my father?
Just stop moving around.
Asshole.
It's Wheatley!
Wheatley's coming to save us!
Sticks in his...
Sorry!
I didn't mean to...
Alex, run!
If you see something here, just be...
I'm sorry!
Nice.
PlayStation 2 gamer headset.
Russell?
I told you.
I've been in an accident.
I know!
I caused it.
So, technically, not an accident.
You've got to get moving.
Wait.
Where's Dad?
He's fine.
Follow the drone.
It's Wheatley.
All right, let's go.
So, Dad's okay, right?
Yeah.
Well, no.
To be honest, he's in huge trouble.
But...
I still...
I can't help it.
I have to help him.
I need to have something in my hands.
I'm one of those weirdos.
I had no way of knowing who was in the window.
If I don't have something in my hand, I can't function.
Yes.
The result was that I saved you.
Do we know where they're taking him?
Criminal holding.
And then, when they realized he was Eli Vance,
they want to plan to get him back.
Hey.
You're close to my lab.
Keep following the drone.
What's true?
Bring up the jump indicator and release to jump.
Russell, what did you guys find back there?
Well, that's the crazy thing.
I don't know.
Just...
Just very picturesque building.
Citadel?
Something else.
And whatever it is...
Okay.
Jump indicator.
Russell, just hang on.
I'm almost there.
When do I get a gun?
Force push!
Minus two.
Come on.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can we get to play?
Can I play this with him?
Please tell me I can play this with him.
All right.
It's me versus you, chat.
Ready?
I'm X's UROs, okay?
Guess what?
It'll...
Okay.
I'm over it.
Wait, can I?
Ow!
And here's the best feature of the game.
Hey!
Ah!
He's dead!
He didn't see us.
Oh, no.
It's the last...
It's the last remnant of Wheatley's chat piece.
What did that say?
I need that tutorial.
To mantle, push, and hold while moving.
Hello?
Hello, hello, hello?
Whoa, stop.
There was a phone on there.
It's too heavy.
Holy shit, this is like 50 pounds.
Secret entrance.
Okay, let's wait.
Nope, it exploded.
I'm fine, by the way.
Right.
Let me get the tea.
Okay.
I promise I'm your grandmother.
Russell.
They've got Dad.
I know.
This...
This is bad.
They're gonna find out what he knows and then, yeah, they're gonna kill him.
Oh, God.
But, the good news is, we've got something they don't.
Which is?
My plan to get him back.
Great.
Let's hear it.
Now, pretty soon they're gonna realize that your Dad is not gonna talk.
And when that happens, he's off to have his brain sucked out.
Russell.
Potentially.
Maybe not, though.
I mean, they could just drill into his...
Stop.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Well, what they will do is take a train from here...
What's happening?
This is Eli to Nova Prospect.
And if he gets on that train, that's it, right?
Not necessarily.
Grab something that represents us.
It has some cool computers in here, man.
A teacup?
There's plenty of these around.
Of course, it's a teacup.
Okay, that's you.
That's us.
I thought you said us.
Well, one of us, me, will have to stay here for this plan to work.
All right.
Fair enough.
Just outside, there's a second train that also leads out of 717 through the quarantine zone.
Okay.
Both trains intersect here at the Fairview Junction.
I'm ready to go.
Get there before this train and hack into the controls.
That'll let me take over the system.
Train comes to a halt, you deal with the Combine situation, and we get your Dad back.
Sounds good.
Where's the train I'm taking?
Out the back, through the yard.
It's decommissioned, but I think I can hack into its controls.
Oh, and get yourself a pair of Russells on the way out.
Anybody else feel like this is two people under a train show?
Alex, you know, the Gravity Clubs.
I have a few sets through there.
You can calibrate them out by the ship.
Got it.
We can do this, Alex.
You got that, didn't you?
Though I said we could do it.
All right, here we go.
Yeah, we are.
Oh, yeah.
This is where you get the portal gun.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I...
That's hard.
You guys take that up.
I can't see that.
You guys are in the way.
All right, I'll do it.
What am I touching?
Back up.
Time to get a gun?
Can't even get the light bulb.
The game's not even good.
I missed it.
You missed it.
What?
Did I miss something?
Did I miss?
I missed it.
I thought that was really the wall right next to me.
It's the same color as the wall.
I thought that was the wall in my house.
All right, you know how this goes.
There should be a bunch of junk down there.
Aim at something with your hand open.
What?
You're attached.
Make a grip.
Now target something with the rustles.
Target it.
Close your hand.
Register it.
Now flick your wrist to bring it in.
Catch it.
Try again.
That's it.
That's cool.
One more time.
Yep, you did it.
Make a grip.
You've got it.
Just a little flick of the wrist.
Just like that.
Perfect, we're done.
Oh, wait.
I almost forgot.
Alex, up here.
You're going to need a gun.
Don't worry.
It's unloaded.
It's unloaded now.
Oh, almost forgot.
Guns need ammo.
I really could have used that bullet, Ted.
Force push.
Got it.
Press button or pull slide to do it.
How much ammo do I have?
I have a lot of ammo?
What was the last thing you said?
At the gnome.
Where?
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
There's an herb here.
Resident Evil told me I could eat these.
This is no.
What do you want me to do?
Where's my gun?
Where are you?
Where are you guys?
Okay.
Move cam top right.
Let's see if I can do it.
And go.
Got it.
I got it.
I actually got it.
Well, okay.
So what does he want me to do?
Shoot at his...
Shoot in his window?
What does he want me to do?
Jump over this?
Can I be able to vault over this?
Am I blind?
Well, that, that, that, that, that.
Okay.
I don't know where the gnome is, guys.
All right.
Shoot this lock off.
Nice.
Oh, you took care of that lock then.
Good.
Great.
Did have the key for it.
But should have given you that.
More ammo in backpack.
That didn't work?
Okay.
There we go.
All right.
Here we go.
Next stop, Fairview Junction.
How do you reload?
And good luck, Alex.
Goodbye.
Obviously, just to let you know,
I am still here though.
I know.
Okay.
Oh, it's a load.
It is a cool loading screen.
It shows you the entire Sim,
Sim City area.
City Skylines.
Whatever.
You think this city is better
built than anything I build
in City Skylines?
Look at this.
What's the traffic doing over there?
What kind of roads are these?
Look at...
Oh, curved roads.
Oh, mega-lull.
Give me a break.
And I get shit for how I design a city?
Don't see the loading screen though.
Hello, Alex?
We might have a problem.
Probably nothing to worry about, but...
I'm just...
Did the train stop?
It stopped, didn't it?
Yeah.
What happened?
Oh, it's jammed.
When the Combine shut down
the quarantine zone,
they must have tightened security.
Which means?
Yeah, you're nowhere near
Fairview Junction.
You're just outside the QZ.
And this is as far as
we get by train.
Then I'm headed on foot.
Good.
I'll see if I can get you
in some other way.
Here we go.
Are you guys going to stand up?
There's a dead zombie here.
I thought the Combine
sealed up the QZ.
Oh.
This one must have...
with barnacle spores
outside the containment area.
Probably not a one-off then.
Oh, so you can pick them up?
I doubt it.
Press to bring up jump indicator
or at least...
I don't think this is going to stand up
and I'm going to have to shoot it.
I'll go that way.
That looks dangerous.
Wait.
Ooh!
That's...
I'm not going to be very good at that.
Perch the environment
for useful items.
Ooh, what's this?
Would you look at that?
And if there's resin around here
there should be a Combine fabricator.
Keep an eye out.
We might be able to upgrade
your firepower a bit.
Really?
This upgrades?
Wait, was I supposed to wait
for somebody?
Key plots?
Do not enter.
All right, this is...
I know something's going to
fucking jump out.
They don't give you the gauntlet.
When the guy comes in
the one enemy you have to kill.
I think I can reroute this
with my multi-tool.
Your what?
It's a tool with multiple functions.
So, you know, multi-tool.
Oh, it's...
Okay.
Use multi-tool.
This is cool.
All right, did I just turn the power on?
Did I not do it long enough?
Hold on.
Oh, it's a puzzle game play.
Alex, that thing's incredible.
Something that really sells it.
Who am I going to sell it to?
I'm not telling you.
The Combine's not going to be here forever.
You should be thinking
about the future, Alex.
Well, how about I call it...
His step ladder.
The...
Alex.
It's a little derivative of the Russells,
but yeah, provisionally, sure.
The Alex.
Yeah.
Sweaty ears.
I gotta reroute the power
from here.
Hold on.
Oh, just like in Saw.
Fucking Saw.
Why is it...
Russells.
The Combine use these.
Are they safe for people?
Yeah, I use them all the time.
Wait, what just happened?
Yeah, they're great.
Ow.
Hey, you were right.
These are great.
You got a flashlight?
You have to quickly switch to and from your hand.
Heavy objects with both hands.
Don't touch everything.
I'm touching every single object
in the whole game world.
Oh, careful of that barnacle, Alex.
Oh, these things are in the game?
Oh, I hated these in Half-Life.
Oh.
Is that right?
Yeah.
First try.
They said try again in a year.
I don't need to tell you
what happened after that.
Lucky break for me, really.
First try, guys.
Honestly, it's a miracle
you and your dad got out of it.
All right, watch out.
Don't touch that.
Something moved in there.
Come here, come here.
I need you.
I need you for a minute.
Get it.
Did you get it?
He doesn't want it.
He's like, eww, gross.
That's a dead body, dude.
Get him.
What are you holding on to?
Throw that.
Put it down.
Take him.
Take it.
Come on.
I'm about to throw this guy out of the bar.
Oh, God damn it.
What happened?
What's going on?
Where am I?
I just see a sun setting.
I think I'm in the ceiling.
You're out of the play zone.
I got eaten.
I got eaten by the barnacle,
Did I touch it and then just get sucked straight up?
Hey!
It doesn't miss.
Shit, I need that.
I need that.
This is the worst ride at Disney World.
I need to reset.
I need those things.
I sucked one of those upgrade stones into the thing's head and it destroyed it.
I need that thing.
I don't want to shoot it because that's a waste of money.
That's a waste of ammo.
Careful of that barnacle, Alex.
Okay, I'm ready.
Yeah.
Where am I?
I interviewed at Black Mesa.
They said try again in a year.
I'm not going to fuck this up.
Honestly, it's a miracle you and your dad got out of it.
Give me that thing.
Oh, shit.
I have to shoot them.
What?
Fuck.
Give me that.
Don't touch anything.
I missed the resin?
What?
No, I didn't.
Where?
Where's the resin?
Oh, right.
All right, we're good.
Here we go.
Ready?
What the fuck?
Can I get in here?
No, wrong fucking guy.
Should I shoot?
Kill it?
How do I reload the gun?
Let's go.
Finally.
Quiet.
I mean, it is quiet.
I'm going to get ambushed.
How many do I have in this gun?
Six.
I take it the quarantine zone is behind this hatch?
Yeah, yeah, that's where they keep it.
Look around for a control panel.
Oh, no, no control panel.
Shoot that thing and it'll go ding!
It'll turn to green.
I mean, it was worth the shot.
I didn't even know I was back there.
I can't wait to upgrade.
This is going to be so much fun.
What about anything over here?
The combine?
Where would I put a control panel?
Oh, does that hurt?
Is shit in here?
These things are everywhere.
This is like an Easter egg hunt.
This is awesome.
I hear a bug.
Why am I looking in the toilet?
What the fuck is wrong with me?
I thought that was going to be a resin stone.
I got a lot of these.
My face is itchy.
That's a bad sign.
Is this how the speedrunners do this game?
Okay, we're looking for a control panel.
That's it right there, isn't it?
Climb this.
Control panel.
Wait, wait, wait.
I have a tool.
I feel like I'm struck by lightning doing this.
This is like a Chevy Chase movie.
Oh, I got it.
I'm just trying to get a signal.
Yikes!
What do I do?
That up there?
Harry Potter joke incoming.
What do you mean by Harry?
That's a control panel right here.
This is electricity, right here.
This is an electricity panel.
What the hell is this?
Look with your special eyes.
Aren't I doing that?
This is definitely a control panel.
Absolutely.
It has a handle on it.
Look, it's got a handle on it.
Am I dead?
Follow the wire.
I think I may have found it.
Oh, you grabbed me, you resin evil.
Yep, up there.
Wait, I keep climbing the window.
Oh, you're alive?
Oh, that's me making that noise.
I need this window, dude.
Wait a minute.
Stay right there.
And before your very eyes,
I'm going to take the dollar out of your pocket
and put it in your girlfriend's.
Can you believe it?
Street magic with Gerber 985.
I'll get it, sir.
Not what I'm supposed to do?
Fuck.
Can I just push it?
Oh my god, oh my god, I can't use this.
Ah, a lot of shit in here.
Okay, right here?
Look at that.
Ooh, cigarette.
Okay, if you put it into your mouth,
it just goes right in.
Really important.
Anyone have an ashtray?
A control panel, wait.
There?
There's something I can turn on in there, right?
There's something I can turn on over there.
Control panel.
I've probably scrambled the circuit,
but considering no one would be dumb enough
to open the hatch,
it shouldn't be too hard to put back.
Okay, wait.
How much debt do I have?
I got full health, I don't need that.
Okay, let's go.
Oops, who are you?
What's that?
Okay, multi-tool.
How much?
Oh, okay.
I need to put a device in here?
Yeah, I need to put a tube in there.
How's that?
All right, what's that?
Does it explode?
Is that to put?
Where does it want me to go?
I don't understand which one it goes in.
How do I tell?
Can I tell?
Can I get a thing that tells me?
Oh, can I get an emergency thing?
Now that I'm walking into the quarantine zone,
it just hit me.
Is that in the game?
Well, actually, the word quarantine
means 40 days.
Oh, shit.
The period that all ships were required to be isolated
before crew could go ashore during the Black Death.
That's an amber alert.
Let me look at this for a sec.
It's not around here.
I thought that was in the game.
I was like, that's the complete demission sound?
Yeah, it's in Utah, apparently.
Jesus Christ.
Hold on.
Actually, I'm going to take this opportunity to pee
and this is so fogged up in here.
I've been playing for a fucking hour.
It's been like 10 minutes.
Holy shit, I must be having a lot of fun.
All right, let me go get a water
and let me just clean this out.
I'll be right back.
Okay, I'm back.
The worst part about VR
is you get so sweaty in this thing
that I almost wish there was a way
to make it so like you didn't bog up
the lenses every 40 minutes.
Are you guys counting?
Spectator smoothing.
The spectator smoothing is on high.
I'm out right now, so
are we good?
Let me just do a check here.
Are we good?
I'm making sure because when I'm in there
it's kind of hard to, you get in VR
and you can't even tell what's going on.
How are the subtitles?
Oh, I don't see that on the screen.
That would be awesome if I could see
how much health and breath.
I'm going to have to ask you guys these things
because I don't even see that shit.
I'm going back in.
Chat is on that hand too,
so when I see how much health I have
I see you guys spamming like omega lulz.
Move it.
No, I can't, it has to be on my left hand.
My right hand is my shooting hand.
I can't be like in the middle of shooting
and be like, hey guys, hey, hold on a minute.
What are you saying?
No, that's not going to happen.
That's better.
Better, better, better.
Oh boy, it's starting to crush my eyes.
All right, let's go.
We're good?
Look at it.
Okay, we're good.
Oh, there it is.
There's the power thing.
I'm sick.
What am I, like 60, 70% of the way through the game?
Maybe 80% of the way through the game?
It's pretty good so far.
It didn't do anything?
What's in there?
There's like guts in here.
Oh, don't, no.
Get him out of there.
Oh no, he's like part of it.
Part of it.
What the hell?
How do we get him out of there?
I can't.
It's the inception sound.
That's the inception music.
Ha ha.
Finally.
You'll go through the old subway tunnels on your way to the train yard.
Have they started moving down yet?
I don't think so, which is good news because we've still got time.
Great.
Or bad news because they've already killed them
and you don't need to move a corpse.
You just bury it.
Yeah.
Can that get on me every five minutes?
Get that gun out.
I feel like it's going to be trouble.
Load it.
Russell, are you seeing this?
What is this?
Great.
There we go.
Can I take that?
It's so annoying.
I tried to shoot the alien, whatever.
I haven't seen any resin for a little while.
Oh, why not?
Oh, all right.
Next part of the game.
Resin.
Been at the same bit for 20 minutes.
I took a break too.
That's going to explode.
That's an explosive barrel.
It's going to blow up.
It doesn't work every time.
Hey, Russell.
I just found a loose syringe of God knows what.
Is this medicine?
Does it have a skull and cross spines on it?
I don't see one.
Adrenaline should probably be medicine then.
Back in like 2004 when this was ridiculous.
God, how we've gone so far.
Back in 2004, this was like showing the movie of the train to the people in the 1800s.
They thought they were going to get hit by the fucking train.
The first movie ever when everyone in the audience was like,
the train's going to hit us.
That was 2004 with like the first physics based game.
Is there a...
This is going to explode.
Resin, search.
Any resin?
No, that's stupid.
The old prospector.
Don't go near that one.
Let me see.
I've got a lantern here.
Let's see if I can see where the gold is.
Get that fucking guy away from us.
Don't do that.
Get the old man out of here.
I changed my mind.
I want it.
Let's take a look and see.
Be careful.
I heard there were monsters down here.
Oops.
I can't hold it.
Oh, it's one of these guys.
I heard they will suck on your brain.
Yeah, that is.
Eat this, motherfucker.
Oh, it didn't go far enough.
Oh, shit, I missed.
I could have had him just suck it up.
Clock it, clock it, clock it.
That seemed to work.
Keep doing that.
I got it.
Clock it, clock it.
Yeah, clock it.
Oh, quick.
Oh, just so you know, the Russells have a built-in display.
The show might come in handy.
Yeah, I got it.
Thanks.
Check for resin.
I haven't gotten any resin.
I'm terrible.
Is resin this bad at the game or am I not seeing any?
What's a gas mask?
I put it on.
Holy shit, I didn't even know you could do that.
I heard a noise.
I heard somebody heard a noise.
Oh, this is a Ghostbusters thing.
Do I actually need that, though?
Oh, shit, all right, good.
Oh, what's the point of doing that?
Just go like this.
This is fun.
Can you do it to the skull?
Oh, get the hat.
I don't need a hat.
I have nine resins.
Is that good?
How much ammo is in this?
Can you tell how much bullets?
Wait, does it say that on here?
Look, bud.
How am I going to let this mean lover try to get over here
and try to shoot me?
I don't work.
Smash his head.
Back.
Am I shitting him?
Out of here.
Lock it in the head.
Do you think I'm aiming for his toes?
I have 90 ammo.
Are you serious?
Why am I trying so hard to not waste it?
Ace, what's in it?
Oh, there's a lock on it?
Of course it's impossible to get into.
It's a Samsonite.
I'll jump for that guy.
I like to pick him up and pretend to be an alien.
Oh, shit.
Oh, man.
I don't want to do it, man.
I don't want to do it.
How much ammo is in this?
Six.
This is fun as fuck.
What is that?
Is this a coffin?
Alex, I think that's a combined fabricator.
Put something in it.
Will it work on a Russell's?
No, but it should fix up that pistol nicely.
Good thing, too.
I gave you one of my lesser gum.
Resin?
Thanks, Russell.
Oh, resin.
Come on, it's got to be resin in here somewhere.
Come on, man.
It's got to be resin.
All right, it'll do.
See?
Wait.
This is probably resin in this old grandmother's attic box.
I knew it.
Any more?
I can't put the glove on.
Can I open this?
Fun. Very fun.
Wait a minute, over here.
Batteries?
I'm a resin boy right now.
All right, I think I got it.
Please take the hat off.
There's only the hat?
Get over here.
Oh, I get it.
You got to have the line go through everything.
I got it.
It takes a second to figure out a puzzle.
Oh, man.
Oh, yeah, this is cool.
Reflex site?
Or should I hold the laser reflex site?
I might as well.
I always feel like this.
Whenever you go to a store and they have the iPad that you have to sign and touch,
I'm always like, I don't want to touch this screen, man.
Reflex sucks.
It's terrible.
Is it?
Whatever, I'm good.
How do I insert resin?
Oh, oh, reflex is ass.
It's all right.
Looks pretty cool.
What are you talking about?
Wait, so that circle is not my crosshair.
How does that suck?
That's sick.
Who's this head so much?
I mean, am I moving my head too much?
Fun guy.
All right, let's, let's heal.
Oh, I can see the dot.
Oh, this is actually going to be fucking kind of hard to use.
I get it now.
I'm hurting them.
All right, I'm good.
I got my reflex site.
I've got my ready to go site.
But my resin, it's all right.
There's tons of resin in the game.
Right out.
Oh, my God.
Lock it.
It actually, I, it doesn't, it's actually kind of good.
Seriously.
It highlights the head.
No.
You guys see what I'm saying, right?
Oh, my God.
I thought it was going to explode.
Oh, buddy.
Get out of here.
It's not bad.
What?
I don't know what you could do.
Somebody came in the door.
You can do that.
All right.
Resident search, thank you.
What the fuck is this?
Oh, my God.
Resident Evil 4 taught me so well.
I don't have any more.
I got plenty.
Any complainers?
Five minutes you play.
Guys, something that you guys have to remember is Resident Evil 4 was the original GTA V.
What I mean by that is they came out with the game.
They've re-released it like eight times.
This is like before Skyrim did this.
This is before Resident Evil 5.
I mean before GTA V did this.
They released it on like 12 different consoles.
I've played through it like four times.
Why are you talking about releases?
Somebody just said I've never played.
Somebody said I've played four minutes of Resident Evil 4.
They don't understand.
What's that?
I see it.
The what?
The lamp?
I hear it.
I hear this motherfucker up in that vent.
I heard him in the vent.
He's in the vent.
I know he's in the vent.
I know you're in that fucking vent.
I see him.
I hate those things.
Do what he just did.
Can I ask a question?
Why do I continue to make Among Us references when I've never played the game?
I don't even play that game.
Why do I keep doing that?
I don't even watch it.
I don't even care.
I'm never going to play it.
I don't get it.
How do I know all this?
I need to stay relevant.
I'm not even trying to.
It's just for some reason.
I'm just talking about it all the time.
I talk about Among Us more than I make WoW references at this point.
That's how you know there's a problem.
I don't even watch that fucking game.
You don't even know what I'm talking about.
I know half of you have played WoW.
Untrue, untrue.
No, come on.
Everybody's played WoW at some point in their life.
Even if you got the get to level 10 trial and said,
this game sucks, I'm never playing it again.
Get pissed off at your friend that introduced you to it.
Be like, dude, fuck it.
I'm not playing this stupid game.
Level 20, whatever.
No.
Radio silence since you got on the train.
Damn.
Well, the good news is he's probably fine.
How do you know that?
Because they're taking him to Nova Prospect to toy with him.
Oh, shit.
So they're hardly going to toy with him.
Yo, what's up?
When did I get hit?
That box?
I didn't think that was going to do anything.
I need a thing over there.
Wait, resin.
I need to make a new indentation on my face.
There we go.
Get this shit out of me.
That's in.
I have to try this.
Floppy disk.
We used to store information on them.
Specifically, two micrometers of magnetic iron oxide.
Three micrometers.
How do you know all that?
I'm reading it here on my computer.
I downloaded the internet before the war.
You downloaded the entire internet?
Most of it.
That's Tim and Eric.
Got the whole internet on this one CD.
That's one of the best bits.
One of the best skits of any comedy television show is the internet on the CD bit that Tim and Eric did.
That's one of the best.
Ah, there we go.
Hosted all options.
Heal.
That healer.
No, it's somewhere.
What did I do with it?
What?
What do you mean, what the fuck?
What happened to this?
I got ultra-resident instinct.
What the hell is that?
Is this electricity or what?
Can I walk into it?
Wait a minute, I'm going to throw something in there and see what happens.
Safe.
It's an eye.
It looks like garbage.
Right.
It seems harmless.
Can I put my hand in this?
This is why I can't play Luigi's Mansion.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
Aha, aha, aha.
Okay.
Resident anywhere else?
Let's go.
Alright, I made it out.
I have to press the series of buttons.
I'm so glad to be outside.
Is this like Kinect 4?
Calling it now, he's going to hit the two correct ones accidentally.
I don't know what makes them correct.
One of these is the right combo.
Going anywhere?
Oh wait, they're over there.
This is just the thing that's in the doctor's office to keep your child occupied.
It'll say it right here.
Look, look, look at that.
Would you look at that?
This tomb is a lot of them.
Which one is the right one?
Any of these.
Do I have to try them all?
Alright, it's that one and that one.
Second row three, fourth row two.
Try every single one.
This one.
Hey, I told you guys I did.
I think this mask in here has been worn down so raw that I'm getting hit with plastic just digging into my face.
I'm going to have to replace it.
Press it?
Might be a waste, but I don't care.
Brick.
Beginning with a brick, I gotta try.
Who bricks?
I can make fire on somebody's head.
Can I crush somebody's head?
Alex, are you alright?
I'm fine, Russell.
What's up?
I'm fine, I'll see you in a minute.
Just get me a large.
Get me a large steak and cheese.
What did I have to say that for?
Why did I say that?
Now I want a large steak and cheese.
Something so bad right now.
Why did I do that?
What the fuck is wrong with me?
That would hurt so much.
I'm ready to pancake somebody's head.
Alright.
Hello?
This is weird.
Ring the doorbell?
The Alex Vans.
I said Gorgon, I-
You see?
Did?
Come, enter.
Okay, thanks.
You are welcome.
So, what's that vortigaunt doing here?
Cooking.
Right, but I mean in general.
Okay.
I do too.
I'm sorry.
My brain is injured.
That's terrible and I hope-
Look, I'm actually pretty busy looking for my father.
The-
Eli Vans.
Yes.
The Combine have him and I really do need to get moving.
The Combine?
Yes, do not go yet.
I will show you something.
Look, I appreciate it.
This way.
I can't stick around.
Is this important?
I know, I'm sure it is.
The Alex Vans must go this way.
This way.
These guys are so cool.
I want some.
Oh, he's the one doing the spells.
Hold on, wait.
I'm missing lore.
The Combine and Alex Vans.
I would help.
I really would, but the Alex Vans is honestly very busy saving her dad.
I will not save him.
He is dead.
What?
Or he will be.
Is or will be?
It is a matter of perspective.
Alex Vans alone cannot prevent his fate.
I-
Look, thank you for everything, but I really have to go.
I'm sorry, but I really don't have time for riddles.
No riddles.
The Combine drilled here.
I am severed from the Vortessence.
I am alone in my head.
I'm sorry.
This is your war.
If I can, if I run across your friends, I will see what I can do.
You have saved my kin.
I haven't.
Then you will.
Venge Alex Vans.
Risen!
Risen, over here.
Oh no, I got-
You must go.
Risen?
You're baiting people with resin over here.
It's probably right there.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
I think I see some resin.
The mission begins.
They might be-
Calm down!
He's gonna suck it in the back of the head.
Whatever, I probably missed the resin.
I'm a fucking maniac.
Just go, Omega Well.
Tell me you didn't get baited from the resin over there.
Oh, he's the one doing this shit.
Oh!
I will help you.
Look to the northern star.
Why?
For guidance.
Okay, thanks.
Are you done helping?
I am not here.
Sustenance.
I'll eat it later.
Thanks for the help.
You'll be welcome.
Why is that such a big deal?
Eat those.
They're just protein and shit.
Why not just eat them?
I don't know, but test it for like, disease?
Let's go.
Why don't you just eat slugs?
Well, I would eat like slugs and bugs and shit if that was the only source of real food that was still around.
There's only so many cans of Chef Boyardee, ravioli, mini raviolis that exist.
Once those are gone, they're gone and then you have to deal with whatever the fuck you have to deal with.
Is it horrible?
Alex, the signal's back.
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
Russell, I'm good.
How's Dad?
I've got him on the train.
He's on the move.
You've got to find Sea View Junction before they get there.
I'm working on it.
Why are these guys going to stand up?
No, come on.
I can't.
I don't want to say it.
I found Yellow, the dead body, among us.
Like, I found him.
Who was it, right?
Like, come on.
I'm sorry.
Why?
It doesn't even make any sense.
Can I use this?
I'm like...
Oh, it's a hat.
Or the Half-Life door sound.
I'm not going to believe this, but I ran into a building.
It's in the heart.
In the heart.
These are the spiky ones.
That brings me more to that stuff.
Fuck!
Try to give up.
Get that off.
I just don't care.
I don't care if I miss.
I don't care if I miss, right?
Like, I don't care if I miss.
Stop caring and you'll get it.
Right?
No, I don't care.
I don't care if I miss.
I don't give a shit if I miss.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to keep moving.
I obviously can't shoot that guy.
I don't even care if I miss.
I don't care.
I don't care if I miss.
Fuck off.
Oh, electricity.
What was that?
Oh, it was just his shoes.
Never mind.
What's in here?
Oh, wait a minute.
Something in the barrel.
What is this?
What is that?
Mask on.
Where's the mask?
Russell, Russell.
I didn't eat it.
Right.
Of course you didn't.
I can check down there, but what is this guy holding?
Pressing.
Oh, that zombie has a shotgun.
What?
There's a shotgun in the game?
All right.
That's shit.
That's the only brick I had.
What do I do now?
I don't drop him?
N-A-A-M.
I'm shooting it.
Omega Low, you idiot.
I just like force walk to the ground.
Okay, hold on.
Okay.
Oh, it's a pulley system.
Launched.
Oh, all right.
There we go.
You hear that?
Yeah.
Let's get this shotgun and get out of here.
What's down there?
I don't...
What do you mean you hear that?
What are these?
I don't know.
The bullets.
Give me the...
Oh, my God.
There's something coming through the door.
How do I get this shotgun?
Give me the shotgun, dude.
Let it go.
Oh, stop.
Where's the thing?
All right.
Stop it right there.
Give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me,
give me, give me, give me.
Oh, yeah.
How do I open shotgun to load shells?
What?
Oh, shit.
Click controller to do that.
Okay.
I got the shotgun.
Oh, this...
What did I just throw?
Get out of here.
Okay.
Whoa.
We did it.
I lost this gun.
Last shell.
I'm out.
Last shell?
Fuck you.
Any more?
Bottom of a gamer?
Really, man?
Maybe?
I'm basically going to stand up.
I haven't gotten any resin either.
I'm so bad.
Such a bad player.
Stiff gamer.
Yeah, kind of.
What's over here?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's something over here.
Oh!
I almost died.
Bottle or something.
Ow!
Oh!
Hell, yeah.
The headcrab.
Can I do that?
Wait.
Who wants a drink?
Fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine.
What does that do?
What does that do for me?
What did I do that for?
Look at the liquid of the bottle.
Look at the liquid.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm going to die.
Okay.
Let me ask you a question.
If you could eat this, if this was completely edible, but it stunk like rotten trash, but
it was like 25 grams of protein in like all your vitamins, like vitamin C, vitamin B,
vitamin A, all of them.
This was like six years worth of food.
If you eat this, or over here, on that pallet over here, is a stack of food.
If you eat this, or over here, on that pallet over here, is a stack of a year's worth of
Chef Boyardee mini raviolis.
And this is like stacked up to this height.
This is at least five years.
This is one year.
I would take that one.
I would take the short thing.
Coming in here.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What?
How could there be nothing in a chest?
That's bullshit.
Wait!
I have a gas mask, right?
I did.
Oh shit.
Okay.
We're not going to fuck around.
Wipe out!
Wasn't even the right guy!
Holy shit.
Okay.
Overkill?
Was it?
Wait, I need to.
I'm just going to...
Who holds a shotgun like this?
I need ammo.
Okay.
Overkill?
Was it?
Wait, I need to.
I'm just going to...
Who holds a shotgun like this?
I need ammo.
Bad, dude.
It's not looking good.
Oh.
I need a resin.
There's a ladder over there.
Holy shit.
Did I kill him?
I almost have full health.
Go there.
These things again.
Okay.
Got it.
Oh, it's an upgrade station.
Oh.
What the fuck are you doing?
More resin.
Okay.
That's it.
Yeah, that's the one.
Look for more resin.
Okay.
What the fuck are you doing?
More resin.
Okay.
I'll take an eye out.
Resin.
Yeah, that's the one.
Look for more resin.
Shit.
Come on.
There's got to be some resin.
Don't I have one of those?
Resin hiding under one of these, I guarantee it.
One of these.
Oh, yeah.
Resin, but I'll take the ammo.
I need it.
Okay.
Do I do the side or do I just hold it?
Do you need a...
Yes.
Okay.
I'll take the ammo.
I need it.
Okay.
Do I do the side or do I just hold it?
Do you need a...
Yes, I would eat a headcrab.
If I had to, if I was like life or death, I'm not going to go like, oh, ew, gross, ew,
no, I don't want it.
Like, if I'm going to die, if I'm starving to death, I'm going to eat a headcrab.
Why wouldn't you?
Why are you so against doing that?
Ew, but I don't really need to.
I saved the resin.
I'm not going to use it.
What point?
The Easter egg.
I swear to God.
Okay.
Where am I?
I'm somewhere in the house.
I don't know where I am.
Where am I?
At the shelf.
Okay.
That means I should be facing the right way now.
That's good.
Crack my fingers.
Ah, damn it.
They take three hits each.
Did I not catch that?
How?
I've been catching it all day.
Wait a minute.
Get closer.
I need 25, right?
All right.
That's good.
Where do I go?
Ban the counters.
All right.
Start banning them.
Start banning the counters.
They need to get like a five minute timeout.
Start banning those counters.
What did I miss?
Monster.
Fuck.
Here we go.
What about down there?
Ah!
Go to catch.
Oh shit.
Here we go.
You just threw a bullet.
Oh shit.
Here we go.
You just threw a bottle at me.
I just whipped a fucking glass bottle in my face.
I do appreciate this mechanic.
But like, well, it's actually really, really fun just to do it.
Works out pretty well.
Let's see if we can do anything.
At Krasity Field.
You're alive.
Oh, he's alive.
That kind of was scary for a second.
Can I go through that?
Doesn't look like it hurts.
Where does this go?
Okay.
Off.
That isn't how this has to go over here.
Oh, this one's off.
What the fucking floor?
Get on.
Okay.
Door is locked.
It's a locked door.
Curious.
It's a locked fucking door.
Don't get this one down.
Oh, we get the key.
With both hands.
Beep!
I knew there was going to be a guy.
Hey!
He's supposed to be dead.
Show penis.
That's literally the first thing I see.
Show your penis.
No!
Why even say that?
It's never going to happen.
Why even write it?
It's just never fucking happening.
Show your penis.
I think that's probably the key.
Get collapsed on, so let me get this shotgun out.
Yeah, I'm going to get collapsed on.
I guarantee it.
Everything all right?
One good?
Good.
Okay.
Last four.
Two shells left.
Whoa.
You got to give me that back.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm ready for whatever the fuck is supposed to happen.
I'm going to pick up the key and there's going to be ten people.
Look at how many shotgun shells.
Yeah, how they're setting.
This is like a boss fight.
That's a lot of ammo.
Okay, here we go.
Flashlight and gravity glove.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, shoot.
Okay, I'm ready.
Oh, no.
No, this became another game.
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
I can see them.
Ah.
Okay, close it up, please.
Thank you.
This is fine.
It's fine.
I hate this.
Yeah?
Can you just talk?
About what?
About anything.
Literally anything.
Oh.
Oh, this hand.
Oh, yeah.
So, when you're in a situation
your irrational fear of the dark is actually quite appropriate.
You know, I can give you easily a hundred reasons to be terrified.
Okay, that was my fault.
I'll be more specific next time.
Everybody boo.
Love it after we get real funny glass break joke.
I still got it.
Big fan of this flashlight.
And it's not unlike yourself is also sensitive to the dark.
Oh, yeah?
Meaning it should go on automatically when the lights go out.
Oh, how do I turn it off when the lights are on?
Yes.
How do I turn it off?
What am I swapping out here for?
I thought I was pooping.
Oiling yourself.
Yup.
Off.
What is going on?
Dude.
I just didn't know.
Aha.
It resonated behind me.
Hot gun shells.
No.
Well, fell on the ground.
Okay, does it matter what shoulder?
Like I keep messing that up somehow.
Back up to the electricity thing.
That's the door that was locked.
Did I get a key or anything?
I got a flashlight.
Is it making him uncomfortable?
I mean, ignoring them?
Well, yeah, I'm trying to pick through, like, look at his dick comments to see if anybody has an answer.
Okay.
Going back out.
Wrong way.
Back in the dark tunnel?
Oh, no, no, no.
I was going the wrong way?
Wrong way.
You fucking idiot.
Oh, please.
Nobody mentioned your dick.
It's all anybody's saying.
It's like the only thing being said.
Am I going the right way?
I'm going the right way, right?
No, the taser's not going to work.
Yeah, I'm going the right way.
I got jumpscared.
Hey.
No, no, no.
You're fine.
Get it off your face, Alex.
Get it off my face.
I'm fine.
I got two hearts.
I'm good.
I don't even think about it, you little shit.
That's where I got to go, but wait.
Ammo.
Both?
Let me just check.
That's why you check.
Why you check.
Guys.
You want an ammo?
830?
I got enough.
All right, rest.
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
Before.
What was life like before the combine?
Ah, excellent.
Have a club sandwich.
Uh, nope.
Not once.
Right.
To make a club sandwich, you need to start with bread.
Not from a bread line.
From a bakery across the street.
I actually would rather you talk about something else completely.
You had tomatoes, lettuce.
We've been eating fucking soup out of a can in the last five years.
I don't want to hear about this.
Tell me about something else.
You toast the bread.
And you put all that in.
You're making me want to turn the stream off.
You guys have all that.
I want one of those now.
That's insane.
It is.
And I'm not on top of the first one.
You put ham in it.
Also from a pig.
And turkey from an animal we used to call.
Back up.
Back the fuck up.
And more tomato.
I can't back up.
And one of the other things I'm forgetting.
It was six inches tall and weighed up to continents.
It was the most impossible food item you could imagine.
In any age before ours.
Shit.
Wow.
I know, right?
That is.
Wow.
Okay.
Thanks, man.
You're welcome, Alex.
In.
Thank you.
Else.
We're good.
After that fucking thing.
Okay.
This is going to be weird.
I need to pull this out.
Hey, get over there, dude.
Just get over there.
Get this over there.
What happened?
What did I just do?
It's too dark.
Where's the thing?
What happened to the healing thing?
Where did it go?
Oh.
It's a.
It's a box down.
Give me it.
Watch out.
He's going to get you.
Back up.
Do it.
Get out of there.
Go.
Get out of here.
Oh my God.
What is he?
He's inside of my desk.
Sicken.
He's in a sicken.
Where's the.
Exploder.
Holy shit.
Is he dead?
Let me do that.
I ain't even scared as shit.
Wilhelm scream?
That was not a Wilhelm scream.
What was it?
I did the Wilhelm scream?
Get off of me.
It was?
Maybe.
Nerve-racking, man.
This is scary shit.
I thought this was an ammo.
Really?
Uh-huh.
One thing I don't...
Why?
I have to scratch the very part of my back that I cannot reach to put that in my backpack.
What does it even do?
I only have one of these?
Oh, shit.
I can only hold one.
Can I hold it in the other hand?
We're good.
Here it is.
Fuck.
Ah, there's another one of these rooms with a bunch of shit in it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
I'll take a shotgun, please.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
This is how I got here, you son of a bitch.
There's...
Everybody's running!
This is true terror.
Okay.
ER is too much, man.
No, no, no, it's too much.
Okay, I've like been bumping into walls and screaming.
They're shooting at me, smash!
Oh my God, boom!
If you're like a neighbor, I'm being attacked in here.
Like, I'm being physically fucking assaulted in here.
There's a fight going on in here.
Especially if you have this playing through speakers, too.
Like, let's say there's like two or three buddies in the room and like you're hearing
like glass breaking and like explosions and stuff.
Wouldn't you be like, holy shit, what the fuck is happening over there?
Oh shoot, this?
What the fuck am I doing?
I'm gonna take this...
Let's check for resin, now that we can calm down.
I don't see anything.
I'm not gonna freak out this time.
They've given it to me for a reason.
Okay, what's that?
What's this?
Relax song?
Oh my God!
Run, run, run!
It was the same energy.
Give me this thing!
Oh shit, chapter complete!
Sucks but the video is kind of cool.
True?
I haven't heard that song in a very very long time.
What do we got?
I was just looking for resin.
When you're looking for it, you got it.
Okay, bad?
Breakable blocks?
Resin in here?
I know me, aren't you?
Flashlight?
Wait, is that a dead combine soldier?
Yeah, that is a dead combine soldier.
When you guys were off to do the reactor, I saw the combine leaving some ties in here.
So, I guess they're interested in this place again.
Right, well keep an eye out. Something's definitely up.
I didn't want him to get up.
I didn't want him to get up. He's a fucking bad guy.
What the hell is that?
Oh my god, what did I do about it?
Oh my god, it's a dead combine soldier.
I didn't want him to get up.
Oh my god, it's a big...
I'm gonna fly your drone inside in the hallway.
I hear a little...
I hear a guy.
I hear a...
You guys hear it, right?
You can always tell when a combine's around because they sound kind of like a pig relaxing.
Okay, so...
Right now, what it's like to live on Earth on a scale of one to ten.
What it's like to live on Earth on a scale of one to ten.
I'd say right at two.
What would you rate it before the combine showed up?
Ooh, that's a toughie. I don't know.
What the fuck was that?
Good day, I'd say six.
Do I have any healing?
Six? That's not great.
Well, that's life, Alex. You know, it's not always great.
Well, maybe we get the combine offer.
Oh, here we go.
Get up.
Ooh, an eight. Yeah, that really would be nice.
I'm gonna go yellow to yellow.
I don't...
I just have to remember where they are.
This is green. Green to green.
Red.
Okay, red to red.
Over here. Nope.
I don't know. Purple. Green. No.
There's just green over here.
You know, purple.
Invisual lockers.
Probably going to be a thing. Yes, there is.
Something is stomping around upstairs.
I seriously don't know what it is.
Resid.
That thing.
How do I use this? Empty?
That's it. There's the guy making the noise.
Hear that shit?
Fucking chest. Box.
Fucking box.
Fucking box. Hold on.
Yeah, guess what?
There ain't gonna be shit in here.
It's gonna be empty. Ready?
Okay, if this chest is empty,
I get 100 subs.
If this chest is full of stuff,
I'm gonna shout out your name. That's right, you.
I'm gonna shout your name out in the chat room.
My fucking arm.
That really hurt.
Really, really hurt.
I look like I'm bleeding, am I?
Okay.
It's full of stuff.
Sawdust bunnies. Got a shout out for you.
Hey, Russian space fruit.
Got a shout out for you too.
Hey, Funder Dunder.
I'm talking to you.
You and me. We're friends.
Hey, the My SQ. You and me.
We're best friends.
Don't shout me out. James. W.
Hey, the train doctor.
Alright, very close.
Hey, Les Manda.
Hey,
I'm talking to you.
Hey, Ecalb99.
Suck.
Alright, that's enough.
What is this? Television?
What about me? Hey, Yellow.
Me, me, me. Okay, one more.
Lemon, the lemon guy.
Alright, we'll do five more.
Hey, Jabe. Hey, Goat Boy.
Hey, Navy Bog.
Hey,
Daisy Day.
Hey, Believe Blood.
Hey, Axolotl Inferno.
I'm talking about you.
Hey, Squeezy Chips.
I'm done doing this.
This joke was over 15 seconds ago.
I'm gonna fucking
smash the computer.
Alright, let's head down here.
Oh, shit.
Hey.
Okay, he's dead.
He has a backpack?
He's gonna, I know
when he's gonna be alive. He's gonna be this one.
Alright, this, we're gonna go this way.
Oh, sub.
Wait, Vinny got a sub. Vinny got
a vinesauce sub.
Well, follow Vinny. I'm talking to you directly. Go follow Vinny
if you have any. He's fucking one of the best streamers on Twitch.
Vinesauce, go do it.
If at least half of you don't go follow Vinny
right now, I'm gonna turn the fucking stream
off. Is this liquid in here?
I thought, I always thought it was, propane was just
gas. Is this propane
or is this gasoline?
Gasoline doesn't explode, does it? When it comes into
contact with combustible material.
Yeah, no, gas doesn't
explode. Not the only light on fire,
but gasoline, like, unless
when it comes into contact with combustible material.
Combustible.
Not like, gas.
All right, here's my review for
Half-Life Alex so far.
Gunplay, nine.
Hori, nine.
Atmosphere, nine
point one. Put things in your
backpack. Average it
out, although that doesn't have
very much weight. What are you gonna
explode through here? Why do I have somebody else?
Oh, yeah, best VR game
ever. I don't know where to go, therefore it's a
bad game. I don't know where to go
right now, therefore it's not a good game.
True. Not true.
Stupid. Pull these
guys up. Oh, then I can go that
way. Here, explode.
Oh, true LMR.
It's great.
It's very, very good.
Oh, you can't get me.
You can't get me. That one you can't get me.
I need a shield.
Resin, please.
Flushed up can.
Dude, I like this song.
Oh, yeah.
It's like, like, racquetballs.
It's already playing squash back there.
Resin.
Oh.
All right, I'm just gonna have to
just be crying. Like, ten people that
are gonna come into this room randomly, like, as they say,
oh, this guy's pulling out. I'm just gonna be crying. They're gonna be like,
oh, what's going on? I said,
I guess it's all right.
Oh, I don't want it.
Guys, stop. Leave me alone.
Fuck.
Shotgun show. Great.
And I'm done. I'm done for the month.
I'm fucking out of here, dude.
Dude, my game is
stupid.
Okay, fucking, oh my god, there's people here.
I know what you're gonna do.
I see, dude. I know what you're doing.
He's
made out of metal. You gotta shoot the guys
that have made out of metal in the chest.
Broke the acting. Okay.
Oh, no, those are my shells.
Broken acting. Broken acting.
Who thinks he's an actor?
Oh, they think he's
a shitty actor.
What did we give it for a rating? What did we give it?
What did we give it?
Any of the dumpster? Somebody was hiding
in there and they're not anymore.
That's not gonna work.
Don't move.
It's not a person. Holy shit,
he threw a chair at me. My god.
I see a guy.
Acting challenge?
Where am I? Give me a scene.
You have to say acting challenge
and then you gotta give me a scene. You gotta give me someone to work with.
Grocery store.
No, no, no, thing. We got a place now.
We need an adjective.
It's a challenge. Okay, where's the grocery store? Fine.
Let's steer.
Let's,
onions, I gotta get a whole onion.
A shopping bag here.
Okay.
I already have a basket.
What's up here?
look at that we've got oh yeah I've got my I've got my I failed the acting
challenge all right fuck you no not you not fuck you fuck me
how is this supposed to be a grocery store I got my tuna fish here gonna put it in my
basket oh no fuck you fuck me look I can't act in VR I can't it's like
patting your head scrambling an egg and rubbing your stomach at the same time
all I can do is go like this oh I can't do anything else that's all I can do
alright let's skis do a forklift joke here this is a forklift job
it's an actor go I'm skiing I'm skiing I changed my mind
damn do this this is really tricky house
sup bro either less than or two I can help you there hey hold on I need to
fucking come on I leave this room open what's the point of coming in here oh
right here okay oh I can't just go like hey
need a wheel oh look I think what the fuck they have done with this bit all
right I gotta stop like screaming it's seriously like what am I no more
fucking screaming like for real like relax dude hey I see you losers in the
bottom of the mountain I'm going full production mode on the Russell
course we'll be sitting on a landmine gold mine yep
I think a one year to get the world unconquered by the combine get them off
the planet so that's year one then another year to mess with no more job
quietly we will need to be society first you know it's funny for five minutes
structure jobs money that sort of thing otherwise people won't be able to buy
them you know
okay no chat no chat I'm not gonna cut off one finger no I'm not gonna do it
all right I just want just one finger okay that's it I'm not cutting off any
more fingers all right a bit maybe two I'll cut two somebody do that pasta
please not as well where's that where's that pasta where's the pasta and I'm
doing that you're allowed to say that I missed a lot of shit so I need to like
Alex Alex still there it took the auto-save when I was tubing that's so
funny it wouldn't it wouldn't be funny if it weren't where the fuck am I where
am I where am I this is far away isn't it
the aliens down here I don't want to blow anything up all right man we're
soft I walk through this I am careful all right I need the wheel it's one
Minecraft song what really you dicks you're gonna put it right there oh shit
okay yeah what I shoot through the glass fuck dad only take a shot that you know
you can get here Russell plan I fuck it up think you have a job for me job
Alex you invented the Alex of course you can have a job oh well it would be
stock options five to ten year vesting period obviously could be very lucrative
for you Alex sounds good yeah I'm gonna sneeze good I'm gonna sneeze and I can't
stop I can't I can't buy behind me hey don't you fuck towards me you get sucked
up by the fucking the antlion whatever that is come on over here and get sucked
up by the antlion oh this is hell okay hold on line it up line it up line it up
just line them up okay this one is to get them the fuck was that song oh shit
he has a thing wait I didn't get the resin oh no wait a minute I'm yet at
this term and not know about round in the chamber this is so dangerous I hate
this place too dangerous man it's too dangerous I don't like it here fuck go
in the right way I think so that way first let's kill this guy don't okay I
think it's on the exit but over here I don't care give me out wait that's gonna
blow the whole place that's gonna blow the whole place isn't it
this little place why did you go back with a wheel because the wheels down
there I didn't get the wheel bro I didn't get the wheel bro
this is not bad right here any full shots with this go go go go go go give
me it give me this hey hey hey hey hi what hey my safe in here close the door
Alex oh I know what to do I get a kill the thing before it sucks up like yeah I
didn't know I didn't I didn't know that I had to shoot the thing before it got
the thing up there bro what you guys fucking say oh yeah this guy oh we got
we got a fucking comedian huh I'm gonna hit something if I don't get the round
in the gun when loading the new gun I don't know anything about guns I have to
kill this guy first killing hey hey hey don't move whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa we
don't you keep that you keep one of the chamber oh that's what you guys mean
oh I get I get it that shortcut though what do you say I was actually I'm not
we'll use it because I'm right there
bro that's the shelf I knew it
glass f-life Alex it's the funniest movie of the year critics are saying it's
the best VR game of 2020 half-life Alex we didn't beat you he see I'm not
but you look like an hour to figure this out what was that 20 minutes that 20
minutes I'm ooh next chapter four hours how long has it actually been wait what
I've been in this three and a half hours I'm surprised it didn't in here for that
I mean I'm still I'm still good I'm all right I'm good to go for like probably
other hour look I'll be honest this is like a real video game I'm like playing
through the actual video game so I mean I'm not I think it's a good so far
holy shit air
trains gonna turn on and come right at me ready one two three
right waiting for it okay I can make this whole jump can I oh hell yeah let's do a
skateboard video upgrades what do I upgrade I do she knows laser sight on
pistol 28 double shot what is double shot dude adds the option to fire a
second shot immediately after the first oops cancel cancel cancel cancel cancel
cancel fuck I never has ammo ass we got here first fire has a toggle between
three shot burst I hate burst fire laser sight is 35 look reservoir has a reservoir that
holds ten additional bullets David should I just say for the laser sight
just go all the way to the bottom go all up that's like a good idea
I'm just dropping bullets oh fuck dude oh almost there I feel like some of them
have actually hit the ground I didn't even know oh fuck what's that me
I think you saw me oh shit don't look at your phone when you're the middle of a war
zone does it start with a head like three times um even machine gun if machine
guns okay this is machine gun what you wish you machine gun I can't get his
machine gun or something what why like every time I do that you guys can see
my I guarantee you that's happened at least one somebody is going to zoom in
zoom in zoom in zoom in zoom in sharpen sharpen zoom in sharpen zoom in sharpen
and he's gonna get like a picture of my ass crack like blown up in like upscale
to 4k they're just they're just blown off firecrackers it's okay all right
lock and load let's go this is what this is why we separate the boy the men from
the boys and we're gonna go and answer it's you it's me it's me I think you're
both dickheads you'll never shoot me ever you'll never get me he felt good felt
for it oh thanks a lot man you saved my ass sorry what why would you not take
cover before reloading um I got him alive aren't I oh there's more oh we're clear
that's in open that's a fucking door open already but a lot of God move out
of my fucking way oh thank you to the windows oh my god
give me now it's not the time for this bullshit
it's expended ah god I think that's the last of them good because we don't have
much time am I like 10 well I did I grow like 15 feet what wait what I feel huge
oh I don't know what happened they shot me full of something weird why can I
I'm gonna leave it for now it's kind of funny oh electrical grid electrical grid
electrical grid there's a control station override nearby
all right I'll be able to stop the train right here you sure you can do that
absolutely nice then you'll need to be ready for a fight all the way over here
we're not those like stilts that like that uncle Sam wears wherever okay I
really do use your left shoulder right that's the terminal there I'm on it do
hurry though oh what happened oh back down to here so powerful oh battery
around here someone always a resident like book is all over me this book is on
me this book is on me somewhere I get it I'm coming out I'm coming up oh shit
why's my webcam so laggy I was a webcam so fucking laggy this bullshit hey what
was that that was bullshit I just took off this low light compensation get the
fuck out of here we're at 60 FPS now what was that how's the hair yeah it's
time for a break it's time for a pee and water take a look yeah it's a water
and pee break time put the BRB on how do we look uh really squished not good not
good I'll be right back water and pee okay let me you for a sec in the mic
let me wipe this down one more time yeah I probably like another half hour or so
I'm still feeling okay I woke up pretty tight this morning but I know I'm
probably gonna be very very very tight tomorrow but it's alright after today
I'm coming back this weekend anyways well however far I get tonight I'll be
back on Saturday and Sunday we finish half-life Alex and for whatever else is
on tap ends around 15 hours long holy shit well we do it for the next couple
of streams that's you know four eight five eight twelve how's your gamer
finger it's okay healing rain is a good stopping point like right here game is
long well that's that's pretty good mix it up all right how about this after
today I plan on being back on Saturday Sunday how about this on Saturday we'll
do some like goofy shit and then Sunday we'll go back in a half-life Alex how's
that sound I don't know what month all right I'll do Chubby Bunny on Saturday
all right I'm gonna do VR but I'll before the VR starts I'll do Chubby
Bunny for five minutes okay that's Saturday that's how I'm gonna open the
stream I'm gonna get embarrassed in just chatting all right I'm ready to hop back
in for like maybe like another 34 minutes actually really fun though I'm having a
lot of fun like over here I have returned you are not having any fun that
would be that would be bad wouldn't it what does it look hazy in here I'll
clean it later all right let's just continue our through half-life Alex don't
leave that on the ground I need that all right can you guys scream at me when it's
been about 30 40 minutes I'll lose track in here good to go our puzzle fuck good
I wind up really got one in here I take this out maybe it's missing a face you
think I'm stupid all right let's find the wheel even close hey oh great
hide hide hide hide hide hide hide where you go where you go where you go he was
right here where you go oh down there that's a win all right got it
Nick let's go
okay
that's pretty fun okay look for the prisoner transport car should be
towards the front of the train okay I'll find a way into the wreckage
you can hear I don't know
dude what are they man I don't know
as in a resin that's your dad's personal board dad dad dad dad okay I'm gonna
reach out and pull you up reach and it'd be okay reach out and pull you up
okay give me your hand I'm not strong I'm not tall enough for this I can't do
it just ghosts oh no he said that I have to come to help as I said I thank you
thank you just stay there I'm gonna figure out how to get over to you no
Alex listen the thing was what I found is some sort of some sort of super
weapon a super weapon it's something big they got it here in the QC
I was trying to get closer to here of all the things to kill you in half-life
really okay in my defense listen to me in my defense I couldn't walk forward
when he was reaching his hand out I could there was a wall there they took
the invisible wall down while that conversation happened
oh my god watch ready dad I'm saying look I'm holding up I'm holding up right
now come on you do it wait what if I actually get there here I am it's me the
flying Dutchman
Spongebob!
Alex Spence I have come to help as I said I will
thank you thank you just stay there I'm gonna figure out how to get over to you
no Alex listen the thing was what I found was some sort of super weapon
a super weapon?
super weapon
something big
something huge
they're here in the QC in some kind of vault but they're about to move it
where are we soon?
then we gotta steal it before they do
yes and look look I managed to pocket the combined data pod
if I can decrypt it we can figure out how to use their weapon against them
so what's the plan?
you head to the vault I'll take this thing back to Russell's and get to work
wait where is the vault?
dad where's the vault?
look to the northern star
I guess look to the star got it dad
it's right in the middle of the QC and it's big
get up up around and see what you can find
I will accompany the alive and sure to save you
great thank you
oh the the
dad I'm gonna go find the vault
what are they called the vortigaunts?
no stay safe baby
I love you too
what are they called?
the vortigaunts
thank you
the vortigaunts are good guys right?
they don't like the G-man
don't do it
you know you know it's available but don't do it
I never said I would tell them to stay
no no no no absolutely not
why would you do that?
oh they're the bad guys and G-man is the good guy
nobody knows
I'll let you know if he gets here
oh when?
when he gets here
that's the G-man
I mean they never like really made it clear
it was open to interpretation of what was even going on
I just you know I'm one of those people
I think G-man is Gordon Freeman without the goatee on
and it's like him like thousand years in the future or something
and going back and like well I'm in that camp
true true true yeah I know come on
all right we're gonna go green green I see where they are
got it already
oh what?
let me pull free
bottom of the game
there was like a plants versus zombies joke I was thinking I was going forward like oh look at this
I was like oh look at this
scared the shit out of me
I was like whose hand is that?
can't break it whatever
that didn't open
alt over this
after complete
cone on head
no
yes you can have the same shoulder as your hand for ammo and resin
oh I missed it
what do you think Jerma class or swag?
why can't it be both?
you'd be classy with some swag what do you mean?
hey
take notes
you're looking at it
oops uh uh haha
I hit the thing
I'm classy but no I'm not
I'm I'm I have no idea what I'm doing right?
haha
mutants
did did did did
I haven't shoot it
D2 pallet in charge
did did
PVP fucking master
so much pressure in fact that I
while I hit you reached out for your father's hand
had his grip would have crushed all the delicate senses in the Russells
ah
okay
totally understandable and would have been worth it by the way
in this case
great
having said that I have a hard time imagining another situation where that would have been the case
I'm screaming I forgot sorry
and uh much like your father the Russells are priceless
okay so just you know moving forward
Russ
I promise
your gloves are safe with me
that's it
I definitely have enough to do the laser sight by the way
right? I definitely do
uh
I need two more
two more and I can do it
your balls are hanging out
well
see see you on like fiver
bye
can't open these?
oh shit
whoa
oh butterfingers come on
no I didn't even know that's what I was doing
how do I get in there?
fuck it those are the two that I need
how do I get down there?
resin on the ground restart
load save
wait
I mean load save
eventually I'm gonna get up there aren't I?
aren't I gonna get up there eventually?
shit
fuck
fuck dude
no
can I do it again?
can I do it twice?
load save
I'm not gonna
I'm not loading the save
anything over here?
is this where I came from or what?
I got enough
I can do it
see I got enough
I've got 35
what actually do I do?
probably open these somehow right?
how do I get over there?
this
okay let's go
authorized personnel only
is a key card of some sort that I don't have
terminal authority sure
it's alive
he's moving
the guy was clearly moving around
I tried to do it
you have a security card?
perfect
thank you
how does it go?
this
I think it's the wrong door
oh this one
oh it's nothing
okay whatever
progress
it's alive
you
can't be serious
what?
dead?
well when it comes to
combined data encryption
yay
it's robotic
it works
I can make short work of those
I feel like I'm trying to kill a cockroach
in my living room
might as well be an alien
it is an alien
god damn it man
wait for a resin
what makes you wish for a resin?
big brain resin
there's a combine over here
phone in prepared
fuck this
shit
look out the window
what's that?
what is that?
that's gotta be the vault
yeah
your dad didn't mention it was floating
so even if we make it there
we still have to get up to
this motherfucker is stealing all the neighbors internet
all the cables
look at all the cables attached to it
all we have to do is follow them
and break whatever's at the other end
and down comes the vault
simple
yeah I like this plan
here
done
wait that's a key card
nice okay
do I still need this key card?
or can I
what about this key
do I get rid of this key card?
that's a lot of cables
is that?
what do I just throw?
no I want to
where'd the ammo go?
called the injector thing but I don't need it
I don't need this at all
take it for fun
that's a real kind of VR right?
you guys remember
some of you older viewers might remember the PSVR shit
do you guys remember when I was playing the Batman game
and the thing was so fucked up and so shitty
and the calibration was so wrong
that I could not reach my hand this far in front of me
I had to put a key into a safe
and I physically couldn't do it
I feel so nice to actually be able to do this
it's fun to do that
okay I got that key card let's go
that should be for the other door
healing watch it
they're gonna break this
I mean of course they're gonna break this
fuck you
fuck you dick
let me see your face
flip over
flip over right now
you flip over
drop it drop it drop it drop it
hey hey hey hey hey drop it what's he got
drop it
drop it drop it drop it drop it drop it drop it
come on
what does he have in his mouth?
come here
oh my god alright finally
have you heard any combine chatter about dad escaping?
no nothing
no that's not
on the plus side
that means dad is still on his way back home
okay
we've heard they recaptured Eli Vance
and on the downside
getting to the vault isn't going to get any good
wait a minute I just saw
wow I can play with this
let's go
pretend it's your dick
hey
here hold this for me
fucking disgusting don't do it
you sure this isn't measuring tape?
I can't take these with me
I was gonna say what the fuck
how much time do I
ah
oh no this sucks
come easy
that was simple why did I freak out
fine monkey ass yeah
holy shit that's a lot of grenades
ah
did I get him?
you can press both buttons
oh
oh I won
where did it go?
backpack only stores ammo and resin
well that's stupid
I see it I got him
I got this motherfucker
hold him
hey no what?
hey fellas
heads up
heads up zombie
I said it first I went
look out
who else is down there?
who else am I throwing water balloons at?
oh
oh no
what makes me a good demoman?
if I were a bad demoman
I wouldn't be sitting here
discussing everything at all would I?
his aim is godlike
his vision true
oh I didn't want to waste a fucking bullet
hey excuse me
I just dropped it
I know Jim Carrey
that's all I know
what do you want me to say?
bring the box?
fucking stop
I know I grew huge again
why am I so big again?
alright so now what?
bullets
alright how do I what the fuck do I do?
I can't wait to hear it
that hasn't been in the game yet
we've been there the first like 10
is it a dud?
I want that baptized
39 of these things
great shit you have a grenade
yeah I know but I don't
great shit
don't tell him
I have one shot
and you missed
don't blame me for your mistake
hey can you open the door?
open the door
yeah this is still kind of fun to do though
they're not
oh my fucking god
are you serious?
what happened there?
my fidget spinners
are that shit fucking wrong with you?
what does this one do?
so many grenades
where's the damn power source?
oh press the button
press the button first
I win
I'll take a couple of these for later
there's so many of them why not just
who cares?
check a room before you go in like fuck it
doesn't even matter
give me this one too whatever like I'm just gonna throw it around
any enemies down that fucking hallway?
not anymore
I'm off?
laser sight
they coming? where are they?
oh fuck, hurry up
open! before they get down here
red dot sight let's go
laser sight
yes I will take one of those please
that's a lot
I hope this is worth it
let's see it
wow, my gun's looking pretty good
rat, come on
at this point it's kind of a bad gun
oh that's so good
germa, germa, germa, germa, time's up
time, not yet
no it's not time, it's been 40 minutes
time to log off, no it's not time
after this
what the fuck did I do?
what just happened?
I shot it off, what did I shot off?
this, okay cool
should I take that now?
oh, not yet
what's up with those grenades though?
a couple left right? one grenade left
I'm gonna need this
wowie, that's a big guy
who wins the round? who wins the round?
that's a double
that's a double, that's a double KO
draw?
oh man if you only had five
no more grenades
I know dude
I didn't know
alright, now I know
now I'm gonna
I'm only gonna be grenade guy
I'm gonna throw these down there
dude is fucked, I have so many
ah
Jesus
yeah
fuck, you fuck
you ain't got nothing on me, nothing at all
what's with this utility belt?
anything? I can't take anything from him
can't take anything off his belt?
he has a bunch of shit on him
I can't
where are those guys?
on here
what's going on here?
I'm gonna take this
now let's break this shit
take a grenade
how do I get in here?
oh, that is
amazing
what?
give me the thing, give me the thing, I need the grenade
I need this, there's another one of these guys
one, two, three
throw it over there
nice
I do this in
exactly one and a half seconds
in a full one count
one
I get something
I don't get anything
should I even use the healing
healing right now? I don't think I need it
I think it's been more than 30 minutes
that's fine, that's alright
I'm still alright
I bought grenades everywhere for some reason
why
oh shit, he's alive
oh, got him
fucking mouse
gamer mouse perspective
mouse cam
take that footage
whoever's editing this video
I want you to take this
this footage I'm doing here
I want you to put it, like
cut to it when I'm doing something crazy
like shooting and stuff
the editor
oh, by the way
if it's not there, you're fired
I'm kidding
what's going on in here?
I can't use it
I might as well fill up to full health then
my sweat is dripping
it's curving down into my nose
tell people on Twitch you can do it
the guys up here have no idea
what's about to happen
I'm gonna get up here
throw a grenade around the corner
it's two of them
oh shit
that's what the grenades are for
it's gonna be like a fucking mystery
magic act for a children's birthday party
I have two wrist pockets, I do?
I thought I only had one
alright, here we go
no fucking around, this is it right here
I'm in there, man, alright, shotgun
I'm bolted, fucking
wha
good
do a Fortnite dance, sure thing
sure thing
got them back
nice, I knew I was gonna end up over here
now what?
the northern star, that's where I wanted me to go
how dark is that?
did I move?
that was just the beginning of an acid base
I'm gonna go to bed
I'm doing alright
I will in a minute
I'm almost at a checkpoint, right?
alright, I'm gonna stop
when I get to a checkpoint
whatever the next checkpoint is
shit
not gonna hide shit from me, dude
no, I don't have two wrist slots
I thought you guys said I had two
you guys lied to me
I said I had two
alright, hotel arc incoming
alright, here we go
alright, there's nothing fucking in there
alright, here we, there we go
hotel, in the hotel now
now I can stop
you could have killed someone
now we can stop
that was a ton of fun, this is great
I understand why
everyone says this is the game to play
it's very very fun
it's very fun
it's not too overbearing
sometimes you stay in these games for like 3 or 4 hours
it gets delayed
this is good, this is solid
I just wanna see what's inside here
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, that was cool
and the power's out
looks like we're taking a stair
alright, save
northern star, chapter 5
the northern star
that's, this one's good, right?
save right there
yeah, we're good
there's a piano?
alright, I gotta play, wait wait wait
there's a piano
I don't even care, I just wanna play the piano
get the fuck off me
play the piano, I don't care
don't ever have children
and have a piano in the house
I just wanna make sure I warn everybody about that
cause you'll get this
they'll do it every day
it's not enough
it's not good enough
oh, that's not gonna get me anything
I won't win the grammy
open this fucking thing up
oh, that was fun
alright, see you guys later, see you this weekend
I can't get out, I can't leave
I can't leave, I'm stuck
get out
I'm out, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out
I'm out
that was a lot of fun
now that I come out
I just take a cheese sub, right
I'm gonna just take a cheese sub
and take a shower
I have two slots on each wrist
oh yeah
yeah, it's been almost five hours, I'm surprised
that was fun
alright, I'll see you guys on Saturday, we'll come back with something else
you were in there for a while?
yeah, I was, I only took like two breaks
I usually take like five
we'll see how I feel, I'm either gonna come back on Saturday with Alex
or we'll do some other VR stuff
or we might take a break from VR and then come back on Sunday
I don't know, it's all set up so I might as well do it
he's never gonna play this again
it'll be fucked up
but here come the subs, thanks everybody, actually let me see
I probably missed some shit, I did
it was a huge amount of money
given a little while ago
$250, what the fuck
$250
in bits, 25,000
bits from Foxy
Muffin, that's insane
thanks for the ridiculous amount of money
an amount of money that I can't believe any
one human would give
one human to me
that's too much, it's a lot
thank you, we had five community subs
from Germasucks, which is part of the ones you're seeing now
ten community subs from
TheMySQ and then five community subs
from Bocuck, thank you
thanks a lot guys
VR, I'm so glad to be back in VR cause it's
it's just pure fun
it takes kind of a lot out of you but
it's just fun, I missed it
I'm so glad to be back in it
raid, raid, raid, alright hold on, wait
there's a lot of people live
right now, let's see, Sark is
if Sark is live I have to
raid him, like it's just
that's just the way it is
Mr. Sark is just like
such a comedy legend, I have
to, what about Wayne
wait hold on, let me see
what do you mean Wayne, Bruce Wayne
what about Jim Carrey
he's alive
what about Joel, alright this is where
as a streamer you gotta
go with your first thing you say
cause there's like 15 people
20 people that I follow that are live right now
and like I said Mr. Sark, we're going to
Mr. Sark, that's just how it is, if Jim Carrey
was live right now I would raid him
right now, yeah go say hi to Sark
Sark is awesome
you guys know, okay let me tell you a quick little story
so back when I was, I had like
maybe like
50,000 subs on YouTube
I went to like a party, like a machinima party
and I didn't fucking know anybody
I was just like a guy that was there
I guess I'm like a YouTube partner
and I remember Mr. Sark
we were at a balcony and he
kind of looked over at me and he was like
hey Jerma
you know who I am?
how is it possible?
and he was like yeah I love your stuff
you keep going man you're doing great
when you get that kind of encouragement it's like
holy shit this is like Mr. Sark
he's saying that about me?
he's a really really good dude
I don't know anybody, I still kind of don't but you know
everybody clapped
and then he chokeslammed you
off the balcony and said
never talk to me ever again
no he is like
he is a top notch gentleman
so go say hello
thanks for all the subs everybody and thanks for the huge
amounts of money, I'll be back on Saturday
and Sunday, we'll do something fun
in the meantime
have a great rest of your night
I typically don't start around 2 pacific
but we did and I'll see you guys Saturday
see you later
go say hello to Sark and goodbye