No, no, I'm not late and I'm not canceling.
I'm not late and I'm not canceling. Look what you made me do.
Look what you made me do. I just tried to take a sip of my coffee.
I stabbed my mouth right into the front of my lip. Look what you made me do.
Hi guys. How are you? Hope you're doing well.
I had a little bit of a surprise. I was kind of, I forgot that Hitman 3 came out yesterday.
I forgot. And here it is.
I have a few things to talk about with you for a little while before we go anywhere.
There is a very certain stream that some of you have been maybe waiting for the last week.
Not the Catboy one. Don't worry. That's being worked on too.
All of you Catboy enthusiasts. Just hold on.
So the Bionicle movie, interestingly enough, I cannot stream that to Twitch.
I need the rights to it. That's something that I cannot do.
But hold on a second. Hold on a minute. Reach out and see if they'll let me do it.
So right now we're reaching out to see if that's something I can do.
We're in the process of reaching out. Probably going to get instantly denied.
But you know, we're probably going to get denied.
Look, there's like all kinds of music and shit in there.
I don't have the distribution rights to show that even though it's free on YouTube.
There's a lot of legal gray area there.
So that's currently being worked on. Something else is being worked on too.
There are four major, major things happening stream-wise over the next probably three months.
I'm just going to give you a quick little hint. I'm not going to tell you what it is.
If you haven't even heard me talk about this. What's going on here?
There's like a floating thing of dust right here. Get out of here.
I'm going to say two words. That's all I'm going to say.
You will see this within the next couple of months.
The archaeologist stream. Maybe work your brain around what that means.
The first word was not even a word. It was a beginning. A preposition? What is it?
What's a the? It's not a noun. It's not a verb. What is it? It's an article.
Oh, okay. Whatever. Yeah, the title's bad. Whatever.
What is a preposition? It's an article adjective.
Yeah, what's a preposition though? What does that do? What does that mean?
You see, you should what? You should see if you can get on the coliseum.
I don't even know what that is. The location or time. Okay, cool.
Yeah, there's also there's a lot. This is the baseball stream is happening.
Every like 20 to 30 days here, as of like the 1st of February,
this is going to be something else. 2020 got destroyed for big streams.
Two of them were pretty much already paid for and ready to go.
One of them in particular had to be cancelled. So we had to move a bunch of stuff from 2020
into 2021. So 2021 is going to be stacked. It's going to be loaded with potentially fun stuff to
do. Is this going to be the best year ever on the channel? I've refused to say that because
if I say that, then it might be the worst year on the channel. I'm not going to do that.
No, this might be some fun things to do. I can't say that if you say that all of a sudden,
it's become something. It's now if it's not, then Oh, every year is better than the last year
until it's not muck. It's year of the cat boy. Are you peddling fried chicken to people? I saw
that. What am I supposed to do about it? You want to see how far that meme has left this community?
Like we talked about two or three weeks ago, look no further than the Kentucky fried chicken
account on Twitter. KFC underscore es. It's the it's the it's the it's Espanol, right? It's the
Spain version. Yeah. The Spanish Kentucky fried chicken. They made me Colonel Sanders with the
sus face thing. That's just how you know it's out of our control anymore. And I can't I can't
control it anymore. What's that thing? I'm gonna tell my kids that this was Colonel Sanders.
I mean, that's that's funny. I think it could be. So what do you mean? What am I supposed to do?
Do you think the Kentucky fried chicken Twitter account made any money on that post?
But should I like claim that post? What does that get me?
Do you see a them? No, I don't I don't care. If I'm not going to go after the people that used me
in a porn ad, am I going to go? Am I going to try to go after Kentucky fried chicken Spain?
Are you guys out of your minds? I mean, what? What? What? What? I don't know. Is it? You guys
weren't around for that? That wasn't that long ago. That was only like a few months ago. It was like
six months ago. No, I don't think it's funny. Whatever. If people want to have fun with that
image, that what do you want me to say? It's okay. Does. Let me ask you this. Does bad luck Brian
like sue somebody for using the bad luck Brian image? What do you want me to say? He should.
You are no bad luck, Brian. Um, I didn't say I was. I just just saying that like
once it's kind of on the internet, it goes out there. What am I going to do about it?
You are no bad luck, Brian. Oh, let me just dump an entire bottle of detergent on the ground real
quick. Almost done. There it is. Gotta clean my room. Gotta clean my room. Gotta clean my room.
Little horse today for some reason strized end effect for exposure.
What was that? That was a fucking fresh. Let's hey, let's let's let's get let's open it. Let's
see what it sounds like. Yeah, that's as a fresh fuel. Let's get a good sip of this berry fuel.
No soy in that. Shut that mouth of yours. We're gonna play the hitman three today.
There's no soy in it. There's no soy in this bottle. I like this shit and I'm not sponsored
by them. I was kind of cool, you know? No, I'm kidding. I actually this helped me gain weight,
helped me put on some weight back when I was having some trouble. So no, they get a they get
a stamp of approval from me. They're peanuts. They're peanuts and heal. They're peanuts and
heal. They're peanuts and heal. They're peanuts and heal. They're peanuts and heal. Okay. Oh,
okay. Did I say gross to that? What are you able to say? That's fine. What's wrong with that?
Where are the peanuts? Contains tree nuts, coconut. So you were wrong. This coconut,
there's tree nuts in this. It's like probably made in the same plant that produces nuts or something.
Free nuts equal peanuts. Free nuts are unshelled soy. What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh, that's you're ridiculous. All right, hold on. Uh, where am I going here? I need to put this up.
Yeah, apparently, from what I've heard, guys, I heard Hitman three is like unbelievable.
Thanks to the 10 subs. Watch Meister. I've heard this is the best one yet. Very excited. Those of
you that know this channel, we are, we are Hitmen enthusiasts. Hitman two was one of my favorite
games that came out a couple of years ago. The new kind of re-handled. I'm sorry. I've read
somebody that said 1080 can't handle it and you just threw me off completely. Um, what was I doing?
Anyways, uh, well, I did, I think it'd be fine. If it's not, then whatever. I heard it's very good.
So I'm looking forward to it. We're just going to play it. I have no set. Uh, I want to do the VR,
but it's PSVR only. I was serious. I, I, all right. I had a PSVR and I gave it away. I just,
I gave it to somebody because I was like, I'm never going to fucking use this ever again,
ever. It was not a single reason in my mind where that would ever turn on ever again.
Because I had the Vive. If you buy a Vive and you have a PSVR, what's the point of having the PSVR
at that point? The VR is really bad though. Okay. I didn't break it. Stop. I'm procrastinating.
Stop procrastinating. Wait, did you just, I've read that wrong. I think the title is bad. I don't
care. It's just hit, man. That's all it is. That's what you came here for. My headphones,
stop stalling. I haven't seen you guys in like four or five, six days or something. I can't just
hang on and say, what's up. I can't like, I can't turn on the fucking webcam. I can't turn the
webcam on and I can't, what? I'm not allowed to turn on the webcam and I can't turn the webcam on.
Was I naked for a frame? I hope not. I can't turn the webcam on and show you this scrumptious cake.
What do you think about that? That's a 2021 Rice Krispie Treat planetary cake. This was supposed
to be shown on, hold on. How's the hair look? This was supposed to be shown on New Year's,
but I didn't have it. 2021. Let's go. You're a comical British villain. You guys want to
see something funny? That bed was like $200. That bed was like 30. Who made the cake? My mother did.
My mother made the cake. I'm not going to bite it. I want to preserve it. $200 dog fed. Yeah,
my, my, by the way, my mother's the one that made the shoe as well. Remember we talked about that?
Bite the cake like it's an apple. I'm not going to bite. No, I want to preserve it.
I want to put it in the freezer and like keep it frozen. This dude's a millionaire.
No, I wanted my dog to be incredibly comfortable. I wanted my dog to be incredibly comfortable.
Is there something wrong with that? And I'm going to spend money on my special boy.
He's worth spending the money on even though he doesn't even like the bed. In fact, he like
refuses to sleep in it now because the $30 circle bed is this is so much better. Apparently your mom
puts up with a lot of your shenanigans. I love my mother. Come on. She participates. Sleep on it.
You sleep on that one. You just keep him around for YouTube revenue. Let's get this fucking bath
robot because it's hot and I can just be naked like I was the way I should be. Make sure I don't
accidentally turn the camera on because no, that would be very bad. Okay. This game is so good. I
know. I'm so looking forward to it. IO interactive just gets so much credit from me so much. I want
you to think of a company that is made that has like a franchise like this. They, they bought out
their assets. They bought them out. They pulled away from Square Enix. They, they were like,
you know, fuck it. We're buying you out. We're buying out our shit from you. They went over.
They made Hitman, Hitman 2, this one Hitman 3. They know what they can do. They know what they're good
at and they just do it. And all of these have been very, very, very good. Nobody talks about this.
Nobody talks about how Square, I almost said Square Enix. That was wrong. Nobody, does anybody
talk about how good of like how great IO interactive is with their releases? It's been like every,
they just, they know what they're doing. How do we talk? But people are always like,
I love Bethesda. No, no, no. Love IO interactive. That's better. You said, you already said that.
So what? This might be like one of my favorite game companies. Okay. Are you guys ready? I'm excited.
God damn it. I should, whatever. God. Great. Is my, turn the cam on. No. Wait, I gotta make a pasta.
You, I, it's 4 PM Pacific. You had time? Stop stalling. Stop stalling. This is like my favorite
game of the year. This is going to be my favorite release of the year. I play like four new games
a year. This is definitely going to be, just watch, clip this. I'm going to be sitting there
at the game awards this time next year. Hitman 3 is going to be on that list. And I'm going to be
like, Oh, I'm going to be pursing my lips, leaning back, leaning back in the bathrobe, pointing.
There it is. That's the one. And it's going to lose. It's not going to win. And I'm going to be
like, you know, I really wish I hitman 3 would have won. I'm going to be like, that's my boy.
Right. Look at this shit. You can just, I can play them all. I can play every single one of these.
Is agent 47 the super Mario of PC gaming now that we haven't seen Gordon Freeman in a long time?
Okay. Should we get like a previously on the next game of Thrones? Let's do it. All right.
We're going to do previously on the next game of Thrones. Agent 47 are the world's top assassins
working for the ICA. Unknowingly, they have been hired by a shadow client to target a number of
operatives of Providence, a secret organization working so excited. I love this game. I'm already
going to love it. I can't wait to throw a plate. The first person I see approaches Diana and makes
her eliminate the shadow client. 47 asked my past, but when my past was that the shadow client is
Lucas gray lost childhood friend. He and Diana switch sides to fulfill an old pact, destroy
louder. We need more fuel. Hold on.
The three Providence partners eliminate them and the war would be over. I took my headphones out. I
have to like, however, the constant has an ace up his sleeve. I don't even need to pay attention to
the story. I know how to play hitman. Throws plates, shoes, strangle people in the bathroom
and you have a barcode on your head. That's all I know. That's all I really need to know.
Holy shit. Do you actually go in a plane in this one on top of the world?
47. This is Diana here. Come on, do it, do it, do it, do it so I can fucking just move on.
Look close. No, that's not you in the shadows behind the everyday world,
beyond the headlines and the seats of power.
Why? All right.
You get to drive a car. Did they finally let you do that in hitman?
We were just please. Do you drive a car and hitman three and throw away,
do the unthinkable, the unforgivable. And it never gave us a second thought.
Okay. If it's a full letter grade, if I can drive a car, what if it's an A after decades in the
shadows? We are fighting because the S me and 47 much has been lost, but we are closer than ever.
We trapped the constant Providence is chief control and finally learned the names.
Don't see very much water in their downfall, asked to rest and just maybe.
Look, they must've had plenty of heel on them. I'm not. Okay. I'm done doing this.
I'm not sponsored by this company. Hitman hitman pause button, not an Xbox control.
This is the Xbox version. You know, I never planned this far ahead.
You never do. I just got his memory back. Wait, is that a beacon?
Is it? Whoa, pull it, pull it, pull it, pull the wire.
I would laugh so hard if it's, if I took control now and the first mission was to kill the guy in
the helicopter, the pilot fly over there. And I think I know why the constant has escaped.
He persuaded one of the sailors into setting him free. And since then he's been seizing
control of Providence assets and resources. I can only assume Carlisle is rushing to contain
the damage. If she slips away again, we'll keep track of her. Make sure she doesn't make sure
she doesn't get away and stays the same. Your destination is the sector. The world's tallest
building where the partners are laying low. Throw people off the building, right? Come on.
Carl Ghazali. Marcus Stuyvesant is fifth generation old money. His family made its fortune
in real estate and banking and were at one point the chief landowners in New York. Carl Ingram is
a powerful Washington kingmaker. I thought that was the one ring for a second. I'm like, holy
shit. During the American civil war and later established a globe spanning empire in oil,
coal and steel. Both families long since retreated from public view, but their quiet dominance
endures to this day. Now, the partners likely suspect that we're coming. So Mr. Gray will
infiltrate building controls and disable all electronic doors and elevators. Stuyvesant and
Ingram are about to find they have nowhere left to run. Lockdown is this one. How tall is this
building? This is our moment, 47. Providence ruined our lives with a flick of a pen. Today
we return the faith. Happy hunting. Mission active. Oh god, IO Interactive just fucking nails it
every time. All right, we got a target is Carl Ingram and Marcus Stuyvesant. Okay, kill conditions.
Any method, any disguise. We're not doing any weird mischief. That's gonna play.
Difficulty is on, uh, yeah, just professional. That's fine. Unlimited saves. We can just,
story missions are there. I'm not playing on master. I just like walking around and strangling
people. All right, we just gotta kill these guys. You ready? Now I know what to say. Stuy?
Professionals have standards. He's bad at the game. I haven't even pressed play yet.
I haven't even started playing. What are you talking about? All right, here's the real test.
Uh, is because my computer play this game and a big lead up leading to it. Let's see if I can
stream the game. Welcome to Dubai. 47. Oh, look at those hot air balloons. Today is the inauguration
of the scepter and the ceremony is well underway. You will find me near the building's signature
art installation. Well, apparently Carl Ingram has ensconced himself in his penthouse suite
security on highest alert. Let's do like an alley hoop with a grenade, a floor under done. What?
Good luck. 47. Wait, what? 47. Oh my God. 47. Do you copy? I'm here. I will be shitting my
pants right now. Okay. Wait, I forget how to play hitman though. How do you play hitman?
How do you play hitman? I don't even remember how to play. Can I climb this? You're a fake fan.
I needed like a, uh, I'll get it. No harness. No, why'd you? I have a parachute. What's in here?
That's a long way to go. Just do the joke already. I'm not gonna hold on. Oh, it's control. Right.
Control. You can see I snipe that guy. How do I stand up? X is climb. It's not C. Hang. All right.
And then scale. It's X is scale and climb and everything. Okay. I thought I missed. 47. Use
your camera and scan the lock, will you? I think I can override them. Use your camera? How do I
stand up? Oh, C. Okay. You guys weren't lying. Equip your camera. Press or I to open your inventory.
Camera. Aim at the camera. Are you fucking kidding me? No, they didn't. Did they, did they, did they
add this? They added a little like best buy all the way to the left camera. Are you serious? Holy
shit. That's unbelievable. Okay. Can I do a, can you take a selfie? I hope you can take a selfie.
Oops. Hide menu. How do I navigate? Cancel. Z and X. Oh shit. Look at this one. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right. Hold on. Let's do every single wedding invitation you've ever seen. And then of the top
left here, there's like a photo of them like kissing at a movie theater. If it were me, if it
were me, they'd be like a guy in a groom outfit falling out of this balloon on the right. Just
like I'm falling out of the balloon and, and the whatever the bride would be. It's like screaming,
yelling like, oh, with like this terrified face and I'm falling. I'm like, at least what happened?
Did it upload that? Stop. What are you doing? What? What happened? It just went up to your Twitter.
I get the camera out of here. There we go. Fiber wire. That's a sprint button. I'm in position. 47.
The inauguration is taking place close by. Stop taking photos of shit. I'm sure there must be
floor plans somewhere. Understood. We need absolute focus on this one. If Ingram and
Stuyvesant are alerted to our presence, we may lose them for good. Oh, there's a coin over here.
We are so close, 47. Don't worry. I had to just see what it was like. Dude, you know what? I owe
interactive. I love you. You're like the best video game company. But let me do like, no, I don't want
to do that. I want to throw the coin to be able to throw people's eyes. I want to just be able to
baseball complete pitchers, throw this into somebody's head and try to hit him in the eye.
All right. That's what I would add. OK, here we go. But there's got to be a costume over here,
right? Oh, his drinks. That's typically might be a little too high. This is normal for a guy to be
walking in like this. Oh, OK. OK, I'm sorry. Restart the mission. Did it not save? Yeah,
this is for you. No, it didn't save, right? So I just restarted. Wait, just how do I die? Somebody
kill me. Somebody kill me. Somebody kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Thank you. OK, here we go. Load.
There we are. OK, let's go. You have to just punch somebody when you first. It's like GTA.
The first 45 minutes that anybody plays Hitman, it's the first 45 minutes that you play GTA.
Don't lie to me. You run over the first person you see, you punch the first person in the face
and you just shoot a rocket into the sky. That's what it hit, man. The first thing you do,
punch the first person in the face, strangle the first person in the bathroom position.
And then you play the game close by. Once you've infiltrated it, get your bearings.
I'm sure there must be floor plans somewhere. Understood. We need. You're a psychopath.
No, and we all are. We may lose them for good. We are so close. 47. Don't worry. You're telling
me the first thing you did in GTA 5 was not immediately punch the first pedestrian you
find the first one immediately. No, would you would you stop at every red light?
All right, here we go. It's time. All right. So now we go. Here we go. What's this quicksave?
What's quicksave? Is there no quicksave? Is it F5? I don't see it on here. It's F5 is there.
There is none. F5. It's not F5. Okay, here we go. Eliminate. Thank you. This is cool. All right.
Hold on. I need to change sensitivity. Way too high. Let's go with the 45. My most importantly.
All right. Bright light. Holy shit. So we drink. You've served drinks. I'm trying to get a drink.
You have a tray of drinks. Was this weird if I come up to try to get one? What? Whoa. Sorry.
It's been. Look, it's been a couple of years. I need to. I'm going to do this. Welcome to the
next like fucking six hours, guys. That wasn't the target. The bit rate is fucked. Is it? Oh,
because of the sun. I see. All right. So let's I'm going to I'm going to I have to be a good
at Hitman. I brought this up before. Playing Hitman the right way is like driving and stopping
at every red light in GTA. It's very hard to do. Okay. Very cool. Thank you. All right.
Where we're looking for we're looking for an opportunity. Okay, back here. Let me just I'm
going to schmooze for a little bit. You'll breathe one. Looking for an opportunity. Anybody have an
opportunity for me? What are they? What can I do with these? Can I walk up here? Is it allowed?
Who's talking?
This guy? I don't know. I don't know who is just talking. The guy in the jacket.
Okay, this guy is looking for private access to the guy's penthouse upstairs.
I'm going to follow this guy around for a little bit. You have to subdue this guy.
Hold on. I have to know what the plan is. Kill him now. I'm not going to kill him now. I'm looking.
You need I need an opportunity. Wait, so Whipple just guessed at the party. So he doesn't have
like special access to anything. Upstairs. Do you by any chance know who's staying here?
You smoking here? I hear it's not just the world. Ask you politely to move along.
Is this guy a hitman too? We're both hitmen. Is this another player? 47. I would like to address
the Providence partners directly. What's this? Them to know why this is happening. And I have
an idea. But it requires you finding a map terminal. Wait, I can't just I was just about
to just hold right trigger and just shoot a like I was gonna shoot that guy in the red dragon.
Listen, I want to talk to the partners directly. Make them understand why all of this is happening.
And that terminal gives me an idea. Okay, there's a server room personal reception. If you can gain
access to it, we might server room useful Intel from it. Okay, we'll have to work together to
hack the system. But it's our best. Is this person actually in my ear? Should I follow this one?
Okay, we have bird of prey. Here we go. Let's follow this one. Let's do it. Interact with the
map. Didn't I push button? Oh, it looks like the staff area could provide you with a viable route
to the server. Push it harder. Okay, staff area. What do you got on yours? What iPad game do you
have? Why can I? How do I get up? Get up? I can't get up. I can't get up. I can't get up.
Here it comes. No, I'm fine. I infiltrate the staff area. Wait, an apple. I eat it. It might
be an opportunity that presents itself right there. Oh, you can throw an apple in somebody's
face. Oh my god. Okay, I'm just gonna, I'm gonna bring an apple. I'm gonna go this way. Staff room
I probably need a staff coat. There's a keypad lock on the doors to the staff area. That's the
staff right there. One moment. All right, try this. 4706. 47. What are you doing? 47. Yeah,
I have the code. 47. I don't know why you're doing this. I have the code. It's four. Okay.
You go to staff outfit. Nice job. Where's your code again? It's four. Uh, 47. What was the code?
That's not it. How do I? What are the, what's the code? 47 something? 4708. It's not right. 4706.
That's not it. Oh, it is. Okay, I have to press okay. There's quite a bit of security here.
One moment. You ready for some more fresh air? 47. I got this cool costume now.
Wait, we have an opportunity. His highness has everyone working triple shifts. There's so much
going on here of a full staff update meetings already. And now that crazy manager called us
into another meeting. So now we've got to memorize new lists of guest names, new passwords for the
terminals and new special dietary needs. Yep. What else? To the amount of information the human
brain can contain. What else? Pretty sure I've hit it. And to top it off. Don't forget that.
We wouldn't be getting overtime payment because we're just expected to be here. Can you believe this?
Got a wrench over here? You got, you have to have a wrench in there, right? Oh, they don't,
do they care? What if I, okay, they're not going to care, right? What if I need this for something?
Just throw a cigarette on the ground. You just littered a cigarette. How do I like to,
how do I go stop? You violated the law. Littering. That'll be 400 coin.
Fuck you, guard. You were just watching. Oh my God. That was horrible.
Don't mind me. I'm just getting a can. Oh, bathroom. Pog. Pog bathroom.
Toilet control panel. Oh shit. What is malfunctioning? Is there a camera in the
bathroom? I think that's stuck. I think that's going to be stuck there for a very long time.
Can I plunge somebody? What? Wait, do you have a card? Oh, he's got something. What's this?
He has some other stuff on him. I don't know why I was just trying to flush him down the toilet.
Wait, people won't come in here now. Put it down. Good enough. No, no, no. Just, like I say, repent?
Repent! Give me the axe. Wait, a pair of scissors too. I want those. All right,
get in the server room. Fringe browsing. Okay. Well, would that just use the coin to do that?
I think I can open that window remotely. Cool. All right, to do it with your camera and I'll have a
try. Camera, you got it. What is it? What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing?
Okay. How do I get? How close can I get? Flash right in the face. How do I save this photo?
How do I save this photo?
What kind of system is that? That all sounds pretty harmless.
Wait, do they care that I'm doing this? They must not care, right? All right, they don't care.
They're gonna watch me go out the window. I have to stop this from happening. Try to give them the...
All right, leave, leave, leave, leave. Get out of here. Throw them out. No. Why would I do that?
Because I'm not doing that. I don't need to. I want that axe though. What the fuck? Give me the axe.
Cheek Al-Ghazali is reaching out to his worldwide network of lawyers and financial contacts,
attempting to restore the lost power base of the Providence partners. How do I turn this on?
If Ingram and Stuyvesant were asked to a meeting, thinking they'll be told of new developments,
I suspect they'd jump at the chance. Is there ray tracing? I don't have a 10... I have a...
I have 1080. It can be sealed off for private conversations. If we lure the targets there,
they'll be trapped. Okay. Got it. I can't take it with me, so I might as well throw it over there.
Okay, take the scenic route. Holy shit, he's right there. All right. Shit. Whatever. What am I
supposed to do on this ledge over here? Get... What am I supposed to do? I can't get on this ledge?
Use the camera. I don't have to go down there? What am I... What's the point of this?
What? What's the point of this? What... I... What was the point of doing this? Other ledge? Use camera.
Use camera. On the other one? Use camera on the... Oh, shit. Neanderthals just came in with a raid.
What's going on, Neanderthals? It's me, German985. I hope you had a good stream, Neanderthals.
Maybe go the right way. Hold on. Apology raid? Why is there an apology raid? Apology raid? I hope
you had fun in whatever you're doing. Always... Always a welcome... Welcome presence, Neanderthals.
Sing the raid song. Uh-oh. This is like the part of the live concert where the singer, like,
is just waiting for the time to come in, and they kind of forget the fucking lyrics,
and the whole band is playing the intro, and the singer's just kind of dancing around.
It's like, come on, do it!
The singer goes over to the fucking guitarist and starts, like, hamming his head back and forth,
and the guy's just fucking doing a crazy riff, and he's just begging. He leans back and he
whispers, like, fucking, come on, man, this is killing me.
It's always... Where do I go? Where do I go? Where do I go? I don't know what to do. I'm so stupid.
Vault? I know, but I can't... I'm trying to grab this ledge over here.
Wouldn't this be the scenic route over here? I can't grab this ledge.
Viewers gone? Oh, whatever. I can't drop here. Look up. I shouldn't be able to... What the fuck?
What? Why can I not figure this out? So, I don't... Why can I not do this? Just keep going left?
I can't. Tell me about that, right? I would assume to climb that and grab that and shimmy.
Climb this and shimmy this way? Okay. He did it. Well, we got a raid came in, too. I'm sorry.
A raid came in. I had to sing the raid song. Oh, my God. That's horrible. Look at this zonked brain.
So, it's the raid's fault. I didn't say that. I just said I had to sing the raid song.
I can't save on the pole. All right. Scan it. Shit. I didn't get it. I want to save point right here.
Blend in. Okay. Server room is behind... We got a guy over there that can see through my disguise,
though. Do I have... We got two guys over here. We got toilet three. I don't have to do that.
Okay. Toilet in here. Turn on the sink and seal. No, I don't... What do I have for items? Oh,
I have a soda. What the... What's that? What's that? What's that green stuff? There's a camera
right there, isn't there? Does it matter if I get seen on the camera? Oh, shit. All right. Hold on.
What? Oh, shit. What? It was full? I thought it was an empty can. Are you serious? Okay. Well,
who's in here? Oh, all right. Hold on. I can... Where do I put him? He was thinking. Oh, janitor key.
So now I'm the janitor. All right. We're going to find that server room is not... This is not... Oh,
it's right here. Nice. Okay. Save it. Terminal is locked. Can he do it? Can he do anything about
this? Hmm.
Okay. Pull one of the racks. How about this one? Wait. This is sabotage on 1080. Let's go.
People hear this? Who hears this? Oh, thanks. Where am I supposed to hide? I can't even hide
in here. What? What? How do you not know? How does he not know? How did he not know? What?
What? Let me see how the gunplay is in this one. Where'd he go? Okay. I got to clean this
up a little. This is a little too much. Clean this up. Just dump them. Is there a party still
going on here? He's still falling? How far is that? How did he land? He landed right on the
crown of his head and stayed that way? Oh, I got the penthouse card. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh,
shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Over here. Over here. Over here. Hey. I don't think I will. I don't think I will drop the scissors.
Oh, shit. My stomach. I just let him punch me in the face as hard as he could.
Oh, shit. I flinched a little too. Oh, my God. It's time to drop the scissors. Oh, that was
fucking funny. I love this game. All right. Let's go. I'm going to try. Okay. Let's pull this out.
Oh, get me out. Get me out. How do I hide? How am I supposed to hide? Fuck. There's no cabinet
or anything. Oh, I'm putting my hands up. No shit. They're gone. Oh, wait. Is this going to kill him?
What? Oh, my God. I can't be trusted. Just pull the server out. All right. I'm playing the game for
real now. I'm not. I'm playing the game for real. Let's go. Play the game for real. Leave the room.
I'm going to play the game for real. No more fucking around. I promise. I'm going to get to
the end of this. I'm going to get to the end of this mission. I promise. Yes. 47. Pull one of them.
And I'm going to run out.
A silent alarm has been tripped. Security is on its way. Hide 47.
Nice stormtrooper aim. Did he look in the toilet? You looked in the toilet. You looked in the toilet.
Like he could be in the toilet. I mean, they probably heard a ton of stories about this guy.
He can be anybody. He can be anything. He can be any object. They probably think I can be objects.
Okay. Am I good? He's down there. All right. Hold on. I got to get the penthouse key.
I got to get one of these guys in this room. Get out before they come. Wait, what?
Oh, get back in. Get back in. Get back in. Check the toilet again. Was it too late?
There's a guy. Who's that guy in there? Fuck. Did I? Yes. Sorry about that, 47. Let's try again,
shall we? I think I've got it. We'll need a key card to gain access. Someone in maintenance should
have one we can borrow first. I have one. Don't I have one? I don't have a card. I am maintenance.
I'm compromised though. I need to reload the safe. No, not yet. He doesn't hear this. Come here.
All right. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Put him in here. Take his gun. Body
hidden. All right. I'm good. Let me take the gun. Does he have a card too or anything? All right.
We got the gun. How do you holster? Okay. H. Save it. All right. Into the maintenance room.
Get a maintenance key. Do not throw this guy off the edge. It was an insane idea to start with.
Come on. Exploding golf ball. I've never taken things to such an extreme before.
Let's see. I, but no, but I know I have it. Fuck this guy too. No, I need his key. I need his key.
Oh, I got it. All right. We're good. All right. The people down on the first floor right now
are probably just like, um, this is a really nice party, but people keep coming, keep falling from
second floor. I think that's something we should probably look into. That must have done something.
Can you see anything different in the room? Um, is it the letters? The letters lit up. R. O. A. D.
Road. It's the screens or the A. M. M. Row. Rome. More. M. O. A. R. More. O. M. A. R. Okay. We're
doing it in this order, right? Oh, I'm a guard too. Fuck it. I can keep going. I can't. Oh, A. M.
A. M. R. More. Look at the screens. Video feed. Downloading video feed. Monitoring server disabled.
Body. Monitoring server disabled. Did I do it? What about this screen? Open.
Reinforcements are incoming. More guards on their way. Look on top. Yeah. Is it the letters?
Central processing unit. Oh, do I have to spell somebody's name? M. O. A. R. More. Guards are on
their way. Spell Andy. A. N. D. Y. More guards. Get reload on that. Nice. Okay. Okay. There we are.
One of the screens. This screen is different. It's this one. It's this one. The screen is
different. It's this one. Pre-order the schedule. Oh, shit. Rearrange the meetings. Meeting time
updated. When? Oh, shit. Really? Wait. Turn all the cameras off too. Andy?
What? Open all the doors. And deposit emergency funds. What happened? A bunch of gold bars just
came out of that. What happened? Did I just make a frenzy at the first floor? All right. Wait. I gotta
go to the meeting. Save it. Save it. Save it. Save it. Okay. Go to the meeting. Shit. I gotta get in
there. Shit. Conference room. These guys see through my disguise. Oh, fuck. Okay. We're good.
You don't have to search me, right? Oh, thank God. Oh, my God. There he is. There he is. Get a
chainsaw and cut the tree down and drop the tree on his head. Save it here. Nice. Hey, I'm with him.
We're together. I'm his personal bodyguard. Martin, would you like an apple? I know you love the
golden delicious. I do too. We'll just wait for the partners to be alone. Then you can activate
the room's lockdown feature. I can? How do I? Wait, both of them are in the same room.
The partners are alone now. Activate the panel controlling the room. That doesn't matter. The
panel doesn't matter, dude. The panel doesn't matter. Use it to start the show. I don't care
about the panel. I just want to. No, no, no, no, no, no. I want to drop the chandelier on his head.
In any other way. Come on, hurry. How do I drop that? At this time in particular,
we need a solid foundation to rebuild from and someone to help us hit that traitor, Edward.
Shoot it? Oh, he'll get coming to him. You know, Marcus, my father taught me many things throughout
my life. Oh, what happened? Are you guys all right down there? Oh, this. This shaky building. New
construction. Brand new. Oh, quick. Play the piano before anybody figures it out. Carry on
with the meeting. I'll take care of the rest. Nice family guy joke. Wait. That's just at my mercy?
I can't just stand up from behind this vertical video. Really, Carl? You're making us look real
shitty here. Can't even save it. Zoom call. I kind of want to hit him with the apple and then let
him get up and go. He turned off the video. OK, right now, he threw the apple at him. Why did
you throw that apple at me? That was ridiculous. He's dead. Oh, I just skipped it. Does he fight
back? Hey, it's me, 47. You're trapped in here with me. I'll tell you what happened. He is dead.
Touch that. Oh, shit. He touched it. Get rid of the exit quick. Give me the exit.
I thought I locked it. I thought I had it locked down. Oh, Jesus. All it took was for him to kick
it and all the panels come back up. Tell me what to fucking do. Why did I do that?
Just go to the meeting already. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You're so bad at
this. I just need to press buttons and throw things. All right, let's go. Agent 47 IQ.
You have a monkey brain. Yeah, I know. You guys know this. So I can do this cleanly by just
dropping the chandelier on them. Are they going to shimmy around? Fuck. Don't get spotted. How
you doing? There's a chef. There's a chef over here. Hold on. There's a chef over there, dude.
Inhale sharply and you're gonna lose consciousness because of your proximity
to me. There won't be enough oxygen within this square meter in order. I just want a bottle of
water. Who do you want to serve? Am I playing Skyrim? Why am I just taking everything in this
guy's room? Okay, I got what I wanted. Just keep calm. It's a busy day for surely we can get.
What's this? Do that. I certainly did. What's the meaning of this? You. You are the one
responsible for all this. And the layer meat on the chandelier meat on the chandelier.
Just wait. Wait, wait, wait. Drop the chandelier. But oh, do it now. What is this?
Model of the scepter. That's a meat. Shoot it. But I don't want to activate the. Won't they hear
this? What the fuck? No,
what do you mean reset? I disguised as him. It hasn't been noticed. Shoot the chandelier. Yeah,
I did. And it didn't do anything. It just like bounced off the metal. I wanted to hit him with
a bone too. Damn it. We meant the string. Yeah, I didn't know if it was the hit box would be on
the actual chandelier part too. Oh, let me drink some of that whiskey. Drop them behind the TV.
Okay, I have to get out of here. Will they see the blood on the ground? What if I turn that?
Wait, I didn't even get to use this. All right, I'll hold it. I can't save it. How do I get out of
here? I'm okay. No, just go. Oh shit. I'm close. Almost there. Nobody over here, right? Oh, I open
the elevator. That's right. Nice. Okay, cool. Did I go too far? Oh, I did it wrong floor.
This one here. Oh, it's right here. Wait, what? Wait, why is this right here? It's right here,
right? That's the button. You have to press the elevator button. The elevator is already open.
What? The elevator is open. I have to press the elevator button. Oh my god. He didn't even know.
How did you? It was you. Give me a break. I thought I just have to walk in. Really? I walked in there.
I had to hold G on the elevator button. I thought I was going to be just to walk in and it would be
like, oh, you did it with the cut scene. Yeah, that's my name. I've never played Fortnite even
for one minute. Not one single fucking minute. Nice. All right, that was fun. A new melee. A
hidden stash in the kitchen. A man behind the curtain. That's your winning face. I'd hate to
see you lose. We underestimated the constant. Now he's a glorified desk clerk. He's not just after
the money. He wants it all. Anyone's feeling they eventually keep her supplement is going to replace
him. Well, we're not the ones who let him escape. You still don't trust her. I don't like executive
decision makers. Look, you don't have to follow her. You know, soon this will be over. This is
2021 game. Maybe it's time to think about the future. Get out of here. You have to face the
possibility that what a way to ruin a cut scene. The ICA knows what you did. She'll make it right.
Oh my god, dude. Okay, that's the same exact thing. It just completely pulls you out.
We're at like a fast food restaurant and they have one of those digital menus and the Windows
update restart. Please continue thing is in the middle. It's just that's not supposed to be there.
You just completely remove me from my fast food environment. Okay, well, whatever. This is death
and the family. It's time to put the scissors down. I can't even. I keep thinking about that.
You tend to be reminded of what truly matters. So the end of the line. You ready for this?
Are you who will you be without a score to settle? I guess the world's most wanted fugitive
will have to do Alexa Christine Carly see Alexa Carlisle is dead. According to the funeral
invitation that is so naturally it caused quite a stir when the late matriarch turned up at the
breakfast table alive and kicking. So now we have to kill her. Why is that a number is up
has emerged from exile to tie up loose ends and secure the Carlisle legacy.
She may be a monster, but you have to admire her due diligence. Carlisle descends from an ancient
line of warrior aristocrats. Her great grandfather made a killing in the second opium war and
established an empire and shipping railroads and newspaper publishing while largely unknown to the
public. The family still asserts its quiet dominance over global transport and logistics, media and
technology. Most senior of the partners, Alexa Carlisle is cold as ice, tough as nails and sharp
as a razor. But an apple will do as always father who first brought the three families together
after the end of world war two at this very house. Meaning that this gentleman is the birthplace of
Providence.
Why is it on fire? It began here and it ends here. Manch, we're doing like a big mansion mission.
One more thing. According to our intel, Carlisle keeps a case file on the constant information that
may be helpful in his recapture. So eliminate the estate without it. Alexa Carlisle. Right.
Happy hunting 47. See you on the other side.
Hmm. Cool. Alexa Carlisle. Find the case file and eliminate Alexa Carlisle. Hmm. Okay. Hmm.
I want coins. Coins. Smuggled item. I want I don't have any unlocks. Classic outfit.
Oats. Yeah. Listen, I like that. I like the way it looks. Let's go. It's a spooky mansion.
Like the spooky mansion atmosphere. This looks fun. I like when they're self-contained in one
spot. Give me that fucking motorcycle please. The revenant Alexa Carlisle and her three adult
children. You skipped a mission. What? Grandson and daughter-in-law are all gathered to conduct
Carlisle's sham funeral. How? Curiously, Carlisle summoned a famous London PI soon after arriving
this morning. But his purpose at Thornbridge is yet unclear. Now, the target knows that you're
coming and her guard detail is top- Hmm. Cause she knows I'm on the way. So Mr. Gray will secure
their nearby field HQ and intercept all calls going in and out of the estate. Any appeal for
backup is going to fall on very deaf ears. Good luck, gentlemen. No. Give me that motorcycle.
Please. Please. Oh, no. Please. Oh, this is gorgeous. This is beautiful. This is really,
really pretty. All right. The PI. Is he going to come take a piss or something?
So disguises as Carlisle this morning. Take the car disguise and like walk through the gate
and just be like, interesting. Okay. A famous private investigator summoned by Alexa.
It's all the mystery. Has arrived at Thornbridge Manor. If you take his place, it may be an
opportunity to get close to Madam Carlisle. Okay. I like that. But, oh, okay. I'm going to go. I'm
going to get him. Excuse me. Excuse me. Uh, Tom. Tom. I'm such a huge fan of your work.
Oh, fuck. I'm trying to get. Oh, don't come. Don't come over here.
Don't come over. Where's my coin? I need a coin. Oh, come on, dude.
Just like, come on. Where? I didn't get a safe slot. Whatever. I can't walk across the water.
I can't like step into the little river. I can't. Why can I not walk in that?
It's an invisible wall. I can't walk in the water. What do you mean? Jesus. No, I'm talking about
dunking. I can't like dunk in here. I can't walk in here and dunk in this.
Why? All right. Let me get in front of him. All right. Two guards over there. Let me save that
right here. Check this out. What have we got? These guys over here. Famous. Yeah. I'm going to try
to get his autograph. He's famous. Okay. Save it right here. What just happened? You can see
me right now? Fuck. Hold on. I mean, you. Both of you should go. What the fuck? I can cross the
river? What? I tried to do that earlier. What the fuck? All right. The hedge guy. Hedge bushers.
The hedge trimmer. Come over here. You can see through the bushes? Just like scoop them up?
Oh, shit. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is that guy going to see? Grab him. No. Oh, I'm fine. Maybe the hedges. Where are the trimmers?
Where are the trimmers? Where are they? He had hedge trimmers on him. Where are they?
No, I need to be you. I need to be you. I need to be you. I need to be you. I need to be that guy.
Nice work. I work here, though. Okay. That was very, very. Okay.
That was extreme change in. I guess we have a history.
But don't go in the window. It's right over here. Open. Complete fucking security hole.
What are you looking at? Who's looking at me? Shut the fuck up. Oh, my God. He saw.
Was it a butler? It was the butler. It was the butler. It was the butler. It was the butler.
It was the butler. We're good. We're good. We're fine. We're fine. We're fine. Oh, shit.
It was the mother of worker or something. I don't know. What? My computer's hard crashing.
My computer's hard. I think my computer's turning off. My computer's turning off.
What the hell happened? Everything just crashed. My computer did. What the fuck?
You ripped too big of a hole. Oh, okay. Let me restart it. I couldn't even see an indicator
on my screen. I have a thing where it shows my mic level. My mic level shows up, right?
That wasn't even visible anymore. Everything turned off. Okay. Well, let's try that again.
You are online. I don't want to be online. Sign up. Don't ever ask me again.
Death and family. Okay, let's go. Load game, right? Just load game. What the hell is load game?
Age up? Oh, okay. How far away was this? Oh, okay. Now it's right here. We're fine.
Oh, that was the lady. I thought that was another worker at the hotel or the mansion. I thought it
was a worker. Idiot. What does he have on him? What do you have on you? Anything? No. All right.
Where do I hide him? In that little closet? Somebody's going to see over here. What's in
here? Can I dump him in here? I'm going to dump you in here. Come here. Where can I put him?
Break open the... No, no, no. Where can I dump him? Does anybody come in here for any reason?
Whoa. All right. Well, window, window, window. No, not window. There's a guy right here. This
is the only guy. Won't he see? Okay. I think I'm all right. I can't walk around with a saber,
but I feel like if I was like a really esteemed private eye, I probably would. Can I just pretend
to be Indiana Jones or something? Meet Alex in the foyer. Oh, wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm here. Sure. Whatever you need, I can do it.
I am Mr. Fernsby the butler. Hello, Fernsby.
How are you? Mr. Whitmer, I understand that you've traveled to London.
Do I care? I am Mr. Fernsby the butler. Madam Carlisle has asked me to assist you in any way.
I could have just followed her up. I understand that you've traveled from London. Would you care
for some refreshments? I didn't have to listen to her. Would you prefer to go straight to Mr.
Zachary's sleeping quarters? Hmm. I would. I prefer to get started as you wish. If you'll
follow me, sir. Wait, like I was going up here anyways. I feel obliged to point out the current
affairs surrounding Madam Carlisle are of a delicate nature. Are these her kids?
You may be familiar with the recent announcement. Are these you? You'll probably learn that the
stage show is scheduled to take place tomorrow. Adam's children were not informed until this
morning at all. Wow. So please bear with them if they seem affected by the situation.
Are they in the house? Wences gets out of them. Consider her dead when I leave.
And I nudge him really fucking hard into his waist and I wink a shitload of times.
The case concerns the death of Mr. Zachary. He was found dead in his bed this morning.
Really? The door was locked from the inside and a suicide letter was found in his room.
Interesting. Madam Carlisle suspects Fowl did not accept that he took his own life.
Sure. I've prepared some information for you. I have to do some detective work. So please do come
and see me when you've finished your investigation of the crime scene. This is Mr. Zachary's room,
to my right. Okay. Holy shit, I was gonna say disappeared. A locked room murder mystery 47.
Hmm. I trust you'll get to the bottom of this. It's a murder mystery?
If it don't, I end up being the murderer at the end anyways. I'm the killer. Oh, what a twist.
Somebody in here. Why don't you use your camera to scan the dead body? Oh, this person's dead.
Tell me what happened to him. Throat markings indicate a rare short-lived spread shows time
of death at around this night. Do you know your poisons 47? Okay. We're looking for poison.
There it is right here. He must have drank out of that. Just check that for poison. Whiskey glass
and bottle found on Zachary Carlisle's bedside table. What else is down here?
Oh, there's a fresh fire. This is very recent. There's a fresh fire over here.
It's fresh wood. Computer. Yep. What was the last email he sent? Zachary was shopping for
new Wellingtons last night. Not exactly what you would expect from someone suicidal. Interesting.
Okay. Interesting. Very interesting. How much is his horn tabs? Who's this? Who's this person?
Are you supposed to be the one that's like guarding this guy all night? Who are you? What about out
here? A lot of booze. That's pretty much. Oh, that's pretty. That's really pretty.
Get me out of here before I do something stupid. What else is there? Oh, this looks like it
can be opened. Let me tell you guys something. Let me give you guys a little bit of advice.
If your Tinder profile is all this, delete them all now. Right now. Delete them all. You're going
to need a few different photos. This is a swipe. This is a swipe left. It just is. Set it up. Take
a photo. Take a selfie. The camera in the mirror is just. There's an immediate swipe left. I don't
have to tell you that. You should know that by now. Especially if it looks like this too.
You'd be a really bad wingman. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Let's get this right. Perfect. I don't even know
what the hell you look like. Bad wingman? That's a good tip. That's a good tip. That's a good tip.
Okay. What else we got? All right. Get this stupid filter up. Investigate the room. But what else is
there? The blood stains? Shoes. He was looking for those. Wait. Something hidden under here.
Anything else in this bed? Telephone. Can anything be interacted with? Wait.
We're at the computer again? Oh, there's a note here. Zachary's suicide note. It's a handwriting
sample. Suicide note found on Zachary Carlisle's bedroom. It reads, I am haunted by horrible past
choices and their all-consuming consequences. Alexa was the raft keeping me afloat. With that
I cannot go on. Goodbye. Oh, we see if it's a forged signature. Okay. I get it. Forged signature.
What else is in here? Does he have a pair of shoes in here? I don't see anything else to interact
with. A climb? Wait. There's a lemon over here. That's a kitchen knife. Is he my trolling? No.
What am I supposed to be looking for? Turn around. There's a big book over here. Bookshelf.
Go to the bookshelf. Bookshelf next to the ladder. Oh, the ladder was like blocking this.
It's a secret passage. This could explain how the door was locked from the inside.
Peep? Oh, this is... Can somebody see my eyeball? Let's just stop pretending. Okay, we got another
note. Floor plan. A photocopy of the floor plan. Floor plan of Thornbridge Manor detailing several
hidden rooms and passages. One which connects to Zachary Carlisle's bedroom. Somebody's been
researching the secret ins and outs of Thornbridge Manor. This is a two-way mirror. I believe you've
done a thorough search of the crime scene 47. Maybe it's time to see the butler. I'm curious
about the information he's prepared for you. Oh, close that. I want people to know I know what this
is. Mystery switch. Save it. All right. You got info. This is cool. A little investigation.
This is fun. All right. What do you got for me? I got some info for you. The signature was forged.
Mr. Furnsby? Hello there, sir. I'm done. I'm seen. Did you establish a time of death? Zachary died
around last night. Well, that means the staff were off duty and Carlisle and her security didn't arrive
until this morning. Hidden passages, though. Madam's family and myself as the only persons here when
he died. I don't have to bring you in? No, I do not have. Well, I was alone. Let's investigate that.
Here's the material that I prepared for you. It's a list of the possible... No, I was... I don't have that
out of my... I was in Zachary's bedroom murdering him with poison. Oh, don't... Oops, sorry.
This is very useful information, 47. Okay, very useful. Who's this? Gregory Carlisle,
the oldest child of Alexa Carlisle. Gregory is a suspect in the murder of Zachary Carlisle.
Rebecca Carlisle, the youngest child of Alexa Carlisle. Rebecca is a suspect. Emma Carlisle,
the wife of Gregory, Patrick, the son of Emma, and Mr. Fernsby. Butler at Thornbridge Manor,
Mr. Fernsby is a suspect in the murder of Zachary Carlisle. Hmm, okay. Suspects. Hmm.
Am I supposed to be killing the lady? This is cool. Wait, I hear somebody talking.
Okay, there's the son. Let's do it.
Okay, let's question him.
Kill this guy. Where were you yesterday evening?
Kill.
Shit, I was trying to close all the doors.
Okay. The library is... Sure, but what happened? What do you think about Zachary?
Or do you think about shoes? Boots, specifically? Size 10.
Just kill them all.
Interesting.
Just kill all the suspects. Kill all the suspects. That's how you get it? That's brute
forcing. Patrick, it was me. Okay, bye. Who else is here? Targets. Am I allowed to go upstairs,
right? Why are you dressed as a bad guy from, like, wait, Mr. X? It is kind of Mr. X, isn't it?
Can I just go... Wait, hold on. Should I solve the mystery or should I just go in and shoot the lady
and then leave? Where are they? Are they underneath me? Where are they? I can hear them talking
through the wall. Solve it. Solve it. All right, I'll solve the puzzle. Let me see who actually did
the killing and then we're gonna get them all in a room and I'm just gonna just throw axes at them.
I don't know. You know what I do. You know how I do it. I'm the private... I'm the private
investigator. I can't... I can't go up here? Why not? Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. No, no, no, no, no. Okay. Let me solve
the mystery. I gotta find... Where are the other people? Where are... I've questioned you. Questioned
you. You were, like, with a girl somewhere, right? All right, where are you? I'm looking for Emma.
This is a big ass house.
Where were both of you? Oh, wait, you're not... I thought you had kids.
Somebody in the garden? Is that a brick? Holy shit. Best item in the game, thank god.
I thought they were... I thought they were, like, the... I don't know. I thought they were the kids.
Like, her kids? The people that could be killers? Give somebody... Give somebody a brick massage.
What does that even mean? All right, I'm looking for more people to talk to.
Somebody else in the garden? I have to investigate. I can't just have things given to me.
Okay.
Ohhhh, the butler! So the butler and Rebecca have half of a key. That's good to know,
and that's how you get into the safe trophy room. Oo, hello there. Rebecca.
I see. What's your story?
Lye.
Lye, how would you know that?
He snuck away to hang out with a girl.
Oh, nine?
That's- we're Pacific time.
10-12, did you talk to somebody at 12am?
All those- all those offices are closed. Lye.
She did act a bit strange.
You know, I bet she was making lists for changes needing to be done once she gets her hands on Thornbridge Manor.
Quite the shock she had when mother arrived during breakfast.
That's a lie too.
Tell me about Zachary. Did he act strange last night?
You know, now you mention it. He was a lot more chatty than usual.
Hmm.
He wanted to know about my connections in the publishing business.
Where'd you get these?
Apparently, a friend of his is writing a book.
Where'd you get those?
Which strikes me as very peculiar. I didn't think he had any friends.
Is that everything, Mr. Whitmer?
Where'd you get those?
I do have a lot to see to.
Where'd you get them?
Anything else you feel like mentioning?
I may be wrong, but I saw Mr. Fernsby, the butler, leave Zachary's room early this afternoon.
And he seemed a bit startled when he saw me in the hallway.
It's probably nothing.
Oh, and one more thing.
Please be kind to Edward. He can only take so much.
Keep your distance, sir.
Okay. Thank you for the help.
Now we know we need to talk to Edward.
I'm probably just going to get fed up that I'm trying to talk to people that I need to find.
And I'm going to not find one family member, and I'm just not going to care.
I'm just going to go up and shoot her in the head.
Ooh, a garden fork. Nice.
Alright, somebody else down here.
Revealing a mission?
What?
So, Madame Carlisle wants a picture taken.
If you were to assist with this refuse, I'm sure the portrait would be one for the audience.
Bring the whole family together?
And just explode the camera?
Oh, that's...
Shit.
Okay, hold on.
But I'm supposed to be investigating a murder right now.
Hold on. There's too many things to do.
Who's in here?
Solve the murder. I want to take a picture of people.
Believing his sister was dead.
I'd say worried about how things would be handled with Gregory and Emma taking over.
I said they'd let him stay here.
But Ethel was sure Emma would throw him out.
First chance she got.
And now we'll never know.
You're taking this hard, aren't you?
Okay.
Solve the murder.
I will solve the murder.
I'm going to solve the murder.
Can I at least kill the photographer?
You guys...
Holy shit.
Alright, where's the map? I want to see where people are.
I need...
What's this? Area undiscovered.
Alright, I'm going to go back in.
I have two or three more people to talk to.
Hey.
What's going on, bro?
I'm sure it is.
I want to question some more.
I questioned you.
Did I go this way?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Awkward how do you have a meaningful conversation with a man who only cares about what's the strongest poison in my opinion your opinion?
She supported his self-limiting behavior by letting him live here anything else you want have you noticed anything else out of the ordinary?
Nothing special comes to mind
Yes, I did get a feeling exactly was depressed not just sad I
Suppose he realized that he had no one with Alexa gone
Even Alexa must feel the pangs of guilt over that one letting him believe she was dead
Then again guilt isn't her strong suit
Okay
Hmm. We'll go over this so we need there's a couple more people to question like you
Come on if I sit can you tell me where you were yesterday evening? Oh, you're wondering about my
Well
He's like scratching his ass in his coach
Why
All here's the thing guys all of them did it
They all walked in different times of the night and like stabbed him with a different knife
One of them poisoned him one of them strangled him one of them like shot a dart into his neck
One of them just shot him. They all did it. Tell me about Zachary
One of them bricked him everybody gave him a really rough brick massage
Obviously fucked up didn't she faking her own death
She's explained nothing to us. I think she's scared to own up to her own mistake
Okay, we have one more person to question we need to question
Flanders Edward Carlisle the middle child of Alexa Edwards is suspect. I were you one more to question look at the wait
Wait, hold on. What's that poison? Where is he? Well?
Mm-hmm. I'd one more thing to ask one last question
Alexa Jim the Lies
Where's Flanders areas? Where were you?
Where was I? What was that save? Oh
18 which one where is it this one just go on a rampage? No, I want to I want to do this and right I
Want to do a mission correctly for once may I help this is beautiful song. Excuse me
Can you put get back to work, please that was beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful air
That deserves at least two bricks
What just happened serves him as a service of brick
But he's not dead
Wait, they just watch that
Okay, I need to see if he gets up and plays the piano when he wakes up
I'm gonna fucking shit my pants
How long does it take to wake up is there a way to wake him up faster
Like can I go over and like I mean I hit him in the face of the brick
I don't think he's getting up for a long time. Don't do it. Just solve the murder. I'm working on it
Oh, we have to just listen to this and drop a chandelier on him. I'm not gonna brick him
I already did that and I'm not gonna ruin it. Holy shit. I got a great photo opportunity here
You were just playing that's all it took you to stand up. I'm here
Oh, yes
Detective I have to take photos
My mother's supposed dad, but he seemed more engaged than usual. Mm-hmm. You should ask Rebecca
They had a long talk. I did talk to Rebecca already your last
Interesting did you notice anything else out of the ordinary?
I mean apart from the fact we came here to bury our mother as she shows up alive and kicking
The Zachary found dead in his bed this morning or perhaps of the plant funeral is still taking place and I have to do the eulogy
Okay, okay, what's going why are these blocked out wait have that did I clear these guys
Oh
Unsure phone call I've ever heard
I can't be my legs. My eyes are not okay
You can't tell anyone, okay
But even though mother is still alive we still have to go through with the funeral I have to write the eulogy I
Don't think I turn drive right the eulogy form
I just know she'll be disappointed in me
My legs are really weird. I can do it for you. I'll do it
Stop stop stop. I'm sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry
I can't I can't see I'm sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Okay. That was a very long hang up
Did I clear him okay who has not been cleared this is the important part
Intel
Suspects. All right the I gotta talk. I have to go talk to the butler. I gotta talk to the butler
Where is he there is that fucking snake wait conclude investigation
Come on and stand up. Come on. Put your hands up. Come on and stand up
Hmm is the door to Rebecca's room is it I get in Oh secret secret
So the secret secret secret secret secrets the secrets the secrets the secrets their secrets. Hey, there are secrets
Nobody in there. All right, we're gonna get it. I'm really gonna be able to investigate now. Oh
Boy Rebecca's room Rebecca's laptop Rebecca's
Okay, here we go right to the computer
I can see from the log that Rebecca was in a conference call from 9 p.m. To midnight last night checks out
Okay, that checks out. Yeah, she's got her alibi checks out a notebook here
Rebecca Carlos notebook found in the bedroom which she is staying the notes concern various Carlisle assets as well as a board meeting from
The night before and handwriting does not match Zachary's suicide note. We've cleared Rebecca. She's been pretty much cleared completely
Although she's kind of a slob. Just we're just gonna leave that there. I think she is guilty of is major disorganizational skills
Alright, I think she's clear. I don't think there's anything else to look at wait what's behind the painting the dog? Oh
Man, we're gonna catch somebody talking about something. Are we I feel like that's how it's gonna happen
I can oh my god, is that me?
I can go in here
Silent okay, here we go open
Hey, what am I doing?
What about him oh shit you saw all right to stop I
You've been in a horrible accident, I should have shot him in the head she said that all right here we go
It's an accident. He fell out of the window. It's okay. He fell out of the window
He tripped out of the window
Double check and get back to you got it
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I need to be the investigator send the picture to him and then strangle him
What
Perhaps you should let her know how bad it is
47 wait, did I solve the mystery? I'm not gonna come in here. Are they my still trespassing if I leave that room? Okay, we're good
Reload what I didn't do it, right? I don't know who did that
Just use the people
She got up quick after getting hit can we just say I
Threw a brick into her head and she was up immediately. What's he doing? This is another mission
Well, I need to get more Intel Jesus. Okay. Um, he's gonna see me. I just wanna leave
Can't do it again. Why why can I not?
These guys don't exist anymore. What the hell what?
Why can I throw apples at them I doing I what am I doing?
I'm just gonna leave that's madam Carlisle taking care of time to get the file on Arthur Edwards
I'm just kidding. All right, so don't do this mission. There's no reason to I have cleared
So it's the it's one of these three people. It's the Emma Patrick or mr. Fernsby. What's that?
Somebody's gonna crushed in there. So with this if we did Emma's room, let's go over here
There is a room over here this way Ryan straight ahead
Whose room is down here? No, this is a new area. They're not
Where's this little room on area undiscovered? What is it? Wait, is it behind this?
What is over here? The first floor. It must be wall dad. Okay, what about down here staff room?
All right. I didn't check anything on the other side. Let's do that. He's in here. Should I follow him around?
Are these rooms upstairs? No, this is level zero. Here we go staff room. I was in
The door to mr. Fernsby's office, how do I get in here? Wait, should I camera icons on the map? Oh shit
Okay, and then there was a brick
What is in there?
Whoa, what's going on here ask about Patrick Rosie tell me what you did last night
I
Yeah, this is you went to the garden
Hmm, okay
That clears you it's definitely the butler it's always the butler or it's Emma
It's the butler no, we saw no one outside except it was both of them they work together
What did she say
I'm gonna throw you under the bus
Things will change once she's in charge of Thornbridge Manor. Hmm, really I get a photo for evidence, please purposes
Thank you
Okay, so very so is Emma it was Emma and the butler they work together
Right. Got it. Yes, of course. I'll take a fish. Okay me take put up to both. What's he got?
How's dinner so that degenerate can eat dinner
You really that I just turn the fucking stove off are you kidding me I
Turned the stove off. I turned the stove off. I turned off the stove really. Oh
God damn it. Are you kidding me?
What the fuck? That's a crime
Just hide. Oh my god. What was that? Whatever. I have a safe point here, right?
Yeah, thank god. You've ripped off the dial
Talking that happened to me at Thanksgiving what you turn the stove off
And every single person in the room all stood up out of the tables and exclamation points went on their heads
What's going on there? What are you doing? Don't do that. Hey, what are you doing in here? They're bumping the wall. Help someone. Help me help
That minute you're Thanksgiving this year actually happened a whole bag of milk
To Alexa's office. Yeah, of course. It was her
Of course, it was Emma
It was Emma
Soap nice, I'll take it a sink. I'll take it. That's not illegal, right? Okay. No turn it off turn it
I
Don't care about my connection to stay offline
Okay, now get me the hell out of here before I continue to get myself in trouble
All right. I need to catch them doing something Emma. She's seen nothing out of the ordinary
Except that Zachary prepared depressed and Mrs. Zachary's company was always awkward due to all this consuming fascination with plants plants
She considers Madame Carla at least partially responsible. Okay plants
Got plants we got in here. Hey, where's that camera?
This is a bag of sugar. It looks kind of like a camera something in here. I can take a picture of Oh
Whatever that is. No
What can I take a picture of in here
Piano the book on the piano. Oh, he's writing the thing
And when you saw me you climbed a tree I was relieved that help had finally arrived
But you went down immediately and said when a grown-up can do it. So can you Edward you?
Trouble with your back. I can relate
nice, I
clearly remember when I was five I
Climbed a tree and could not make my way down. We're scared and called out the hell of all people
Can I take a picture of in here up here up in the in the closet?
I've been five and climbing trees is supposed to be your area of expertise
Wait a minute
He's signing this oh
Shit, he is
Was it not the same handwriting? He's clear. He's already been eliminated. So we don't need to even be in here
All right. What about the sitting room?
But in here is the strings of my heart with that piano
Don't this way
What is in here you are a suspect
Does he sign his own newspaper
Is that I can't use a fire poker something to take a picture of in here
He's too young to appreciate
Something in here to take a picture of is it back here
Hmm, they're on the table. Hold on big thing lemonade. I could push her out right now
painting
painting of Walt Disney
Portrait of Montgomery Carlisle, but the Madoka late older brother located in the sitting room
What does that do for me though? I didn't do anything you're clear. All right in the trophy room
There's something to take a picture of in the trophy room
What is it birds?
Poison missing poison. Oh
And writing has been cleared. I gotta get into your room or something. I gotta like catch you
I've got a level one phone level two. Well, what go check out the career
I gotta I want to go check that out
If I'm gonna do the
Walk around and look at stuff mission and solve the mystery mission. I have to go over here
I've not been over here yet. I can the graveyard. They're about to bury her fake body. Now. This is another mission
This is her funeral, right? This is what ill oh, we're gonna kill her. We're gonna okay
We're gonna bury her alive. Is that weird for me to say? Oh, wow, that's like fucking weird, right?
No, that's a whole nother mission
question suspects in search location of interest I
Gotta get into the butler's room try just go tell the butler that I think I I think I figured it out
Let's go in your office. I go back upstairs. Let's go up in your office and we'll figure it out
No, no, no
Go to the bedroom. Go to the bedroom. There are like eight bedrooms in this house. What go to them?
Didn't I go in most of them this monopera didn't go in this mother bedroom
Or leads to Emma and Gregory's room doesn't know I was gonna be mad at them
No, uh, I need to go and I open this I'll get the chainsaw
Can't no I'm gonna go up. I mean why what balcony? What the fuck?
Somebody somebody said go on the roof a bunch of guys are saying go to the roof
I want I got one to investigate. I think five hundred of you wrote go on the roof. I'm like, yeah, maybe I will
Somebody said go through the roof and there's nobody in here. What's that? Nothing in that's oh my god
Nothing in the safe. You stole stuff out of the safe. Oh pain flask. What?
Take a dump down there. God get in the tub. Well, what's over here shoes? I knew it
I knew it shoes and footprints found in Emma and Gregory's room. And would you look at that? I solved it
You are footprints you stepped in mud and you dragged it all the way over to the other room. What's even in here?
Is more what else is here walking cane pictures or something shoes footprints this dirt over here
Like wait follow the footprints. All right, it makes sense. Wouldn't it ath luggage balcony? What's this?
No, this is interesting. Oh shit
Hold on a letter from Emma's mother found in the room in which Emma and Gregory Carlis staying the letter details that Emma's father
Was the late Montgomery Carlisle Alexa and Zachary's older brother and the two younger siblings murdered him
Apparently the two murderers were unaware that Emma's mother was expecting his child
There's a smoking gun a letter from Emma's mother
Stating that Emma is the illegitimate child of Alexa's late older brother Montgomery and listen to this
She claims to have witnessed Alexa and Zachary murder him. Hmm
Wow
What's that? I don't know what's happening. I don't either this was kind of nodding
Uh, Emma's got it out for everybody. That's what's happening. She's got to prove it. She loved me talking about plants
Where's the greenhouse?
Where's the greenhouse? I want the greenhouse
I'm going over here. I gotta get into the butler's room. Yeah, I know but let me go on the roof first
Get the key you fuck
luggage
What do you want to do with the luggage? Oh, thank god, I got the key to the greenhouse
Doing an emma and Gregory's room. I wonder
Missing thank you one guy
Finally, oh mega lol. It's not fine. I'm trying to take my time and play hitman 3. I want to go on the roof
Get over here trespassing on the roof. Sure
This is really cool view, but doesn't really do anything for me
T and THC tincture. No, you fucking assholes. I can't reach it. I can't reach that
Oh my god. I'm just gonna burn my ass. I don't even care go all easy. I want to go to the greenhouse
I just fall from here. I can't fall why shoot the ladder
I mean when I'm gonna shoot you want to shoot the ladder and alert the entire mansion shoot
I'm not gonna shoot the ladder. What are you crazy?
There you are. Okay. I want to get out. I want to go across. I'm gonna go to the greenhouse
It's gonna be a plant in there. It's gonna be a poisonous plant. Hey, what's up murderer?
Received 28 intimate pictures of sexual character from minister fuck
Okay, I need the key I don't have the key I need the key I have the key chain
I don't have the key. How do it but you'll open that this for me. You'll open this door for me
You must have the key and you get in there. I have the horn you tell I have the key chain, but I don't have the key
It's definitely hidden in a plant
Wait, what I don't even need a key you guys even care that I'm about to do this
I have so many objects that just distract them. Hey, look, there's an apricot that like flew over. Do you see that pretty ridiculous, huh?
Okay, ready. Oh, I got a boat key. All right. Where is look at this? This is poison poison
Repair distillate many of wrench get all this shit. What's that poison Emma?
for the poison
Really something is circled 47 female age 65 to
64 kilograms
Say madam Carlisle is next in line for a poisoning
Uncovered enough evidence to tell madam
Jim Carrey
Mr. Fernsby
Unless you think there are more secrets to uncover
So I can report to mr. Fernsby
Yeah, wait, who's this? I just poisoned his lemonade just for fun fine secrets reload reload reload reload reload why?
Reload. I'm gonna reload. I just solved the mystery you killed four people
So yeah, I killed four people and just because you brought that up. I'm gonna kill another
I think he did it too quick brick massage
Butler's office Butler's office Butler's office. No, no Butler's office. Check the butler's office check his room
You need to go to the butler's but how do I get his key?
Boy, I have a crowbar. Where's his office down here reload reload. Ah, reload. Ah
All right, let's say let's check it out. I think he did it too
I'm gonna take the saber in case he comes in with like a sword or something try to fight me
He did it too, of course he did he has like probably poison up right here. He's probably got like a gun
He's got something going on here. Yeah, here's a diary burnt diary
Mm-hmm, of course. I told you guys
He did it did he and 47 the handwriting doesn't match the suicide letter in his room interesting
write it himself on
Mr. Fernsby's list a list written by mr. Fernsby the butler
It details various preparations for tomorrow's pretend funeral and a photo shoot scheduled for today by the fountain in the garden
The handwriting does not match
Carlisle's suicide note. Oh my god
that
mansion master key
every door
mmm
interesting
Mmm. Oh
Oh
But not the poison used to kill Zachary. Of course, madam Carlisle doesn't know
Okay, we're supposed to kill madam Carlisle. I feel like we should be frame the butler 47
I feel like we should just be clearly didn't commit the murder
You know, I mean like what you have enough evidence to convince madam Carlisle. He did we could do that
You should tell him you are ready to present your findings. Mmm
Unless of course you want to do some more detecting 47. Mmm
Frame the butler. I like that idea. Let's do it. Something else in here to look at throw away the saber shit
You're right. Use the boat one. Don't do that. Fuck Emma. Fuck over Emma. Not the butler. I
Could put about the boat key. Um
What about it? I don't know. I have to pee really bad. I even bother solving the mystery
Yeah, I don't know
Doesn't matter. Is there a note somewhere I can take a picture of that like a handwritten note
There's two out of three clues in here. What's the other one? Oh, no, I got them all. It's just for achievements
What about the picture? Wait a minute. What's up here? No, take a pee break. I know I have to pee so bad
I gotta pee. All right. I'm gonna what do I do? I'm gonna save it and we'll do like two or three different YouTube endings
I gotta pee I'll be right back offer watch. Was that what that was? You're a consumer
Yes, so are you you don't always have to be a comedian clown. You don't always have to be a clown
This one moves
Remastered pixel art planets. Hi chat. Hi. Hi Lily. Pretty good shit and
absolutely destroyed on
Red wine go. Let's go. Oh, I mean that I could let Otto in my room. Hold on. When is Otto's pog-tastic adventure?
Wouldn't you like to know interesting?
It's not like it's not like that's gonna you think it's gonna be a cell phone video of Otto running around
What you don't know you have no idea what I say four projects called five five five projects coming up
He's cat boys
All right, let's go. Let's solve the mystery of
Man Manor, whatever this is. I am ready
You need to go to the boat
No, I'll go to the boat after this look
I'm just gonna throw a brick at her and snap his neck and then I'll go to the boat
I'll go to the boat. I got to do every single thing. It's hit man. It's not a collect every achievement, man
It's my goal is to kill this lady. Don't kill the butler. I will make my decision when I get up there
What I feel like doing I
Might decide to push him out the window. I might decide to throw a brick at him
I might decide to poison her and then punch him
I might decide to leave them both in the room and have them kill each other
Please step inside. I might just brick him right now. You just pointed the wrong way
Oh, no, you didn't your detective skills have gained you access to the lion's den 47 now go claim your reward
Okay
Oh
Wait, how far away was that safe you thought you were so cool? All right, I'm ready. Let's go
I know where it is
Come on slow. You're too slow. Hurry up. Go. I know where her office is. Just hurry up
Go to the boat 47 47 use the boat 47 go to the boat
You should use the boat before you do I just saved over enough to sleep
I didn't even mean to do that, but I did god damn it
I hope I didn't really need to do the boat or anything. I just poisoned the drink this okay
Is it illegal to put bring soap into a room? I'm gonna get so many achievements for doing all the detective work stuff
I know for a fact that half you guys had played this level you threw a rock at her
And then you've ended the game and you might do the next mission. I know you did
So I definitely did more than you did. This is madam Carlisle's office. I didn't buy this game. Yes, you did
Yes, you did your detective skills have gained you access to the lion's den 47 now go claim your reward
Here we go. Mr. Whitmer. You've reached a conclusion. I have what is that?
What if a button on your seat
Sit down we talk please
What does she have a button on her chair?
Why do you have a button on your chair? I have to press it. This is a reverse doorbell
What I don't understand what that's for. Why do you have that? It's just you're gonna dump me
She's gonna dump me. She's gonna dump me. I get it. She's gonna dump me. Let's just get dumped
Accused Emma accused mr. Fernsby or accused Zachary I have that I can I can do the evidence on mr. Fernsby
Let's do Emma because it was definitely Emma
Posture you and Zachary killed 46 years ago
You asked me to find out what happened to Zachary would you rather not know?
No, go on I found a letter from Emma's mother Jane who was the fiance of your older brother at the time of his death
She witnessed how you and Zachary pushed him off the balcony. She believed you did it to steal the Carlisle Empire
Don't let her remove the diet coke button
Revenge and secure
Oh
He pressed the diet coke button everybody kill him I just wanted a diet coke
So, why don't they just kill me why are they letting me do this
I'm gonna get a lot of achievements for this one
What do I get? I have a diet coke
Money I can take the case file. Give me the case file
Oh you blew it you blew it lady
Doing a double-cross here
What a shame I'll have to see to it some other way then oh
It opened the safe. I want to soap her in the head so bad right now, but
Oh my god, he's good. I can just take it I got the case
Just giving this to me
Secured time to take care of madam Carlisle. You're just giving this to me
You're giving this to me. I just I'm gonna go stand at the balcony. Really?
I'm gonna just go stand at the balcony
No, no go back and do that go back and do what you're just doing go back and do what you're just doing
Go back and do what you were just doing go back and do what you were just doing close that door don't open that again
Close that door do not open that door go back and go to the balcony. She's not no she's not ready to go in
She's not ready
Why she's still alive why he's still alive
Just various objects
This is gonna kill her. They're just stepping on her die
Too many comedy utensils. Yeah. All right, here we go. Hey
This car has the view
He's alive mission complete
That's so loud turn your mic your mic is peaking go into windows and turn the gain down
I
Tried I'm sorry guys like this. It's this is too simple
Someone's killing people for fun. It seems, you know, I thought under a court of law
I might not be I do it might not be it could be though. It's possible
He's still alive
Someone is out here allegedly killing people
All right, I'm gonna dump her and I'm leaving whatever I'm gonna get some good achievements for this one turn it go
But go online. You won't get the achievements. How do I go online? No achievements offline offline? No achievements. What? No, you're offline
Don't oh online. What are you talking about? What if it kind of sick so per in the head? I can't okay
I can I just soaked I just punched her in the face with soap
Give it up. Let me see your hands
Wait, if I go online, is he gonna wipe my progress? It is isn't it? I was a nice bounce. That was a nice bounce
It's leaving go online. I'm scared to do that. It will won't it
This is the first time in probably two or three full video games
I'm not supposed to be in here
Jesus how do I get it? Wait, what's this?
I don't know what's going on
Where's the boat get in a maid outfit I can't I mean get in a maid outfit
How do I drop down? No do it in real life. Oh, it's okay. What am I doing? Jeremy?
Why you don't have to do that to everybody just don't it just run it just leave the mission who cares
It's when I can't find the exit within 10 seconds. I'd have to throw a brick at somebody remember
It's not funny Lee. I'm not trying to be funny. This is what I would be doing this at the camera wouldn't on
So take me ten tries. You know, how hard does it mean to not shoot that person in fact?
I'm trying to be better about this with the camera off. I wouldn't have even beaten the first mission yet guys
Oh boat boat boat, where's it
Go to the dock on the map. Yeah. Yeah. No that ain't happening. No, I'm just gonna I'm done. I'm going to the next mission
What quick get back all right the mission was completed while offline scoring progression and challenge completion are not available when offline
This is a problem though. Alright, I heard this is a launch problem
And then there were none thank you miss Burnwood you hit the don't go online button
Yeah after it kicked me out of the game five times in an hour
Yeah, they still did want him alive, I don't know you should I don't know why you shot him
Just shot the gun under his hand walk away
Or what you're gonna take us all on me. It's bad. It's me don't
The constant to start running
You think you've won
47 is out there and 47 never misses his mark neither do you miss Burnwood? That's what makes you valuable
You think I would betray 47
Trust me. You owe him nothing
Besides what is this about I told you two hours and 40 minutes to take ten pictures and talk to six people
I'll look forward to your call. Oh, I'm so scared of this guy
Yes, I told you was him go to Berlin and stay out of sight
Let's left now. That was Vin Diesel. I kind of sounded like
Continue story apex predator, but I'm not gonna do that right now. Hold on menu. Oh online
Mm-hmm. Okay, apex predator. I'm online. What's the plan here start location bus stop? Let's try
There's a reference to you in this level Jeremy
Really? That's interesting because there was a reference to me in the first level and the second level and the third one, too
Wow, these devs must really like this stream
There's a gas station level. Oh, I like this one already. Oh, okay. I like this
I like there's a lot burner phone and camera. All right, call Olivia. I wait I go to a secure location
fortnight do out and do fountain view find Olivia
Okay, this is the rendezvous point. I can't wait to turn a corner and hear the
She's behind me with the gun out like at my head. Mmm, not so hard to track down. Are you can't wait liar Intel
Farzul hole dumpster. She's crouched in there. Oh
Examine don't be in this one. Something is off with this van
Why is an unmarked van parked behind the bus stop in the middle of the night? Yeah, why is that?
Mm-hmm. Is that picture the license plate loading something chat? Don't turn around
Okay, oh wait a minute. Oh
Somebody was here
Somebody was here earlier better reception or something. No. Oh, oh shit knife. Okay. I don't know who that is, but no
Bunker. Oh my god, dude
You know what I mean?
Retreat and verboten electric fence right behind you
Oh
We want to the Homer Simpson plan
Okay, eliminate the agents. What is going on here? How can I tell if they're an agent? Is this an agent?
It is that's an agent agent price an excellent trapper agent price prefers to hunt alone a man of nature and solitude
This is his first assignment with fellow agents where communication is his greatest foe
I wasn't very good. He's walking around. Okay, it's a compound and locate
They're looking for me
Can I drop interview like yeah, I heard he's really had
Family guy skip. No, I did it wrong. Yeah. Well, I heard he's really handsome
Yeah, okay, whatever family guy makes like a thousand jokes an episode
They've made like 50,000 jokes a day. What do you want to do? I gotta sniff out agents. This is like a line to the club
Where the hell is this?
That's an as definitely an agent right here. No way. That's not an agent. You serious. This is an agent
Yeah, without a doubt. I don't even care if they compromise the mission. This is an agent right here. I guarantee it
I guarantee this is an agent see if I'm right
This is definitely like I'm dressed up like this to pretend to be going to this party. He's an agent
Agent he's no he wasn't whatever. It's okay. Don't give me a shovel right now
Come on. Don't give don't make me like the home alone guy. Come on
I'm sorry. Well, we have to do it once
An agent that's an agent. He's that guy's an agent writer. I guarantee it right now. This guy's right here
No way. He's not an agent. This guy's an agent
Soldier game player. All right. I'm just gonna run in the agents are in suits. Wait, they're not hiding
They don't just have like sunglasses on and like a dark t-shirt
They're looking for you. But aren't I disguised as one of them? I'm not yet
They're looking for me. So I have to be aware of people looking for me. Let's get the line
Why
Why why not
Okay, do I have to be dressed like this?
No, you know, what's freaking me out. This is all just GTA online outfits
Oh
Shit, okay
Man outside the entrance claims he can get you into the club if you help him find his missing medicine
Should be in a basket on a green bike. You got it, man. You got it. All right, looks like a green bike
That's an agent. It might be I was bike over here
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse the fuck out of the way. Excuse me. Uh
Green bike did I miss it?
Hmm back here is the green bike ask it on a green bike. Hi, this is a
Mmm, I don't see it over here. Wait. Oh, it's a brick. Of course radio tower key. Holy shit. Okay
I look bad. I didn't look back here. I mean, there's a bright green bike back here. That's incredibly green
There's a basket on it, too. All right. Here it is. You got a bag of medicine pills
Oh, it's gonna kick me offline. Isn't it? Is that written verboten? All right. Let me in this club
Give bag of medicine pills. There you go
Life saver. Thank you. Hey, look if you want to get into the club, I could get you in for free
You know look like a man who needs to let off a little steam an agent. Oh
You are a little stiff
You really need to come inside, but I promise you my allergy pills. We think you're drugs with this dude
Well, well, wait, we have to be together. We have to enter as a group to your apartment and we all have to do the drugs on
Your couch and drink the green smoothie and puke
There we go, all right, I'm in I'm in the club now an agent I don't know
What do I have anything illegal oh
Shit, hold on the shovel allowed. What was part of my costume?
Hey
All right, fine, fine
fine
Fine
It's the gun drama
All right, i'll get let's do the illegal items in inventory. Hold on. All right. Let me nobody nobody look
That was so loud
What else is illegal?
The knife god damn it
retrieve
Mike can I get back in I can cut I can cut you guys ever want to stamp my hand or something?
You don't have to say that again
Okay, i'm ready for the frisk
Sir, I can't let you enter before I have a look in your pockets
Sorry about this, sir. Won't be a moment. Follow me. I can show you around if you want. Let's go do drugs
It's hard to get you, but that's it
Anywhere. Oh and thanks for your help by the way, you're welcome. If you want to warm up first there
Oh this job, there's a chill out area over here nice. Okay
Ooh chilling out
Okay
Makes all your allergies go
I'm gonna get ambushed by somebody
I'm gonna get something to get he's an agent. It has to be look at that strange way. This guy's walking down the stairs
Absolute agent that's like a dump in the pants agent walk
Yeah, there's wires going through his whole body right now. He's got cameras everywhere. He's got fucking wires going down his legs
Recording this whole thing. Yeah as an agent
All right, so where are you taking me? Um, okay
Is that that loud?
Is this allowed?
I feel like everyone else has their clothes on but this guy
One naked guy who's an agent that guy was an agent
Okay, let's go
I think it was an agent. Why does he keep killing random people?
My god, there's been so many community subs at 69 from zapx. Holy shit
69 community subs out of your mind. That's an insane amount of money
Thank you
And that's also thanks to shy sprite vectrobe
ben's grandpa
Ridge p of five community subs each six from vector
Thanks a lot guys. It's a lot of money. Okay time to track down agents
All right, i'm gonna go to the juice bar
This guy keeps talking about it
Allergy pills juice bar juice bar. All right. Well, let's try it
What's wrong with this?
Why is that guy looking at me weird?
This is not the juice bar
Blend in as a guest. Yeah, I mean what's wrong with the juice. It's an agent. Is it an agent?
Search the combat and locate agents
But it really freaks me out when people stand too close to me
I would leave now then I would actually leave this club
Everyone's shoulder the shoulder right now. What's going what?
We got i'll be knife
juice bar ticket sick
Ticket needed for the juice bar bartenders to gain access to the backstage area so they can work their station on the back
It says to enter at the back by the canals. Oh shit. Hold on scream projection tamper with it. Why would I do that?
Oh shit. Wait, it was a
Pretty juice can't open this
Of course they heard this shovel
That's an agent
He's a gun. Oh, it's a security guard
All right. Don't tamper with this. No reason to this is a legit gta of it. Yeah, it's pretty good actually
Okay, so I have the key to the juice bar. I can't leave though. Wait, hold on open this
back here
Hold on juice
Washing machines or something
Hmm, wait a minute pipe room can go down
Drop the goddamn shovel. Is that hold on they're all gonna hear this. Oh shit. These are security guards
Remove the shovel. I know i'm just but I can't throw it. It'll make noise
How do I drop it? Are they gonna hear this if I just drop it? I need one of their disguises
Z i'm not exactly sure what i'm doing here, but oh this guy's asleep
That guy's asleep is the guy having like a key or something. Will he hear this and wake up?
No, what how did you hear that?
How did you hear that
The music is so loud. You heard a stab you heard that he yelled. I think you can't hear shit
It's a very loud knife. I don't why am I going all the way down here?
I feel like I shouldn't be doing this. I have to go. I'm gonna i'm going back up if I can even play the game
Still this is why I went offline
This is the reason why I just didn't go online in the first place for all of you
Screaming at me. This is the reason why he's level six and he's in berlin ban that guy for at least a minute
Uh, I have to reload
It was what is this? What was this happening? This didn't happen with the last game
I don't remember this happening with hitman 2. Why is it happening with hitman 3 level six?
All right, but is it
Is it a bad thing? Do you mean i'm way too over leveled or i'm way too under leveled very under leveled?
Well, half of my unlocks and achievements can't go through. Of course. I'm gonna be level six epic
Oh, is that why?
Is because it's going through the epic game store
Oh
Right, right. Remember all the praise you said?
Yeah, the iro interactive makes great games, but they decided to put it on epic game store for
some
Potentially large check i'm not there. I don't know the deals but there was a large check that was involved
That's all I know
All right, drop the shovel
I'm going back up
I'm not I don't I don't want to be down here right now. I want to go to the canals
Let me get get back up here
You're gonna be pissed that i'm back here, but
All right. I'm good. Why?
I don't understand why that person's looking at me
All right, the canals I don't have do I have a map here? All right, the canals look like they're
All right, if I were canals
I would be here, right?
It's an agent
Agent mongomery the leader of the group ex-navy seal mongomery is a true professional and one of the top agents
He's highly self-assured. He's arrogant. Oh man. All right, hold on
Stop looking at me
No, no, no, no, no. No, why what is everybody looking at me?
Why is everybody looking at me?
What
I'm right. I'm leaving
I'm leaving
What crime did I do?
What crime has been committed? Who's arresting me? What did I do?
What did I do wrong?
What crime did I do? I didn't
Um
You're a hit man
Get me out of here
Get me out from behind here. I didn't do anything wrong
I need to probably steal a disguise. They're literally looking for you
I need to disguise. Okay, I have to I need I gotta take this disguise. Come here
Somebody come over here. Have you ever tried a disguise?
What are you doing back here? Why are you back here?
Come on, I didn't even save it
What the fuck are you doing back here?
Montgomery just like walking around following me around. He doesn't even know i'm over here fucking montgomery get the fuck out of here
Leave me alone. I can't walk by here. Stop it. Don't look at me. Leave me alone
Where is he? There he is distant. Okay montgomery coming up
Yeah, he went the complete opposite way
I have to identify him as an agent
The music's so loud. I can't identify him as an agent
out of the way you
Asshole
There he is. Okay. All right identify
Nice. Okay. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good
Is he telling me I can't come over here? I
Is this an agent over here?
I feel like it is
Can I get an identification from this person?
No, all right. Well, I have you on the map
I'm gonna head down here
You still need to disguise. I know and I also need this music to turn down by like
80 percent
Right now I didn't do anything. Did I not save it? All right, there's definitely an agent down here
I guarantee it
Can I dance? What the hell is this?
Looking for agents. What about you?
Oh
agent
Blend in with the crowd
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Ah got him
Agent chamberlain first lieutenant as a former operative of the sas. He shares a common background
Chamberlain executes his assignments with expert precision as a flawless tracker at work. I say okay
Are you taking requests?
Can you play earth wind and fire?
Well, so I get this too I got two on the map right now tech only allowed back here
I'll get a costume now. So I i'm gonna try I got a wrench nice good
Unlock this cabinet with the crowbar. I don't know what's even in here, but i'm gonna take whatever it is
Modern sedative a syringe. Ooh
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. I get to be the dj
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god dj dj. I want to be the dj. I want to be the dj
Oh my god, I get to be the dj. I get to be the dj
Okay over get over here b b motherfucker b
Yes
All right
Can I go on to do a set pick up? What is it a cable? Ooh staff key?
Oh, here we go. It's time
technician notes
Can I do one?
Hey, let me do one
Let me do one. You're yours upstage the rest of us
It's always about you. That's why your name is first
john and the masks, huh?
Why do we have to be the mask? I want to be the mask
My turn for a set
Can I get some hands?
Let's see them
Yeah
A lot better than the last guy, isn't it?
I'm gonna do die what I love doing. Can I see the hands hands up?
Everybody put your hands up
Everybody just stand up. All right, that's fun
Okay, so now i'm gonna get the keys
staff key
There's a lot of random shit over here to take
I mean, i'm sorry. I'm really sorry, but I really have to I gotta hype the crowd up a little
Can I hype the crowd up like really bad?
No, I don't think I can
Let me save it
Press g
This person in the front
It's silent in here
All right light show
What does this actually end up doing for me?
It's probably you probably one of these lasers probably can kill somebody with it, right?
You make it a real laser and you're like saws through somebody's head
Holy shit. There's an agent right there
Do I get any more info from this?
Make cause a mosh pit. Can I actually do that?
Do all djs work in the mixing desk?
Please talk to one of the technicians first if you want to trigger the climax light show as it's highly unstable and could be
Very dangerous why what?
I can probably mess with it up there
I bump light show and then trigger climax, right?
Yeah
Yeah, there's definitely something up there. I can go mess with
Yeah, I can mess with it. I got a wrench now. All right, I know what i'm gonna do. That sounds like a fun way to do it
Um put this back
All right. I'm gonna go mess with
Whatever I can mess with
medicine cabinet key
Just play the dj for the rest of the stream
I turn the fan off
All right, where
I might can I get up there?
Unlock the door
Let me in what?
I'm the dj
So should I go up from here?
Maybe
Let's do it at the right time
Well, there's no agent walking around
Am I gonna I want like
Kill people on the dance floor. Will I?
Jesus this is I I don't like this. No, no, no, no, no stuff. That's up. I climb this
How do I get up there? Wait, what's going on?
Oh, okay. Oh fuck. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, who's seeing me? It's fucking montgomery. You piece of shit
I swear to god
You didn't see me. Did he leave the way which oh my god. I didn't want to do that
I didn't want to do that. I tried to press a different button. Oh, fuck me. All right. I'm trying to drop down
Okay, climb this fucking ladder
There's the dj said go this way. I have the wrench, right?
Go across
Up again. Should I even go up again?
Okay, go over here
Can I climb and then go around?
uh
I drop right here
Kind of confused what I need to do here
I guess go up but
this is
Um, okay
I made it up here
Wait, they don't care. Why did they care before because I was hanging
All right, this is what this guy's sleeping. Oh my god banner fucking banner
Oh fucking banner
Who is seeing me through a wall?
Okay
Oh jesus
Oh, no, I they gotta die right now. Don't turn this way. Of course
I gotta I have to kill them. I gotta kill this guy right now
Will he see me?
Who?
Just shoot
Wrong save file. Oh god
They're coming for you
I'm thinking about just honestly shooting this guy in the head right now. This guy always seems to be in the worst possible place
I'm just gonna shoot him. Who cares? Just shoot the guy in the face
Does it really matter? I'm just gonna dump his ass. Is he coming this way? I might need that. All right, save it here
There's an agent, right?
No, what the fuck these people here?
Push joke again. Sure. Okay. Here we go. I have to distract these people somehow and he's an agent so
Technician knows okay
Check the volt regulator before the dj goes on tonight
If it's broken or overloaded the light showed rigged on the tree trunk might blow up when the d. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, that's what this this is. Okay. How do I get you guys to leave run off high voltage power outlet?
I could turn this off. I gotta get rid of the I don't make coins like a soda can
uh
One of them walks away for a second. Let me see what happens if I turn this off turn these
Turn the fuse box off. Okay. There we go. Investigate that. I'm checking out. I couldn't walk over there
All right. Can I get them? Okay. What if I do this short circuit the tree turn it on? Okay
So now this is like super powered now do the dj climax
Explore expose the wire put the fuse back put the fuse back together
Fuse box the other switch
They're all off. All right, turn it on. Wait one. No the fuse box. What?
Why do I have to kill both of these people?
Oh fuck
Oh shit, you know what fuck you who cares?
That was the target
All that setup was so pointless
They got like 10 wires on the ground. I can't
Give me that earpiece
All the setup to just wait. I need the dj outfit
Okay, so let me get this straight
Short circuit the light installation unplug the wire fuse box turn off the voltage
What what's what's button do I have to press here?
How stoned are you?
The outlet was literally wait am I supposed to what is he supposed to step on this?
Only short-circuited
Just shoot him
Just overload it and shoot him
Okay, here's the plan come over here. I want this outfit. This is not oceans 11
It's oceans 11
Okay. Now i'm allowed to short circuit this so the wire so expose the wire
Right and then short-circuited
What am I actually supposed to be doing i'm not even kidding what am I what am I supposed to be doing here
Who what is killing them?
What what is supposed to kill this person?
I have no idea
Is it the wire?
lady
You're rigging the tree
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
I thought I was trying to like kill the guy up here with like the electrocution or something
No
Oh, I thought he was supposed to walk over like the exposed wire
Oh, okay. Well
So I just have to short circuit this
oceans 11 iq
Okay, okay. So
Let me let me go over this. Let me go over this
Turn the fuse box off get the technician's outfit
Break short circuit this and turn off the voltage. I I what am I supposed to do?
Don't touch the switch
You don't even need the costume. But if I do this, isn't it gonna look they're gonna be pissed about this
Watch
I can't what are you guys talking about? I can't just do that
Just sort wait. Why can why why can I just do that?
Why did they just let me do that? Why did they just let me do that?
Just jump off the bridge. I'm done after this by the way
I'm done
I'm done with hitman 3 for now
I'm too like tired or distracted. I don't know which one
All right. Let me go back here
He's too high
No, i'm not i'm just getting spotted by security camera over and over again
All right. How do I get back down?
Aren't I the dj? Let me in where I can go over the fuck. I want i'm the dj
He's too tired
I don't even remember how to get down
God damn it
How do I get down from here?
I'm too high. How do I get down?
Oh my god
I'll see you later. I'm out of here
Save the game. I will hold on. Let me just do this part
I don't like this mission
Dude, it's too many too much verticality. What the fuck mad because i'm not i'm not even mad right now
I'm just confused
Okay, was it through here? Why am I not allowed to go over here? Where am I going?
This way over here
Okay down this way, right?
Same way you got there. Well, you're implying that I remembered anything about this. It's just all just warehouse space
Most zonk stream of 2021. I hate like the cement fucking levels. It's just like everything's the same cement
Just get me the fuck out of here
I need to go like down here, but they won't let me over here
Why the fuck not
All right, fucking kicked in this shit kicked in what I didn't want it to
God damn it
All right. I made it. I made it. I made it. I made it. I made it
Where's my set?
Yeah, we got out the dj. We have no idea where he is. He's walking around upstairs lost
I think he like took some fucking cbd
All right, get out of the way. It's my turn
All right. Here we go. Ready?
Here comes the drop
shock him
I get him
I got him there. How many more left? No
My god, damn it. All right, i'll i'm i'm leaving
I'm i'm my brain is like too fried right now to even attempt to play this game anymore
I'm just gonna save it somewhere
What am I doing? What's going on?
All right. Can I please just like stand in a corner where nobody can see me?
Just like let me be
Everybody can see through your disguise in this level. I hate it. I just want to walk around
All right, we're going over here
He has to quit. He's too high. No, i'm fine. I'm not i'm not even high
Not most high stream. I'm not even high
Do you stand out? I don't stand out
Slamming his desk. No, i'll probably call it here though
How do you like eat something
but anyways
This has been hitman 3
I think it's been pretty fun
Except for this level. I don't like this level at all
I don't like it
But i'm gonna continue playing it
I will
There's some stuff to do over the next four days or so
So i'm going to come back to you guys on sunday night and we're gonna don't fucking look at I hate this level
Okay
I'll see you guys on sunday
We've got a lot to talk about
There are a lot of projects that you'll see a couple that will be very soon
It's not gonna come back till monday. No, i'm streaming sunday night. Not on wednesday
There are five
Major streams that you will see before
Like quarter one quarter two is up. They're gonna be very very big. I hope they're fun
Two of them you'll see in the next probably 30 days. I'm looking forward to it
Actual serial, please don't get high. Okay. Let me be real
I'm not high at all. I I think I just got like a wave of tiredness. That's just exploded
I've I have not I I swear to god
Not had a single ounce a single taste of marijuana today. I swear to god
I promise something something waved over me in the last like 30 minutes. I have no idea what it was today
No, stop it
three whole marijuanas
Uh, no, I it was fun pitman's always fun something about this level though. I don't know what happened in the last 30 minutes
I just can't even pay attention
I just hate fucking cement if you have cement levels in your game delete them
Everybody hates them including me. I hate it. I hate when everything's a cement level
Just get rid of it last one was so good one before that was I hate the cement
Here's a dance club get rid of the cement delete the cement from the fucking game. I hate the cement
I hate parking garages get rid of them. I lose my car in a parking garage
I can't park in a parking garage because every every slot is the same. Anyways, it's brutal. No, i'm just kidding
I'll see you guys on sunday. Thanks for watching
Where I don't we might not go back to this on sunday, maybe we will there might be something else
I want to do. There's a few things on the list
When is the cap boy stream?
Within the next six months. There you go game of the year, by the way
I will give my assessment on hitman 3 when I finish it
Uh, that's what you will get. I'm only two mid three missions in you're never gonna finish it
I finished the first two. What are you talking about? I did all the dlc for the first two as well
Oh auto hold on
Oh shit my hand
Auto wanted to run away
Uh, thanks as always for watching though
Sorry, I couldn't figure out how to get out of a parking garage for the last 30 minutes. Well, I tried
So bionicle, we're actually trying to get it. We're actually reaching out to bionicle if you missed the beginning of the stream
twitch
Will not allow me to stream the bionicle movie unless I have expressed permission to do so so
Is not allowed well, we're gonna try to make that happen
Actual reaching out to see if we can do that. So we'll find out which one the mask of light
I all right. I'm gonna say the second part of that you got a raid
There actually was a there was a big raid from neanderthal be stuck around from that. Thank you. Hi
I'm really, you know, i'm really looking forward to the archaeologist stream
Like a lot of you guys are gonna dig that a lot. It's gonna be really fun
That wasn't no I meant that for real
All right, I gotta I gotta go eat like peanut butter or like hamburger meat or something
I don't know. My brain is like shutting itself down
He's got a I have like a I have a good bad hamburger brain right now
Uh raid, uh, who should we raid? Where are we going?
Who's live right now? Let's see
um
We could go
Uh, vinnie's playing metroid. So yeah, let's go. Let's go say hello to vinnie. It's been a while
Super metroid cool stuff
I've never played super metroid before
Also, hi to vinnie. He's a great guy
Great company and i'll see you guys on sunday night. We're not i'm not streaming till sunday night
I'll play i'll play something fun. We'll do something interesting
If it's not hitman, we'll do something else
sunday pst somewhere around
We're going to be late one. It's going to be a late stream late night stream on sunday
And then I will be back to my regularly scheduled sort of streams
You've seen like one stream a week the last two weeks. I've been pretty busy a lot going on
Hopefully, uh, you will see the fruits of that labor in the next month or two. I know you will
So probably not until like seven or eight o'clock pm on sunday. We're doing late night pacific stream late night andy
But as always thanks for watching. Sorry for being like a an absolute moron in the last 20 minutes
I have like no explanation for that because like I wish I could tell you I was high but I just
I kind of leaned into that. Oh man, like I really kicked in 20 minutes ago. No, no, no
I have no idea why I was just so tired. It just hit me like a brick. Sorry. I'm sorry
I'll see you Sunday night though guys. Take care of yourselves. We'll see you soon. Good night. Oh fuck you're gonna leave me now