Quick! Get the health! Get it! Yay! Turn her behind you! Behind you! Behind you!
He just got turned on! Don't ever come in the museum and start firing a gun, Scout.
Don't you know the rules? Please help me defend the museum! Someone is trying to steal the painting!
Somebody... Thank you. Thank God I have this security guard on duty.
I have the security guard on duty protecting the museum spy statue.
Any more burglars gonna come try and steal me?
This really is great how this demo knight is just protecting me.
Is he gonna... No! No! Help me! No!
This guy. I wonder what he's doing down here.
Okay, bye.
Alright. Why did he get right in my face? He got right in my face.
And then just decided I wasn't an enemy.
What is he doing? Oh, it's a spy! Hey! Hey!
He went too late! He stole it!
How long can the spy statue survive if it's up in a very dangerous place?
That's my question.
Like, if it's up here, can it survive?
Can the spy statue survive if it's in a place like this?
That's the age-old question.
I'm kind of in the sniper's way.
The sniper...
The sniper doesn't know. He just figured it out.
He just was like, what the hell?
The way he looked over, he glanced over and was like, oh shit, what the hell is this?
Don't you ever touch the spy statue again!
So get yourselves ready, security guards.
This is an expensive statue from the Egyptian times.
Think about it like that.
This is the most expensive statue you've ever seen in your life.
You are tasked with protecting it.
Yeah, it's like a pharaoh.
This is like, we got this statue at a king-touch tomb, alright?
Are you ready, you attackers?
Come get the statue. Good luck.
This is so dumb.
Well, I've lasted more than eight seconds.
So that's a good thing.
Uh-oh. Have they breached the defenses?
Oh, he's breaching! He's breaching!
Oh, look out on the right here! On the right, on the right, on the right!
Jesus!
No!
Oh, I think we're going to lose this one.
Oh, shit.
It's just me and the two engineers.
I don't know.
I haven't figured that out yet.
Alright, guys.
And on the count of three, the attackers are allowed to come in.
You have 30 seconds in.
Three, two, one.
Try to get the statue. 30 seconds.
Looking good so far, boys.
We're 10 seconds in.
We got a bonk scout.
We got a bonk scout!
This bonk scout might do it!
Nope, nope, good. 10 seconds.
Oh, damn it!
They got it in 22 seconds.
This is the museum.
It's a very nice museum. It's like a rundown piece of shit.
You like this museum? It's like a bunch of boards.
That was a bad... I didn't want to do that.
Yeah, everybody on blue, get in the secret criminal hideout.
Get in there!
Meatball monster, get in there!
Well, he's gone.
So, look, here's the criminal.
This is so stupid looking.
You guys look like such a dipshits.
I love it.
Go for it.
Everybody protect the statue.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Yeah, watch this other door.
The criminals are everywhere.
Oh, wow.
That's not good. That's not good.
That's so...
Oh, I died. I died like right at the end there.
Make sure you do not high five me though.
That's important.
Okay, there is...
Somebody has to stop that
before I say go.
Alright, ready security guards?
Attackers, attack!
Come get the statue.