I-I'm on time. We're waiting pa- I'm on time. I'm here.
I pressed the button at 2 o'clock.
It took an extra 45 seconds to get through the internet tubes, okay?
You understand the remarkable tech no- my throat is all screwed up.
Come with me, I'll just wait here.
Well, my nose is.
Gotta figure out what's going on inside the, uh, inside the nasal passages here.
Some of you know, I've had some nasal problems over the last 6 months or so.
Last few months at least.
It's got- I just went to the doctor recently.
Again.
Probably why my nose is irritated.
I've got these annoying things that I have to deal with.
And it's stupid.
It's stupid.
Anyways, how you doin'?
He's drunk.
Ha ha ha!
Ah, by the way, I drank a fuckin' pint!
This guy's- it's too much cocaine.
No.
I've- I've- this- no.
God.
Alright, let me tweet- we're gonna do some tier lists today.
And some browser, uh, just stuff.
We're gonna do- we're gonna- essentially what we're doing today.
Is it- you know what? I'll tell you in a minute.
I'll tell you in like a minute or two.
Let me tweet this and I'll be right back.
It's a boring title.
But what- what do you want me to have the title- you know, what are- what should the title be?
My titles tell you precisely what is going to happen on this stream.
It's just quick, it's to the point that you- you know what you're gonna get, right?
Facecam?
Uh, I- I don't know.
I don't know about today.
I think of course there's gonna be a facecam.
Stop asking for it!
Sorry, I got- I just got a little upset about that one.
I've- I've been in another mood today.
This is gonna be a weird stream.
I'm already in a-
This is two streams in a row where I'm just in one of those moods.
Remember, did you strangle somebody behind a dumpster or two- no.
Why would I ever, like, say yes?
What kind of question- why would I ever say yes to that question?
Nobody asked that.
Do I like art?
Yeah, of course I do.
All right, you guys ready?
Are you ready?
Hi.
So, as you see here- it's kind of dark in here, isn't it?
Whatever.
It's too big.
Okay, so, I have to update my fast food tier list.
Some of these are updates.
I've eaten at a lot more of these places, but actually there's still a lot that I have not.
And pardon my voice.
Every so often it's gonna go-
With sounds and words coming out and I'm gonna have to go-
Apologize for that.
You got a haircut?
When was the last time you guys saw me on camera?
How long has it been since I've been on camera?
Couple weeks?
No, I don't think so.
Smoker?
I don't smoke cigarettes.
I don't smoke anything.
I need to make it a little-
Hold on.
Needs to be- the brightness has to come up a little bit.
Right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it does.
You look drunk.
I don't look drunk.
Dude, are you drunk?
I'm not drunk!
Okay, I want like brightness.
That's better.
Well, that's kind of weird.
It looks like pixelated, doesn't it?
Is it better?
That's a little better, right?
Okay, I think that's okay for now.
Okay, I'm done stalling.
Don't worry, I'm high too.
I'm not high.
Put the contrast down or up?
Okay, we're gonna start.
I'm gonna update some tier lists.
Hi, everybody.
Welcome back.
Be entertaining.
That curtain hadn't even gone up yet!
This is relaxed!
I can stop screaming at you.
All right, A&W.
We're gonna start here.
A&W.
I'd like- I like the root beer,
but I've never eaten at an A&W restaurant before.
Do they even exist?
Is A&W like Blockbuster?
Like this one left somewhere?
Like in the middle of like,
Ohio or something somewhere?
Where is it?
I've never heard of this.
It's in Canada.
I think it just woke up.
I did not just wake up.
I know I ha- look.
Excuse me.
I need to tell you this.
So over the last like few months, whatever.
You know what I mean?
Like, okay.
I have like permanent wake-up voice.
If that makes any sense.
I have permanent wake-up voice.
From this nasal shit going on,
that has not gone away.
I don't think it's- I'm not getting old.
I have like these cysts that are in my sinuses.
There's one-
There's one right here in particular,
like right there in the back.
It's like this big or something.
It's like maybe this.
Like here.
Right there.
Like that.
They're like these little circles.
And they're pissing me off.
They're causing me all kinds of fucking problems.
Are you pregnant?
Arby's sucks.
I have-
I've had it like-
I've- I've- okay.
The last time I did this tier list,
I ha- I think I said the same thing.
I haven't eaten Arby's in a long time.
I think I've had it one time,
and it was the same opinion that I had
when I had it like two years ago.
Three years ago, right?
I just don't- I don't like it.
If I'm- okay.
If I'm gonna have a deli sandwich,
I'm just gonna-
I'm gonna make it at my house.
If I want like a turkey and cheese deli sandwich,
I could- I could just do that at my house.
That's like the reason why I don't really care about Arby's.
When I go to like a restaurant,
I like to get stuff that I can't really get at my house.
Stuff that tastes different,
is prepared differently, right?
Maybe it's not, you know,
it's probably not fair to put it in poor,
because it's just like deli sandwiches.
It's not like bad.
I did just say it sucks,
but that's like- that's fake.
I didn't mean that.
All right.
This is, uh,
a- a- a Bon Pain.
I actually have- I've walked,
I think by this restaurant,
like three or four times.
I think I've seen it on like Google Maps.
I've never eaten here.
I have like opened up like Google Maps to look for food,
and I've seen it pop up.
But I've just never- I'm just like, why?
Onions is-
I'm not- I don't like the buttery pretzel.
I like a hard,
like bronze pretzel on the outside.
That's kind of crunchy.
Onions is like kind of soft and buttery.
I don't like- it's like more-
it's more bread than pretzel to me.
I hope you die.
And a lot of this guy.
I like, uh,
really like crusty kind of dark pretzel on the outside.
And Onions is-
it's kind of like bread.
It's not-
I know pretzels are bread.
I know, I get it.
But it's like eating bread,
not like pretzel bread.
Does that make any sense?
I feel like when I go to Onions,
I feel like I'm eating like a dinner roll,
not a pretzel.
Am I insane?
I don't think I am.
I like it,
but I'd rather have like a different kind of pretzel.
You have awful taste.
Oh, just wait till we get to Domino's,
or you have no idea it's going S tier.
Okay, uh, Baja Fresh.
I've never had it.
This is Baskin Robbins.
I'm going to put Baskin Robbins in good because of one particular-
I got- my fingernails are a little too long.
I'm going to put Baskin Robbins up in good
because of one type of ice cream they have,
and that is their Mom's Making Cookies ice cream.
It's so unbelievably good.
It's like one of the best ice creams I've ever had in my life.
I made a tweet about it.
Yeah.
And the tweet like sucks.
I went back and like looked at that old like tweet.
I was like, this joke sucks.
And I wanted to delete it,
but I didn't keep it there.
But yeah, Mom's Making Cookies puts this in good.
It's got other stuff is good there too.
I would probably put it here if it wasn't for that one type.
Now, here's the worst part.
Actually, I'm considering dropping it down to average
and because that shit's not year round.
It's like a weird seasonal thing that they put up sometimes.
It's the best flavor you've ever had.
You can- Baskin Robbins, listen to me, please God.
You can- you can take off like strawberry cheesecake.
You can take off like Rocky Road.
I just put it up there.
Take- take off strawberry cheesecake and put this on.
You know how many times you go- how many times you go on to like Baskin Robbins
and there's a tub that like had not even been used.
Like shit's not even been opened.
Nobody's ordering it.
They definitely have data.
Just take the one that like nobody's ordering
and fucking just replace it with Mom's Making Cookies permanently.
I don't know why it's not there permanently.
It's the best thing they have.
Strawberry cheesecake was-
I mean, that was just me saying a random one.
I'm just saying there's ones there that like have been there forever.
And I'm going to be- maybe I'll sound like a weirdo here.
Why do we have vanilla ice cream still there?
I don't- I've never- I don't think I've ordered a just vanilla ice cream
in 10 to 15 years.
When was the last time you ordered just like,
oh yeah, I'll take one scoop of vanilla ice cream, please,
from one of these places.
I mean, like, yeah, everyone- it's good.
It is good.
But like put it in the back in a freezer.
Because nobody- people don't order it.
Who orders a vanilla ice cream?
You order like- I want like half Oreo cookie.
I want like half cheesecake.
Nobody gets just vanilla ice cream in a cup.
This is the worst take.
I don't think it is.
You can get vanilla ice cream everywhere.
Baskin Robbins, all these like craft ice cream places.
It's like, oh, look at all our crazy craft ice creams.
And then you got vanilla ice cream just sitting there.
Not even vanilla bean, by the way.
Excuse me.
I can get vanilla ice cream anywhere.
I tell you, my re- look, my restaurant opinions
are based on getting things that I can't get anywhere else.
I can't get moms making cookies anywhere else but Baskin Robbins
for like two months out of the year or whatever it is.
I can get vanilla ice cream in 700 fucking locations
within five miles from my current location.
I don't think I have to explain this.
It's staying an average.
I have eaten all tubs of Ben and Jerry's pint ice creams
in more than like five to ten thousand times, I think.
Well, that's way too much.
That's, um, half baked is the best probably ice cream
you can get at any grocery store or any place.
Half baked.
And Ben and Jerry's does this awesome thing
that other ice cream places don't do.
So Ben and Jerry's does this thing.
And I may have had this opinion a few years ago,
but I'm going to reiterate it.
You, they don't fucking skimp on the cookie dough.
It's not these little teeny little sand crystals of cookie dough.
They give you these like gobs of cookie dough.
Huge chunks of fudge brownie.
They don't, that's why they're up here.
I hate, there's nothing more that I hate
than eating a cookie dough ice cream
and you get to like the four or five little chunks of cookie dough
that are in there and the rest of it is just ice cream.
And you have like half of your entire treat
that is just ice cream.
And there's no cookie dough left at all.
Ben and Jerry's has cookie dough or fudge in almost every single bite
if you want to.
And that's the best part about it.
You can like, you can maneuver around Ben and Jerry's tub.
Let's say you don't want a bite that has cookie dough in it.
Oh, it's available for you.
It's available.
There's a little space right there you can carve into.
That's by far the best ice cream brand that you can just buy.
I like a store.
I don't know what Biscuitville is.
Bro, that's not a restaurant.
Wait, yes it is.
Don't they have, yes it is.
They have Ben and Jerry's like little like restaurants and stuff.
Yeah, they do.
They have locations.
Blaze Pizza.
I'm going to put Blaze, hold on.
I know everyone's freaking out.
Blaze Pizza might sit somewhere here,
but I almost feel like it's unfair for...
Okay, I'm going to go on.
I'm going to tell you a cookie dough rant here for Blaze Pizza.
Blaze Pizza does half pies.
It's a little rectangle box and it's half a pizza.
It's actually pretty awesome.
Forget about the taste.
Just the fact that they package that that way.
You can order a half pizza and you can DIY the whole thing.
Yeah, I'm going to keep it here for now.
Because I think I've only had it like a handful of times
and I don't really remember how much I liked or disliked it.
It's definitely better than the Domino's.
Blimpie.
Blimpie?
Why does this look like somebody wanted to put like Subway in a video game
and not get like copyright striked?
That's like what I'm seeing.
What is this?
I never heard of it.
Blimpie.
I don't know.
I love subs though.
It sucks.
I've never had it.
I can't say that.
Bob Evans restaurant.
I've had Bob Evans mashed potatoes, the microwave ones.
And those are...
Can I rate those?
Can I rate the whole restaurant based only on the mashed potatoes
and the microwave section?
Is this even the same person?
Is this even the same company?
Make a new meme.
No, because the rest of the place is not...
It's your tier list.
I don't think that's fair.
I would put their mashed potatoes like somewhere up here though.
Although they could be a little too salty sometimes.
Depends.
But the microwave Bob Evans is pretty good.
I don't know about the rest of the restaurant.
Bojangles I've not had.
Boston Market.
It's been a long time, but it's good.
I think it's very good, but I don't remember how good.
Make a meme.
All right, fine.
No, never mind.
I was going to just show you like all my teeth and I don't want to do that.
I was going to put my fingers in like this and just go like that.
No, that would be very bad.
I've never had it.
Roosters?
I've never had this.
Burger Fi.
Or is that Burger Florida?
I've never had it.
What is this one?
Burger M?
What's Burger Fi and Burger M?
Are these two the same place?
I don't know.
Burger M and Burger Fi.
Burger King is just...
It's just not.
I'm trying to think if I would rather eat Burger King or Domino's.
And I would rather eat Burger King.
This is going to get cleaned up.
Relax, I'm going to clean this up.
So people are saying, I can't believe Arby's is ahead of Burger King.
I'm going to clean it up.
And Auntie Anne's should absolutely be ahead of Arby's for sure, without a doubt.
We're going to sort this.
Just hold on.
California Pizza Kitchen I've had once and I don't even remember what it tasted like.
I can't rate it.
I had it one time.
I have no idea.
I have no memory of what it tasted like.
Captain D's.
Charles Jr.
I've never had it.
Charlie's Philly Cheese Steaks.
I think I've had this once.
How many places have I had?
You're insane for putting Blaze Pizza above Domino's.
I'm telling you, I'm going to clean this up.
This is just to get it in general location.
OK, a lot of sandwich, hot sandwich places.
I go to local places for this.
I don't go to most chains to get a Philly steak, Philly cheese steak.
I go to like a local place.
I may have had this once, but not really.
I've not had this at all.
All right, Chick-fil-A is going up here.
I don't know.
I think I would rather have Boston Market, although this.
OK, here's one thing about.
OK, I didn't like that drive through experience.
It's good, though.
It's like too crowded.
I don't know.
And is it too crowded and too obscene to like go get that for how much I think I like it?
We'll see.
It's better.
Auntie Anne's is better.
Auntie Anne's is probably should be here.
I was I think I was a little too harsh.
I think it was a little too harsh on Auntie Anne's.
I think so.
Maybe should I put Auntie Anne's up to good?
McChicken will always shine brighter.
I am going to.
OK, let's just do it now because people are going to fucking freak out.
McDonald's is up here.
I love this place.
Like, I'm sorry.
I do.
I love McDonald's.
People are going to fucking freak out.
I know you are.
I know.
I look it's like I like grew up eating McDonald's.
It was like like a childhood like memory.
The McChicken is so good.
It's so like it brings me back like memories and stuff.
I don't know.
I love McDonald's.
You can call me a fucking disgusting loser all you want.
I actually really do like it.
Look, I don't just put how much I like the food.
I put like memories, atmosphere, 500 cars in the drive-through.
You know what I mean?
Like I just all comes into my brain.
Right.
So when I'm sitting here going seven years old, four piece chicken nuggets,
apple slice, not a thousand fucking people at the restaurant screaming at each other.
Good.
Good delicious McChickens, McDoubles, everything.
Oh, yeah. It's up there.
Using nostalgia.
Yeah, I am.
It's not about just how good quotes the food is.
There's other things that factor in.
A play place. Yeah.
Fuck this.
It's going up. No, it's not.
You're literally conditioned to like McDonald's.
That's fucking stupid.
Yeah, I remember that comment from last time.
Eat a McDick.
Oh, I remember that one.
I knew three years later, two years later, I was going to have to defend this again.
Oh, man.
People are going to be really mad.
I don't think I think this is very overrated, like very, very overrated, but it's better than Arby's.
Look, I don't think it's bad,
but I'm telling you right now, there are especially here,
especially in the southwestern United States,
there are some incredible local Mexican restaurants that I would rather go to a hundred times over.
I find them 10 million times better, in my opinion, and a lot of times they might even be cheaper or the same price.
It's like a thousand times better.
If there's a Chipotle like here and across the street is like a local Mexican
like restaurant that serves like authentic Mexican.
I'm going to go here.
I'm not going to go here.
Chipotle is the definition of sus.
I don't think it's good.
Like I've eaten Chipotle more than a few times.
But if it's literally at the bottom of the list, if there's even one decent Mexican restaurant,
like a local Mexican restaurant, it's not even it's not even on my mind to even think to go there.
But that doesn't mean the food is bad, right?
Like I just it's probably like it's probably like here.
Realistically, it's probably here.
But no, no, I don't know.
But put CC's in F if you've never been.
I've not had Church's chicken.
CC's pizza.
I mean, I haven't had it.
So bro, rate Taco Bell.
Cinnabon is so good.
But I mean, I haven't had it in a long time.
Cold Stone Creamery.
Cold Stone is good.
It is.
Cold Stone is really good, isn't it?
But wait, isn't wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Cold Stone is the place that doesn't have sizes, right?
It has like I like it.
I love it.
I really love you.
Right, right.
Is that what it is?
And if you tip, they have to sing a song.
No, no.
Let me just give the money to the person.
Like, yeah, this is going down here.
No, I just want to I just want to you know,
like I just want to like put like fucking cash in an envelope and like tape it
to the fucking back of the door in front of the restaurant and just be like and just fucking leave.
You know what I mean?
I don't want to be sung to.
I don't like being sung to.
I hate I don't want to be sung to,
especially even like restaurants birthday shit when they come over and like clap.
No, please leave me alone.
Please.
I don't even going to give you like a free cupcake.
I don't want it.
I do.
Please leave me alone.
I would rather just like have us do a transaction and then be done with it.
I don't want to look around and be like, oh, yeah.
No, because I feel weird.
I don't like it.
You placed Arby's above Domino's.
Do you have bad taste buds?
Look, it's not done.
I'm just getting everything in the right spot.
My Cold Stone doesn't do that.
Did they get rid of it?
Wait, I want to read what this person said.
If you put KFC low, I'm going to buy you a ticket to Europe so you can see how much better it is here.
I think KFC.
I like KFC.
I like Cold Stone's ice cream is good.
Well, I don't like being sung to.
Maybe I'm just a weirdo.
It's good.
The ice cream is good.
They do like the weird size names.
I know like I'm not the first person on the internet to talk about this.
I know everyone has made a comment on this,
but just small, medium, and large.
It's so fucking easy.
It's so simple.
I don't know why we have to like, I don't know.
All right.
We'll see.
Cookout.
I've never had it.
Culvers.
I think I've heard of this, but I haven't had it.
Dairy Queen.
I had a cheeseburger from Dairy Queen one time.
I had a cheeseburger from Dairy Queen one time and I'm trying to remember how bad it was.
Wait, I gotta put myself back.
Cheese is melted.
Okay, it smells good.
I remember waiting.
I remember standing around waiting.
I could smell.
Cheese was melted.
There was crispy lettuce on it.
Took a while though.
Mmm.
I wasn't a fan of their selection.
Okay, I got it.
You're a psycho.
What?
I'm just...
I can time travel in my own head.
What do you guys can't do that?
You know that you can time travel?
You can just go back into like your own memories and just time travel back to a different time.
Isn't that insane that you can do that?
Like I can literally close my eyes and just like be like at some point like in the past.
Jack can't even rotate a cube in their head.
Yeah, people gave me shit for this before.
It's just a memory.
I know, but isn't a memory...
We've already had this conversation.
A memory is like internal time travel.
I like Del Taco a lot.
This is going to be very hard.
You know why I like Del Taco?
Because Del Taco has fries.
That's like kind of cool.
It's like, no, that's pretty cool.
Yeah, they have fries.
They have fries.
What an American.
As somebody that grew up like in Boston, in the Boston area,
it feels horrible to put this here, but it's fucking awful now.
Awful.
It sucks because 10 years ago, this would have been like up here, maybe here.
My opinion was solidified on Dunkin' Donuts recently, like within the last year.
I had it and it was probably the worst coffee I've ever had in my entire life.
And I remember just taking like a few sips and being like, what the fuck, man?
Like what happened?
But what about like Dave's making the donuts?
You know what I mean?
The guy with the mustache and he would turn around to the camera with a big tray.
I remember Dave from Dunkin' Donuts.
It was like he was supposed to be like the owner.
He like owned the restaurant and he made the donuts.
It was like, it's me, Dave from Dunkin' Donuts.
That's the only reason why it's up here.
But it's just it's not.
In my personal opinion, it's just not.
It's not very good.
And I remember maybe it was it always bad?
I don't know.
I remember like at least five to ten years ago.
It was like, holy shit, a blueberry iced coffee.
But you know, you guys have seen me drink this shit on camera.
Oh, blueberry iced coffee.
It was like a joke on the channel like five, six years ago.
I don't know what happened.
I don't like it anymore.
But holy shit, the blueberry iced coffee from Dunkin' Donuts was the best thing I ever drank.
Denny's gets points because it's never closed ever in like the history of the human race.
Like that's the only reason why they get points.
But like Galileo was going to Denny's and like they never closed
and they've always been open since then.
So it belongs up and like it's OK.
I like it. It's all right.
Dunkin' is of all franchises.
I'm sure it's total shit on the West Coast.
It's still fire on the East Coast, I promise.
But I have this opinion, OK?
If you have a good product and it's really good and people love it,
you need to make sure that that product is good everywhere.
You cannot have your name on a product and just blow it over
and just over expand to a point where the product is not the same product.
Like it's a worse product.
If you have that good product, it's got to be good everywhere.
Like if I go to the East Coast and get a blueberry iced coffee and I go,
holy shit, this is incredible.
What the fuck am I drinking over here?
You know what I mean?
That's why.
Is it even Dunkin' Donuts?
Does it have to be called something else?
Dave works at every store.
They can't control every one of them.
I'm just saying I've been to at least three or four separate locations
of Dunkin' Donuts in the last like three or four years.
And it's not it's I have been personally thought it was not very good each time.
These are good, but I have not had it enough.
Eat a Dunkin'
whatever time that person out for like five minutes.
What the fuck? OK.
Uh, yeah, I remember this place being pretty good.
I've still not had this.
OK, I'm going to put this up here because I want I want this.
I see it. It's everywhere.
I want this.
I need to have this.
I've never I've not had El Pollo Loco.
Not yet. It's OK.
We have it in. Yeah, I heard it's good.
I heard it's like because they give you
it's like a chicken drumstick and like sides.
It's like it's like I'm not it's like fast food, but it's not right.
It's like a KFC if there wasn't like breading on the chicken.
Right. But do I have that correct?
It's pretty healthy.
Yeah, I want to try it.
I've seen a thousand of these locations and I'm just like, fuck,
I want to have it one day.
But this falls into the same category.
The problem that I have, like eating chipotle, right, is like El Pollo Loco
will be there and I'm like, oh, El Pollo Loco local Mexican restaurant right here.
Yeah, that's where I'm going.
I it's tough for me to do.
Mexican food is my number one, probably at least one or two favorite food
in the world, so I like always don't have an opportunity to go here
because if I if I'm like, I want to try El Pollo Loco,
that place has a burrito that's fucking incredible.
And it's the best burrito I've had in like my whole life.
I like it's hard for me to go there to El Pollo Loco.
All right. Fat burger.
I don't have I have I had this baby.
Why do I remember this for some reason?
Maybe I've had it like once.
This logo is familiar and I like I remember
the logo and I remember like it tasting good.
I'm going to put it here for now.
This has to move.
I'll fix this in a minute. Don't worry.
I've done I've not had Zoli's.
I'm going to purpose going to be gross.
No, I didn't.
OK. Firehouse subs is good.
Hmm.
Although I like Firehouse subs,
but I feel like they're this selection is a little limited for me.
They have like a handful of like their specialty sandwiches.
But again, I would not go to Firehouse if I could go like, you know,
Frank Pizza's Pizzeria and it's like fucking great.
And it's like subs and shit and pizza like, I don't know.
I actually genuinely think it's better than.
Yeah, we'll have to go through this again.
Five Guys is really good.
It is.
But their fries are total absolute ass.
I know people think that's a weird opinion, but I think the fries are fucking awful.
Their burgers are amazing.
I'm going to. OK, the perfect French fry to me.
And you guys all know what I'm talking about.
And maybe, OK, whatever your opinion on me after this is how you're going to have
the opinion, right? French fry.
I like the I like the orange French fries that are crunchy on the outside.
And they're a little bit long and thicker.
They're like crunchy and they're orange.
You guys know exactly what I'm talking about.
They're like a dark orange color.
They're like crunch.
And there's like it's they're crunchy and they have like this potato in the middle.
Not a carrot. I'm not eating carrots.
Not sweet potato.
It's like from takeout restaurants, the dark orange long French fry.
Not a wedge, no.
I know that some people know exactly what I'm talking about.
It's like that either.
Yeah, it'll be like orange.
I don't like French.
OK, this is how many times I said, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK.
How many times? Listen, OK, OK.
I know that French fries are potatoes that you just julienne them
and you put them in some oil and that's a that's a French fry.
Right. But I don't like potato French fries.
I like my French fries to be crispy on the outside with like a good crunch,
with some of that like potato in the middle.
You're insane.
He doesn't know what you julienne julienne slice.
You guys don't know how you guys don't know what that means.
They're too mushy. Yeah, they're chefs in chat.
What's going on here?
Does he know that he's on stream?
All right. For a second, I thought I had like a electrode on my temple
because this I just like glanced over here, like at the preview.
So you're here and the preview is here.
I just looked over here and was like, what the fuck is attached to my head?
Am I like what am I connected to?
Electrode.
OK, it's been a very long time since I've even seen a Friendlies,
but I remember it being in the same tier as like Denny's.
But they had this thing called a Jubilee roll at Friendlies.
And it was this ice cream roll that had like frosting on top.
And you had to cut it.
It was like ice cream roll.
It puts it ahead, puts it ahead.
Arby's has mozzarella sticks.
Sorry, I came here to defend Arby's.
I gave my opinion on Arby's.
I if I want a like turkey sandwich, like deli sliced, like roast beef sandwich,
I just can get that at the deli at the I can make it literally from the fridge.
That's not to say it's bad.
Arby's defenders exist of Fuddruckers.
I've had it. It was good, but not good enough for me to remember and go.
Oh, yeah, I feel like it was better than this, though.
Brash green burrito.
I've never had it.
Hardee's and Carl's Jr.
This is like the correct me if I'm wrong, but Carl's Jr.
or Hardee's is just a League of Legends skin of Carl's Jr.
Right. I've not had either one of them.
Harvey's, Uddlehouse, IHOP is kind of in the Denny's tier.
It's just always open.
But I think I would rather go to Denny's.
Oh, certainly alarm off.
Oh, shit, there's a lot of new viewers.
There are a lot of new people here.
Oh, how many people are here?
I think the average concurrent viewers
that I have when I did this last time was probably like 4000.
There's a shitload of new people that probably love this place.
And I'm about to literally just I'm about
to literally just fucking make you probably leave the channel.
What do I say to them? OK.
In and out is good, but I put it in the same category as no, that's not fair.
I was going to say Chipotle. That's unfair.
It's way better than Chipotle.
And I like it. I would rather go there than Chipotle.
It's good, but it's not so good that I would.
It's not S tier.
I have a problem with the secret menu in a lot of these places.
I have to this like 10000 plus more people here than we're last time.
I have to tell I have to tell them about this.
Dick, they have a menu and then they have this secret menu.
But like, who fucking cares?
Why is it even on? Why?
Just put it on the menu and wrap the burgers.
I don't want like
like half open and it's like in a bag that I got like through the drive through.
It's not a secret anymore.
Animal style fries.
It's not like, oh, quiet.
Hey, I think I'll order that burger animal style.
Whoa, what?
What do you say, Stu?
Don't fucking say that so loud.
What's wrong with you? Don't say that so loud.
Just put it on the menu.
Wait, wait a minute.
I was told that in and out.
This is another problem I have with it.
OK, big problem I have with in and out.
I ordered in and out the way I am supposed to order the burger, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't just go to in and out and order the burger on the menu.
Nope. You've got to do animal style with
grilled onions and make sure that they put it in a to go box.
Just why do I have to order this thing
so special to make it taste the way that it's supposed to be?
Like every time you talk to somebody that loves in and out, they tell you,
don't order fucking anything off the menu.
You have to change everything.
But I'll tell you, I ordered a burger with the grilled onions in it,
take out box and I sat there and I ate it and I said, holy shit,
this is fucking really, really good, way better than the default burger
that you just order off the menu, way better.
And I mean, like, probably like a hundred times better.
So I'm going to.
OK, you ready?
In and out is going up here.
But then it's being it's being like it's being like changed, right?
Like it's up here. Then it comes down here.
This is like the hold on.
This is this is fucked up.
Like this can't be here. Neither can this.
Neither can that. Your pressure chain.
No, I'm just telling you that I I finally ate in and out the way that I was told
I was supposed to quote order special the burger and it was better than just
ordering it off the menu, which makes me want to put it down here.
Even animal style dick.
And this is another place that's fucking crowded all the time.
It's just like, look, if I'm hungry and I want
like a quick burger or something like time to go sit in an in and out like 10
to 15 minutes, sometimes that line is like as the same as like Chick-fil-A.
I want to make this clear.
I don't think in and out is bad.
I think it's good.
But the process to get it to be good is a little irritating to me and wrap the
burgers up like every fucking other restaurant does.
Every other restaurant does this.
If it was like one or two other places did this, it's fine.
Every single fast food burger place does not have your burger.
Out in the open in the bag to wrap the burger up.
I don't care what I don't care.
Just please put it in a wrapper.
Let me wrap it and put it in the bag, please.
Fuck out of here.
Jack in the box.
Why is in and out before McDonald's?
Because that's where it is.
If you want a wrapper, you ask for the takeout box.
If you're driving in your car and they give you a cardboard box,
that's like this cardboard fucking shoe box that you're supposed to.
I want a bag.
I don't want like this cardboard box that like somebody has to fucking hold like this.
Put it in a bag and wrap it.
It's a box in a bag.
Why don't you just put it in a bag?
Like Joe McDonald figured this out in like 1910 or whatever the fuck this was.
He figured this out in like the fucking 1800s.
When McDonald's opened for the first time,
you just like wrap it in a little bit of paper and you give it to the customer.
I'm not going to stay on this.
Just know I like the taste.
I think it's fucking good.
But I have but but but but the Simpsons.
Wait, did we do this already? Hold on.
Sim I'm freaking out.
Simpsons intro.
Don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't.
I'm done.
Don't don't don't.
I'm loving it. That's weird.
What is Jack's? Is Jack's not Jack in the Box?
Oh, is this the same?
You can see the insanity in his eyes.
Why do you like your burger mushed to shit?
I just I OK, if I eat in the restaurant in and out, I I need to be fair.
I cannot remember the last time that I
went into a fast food restaurant to sit down and eat there.
It's been I can't even remember when I did that last.
I knew I was going to have to defend this to the new viewers here.
Hey, Paul, I don't this is not Jack in the Box.
I don't know what it is.
I've never had Jamba Juice.
No, Jason's Deli is just Panera Bread with a different name.
I mean, that's just kind of how I see it.
Jason's Deli is for men.
What do you mean it's for men?
What is like is like the number one at
Jason's Deli like a steak sandwich with a beer and it comes with a free lawnmower
coupon. What do you mean for men?
Does it come with like aftershave?
What are you talking about? It comes.
I've had it before.
It's I thought it was good.
I thought I mean, I don't know if I'd put it like up into like our coveted in and out here.
And I don't know if I'd rather probably just go to OK.
I ate at a restaurant. Is this weird?
This is kind of a completely off topic story.
I ate at I feel like people like I don't know.
I ate at a restaurant one time and then I walked.
I finished my full meal at this restaurant and there was a Baskin Robbins right next
to it connected to this place, connected to the restaurant.
And I walked out of the restaurant.
I had a full meal. I was full.
It was a lot of food. Right.
And I walked out and like in to the Baskin Robbins.
And like I felt like it was I don't know.
Something was weird about it.
Like I walked out and then in and they came up with a big ice cream.
And I don't know. I feel like the workers are probably just like,
holy shit, this guy's fucking hungry.
This dude got like a large big ice cream.
He just had like a full dinner.
He had the munchies.
But it was I don't know.
Because it was immediately after I finished.
It was like, thank you.
Now, that was great. Thank you.
In the other door,
Jersey Mike's or what I like to call this place,
Oregano Mike's, because it's on every sandwich.
I actually not that big of a fan of this place.
It's good.
It's just Oregano Subway.
Yeah, I definitely I was definitely better than like fucking.
It's probably better than Arby's.
I had a turkey sandwich from this place
before, and it was like, that was fine.
It was just too much oregano on it.
I think I ordered it the wrong way.
It was fine.
Not like, oh, wow.
I would probably rather go to Firehouse than Jersey Mike's.
Jimmy John's.
These are just the same place in my brain.
I cannot distinguish between the two of these in my head,
but I should be able to. Right.
I feel like if I have to remember like the few times I've had both of these,
I don't know. I just don't know.
Johnny Rockets. Oh, man.
I got boogers coming out of my nose, I think.
Just be aware.
Johnny Rockets is good.
But how good? That's the question.
Keep in mind, I ate at this restaurant last time.
I ate at it. I was probably 11.
So I don't know how much of an opinion I can form here.
Eat your boogers, booger boy.
I cannot speak to it.
And unfortunately, if I haven't had it in over 10 plus years, it has to go down here.
It just does.
Jollibee is a really interesting place.
Jollibee is one of the only like fast food restaurants that has like fucking
spaghetti. It was like, holy shit, what?
I've had it a couple of times and I like it.
That doesn't mean it's good.
Well, now, why am I? I'm too bright now.
What happened here?
OK, um, I don't remember being like, holy shit, this is good.
Five guys should not be here and neither should Chick-fil-A.
McDonald's should be here.
Oh, my God, German.
Oh, my God, based.
Yeah, thanks.
Was that one guy in the chat that said
that he was going to be mad if I did this?
I like this place.
You know, it sucks about KFC.
Doesn't it suck being the only person in the group of your group of friends that
recommends this place and wants to go, but nobody else does ever.
What do you want to get for food, guys?
Oh, you know, let's think about it.
KFC is around.
There's a KFC. We could go to KFC.
No, no, yeah, we could.
But we could go here. We could go here.
OK, we're not going.
It's like I feel like I'm the only person that ever recommends to ever go here.
Like ever in all my groups I've ever been in.
So I don't get to have it that often because it's like it's hard.
OK, when I think of going to KFC, I think of you get like all the sides.
You get the bucket of chicken.
You get all the biscuits.
I don't really would want to go to KFC to order like just one little thing.
I only want to go to KFC if I get like the whole spread.
But I like it.
I do.
Their mashed potatoes are great.
Their macaroni and cheese is awesome.
The corn, I love that watery ass corn, don't you?
God, I love it.
I try to deliberately get the water in my mouth.
I deliberately try to get like the liquid.
Oh, I love it.
I'm sitting here thinking about like that watery ass corn.
And I want it up here.
But this is like just kind of like I haven't eaten today.
I've not eaten.
So right now you are this.
I'm just realizing what's going on.
I'm rating these based on what I want like tonight for dinner.
Not about how good they are.
I want that fucking watery corn tonight.
So that's happening.
OK, Krispy Kreme.
I mean, this is like the meme.
It's good.
I mean, it's good.
How good, though?
I remember biting into a Krispy Kreme donut and before I could chew, it was gone.
And I don't know if that's a good thing or a bad thing.
It was like it's like a cotton candy of donuts.
It's just gone.
This is kind of unfair, though, because Krispy Kreme just does one like meme
thing where it's like the Krispy Kreme, delicious, yummy Krispy Kreme, sugary
melts in your mouth donut.
But I would I'm not going to go to Krispy Kreme instead of firehouse subs.
It's a different world.
I'm going to keep it here for now.
I've never had this.
I am I haven't had this in probably since I was probably like 12.
But I but I like the little guy.
So he's going up here.
I've not had long drawn silvers.
I've never had Marcos.
I've never had the Callister's mod.
Mo's Mo's is Mo's is fucking good.
Mo's is way better, way better.
But it's been a long time.
Mo's is better than Chipotle.
It is. It's far better.
It's far superior.
I mean, my face, why am I so blown out?
Where's this light coming from?
Heavily disagree.
You know, I honestly, if you think Mo's is better than Chipotle, like that to me,
to hear somebody say that to me, that's like, oh, OK, you and I are on the same
page based like that's my based for me.
If you say Chipotle is better than Mo's,
it's like, oh, you and I are not going to get along.
We're just not at all.
I mean, we may just delete my number from your phone.
Like, we're not going to hang up.
I keep saying based.
I don't know why it's just like it's in the brain now.
Oh, I know why it's because the light's not on in this room.
I was wondering, like, why does it look so weird in here?
I'm sitting kind of in like a dark room and I didn't realize it.
Now it looks like normal.
OK, that was weird.
There we go. OK, what are you guys saying?
Noodles and Express.
Wait, what did I just put up?
I put something. Where did what was it? Oh, Little Caesars.
OK, Panda Express is hard.
This is not Panda Express.
Anyways, it is. What else?
Yeah. What are you talking about?
There's another panda.
Stop ignoring us. What are you talking about?
I don't think I've I think I ate.
I tried it off somebody's plate.
Somebody ordered it and I was like, oh, I'll try it.
I ate like one piece of chicken, but that I've not I've never really eaten it.
I haven't. Did you forget about the phenomenal tier?
No, I just need to make sure that stuff
that goes up there is stuff that I absolutely am certain of.
And then some of those might move.
So we're going to move a lot of the shit around this Panera.
There is. All right.
I do like cheddar broccoli soup and a bread bowl.
As much as people want to talk about Panera, you got to remember something.
Panera was like the first restaurant to really do shit like that.
Wait, I can get like soup and a bread bowl.
Like nobody did that shit like 10, 20 years ago.
So they kind of paved the way for a lot
of these restaurants that you see now. It's hospital food.
If you really think that friendlies is better, like what is friendlies then?
What would you consider friendlies to be in this scenario? Quality.
OK, it's all right.
It's better. I'll fix it.
But it's I don't think it's like great. I think it's good.
I've had it a bunch of times. Papa John's.
I think I've had once.
I think about it one time.
I don't like I haven't like had it.
I don't I don't really order from very many pizza chains.
Like I said before, if there's a local place that I would get it.
So it's not even on the list.
I don't eat it off of Papa Murphy.
East Coast subs, Peter Pitt Pizza Hut goes way up here because it has the stuff
crust and everybody, all these all these other pretenders that did stuff crust.
It's not even remotely the same.
It's not even fucking close.
Stuff crust pizza from Pizza Hut.
I don't know what they put in that crust.
I don't know what they do to it.
I love it. I love it so much.
And other people have tried to imitate and it's just not even close.
But it should be up here.
The only thing I order at the whole restaurant, nothing else.
You're tripping. Pizza Hut is garbage.
Have you had the stuff crust pizza?
Have you had a stuff crust pepperoni pizza from Pizza Hut?
I understand your concerns here.
Have you ever gone, I know, like, oh, I had a pizza at Pizza Hut.
It sucked. Yes.
Answer my question.
Have you ever had a stuffed crust pizza from Pizza Hut?
If you have not, you need to rethink it a little bit.
Even if you hate Pizza Hut, it's the only thing that is on the menu that I order.
It's just like Taco Bell and Taco Bell.
Let's just put it up there because I'm going to.
Right. Like, let's just do it.
Let's do it now because this is where it belongs.
The Cheesy Gordita Crunch is the single best menu item on any fast food
restaurant that has ever come out across every country on earth.
Everything else at Taco Bell can suck, can be disgusting and worthless.
It does not matter.
It doesn't fucking matter.
It doesn't matter.
Cheesy Gordita Crunch puts this up here just on its own.
It carries the whole rest of the team, the entire team.
The Cheesy Gordita Crunch scored like a hundred points in the basketball game.
And everybody else on the team was sleeping on the court.
They still won the game, didn't they?
Doesn't matter. It has to be there.
Quidditch and team fucking Gryffindor won that match.
Quidditch. Taco Bell, I fucking love this place.
There are times when I know I've eaten
Taco Bell yesterday and I sit there and I go, fuck it, I'm doing it again.
Doesn't happen that often, but it is the only place that I will reliably say I
would eat that instead of the local Mexican restaurants.
It's the only one.
It's the only exception.
Local Mexican restaurants are so good and you put Taco Bell up in S tier.
I have very, very specific reasons why, though, very specific that oh, especially
holy shit, if you get the Doritos taco, if you get the
you want to talk about this shit goes up, this shit goes into the stratosphere.
This is like aliens.
Aliens wouldn't even see this.
It's going to go so high into the goddamn cosmos.
If you put the Doritos Locos Taco in the Cheesy Gordita Crunch,
it can't even be on the list anymore. It'd be gone.
You would think I removed it. In fact, we should take it off.
I haven't had it ever.
And I always say I want it.
I say I always want it.
I always say I want it.
But I've never gotten it. I've never eaten it.
And I really do feel like if I had if I did eat it, that it would probably be up here.
I've seen like I've seen other people eat it.
I've seen like commercials.
I'm just like, holy shit, that's right up my alley.
I've never eaten it.
They have the fries you like.
Are you serious?
Wait a minute. Explain it to me.
What are the fries like it?
Are you kidding me?
Are these the fries that are these the actual fries that I like?
Oh, my God, they are, aren't they?
I mean, this night I'm going to get it tonight.
Yeah, I Popeye's fries and go to images.
Holy shit.
This is exactly what I want.
This is the exact thing.
The orange French fry and they're crunchy and they're crispy.
Holy shit.
This is precisely what I want.
All right. This is going up. This is going up here.
I don't even care if I've ever eaten it.
It's going up here because like it just has the it has the absolute best French fry
you could possibly want. It's going up there.
I don't even I know what those taste like.
I can put it up here.
Holy shit. It's unbelievable.
Let me show you.
So you hear this is what I was talking about.
Where is it?
That is exactly what I want.
I know what they taste like.
Is it where I know the exact sound that those make, too.
It's like
Popeye's is going up here because I know what those taste like.
Let's continue.
We're for two lows hot belly.
I think I've only I've only had to do it once.
This nose.
Oh, man, the honey bacon club from Quiznos puts this up here.
But it's I have not had it in a long time.
They even have this quiz nose.
Did Quiznos go to business about moving McDonald's?
It's it's dynamic.
It's going to be moving around.
I have to make sure it's in the right place.
Quiznos is bankrupt.
What a fucking unfair world.
What an unfair world that Quiznos has to go away.
But Subway continues to be on every other street corner.
What world are we in?
Why? That seems so unbelievably unfair.
And because of that, it's going up and asked here.
That's I can't believe it.
That place is incredible.
It was the best fast food sub place I've ever had.
What happened?
Canes, Canes is very, very good.
Canes is very good.
And Canes, in fact, is probably going up here.
I would absolutely rather have Canes than anything on this list.
Yeah, I think so.
It might even level up here.
It's possible.
Canes is the best fast food restaurant.
Well, it's one of them because it's obviously top four right now.
I can't Boston Market cannot be in my top five favorite fast food restaurants.
I haven't had it in like fucking 10 years.
It's going because of that reason.
It's going down here.
It gets hometown advantage.
Yeah, I can't know.
Reader Rita's Roy Rogers.
I just know the drink Roy Rogers.
I've never eaten there.
So borrows.
This is the pizza that you see at every airport and every mall.
It's OK. I think it's all right.
I would say it's better than Pizza Hut.
We'll see.
Shake Shack.
I remember Shake Shack was in S tier the last time I did this.
I said Shake Shack was the best burger
of any restaurant like fast food or other that I've had.
But I need to I need to update it and update it.
This is dropped for me.
It's still very good.
But the last few times I've had it, something changed.
It was OK.
It was it was very much like, OK, I mean, it was very, very good.
But something's something's different about it last year or two.
I don't know. It's dropping.
It came down.
Sheets never had it.
Smash Burger.
I want it, but I've never had it.
Smoothie King.
I don't think I ever had it.
Sonic is fucking horrible.
It's horrible.
All the wonderful drinks at Sonic try desperately to push this up here.
But when you eat like for the fifth time in a row, just cold food,
it's just like no fucking stay down there.
I'm going I'm I'm not kidding.
This is not I'm not trying to say anything bad, but I have to be honest.
I have never had hot food from Sonic.
I've only had it like four or five times, maybe in my life.
It is I have never had food that was even remotely warm from this place ever.
Not one time.
It cannot it's not even if the food is good, it's not allowed to be up there.
You only get drinks at Sonic.
OK, can we split Sonic into two different companies?
Can it be like Sonic Food and Sonic Drink?
Because Sonic Drink is like up here.
Sonic Drink is probably somewhere up up in this area, I'd say at least.
But the whole rest of the whole restaurant is fucking awful.
In fact, I think Sonic could probably save
a bunch of money and like redo their whole business as just being like a dessert
drive thru place. I feel like way more people would care.
Add more like desserts.
Have it be like a cool dessert drink drive thru place.
Because if it was just that, it's up here.
It really is. It's good.
But I cannot give that rating.
It's not fair to do that.
The drinks are like a tier.
Everything else.
This place sucks, too.
Have I become like a coffee, like snob or something?
Like I, again, over expansion, right?
Starbucks has got this is OK.
Starbucks has gotten to the point where there are so many of them that they're now
infiltrating grocery stores, targets, like malls, like what?
They have five locations in a mile radius.
That's not enough.
They need to be in your they need to be in your target in your grocery store,
in your gas station.
Like, why do they have to be?
Why do you have to be in so many places?
Why like when I go to like a target, it's just like there's a Starbucks in here.
It is just attached itself to every single other business.
Relax.
All right. All right.
All right. I'm going to relax.
All right. In your house.
Yeah, I wouldn't be surprised if one day I just like walked out of my bedroom
and there was a kiosk over here, just sitting like in the hallway.
What can I get you?
Um, I don't I fucking don't want a Starbucks right now.
I'm going to go down to the bathroom and like use the bathroom and like wash my
hands and like fucking coffee is going to come out of the faucet.
And this is going to be a counter, like a money counter.
Just
of how much money I'm spending by using my own fucking toilet.
I'm going to flush the toilet and like coffee is going to go down the toilet.
Starbucks, I've had it many, many times.
But holy shit, it does like it's in too many places.
It's so it's too much.
That's not coffee, dude, that's poo poo.
All I'm saying is when you expand so much that like when you can't what happens
when you can't expand anymore, there's a point where there's no longer
any further you can go there in every fucking store you then you win.
So it's like it's Starbucks going to go
on to like the Nasdaq or whatever, like one of these days and just like
smash the gavel and be like, boom, we won, we win.
And then they're going to just take the D list, the stock.
You know what the fuck is going to happen?
I just want everyone to know that, yeah,
Starbucks, we are in every single location, we're in everybody's house.
We're attached to everybody's skateboards and bicycles.
We have a nozzle on the back of your hose on the back of your house.
We win.
And then they'll move on to do something else.
And it'll be you're going to it's going to be like fucking Starbucks Prime.
I got to get Starbucks Prime.
Yeah, they're going to ship me my fucking like
they're going to ship me my fucking deodorant that I ordered.
They're going to start to get in the shipping business.
The coffee's OK.
I thought you meant like like Optimus Prime.
What? Every Starbucks comes together.
That's the big master plan.
They just like press the button that activates every Starbucks building.
And they all come together and like
Minecraft block, make a gigantic transformer and like take over the fucking galaxy.
It was all operated by like baristas doing like espresso machines.
It's like steam powered.
Anyways, I've never had it.
I know people love this shit, but I've never had it.
I've seen a bunch of these.
Well, here's a great way you can call me out on my bullshit, right?
You want to see like you want to like compare data, see how much of a liar I
possibly am, right? I did this like three years ago and I'm updating it.
Did I like fake Andy like pretend that this place was good because everybody
likes it and put it like up here like, oh, yes, take a shake.
It's good shit, man.
Like, did I like fake pretend like pander Andy, everybody?
Because you can like compare this list,
especially to like places that I don't really remember eating and be like he put
he put like steak and shake there.
You did that with Popeyes.
Yeah, this is illegal. It can't be there.
I have never eaten it.
I can't say I like the way the menu looks and put it in a tier.
That's not fair.
That's so unfair.
I hate this place.
I'm sorry.
I was standing in front of a subway one time and there were other restaurants
like around this place.
I was really hungry and I looked up the other restaurant on like Yelp
and this shit had like a three on Yelp, like a three, four.
I was like, oh, oh, I don't know about that.
And I didn't I didn't go to the subway call.
All right. I'm going to say this, too.
I probably said this before.
Oh, I'm going to be elitist, Andy.
No, I'm not.
If you don't have at least a high three or four or four point, at least not going
to your restaurant like you got to have at least like a high three.
I refuse to go.
I'm not going to go.
None of these count, by the way, because you want to do an experiment.
Go to go type in McDonald's into your like Google Maps or like
Apple Maps or whatever, right, and try to find a McDonald's or any
of these fast food kind of restaurants, right, that are over like a two five.
They're all like two point six.
Yeah.
All these fast food restaurants match my GPA that I had in fucking like high school
and college, but I'm talking about like a non chain restaurant.
If you're a non chain restaurant
and you don't have at least like a three, six, three, seven on like Google and Yelp,
I'm not eating it. I'm not going to eat there.
It's very powerful.
It's incredibly powerful.
Or five, four, three, four, eight.
What's wrong with your McDonald's?
Where you guys have high ranking McDonald's near you.
My local ones are three five.
What? Why is every McDonald's have been to like a two, a one, like a one point five?
It's because you live in a city.
My McDonald's has a three eight.
What is because you live in Las Vegas?
I think most of the McDonald's around here,
I think have like high twos or like mid twos or at least three or low threes.
Hold on. I got to fucking see.
Yours is three nine.
No way. I don't believe that everybody.
Look, the reason why I'm saying this is not because all these those restaurants are
like twos, it's because people find reasons to fucking hate fast food restaurants.
I don't know what it is,
but like you will read some of these reviews and you will I'll be OK.
I'll be like in the drive thru and you like over here.
The things that people are saying.
And it's just like, why is this person such a dick?
Like, what is it with people that I like?
I don't understand.
Like, let me tell you something.
There was a ketchup packet that wasn't put in my bag and the food's fucking awful.
It was awful, by the way.
It was it wasn't like the most high quality
five star restaurant food that I come to expect when I pay good money for something.
It's like, dude, you're at McDonald's.
Like, what are you talking about?
People put like fast food on this like fucking insane pedestal where it's like,
is that burger Angus beef?
That'd be like, well, it's fucking McDonald's, man.
Relax. It's like Burger King.
And a lot of those workers are like trying to fucking help you.
I feel for some of these fucking workers, seriously, because, man, you hear the stories
of people that just you just mean just shit people through the fucking drive
through people fucking with the restaurant and stuff.
Holy shit, man.
Give me your money.
Why did I read that person?
Anyways, I've never had taco bueno.
I've never had this.
I don't live in Canada.
I've never had Waffle House.
I've never had Wawa.
I've had Wendy's.
This is not done.
It's not done.
I'm not done.
I've not had Wawa.
This is unfair, though, because I'm biased towards Mexican food.
Would I rather have Wendy's or Del Taco?
I'm completely biased to Mexican food, so I would probably rather go to Del Taco
or Taco Bell or fast food.
You put Wendy's behind Del Taco because of fries.
I would rather go to a Mexican restaurant than a burger restaurant.
I just told you that Mexican food is my number one favorite food of all the genres.
It goes Mexican, Mediterranean, Italian,
or sometimes depending on the day, that flips.
I've not had Whataburger.
White Castle should be here, but I've never really had it.
I've seen it in the freezers.
Wait, I think maybe I've had it once.
Some of these places that I just don't remember eating, I've had maybe one time.
Fuck, which sandwiches?
Never had Wienerschnitzel.
I've never had Wingstop.
I don't know what this place is, and I don't know what this place is.
I've never had Wingstop, I've never had it.
It's time to clean this up a little bit and get this in a spot where I'm comfortable.
We've got to start at the bottom.
You have this. I've been here for two hours.
Holy shit, this is a lot of fun.
I like life. I love this.
This is great fun. I'm fucking blessed.
I love this. All right, subway.
We have so many more things to do today.
This is the longest one because this has the most amount of things on it.
This is probably arguably the most important to a lot of you.
This is the big one, so we're going to do the big one first.
You know what I'm saying?
All right, Subway and Sonic.
I would probably rather I would rather go
to Subway than Sonic just because I know I know the food will be fucking warm.
I just I really hate to say it, but I do mean that.
I'd rather go to Subway than Dunkin' Donuts,
but I don't know if I would put Dunkin' Donuts disgusting.
I know it's so itchy.
Would I rather go to Subway than Domino's?
I don't think so.
Would I rather go to Burger King or Domino's Burger King?
Yeah, I can say that.
Would rather go to Burger King or Dairy Queen?
I would rather go to Burger King.
But does that mean the Dairy Queen should be down at poor?
Would I rather go to Domino's than Dairy Queen?
Nope, because the ice cream that stays.
Would I rather go to Burger King than Cinnabon?
Yeah, Cinnabon is just like a one menu, Andy.
Yeah, I probably would.
Would rather go to Dairy Queen than Cinnabon?
Yes, I can say an average one menu item, Andy.
But it's good.
I just don't think if we're basing this on like where I would where I would rather
go or what I would deem to be better to go, I mean, I could just rate on the merits
of just quality of the food, but then this shouldn't be up here.
You know what I mean?
I'm basing this on like what I would prefer to do, where I would want to go,
where I would where I would go.
I'm going to keep it for now.
All right.
Would I rather go to Burger King than Starbucks?
Probably not. I would rather go to Starbucks.
Denny's or Starbucks, Starbucks, IHOP or Starbucks?
What's better? Probably Starbucks.
Hold on. We're moving a lot of people around here.
Burger King or Denny's?
I'd rather go to Burger King.
No, I'd rather go to Denny's.
No, depends on the day.
What time is it?
What time is it right now?
Is it over midnight?
Is it like 2 a.m.?
If it's 2 a.m., this is up here.
If it's like four o'clock in the afternoon, it's like down here.
This is hard.
I would probably rather go to Denny's than Burger King.
No, I wouldn't.
I would rather go to Denny's than IHOP.
That's for sure. So this has to go down here.
Do I think Arby's is better than Cold Stone?
No. Do I think Starbucks is better than Arby's?
Yes.
Again, it's just like a quality and like food and like what I'd rather have.
I'd rather go to Denny's than Arby's.
I'd rather go to Burger King than Arby's.
Would I rather go to...
Do I think Dairy Queen is better than Arby's?
Yes, because they have ice cream.
But Arby's too disgusting.
Arby's has ice cream?
Not Dairy Queen is known for their like blizzards and ice cream.
That's not the same.
Are you wearing lipstick today?
I'm using chapstick because my lips get very dry.
Thanks for reminding me to do it.
But Arby's has a funny Twitter.
If you honestly think I give a shit about like what is going on on like a comp,
like a fast food Twitter, I fucking care.
That's the last thing I can think of that I would like care about,
is what does Arby's have to say about this?
It's funny, I guess, right?
Like if they say something funny,
but I'm not like actively searching for what like Dairy Queen had to say
about something like a topic.
I don't... Have you seen Twitter?
Guys, I'm on social media maybe once or twice a month, maybe.
I like Twitter, Discord,
and it doesn't matter.
I like I don't use social media really that much at all.
So if I miss like the cool thing that like Burger King said, I'm going to miss it.
Make a tier below disgusting and put Arby's in it.
No, because I can't speak to that.
I've had it a few times and I don't remember it being like horrendous.
I remember it was just it was fine.
And that's sometimes all you want is fine.
You don't need to have every single restaurant.
Everything in average is not bad.
It's stuff that I would eat.
If you presented me with a Jimmy John's sandwich right now and said,
would you eat that? I'd go, yeah, I would.
If you presented me with a fresh Cinnabon, I'd go, yeah, sure.
I'll take it.
If you presented me with a gross grilled cheese from Friendly's,
I'd eat it, but I wouldn't be very happy about it.
But Friendly's shouldn't.
Friendly's is like a restaurant for kids.
OK, Friendly's is a place where the whole menu is the kids menu.
I'm doing it, I think a little bit of
disservice here by putting it here, but I think I'm going to keep it here.
It's a great place to take like kids.
I've been to a few, at least three or four
Friendly's before in my life, and people were really nice.
They were really, you know, if you go with like a couple of kids,
it's like they come and get milkshakes and like the staff was really friendly
and everyone was like, it was fine. It was good.
It was it was fine.
So I don't I'm not going to put it down here.
I don't think it deserves to be down there.
It's a place to get like an ice cream
and bring like the kids to have like a lunch or something.
And they get to go the kids get to go to a restaurant.
Excuse me, I'm putting this up.
They give you the little thing with the crayons.
They give you a piece of paper with like activities and quizzes on it and stuff.
Yeah, this is not fair at all.
It's unfair.
This is a nice this is a nice place.
It's a really just nice little place.
I'll fix it later.
Every time I've gone to like friendlies,
the response from the children was that was great.
That was it was a great time.
And if that's what they're trying to do, then they know they're not going to go
down here. No, they're not.
What children?
As I have nieces and nephews, I have like siblings.
A place to take the kids.
OK, I got to hurry up because we have like 30 things to do.
And I've already like on this for three hours.
Holdstone is good, but it's hard to rate the ice cream places
because they only do ice cream. It's hard to do this.
So I'm just going to say I'd probably would go to Starbucks.
I would rather I would probably go to Panera.
Yeah, I'd go to Panera friendlies.
Yeah, I mean, of course, take those kids.
Chipotle can stay here.
Most can stay here.
Einstein Brothers Bagels needs to come way up.
Little Caesar has to come way down.
Jason's Deli needs to go down as well.
I would actually have to put these here and I would rather go to Panera.
Like just straight up.
They are they are like equal in my brain.
But I would I have that cheddar broccoli soup from Panera.
You just you can't you can't beat it.
I'm imagining me going into Jason's Deli
and getting like what I would order at Jason's Deli.
And then the the cheddar broccoli soup in a bread bowl.
And I want that more.
What are you eating at Starbucks?
Like I said, that's why it's hard to do
some of these restaurants that only have one product.
All right. Little Caesar's.
These are kind of on these are all in the same tier for me, I think.
These are on the same tier, but I'd rather go here.
I'd rather go here than all these places combined.
I'd rather go to KFC.
I'd rather go to I'd rather go to KFC than Pizza Hut.
I'd rather go to Einstein Brothers Bagels and all these.
So Baro's good.
Where do I put Jack in the box?
I would probably rather go to KFC than Jack.
No, I wouldn't. Those little mini tacos.
Holy shit.
A little mini ones.
It's like taco popcorn.
But Rutgers is coming down a little bit because to me,
Rutgers is like it's like an attraction restaurant to me.
I've been to a couple of attractions
that had a Fudd Rutgers there and I've never seen it anywhere else.
And I think I've only had I think it was a good it was good.
It was I think I've only had it like once, though, twice, maybe.
I don't remember how much I liked it,
but I would probably I would rather go here if I'm honest.
All right. This is where it gets interesting.
But I'd rather go to Jack in the box.
I'd rather go to I'd rather go to Moe's than Blaze Pizza.
Blaze Pizza I think is lower than Moe's.
Jimmy John's has to come way down.
Krispy Kreme come way down.
Jersey Mike's way down.
These are only down here because they're just you go get a donut.
You go get a Cinnabon.
What do you want me to do?
They're good, but it's like there's only one thing you can do.
Firehouse does not stay.
Firehouse is going to move to a dessert category.
That's probably not a bad idea.
That's not a bad idea to just have dessert be a separate category.
But is there even enough to do a separate category?
One, two, three, four, five.
There is. OK.
Play Elden Ring. It's not out yet.
And I'm going to I'm going to piss my pants.
I've been drinking fucking coffee.
I'll be right back.
Airbnb. I have returned.
How are you? All right.
What were we doing? Oh, yeah.
I was showing you my awesome tier list that everyone is going to agree with.
Oh, would I rather I got to get the top done, right?
Do another tier list.
I had there are I have a lot of tier list.
We're going to have to go quick for some of these.
I think I like this.
I like how this is.
I would rather go to I would rather go to Jack in the Box than Ania's.
Oh, I probably would rather go.
I don't know if I would rather go to Jollibee.
It's good, but not to bar.
I think this is accurate.
You need to put a time limit on yourself.
I don't have to put a time.
Look, I I'm going to be live for a while.
I said a few hours, but I should have said several.
I should have said several hours because this is going to be a lot longer than I
think it is. I'm so burpy.
OK, all right, let's go.
Let's do it.
I'd rather go to Del Taco than Wendy's.
I just would.
I would rather go to In-N-Out than Del Taco.
I think that Boston Market probably can stay there.
That's just bias from the part of the country that I have like lived in most of
my life, so I don't know if it should be there.
I would five guys.
Haynes is so good.
This is a battle because I've had both of these pretty I've had them pretty recently.
Ben and Jerry's just Ben and Jerry shouldn't be up here.
I I like eating the pints of Ben and Jerry's from the grocery store.
This shouldn't be up here.
I'm going to keep it here, but I'm going to move it because like it honestly
shouldn't be here.
This is really what it probably looks like.
We're just this is because like nostalgia purposes, this is here ego.
I have completed my updated tier list.
There's no being too high.
The reason OK, the reason why Keynes is
number one is I just imagined myself taking that hot dog roll Texas toast thing
and dunking it in the sauce and biting it.
And it was a far better experience than everything else on this whole list.
On the whole list.
So that's why I think it deserves to be there on my updated list.
Haynes sauce sucks.
What do we do? What do we do with them?
You decide what do we do with them?
What do we do with them?
That's like cross-eyed.
What what what do we do with that guy?
What do we do with them?
What do we do with that guy?
You guys didn't know I could move one eye.
Don't do that. It like it sucks.
Stop. I can.
Oh, shit, I forgot.
I forgot there's a screen cap feature.
New meme.
Yeah, what did it look like?
I already regret it. Yeah, I regret it already.
Can I see it?
When the Keynes sauce hits.
Hold on.
I'm going to get out of here.
I'm leaving.
Oh,
when the Keynes sauce hits.
No,
fuck, I got to zoom in.
Hold on. No, I can't.
I'll mess up the whole thing.
OK, I'm moving on to the next list.
Here's here's my final thoughts on that one.
There it is.
That's the new worst face.
I don't think it's consequences for any of my actions, unfortunately.
Here you go.
It has been completed.
There it is.
There is my official updated list.
We're going to move on to the next one.
Take a look. There you go.
You want your screenshot?
There it is.
I don't know anything about that.
Oh, wait, I was facing the wrong way.
Who cares?
This next one is an update called best fruits.
I've done this already.
Let's see if I can see.
This is going to take a long time.
This is going to take a while.
I've been eating a lot more fruits.
I've been eating a lot more vegetables and fruits lately.
I'm going to see.
We'll compare it to the last one.
I'm going to do this very quick.
OK, lemon S.
Banana S.
Hair B.
Green apple A.
Red apple D.
Fuck red apples.
Apricots.
I don't really eat it.
I've never had one. Avocado B.
Blackberry flavor S.
Practice C.
I don't I don't like the fucking popcorn shells you get in your mouth.
All the all the berries, raspberries,
blackberries,
any of the berries that have the seeds because you'll bite them,
you'll eat them and you get the fucking popcorn shells.
And it's like, oh,
oh, I feel like a little like hard ball.
I don't like it. They taste phenomenal, though, but we're just going on.
I have to be fair to myself.
Kiwis S. No, they're A.
I've only ever had blackcurrant juice and blackcurrant jam.
I've never actually eaten the real fruit.
So I'm going to put it down here.
Blueberry. That's going to be that's going to be low A.
And I'm putting blueberry in low A and not S where it belongs,
because blueberries are very interesting.
They either are awful, like mushy and gross.
Or if you get a good pack, if you get good ones, they're unbelievable.
They're better than anything in the world.
I have to take that into consideration.
Cantaloupe D. Worst.
Absolute worst. I hate melon.
I hate I hate it. I think it's awful.
Cantaloupe is this stuff again.
I'll say it again.
And I probably said this a few years ago.
Cantaloupe is the stuff that you pick around in a fruit salad and you just leave.
And then if you still are really, really hungry and you still.
Whoa.
If you still really, really hungry,
you'll eat those last if you really are still feeling it.
Cherries, the actual fruit is probably
like a C, but cherry juice and cherry stuff is higher.
But I'm just basing this not on flavor.
I'm basing this on if I were to eat this thing.
So that means this should not be up here.
But I do that shit. I'm a weirdo.
I'm a weird motherfucker.
I like and go,
dragon fruit is I think dragon fruit takes over lemon.
But is it flavor?
I think we have to take everything into consideration.
Dragon fruit is what I want blackberries and raspberries to be
because the little seeds in dragon fruit are wonderful.
You bite into a dragon fruit and it's like this little nice crispy crunch.
Go through the seed.
It's so wonderful.
You can't do that with blackberries and raspberries.
Biting into a blackberry.
It's like the dragon fruit.
It's like pillowy little crispy seeds.
I love dragon fruit.
Coconut, the coconut flavor is F,
but the coconut water, coconut milk and coconut flavor is somewhere around here.
So that's what we'll average it out.
Cranberries. See you later.
Flavor, S.
Texture, S.
Health factor, S.
Tanginess, S.
Sweetness, F.
I've never had it, but I know it smells.
Figs are depends on how they're prepared.
I'm going to put them in C. Gooseberries.
They got a funny name, but I've never had them.
Grapefruit is F. Grapefruit just tastes like stomach acid.
I think I've said this before.
I've I've had burps that taste better than grapefruit.
I get to use that joke again, don't I?
OK, grapes.
Grapes are like blueberries.
If you get really good, like firm, juicy, cold grapes, they're amazing.
But if you get the fucking wilty kind of like sludge and they can go really low.
So they have I love them, though, if they're good, especially frozen grapes.
We might have to update this. Lime, S.
The only time I've ever had lychee is when it was in like a weird booze drink.
Oh, not really mango.
Hmm. What could it be is all right.
Nectarine. Excuse me.
This goes up here. Orange.
The fruit sucks worse than probably everything, but the flavor is unbelievable.
I hate eating oranges because of the weird,
gross sinew that's in an orange, that like white sinew.
Like, it's like a fucking like, you know,
disgusting.
I'm going to put it down at sea because I love orange juice and I love orange flavor,
but I cannot eat oranges. That's that's like weird.
It's got that. OK.
You know, like a raw chicken, like the raw chicken, like like fat that's on it
that you like kind of have to take off.
That's what it's like on an orange pie.
I don't really I don't really eat pie.
I don't really eat passion fruit.
It's just on every single box that has like tea in the name.
Oh, it's got passion fruit tea, passion fruit.
Like, I don't know.
Peaches are underneath nectarine, but they're still really good.
Although I'd probably put them down here at the permission.
I don't know what that is.
Pineapple is up here as well.
I love fruits, as you can tell.
Plums, I like the way they taste, but they're hard to kind of like weird
pomegranate or also like weird alien fruits, but they taste really good.
They're just hard to eat.
And I don't know, it's difficult to eat.
I don't know what this is.
Redcurrant, I don't know what that is.
I'm going to put it next to this one starfruit.
I mean, like if I was 12, I would probably put this higher
because it's like a Super Mario star.
But like, I don't really I've never had it.
I don't care.
Strawberry is up here somewhere.
Probably, I would say probably above, it's probably A.
Tangerine gets to stay with orange
because they have the gross sinew bullshit.
Watermelon is A at least.
I'm going to do melon F with cantaloupe.
Not as bad as grapefruit, though.
I've never really had an Asian pear.
I've never really had guava.
A lot of orange.
It's kind of just like a grosser version of a grapefruit.
It's like just weird.
Like, I don't know.
It's like it's too deep.
It's too like it's too heavy.
Grapefruit, at least to me, has like that acidic taste.
Blood orange has like the acidic taste and like the deep flavor.
I don't like it.
It's like an orange.
It's like the sinew of the of the orange and the grossness of the grapefruit to me.
I mean, I like the flavor is there for me, but it's just like the combination
of how I don't like I don't like citrus fruits eating them like this,
unless I'm like going to bite into a lemon and be a weirdo.
The citrus fruits have all that gross shit in it, especially oranges and things
in the orange family. Stop saying sinew.
Like it's a cool new word that I found out.
What is a custard apple?
I don't know. I never had a kumquat.
Never had a mulberry raisins.
If I'm in the mood for it are very high, but you have to be in the mood for it.
Jackfruit.
Have I ever had jackfruit? Maybe like once.
Sour cherry.
I don't I've not had really any of these.
All right, let's get this right.
Bananas are I don't know if I would.
Dragon fruit is like here.
Pineapple is higher than this.
Pineapple is probably here.
I would I would rather just eat a bowl of pineapples.
I know it's got the bromelain in it, right?
It's kind of hurts your mouth after a while, but it's really good.
I'd rather have a nectarine.
That's good.
You know, when you get a good nectarine,
when you need a napkin in your other hand to take one bite because it's going to
you're going to get sprayed with like a super soaker.
That's how you know it's a good one.
It's just one of it's just the it's arguably the best fruit.
But I like bananas flavor a little better.
Strawberry is no, it's not.
No, it's not.
And you know why strawberry doesn't get to level up and strawberry might actually
come down. How many times have you gotten strawberries?
And it's just texture.
There's just nothing there that you can't taste anything.
Oh, a strawberry bite.
I don't you don't taste anything.
It's just like you kind of can like smell strawberry, but you don't taste strawberry.
I'm going to put them down here because they live in the same world.
They need to be really, really picked at the right time and in the right place
for them to taste the way and be texturally the way that I want them to be.
So it has to come down here.
Green apple is so good.
You know, it's funny about green apple.
The only reason why I like green apple is because of Jolly Ranchers.
That's it.
When I was younger, I loved green apple,
Jolly Ranchers to a point that it made me want to eat the fruit.
And ever since, it's been my favorite apple.
Delicious is S tier.
Is that what you said?
Because that's probably one of the most incorrect things I've ever heard.
There's no nutritional value in Las Vegas.
This is strawberries have the same problem everywhere.
Back when I was in Massachusetts, I had the same problem, too.
It's not like, oh, everything in Vegas is
devoid of all flavor and all know what some of the best restaurants
in the world that I've ever been to have been here.
Excuse me, I'm going to have a reason to stay.
OK, kiwis are amazing.
You know what I've come to realize?
I love crunchy seeds that you can eat.
I love that texture of biting into a kiwi
and you get to the seed part and it's like that little crunch.
I love it.
I don't know, avocado shouldn't be on here.
I know it's a fruit, but it's not used the way that fruits are used.
I'm taking it off the list.
Avocado is a vegetable and I know it's not.
I know, but I don't care.
Avocado is like a tier in a vegetable list.
I don't put pineapple on my like cheeseburgers.
I don't put like I don't put like a slice of nectarine on like a sandwich.
I I'm I'm just saying that sounds good.
It's literally not a vegetable, though.
And where's tomato then?
Show me the tomato. Where's the tomato?
Where's the tomato?
You want to fight semantics on me here?
Find me the tomato.
Fine, it'll fine.
It stays up here.
I would probably rather eat an apple than an orange, a red apple.
Little Macintosh apples are amazing, but nobody fucking has them.
Nobody sells them. I don't know why.
Why? How come I've not why have I not been
able to find a Macintosh little apple in like the last five years?
Why? They're better.
They're the best.
Now, even when I was in Massachusetts, I couldn't find them.
I love Macintosh apples.
They're the only red apple I like.
OK, I think this is good.
I'm happy with this lemon lime.
It's just it goes on everything.
It goes well in everything.
Lemon water, lemon candies, lemon, like a slice of lemon on something
like a squeeze of lime on stuff.
I mean, it's like you can't beat it.
I think this is good.
I'd rather have a nectarine than eating a banana.
There it is.
You just proved your avocado point wrong with lemon and lime.
What do you mean? Macintosh suck so bad.
I'm still not over that.
It's fucking I love it.
Would you just eat a lemon or a lime?
Yes.
Every time that there's a lemon or a lime
from a restaurant that they put on the side or something, I always just go
every time I love it, prove it.
Do you really want me to prove this by
like biting into and like enjoying a lime on stream?
That's not hard to do.
That's very easy.
That's a very easy thing to do.
It's not like eating a raw onion.
Limes are not as harsh as a lemon is.
It's not like biting into like an onion.
OK, here you go.
Let's move on to the next one.
We did that one. We did that one quick.
That's good. All right.
This is a American Mammals tier list.
Why am I even doing this one?
Who cares?
Who gives a shit?
Who actually gives a shit about this one?
You know what I mean? Like, who cares?
All right. How about we need some music?
We could use some music.
What's an OST you want to hear?
Mario Party OST.
But Deltarune. Oh, yeah, it's not bad.
It's not a bad one.
All right.
It's got a nice and low just in the background.
We don't need to be loud.
It's a good shell in the background.
You know what I'm saying?
You know what I mean, Bird?
Let's continue.
Armadillo is Est here.
It's just what a cool animal.
Uh, Badger.
OK, wait, what's the criteria here, though?
Is it animals that I think are like cool, that I think are cool?
Or what's like the strongest one?
Just coolness factor. OK, I can do coolness factor.
About all right.
That's a pretty cool.
They're very cool, actually.
My dad is the only person other than you that says,
you know what I mean, Vern?
Well, your father is a hyper intelligent
individual who consumed countless hours of earnest.
So that's your dad is a very smart person.
Beaver.
Beaver, I would say probably be a beater.
Sheep, bighorn sheep, see?
Bisons, they're like big and cool.
Black Bear's ass, they're the cutest things in the world.
They're just so I just run through of Otto.
Bobcat.
Hi, B.
Caribou, C. Chipmunk is A just because it's
fun to watch them kind of scurry around and stuff.
Yeah. Iotis, B. Deer, B.
Well, baby deer is like holy shit.
What an adorable like the world is at peace right now.
When you look at like a baby deer.
But dolphins, dolphins are kind of cool.
I have all the horned
mammals that then come down to about C for me.
Fox, I feel like is S tier for too many people, which I'm a contrarian.
So I'm going to put it down at C because I can't like the thing that everybody else
likes because I how could I I can't I have to be the contrarian.
I like armadillos. I'm different.
I'm not like I'm not like everybody else.
Gophers are funny.
Grizzly bears are just huge grizzly bears are the bear of the bear world, I think.
So they get to be a pretty high.
Groundhogs and gophers are just like the same animal in my head.
So I don't even know what that is.
A javelina was a javelina.
Manatee is pretty high.
We might upgrade the manatee.
A marmot.
It's kind of like a beaver. Martin is kind of like a it's like a ferret.
Moles are S tier.
They're so weird.
What a strange animal.
Moose get to upgrade from the horned
animals list up to summer and B because they're just so huge.
They're massive.
It's interesting.
What is that?
What the fuck is that?
I thought that was a dog.
That looks like somebody drew like a Chad Brian the dog.
It's a mountain goat.
Why does it look so photoshopped?
Mountain lion.
You guys can hang out in the same place.
Mouse.
A tier. I love mice.
I love mice and I love rats.
Oh, a musk of the musk rat.
Kind of cool. Possums are weird.
Like so it's too weird to not be S.
I love otters.
I love when they go like this.
I love. Yeah.
They just because of this is the reason why they're up here.
I mean, like the sea mammals are really cool.
Whales go up really high just because this thing is just how does it even exist?
This is a dinosaur.
We have so many weird.
And OK, when people talk about I wonder what they imagine,
like how crazy shit would look on other planets.
Wow, like how fucked up and crazy would the animals be?
They'd have like antennas coming out of their heads.
They'd be this is look at a whale, look at like a big blue whale.
And you try to tell me that that wouldn't
be insane to see that if you were from another planet.
They're a big floating mass of just like soft tissue.
And they have these huge, huge like Muppet Mouse that go like
it's they're completely strange.
They're abnormal.
They're not from Earth.
They're like living machines in a way.
They're just giant hulking like monolith machines.
It's crazy.
They belong in us.
Why you cut my mic? Why?
That's kind of cool. Whatever that is.
Orcupine is kind of cool.
Furry dogs are kind of like, hmm, they're all right.
It's kind of like another dog with horns.
This is a German shepherd with horns.
What is this? A pronghorn?
Rabbits are pretty cool.
Raccoons are really cool.
Rats are rest here.
We'll mess with this in a little bit.
This thing's kind of cool.
Sea lions are kind of cool.
Seals are kind of, seals are all right.
I like when they go like this and their whole head kind of stuffs into their neck.
A shrew. Oh, yeah. Shrew is up here.
Skunks are fun.
Squirrels are cool, but it's just like it's an oversaturated market for squirrels.
You know what I mean?
It's not interesting to see a squirrel,
even though they're really cool and they're really funny.
It's a very oversaturated market, I think.
Vols are cool.
I don't know if they're est here, though.
Weasels are est here.
Walruses are kind of like, I don't know, weird to me.
Wolf is, I mean, it's just like so easy.
Wolverine is just so angry, it's funny.
OK, let's get this accurate.
Which one is your fursona?
It's one of these in est here.
Armadillo versus rat.
Armadillo versus otter.
Yeah, Armadillo is cool.
I think skunks are funnier than black bears.
I don't know why. Mole, weasel, possum.
Whale, I think, comes up high like here.
All right. Mouse, antity, chipmunk.
Orca, orca and whale.
It's just so huge and hulking.
It's so interesting.
Where's Wolverine? Wolverine has to come up.
Yeah, well, that's not fair.
I'm basing the opinion of bringing the fox up,
not because I want to be the contrarian,
but because of that video of the fox going like,
that's such a cute video.
I love it.
It's like one of the cutest videos ever.
The fox is so happy and just like, it's like,
man, it starts like just making noise and it's so happy.
They're about to get a treat and they're just like, oh, my God, yay.
What do you mean, what? You guys have not seen that video?
The video is so good.
Yeah. How many of you guys have not seen that video?
I'm supposed to be the one that doesn't know anything about the Internet.
You guys are supposed to know all this.
OK, rabbit. Yeah, I think this is good.
I don't think I need to change anything.
You can probably tell that I think most of the animals and horns are kind
of interesting, but not really.
They always do this.
OK, the horned animals are like the Ford truck commercial
of the animal world.
They always have they always take the same picture of them sideways turned head,
like looking in the camera, like sideways profile head turned.
It's I feel like it's like a car commercial.
It's just a model pose.
Yeah, I think my drink is leaking.
You just have to drink it faster.
Oh, American made.
Yeah, this is what I think of.
These things are going to start to leak.
It's starting to kind of compress on itself.
I don't know why.
All right, there you go.
Animal tearless.
That means my fursona is an armadillo or a rat or an otter or a skunk.
I don't want to be a skunk, though.
I think I would be an armadillo.
What's next?
Uh, he's a fast food mascots.
I could beat in a fight.
OK, well, I'm going to tell you right off the bat, I'm just going to stomp this guy.
You know what I mean? I'm just one shoe print is going to instantly kill
and break every bone in this thing's body.
This is going to be like
this and it's going to be squished.
So that's guaranteed.
Wendy, I'm not so sure.
I think I get I think I get beat up, Wendy.
Hmm.
You might kick the shit out of me, though.
I feel like I would I might actually get my ass kicked from Wendy.
I would not be prepared for what Wendy would do.
Like, I feel like she would come with like a fucking pitchfork or something.
Wendy's 12.
Well, what would you like me to say about the baby then?
What do you want to say about the baby?
What should we say about the bit, the literal infant baby on this list?
OK, this guy's going to kill me.
I'm just I've already died.
The Quaker Road guys fucking kill me.
Why and punch? I'm just going through the happily.
OK, the Happy Meal Guy, the Happy Meal Guy.
I would just go like this and like fold them and just crush them.
This flight involved here.
I don't like I love bees.
I love what they do for the environment.
I need to protect bees at all costs.
But if one bee gets like too close to me, I'm going to go like this and fucking run.
So I don't know.
I'm not sure if I would be able to do it.
These these these three little guys here, they could they could be anywhere.
I feel like this big like this big and they OK, not only are they small,
but they have like sentience, like human sentience.
They're like intelligent beings, right?
They could literally just poison my drink.
Yeah, they could come in with like a cyanide capsule and fucking just like
heave it up there, get up there and dump it into like my coffee.
I would lose. Absolutely.
Tony the Tiger is not is not going to be a fight.
Tony the Tiger would destroy me.
OK, this is like a this is like a old revolutionary guy, right?
I feel like this guy would just shoot me.
Chuck E.
Cheese, that's a fair fight.
Why is the jelly bean even on this list?
You it would be I would just eat them.
It's like, oh, you are you want to fight?
And then I go, oh, you were popcorn.
Oh, Bakers were pacifists.
Wait, they were. Oh, I'm getting deja vu.
Do we have the same conversation like three years ago?
We did the same thing.
Did I do the same list?
Why am I acting like this is so different?
Mr. Peanut, easy.
Grimace, this is I don't know, Grimace.
Grimace, I feel like doesn't have very much access to his hands.
So all it would take would be like a full sprint drop kick right into his stomach
and he would just tumble off a cliff and he'd be over.
So I think I would I would think I would destroy Grimace.
Hmm.
I could beat I could be I could absolutely be the Lucky Charms leprechaun.
Again, we have the same problem here.
The same problem here. I could just get poisoned.
I could just get poisoned.
It's just a cyanide pill.
They're like this tall, right?
I would be in big trouble.
Poison isn't a fight.
What do you mean?
I was wait, it's not which one of these
could like murder you in your sleep.
It's fight.
Oh, oh, OK.
Then, yeah, I would just it would be pretty easy.
I guess that would be very easy.
What's the point of this whole list?
This is an old man like
nobody on this list could stand a chance
besides Tony the Tiger and maybe Chef Boyardee.
You can't say he has flight, which is very important.
This is just another another like this is like another little kid.
What's the difference between these two?
What's the difference? We already did this.
I don't need to do this again.
This is a cow.
So I don't I mean, I feel like I could get like really fucked up.
This is a this is a cheetah, which I would be.
All right. What's more dangerous, a tiger or a cheetah?
By the way, like a cracked out cheetah.
Tony the Tiger is like fit and he wants to help and he wants you to go
and have a great time and go out inside and play soccer.
This guy's like Cheetos.
Yeah, like this guy's fucked.
I don't know about this guy junk food, motherfuckers like this.
Yeah, this guy's an absolute this is mayhem.
I would be this is S tier for sure.
Who's this?
I mean, I would I would annihilate you.
This is the Taco Bell dog.
This is very important because there is a very high chance that they could be
a 90s comedy scene where he like bites my balls.
Right. And I got to be like, oh, the dog that this could be very, very difficult.
Keebler elves goodbye.
Eminem's goodbye.
They're just like they're like an inch tall.
Why are you on here twice?
I would kill both hands, your left and your right.
Ronald McDonald, I would put up here.
Yeah, I don't know why.
I'm just imagining Ronald McDonald with a pissed face
in like in like a candid TikTok video for some reason,
like just slapping me in the fucking face,
like on like somebody's filming it like on TikTok or something.
Like I'm just I don't know why I just imagining me sitting there like,
fuck you, you piece of shit.
And he just goes like, and I go up.
Yeah. So he'd win.
He would kick the shit out of me because this happened.
Oh, the Kool-Aid man, I he's got size,
but I would absolutely beat them because he just made it a glass.
I would just pick up a rock and throw it as hard as I could.
And it would just Kool-Aid man is also like cracked out.
It doesn't know.
But the Kool-Aid man's made it a glass.
He's made it a bulletproof glass.
Where do you who said that he breaks through walls?
Oh, shit, he does.
That's a that's a big problem.
I feel like like the Hawaiian punch in the stomach would probably hurt.
But that would just probably just drop, kick him after that.
I think I could do it.
Oh, here's another like this is not like racked out guy.
You know what I mean?
I don't know if he's higher that he's up here.
This is somebody that when they eat chocolate, they turn to like it's like
Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
So if I kept chocolate away from the cocoa puffs bird,
I think I would be able to do it.
But if he like Popeye, the sailor man,
spinach like crushed like a chocolate bar in his mouth, I'm going to run.
That's up in the air. I'm not sure.
Sun of raisins.
OK, I think that'd be pretty.
Hmm.
Farmers are ripped.
Yeah, that's why I'm sitting here thinking about this.
But you're like out in like the sun.
You're out like where you're doing stuff.
I'm such like a soft, supple, like fucking blob person at this point.
I would probably crumble in one fucking hit.
I have like my stomach like is
made out of it's like shakes now.
I would probably lose.
It would probably lose, especially if you caught me on like you're dead.
No, it would be fair. It would be a fair fight.
No, it wouldn't.
You're supple. Well, I mean, just like my supple.
What I don't have words to describe.
There you go.
Is the list of food mascots I could beat in a fight a tier list maker.
M&Ms are human sized.
No, they're not.
What are you talking about?
A human sized M&M is just grimace.
That's not what you know.
That's wrong. What?
No, it's not.
He does exist.
They do exist.
They're like up to his shin.
They're not even up to his knees, guys.
In that Santa Claus commercial.
What are you talking about?
They're not human size.
They're tiny. They're like two feet tall.
Santa's huge.
Santa's not like 15 feet tall.
Sorry, Santa.
Santa's not as tall as a monster.
OK, Santa's not as tall as a monster.
All right.
Come on.
You guys trying to say that?
Yes, he is. Santa is not fucking 30 feet tall.
No, he's not.
I'm going to write how tall is.
How tall is Santa?
How tall is he? He's 6'6".
OK, but if you're 6'6",
somebody that's of M&M's come up to his shins.
We're watching that fucking commercial and I'm going to put this to rest.
Oh, yeah, they're human sized.
They're not even to the base of the Christmas tree.
This ad is not canon.
Oh, please.
I'm putting it on here.
What do you mean not canon?
You guys ready?
Don't listen to that ad.
OK, you ready?
Look at them. It's a pissed eye look.
I'm like, all right, we're going to watch this
because I want to prove once and for all that you guys are completely wrong.
So what we have here.
Stop. Can you see it?
No, you can't see it.
Let's find out how tall the M&M's are.
I don't know.
I never met the guy.
OK,
explain to me how this guy that's 6'6", he's six feet tall, six and a half feet
tall. So if you go up one foot or these guys are like maybe nine to ten,
like 12 inches tall.
We exist.
And by the way, all it took was for them to see Santa Claus and he fainted.
I would kick the shit out of these two.
Are you kidding me? Imagine meeting German 985.
Imagine you meet me.
Well, German 985.
Oh, I rest my case.
So, oh, my God, he does exist.
Do exist.
That's what I would do. I wouldn't faint.
Why is it so bright in my room?
I hate cameras.
All right, we did this.
Let's go. This one is Super Mario characters.
Every one tier list.
I'm not doing this. This is too much.
This is so many.
Can I skip this one?
I mean, look, everyone is here.
Yeah. Wait, why?
Why King K.
Rule? Yeah. Why is he on here?
Please don't do this one.
This is going to take a million years.
Maybe we'll come back to it.
It's a lot.
Thanksgiving food tier list.
I can do this one.
We'll save it. We'll save it.
I look, I'll go back if people still want me to do it.
All right, let's go. Easy.
In fact, this is so easy that this is the only thing that's up here.
It's on a complete other level.
Stuffing is on another level than every other food item at Thanksgiving.
A stamp on it.
Pumpkin pie. Yuck.
Apple pie. Yuck.
Biscuits. Very high.
Brussels sprouts.
Squash made no jellied cranberry jellied cranberry.
They whoever made this list, you know what you're talking about.
Cranberry sauce. Get out of here.
Is this a green bean casserole?
That's also up here.
One bread that's also up here.
This is going to be close.
Corn.
Hmm. Creamed corn.
How would dinner dinner rolls?
No, I want the biscuits and I want the cornbread.
Gravy. That's OK.
Ham. No, I don't want ham.
Mac and cheese. It's up there.
That's all right. Mashed potatoes.
You better believe it. Red wine.
No hard pass. No, no.
I don't understand this whole pair alcohol with shit.
No, I want to drink alcohol separately.
I don't I don't get it.
I don't want to drink like I would give me like a sprite.
Well, I'll say I was like a glass of milk over a red wine at dinner.
I don't like drinking. I love wine.
Don't get me wrong. Red wine is est here for me and alcohol.
And I would pair it with this meat.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I feel like you're just making that up.
Do you feel like the people just make that up, that they just go like, oh, oh, oh, yeah.
And that's that piece of steak.
Yes. Oh, that that that.
Wow. I feel like you're just making it up to like seem sophisticated.
I've done that before.
And it's just like this.
I just like I just drank wine after eating like a piece of meat.
And guess what I did?
Guess what I did after I did that?
Oh, yeah. Oh, no.
That pairs very well.
That pair. You know what I want to try?
I want to try that with the fish.
It's like, what the fuck are you talking about?
You're making this up.
I have done this at least a handful of times before.
And then you're at dinner and you tell other people and you don't give a shit
about any of this, but you just do because then that person thinks you know what
you're talking about because you've like had that experience before where it's like,
oh, you get you're getting the chicken.
Let me tell you something.
I'd recommend a Malbec.
It's like, oh, wow.
You you you know why you must die.
You're much more sophisticated.
I thought you just ate McDonald's,
McChickens and ate Capri's drink Capri's son juice boxes.
No, I do more.
I just don't get it.
Maybe call me like uncultured weirdo.
I I want to drink wine.
I have a bottle just like drink it.
I don't I don't want like to have you want some wine at dinner.
Oh, here you go, sir.
OK, great.
What am I supposed to do with this?
What am I supposed to do with that?
Thanks for the sip of wine.
That'll be like that'll be like $19, by the way.
The whole meal was like fucking 20 bucks.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I could see that.
I could see that with a casserole.
Let's backtrack a little bit.
If you like, like what?
No, no, I'm not backtracking on this one.
Roasted vegetables, pretty good scallop potatoes.
Holy shit. Absolutely.
Sparkling juice.
Yep, that I don't have to pretend with that one.
It's just like it's sparkling like grape juice.
And I go, oh, my God, this is great.
I love this.
I don't have to take the sparkling grape juice and go, oh, oh, yeah.
Oh, no, just give me the fucking goddamn grape juice.
I don't you know what I mean?
Sweet potato casserole.
It's all right. It's good.
Fuck you. You put dinner rolls at a hard pass.
Well, because I there's only enough real
estate on your your plate to have dinner rolls, biscuits.
They take up a lot of real estate because they're kind of they're a bit like solid
shape and they have to like you really want like more than one or two.
But they kind of slide around.
They take a lot of space.
I like everything separated, by the way.
When I go for Thanksgiving dinner and
if I like somebody made it because I don't fucking do that.
I fucking don't know how to cook.
I don't know. I'm not a good like if my mother would make Thanksgiving dinner,
it's not going to be me.
I'm going to go separate everything.
You go up more than once.
The people you're at the kids table.
No, I'm not. I'm a grown up.
So you go get enough.
I don't like putting everything on top of each other.
You look at like, oh, I'll go Jerry over there.
And he's got a plate this high and he's
putting stuff on top of the biscuits and shit.
It's like, just come back like you can come back up again.
You don't have to do that.
You know, like, you know, like, oh, here's the big turkey.
Here's like the biscuits. Here's the cranberry sauce.
Like Uncle Jerry, you don't have to like
put everything on the plate at the same time.
I like having turkey sectioned, stuffing sectioned.
I have everything has to have its own place.
I don't like when everything's just mixed together and mashed together.
No, I like it in its own place.
It gets too messy.
Things start to blend into each other.
I would definitely say that
I'm going to put this at great.
Scalloped potatoes, I'd rather have that that's not accurate.
You put pie in hard pass.
Banana cream pie is the only pie I like.
Chocolate cream and banana cream pie are the only two pies that I like to eat.
I don't like any other pie.
I'm sorry that everyone doesn't like that.
Let me put some lip balm on.
I just realized my eyes have been open for a long time.
The pie opinion is wrong.
I just I just don't really like pie.
I don't like hot pies, like warm pies.
I'm starting to realize this.
I know the pumpkin pie isn't necessarily warm, but turn on the music.
What happened? Did we lose it?
What about the ice cream? No, no.
Because the ice cream just like melts and turns into liquid.
And then it's like you it's weird to scoop it up.
I don't like it.
Um, what happened to the Deltarune soundtrack?
OK, here we go.
Hard pass on ham.
Yeah, to me, Thanksgiving's turkey.
I don't I'd rather not have ham.
I'm actually not really a ham guy, if I'm honest to crusty lips.
I know that's why I have to continuously lubricate them.
I'm aware.
I think this is good.
This is good.
What's up next?
This one is a create a Christmas movies tier list.
I'm not even sure I've seen half of these.
Um, we'll find out.
I remember this movie because there's a scene in this movie at the end where Bill
Murray is trying to rile up a crowd and he's like, yeah, let's hear everybody start
screaming. All right.
Just just the parents.
Oh, just the men.
Oh, just the children.
Oh, and then he goes and you, you that's been talking through the whole movie.
And I freaked out.
I thought he was talking to me.
I was terrified.
I was like, I was talking through the whole movie.
He knows.
Skip what? Skip.
Let me skip.
It's November.
All right. Can I just find where my favorite Christmas movie is?
There it is.
These one and two are up here and this one.
All right.
Can I?
This is not going to take me very long.
Everything else doesn't even I don't even need to put anything else up here.
Yeah, I'm done.
Oh, wait, this one. Yeah.
Uh, where's the where's the claymation, Rudolph?
Where's the Frosty the Snowman?
The claymation. Is it on here?
Oh, there it is.
This is absolutely legendary.
What about Die Hard?
I'm not going to watch Die Hard.
It's not I'm not going to watch.
Oh, my God.
I didn't even see it.
Ernest saves Christmas.
Mm hmm.
I've never seen any of the Die Hard movies.
None of them. Never.
Never seen Elf.
I don't know why, but like these are these are all these are all Tim Allen to me.
I don't know why it's all Tim Allen.
Every single time that I see like Santa, it's Tim Allen, but it's not.
But why is it? Why is that happening?
This is Tim Allen.
I don't know that jingle all the way is Arnold.
Yeah.
And by the way, that's a great one.
But like are these all Tim Allen?
I feel like there was a point in Tim Allen's
like career where he just was Santa Claus, but like 10 years straight.
Put that cookie down now.
All right.
The list is over.
OK, we'll move on.
This is create a Kevin McLeod royalty free songs tier list.
We're doing this one.
All right.
This one.
This is called Amazing Plan.
Like, OK, we're going to get make sure we can all hear it.
Amazing Plan.
Yeah. OK.
I'm going to put this somewhere in B for now.
All of them are bangers.
Hold on. We got to make sure we get this right.
Carefree.
There's a whole playlist here I can just open.
We're not on that one yet.
We're not on Sneaky Snitch yet.
We're looking for Carefree, Carefree.
I've used Sneaky Snitch like five times.
So look at how many songs there are.
All right. Let's see where this one goes.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, that's high.
That's incredibly high.
I've sung over this one before.
OK, good. What about Cypher?
It's a 10 hour version.
OK, I would put this one at S,
but unfortunately, it's been in like 40 percent of every mobile game I've ever
played, so it's got to come down a little bit.
I think it's, yeah, right here.
It's, it's so good, though.
It's so good.
All right.
A Darkest Child.
OK, this one's a scary one.
I like it.
I'm going to keep it in A.
Fluffing a Duck.
Where's the one that I've heard a million times?
It's going in S. What's it called?
Yeah, this I've heard this so many times.
That's up at S.
God, so many of these just are used
for when like the vlogger is like moving from like one room to the other.
Or from, OK, we're going to go do this.
And there's like a small montage or it's just in the background.
This is in the background permanently on so many channels.
I've heard this song so many fucking times.
I've used this song so many times.
Yeah. OK, what about Hitman?
Let's see, how about this one?
Hmm.
Eh, it's all right.
It's OK.
Yeah, it's all right.
I guess it could be used for some kind of action sequence, right?
This one's called a jaunty gumption.
This is glue man's fucking original entrance music.
Yep, there's the
penis music.
Kind of.
That's probably the best one so far.
All right. Local forecast.
How about that one?
Oh, this is in so many things, too.
This is in so many games and like ads.
Oh, I just like keep seeing it.
No, I can't put it in S.
I've heard it in too many things that traumatized me.
I'll put it in A.
OK, this one's called Look Busy.
This is a classic, but I don't know if it should be up all the way at S.
It's good. It's good.
But I put it above this, I think.
Yeah. OK, Meatball Parade.
I feel like I know this one.
Oh, yeah, this is S.
Without a doubt.
This is the cartoon music I played when I
streamed Overwatch back in like 2016.
Yep. OK, that's brap music.
I don't even know what that means.
All right. Marigo.
Marigo.
No, I hate this one. I hate this one.
It's not because the music's bad because I've just seen it and heard it so many
times and play it. Just I don't like it.
Monkeys spinning monkeys.
Oh, God.
I can recite this one by heart, so it has to be up here.
All right. Pixel Peeker Polka.
It's good, but it can't beat the classics for me.
Yeah. OK. Yep.
I think it belongs there.
This run amok.
I feel like this is the ultimate YouTuber one, right?
This I think this is the ultimate YouTuber song, isn't it?
I know. Oh, no, no, this is it.
This is the way this is Glooman.
This is Glooman.
Wait, no, this is this is the OK.
This is Glooman 2.
Yeah, this is Glooman second entrance music.
I actually like this one better.
And then down down.
Then it did.
I don't like that part.
That's the only part I don't like.
All right. Scheming weasel.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Does this take over fluffing a duck?
I think this is I think this is like a better version of fluffing a duck.
I think we have to change that.
Yep. OK. Sneaky Adventure.
This is in the archaeology stream, right?
Was it this incredible space program?
Dude, look at this bucket thing. Ready?
Look at this.
You see the bottom of this cup.
It's like starting to get like so wet down here that it's like losing its.
It's kind of like it's going to come out.
The bottom is going to fall out of this thing.
Yeah, look at this.
It should not be doing this.
Drink it faster. I'm slowing down as it's all right.
All right.
We already know what the sneaky snitch sounds like, but let's just put it up there.
It's not going to it's going to be lower than I think a lot of you guys think.
I don't like it.
I use this song in Otto's dog farts messing up my game.
And I hate it ever since.
What a bad video.
Jesus Christ.
OK, like I thought to record, put music on that, render it, upload it and publish it.
I don't know why.
Why would that you know what it was?
That was oh, my God, it's been like three days without a video.
I don't have anything ready.
I need to do something.
Sometimes that would happen.
Yeah, that that's the YouTuber panic mode where it's been four days.
I have to upload something that really
only happened like maybe 10 times total.
And then after like after like 2013, 2014, I did not really give a shit about that
anymore. And it was smite gameplay.
Yeah. Watch that.
Watch it. Delete it on stream.
I don't want to watch this video.
It's two minutes.
I'm only going to stomach this video for like 30 seconds, I think.
If you want to eat healthy and feel your best.
That's not my video.
All right. I'm willing to give this 30 seconds because the music
and ally has been.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my dog just farted.
I thought all this sucks.
It's horrible, dude.
I can't
shit me right now.
I can't like play the game.
Be careful. They're right here.
I can't I can't get smites.
One of those games where you can't leave.
I can't leave right now.
I have to like accept this for what happened.
It's not like I can just get up and like walk away right now.
Seriously, man, this is horrendous.
It's the whole video.
God, hold on.
I'm serious.
I hold on a second.
I'm fucking sorry.
Oh, my God.
What happened to your voice?
I aged 10 years.
Here I come.
Oh, you don't even need my help.
What do you? I got him.
Seriously. All right.
Right, go on.
Yes, shoo.
Dude, can you can you imagine if I just like
if you guys both died right there?
I'll try.
What?
No, that was miles away.
Boston wore off with age.
Yeah, it did. What?
Especially since moving to like three years ago, I was losing it a little bit,
but then it was it's almost still pops up now and then.
No, no, I just saw her.
You're dead. You are dead.
Yeah.
Fucking dog.
Oh, blame the dog for your bad.
Your dog didn't like fart in my face.
Like that would not have happened.
I didn't like poop.
No, he didn't. He's right here.
Have you like checked the floor?
No, there's no like, oh,
that like completely threw my game off.
We were doing like, oh, actually, we killed him.
But I was doing like well.
And then the dog farted in my face and it was just over.
That's the entire video.
Is it say, did you like that video?
Make sure you like like the video if you did.
Oh, I lost. Oh, what the fuck, dog?
Well, I can't believe you did that.
Please, God, upload a video.
It's funny. It's it's funny enough.
It could go up. Terrible video.
Apologize to Otto.
Did he actually fart?
You think I made it up?
I made that whole thing up for like the video?
No,
it would have been so stupid.
That was, yeah, it's called uncensored.
Back when swearing, I was concerned about Jesus Christ.
I didn't pretend it really happened.
It did. And what happened to your voice?
Well, I have a new old mic from like almost 10 years ago and I've aged 10 years.
Well, that that guy is so funny.
Where did you find this guy?
Not even watching VODs from last year.
You sound different.
I also got like an Excel, a GoXLR, too.
I remember when I changed over to the GoXLR,
everyone was like, what the fuck happened to your voice?
That was like a year and a half ago, two years ago.
Yeah, I changed like my setup.
I had a different mic and everything, so I missed the old German's voice.
Well, it's never coming back because apparently I've got like all kinds of
sinus and throat weird issues on top of my other medical problems.
I'm just I'm getting old.
I'm so I'm going to start talking like this.
Once I start talking like this, that's how you know that things are.
I'm getting a little older.
This is exactly how I'm going to sound by the time I'm like 55, I think.
So I'm just it's just going there.
All right, we'll get a wallpaper.
Let's watch that one wallpaper.
OK, let's do it.
I don't remember this one.
What is this one?
Yeah, this one's in every mobile game as well.
F, I don't think it's F.
It's just not that high.
OK, how about there it is?
What keeps happening to the Deltarune soundtrack?
I just keep deleting it.
I was wondering, I was like, where is it?
Yeah, that's not porn music.
Who likes to party to wrap it up?
Let's see.
This is climbing,
falling back, it's losing traction.
Wait, I like that little organ.
I be there you are.
There's your Kevin, your Kevin McCloud
McLeod tier list for royalty free songs.
There it is.
Claps very lots of claps.
Yeah. OK, now difficult games tier list either.
I have to rate these by impossible to like angry to.
This is going to be hard.
Some of these I haven't played.
All right. Lord of the Rings.
Fuck this game.
I would say not that I can't beat it, but it was just stupid.
OK, that's going all the way up here.
Cuphead was I got angry, but I was able to do it.
Jump King was unbearable as well.
And everyone wanted me to do the DLC.
I was like, I refuse.
I absolutely refuse to do the DLC.
I won't be able to get through it.
Ikaruga.
I I don't remember.
I think I played this for like an hour.
I don't remember.
I cheated. Yeah.
Well, OK, can't beat it to me is like I beat all these games.
But should this be OK?
So this should be on the list of like things I actually just did not play.
You played Ikaruga as a joke.
Yeah. All right. So let's put it down here.
What is this? What game is that?
I can't I can't tell. What is that?
What is it? Is it Monster Hunter?
I don't think Monster Hunter is kind of hard, but it's I thought it was fine.
This was some annoyance.
Is this I can't tell what that is.
Oh, it's a different Monster Hunter.
OK, well, I haven't played it.
What's this one?
I don't think I've ever played this one either.
That's what is it?
Mushi.
Oh, I haven't played it.
Salt and Sanctuary was was hard, but that wasn't that bad.
It was some annoyance there.
I don't I don't think I played this either.
I don't know what that is.
What is this one?
Oh, there's all these Monster Hunter, Monster Hunter 2.
No War Fortress never played it.
Spelunky.
I just like I didn't really like it.
I wasn't into it.
I'm going to should I put it?
It can't beat it.
But I played it, but I just didn't like it.
So I'm going to put that down here.
Battle.
Yeah, Riga.
I don't know what that is.
Overwhelm.
Ninja Gaiden, Ninja Gaiden, Ninja Gaiden Black.
I don't think I've ever played this.
I never played this one.
Finding of Isaac is it depends on your run, I think.
Oh, everyone's OK.
I was completely ignoring everybody saying
Deltarune because I was I thought you said it was you were saying it was on this list.
I was like, they just say it's not on this list.
Why are they saying it's a hard game?
It's like people like Deltarune, Deltarune, Deltarune.
It's like it's not even on here.
Why are people saying that?
And then I realized what was going on.
I have not played FTL.
I've not played Into the Breach.
I've not played Battletech.
I have not.
I played Enter the Gungeon for a little bit, but I didn't really play it.
I didn't really really care too much.
Hotline Miami.
This game is fucking unbelievably unbearable,
although the second one is way worse.
This one is still up here.
The Witness is that I didn't play.
That's just like the line puzzle game, right?
I didn't play it.
Mario the Lost Levels are they're pretty bad, but not really.
Hades was challenging, but it was still like doable.
Hades is probably now Cuphead's probably more annoying.
Bloodborne is up here too, but I don't think it was.
I wouldn't say Bloodborne is it's up there pretty high.
Some of those bosses were horrible.
This is literally an uncompletable video game.
You cannot beat this without cheats.
It's it's not possible to beat this without like a game genie.
Louder.
I'll give you 10 percent louder.
What else we got?
Stuntman. Why is this on here?
Did you make this list specifically for me?
If this wait, why Stuntman Ignition on here?
I was like pissed at this game, but this is not considered a hard game.
Is it? Is it?
I don't know. What an egomaniac.
All right.
What is this?
Drifter or played it.
I think Celeste was balanced.
I don't think I got too annoyed with Celeste.
Noida, on the other hand, I could I just can't fucking do it.
I cannot fucking do it.
Super Meat Boy was bad, but it was possible.
I don't think it was that high up, though.
Original Castlevania was annoying.
But like, I'm not going to who's going to play that right now?
Like, it's like, oh, OK, like Castlevania, the original one.
Like, yeah, it's I was hard back then.
But I can compare to like Jump King.
It's like kind of two different.
I don't know what this is. I didn't play it.
The original Dark Souls.
What's harder, Bloodborne or Dark Souls?
I feel like they're hard for different reasons.
The original Dark Souls is probably more annoying.
Yeah, Super Meat Boy is not really hard.
It just takes memorization.
You just have to memorize levels,
which you could say the same thing about Dark Souls bosses, but not really.
Because Dark Souls bosses, unlike Super Meat Boy,
they have a range of attacks that they will do,
but you don't know which attack they're going to do.
In Super Meat Boy, you know the levels are just the same.
You just have to memorize the level.
So these are probably that's probably a good spot.
Isaac,
Isaac can be really annoying sometimes, but Demon's Souls was probably harder
than just like the world tendency shit made this game so fucking hard sometimes.
Hard or frustrating?
I feel like the first few worlds,
like the first two or three worlds in Demon's Souls were not that hard.
That's still annoying.
Desert bus doesn't I mean, why even there's no reason to do that.
I have not played any of the Devil May Cry games.
I I got through some of Hollow Knight on stream,
but people are mad that I never went back to it.
But just that's the way it is.
Surge.
We have a lot of new viewers.
I was I said a lot of mean things about the surge.
Do you know those?
I was streaming the surge to like 600 viewers or something like it was.
I had like 500 viewers at the time, but like less than a thousand at the time.
Right.
That was very beginning of my like Twitch life.
Holy fuck.
I hated that whole thing.
I was infuriated by that whole experience.
You said it was literally the worst video game ever made.
It's a good game.
You're just a literal baby.
Does anybody have like a clip from that stream?
Any of you guys, some of you like lore masters
that have like a like a saved clip of me being like a psycho on that stream?
Somebody does.
OK, well, I'm just going to I'm going to put it down here because I played it
for like maybe an hour and a half.
Just watch the VOD.
OK, hold on.
I'm going to let's see.
Let's get it.
It's definitely on the archive.
The surge.
Yeah. OK, this is from like five years ago.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
OK, you guys ready to see what my thought?
Where should I put the surge on this tier list?
We're going to skip through when I'm going to watch the whole thing.
Hey, how long did I scream this for?
I wonder. We'll find out.
So this is the surge.
An hour and 55 minutes.
Holy shit.
And the first 10 to 20 minutes is absolutely me like introduction.
And the last probably 40 minutes is doing the old bit readings, right?
I played this for probably an hour.
How excited do I sound, you think?
Who, who, who fucking who cry, crying.
I'm tears are streaming down my face, angry.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, this is one of those plant, the trees.
What is what it's going?
What does that make that clicking sound?
Isn't when they turned me into Darth Vader.
I was just going to say that in this part.
I was just going to say that I was just going to say that
is where I practice punching things.
Right.
All right, here we go.
How much do I hate it?
Press circle to heal.
Use your vital injection.
That's that's quick.
Our three is lock on.
Sure.
Our one is horizontal.
Our two is vertical.
OK, they can be going to be strung together.
OK.
Yeah.
Whoever made this game, fuck you.
Shit.
Um, I don't actually I don't actually mean that, by the way.
I was just like frustrated at the game.
Who made this game?
Fuck you. Dark Souls is way better.
Oh, my God, I'm such a dick.
What the hell?
What's wrong?
No, I'm this is not who I am.
Yeah, delete this, delete this from deleted.
Is he writing this right now?
Rhonic in a game like fucking stuff.
Why is there time based retrieval?
That's fucking moronic in a game like this.
All right.
I'm not throwing in the towel yet.
Not yet. Not yet.
Not yet. Toxic.
How much does this block?
OK, I gotta be very, very real with everybody here.
So this been a lot of times I've played a game
and on stream, I never I never want to like just like talk shit about like a game
company because you don't know. Right.
Like it just the game might not be for you or like maybe it's like it's better
later or maybe you just like have to learn if it's like it's a learning curve.
I always hate like talking shit on stream because like I
would I try to condense my rage to not get that far.
So when you hear me do that, when you ever hear me do that on this
broadcast, I it's I've been holding it in and I just have to fucking say something.
I've hit the boiling point at that point.
And sometimes it happens really quickly and sometimes it happens over an hour.
But I always try to like bottle it because I don't want to like obviously be
like a dick or anything, but like, holy shit, listen to this guy.
Stream looks like ass, too, by the way.
They stream it like 480p, but four years ago, five years ago.
Was it 720? It was probably 720.
While you can.
No, it's probably a low bit rate, though.
My bit rate that I'm doing is probably doubled since like 2015, 2016.
All right.
And wait, this guy might kill me.
Oh, I got hit.
Immediate anger.
Apparently, I didn't have invincibility.
Apparently, apparently, apparently.
And he's going to go, OK.
See, apparently means it's not my fault
that I got hit because, like, apparently you get hit if you do that.
Like, I'm it's not my fault, right?
It's this clip here.
Well, I mean, where is that in the time stamp of the stream?
I need a new weapon or something.
I'm literally in the stream right now.
No.
Oh, awful.
This game is fucking terrible, like a zero out of fucking 10.
It's awful.
Don't fucking buy this game.
Oh, my God. Dark Souls game.
Go play Dark Souls. This game sucks asshole.
I can't. This is awful.
This is awful. I would rather use like I would rather you.
No, I'm not going to say it because that's like lewd and fucked up.
What?
I was about to say something like fucked up right there.
So glad I didn't watch the rest of it.
I'm say it. Say it.
What am I? Don't say it. I don't know what he's going to say.
This game is just fucking bad.
How did this game get an eight?
Who gave this game an eight?
No, don't. Don't.
This is a fucking six game at best.
Maybe a five.
It's probably fine.
I'm just such a fucking over dramatic asshole.
I can't. What the fuck is even happening with this guy?
Oh, I don't know.
I was like, no, I'm speechless.
I'm just speechless.
We want all German.
No, I literally said fuck Capcom like six weeks ago.
What are you talking about?
He never left.
It's under it's try harder.
Oh, I'm almost there.
Somehow.
No, I don't want to hear it.
Two health bars.
First game of two thousand.
I don't want to hear it.
What if I don't want to hear it, though?
I fucking hate this game.
I hate this game.
I think that honestly, this is the first game of 2017 that I fucking despise.
I fucking hate this game.
This must have been so miserable to watch live.
This is the first game of 2017 that I fucking hate.
Oh, listen to that. Fuck.
That's not like, oh, I fucking hate this.
That's I fucking.
I fucking hate this.
Wow.
If you want to add a list, make a list.
This is the first one.
No, I didn't.
Outlast 2 was like I wasn't a wasn't a huge fan of it, but it was, you know,
it was it was all right. I didn't mind it.
It was OK.
Outlast 2 was like,
it wasn't really like it was didn't feel like I said a lot of swears and stuff.
But, you know, what?
What are you talking about?
I hate this game.
I didn't say any squares funny in some places.
It was like fun.
Well, I don't think it was as good as the first game, but I didn't.
Like I enjoyed it.
OK, so when I say this thing, I give it like a stamp of recommended.
If you like those games, right?
But for me, for me, for at least this year,
this is the first true game sucks like for me.
This was the first year that I watched the screen.
You are more than welcome to enjoy this game.
It's one fifty three.
You bought it. I hope you love it.
Real boss. That was the asylum demon.
What? Oh, my God.
It's just this is like 30 straight minutes.
Thank you for the hundred dollars.
Thank you.
Thanks for the hundred dollars.
Like, what the hell? What is going on in this video?
Where is it? One fifty three lift in the boss room stops.
Channel switched microphone.
Hey, you here?
Am I talking to I am here?
OK, I was told that you needed saving.
This is the worst game I've ever played.
Really is that the first one you turn you up first to Alex.
You sound very quiet to me.
I'm very quiet.
Yeah. Hold on, turn me up.
I am what I want to go like rant to six decibels.
Well, did I like call one of my friends
to like I was so upset that I had to like rant at him?
Why? Why would I want to stream this?
No, I got to turn again.
I got to turn you down.
Oh, I'm a loud boy.
I turned him way too far down.
You shouldn't. Why are people saying there's an echo?
I'm going to mute my mic.
When does this quote happen?
Friday the 14th.
Where's this quote? You guys you're linking me wrong stuff.
One forty three.
Down on your fucking hands.
One forty four.
You guys, you guys are saying random numbers.
What?
I'm done. I'm done playing.
This is a fun game. Italics, where are you?
Italics, where are you? Are you here?
I tried to warn you. I played for an hour and refunded.
Italics, where are you?
You made the surge on stream.
Just watch the clip.
Why are you referencing Bible verses?
What are you talking about?
Fuck this game. I don't even care if I won.
And I feel like good about winning.
No, I don't. I don't.
It was like the tutorial boss.
That was the asylum demon.
Why? I don't care.
This game doesn't suck.
I'm sorry for saying that.
If you're like a developer and you're watching this game,
try fucking harder next time.
Oh, my God.
OK, so I'm going to say that it should probably
on the on the tier list, the surge should probably be on a game that I couldn't beat.
I can't beat.
Whoo.
OK, you know, like, you know, OK, like
I have to get out of here.
I'm not allowed on here.
All right. Oh, this is F zero.
I never played F zero.
Oh, I did.
I hated Neo as well, didn't I?
I didn't I talk a bunch of shit about this game too?
No,
I did.
I remember being like this fucking game, like fucking sucks.
No, no, I couldn't do it.
No, to be fair, I was like shit faced when I played this game, wasn't I?
No, no, we're moving on.
What is this one?
I remember people saying, hey, you should go play Neo 2.
I don't think so.
I don't think that's going to happen.
No, I've not seen it.
I'm not looking at it.
I'm going to go pee. I'm peeing.
I'm not even here. I'm leaving.
I got to pee.
Yeah, but I've heard me say it.
You can cut that shit. No, don't.
You don't have to.
I'm certain of it.
I don't know.
OK, 2017 in Germany was mean.
I don't think so.
Have I gotten less mean?
Was I mean? Maybe I was.
No, I wasn't.
I well.
All right, let's finish this.
And then I'm going to move on from Tierless.
I want to play a couple of these little games.
I want to I want to play some of these little like browser games.
That's not supposed to still be on.
Oh, but the Deltarune soundtrack back on, please.
Yep.
Toby Fox is the Mozart of fucking like this generation.
All right.
Over here. All right.
Deltarune OST is on again.
Odd hand, I know people really want me to play this, but I just didn't.
I kept. No, don't put me another one.
I did it again.
I talk about how much this game sucks and how it's fucking terrible.
Is this is it in this clip?
I just think I'm when I play hard games, I just get really, really mad.
I just get things just piss me off.
I don't know why. Like, I just get so infuriated.
Requested this game a million times.
Are you here?
The only reason why I'm doing a fighting game in the arcade.
Stinger.
What is it? What is that?
What button is that supposed to be?
Pretty good DDT.
He's not here.
He's not even here.
He's going to shit his pants when he realizes he missed this stream.
But I hope the guy is here.
That is requested this game a million times.
There's not any more clips of me talking about how like, oh, yeah, there is.
These are every game on this list.
Don't you understand, guys?
Every single game on this list, there is a whole vod of me talking about how much
the game is a piece of shit and how I fucking hate it.
And it's like the worst game I've ever played.
Everyone on this list.
That was really high, though.
I didn't beat this one.
I did not beat getting over it.
Show the hit and run meltdown clip.
It's the whole broadcast.
It's the entire broadcast.
It's like that was like a 12 hour stream.
After the first 45 minutes, it's all it was.
I probably, you know, that stream,
Simpsons Hit and Run, that one day of streaming Simpsons Hit and Run,
I believe was the equivalent of me smoking five to six thousand packs of cigarettes.
That's like the amount of damage it did to my life.
That's the amount of damage it did to my brain.
Like, if I went to get like a chest x-ray, they'd be like, what happened?
Do you smoke?
Do you smoke cigarettes?
It looks like you've been a smoker for a long time.
I'd be like, no, I haven't smoked ever in my whole life.
Oh, well, what happened then?
Well, you know, a few of these fucking games that are hard games like Simpsons
Hit and Run, like I would have damage that you could see on like an x-ray.
Anyways, I didn't play this.
Oh, there's a clip in that one, too,
when I talk about how stupid the devs are.
Oh, this is like a horrible epiphany I'm having.
This is like I'm being I'm being shown all of my demons at once.
He's sweating. Yeah, it's fucking hot.
Yeah, there's a part where I'm in the steam room and I'm like,
this is the worst game I've ever played, like all the devs are fucking morons.
Like I am being shown all of my bullshit right now.
I mean, Hotline Miami 2 was so unbearable.
I would put it here.
But at least I beat it.
Was that worse than Hit Simpsons?
Probably not.
I haven't played Ghouls and Ghosts.
My summer car.
I mean, I played it, but I thought it wasn't like hard or anything, was it?
Don't Starve didn't really play it, didn't play Boshi, didn't play Spelunky.
I'm just going to pick up things that I played.
This game was annoying, but at least I beat it.
Play Dead Cells.
All Mario. Oh, no, don't say that.
I was going to say that all Mario carts.
No, no, I'm this is 2021 not toxic.
I am not toxic.
I am going to give everybody the benefit of the doubt and I'm not going to say
anything and I was going to tell you that after the let's say since they OK,
since Nintendo started coming up with consoles that you shook around a controller,
they've been awful. Don't hurt me, please don't hurt me.
OK, your Thanksgiving tier list was awful, but this is a redemption.
Dark Souls 2 is it's kind of I don't know if it was harder than all these,
but it was it was a lot of stuff going on and I wasn't a big fan of Dark Souls 2.
Darkest Dungeon was really annoying, but it was still doable.
Although now I never beat it.
I actually did not beat the Darkest Dungeon.
I did not. I didn't play this.
We play this and played and played and played and not played.
Not not not not not not not not.
No,
no comment.
Oh,
hmm.
Dark Souls 3 is up here somewhere.
Oh, boy, this one was bad.
Did I beat I beat Lifeline, though I beat it.
Punch out.
Mario Tennis Aces.
I'm going to want to link the clip where
I talk about what I'm talking shit to the kid like I'm making fun of a fake child.
Damn, I really was fucked up.
Holy shit.
I'm like, look at these are all these things were from like 2016 to like 2018,
like 2019, I was mean and rude to people.
I still am. Well, am I?
No, I'm not.
This is the one, right?
No, I know. I'm fine.
Fine.
But I hope the guy is here.
This is the clip. I think it is.
Good job, Nicholas.
Good luck in the first grade next week.
Damn it, man.
Now, this is not the clip.
This is not the right. I mean, that's mean.
Good job, Nicholas.
I mean, that was kind of rude, but I
it was like I said a lot more awful things, I think, on this one.
You got destroyed by a first grader.
All right. I'm playing it.
I'm done with Tierless. I'm done with Tierless.
It's too I don't like this.
I'm done. Portal 2 was a lot of fun.
It was balanced.
Which Ninja Turtles game is this?
Because they were they were always really fun, balanced.
Buster Truck never played it.
Chilly Time is actually uncompletable, so that's fine.
There you go.
Now we're going to play
a little browser game.
There's a couple here.
Let's do this one, but find the U.S.
States with no outline.
This is you know what?
I've said to myself I probably shouldn't
do this because I don't think I can do it.
I did not practice.
I promise.
I really don't think I can do this.
I don't think it's possible.
North Carolina, Vermont.
That's what I clicked. I just clicked right there.
What the fuck was that?
Arkansas.
I'm sorry.
Iowa is like here.
Fuck. I'm like I get every time I think
of where a state is, it's one inch to the right of where I'm going to click.
Idaho, Vermont, Mississippi is right here somewhere.
Where is it? Yep.
New Mexico.
That's Arizona.
I get Arizona here.
Tennessee.
Tennessee is like here.
Tennessee is like right here.
Fuck. I'm so close.
Arizona, New York, Wisconsin.
Wisconsin is like right here somewhere.
Fuck you.
Stop restarting.
Oh, I thought I had to restart.
I do have to restart.
I mean, stop restarting.
I have to replay the quiz.
I have to replay it.
Montana is like here.
Minnesota is here.
It's like right here.
No, it's like, yeah, like right here.
Where is it? It's like right here.
Yep. Alaska.
Mexico. Don't fuck it up.
Nebraska, Texas, Oklahoma.
God, like all these states right here are just one gigantic like Pangea of the same
state for me. Alabama is this one.
It's Florida, Georgia, Mississippi, Alabama.
Fuck. It's Florida, Alabama, Tennessee.
I.
Is it going to be so hard?
You need to get the outline first.
Missouri is here.
No, it's not like here.
No, this is like North Dakota, South Dakota.
Missouri is like here.
Oh, my God.
I don't know. Oh, no.
Iowa. It's like here.
They're all there.
Don't don't get mad.
Maryland.
Jesus, I don't know.
They're such small states over here.
Like right here.
Oh, yo.
Ohio is here.
Oh, Ohio, Mississippi, New Jersey here.
What? That's Delaware.
This is in that Delaware.
They're the same shape.
Maryland here.
Wait, I don't remember.
There it is. Georgia here.
Oh, fuck off with this.
Maryland here.
Oh, I just don't remember.
It's like what a weird shape.
I know it's like here, but this that's such an odd shape.
It's such a small, weird shape.
Fuck the founding father, Rhode Island.
Like it's so tiny over here.
How I could miss click so easily.
Oklahoma.
Texas is right here. Oklahoma.
That's what I just clicked.
It should be at least Tennessee.
Oh, my God.
I'm never going to get it.
I don't think I'll ever be like I'm never going to be able to do this.
Wyoming is here.
Oh, man, that's no, that's I don't know.
Georgia, Oregon, New Jersey, Nebraska was here.
Even when it shows me, guys, it doesn't matter because it's without the outlines.
I don't I don't know what you can cycle.
Holy shit, I did not know that.
Tennessee.
Holy shit. All right. All right.
Right. Right. Arizona, Florida.
That makes it so much easier.
Delaware. Nope. North Carolina.
Nope. Iowa. Nope.
Pennsylvania is right here.
California. That's not what do you mean not California?
That's what I just clicked.
I just clicked right here.
That's the easiest state in the country.
What I clicked right here.
Medicaid right there.
Pennsylvania.
I don't know. I don't know.
Montana. I don't remember.
California.
Jesus. Washington.
South Dakota would be like here, but I don't know.
I need more info.
New Hampshire, New York.
I don't know. I need more info.
North Dakota is right here.
No, it's not. What's right there?
I don't know. Florida, Texas, West Virginia.
This is right here somewhere.
Illinois is right here.
I don't know. Vermont.
Idaho is here.
That's like what I'm clicking.
Like I'm literally hands up.
How is it? What are you talking about?
Colorado is right here.
This is Utah. Oops.
Georgia is here.
Iowa, Arizona.
OK, slow down.
Just slow down. I can get it.
Just have to start filling it in.
North Dakota is right here.
I'm not going to do that. I don't have that info yet.
Virginia. They're all over here.
Virginia is literally right here, but I'm not going to click it.
Ohio is right here.
Pennsylvania right here.
Florida, Kentucky, Alabama.
Delaware is like right.
I don't remember. New York in Nebraska.
Vermont. Maryland was.
That's New Jersey. Maryland.
I fucking hate this game.
Like, that's what I'm clicking on.
Like, I clicked right there.
I'm just going to go. It's right underneath Pennsylvania.
I'm going to set up this Maryland.
There it is.
I fucking hate the state.
But what is this like?
It's all the states should be equal cubes across the whole country.
Equal cubes, just cubes, cube Andy.
I've got to get this right. It's right.
I'm going to get this, I swear to God.
Maryland, one, two.
Oh, my God.
Where is this fucking ghost of a state that I keep missing somehow?
I'm just not going to fill it into the very end because, like, obviously,
I can't do it. New Jersey, Kentucky, Tennessee, Georgia.
I almost clicked on Texas, Massachusetts.
Let's just I got to slow down Idaho.
Don't click it. I refuse.
Fuck out of here. Michigan is this one, right?
No, that's the cheese one.
Wisconsin, they're both right here.
They both literally Michigan and Wisconsin is here.
Delaware, I don't remember which one is the one that's right.
Which one's here? Pennsylvania.
All right. Connecticut.
Don't miss click. It's right there.
Hawaii, Nevada, Texas, Ohio.
Don't do Colorado yet, even though I know it's right here.
OK, we're good.
Rhode Island.
Thank you. Utah, Washington.
We have the whole West Coast done.
North Dakota.
No, it's this is Illinois right here.
Indiana, Indiana, Illinois, South Carolina, Florida, Maine, Ohio, Illinois, Illinois.
What's right next to Ohio?
Is it Illinois or is it Indiana?
I think it's Illinois.
I don't remember. Delaware is right there.
OK, Oklahoma is right above Texas, right? Right?
Yeah. Louisiana is right here.
Please. Yes, North Carolina.
All right. Is that Virginia or is that North Carolina?
Because it's North Carolina, South Carolina, Virginia.
I think that's Virginia and North Carolina is right here.
Colorado, Kentucky is like here or here.
And I see is right above Georgia.
I think it borders Georgia, Ohio, Illinois.
I clicked that fucking thing.
Oh, I missed it.
All right. All right. We're good. We're good.
We're good. Nevada, Utah, Washington.
I don't know. South Carolina.
I don't know. Florida, Wisconsin, Oregon, New Hampshire, Delaware.
Don't. Yeah. Delaware is this little one right here.
Idaho. Wait. Yes.
Indiana. Gosh.
Louisiana, New York, Vermont, Kansas.
I don't remember. Virginia.
There's just such a it's such a bunch of weird shapes over here.
You hate the Midwest.
I just never I there's no I've never been there.
Well, I mean, that's hold on.
That's not true.
Mississippi is I don't know.
I believe this is Wyoming, Wyoming or these are Wyoming, Wyoming and Montana.
And I don't know which one.
All right. I got it.
North Dakota. It's like right here, but I don't know what the borders.
It's constant is right here.
All right. I got that.
South Dakota is above Oklahoma.
Iowa is like here.
Kentucky is here.
That's Kentucky.
All right. Hold on.
And this is like here, right?
We're here in your shit.
And that's this is West Virginia.
I know this is Mississippi or Alabama.
I just don't remember going a friend.
No, I'm going for it.
If I get it wrong, I'm just going to skip.
I don't even care.
So North Carolina, South Carolina.
Yep. West Virginia.
OK, we're getting there.
Let me finish the right side here.
North Carolina is here.
Virginia here.
We're getting there. Almost there.
Now it's just all these things that I have no goddamn idea.
Alabama, Mississippi, Alabama or Alabama, Mississippi.
North Dakota is north.
Yeah, I know.
But I don't know exactly where the borders are because like Wyoming is huge.
Montana is huge, aren't they?
It's like here.
I got it. OK.
So what is next to North Dakota?
What is this?
What the hell is this place?
Missouri. That's Missouri.
How do I make it to Europe?
OK, this is Neural Blender.
Jeremiah has a fun day at the beach.
He makes a sand castle.
How does this work?
In progress, Neural Blender can be safe, unsafe for work sometimes.
Oh, shit.
Well, let's go ahead and fucking make sure I don't show that.
That it takes a little bit to make it right.
How about this one?
What about the video game sound effects quiz?
See if I can get this right.
Go like this, make it a little bit bigger and get more.
OK, so I just input what I think it is.
OK, well, I'll try.
Number one is
that hurt my head.
But that is like Mario input answer like Mario Jump.
Does that have to be like Super Mario?
OK, good.
It's World of Warcraft.
That is the you completed a quest sound.
World of Warcraft.
Superhot.
That was pretty easy.
That's Half Life.
Thank you.
Resident Evil 4.
I only know that because I just I do that voice like every week.
What was that?
Put it in emote only mode.
Emote only, emote only, emote only.
I don't want to see it.
I don't know.
Die, monster.
You don't belong in this world.
What the hell is this?
I don't know.
Hail to the king, baby.
Duke Nukem.
It's not Duke Nukem.
Yes, it is.
Duke. What is it?
How do I spell it? Duke Nukem, Nukem, Nukem.
Am I spelling it wrong?
Hail to the king, baby.
It's Duke Nukem.
How do I spell this?
Is it not? It's not Duke Nukem.
Duke Nukem.
I don't know.
That's, um, what is this?
Tony Hawk. It's Tony Hawk.
That's Tony Hawk's Pro Skater.
What?
That's when you do like a trick.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Tony Hawk.
It has to be completely spelled accurately.
That's the Legend of Zelda, the Ocarina of Time.
Thank you.
Final Fantasy X. Dark Souls.
That's the new area.
You found a new area in Dark Souls where like you just you resurrected.
How do you find it? Come on.
Street Fighter 2.
What is that?
I know what it is, but I don't look at you, Hacker.
A pathetic creature of meat and bone.
System Shock 2.
My God, I hear what is this one?
This is a new day on a game.
This is a new day.
You started a new day.
But what game is this a new day of?
Yeah, I'll come back to it.
It's Mario Super.
Do I have to get the whole thing?
Super Mario World 2, Yoshi's Island.
Oh, I already got it.
OK, then, then, then, then, then, then.
Excite Excite a bike.
How do I say it? Excite a bike, excite bike, excite a bike, excite bike.
That's right, though, isn't it?
Excite bike.
I don't think I got it.
Maybe it's not right.
Sonic the Hedgehog rings been removed.
How come Sonic the Hedgehog doesn't need to be spelled out for the other ones to do?
Minecraft, Smash Brothers.
Oh, no, but they're not about to rob it.
It was a good idea to sell a whole lot of food.
Tear him up.
Oh, what a day.
I didn't mean to let it burn and tear it up.
Big Doug.
No,
Pac-Man, what am I talking about?
It's my favorite video game character ever.
I have no idea.
Mario Kart.
Mario Kart Wii.
I don't know.
Jason, Jason, Jason, Jason.
Oh, it's Papers, Please.
I need to move my my dumb ass out of the way so you can see them.
OK, so this is Papers, Please.
The reloading sounds familiar.
i don't know what from though present evil you must construct additional pylons starcraft
it's uh i don't
earthbound that's not earthbound no ah shit here we go again gta mario tennis mario party
what that's waluigi what's he doing i don't know it's it's a party game it's mario golf
it's mario golf all right what other games is waluigi in he's only in the fucking party games
what other games is he in mario golf mario tennis mario party mario kart he's not in
any of the video games waluigi is only in those party games but there's mario baseball mario
strikers what i everyone's saying not like this i don't know i don't know that motherfucker's
never had his own game goose untitled goose game shit this is radio from oh i know it i know it
i don't know but i do i don't know do a barrel roll oh oh star star fox what have i got crash
brandacoup it's like hitting the back button in a game it's like a resident evil type cut type
game might be resident evil 3 maybe resident evil see if i get it no what is it it's like
one of those kinds of games bale the gates of sesharon have been closed for eons and you shall
not reach them now ready to combat uh duck hunt a classic come on for rapper the rapper rapper
how do you spell it a rap uh the rapper locked isaac animal crossing what the hell was that
i don't know i have no idea play of the game oh my god overwatch metal gear solid
what the hell is that it's mario it's some kind of mario game i don't know which one though
what's going on with my hair what happened
huh could be anything like toy story aliens i don't know
doesn't somebody go like oh like goofy it falls down
something like that right what is it let's go back up here i don't know i don't know die monster you
don't belong in this world i have absolutely no silent hill maybe
sound hill 2 no it's not silent hill just sounds like the guy from silent hill 2
this is a heartbeat maybe i don't know hail to the king baby how is this not duke nukem somebody
explain that to me duke nuke dash um duke nukem how this is duke nukem duke nuke um how do you
spell it this is duke nukem i don't know how am i getting this so wrong hail to the king baby
duke nukem it's not like no it's a k duke nukem nukem nukem nukem nukem nukem no it's duke nukem
wait is there hyphen in here what hail to the king baby duke nukem duke duke is it one word
no spaces or anything is it an underscore i think it's an underscore hail to the king baby
why are you guys doing Doritos hail to the king baby i don't get it i don't know why i don't know
what that i can't spell it this is like a rail gun wake what was the unreal unreal tournament
why are you guys doing all the Doritos stuff i just thought i had it in my head i just had it
it's here's i'm here's my magic i had it got it this is another one that
pokemon
i'm never gonna get this i will never get this one
probably not gonna get that one either or that one this team fortress no i was thinking like
the sniper rifle oh that's call of duty cs go counter strike yes there it is it's the same
sounds they use the source engine same goddamn sounds professor professor leighton what
that's professor leighton it's a raid oh shit who raided we got a raid can't see it from here
hold on who raided we're in emote only mode right now you're liars nobody raided that there's no
raid you guys are lying there's no braid anyways what we're doing right that's like professor
leighton and all the professor leighton games i have no idea what there there's a colon and then
it's like a bunch of word soup it could be a professor leighton and the ungodly kitty from
london like i have no idea what the fuck these names are professor leighton and the magical
grandfather clock i don't i should be able to get this one you guys keep saying raid i don't see
any raids why are you saying raid oh you're just a spoiler thank you i appreciate it
i don't understand what could this possibly be mario golf mario tennis mario soccer mar
let me spell it out mario super star sluggers or something right all right maybe it's mario
party like i have to put a number i don't know mario party mario pizza that's not a game i don't
know what i'm thinking that mario song singing um it's that it's waluigi but i don't have any
idea he's not in any other games is he this is the combine this is half life it's not the combine
it's something like that i don't know i can't get it this is like you're in the menu you're in like
and you're like i don't know what menu it is though
like bowser or is this um we just mentioned that's like a mario enemy mario not 64
mario sunshine mario odyssey it's like bowser he comes over and he's like
where was
start start that's mario party wow no that's pikmin no i think it's gotta be a guy doing that
it's not even like a sound effect from a game
animal crossing i feel like it might be animal crossing
I don't know.
This one, what is it?
It's like, it's that, it's something.
It goes like, whoa, whoa, right, oh my God, what is it?
Somebody over this sound makes like a high pitched sound effect.
It's like, whaaat?
It's something going, what is it though?
It's like a star or like a collectible and it blows up.
What is it?
It shows up on the screen, boom, you collected it.
Maybe this is Mario Odyssey, fuck do you spell Odyssey, Mario Galaxy, Mario Sunshine, Mario
60, no, Mario 64 goes da da da da, here we go.
Die monster, you don't belong in this world.
House of the Dead?
I feel like it could be House of the Dead, but it's not.
Die monster, you don't belong in this world.
Hail to the king, baby.
Doesn't make any sense that this is not Duke Nukem.
There's nobody else that is, that's Duke Nukem talking.
Shhh.
Jason!
Sounds like a clip from a movie.
Let's put the cheese, hold on, what does it say?
What's the cheese?
Doritos chip, cheesy Doritos, Doritos, corn chip, chip.
Hail to the king, baby.
Cheesy chip, Duke Cheesem, Duke Cheesem, cheesy, Cheesem.
Duke Cheesem is I think like a McDonald's Play Plays character.
Cheez it?
I don't know, what are you trying to say?
Duke Cheez it, Duke, Duke Nukem?
I don't know what you're trying to convey to me, I don't know, I can't figure it out.
I have no idea.
I think I'm going to have to reveal.
This is like Galaga or, it's an old game, like an old Atari game.
It's like an old Atari game shooting sound.
Alright, alright, it's time to reveal.
It's time to reveal.
I don't think I can get any more.
Alright, here we go, I don't know, reveal.
Okay.
Enter the Gungeon, I would not have been able to get that shit.
The Elder Scrolls 3 Morrowind, nope.
Castlevania, Symphony of the Night, I thought it was Silent Hill, I didn't put 3D in front
of it.
I thought I was losing my mind.
I was like, who else is this supposed to be?
Alien Isolation, eh, that's too specific, I don't think I would have got it.
Max Payne, oh, the slow mo dive, alright, uh, okay, what's Fortnite?
What did I say I thought this was?
So what's the Dorito, what's the Dorito shit?
Oh, 3D Doritos, okay, well thanks for the help.
Age of Empires 2, yeah.
Heavy Rain, Metroid, right, right, I knew it was an old game.
What is Luigi, which one is this one?
Didn't I write Luigi's Mansion?
Wait, that's not Waluigi, I thought that was Waluigi winning a game of Mario Tennis.
Where did I write Luigi's Mansion?
I wrote Luigi's Mansion for one of these and I got it wrong.
Oh, that's when you activate the VATS, right, I had played no Rocket League ever, so what's
this one, Silent Hill 2?
You're in the menu, Halo, I thought this was like Bowser, Quake, no, Oddworld, right, when
you can kind of communicate, I forgot, I want to see 7, oh, it's a Chocobo, Puppet, Puppet,
do you know why I said that sound is somebody going, oh, it's because that's me making that
noise, playing it, when I streamed it, I just fucking screamed and made weird sounds whenever
I would die, so stupid, I would not have gotten that, that was cool, I liked that, that was
fun, that was fun, okay, oh, I need to check on this neural network thing, make sure it's
not like somebody's asshole or something, hold on, give me one second, I don't know
if this is a dick or not, I don't know, it's hard to tell, this is so funny, this could
be like a dick, I don't, is this like a dick, okay, it might be, I don't know, I don't know,
I'm going to clip, I'm going to, hold on, let me make sure I can clip, cut this out,
I don't know what that's supposed to be, but it's hard to tell, but this image is so funny
hold on, let me like, I gotta zoom in, I'll cut the bottom part off, give me a sec, how
come I can't see it, wait, I gotta go back to here, hold on a sec, there we go, alright,
if I go like this, okay, this is, Jerma has a fun day at the beach, he makes a sand castle,
and I'm not going to scroll down more, tweet it, I don't know what that could be, but that's
a, what is on my head, alright, I'm going to put, I'll put another one in, what should
the prompt be for this next one, how about, Jerma enjoys his favorite cheeseburger restaurant,
Jerma enjoys his favorite cheeseburger restaurant, alright, it is in progress, wait, it's like
already, it's literally already done, oh no it's not, okay, now, what's the next thing
we want to do, what is this, okay, hold on, first I need to know what Fortnite scene I
am, we'll do that, keep in mind I've never played Fortnite, I have no time in the game
at all, zero, so, I'm going to find out what Fortnite skin I am, move the cam back to
where it was too, okay, put face cam and toons back on, yeah, I will, what should we do for
toons, what do you think, I did this one already, I did, no I didn't, alright, stardew, OST,
great game, maybe I did, why did that, put on, I did, I didn't, I don't remember, I really
don't, put on Fortnite music, alright, I'll put on Fortnite OST, Fortnite complete soundtrack,
alright, here we go, what Fortnite skin are you, you're playing battle royale squad mode and are
flying high over the map in the bus, do you leap up because I have no fear, just wait a bit longer
there's no rush, stay in the battle bus as I have snacks, or, I don't know, what would you do, I'm
gonna say, I don't know, what would you do, is this DMCA, what, it would be, I don't know,
what would you do because I don't play this game, you go out to buy a new jumper, which color code
do you favor, like purple, yellow and green, all the color, different shades of blue, it would be
blue, what is your favorite holiday of the year, Halloween, summer, Easter, Christmas,
your holiday is probably summer, my favorite holiday, this is so cute, okay, it's either
I'm gonna say Christmas, what is your favorite film genre, horror, comedy, animation, or action,
I don't know, none, how about horror, animation, yeah, animation, which type of music are you most
likely to listen to, any heavy metal band, dance, classical, or pop, out of everything on this list
probably pop, or is it I'm reverse aging, what, you're playing Fortnite and your teammate comes
under attack, okay, do everything you can to help your teammate, get into a flap, I don't know,
that's lingo for something, I don't know what that means, um, distract your enemies by pretending
to be a big jelly baby, I would help my teammate, which pet would you most like to have, a crow,
anything but a chimpanzee, let's go with a cat, why is it a big chicken, an old dog with a kind
face, what would you most like to eat, I have no time to eat on the battlefield, but might have
some crisps, this person is English, a slice of cake, vegetable fingers, and some baked beans,
I'd love a burger right now, yeah, I thought underneath this was an ad for like dental implants,
you would get those, I honestly thought this was what this was, I'd like a burger actually,
which item of clothing do you prefer to wear, a black hoodie or something, a suit and bow tie,
a cape, um, probably different hats, yeah, all right, finally, you're trapped under this desert
island, what one item would you take with you, a helicopter, yes, your, is your ripply, we're not
sure why, but when we see this Fortnite scheme, we want a bowl of jelly or something, that was
very cute, all right, let me just check on the neural network thing, it's still in progress,
it's taking a while, it's trying to figure out what to do, and I'm gonna do the thing I do every
time I do this, I hopefully doesn't take this, it takes between 10 minutes and 15 minutes,
we're just, we're just gonna do another fucking IQ test, like I mean, I'm gonna do this, I'm not
really ready, I haven't like eaten any protein today or anything, so I'm telling you right now,
this is probably gonna be very inaccurate, we take an IQ test every time, just to make sure that I'm
still above at least like 60 IQ, who knows, here we go again, begin assessment, the section you will
be given a word, and I don't want to listen to this music, it's fucking distracting me, in this
section, you'll be given a word and asked to select from a list of other words, which mean the same
thing, it'll be 10 answers for each question, and three to five of the answers to each question
will be correct, you get, so no more than five, you get plus one point for each correct choice you
make, and minus one point for each wrong choice, so select as many as you know, but don't guess,
go, all the words with a similar meaning as the one above, big, mammoth, large, huge, colossal,
I don't think this is a word, hippopotamon, small, yeah, done, lame, charge, cues, incopulate,
oil, borebear, borbear, harassed, indict, pulled, chilly, nippy, freezing, boreal, it's boreal,
it's boreal in here, it's boreal, it's boreal, boreal, boreal, it's so boreal in here, stop,
halt, end, terminate, degroute, vestige, reprobate, that's like a legal term, I think, maybe, short,
brief, fleeting, it's only three to five, okay, beginner, a beginner, a newcomer, a novice,
a rookie, a neophyte, greenhorn, I don't know, well greenhorn is, I don't know, thin, thin, thin,
sheer, skinny, no, sheered means see-through, skinny, narrow, um, lupay, anem, anemechel,
smiggly, there's another one at least, I don't know, these are all these words, nobody even uses
these, I don't go to Starbucks and go, oh yes, could I have a, uh, a, uh, anemechel coffee,
please, nobody uses these words in real life, I don't care how high, how smart you are, chat
can't even do this in their head, mental rotation subtest, in this section you'll be given an example
shape and asked to select from a list of other shapes which ones are the same, okay, so it has
to be the same image, for example, the two shapes below are the same just viewed from a different
direction, but the next two shapes are actually different, see the animation that shows they are
mirror images, so I have to pick the things that are the same image, which of these shapes are the
same, oh god, I'm gonna get an F, relax, not this one, this is not the same, this one, this one,
this one, I can see you guys talking, I don't want to see it, emote only right now, I, I can,
I can sense them making fun of me, this one, this doesn't tell you anything by the way, like, oh,
can you like go like this with a shape or what side is it on, no, I want practical fucking shit,
you know what I mean, I'm practically intelligent, I'm not on paper intelligent, I'm practically
intelligent, where do you use this, all right, I can, god, find me a situation where you can like
get yourself out of trouble with this one, yeah, how do you, how do you solve a problem with this one,
it's not, okay, it's not this one, it isn't, not this one,
not this one, wait, maybe it is this one, it is this one, this is going the wrong direction,
nope, it's this one, do I spin this, it's this one, spin it, this is wrong, flat, flat, this way,
stop it, one goes wing, wing, wing, goes wing, wing, wing, goes ee, oo, mm, wow, wrong, this one goes
ee, oo, mm, this one, not this one, this is incorrect, it's going the wrong way, if I take this
and I turn it, it would be going, this is correct, if I put it flat and turn it, this is wrong,
this is cringe, all right, you know what, if I, if you had 10, what, 50, 500,000 people breathing
down your neck while you take an IQ test, you don't think you'd have a little bit of trouble,
there's like 500,000 people breathing down my neck right now,
I, I can't, get away from me, let's relax and go for it, this is going this way, this one's wrong
in the lower left, I believe this one's accurate, if I flip it up, I mean this way, that way,
and if I turn it, this one's correct, this one might be correct, hold on, if I take it like this,
flip it, no, if I flip it this way, no, it's wrong, if I stand this one up, turn it, this one's
correct, yikes, what is playing right now, oh my god, this is like Fortnite music,
what do you mean, no, whatever, you take it, okay, I, can I just skip this one and just get enough,
this one, oh yeah, it goes down, it goes right down, left down, right down, left down,
so if I take this one and I flip it up, go right down, left down, holy shit, this is hard,
I turn this one, this is correct, put this up and turn it, it goes that way, down, right, down,
this is not correct, I take this one and I flip it, oh yeah, this is fucking hard, this is really
hard, if I turn this one that way, it goes wham, yeah, it's this one, all right, I'm done,
visual memory subtest, you'll be shown a grid with some cells shaded for five seconds, then you'll
have to reproduce that sample pattern from memory as best as you can, okay, so just fill in the
fill in the shades, memorize the arrangement, got it, fuck, where was this one, I don't remember,
nailed it, in this section you'll be, you will be a list, you'll see a list of scrambled letters
and asked to find as many as you can that can be unscrambled into real English words,
oh shit, okay, I have to unscrew them, I'm so bad at these ones, I'm so bad at this,
like as many, wait, hold on, like as many as possible that can be unscrambled into an English
word, okay, I think that's it, okay, okay,
that felt, fade, toughed, puffed, come back to it, easy, we, we, at,
Aaron, stop, stop, it's a test, I fucked it up, that, I've screwed it up, I can't concentrate
anymore, save, disc, rain, pale, Borg, no, that's a Star Trek word, it's not real, eight, okay,
algae, gal, plane, nail, salt, slate, shpey, peth, peths, hep, sin,
tassin, ten, waste, laro, I'm so bad at these, edard, tardy, trade, dry, I can't, it's just,
I can't do it, my brain can't do it, I can't do these, I'm so fucking bad at these, oh no,
this doesn't even mean anything, I bet you I can fucking destroy you in arm wrestling, okay,
it's an old joke, all right, in this task you'll be given a grid with some points shaded in green,
you will need to select the point that is most in the middle of all of them, the one that has
the lowest average distance from it to each of the green points, for example, in the grid below,
what point is closest to all the green, all three green points at the same time, it would be like
one, two, three, one, two, three, it's something like here maybe, here, here, two possible answers
are below, blue lines have been added to show how good each is, so it has to be like an equal
distance away from everything, like do I have that correct, did I get that right, how does it
get resident sleeper, sorry man, whatever am I, so it has to be like an equal distance away from
all of them, all right, let's just go for it, no, I got that wrong, what do you mean, it was the most
in the middle of all of them, oh, I see, okay, this one, oh, I thought I got it wrong, I was like what
the fuck, okay, what, point closest to all the points, it would have to be like up, what, oh no,
I don't know, I can't get this open, I can't physically open this, oh, it's because I have
to take the seal off, the point closest to all the green points, it just has to be one of these,
right, it doesn't matter which one, oh, that is a trick question, okay, closest to all the green
points would be like here, what, this is the point in the middle, maybe like this one, I don't know,
I thought, I'm thinking like, I don't know why I thought that, I'm thinking like they all like
meet at this point, I'm getting it wrong, Jesus Christ, it's the middle, the middle most point,
okay, it's definitely like here, or here, here, here, what the fuck are you talking about,
what, because this has to travel, this has to travel, this has to travel, this shit, who fucking
cares about this, here, oh, come on, that's close, the middle most point from here, this has to be
like here, or here, right, I don't get it, I was just the middle most point, what, I don't get it,
I don't understand how that's the middle most point, closest to all of them, holy shit, I'm gonna,
I'm gonna, they're gonna ask me if I'm, if I'm alive, I'm gonna get a thing at the end, this is
gonna say, hey, please, that's like funny, but like no like dead people can take this test,
I've been just putting this on, it's all over my mouth, that was close,
all right, it's definitely, it has to be like up here somewhere, like here, something stupid,
that was also close, the difficult ones of getting better, I almost nailed it, I'm getting better,
this is probably right in the middle, getting better, right here, I'm like within one or two
spots each time, so I'm not, I'm not upset about this, this one could be anywhere, do I have
Fortnite music on, let me get this shit off, I'm also listening to like Fortnite music, like you
don't think that's messing with my head doing the IQ test, there you go, okay, close, oh, I did,
wait, did it kick me off, did I fail, that was only like 16, I was getting too many wrong,
I got slaughter ruled, in this up test, you'll be shown a sequence of icons one at a time,
then you'll be shown eight icons and asked which were in the sequence you just saw,
so I'm gonna be shown icons, and I have to say which ones were in which order, okay, I fucked it
up, I just, I started listening to, I started doing valley music, I was just like, oh, start a
valley, it's really cool, and it was gone, one of them's not on here, wait, hold on a second,
wait, wait a minute, wait a minute, it's not showing, I'm not clicking them in sequence,
I have, oh, I, well now I have no fucking idea, I did not understand the instructions,
god, I don't know, I think this, I don't know, now I get it, it's just, it's too hard to,
it's too hard to remember these, especially, no, they put a check on it, they, they're fucking with
me, man, I mean, this was the first one, this one, no, this is, is this one, this one, this one,
this one, oh, I did it, you want to answer some research questions, no, I, okay, what is it,
get out of here, 117, oh, I don't, I don't know where I am, but, oh, I thought it was gonna be like
85, okay, 117, it's gone down, I want to make that clear, I've taken, I've taken an IQ test
before, a real one, twice, the first time I took it, and by the way, IQ test takes usually like a
couple of hours, like it takes like an hour plus, I, when I first took an IQ test when I was like
17 or so, I had 126, and then it went down to like 124, and now it's 117, I took 100, it was 124 in
college, and now it's apparently 117, it's probably lower than this, it's probably like, it's probably
like 110, probably for real, 99, look at my memory, I got, I'm doing fine, once, look at this,
come on, look at the, look where I am, this is where I sit, this isn't a real test, are you sure,
I, I thought a psychologist was giving this to me, are you sure I, we can't use this in court or
whatever, oh, IQ test of bullshit anyways, what if, imagine if I got like fucking, like 140, there,
print screen, well, this explains why I have a lot of trouble like walking around a concrete building
in Hitman, I do have a pretty good memory, pretty good, not great, pretty good, all right, what the
hell, oh wait, the neural network thing, make sure it's not, somebody's ball sack or something,
let's find out, I can't, it's hard to tell what this is, it's so hard to tell if this is like,
like an asshole or something, because I don't know, it could be, let me just make sure it's not,
hold on, yeah, I don't know, I can't tell, this is like a pair, I think it's like a pair of legs
on the left and it's like somebody's asshole, like going up to their asshole or something,
I'm not sure on it, this is, Jerma enjoys his favorite cheeseburger restaurant, what's the
website, it's a neuralblender.com apparently, I'll try another one, what should I do, let's see,
I have no idea what's gonna happen with this one, we'll see, all right, what time is it,
we could maybe time for a little bit more, what is this one, oh people, people want me to play this,
this is called Monster Breeder, is this game fun, this might take a full stream, it's really fun,
you think so, I do music, what's, somebody just said, what's this shitty music, I'm sorry, I got
my, I just had a gastric upset there, I got my, I had an epigastric reflux there for a second,
what did you say, did you say, you said Stardew Valley's music is bad, come on man, come on,
um, I'll check this out for a little bit, I've been really streaming for six hours, what the
hell happened, all right, music, why not, I'll give it a try, you spent two hours on fast food,
visit, okay, you are at your ranch, from here you can visit your monsters in the stables,
browse the breeder catalog, or get in your truck and go exploring, um, go exploring,
exploring local hot spots is a great way to find and capture wild monsters, you load up your gear
into your truck, to the north of the woods and to the east of the city, to the south of the desert,
let's go to the woods, there's a narrow path leading in, to the west is a castle or to the ranch,
let's go to the castle, drive toward the ancient stone castle, its shape seems to blacken
as a thunderstorm gathers overhead, to the east are the woods, next game, you leave your trunk,
you leave your truck in front and step toward the castle, bringing along your monster catching gear,
oh shit, passing through the castle stone entrance way, dusty room, the walls are decorated
by gray distorted paintings, stop, residents sleep ring me, you're in dusty sitting room,
the walls are decorated by, yeah, yeah, yeah, let's keep going, that's all I can do, oh no,
you're in a library, the books are packed into shelves, two stories high, occasionally a book
seems to move, should I like mark it, oh pull the book, you pull the book, the bookshelf slides open
revealing a secret passageway, that's actually kind of cool, large spiral staircase, you're in
a dungeon, there are large broken shackles on the wall, you hear boots stomping heavily, you turn
around, crikey, it's frankenstein, capture frankenstein, what, you easily bag frankenstein,
put frankenstein in the truck, this is kind of cool, this is cool, should I do this for a
whole stream, yeah, this is a whole stream, I can't, I kind of, I'm very interested in this,
yes, yes, honestly, yeah, yeah, yeah, let's do this again, I'm gonna do this the whole time though,
breed frankenstein, let me get at least one more, oh gargoyle appears, capture the gargoyle,
oh you need special aerial monster catching gear, how many more, okay, this is gonna determine how
much I like this, and if I really actually want to play this, how many monsters are in the game,
just tell me, there's 120, there are 500, there's so many, there's hundreds, okay, this is actually,
this is a ghost appears, capture the ghost, okay, I got him, ghost in the truck, go back to the
ranch, all right, go to the monster staples, frankenstein, breed frankenstein with ghost,
it looks like frankenstein and ghost are mating, they're done, congratulations, you have a bald
frankenstein, frankengeist, talk, boo boo, not frankenstein, boo boo, monster, boo, so wait,
could I do frankengeist, oh you can't do it, I was gonna, why would I, no, that would be weird,
I don't know what I was just saying, I don't know what I was just saying, I'm sorry, your
telephone is ringing, answer the phone, hello, hello, hello, don't do it, I'm, people are gonna
hate me, I can't do it every time somebody says hello on camera, I'm hearing that you're breeding
some groundbreaking new monster crosses, would you be interested in selling, are you a cop,
no way, yes, I'm selling, wonderful, can you sell me a monster like this, slow moving,
clothed, transparent, and magical, I got a frankengeist for you, frankengeist sounds great,
200, 200 bucks, do the staples, do the catalog, this is, yeah, we're doing this, but not now,
I'm probably gonna wrap up in a minute, how long have I been live for,
I'll be back on Sunday, oh well let me check on the art thing, this one sucks, where's god,
Jerma is the one weekend a month dad everyone wants to hang out with, all right, I'm probably
gonna wrap it up, wait, I need to get to exactly six hours, how long do I have to do for that,
how much time, how much time, I haven't looked at my dashboard the whole stream,