All right, let's get this on the screen. I played the last Mario Maker. I streamed the last Mario Maker like on launch. What are you on about here? Yeah, we'll go through my images too. Somebody's asking about it. All the screenshots. Okay, get that on here. We'll do this for like an hour or two. Oh, but um, yes, I want to talk about the somebody's saying delicious. I can't speak when things are blowing up my ears. Post the pics on Reddit or Twitter. I
we're just gonna do a little showcase. This looks good. See, look, I've like already played this game. We'll do a new one. Maybe you won't hate. Did I hate Mario Maker 1? Did I didn't hate Mario Maker 1? Did I? I did. All right, let's cook. Standard difficulty. Yeah, I like my hands suck. My hands are wicked crampy and shitty. So I have trouble doing like that. I can probably use a controller to though. Couldn't I should plug this in? I'm gonna pull the controller in. Well, look, if Mario Maker
If I hate Mario Maker 2, then who cares? We can just load up Cokeserve item shop tomorrow or whatever. No rush. But I mean, I am in a rush to find a USB cable that goes to this fucking USB cable that goes to this. Where are all of my things? Where are my things? Use gamepad. No, it's a free Xbox one. There it is.
All right, here we go. This feels pretty good on my hands here. Let's cook. Standard difficulty. So this game is about being quick and serving customers very fast. This is your main restaurant serving area doesn't look like the best. But hey, you'll fix it up in no time. You can press the menu button to pause the game at any time during the day. To the left is your prep stations. You'll start with four, but will earn more as you gain stars for your restaurant. You can take orders and serve food from here. Let's give it a try. Highlight prep station one by pressing up on the D pad and
press a. This is a customer ticket. He wants a corndog. This game gave me anxiety about an old job like fast food, preparing food quickly. Prep station one is highlighted press right button to prep the food on the right side of the screen. So we got to do we just got to do ketchup and mustard, right? He looks like he wants a corndog cursor on screen. I'm leaving it. You now have the corndog order in front of you. The right menu shows which keys to press for what ingredients and the bottom ticket is how the customer wants the food made.
Once you've done with an order press the LB to serve it to the customer. Just ketchup please. That's mustard. How do I remove that? I thought of how do I remove that? I have to remove that. Is there a way I can take that off? Well, I fucked up your order. Give me three stars on Yelp. Dick. Okay, right bumper. Ketchup and mustard please. More complex food that requires you to cook before serving and that has you access more ingredients. Alright, this is a pizza. The nachos have an ingredient that needs to be cooked before preparing the
food. Highlight prep station one RB. Okay, so I want so it's ground meat. Complete the order on the ticket then press LB to throw the order back to the left side of the screen to start cooking it. Okay, to cook it. Ground meat is cooking. You'll need to wait a few seconds for the meat to grill at the right temperature before serving. Once the order turns blue, it's ready to be prepped. Select the order too soon or too late and your customer will have raw or burned meat and will likely have a bad rating. The nachos are ready for additional ingredients. Highlight prep
station one and here we go. So this person's you need to you will need to hold you need to press and hold LT to access the second page of ingredients. Release the trigger to go back to the original page of ingredients if needed. Be sure to recognize that the left column of ingredients call for the left stick to be flicked in a direction and the right column uses the right stick. What do you want? Queso guacamole. Queso guacamole. Beans, rice, and ground meat. Beans, rice,
and ground beef. I'm telling you I can't I can't play this game. I have to say everything. Beans, beans, onion. Okay great work you just completed a more advanced order. You can always practice more individual foods in the view by food menu. Press A. Alright here we go. There are two types of orders that you'll find in cook serve delicious. When an order is highlighted blue after cooking it will require additional prep. Yep when an order is yellow it requires an
no more prep and is ready to be served to the customer. Simply select to serve it immediately. Press A. You can only prepare one order at a time however you can serve yellow cooked orders to customers immediately even when preparing a different order. Simply highlight the order and press right bumper to serve at any time. Press A to continue. Customers won't wait around forever and have their food to order taken. You'll notice that this food is slowly disappearing from the screen. If it goes away completely the customer will leave angrily and will cause bad buzz for your restaurant. There are ways of extending customer patience with the equipment menu which will be unlocked later in the I have to I can't
like put on my fake television voice because it's just too hard of a game. Sorry guys that's just the way it is. Customers won't wait around forever yet. Okay there are ways of extending customer patience via the equipment menu which will be unlocked later in the I have to. There are also chores to contend with but that's enough tutorials for now. You can always select practice chores in the tutorial menu and try out all the chores you need to complete daily. Let's go. That you just learned the basics. Here we go open the restaurant. Here we go. I'm not moving it. I was about to move it. Yeah I'll move it. Alright welcome welcome welcome. This is your main menu.
Managing menu. For me you can control your food menu. Buy new items and a whole lot more. You'll work from 9 to 10 p.m. Wait 9 a.m. to 10 p.m. Isn't that too long? Then between each day you'll come back to this menu to plan out your business. First when you buy some food to put on your menu you have a starting budget that should allow you to purchase three to five foods out of the initial 20 that's offered. You can do that via the view by foods menu. Speaking of an amount of things I did want to tell you so in the beginning of the stream I talked about it a little bit but I wanted to give just another reiteration
of the next couple months. So there is going to be on this stream somewhere in before September the carnival stream. There's going to be a carnival on this stream. There's going to be a bunch of midway games that you guys are going to play. It's not just going to be a dunk tank. It's going to be a fucking monumental event with tons of games. So the reason why I now have to dial I just I have to dial streams back a little bit. So four days a week is typically what I would typically do. It's probably going to
be dialed back to like three. I want to make sure I like said that a few times. Then this is like as of like next week. I don't want to give like any spoilers. I don't want to give any more information but there's going to be a lot of shit to do. So hopefully it's fun but I have the process has started of a company that's now involved that is going to I may have to do traveling back and forth from this facility a few times. So I will make sure you guys are going to know exactly when this is happening. You're going to see
probably testing in the chat too. There's no way that you will miss this if you want to see it because of the next three to five weeks I'm going to be talking about it all the time. SpaceX. No. Do we get prizes? You're just going to have to wait. You have to wait and see. But this is not just going to be a dunk tank stream. Welcome to the carnival. That's all I'm going to say. I'd rather it be like a fun surprise. You'll know the date but that's pretty much where I want to leave it. It's going to be a sub only stream. Why the hell would I do that?
But there's still going to be a dunk tank. Absolutely. So just to give you an indication. It's a robotics team. So every one of these carnival games is going to be controlled by you guys. This is not just like hey walk around like a fake carnival. You guys control all the games. That's the point. There is an entire robotics team that is on board with this and it's going to be fucking a ton of fun. That's it. That's the end of all the information that I'm going to give you. It's going to happen before
September. Oh fucking need to read this. Or like September-ish. I don't really have like an exact date yet but I will have that information over the next couple of weeks. I will be promoting the shit out of this so don't worry about...wait what? More details. September 2030? No. September 2019. I wish I could like talk about more of this and it's something that I'm like so obsessed with this right now. But I want it at least to be like surprising for a lot of the things that we're doing.
But anyways, that's why I have to start to cut streams over the next like two months. I am fucking stoked. Anyways, you'll notice a few foods require a piece of equipment. Yeah I need equipment to do so. I remember this stuff. You have to buy it. There's boosters and tractors. These are elements of foods that can help or hurt your business by bringing in more customers during the day or run them off entirely, right? If you have dirty trash everywhere. Yeah. Buzz is vital in keeping customers. The higher you buzz the faster customers
will come through the door during the day. Perfect orders gain buzz for the next work day. Average orders add no buzz and bad orders subtract from your buzz. That's true. Gotta add the foods to the active menu. You can do up to six foods a day. Plan on your menu each day to balance out which foods gain the most buzz. I'm ready. So let's do...what's the menu we got right now? Literally nothing. All right I want um pretzel. Yeah I want pretzel. Beer. Pretzels. Beer.
And um fish. No that would a terrible restaurant. Pretzels. Beer. And baked potatoes. And steak. Okay that sounds good. So let's do pretzels. Beer. Baked potato. And steak. That's a carb heavy menu. What about equipment? Are we good? Grill station. Deep fryer. I don't think I need this. Oh I did. I want the tip station. All right I'm ready. Begin. Steak. One seasoning.
Once seasoned. Twice juicy. And one serving is citrus. Season uh juicy and citrus. And then oh fuck cook it. Baked potato is uh sour cream bacon and onions. Sour cream bacon and onion. Serve it. That wasn't good? What was wrong with it? What was wrong with that? I don't understand. Cheese and sour cream. Cheese and sour cream. Why do they not like this? Oh fuck the steak. The steak. Steak. Okay hold. Pour beer. Toilet.
What do you want from the toilet? Did I always wash my hands in the toilet? Nothing on it. Here. Salt and butter please. Rush hour. Sanitize. Come on. Once seasoned. Twice juicy. And citrus. These controls actually are not very good. Cheese, sour cream, butter. Okay. Dude it's the. It's the. I don't like this. I'm going back to the keyboard. No I don't like this. This is not good. It's like.
You can't use the left analog to move up and down. No no no no no no no no. Awful. No. Give me the keyboard. Do it. Cheese, sour cream, butter. I just heard that like raw. Yeah the the the bumper is. I can't do it. Hitting up and down on the analog. You have to do up and down on the D pad. No. It's fucking with my head. Left bumper to serve. Why shouldn't it be right bumper? If it's right bumper to open the menu why isn't it right bumper to serve the food?
Season the toilet. Sour cream and cheese please. Wait doesn't it doesn't need to cook first? Yeah hold on. It's like needs to steam. Cook serve delicious with the controller. You poor man. I know I know. I just I didn't know. I didn't know.
Trees, potatoes. Sour cream and onion. Cinnamon please. That's. I gotta get out of the controller.
Nothing. What do I have to do? Pretty good. Sour cream and onion. Whoa what was wrong with the steaks?
What was wrong with the steaks? Fuck this place. What was wrong with the steaks? What was wrong with the steaks?
God. I know this is a typing game. I'm a moron for wanting to use the controller.
I know this is a typing game and I'm using a controller. Look. It wasn't part of the plan tonight.
Yeah it's a typing game. This is a long day. If only I. Yeah unplug the controller.
I just did. That didn't do anything. It's still on the controller setting.
You have to do it in the menu. Come on come on come on. Season three times
and one juice. No. Whatever. Cheese and sour cream. Derma's IQ is equal to the temperature of
the steaks. The raw ass steaks that he's serving. Well that's funny because the
internal temperature of a raw steak is usually like 112. So that's pretty good actually. Thanks
for the compliment. Like 120. All right I need to change this because hold on.
Save and quit. I'm doing the keyboard. No not quit the whole game. Just like hit the menu.
Shit. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Nice. Enter. Here we go. Wait was this the right day?
I don't know. I think so. Is this the right day? Yeah. Okay. Career menu. Upgrade food.
Corn dogs are easy. I need a drink. I need drinks. Always remain fresh on the active menu.
It's not going to decline in popularity. Customers don't ever tip with this.
Minus five buzz. Trashy food. Then it can be taken to go. All right. What about uh
uh a soup? This is making me hungry and I'm not even playing. I mean I am playing. How about a
fish? Specialty foods. I can't unlock these. I gotta buy equipment for that. Let's get like
a grill station. I don't have any money. All right I gotta make this good. Active menu.
Let's go with uh corn dogs are easier. I want easy shit. Corn dogs. Drinks. This is just
gonna be easy. Maybe like get the baked potato out of here and put like the fish on the
menu. Why am I pronouncing it soup? Pre-record. What are you talking about? Oh oh because pre-recorded
right. All right so we got catering. Simple food. Afternoon delight. That's all right. All right
let's go. All right. Crack my knuckles and here we go. Hold. Is it enter to serve? Am I doing
that wrong? It's just one two three four right? You don't even use the mouse for this game.
So fillet the fish then season and cook. That's so much easier. Get beer at 8 a.m. Yeah.
Uh just ketchup please. Oh large cola with ice please. A large cola with ice.
I? Did I do it? Yeah. A medium cola with ice please. Soda machines are gross.
Well I mean if they're clean and they're taken care of they're not.
Who puts ice in after the drink? I do that. What's wrong with putting ice in after? That's
fucked up? Is it? A large tea. With ice. Ice. Two. Four. A large tea with ice. Oh that's cola.
Dump it. How do I dump it? Can I dump it? Whatever. That's what you get. A large diet ice.
That's just water. Large diet. I can't. It's too stressful. A medium tea with ice please.
fuck press ice ketchup and mustard please there you go cleaning the toilet
small water with ice please I meant I said a soda machine not at home oh my
god I pressed two I'm do I got such bad buzz too
it's a rat what's this this lady like looks like not happy about this
restaurant at all large cola with ice sanitize the cheese just ketchup
give myself a swirly and then go back to work
mop the tables I don't have an option to do that do I I can't fucking believe
it again whatever everybody that wants a drink this is like your parents
when everything was a Nintendo are you in there playing Nintendo it's a
PlayStation oh he really likes his Nintendo you're on like your computer
everything is cold everything is coke medium diet with ice a medium diet with
ice medium a small grape with ice go go go go go go go shit of rush hour
again no just busted yeah I don't know what I don't understand that
people call diet coke a diet no they don't you can have so you can serve
finished order as well you were in a different order you can that's pretty
cool I didn't know that I just mustered what's with all these
mustard people and now I've seen no ketchup large grape with ice take
that mustard only is the best corn dog I mean it's all right mustard
superior to ketchup I mean I think they both have their place so if you have
what hold on this is with clothes to get out of here ketchup is really good
on but for instance french fries ketchup is better on french fries then
mustard is on french fries you don't put you don't do that and if you do
then what in the what are you doing ketchup is way more unhealthy how is
ketchup more unhealthy than mustard they're both fucking puke condiments
that come out of a processed factory they both have a bunch of like dog shit in
them who better beer upgrade includes a replacement of hops classic brew to the
hops classic American brew I'll take it
no no new new menu something we need to get some like actual foods on here
I use them like high-income beer is always popular that's all we have we
don't have any we have beer fuck the drinks yeah we serve beer just be a bar
all right s say SCJ season three times and one juice I gotta be on top of
this french fries with mayo that's pretty good actually I like that I
actually do like french fries and mayonnaise it's not it's actually very
good it is it's not bad if you've never had it before that you look I
know it for some reason Mayo has this weird incredibly polarized opinion that a
lot of people have you either think mayonnaise is disgusting unedible garbage
or you like it there's no in between Mayo is salty jello no it's not jello
sucks I just had to eat a shitload of jello and it's just it's not even
close if I was allowed to eat mayonnaise out of the jar I probably
would have if I could have that would be better than eating a jello season three
times and then no one juice your jello sucks it's horrible guys on jello is
seriously late somebody I mean this is gonna be gross and I apologize to
anybody that doesn't like to hear gross things but jello is somebody
spitting a cold loogie down your throat disgusting I don't want it I
never want it again season one two three
gonna see some once and then two juicy one and then you got it I just saw the
chat rocket by after I said well hold on somebody said jelly jelly is not the
same as jello I don't know where you get no that's not my opinion jello is
not jelly there they're very different jelly is good jelly and jam that's
fine jello gross do I need to pause the game to talk about this the
stuff that you dump from the box and add hot water to and stuff it in your
fridge for two hours is not the same as the jam that you buy like preserves I
don't I don't understand what what's happening here what do you guys know
jello like jello the the fucking sand you dump in the water is not the
same thing as buying like jam what do you what I'll fight you all day on
this one it's the same ingredients it's processed differently it's not
the same there's no real fucking fruit in a gin jello I get I jello is a gelatin
that is sold in powdered form and you have to add it in water and heat and
then allow it to cool down to set and take the shape of jelly jelly and
jello are practically the same thing with jello being a brand name sold in
the United States all jello is jelly but not all jelly is Jeff fucking give
me a break it's not the same it's not the same I'm jelly like the yellow
fucking booger jello is not the same as getting strawberry preserves from the
grocery store that is not even close that one of them is disgusting and one
of them is kind of good and no no no no no no no no no it's okay
smuckers strawberry jams strawberry preserves it's just you cook
strawberries and lemon juice in a saucepan and you do that for 40 minutes
and you stir in sugar it's not potent bones it's not bones jelly I'm looking
jelly jelly a clear or translucent fruit spread or preserve referred to as
jelly in Canada and other countries jelly fruit preserves jelly fruit
preserves fruit preserves jelly fruit preserve there it is
jelly is bones it's not bones all right I'm fucking out of here I'm out
of here jelly is bones if I hope somebody says jelly is bones one more
time I am going to fucking scream I have to pay attention wait wait I gave
that guy an empty glass hey can I get a beer sure here's an empty cup
attempt to put alcohol in there I can't fucking believe people are putting like
no I can't believe it jello sucks what happened whoa I got a picture give the
picture sure you put jello on your french fries I mean no don't do that
somehow I like all my my windows are down how do I close all these
windows cinnamon cinnamon on a pretzel Mayo is okay Mayo is good I will every
I will convert all of you here very very easily you want to love that you
want to love Mayo I'll tell you how you just have to put it on a fresh
crispy chicken sandwich fuck what time is it I have to I'm going to get
food we're talking about like a nice thin crispy patty with one with one
sleeve of lettuce and then a nice slab of mayonnaise and maybe one pickle but
don't put the pickle on there don't mess it up seriously trust me on that
ten percent positive buzz that's pretty good what I got 700 bucks I
need a I need like a gorilla something what can I buy I need like a fryer
lasagna I thought I'd get me started on lasagna sure we had a lasagna
conversations not not that long ago actually Mayo is salty jello prove me
wrong first of all mayonnaise is oil and eggs it is not powdered bones and
neither is jam neither is jelly jello all right lasagna beer here no no more
beer lasagna let's do Italian lasagna pretzels baked potatoes and
soft drinks classic Italian menu oil has bones the strawberry preserves telling
him it's ground up bones just butter please well thought B was bacon and what
world is why butter layer ingredients in the following order pasta what the
fuck was that pasta sauce cheese parmesan pasta sauce cheese parmesan
what it doesn't you just need to sprinkle it on anyways parmesan just
goes on top anyways who cares medium water with ice one of my
things I'm marmalade I'm not sure if everyone really had marmalade before I
don't think so cheese and sour cream cheese okay pasta cheese sauce
parmesan pasta cheese soup done okay top cheese sour cream butter or
bacon and you want everything I don't know did you want everything it's cheese
and sour cream sour cream and onions I mean go what is it it's a pasta sauce
cheese parmesan fucking god damn it whatever that's hard to pasta cheese
sauce parmesan oh just butter fucking be oh it's how cream bacon and onions
sediment what is wrong with the order I don't understand what I'm doing
wrong with the order pasta cheese sauce parmesan pasta cheese sauce parmesan
pasta cheese sauce parmesan pscr three times that's what I'm doing pscr pscr
pscr pasta sauce cheese pscr pscr pscr what a boring asshole all right
he s vr butter and salt you got it don't screw me a pscr I want to get
it right medium cold no ice there you go pscr okay we go this up to
me that's it right oh no small diet with ice oh no small small cheese hot
cream butter I just mashed every button small water with ice such as
suffering small great place a large isle ice please ps pscr like beat up
fuck large grape with ice well they do it butter chives and bacon those
cheese sour cream chives and onion so he was chives H onion and you that's
cheese how good small die with ice please medium cola with ice please hope
you're having fun because we're not what are you talking about now this is
I'm having a lot of fun one guy sour cream chives and onions sh oh all
right I got like 3.5 percent negative buzz but that's not sorry I need a
tip jar how much is it 50 bucks give me that table snacks oh that'll shut him
up any uh let's go with I can deal that I actually can do that pretty
consistently now get the baked potato out of here it's sucks too many
random ingredients um good fish back on the menu no more pretzels corn dog
instead all right let's go french fries oh boy what a meal I love your
restaurant I'm a local blogger and I plan to write a great review of your
the extra buzz helps hey thanks appreciate it all right I should nail
this one how is it already this much trash I served one person one medium
drink the McRib is back on the menu I need a times 12 that always scares me
it startles me every time give you some good buzz I don't want anybody
nobody waiting around for anything McBones small no I tried to can I
ditch it apparently that was perfect this person doesn't have taste buds
it's up not down all right I'm good quiet I'm gonna look at itchy head
medium diet with ice I fucked it up you want a small grape with ice you
want I trash medium marty with ice please thank you a small diet with ice
please so many drinks stop ordering drinks stop ordering drinks there's
too many drinks medium diet with ice please that's time so I've got it I
think I got it am I getting tips for this I better be who comes in a
restaurant just for a large drink old people I'm talking like 65 plus
sometimes I bring in a paper 65 equals old yeah that's when you get your
senior discount I that's I classify that as old old people just wander
around looking for shit to do I don't think that's so funny just like
walking around I guess guess I'll go get a large coke Denny's and then leave I
guess don't we all I mean I kind of I look forward to that though you guys
don't look forward to that no you don't look forward just to kind of like
open up your door and like walking around in a circle and ending up at
Denny's why that would be kind of fun drink a large tea with ice please you
got it damn it I try I press that mmm I tried to press fucking you know what I
tried to do that's a flashed me in the face and it fucked me up there goes
the combo god damn it I got flashed right in the face large cola with ice
I'm making some money though my boy this game looks hard it's it's uh it's
a test of reflexes that's for sure and memorization under pressure it's
pretty fun medium cola with no ice play cooks are delicious too yeah this is
like just a game just it's a kind of like a pick rust we're gonna just kind
of hang out and just talk shit about how jam is not jello and how jelly is
not jam and jelly is not jello and jello is gross these are the kinds of
streams we can have those conversations on alright 20 days of
service not quite there make a hundred dollars in tips I gotta get
something new let's see buy foods pizza wine I want wine on the menu
$2,500 never mind coffee I need to buy some equipment here grill station
burgers and nachos I still don't have enough money French fries fried chicken
well I'm just gonna get it we'll do french fries how much is french fries
it is 800 bucks for french fries damn okay let's do active menu I think I'm
gonna go for it just somebody said do easy cheap shit I mean the baked potatoes
not as no this the fish is really easy easy cheap shit and just perfect
I'll get a perfect here lasagna was glowing was it oh shit is that I get
bonuses for that stuff easy cheap and shitty if it's gonna make my buzz
increase I just want people to talk about my restaurant cinnamon come on
it sucks I'll screw that up I want to make sure it's perfect how is German
seeing over the counter I'm not talking for the rest of this room don't screw
it up I want to get like times 20 good getting tips cheap and easy we're
going for tips we're almost at the low ab and two I don't know what's
going on but minus two it's not fair it's not fair I hate this one
because you can't do it fast this is a Star Wars theme song
this is the the thing that they play in the Star Wars bar that's the cantina
yeah can I do my age in combos here there you go there you go there you go
62 combo no I'm almost there oh slow down don't go crazy they're wasting a
lot of the fish you're getting one fillet out of an entire fish seems
wasteful make a stew come on 40 am I doing a special stream for my 80th
birthday I don't think twitch is going to be a website when I'm 80 you know
I'm saying I don't think do you think this shit is still gonna be around
you guys shouldn't be worried about what I'm gonna scream when I'm 80 and
like what's gonna happen when like the volcanoes erupt in like 50 years
you know I'm saying like that what I'm screaming is not really that
important oh picture yes it is almost times 50 50 50 orders perfect I did it
that's gotta be some kind of record we've left chips in our head and your
thoughts will go straight into our brains that's so scary perfect lots of
positive buzz two rats six dishes washed it should be a decent amount of
notes not at all it's only 400 bucks how much is the it's just 800
bucks any bonuses today there's a bonus yeah I did that this is there's
negative things out here what's the problem here any more greens buy new
food I can't all I can I can't afford anything why would it be 1200
bucks to make a salad ice cream upgrade is now available crazy Dave's
initial bet you're pretty darn good cook I'll tell you that but I bet
you're not as good as you think my name is crazy Dave and I love me some
gambling and there's no better way to earn some fast cash than putting up a
few bets against your skills as a cook I'll take your $300 today and see how
you do you win the bet I'll give you 600 tomorrow I bet you that today you
can't make 15 per you paid fine for that what this is just monopoly chance
cards I just got 200 bucks I can't believe you managed to serve every
single order perfectly yesterday with no missed chores to boot menu rot is
oh shit new item inspection past total put 10% buzz menu rot string cheese all
right let's get some french fries so active menu let's get french fries on
here we're gonna be a little bit of a bar menu rot what should I put up
there instead steak lasagna sounds good all right 15 perfect orders in a
row after that don't matter why don't I just go all that perfect and all
of them in a row lasagna and french fries french fries actually go with a
lot of stuff putting french fries in a in a Giro or a burrito you ever have
like a steak burrito with french fries in it you messin up we already went
over this a thousand euro euro Giro gyro everybody had you know how many
people say it differently doesn't matter you call it any restaurant you
want they'll say it differently yes look ah what am I supposed to say
I'm working here I've been told it's euro like euro but there was a Greek
place that was right down the street from me and the guy said gyro every
time and he was from Greece I don't know hold on wait I go hold on I gotta
hold on almost there small water with ice come on hurry the fuck up 15 got
it what is it large cold no ice please good you can serve orders
while you're in prep yeah but my my tiny like crow sized brain can only do
one thing at a time crows is smart though and where were you going with
that one what would you what we say I would be for an animal then if you
guys would say what kind of animal I would be you're more of a pigeon I
don't know how to do this the done you're a snail weasel I don't know
about that two three four it's like four seconds with a salt with is it a
salt or is it more than one salt small grape with ice squirrel ferret fuck I
think I think I was thinking like orc like strong and cool and big and orc
is not an animal it looks not a lizard you're gonna make me fuck this
up where's the one that's not done thumbs up large tea with ice please
you've got it three no salt you got it is there a date for the next green
screen stream Saturday this Saturday it is the encore presentation I will shout
it out again I will give you the link again if you have a submission one
submission per person not every submission is gonna be taken we are
going to condense them down by a lot because I don't want to have a
six-hour long green screen stream this is just an encore presentation with
what we're gonna try to pull in some of the the high-quality posts almost
reached the age I was already there why would salt not be s that's in weird
cook serve delicious a new items now available garbage service is now
available okay you have a no you have a new item slot as my tune did all
bonus perfect day and crazy Dave's bet thanks crazy Dave I can't stand
it anymore no food compares to you guys no one I hate that I can't eat here
every day girl it's so good sherry soda okay so let's see I think I want
to upgrade something better beer yeah better beer let's go to equipment I
want a grill station so we got better beer now mmm
corn dogs fish steak fish steak steak specialty foods all right let's is
there anybody know uh nobody got any money I can make here I guess not
let's go got better beer now this is different no it's just it's just better
steak is too hard for you no it's not I'll get it perfect every time I
promise see actually I was blew it I almost pressed it more than once come
on more customers hurry up no salt steak should always be well done I
disagree I like steak medium to medium well well done steak I think actually
is alright when it's in a I can't talk and do that one when it's in a
sandwich if you get the first it's like a steak and cheese sandwich I want
that steak to be well done medium to medium well because some people at
restaurants medium well is actually medium and their medium is medium rare
so no oh god hold on medium diet nice got it oh what is it sick nice chicken
chickens better than steak I actually like poultry better than red meat so
I agree with you I like poultry and seafood more than I like red meat like
beef and pork depends on what you feel like yeah no I mean I don't get me
wrong there's plenty of opportunities where I like a great piece of meat
steak I don't do it that often though I probably eat steak two or three times
a year maybe less than that season one too juicy in one citrus you got
it but chicken and turkey chicken turkey and all kinds of seafood I eat
pretty much all week tuna salmon sardines fatty fish lots of turkey lots
of chicken crab I love crab crap is one of my favorite things ever small
water with ice free one juice here we go medium cold with ice not bad I'm
getting the hang of this game brat toilet flush pour somebody reach into
their glass fucking no fuck no no no no I didn't oh my god sorry sorry I got so
into that that was like getting hit by a bus no no no mommy I don't want to
go mommy this guy's a psycho whatever no mommy I don't want to go no is
the restaurant in a skyscraper on a hill probably in a skyscraper it's
probably like a hotel restaurant got it second it happened all right um that's
fine I need some new items I need something else on here Pat rest aside
Pat rat pesticide we're watching you until and keep these tickets safe I
got two mysterious tickets okay it's gonna be raining those working in
larger structures such as sure as soda should consider staying indoors okay so
that's rainy outside so it's not a nice day menu rot is occurring let's go
to the active menu I get this off everyone wants to be inside so I mean
what does what do we get like indoor quality food maybe indoor quality yeah
that one has indoor quality on it big potato indoor quality all right no
rot right buy foods are we gonna I want equipment I want the grill because I
want burgers eventually here let's go oh fuck oh my god what I knocked it off
that I can't see the screen sorry just the first customer who cares this guy
is a psycho so I'll get more money for this right oh no it's a baked
potato I'm terrible at these just butter H is butter why I hate the
baked potatoes that could be anything I'm so hungry now what am I gonna eat
first thing somebody says I don't care what it is and I don't care if it's
like out of the trash can whatever it is doesn't matter what is I'm gonna
eat like you say eat literal trash and I'll do it dirt fuck I can't
play these games with you guys man butter chives bacon butter chives
bacon butter twist chives H where's chives bacon butters why small water
with ice large water with ice trash so I tried to press the toilet this is why
I have to look at my hands whatever I use the computer because my fingers
just collide they glide into the toilet that's right do a keyboard cam
maybe if I have a cook serve delicious too I'll do that my hands
are like really inflamed today no I don't want you look at my hands show
us no I did my hands are inflamed I got like a cut on my hand and I'm
an idiot cheese sour cream butter butters why cheese is see sour cream is
us there we go am I wearing the ripped green shirt no
American tank top because it is like a hundred it's been like 95 to 100 plus
in Vegas these last few days it's only gonna get hotter it's gonna be
like a hundred and fifteen in the next like month or two probably
Fahrenheit it's hot here baked potato to my grandma these to say it what
you want to get it you want to get a baked potato sounds good to me grandma
okay twice juicy one season twice juicy one citrus sour cream and cheese
please that's that large cola with ice you've got it throw it in there a
beer once twice juicy seasoned serve it up just butter it's why get it out
there one probably two rush hour is over good nothing on it you are easy thank
you I missed a sit I missed a citrus when I do that you can't read chat
during rush hour his orc brain is too focused how would I ever read chat and
do this though that doesn't make any sense our cream chives and onion it's
impossible what you're describing you somebody just said Taco Bell and think
that I mean does that that count somebody said dirt that counts I will
absolutely be eating dirt if I go to Taco Bell so like stop slandering
companies no what I meant to say was what I meant to say was I there like
if I would have it's a good restaurant and I'm there was nothing
because because because if I were to go to one of those restaurants and
like the employee there was like being a jerk to me which they would
never do that at an establishment like that but if they did then like maybe oh
no like a friend of mine was in like the front seat and like I ordered a
delicious perfect ten out of ten fantastic crispy juicy taco from this
restaurant and I get I got to go to the bathroom I gotta go like take a
piss and my friend of mine takes a dart and like stuffs it in the taco
being like a dick and think he's funny and he starts to get this
camera such recording and I come back and I take a bite and I'm like
what's starting here and he's like yeah got you and it gets uploaded
that that's what we're referring to robberies criminal activity is there a
crime food it's time for your five-day inspection inspector will come to your
restaurant a few times today for an hour or so and observe how quickly you
respond to chores yeah don't worry I got it under control so I got some
money let's go to buy foods that's let me find nachos pizza how much is
burger 1200 bucks ice cream 750 why is this stuff so expensive to unlock any
bonuses today it was like the crime one the shits rotting get it off I'm
gonna say put french fries back on get the baked potato out of here add the
pretzel get rid of the drinks no keep the drinks no get rid of the add
corn dog all right I don't know what a bit of it I don't understand who
the crime thing what the crime food is you got beer and that's it well
oh well you know order something or what what are you just standing there for you
fucking dummy order something hey stupid oh that's the inspector hi how are you
why are you in a hard hat is the ceiling gonna fucking collapse all right
bye what I did the person just sit there
staring at me I don't know I thought the person just had a hard hat on a
health inspector has like glasses like a suit I'm like super generalizing
health inspectors right now it wasn't it's a safety inspector right okay
never mind that's why I was confused she was in the email oh I don't what I
just brought I've just skimmed my emails
well I'm laughing because somebody said I have a hundred days perfect in
a row how many do you have fill it up give me a chore to do I'll do it
right away so this person doesn't care if I sneeze into the beer they
care about if I drop the beer and I don't pick up the glass off the ground
right so we're good she's just browsing I just looked up my other monitor has
these beautiful brilliant photos on it I can't wait to be able to go
through those see I did it really fast and I didn't wash my hands and I
gave this old guy a corndog that I microwaved I actually went to the
supermarket and bought frozen corndogs I don't make those did we
already have this conversation already how long do you think it would take
before somebody would notice that you would just had like all TV dinners if
you opened a restaurant and you went up the freezer section and you made it
look nice but it was all stuck in the freezer section yeah we're talking
about that never mind I'll have that pay attention all people really care
about is the beer as long as it's cheap a lot of fish must have had
some good reviews about the fish because that's all you guys are
ordering that's fine where was the inspector there that was pretty fast
that's pretty good see did a good job you said you eat a lot of seafood you
live in a desert how can that be good but seafood well this thing about Las
Vegas is they just whatever they want they get it they'll they'll find a
way to get it so most of the seafood pumps in from California so you
actually can find some pretty decent stuff remember Los Angeles is not
even like three hours three and a half hours in a car from Vegas it's fake
food what would you classify as real food you're stealing our seafood
technically well is it stealing or is it paid for pretty good day Salt Lake
City has shit was this 10% boost don't be alarmed good day sir or madam I
hope today is a fine one for you the cooking skills are about to be
challenged cook bets I've taken the liberty of hacking your email client
installing a new bet option on the bottom left hand side beneath the
favorites button on the main main main email menu here you'll find a new
random bet each day that you may partake in the cost of one silver
ticket I'll give you three isn't in game currency all right let's make a
bet your randomized bet get 42 times perfect combos today with the
following foods on your menu I don't have wine and I don't have one
steam leaderboard challenges weekly challenges okay you got an inspection
passed and you rot I know was that wine 2,500 bucks oh yeah if I accept it I get
it temporarily is that for real what do you think upgraded lasagna upgrade
the french fries upgrade the fish or upgrade no upgrade the lasagna no I
need it I need one star I can't buy a coffee maker I was gonna get a
cheeseburger burgers 1200 by chicken why is 1800 bucks pizza is 1600 are they
just the price is getting more higher he's wonders why he has no money he
has no upgrades that's what I'm saying I have I have upgraded beer I'm
upgrading lasagna upgrades increase the price yeah active menu let's get
the upgraded lasagna on there and let's get the drinks to get the
corn dogs off here add the drink french fries of fine pretzels of fine all
right and give me some money upgrade the fish of the steak next yeah space
engine screenshot waiting room new layer pasta sauce meat cheese parmesan
pasta sauce meat cheese like that pasta sauce meat cheese yeah P S M C R
P S M C R P S M C R P S M C R P S M C R P S M C R P S M C R FN AF VR what's
that's not it the five nights at Freddy's VR why did you do that P S M C
VR no P S M P S M P S M C R oh oh I fucked it up it's bad I fucked it up
really bad classic town wait they're not all meat shit meaty uses lasagna oh
man that's fucking tricky meaty P S M C R what kind of psycho do you have
to be to not get salt on french fries and half the people get it like that
imagine just eating dry ass potatoes sodium yeah but I mean if we're
talking like a non-medical what is it people get no salt because they know
it's gonna be fresh oh that's a fast food little DIY hack there isn't it
huh I don't know you guys were aficionados and fast food DIY hacks
you could can you just ask for it fresh can you do that I feel like you
can't all right speaking of fast food restaurant west once it's whatever when
um not when where should I go oh you wanted now saw you wanted fresh sorry
that's not right at all I've that blew that one hard no you idiot I'm
trying to hit them oh my god it's cuz when you when you get to the
P when you get to the P you just your brain P brain something like that this
idiot stop playing with the controller finally you'll find out when you come
back in two months after your band's up a lot of tension a lot of tension
tonight now oh and how do I just throw it away I just walked out and dump
that fuck I just walked out and dump that yeah I move around guys so you
don't understand I'm moving I just did a dump animation I actually did it a new
bet you can't do 20 perfect combos plus have salads and ice cream on your
menu today I don't have any either one of those thing unclaimed money 200
bucks and a challenge then you've brought okay I got enough money to do
a hamburger burger no I don't have enough for burger salads and ice
cream I can't have both I just need to make more money how's the menu
better french fries better drinks jumbo cups and new flavor blasts now I'm
saving for hamburger let's go do it real quick I wish I was a food
engineer yeah I mean they'll kind of be cool job sometimes when I don't hit
the slap when I press the button it concerns me because I feel like it
didn't go I wish I was a dentist do you so be a dentist go do it go go
be a dentist no no no not like just go be a dentist forehead like no just do
it go like dentist school go learn about the tools and go you utilize your
skills and your knowledge and become a dentist but there's a bug on me I
think like over the rats small grape come on and medium coal with no ice
get it out got that what do you what is it what are you blinking why
would it oh it's you want to fight you want to fight don't fuck that says
don't like fuck about that's fucking funny I slap myself so hard in the
face how do I delete that you know it's sad about that whole thing
eventually my mother's gonna see that clip you know I mean in fact she
may have already seen it and just won't tell me that's one of those things but
you watch that and you go and you just don't mention it to your son I think
she probably has already seen it all right rush hour large diet with ice
small with ice this is a meaty this is a classic this is a meaty this is
drink this is a large diet with ice this is what it's like to work in the
food industry in the in the food industry I had to hold I had to catch
up there because I had to press buttons diet water click the link this what
link the link I don't see a link
day is done almost one star new item is now available commercial toilet
catering opportunities really tower peeps are excited very large boost of
patience in the waiting room then you rot it's time for a hamburger I'm
finally can buy a cheeseburger burger try it out I don't know I don't
know how to make these burgers of two stages cooking the meat and placing
the toppings on the bun some recipes don't require meat which will
automatically skip the cooking process we mean no meat you just need two buns
and tomatoes and cheese okay double ingredients okay so bacon lettuce
tomato and cheese BLT BLTC how do you cook it meat two patties which is one
patty this looks good meat lettuce MLB C T isn't gonna get my brain messed
up try one more time meat double meat then we have LBC T LBC T that's how my
brain has to do it two patties meat BBC delicious okay I got it to all beef
patties oh yeah let's get that active menu going burgers on the menu now
and oh I want fries burgers and baked potatoes yeah that's for nope it is
brought there hold on pretzel has to come off and corn dog cool bacon on
burgers it depends speaking of burgers you don't bacon cheese only please what
the fuck is wrong with you just go to the grocery store at that point and
just get a loaf of bread like Oscar Mayer ready-cooked bacon and American
cheese and just make 40 of them I mean you put an egg on there that's a
different story but there's no egg bizarre just mustard you go is this a
flash game though this is cook serve delicious it's on steam right now
there are two of them so the first one is this the space game no we already
did the space game and it was fun okay butter chives butter bacon and
chives one meat patty you got it okay here we go
medium water with ice what just happened why is everybody freaking up
you just want a BLT meat and lettuce were all these people standing outside
at the door is like fucking Disney World did the rope just drop small
grape with ice and sour cream and bacon and onions and then you are
sour cream and onions and that's um S and O medium great with ice get a
couple of beers BLTC butter I'm fucking so hungry sour cream and onions
that's uh I just want somebody to order just a slice of bacon if you one
thing okay like I know well yeah no it gets busy like that in restaurants
Jeremy yeah but they don't play the fucking background music though you're
in a panic background music imagine if the dinner rush came in where you
worked and somebody turned up that kind of music though hurry up and
rush or you're gonna get in trouble music nobody likes that shit nobody
wants to hear that shit this goes back to like Super Mario doesn't want to
hear that shit when he gets to less than a hundred seconds left see what
I'm saying it's like okay what do you need sir I'll do better one by
sesame seeded and you want to pick us on that and you want a hamburger
okay holy shit a triple cheeseburger dude just a triple bacon cheeseburger
it actually doesn't sound that bad although I don't know three patties
too many I'm a proponent of less meat on a hamburger not more meat when I go to
a barbecue somebody's grilling or you know you go to a place that somebody's
making burgers or something and you get those meatloaf fucking hamburgers
where they made like 12 ounce patties and they molded him with
their bare hands shittily and they just sit him on the grill another
weirdo no I think that's gross oops bacon lettuces a sandwich okay you
sour cream bacon and onions sour cream is s toilet overflowing
derma's real judgemental tonight get that off the screen medium cola with
no ice judge germa no I think it's um big patties have I just don't I
don't want to have to unhinge my jaw like a snake to take a bite out of my
hamburger I just finished work at a bar and this stream is making me anxious
well it won't be long for much longer we're not gonna be streaming for that
much longer I'm gonna come back with Mario maker tomorrow I can't this is
like fun hey inevitably guys inevitably when I rage quit Mario maker 2 after
like 35 minutes maybe I'll just play this again
sour cream and onion do cook serve 2 I will do one more one more one
more and then I'm gonna get gone got some buzz all right what about I need more
money how do they expect you to have this much money German is not gonna
stream Mario maker 2 yeah I'm that's what I'm doing tomorrow yeah that's
that's the plan tomorrow's do Mario maker 2 for as long as I think it's
fun oh he's not what am I speaking a different language or something what's
going on here oh I can't make the crunchies I'm just gonna make money
I got the burger on the menu let's go and then I'll can it after this
I can't believe I like a piece of bacon with it it's a bit level set to two
hundred and fifty dollars no it should be two dollars and fifty cents cheese
sour cream butter and bacon that's butter bacon cheese sour cream all
right come on flow together here try to make it perfect come on
it's a room traveling it's several big news serving the David ice how many
patties one beer cheers can I not hitting every button on my fucking
keyboard and I still really saw tribes are on there right a sour cream meat
only please bacon and cheese please I'm saving a lot of money on these
people they're not buying any meat do you wash your hands in real life when
you pee well depends sometimes I've been wearing like each stretchy pants I
mean you just pull your pants and underwear down and you just pee and
then you just pull them back up you don't even touch anything I don't
understand what the problem is here okay see s y HBO I still can't even
get it there is no problem right okay so if I were to okay so let me ask you
a question if you were sitting let's just say you're I don't know yeah I
are a restaurant right hold on hold that thought so you sit at a
restaurant and you grab your pants you just touch your other the leg of
your pants the fabric do you get up and wash your hands yes so if you
put your hands to your sides and touch your pants you're gonna go wash
your hands what how often do you guys wash your hands every few minutes no I
wash my hands every time before eating you touch if I touch my pants I'm gonna
wash my hands so when you go to the movie and you get a big tub of
popcorn and you bring the big tub of popcorn and you sit down at the movie
news and you're like touching the seat and you have your hands on your
sides and you have your hands on your face and you're eating the
popcorn when I go and pee we've both done the same thing we've both done the
same exact process do you wash your hands when you are eating the popcorn
while you watch the Infinity War do you get up every five minutes to wash
your hands so when you like I gotta like scratch my leg for a second I
gotta wash my hands do I not flush I use my I put my foot up and I like
I put I like and what do you mean do I not flush every single one of
these urinals is automatic flushing what are you talking about
have you been to a urinal in the last 10 years that wasn't an auto flush if you
stand five feet away from that urinal and pee into it and it auto flushes you
didn't and you didn't touch anything what's the problem what's going on
there just because you entered the bathroom do you get germs on your
hands by entering the bathroom no you don't touch anything if you just if
you just pull your pants and underwear down down to your leg your
ankles and you pee five feet away into the urinal you didn't touch
anything what's what's the problem you can't be five feet away without aiming
body training a toddler what do you but what about what but what if it's one of
those urinals that's really goes all the way from the wall down to the
ground this is there an issue you mean a ditch no I'm talking about like
the wall to ground urinals they're huge what about the splatter are you
holding your hands down to catch the splashes how far away I've been I how
far away do I usually go in the urinal I usually go really close like I make
it so my chest is is pressed up against the urinal because I don't I
don't want people you know my privacy I press my body into the
urinal like press it so my chest is touching the the ceramic and then I
just I'm done with this save and quit imagine seeing some guy like press his
body into the urinal you'd be like something's wrong here alright that's
it but anyways I am extraordinarily excited I can't wait I'm gonna be I can
promise you guys this I'm gonna be I'm gonna be working my ass off on this
stream so hopefully it's gonna be worth what is hope maybe like a month
or two wait for this somewhere into September but yeah it's I'm hoping it's
gonna be a shitload of fun the ideas that were thrown around and the stuff
that has going on stay tuned because there's gonna be a lot more to talk
about and yes we'll go over the space pictures we'll do that right now I
want to give myself some time to do it and the bits and everything I
took a lot of pictures huh let's see is this the one yeah it's all in the
same spot right let's go to the beginning I wasn't the beginning one
all right let's get these on just pull up the window here Microsoft photos I
don't actually think I have to I think I have to cap the whole desktop
unfortunately yeah can I full screen there is a full screen would you look
at that that's pretty cool all right here come the pictures don't be
alarmed so this is picture number one this was the first I think it's an
accident that's an accident I guess when this was like the cool globe I got a
lot better because these aren't very good decent structure decent placement
I think I was going for like put two eyes here and it makes like a cool
like Grover character like that in the distance that's not a bad
background a lot of these aren't bad backgrounds not very good decent I
don't know I'm getting a weird 80s vibe from this one I'm not sure why
oh there we go now I'm getting now the 80s filters off now this is just a
planet I really do like that have the planet taking up like half of the
picture on the right side that's a keeper I think for sure I would imagine
this is probably what it would feel like and what you would see if you
got hit in the head with a wrench not very I don't know if it's very
good a little too bright I think it needs to be dropped a little bit not
bad it's a messy right here and a little too much too much luminosity going on
now this is good this is we're talking the first quarter of a second of the
Universal Studios intro not bad could be a freeze frame I like this one
this is the ice rock floating in the distance here I think I get another
one here yeah I framed it up or or insect egg under the microscope or
single-celled organism under the microscope not bad I think I get a
little bit better of a picture here doesn't make me hungry I don't know why
these are making me hungry this is like nougat it's nougat I don't know why
that's nougat to me and that's making me hungry delete that one not
even okay I just got hurt what happened here oh because of that yeah this is
pretty basic this could be a screenshot from Kenshi again I drop
kicked you in the head and this is the last thing you saw before you blacked
out yeah or finger on lens this is 3d moviemaker in fact that is I think the
exact image from 3d movie maker it's the same thing I like this one
ominous almost feels like it's moving doesn't it feel like it's
moving it's not but it's kind of wiggling around for me should have
probably tilted a little bit this this this picture is kind of cool I like
this nebula Dutch angle this is not the one this is not the one it looks
great but it's the next one no no it is that one it is this one is the
volcano crab 2020 hindsight I wish I dropped the HDR a little bit because
this is awesome yeah should have dropped the HDR a little bit although
this would be very very good on the you know when you scroll through on
Twitter and you see the speaker's advertisement for like a cool headset
like this is like the latest gamer headset it is like a is a like a
picture of like your favorite streamer like over here it's like some text up
here down here this is like the gamer headset image I don't know that is
this just kind of hurts to look at even worse this you know this reminds
it this reminds me of when you have disposable cameras two people have
them and you think it's a funny joke to put the flashes right up
against each other and get them right next to each other and take a picture of
each other's cameras what a waste of film I was trying to get I was trying
I think the next one is better no no it was this one there was a weird fade
in when it showed a lot of cool stars but I didn't really get it pretty
interesting cube yeah there's the black hole not sure what this is this
would be great without this although it is kind of weird seeing what I'm
not sure what that is I mean I feel like moving I like this one this one's
cool it's almost like a slinky and then the mirror inside and that's it that is
there's all the photos I like a little firework down here oh it was
Florida oh you're right six six and a half hours ago I had a third thing I
wanted to talk about and yes that was the third thing it was the
twitch controls robots at the carnival stream and that I'm gonna be
dialing back streams it was the green screen encore night being Saturday get
your submission in you need to use the Google form if something can be
somebody link that that Google form get your submission in by tomorrow night we
cannot have submissions be sent in like two hours before the stream an hour
before the stream is just you know it's not gonna happen actually do I
still have I think I have the link right here the form is on the
discord and the subreddit yeah but I just want to make sure it's there
there it is if you have something you'd like to submit please do this is not a
contest by the way it's not a contest there are no prizes it's just something
fun for us to do because the first one was so interesting so if your
submission does not get chosen it doesn't mean that it wasn't any good
this is not a contest so please don't think that is but the third thing
was blurred out and blurred I was making he's almost done with his first pass
of some of the new stuff coming to the channel he's working on he just showed
me yesterday the new wind down screen and it looks great there's a lot of
cool things on that wind down screen and a bunch of new music as well so
that's coming pretty soon you guys will probably get a kick out of it
and after this first pass of the new wind down screens and animations and the
music he's gonna be doing cheer motes and a bunch of new emotes and a bunch
of new sub badges but obviously the animations take the longest because of
their animations so should be fun but with that I'll see tomorrow we're
gonna get through the bits we're gonna go through them shouldn't take
very long post the space photo somewhere online I'll just I could
probably just throw them in the discord I can just like dump them into
like the discord or something that probably makes sense right but let's go
back to a few hours ago more than that Mario maker 2 tomorrow and
internet sucked tonight by the way yeah 30,000 drop frames unfortunately I
hope this shit just can finally be over with I actually did get a
message from Cox that said that they were doing I think because of all the
complaints and all the problems and they have real problems too they're
doing I think they're gonna do like a second network upgrade to this node I
think they're because they're gonna like shut us off for a while and I
think they're gonna do like a infrastructure upgrade so I think we
may have complained to a point where like have to do something about it so
we'll see we will see but anyways we're gonna go back to earlier this
evening this afternoon thank you lunch meal for the five dollars we're gonna
find the discord I'll show you right there somebody already got a knife art
already got it public discord if you want to join and just hang out there's
only I think this is only one or two sub rooms but it's a public discord
but yeah enjoy yourself but thanks for the five dollars lunch meal hey
German graduating high school today don't got much else to say besides
thank you for being there for me since middle school didn't think I'd
make it this far but I'm glad I did could buy yourself a sandwich or something
oh I'm gonna I'm gonna get like that five bucks is gonna get two cheesy
goodie two crunches for three how many cheese a goodie two crunches can I
get with is it how much for five bucks at least two or three but thank
you lunch meal sounds like you've been around for a long time so thank
you for the five dollars and thank you for the lunch meal appreciate it we
also had five dollars from captain dread pirate to go as do I believe it
do you believe in gravity well I I believe that what goes up must come
down therefore yes so yes I do no no I don't gravity isn't real baseball what
goes up must come of course it does that's that that's the point hey goose
biscuit thanks for the five dollars found out today I passed uni so I just
want to drop a handful of bits here to say thanks for being there in the
background of all these years and keeping me sane congratulations
grats on the uni university I'm honored to be the person you've put in the
background while you do whatever it is you're doing congratulations and thanks
for five dollars and good luck the world is your oyster go for Leo
Kurtz thanks for five dollars Christopher Columbus simulator yeah I
kind of you just kind of have to go discover something but thank you
for the five bucks goose biscuit appreciate it thank you Leo Kurtz wait
what it is twice why does it do this to me that was Leo Kurtz for the five
dollars already thank you I just wrote I just rewound thank you Leo Kurtz thank
you Leo Kurtz I may as well just played the same audio clip but
nonetheless thank you hey there we go hello soft boy for two dollars and
fifty cents a German I read an interesting take from a guy who was
saying that we're able to stare at the Sun for short periods with no
long-term damage and that doing so alleviates depression regulates penile
health and helps adjust your sleep cycle I don't think any of those are true
and they say I am NOT a doctor I never could have guessed thank you
Freudian weapon for the 250 this seems like a really good game for
getting computer wallpapers LUL I have at least two I know one of them
I've taken penile health for pissing at five feet honey chain
thanks for the 250 Jerma one guy Jerma mustard someday you're gonna be the one
guy it's gonna happen all of you thanks for five dollars all of you Jerma today
was the hardest I've ever left thanks for all the content over the years I
now have a terrible pain in my chest and I have disrupted everyone
within a 50-yard radius well hopefully enjoyed it hopefully you
didn't disrupt hopefully the people in the 50-yard radius were not like
hopefully you don't get a library or a classical music concert or a children's
chorus but thank you it's always it's always a blast it's always fun no
matter what we're doing thank you I hope they were in a library thank you
Lydia Wang am I saying that right is it is it Lydia Wang Lydia Yuda Wang
Yuda Wang how do I pronounce it I'm terrible
Yuda Yuda but anyways thank you for the 250 God bless you Jerma the flush joke
made me cry please correct me if I'm saying your name wrong but here is
here is some art I'll put it on the screen and something interesting about
this I don't want to give away anything but something very
interesting on the screen something interesting on the screen will be there
in a second I'm not gonna tell you I'm not gonna tell you when you'll maybe
see those but there is a fairly big stream coming up for you know might
see them very big stream that I'm doing then they might show up I'm not
wearing a Star Wars shirt today though that's the thing hey well what's
the total by the way let me see what do we got it doesn't work the bots
broken it was up I know it was explain the socks you don't have to worry about
it I was at like minus 600 or something in the first hour of the
stream two hours of the stream and then people started to jump on that
like bandwagon of always do everything's let's do everything minus
two and get about like a thousand but I was able to comedically rise up it
was all the kid humor yeah I've you know what I really probably should this is an
interesting idea and it's not something I have any plans for
immediately but I should probably just like have an extension get made you
know saying that has become such a staple of this whole community but
like I probably should just have an extension at this point that's like
an actual it's extension you can click on so it wouldn't be like in
the chat I don't know that sounds like a fun idea maybe just need at
least to try it the stream turns off when it reaches minus a hundred but I
triggered I mean yeah the stream turns I kind of like the idea of having an
extension built where if I'm not if there's if the stream is not at a
level of like good comedy then it the stream turns off that's actually kind
of funny and what happens at plus a hundred I don't know you add like 30
minutes to the stream I don't know at minus a yeah at minus a thousand it
blares an air horn in my ears it gives you shit minus 200 you get like
shocked that would be so fucked up I didn't realize those scores were
actually counted there they haven't been that's a very recent thing but
thank you for the artwork it's fucking great really appreciate it and thanks
for the 250 as well you would just die in the stream no I did pretty well
tonight we also had flames 192 thanks to the five dolls thank you flames hey
German me and my friend are huge fans that friend's birthday is actually
coming up soon so I wanted to do is something special for him would you
be able to say his name Ethan so I can edit it into the rats
mixtape yeah Ethan happy birthday Ethan no no no what you got to do is you go
no no no you know hey hey I got a good idea for you ready you know like that
the it's your birthday today website just punch in Ethan there and then
just play this audio clip after so it's like oh hey look I typed it in
Ethan it's your birthday today and then when it gets to the end of that he's
gonna be like oh yeah I know this website but then he's gonna get this
shit you can play this clip after happy birthday Ethan your buddy flames
wanted to make sure you had a very special day cake and ice cream is on
its way that's right Ethan it's your day today so your friend has to do
whatever you tell him to you get to tell him whatever you want and he has
to do it as long as it's legal and as long as he's comfortable doing it
as long as they're coming as long as you're comfortable doing whatever it
is they're doing is your birthday Ethan make it a good one can I get
some hype in the chat please wait he's not here he's not in the chat
thank happy birthday thank you Ethan no happy birthday Ethan that's what I meant
to say happy birthday Ethan and cut it slice it there and put it into an mp3
the background music is polluting the audio recording Ethan look it's your
birthday today I just want to make sure you understand it Ethan I am I'm
so I am so excited it's your birthday we're gonna have cake we're gonna
have presents we're gonna have ice cream remotely and I'm and I'm just
just put me to take this audio clip Ethan what I want you to do is take this
audio clip and like tape it to a dummy's head and just sit me at the
table where we're gonna have to look at this look oh that's pizza
pepperoni pizza Ethan I'll take the first slice uh-huh I'll take the second
slice too I mean it is your birthday but I mean come on I gotta eat so
I'll probably take the first three slices and we're only getting one
small pizza so I mean you know you two you and flames can have you know
maybe half a slice each we'll just cut it in half with one of those
slicers and and I'll and then I'll go home but happy birthday Ethan have a
fantastic day use the first one the first one was the first one was way
better it's okay then just drop just the music it wasn't that loud the
background just round it out with like rock music anyway happy birthday
Ethan and thank you flames for the five dollars hey wizards thank you
wizards swears for the ten bucks they say stream sucks thank you for the ten
dollars I appreciate the feedback thank you thank you zizio for the ten
dollars hey Jeremiah I felt it was about time to get back for your amazing
entertainment your chapter and cook serve delicious reminding me of my
few years in Vegas and late night runs to Roberto's taco shop have a
California burrito on me french fries and carne asada that sounds pretty
good that sounds pretty good few years in Vegas but that's pretty awesome but
that's it sounds absolutely fucking perfect thank you the ten dollars zizio
or ZZO I'm from Vegas and it's the best oh you don't think I've ever had
it I've smelled it that's a good ass chain but thank you for the
recommendation also dr. zoot suit five dollars from dr. zoot suit hey
German got accepted to the honors program at my college it's gonna be a
huge pain in the ass thanks for always being funny in a
stand-up guy here's hoping you can help me be sane going forward also
thanks for the birthday wish really brighten my day thank you dr. zoot suit
and congratulations on the honors program hell yeah hopefully you get
some good knowledge from that you get some good experience and translate
that into a ding you know what I mean both eyes light up money symbols that's
what I'm saying but thank you and yeah and of course is your was your name
Ethan as well I only do birthday shout outs for
Ethan's at this point going forward so make that clear from this point now
for now but seriously thank you so much for the five dollars and yeah
happy birthday again much love to you let's get the credits on here they were
a lot of subs I was gone for a while I think a lot of people are holding on
to him so thanks for holding on to him thanks for waiting for me to come
back let's go ahead and show them they're gonna whiz by right now yeah look
at how many people held on to their subs I was gone for like seven or
eight days thanks guys that means a lot thank you everybody still a couple more
bits to do let's get through them DC pro thanks for three dollars I'm not
sure if you said it or not but how was your time off we missed you
greatly thank you for such a mood lifter I'm not sure if that's a
phrase but I needed this to be but I needed this to bring a smile today
hope all is well it was good I've got a lot of stuff done I visited
some family that I'm not gonna see for a long time so a very close
family that because where we are situated in the country now it's gonna
be very hard for me to ever see them so it was good that we got to all be in
a centralized location for four or five days and then the other few days I
was spent doing work on the robot carnival then that's gonna continue to
happen that's pretty much every week here at least a couple days a
week two or three days a week I'm gonna be just completely 100% dedicated
to it I am ready to go I'm excited look mom it's me but thank you DC Pro I had
it was good it's a good time off errorless thanks for the 250 errorless
sorry I don't remember if I already asked this but you ever considered
trying a PC building simulator I yeah I considered it I did but I feel like I
did the PC building simulator like fuckface stream and I think I don't
think I could do like a regular like PC building simulator game because it
would be be Matt I would be actually just putting parts of the PC I wouldn't
be able to do what I would want to do in that season the motherboard he
modded it he can't go back it's true but probably not not on the cards here
spoons for self-defense thanks to the $15 I say terrible what superpower
would you rather have becoming indestructible while T posing or
vomits vomit sentient bees you can control with your brain that one I
would just make them just do everything for me but look look
indestructible while T posing is fine but what are you gonna do you what do
you do with that power you just T pose and just like like fall on your back
you just like T pose and say run me over with your car and like make
money at bars or something I don't get it I bet you I could like
withstand you running me over with your car I'll take that 50 bucks what
do you do with that having sentient bees that you can control with your
brain extends your arms to an infinite length can you imagine an army a swarm
of bees that can go get you a soda out of the fridge that's pretty important
they could carry you up to bed you could just like lie back down in your
bee made bee chair and they would just fly you up and lie you into bed
and you'd get the freshest honey in the world and sell it you'd make
more money than just being the guy that can take a shovel to the head
and not die out like in the alleyway he didn't say the amount of bees it could
be one bee well I mean we don't have that clarification right now I'm
assuming there's gonna be at least two to three hundred that come out of my
mouth be armor no I wouldn't want to harm these bees I'd want to take care
of them no I don't want to be the superpower thing you T pose and are
indestructible all of a sudden you end up in like a government facility
where they're like you're gonna have to permanently be T posed otherwise they're
gonna get you do I have to you have to be standing still while T pose you
just become a statue wouldn't they do the same thing with bees though no
because they're how would they're not gonna know that I would just be the
weirdo that has bees everywhere T posing and being indestructible is not
the same thing as you have bees surrounding you all over the place you
have a lot of bees here if anyone came knocking on the door they would
be like a Toy Story level Andes Cummins scenario it'd be like everybody like
bang I would think about it move out and so half of them would go into like
the forest and a thousand of them would go under the bed like 200 would
fucking just go into like into like the fucking refrigerator or something
for like five minutes a thousand of them would go like pollinate some
flowers would go no no we would have a whole plant and they would just be
bees it would just be bees back into your mouth sir why is your bed
buzzing it's a massage bed I got a bad back and then the dopey fucking idiot
cartoon police officer will look at it and go hmm well okay but you be
careful there son there's something happening out here all right yeah I got
a bad back to is be yes be yes you be careful you get it thank you yeah oh it's
okay don't mind if I use it and then it's like oh fuck he's gonna sit on
the bed and he's gonna realize and then like his phone rings hold on a
second what's that a dog robbing a liquor store down the street oh no
and he like gets into this fucking car and drives away there's always
something that they just pulls him away from what they're doing this is a
freelance police open up anyways what the hell are we doing oh yeah dragon
breath thanks for the 250 I can't think of a witty thing to say German
please make something up for me to say to you and then oh no they say
wait no I got it it's another 250 came in from dragon breath no I got
it peepee poopoo haha forehead pretty pretty good pretty good that's a you
got you nailed it you absolutely nailed it I'm gonna write that on my
tombstone hey groove wizard thanks for the 250 a German I showered okay I said
that wrong hey German I showed my sister the coffee Cheetos chicken video today
and she laughed her ass off until she cried guess your old stuff still
makes people laugh super hard not think it's funny anymore oh such a
fucking idiot okay anyways I showed showed hey I showed my sister and you
know what I anything that can make people laugh that look years ago and
when we made those videos and we did that stuff I thought that shit was
fucking fun and funny I love those old videos so yeah anybody that gets
any joy or happiness or things that funny or things are stupid and
anything you know whatever if you get anything out of these videos or these
frames then it means a lot it's great and I love every second of that so I'm
glad that I'm glad she likes them because I like them too so good stuff
thank you groove wizard for the 250 Phoebus thank you Phoebus for the
five dollars thanks for streaming today my great-grandmother passed this
morning and helped take my mind off that it's okay she lived to be 95 with
a great life and we've been expecting it for a few years 95 that's a long
life on a brighter note I'll be seeing my online seven-year best friend
tomorrow for the first time he's catching a flight here and spending
almost a week and I'm looking forward to it he actually introduced me to your
YouTube channel a few years back turbo heart wow that's I that's I'm happy
for the second half of that comment here hopefully you guys have a lot of
fun and I'm glad that you can have something if you both think that I'm
worth watching and you can get some enjoyment out of that and that's awesome
the first half of your comment though I'm sorry to hear that but 95 that's a
that's a very long long good life so rest in peace to your grandmother thank
you so much for the five dollars and I really hope that you guys have a
good time that was Thievius thank you Thievius we have a couple more
we've got Deva Kitty thanks for the 250 hey German nice to see you
back streaming we've been missing you in recent news my cat got a huge
pustule under their eye and it turns out it was a nasty tooth infection that
does not sound good just that his tooth removed and I got to pick him up
in an hour he's not gonna be a happy kitty but at least he's alive remember
to have your pets dental hygiene checked out every once in a while very
important that's a great PSA teeth in pets dogs and cats they can really
get pretty gnarly and can have a lot of problems so check on your pets
dental health next time that they're at the vet or wherever they you know take
them in for an appointment make sure their teeth are doing alright and if
they need a cleaning then get a cleaning if they need it they need it but
sorry to hear that that happened but also glad to hear that that they're
doing okay I hope but thank you Deva Kitty I wish the best for your cat
and finally to park to park to pack to pock to pock to pock hologram I don't
know why that took me so long thanks for the 250 hey German did you know
you were featured in a haha what the fuck lol streamer fails moment how does
this make you feel it makes me feel great as a bit of a that's what I
strive for I strive to do to be in like a watch mojo calm Ellie LUL
hilarious laugh out loud WTF what the fuck moment of the of the of the month
oh I'm sorry I'm so happy about that that's what I do this for I saw it yeah
that's real it's real and yeah does that does that like qualify as like
did I do it did I do it I did did I do it I did it right like I did it I
made it I was in like a top 10 weirdo video did I make it oh that's
not even the biggest what the fuck moment you've ever had probably not am
I gonna play Baba is you on stream um well you got you put the fish in there
so that's why I'm looking at this comment it's so easy I'm such a bird
brain it's a nice work on that second of all maybe I can't say yes or no I
probably not for at least a little while because there are plans for the
next couple of weeks Dark Souls randomizer cooks are delicious the item
shop story game green screen on core night in a couple of days you get the
idea Sammy Mac season 3 so yeah German
carnival that's gonna be I can't wait for that shit but anyways that's
gonna be it I'll see you guys tomorrow we're gonna do Mario maker 2 for as
long as I can stand playing it and we're gonna move on from there thank
you thank you thank you much love to you see you tomorrow same time take
care everybody see you soon oh let's also raid somebody I haven't done that
in like a few weeks in like two weeks or so since because I was gone who's
streaming right now we got we got we haven't rated Vinnie in a while yeah
let's let's rate Vinnie I'm not gonna I won't be not we not be present for
this rate I gotta go get food but tell them I said that they are a
wonderful awesome person so let's go raid mine sauce say hello for me cue
up if you'd like to go say hello I believe I believe what are they what is
Vinnie doing blood-stained ritual of the night hmm not sure what it is so
yeah don't enjoy that I'll see you guys tomorrow see you later