What's up? Hey, you know shit. I don't want any trouble. I'm already gone.
Thought it was an MPC. Get back or you will get shot.
I thought this dude was gonna sell me like clothes and baggage and potions and shit.
I'm going I'm gonna go that way.
Just this is when you rush the guy. This is when you rush the guy.
Back off.
Don't make me use this.
Okay, you get the idea.
What are you doing?
Back off.
I'm not gonna say it again.
Get the hell out of here.
Thank you.
Do you not hear what I was doing? Like what is this?
I have a gun.
Like are you stupid?
This is one of the ugliest games I've ever played.
Look at the background. It's like a bad TV reception.
I want to like smack my monitor and make it better.
We don't share get out.
This old woman's packing.
Go and tell your friends that Granny's got a gun.
Granny's got a gun. Do I have to kill Granny?
I really don't want to.
Okay, Granny, you know what?
This lady is sitting under a sign that says we won't share get out.
And she's sitting there with a gun.
Why wouldn't you just be inside?
You're just antagonizing people right now.
Are you serious?
And how do you not see me?
And she fucking killed me again.
Fuck you, Granny.
She's freaking out.
I don't feel good about that at all.
I keep thinking about the old lady.
That was terrible.
Not a moment goes by that we're not thinking about you.
I don't care about this at all.
I just slid an old lady's throat.
Too late. You're dead.
I'm not dead.
You asked for it.
Die. I'll take them down.
Why was I looking down?
That's a pretty big drop down there.
Every encounter plays out exactly the same in this game.
Like people just come out of the rafters.
See, look, people just come out of the rafters.
Like it's a play.
All right, it's your cue, guys. Get out. You're on stage left and stage right.
Here you go, he's going to say.
You're in the wrong part of town.
Can they do a different thing?
And watch, I'm going to surprise kill this guy.
Shoot the guy over here.
And then everyone else is going to be scared.
It's like every encounter is exactly the fucking same.
Keep those hands up.
Yeah, I got a gun. That's right.
That's right.
Yeah, yeah.
I do have a gun.
You're stating the obvious.
No, I'm not.
Here's another exciting adventure of Climb the Tower.
Hope you're all excited.
I'm serious.
What the fuck was that?
Oh, boy.
Got to play a negotiator.
Okay, gentlemen, gentlemen, calm down for a second here.
The Tootsie Rolls, there's five of them.
We're going to split them up easily.
Look, you don't have to be that kind of hasty.
Oh, well, I just came into five Tootsie Rolls.
I'm going to take you apart.
I read you loud and clear.
Fuck.
Take it easy, man.
Did he just say goodbye to me?
See you later.
Nice to meet you, by the way.
I'm Angry Guy with Machete Number 48.
I'm scared.
Don't look down.
In fact, just close your eyes.
Open them only when I tell you.
Okay.
No way I can drop that.
Bodies everywhere.
It's your lucky day.
You're pretending to be dead?
Why would you be doing that?
There's no reason why you'd be doing that.
These are the only guys in the whole game that have done that.
When did this become Dark Souls?
I can't even react.
When I get a hold of you, I'm going to take you apart.
Shoot all you want.
I'm bulletproof.
That's not something you should be saying to somebody.
Did you see that guy today?
What guy?
I heard someone saw a guy just walking around the streets.
I thought maybe you saw him too.
A guy?
Yeah, I heard about that guy.
Good thing I didn't see him.
Where are all the guys walking around?
Did you guys hear about that guy?
There was a guy over there.
And it was me.
I'm the guy.
That's right. We're all shocked.
Why don't you go tell your friends that the guy is going to be around for a long fucking time.
That's the whole game?
I feel like I didn't do anything.
I just held my gun at some people.
Carried around a little girl like a kangaroo.
Climbed a couple of buildings.
I did murder an old lady too.
I did murder an old lady so that was pretty significant.