Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary,
and tonight, gonna be playing as the Sniper in a stipulation match. Now, before I get
into this, I want to talk about, uh, it's summertime right now, and the pollen in the
air is making my voice and throat and nose all scratchy and screwy louie, so I do apologize
if in this video it sounds a little raspy, but hopefully this damn pollen goes away so
I can breathe again. Anyways, this is a stipulation match. The series where I take a certain class
and a certain loadout, and I have to follow a very very strict set of rules and guidelines
during the entire video. Now this video, playing as the Sniper, I have to use the Sniper Rifle
and the Jurati only. Now here's the big kicker, that doesn't sound so bad, now does it? The
big stipulation here is I can only no scope with this Sniper Rifle. Now this was requested
a very very long time ago, back when I first started the stipulation series to begin with,
and I've never been able to get a gameplay. It has taken me so long to get this, it is
very very difficult, and I suggest you try it out. If you've never tried something like
this before, jump into a server and just try to do this, throw the Jurati on somebody and
no scope, it is freaking hard. Specifically, because when you throw the Jurati on somebody
and you no scope them, well you know, let's start from the beginning here. When you no
scope somebody in general, it's only going to do about 50 damage. So when you throw the
Jurati on somebody, you increase that number to about 65 to 72, which really isn't that
big of an increase. If you look at the damage spread and the random number generation in
this game, it only ends up being about 20 extra damage. So it turns out, you're better
off not using the Jurati to begin with, if you're going to do this stipulation of course.
Because let's think of it like this. When you throw the Jurati, it takes about 3 seconds
for you to throw the Jurati, get your weapon back up ready to shoot. So after that, when
you shoot somebody, let's say you connect with someone, it does 68 damage. That's fantastic.
But in the time it takes to pull out the rifle after throwing out the Jurati, you could have
potentially already no scoped 2 or 3 times and done more damage than that one Jurati shot.
So with that out of the way, which that kind of goes over the whole process of how this
setup works, I told you it's very, very difficult. This is so hard to do this. I only got maybe
2 or 3 kills in a row before I would get killed by somebody. It's just super, super hard.
And I came to the conclusion, while I was doing this, I'm pretty much a gimped scout.
And here's my explanation for that. So I'm using a hip firing hitscan weapon. The only
other classes that have hitscan weapons are the Soldier, the Scout, and the Engineer.
Now I'm not going to really count the pistol that much, or really any of the melee items,
because those are technically hitscan as well. I'm just talking primary or secondary.
So I have a scatter gun as the sniper, except it shoots a whole lot slower, it does a hell
of a lot less damage, and it only shoots one pellet. And I run slower. I don't run as fast
as a scout either. So when you play this setup as the sniper, essentially you're just taking
the scout, clubbing him in the head with a bowling pin, and then letting him out of spawn
and saying, okay, go kill the red team. And he's like, what time is it? And it really
is no surprise that when you go up against any other class, really any other class, it
is very hard to kill them. And they are going to get you probably 80% of the time. But that
does not mean this is not fun, and should not be tried at least a couple of times. And
it took me, like I said, a while before I got this down, before I got the actual strategy
down. But it is really cool when you kill one or two people like that. It's very interesting,
makes you feel good. So here are just a couple of examples of how I got these kills that
you're seeing. So this soldier hits me with a rocket. I know for a fact he's coming in
the room. And sure enough, there he is right in his face. If I had thrown the Girardi at
him when he came into the room, I probably would have died. He turns that corner and
shoots one rocket at me. I will explode all over the walls, all over all the nice paintings
in that room. There are no paintings in that room, but you get the idea. I would have instantly
died. So killing that scout right there is a pretty good example of knowing when somebody
is trying to get health. Because as you saw, he was jumping all over the place trying to
get over me. And I was certain if I put one bullet into him, I would have killed him.
And those two examples, no Girardi was thrown at all. And that of course goes back to my
previous point of me not using the Girardi and how it's a little easier to not throw
the Girardi. So while this commentary comes to a close, I just want to say thank you of
course for watching. I really do appreciate it. And I will see you guys all next time.
More stipulations are in the works. I think Pyro is going to be the next one. We will
see. So peace guys. I'll see you all soon. And take care, everybody.