Let's ditch him.
Those are some big tires you've got there, Jerma.
They're better to see you with. They're better to eat you with, my dear.
Yep, those are all solid objects. Okay, that is two.
Alright, this is where I want to go. I want to get on this because I'm going to turn around.
We're going to get some big air.
Alright, what's the proper way to change weapons while inside of a vehicle?
Mouse... No, that's not going to do it.
It's mouse scroll outside of the vehicle.
Not sure what it is inside, though.
Whoa, that cop was flying.
Inside the vehicle it is change radio stations.
Ready for some dukes of hazards?
Let's try and catch the mirror with this little leap.
Oh, we didn't get in the air.
That was the leap back there.
I thought it was the leap, but I guess not.
I guess not, huh?
Switch to the driver's seat.
Okay, maybe not.
I probably would have been better off just sitting in the vehicle.
I just spawned and you like flew by the screen.
Why did I spawn at the perfect time? That was awesome.
Oh, how surreal.
I flew you out of the car.
I picked up something that looked remotely like statue charges,
and I clicked the button right as you ran into me.
So, I can only assume that I successfully planted C4 on your vehicle.
You smacked your face on the car.
One of us is going to have a bad day.
A real bad day.
Where's Boo? I see him coming, but I don't see him.
Boo, where you at?
Oh my, police.
Turn around, Boo.
Alright, let's do it.
Watch out for the guy in the Ferrari.
That seriously startled me.
That scared me.
What is blowing up?
What just happened?
Why are there so many explosions?
Apparently, I had my grenade launcher out.
Where are you guys?
I'm trying to play Ski... Wow.
What?
What did you just do?
I'm trying to...
I'm trying to play Ski Ball.
And this is what you do when you play Ski Ball.
Oopsie daisy.
I can't even like...
Who shot that?
What is going on over there?
I just saw that firsthand.
You just crashed into that building.
Yeah, but I landed.
I landed on top of the building.
My character flew through the window, safely, on top of the building.
That was incredible.
Can I still fly this thing?
Is this thing still able to be flown?
My character is trying to find a way.
Maybe that way.
Just get in, you butt head.
Will you just get in?
What is he doing?
He's like so unsure of himself.
I don't know, should I get in?
I don't think so.
No, maybe not.
I get an idea.
I'm gonna move this thing.
I'm gonna just ram into it.
Move.
Get in.
I gotta find you guys again.
I will get in this.
I just need a car.
Like this car.
Hey, I didn't even need to move it.
This moron ran into it for me.
Who would drive directly into a helicopter?
It's gonna be like that, is it, boo?
No.
Dude, seriously, just get in the helicopter.
That's a nice little jump you found.
Alright.
Let's see how this works.
So everybody, keep you guys...
Is it straight down that way or straight down that way?
Straight from where you guys are?
Like right here?
Yep.
Alright, you guys ready?
Let's do it, baby, all at the same time.
Are we going?
Yeah, just go.
We gotta line up.
We're not going fast enough.
Yeah, wait, wait.
Stop right there.
Everybody line up right here.
We gotta get some speed.
Oh, watch out for the police.
This guy's after me, by the way.
This bastard's trying to kill me.
Alright, so everybody line up.
Just like good little boys and girls.
Are these kids in traffic?
Alright, you ready?
What is that guy's problem?
Yeah.
Just like good little students.
Ready?
One, two, three, go.
Oh, the tandem.
Here we go.
All go up at the same time.
See you later, guys.
Oh, there's just all kinds of explosions.
What is happening here?
Oh my god.
I love hitting my face on cars.
It is so...
Whoa!
Please don't kill me.
Why am I running towards you?
I'm trying to jump and grab onto the ledge.
Come here.
I'm gonna get the ledge.
It's gonna be mine.
I'm going to get it.
I'm not careful, man.
You're going to slice off my head.
What happens if I hit you with the blades?
I don't know.
Let's find out.
Where am I?
You just zipped up into the sky.
I'm like...
I don't know.
If I scream, I'm black.
I take it you didn't survive then.
Oh, no.