Hey, yo, what's going on, everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, Monday's edition.
See if I can't hop over and kill this scout from behind to get my first disguise with
the Eternal Reward. Oh my god, I'm like burping and stabbing. Stab! Stab! Playing as the spy
as you can tell. With the, I'll show you the loadout because the loadout is actually pretty
important thing to talk about. The Diamondback, the Eternal Reward, and the Cloak in Dagger.
This was picked by the live stream last night during my choose your own adventure polling
live stream, which was actually pretty fun. I can't wait to do that again because there's
more interesting things that could be done. But let's get right into this here. Let's
see if we can't. Give me another one. Oh, what? He died before I could kill him. Here's the
good thing about the Cloak in Dagger. Ready? You can just sit here. I love it. I can make
a sandwich. I can drink some Dr. Pepper. I had an opportunity to kill that Pyro, but
you know what? Sometimes Dr. Pepper is more important. How come I didn't? Oh, that's right.
You can't run over ammo and get refilled. Yeah! Give me the health. Health. Health. Health.
Maybe the doctor can heal me. Thank you, doctor. Why did I pick up that health? That was a
bad move. So I want to talk about Dr. Pepper for a second because it's kind of a split.
There's a 50-50 split between people liking Dr. Pepper and people hating Dr. Pepper. Now
I'm one of those people that, as you can tell, absolutely loves the soft drink. And no,
I'm not being paid by them. I wish I was. That would be pretty cool if it was like,
hey, Jerma, we're Dr. Pepper. We know you love our drinks. We're going to give you a
thousand cases of Dr. Pepper. I'd be like, shine me up, dude. But that's probably never
going to happen. So that's wishful thinking. But if you think a couple of people in the
comments said, Jerma, I hate Dr. Pepper and I hope you don't hate me. No, no, no. I know
that it's a very, it's a very polarizing soda. And I've just been walking around in circles.
No, I'm real. Look, see, I'm real. Nice job, scout. Nice job. High five. If I had the high
fives on, I would just use it right there. But Dr. Pepper, best drink ever in my opinion. And
well, we're going to win this. They can't even get on the point. Damn. Maybe I should switch
teams. No, I'll stay here for now. That's just, I just knocked this guy off. Gotcha. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Are you seeing this? Heavy, heavy, heavy. Face
stab. Diamondback is not a great option here because there's no engineers early on the other
team. I'll take that though. I'll take that. Let's try and hide somewhere. Whoa. Is that real? Did
I make it to my own spawn? I'm like, Oh, I'm at their spawn. I'm not even. Yeah, I made it to my
own spawn. Hey, look at that. My own spawn. Hey, spawn. Two, three. So let's do another round.
All right. So we change maps. We end up on nucleus. That's okay with me. I thought that guy was
going to jump down. I got him regardless. It's okay. No, no, I just got a disguise. Oh, button
buddy. Bonzi buddy. Does anybody remember Bonzi buddy? That's a very old internet term. I'm not
sure if any of you guys might remember that old school, like 56 K 28.8 K dial up users will know
who Bonzi buddy is. Oh, there's a mini century now. Eternal reward is going to be not so good.
But if I can come here, you got him. He had crits too. He's going to be really mad. That is
definitely a spy. I could probably guess. Now he probably thinks I'm a spy. Spies everywhere.
Spyception. All right. Got my gunslinger out. Let's do this boys. Gunslinger. Hey scout, come
back here. I want to talk to you for a sec. Hey scout, I want to talk to you too. Oh, okay. I was
going to say that made the stabbing noise. That guy. It's okay. Run. Everybody's chasing.
Everybody's chasing. Jeez. I have an opportunity here. No, it's okay. Now I have an opportunity.
Oh, this. No. Get the hells. Get the. All right. Both my fingers just almost went up my nose. I
almost just freaked out. I almost went. That would have been bad. That would have not made for a good
face cam video. Maybe it would have. You know, who knows? All right. We're going to get. That's a
spy. At least I got his disguise. Hey, how are you? How's the wife and kids? Now would be a pretty
good time to utilize the diamond back. Never. I will never get it. I will never get a stair stab.
I probably should have waited a little longer. Oh. The unwanted FX. The X edition. Let's go.
Let's respawn. I'm going to go down here this time because the left area is giving me a little bit
of trouble. Nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody. A lot of people here. Here's the only chance I'm
going to get. I don't want him to put another sentry down. Wait till this pyro gets out of here.
I'm doing a whole lot of sitting still here. Here it is. Three in a row right here. One, two,
three. Now here's the question. Can I get. Oh, I thought that was a sticky from the other team.
Oh, I wanted to get that. Hi. How are you? I'm probably disguised as you. Totally. Yeah, I am.
No, there's nothing I can do. Nothing I can do. Try and make the jump. Make the jump. Oh. Did he
follow me? He did. He followed me. Oh, God. That was a lot of luck in that came into play. I need
the health now. Hoo. Boy, oh boy. That is a spy scout. If I've ever seen one in my life. No,
I thought he just jumped to his own death. Does he have the. He might have the. No, he's not real.
You know what? I will accept that death because I got killed by Marlon Brando 57. Marlon Brando. M
Brando. I love that name. Now here's the funny thing. His name might be like Matt Brandio,
not Marlon Brando, but that's what I saw. We better get him off of this. No, I can't go over
there. Minicentury. Curse you. Curse you, Minicentury. They're gonna get it. I do not approve of that.
Get the scout right here. No, get him. Gonna get a crit. I'll take a crit. Somebody come out of the
spawn. Let's end this. Oh, it's gonna end it right there. Might as well just use it up because I'm
gonna die anyways. And we got it anyways, right? Right? Right? Oh, yeah. All right. That's gonna
wrap it up. Thank you so much for watching, guys. I really appreciate it. And cheers. Cheers, mate.
See you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.