Hello. Yes, I'm currently- I'm currently late, but it's okay. It's a very good reason to be late,
and I'll show you the reason. Well, he's running out. He ran out of the room. Never mind.
He ran out. He was- he was here. Arto. Hold on. Ready? Arto, look. Arto, come over here.
Go! Go over there. Quick, I need to show you on stream.
Arto, what's this? Arto, what's over there? Arto! Hey, Arto! Arto! Arto!
You saw his tail. I- all right, whatever. I was trying to get him to, like, be, like, on camera.
And just, like, bed. It don't matter. All right, go back to the intro. You saw his tail.
See? There he is. Maybe he'll show back up. Arto! What's that? A fishkin? A fishkin!
All right, I'll get out of the way. All right. All right, all right, all right.
Back to the intro. Is Arto a tortoise? Um, he's kind of as fat as a tortoise.
Best in time to see Arto. Yeah, he chased- he chased a little, uh, a little, like, milk boat in here.
Arto is a wise beast, yeah. All right, yeah. We're gonna play more Elden Ring. Hello? Let me just
tweet this. I just did want to show that because people were asking, where is Arto? There- there's
Arto. Now, let's let the intro play out for a minute. Hold on. Okay, I'm back. Okay, so you're
also probably noticing something very important. It's very, very important. Um, there's no drop
frames, and there shouldn't be. I have absolutely no idea why that's been happening, but I think
I've got- I've fixed it. I did, uh, a bunch of stream tests on a bunch of different servers,
and I found a server. I found one of the Twitch servers, a server that is working well.
I've streamed to the same server for, like, two years, and I can't stream to it anymore, I guess.
I don't know why. I have no idea. Nothing changed on my end. It's just, I don't know if the traffic
has started getting routed in a different way, but it gets across your fingers because I think
this is gonna be fine. Please stop playing Elden Ring. Is this your retirement special? What,
like, I'm just going hard and then never coming back? Okay, okay, listen. Games like these only
come around, like, once every half a decade. So, no, look, I'm not gonna go play, like,
fucking bathtub simulator right now. Elden Ring comes along once every fucking half decade,
right? Maybe once every decade. We'll, I promise, we'll go back to, like,
we'll go back to fucking screwdriver simulator in, like, a week, all right?
Well, you play as a screwdriver and you have to, like, roll around and get to checkpoints
only using your body to roll. Like, we'll go back to those. Just give me, just give me some time.
Heart simulator. I actually, it's funny because I, we actually might play Mario Golf,
like, in a couple days or something. That's a, that's a pretty good way to break up Elden Ring,
right? That one person that said you should play Mario Golf, and I was like, no, that sounds like
a dumb idea. Well, I'm just gonna play Mario Golf. So, maybe the next stream after this will
be Mario Golf, and then we'll go back to Elden Ring. But currently very into it, at least into
it enough to keep streaming it. We'll see. I don't, this game is massive, so I don't know
how far I'm gonna get. All I know is right now I'm super interested, so let's go. Guys, ready?
Etterby. Make sure I'm in a good spot. Make sure that the camera's in a good spot.
And, I mean, are we, are we good? We should be. He's still hanging out. He's still hanging out. I
can't promise he'll be here the whole time. He'll probably start running around. He like, he's an
explorer. He, Otto does not have one particular place that he likes. I've had to get like three
different little dog beds because he, I want to be in this room. No, no, no. I want to be in this
room. He'll go down into, he'll go into another room and lie on a pile of clothes. And it's like,
what are you doing in here? I, I could get you a bed. And then a bed, I'll get a little bed in
that same spot where the clothes were. And he sits in that bed all the time. It's like, it's one of
his like bonfires. Otto has literally bonfires all around every place they've ever been in.
And some of them, I got him a really expensive bed and he doesn't like it. I wasn't calling Otto
fat. Is it, no, well you can call Otto fat because he is a little fat. All right. You guys ready?
I'm very happy that the internet seems to be good. I seem to have found the server that works.
So let's hope that continues. You're probably wondering why I have 20,000 souls when I'd had
like two last stream. That's very important. It's because I was testing the internet. So I was just
running around doing like a stream test and just trying to replicate the problem. And the problem
has not been replicated. So yeah, whatever. And I may, I may have like, I may have like fucking,
I may have read a few things. I may have like read a lot. What level am I right now? I am level 73.
Let's take a look. Let's do, let's, you know, let's do this first because we do this every stream.
Let's take a look at what we can, what we can do here. Some of the stuff needs to be updated.
For instance, light fires and knock around that we already did that.
Renes is closed for now. It is no longer closed. We've, we got to it. This is still accurate. This
is still accurate. This is still accurate. And can I, can I get rid of this? Door next to spawn
is blocked shut. Should I just remove that? I feel like that's completely irrelevant. All right,
whatever. So the last thing that I did, I was about to go down here. We're currently doing
Renes quest, which is going to lead us apparently down here. No audio. Let me fix that immediately.
Let's go. Oh, well I already see a huge problem. Face cam is not even in the right spot. It's
already a big problem. That's better. Is it better? It is. Kind of. All right, let's go.
You're wondering the kind of character I'm playing. I'm playing a little bit of intelligence,
a little bit of dexterity, a little bit of int. I think I'm probably about to run into something
that I'm not prepared for right now, but whatever. It's elven ring, baby. You just fucking got to go.
Are you doing a bimbo build? Um, I don't, I don't know. I actually was laughing my ass off.
I was, I was, okay. So before I fell asleep last night, I was laughing. I couldn't stop laughing
because I was thinking about the me strong. Like, no, you have to do one stream as me strong,
but you have to be high on THC. And I just, I don't know. I started laughing so hard about it
because like, imagine this, this fucking, this guy, this caveman, like a loincloth and a big
turkey leg club, just like ate a bunch of berries he found and he's just like fucking fucked up and
high. And he's the guy that can like, he can like kill Margaret. No, they would, that guy would die
instantly. That guy would die without even anyone attacking him. I'm just imagining this like, just
completely hallucinogenic high caveman, just walking around and killing stuff. And it's just
like, why are you in this universe? You should not be in this universe. And like, that's what
would be happening. It would just be, I would be inebriated, I guess in quotes, and I would be
just role playing as this weird caveman. That's how the ancestors did it. Yeah. That's like kind
of fucking weird that that's exactly what happened. If you're this Bush, colorful Bush,
oh, you, I kill you. Like, no, no, no, don't kill me. What are you talking about? Don't hurt me.
I, it was fucking nonsense back then. That's what got me on that is you want to talk about
bimbo gameplay? That's not how weed works. I'm not saying weed, I'm saying like back in like the
fucking, before the prehistoric medieval times, where like cavemen were eating like random
hallucinogenic berries and fucking killing each other. What, of course, that's not what happens
when you, if you have like, what are you talking about? All right, I actually think I can level up.
Let's go. Ooh, that's, that's a clean 10k. That's a clean 10k. 31. Okay. Why is that a clip on
command? I didn't see it. What was it? All right. I, I, I, I think I, I, I, I can't see. I can't see.
He can't see. I can't see. Why am I doing so many mad, mad, mad, mad world references? Maybe it's
because I like watched it recently. All right. I'm going to say, do we just dump intelligence and
try to get it to 50 or do I need to seriously put more points in endurance? I don't, endurance is
not an issue in this game. It really isn't something that's changed in this game. I don't
know what they did or what kind of math or calculations they've been making and Elden ring.
I don't even feel like endurance is the bar. It feels like it's very, very forgiving to a
point where like, you don't even need to put points into it unless you're doing like a heavy
character. Yeah. But it used to be, you would need to put endurance points in because the stamina
bar was hard to manage. All right. How do I get down here? Is it, can I jump from here?
I have to jump. Are you kidding me? I'm going to die if I fall down here. No, I can't do that.
So where do I go? There's a, there's a lip right here. Oh shit. Okay. Old and centipede sick. How
do you like your eggs? I want to know. Uh, over medium. I don't think eggs should be eaten over
easy or sunny side up unless the yolk is, uh, is not, I like a jammy yolk. I do not like a runny
yolk. I find that to be, it gets everywhere. It gets all over everything. A jammy yolk is able,
you get the benefits of having it be a little bit runny, but it doesn't get all over your whole
plate. And you don't need like five napkins to go like this and shit. And I sometimes, I don't know
where, whenever I have a runny egg, it gets all over me. I don't know why I don't, I, I, I don't,
I don't understand how, but it just does like, it'll get like here or something. And then it's
like here and then it's like on a napkin and then it like starts solidifying. No, no running,
no runny yolk. It gets all over everything. Hey, do you want eggs, this, this, and this?
Oh, sorry. What you meant to say was put egg all over all the stuff that I have. I want,
I want egg yolk all over everything that I have on my plate. Now separate it. I like having it with,
I like a jammy yolk because it's still a little runny, but it doesn't get everywhere.
I don't, I don't think that's such a weird take. You eat like a two-year-old.
Enjoying jammy yolks is not a two-year-old thing. A two-year-old would be mommy, I want them
scrambled. So no, I don't think that, I don't think your take is accurate. Oh, I hate these
guys. Geez, your attack patterns are fucking weird. 718 damage. Why would I even normally swing?
Why would I, why would I even swing the Katana if I'm doing that much damage?
Pests. All right, hold on. I can't look at that yet. You're making a mess when you shouldn't.
I mean, honest to God, this is the best. Is this, I don't know how this is scaling with my
intelligence. That magic ability is unbelievably good. It's like, I'm like, I'm actually concerned
they're going to nerf it. It's that good. 700 fucking damage versus like two or three hundred
damage a swing, 300 damage a swing. And then the range is unbelievable. That's getting nerfed.
Sword of the night and fire is better. It's 2000 damage. Really? Holy shit. Well, let's go.
He's, he's such a weirdo. I don't like this guy because he's, you know what I mean?
Sometimes he'll go down, but he doesn't swing. Late game is stupid. So it makes sense.
Uh, okay. That's a good to know. So wait, that's like not crazy. I feel like it is though.
Late game is nutty. Oh, all right. Well, I want these items and I don't care if I die because I,
I'm item run Andy. So I, I don't, I know like some people you've probably seen play this game. Just
look over here and go, I don't give a fuck. Hello. What is this thing? What? Oh my God,
get out of here. Okay. Well, this is like a rot dragon. It really is just that guy that I,
how much health does he have? All right. Well, I can't literally going to die from the rot.
Damn. All right. Well, that's a kind of weird mini boss over there.
Uh, but look at how wise this guy is. He's got a white beard speckles. They just,
there aren't many bosses now. They're just normal mobs. Well, that's kind of nuts.
I got the items. So I'm wrong. What's going on? What's going on here? Come on. Fucking game
crashed. The game just literally crashed. I hope that's not. No, my, it should be fine.
Are we getting Fs? Well, we're getting, that was a hardware F because that almost just
crashed my whole computer. That was not an internet F. Yeah. That was a, that was a hardware F.
And this is like not running well either. This is like bad. All right. Well, whatever. Yeah,
I know, I know, I know. Whatever. Laugh my ass off. Elden Ring sucks. I think so. I just,
where the hell, where am I? Why am I over here? Why did he put me over here? What? My souls are
over there. Yeah. My souls are down here. What level am I? 74. Yeah. I think the game like put
me in a different place because I died. I, I, this is exactly where I died. The game like
crashed and like dumped me in another location. Oh well. All right. Let's go. Yeah. I mean, there
are, there are some technical issues sometimes with the game, but whatever. Not going to stop
me from fucking playing. I don't even care about these souls really either. Was it like 5,000,
2,000? Would you say that you loved it? Oh, it's actually 10,000. Nevermind.
Uh, would you say that you love this game? Um, I don't think I'd be playing it as much as I am
if I didn't really, really easy for you guys to know that considering, uh, considering, um,
how much I play games on this screen, me playing a video game for more than four hours and going,
yeah, I'll play that tomorrow. Oh my God. Not paying attention. I played this game for more
than two screens in a row, which means it's like the best game that's ever been made.
There you go. Don't fucking crash again. Yeah. No, we're good. All right. No, okay. Come on.
These guys hurt a lot. What does it, what's the damage they're doing? They thrust. If German
nine eight five, that's me, is going to play your game for more than 10 hours on stream,
you've got something really special, real special. And that does not hold on. Let me make,
I got to be clear to you guys. That does not mean that I have some incredibly high standard
like, wow, you impressing me. Wow. What a feat that is. No, I'm saying that it's so difficult
to hold my attention on anything that you holding my attention is ridiculous. Like is
really actually impressive because I stuff does not hold my attention that well. And it's not
because it doesn't matter how good or bad something is. I usually move on very quickly
to the next thing. These guys, I don't like these fucking things. What are the ego? No,
I'm saying, I'm telling you, it's not an ego thing. Okay. These guys do this. How many souls
each? Jesus. That's a lot. You assert you refer to yourself in the third person. Yeah. I'm not,
as a joke, I don't actually do that. That's, that was a huge burp. And if I opened my mouth,
I would have threw up. What a bad attention span. I do have had. I've had attention issues
my whole life, man. Even going into my forties, it's going to be, I'm not, I'm not 40 yet,
but you know what I mean? It's going to get even. I don't know. You know, I'm really concerned.
You wonder what my major concerns are kind of growing up and getting a lot older, older.
So I have really bad attention problems. I had my whole life. I've taken medication for it
decades ago, right? I've always had, I had issues that way. When you get older, you slow down. So
when I'm into my like mid forties into my like mid fifties, as my brain starts to slow down,
am I going to be able to like to do it? Am I, am I going to be able to think about anything?
Like I'm going to have like bad ADHD and like dementia at the same time.
Like as everybody kind of slowly goes to that, like kind of like degrading brain into the like
your fifties and sixties, that's going to be really strange. I'm going to, I'm going to make
sure I drink. I'm going to take a ton of vitamin E. Like I'm going to make sure I'm going to eat
fish like every day. Like seriously, take care of yourselves. What am I doing? I just aggroed the
whole camp. What am I thinking? I'm good. Attention deficit, hyperactivity, dementia.
I mean, I'll be honest. That seems like fuck. Like I don't know. I'm going to make sure I'm
going to take, like, I'm going to make sure I'm like eating right. Jesus. What the fuck? I thought
he was behind the, I thought he was behind the pillar. I actually thought he was behind the
pillar. I changed that by the way. Made that to heal over time instead of the stamina because
stamina is not a problem. You shouldn't be eating four McChickens. Guys. Okay. It's time for defense
mode Andy. Just because my McDonald's order is a little elaborate is a little excessive.
That's what's going on. I thought that was an item. What's this? I don't order it every day.
No, I'm not. I don't want to go down the fucking river. That'd be so. Okay. Huge missed opportunity
from FromSoftware. If you died, just showed up on screen right now. Just. Oh, that would be so funny.
What a missed opportunity. Unfortunately, I actually didn't want to go in there.
You eat McDonald's every day. Now what? He eats more than my whole family of five.
I am not eating that much McDonald's. Where the fuck am I? This is going to be like a boss.
Please give me a bonfire so I can at least level up before I lose all these souls.
Look, I love McDonald's. It's McDonald's is the absolute best.
Nothing will ever compare. You know, it's kind of weird. I've been, I've been to five-star restaurants.
I've eaten five-star meals, but the way that my brain reacts to eating, like if I'm hungry,
a double cheeseburger from McDonald's, nothing compares. Like that, if I'm really hungry,
double cheeseburger from McDonald's. Bam. That four seconds. One, two, three, four. Nothing
compares to that. And like, Oh, what's this? What's this? Oh, parsley dusted, um, chicken thigh,
uh, I don't know. Whatever it is. And like, Oh, interesting. Interesting flavors.
Into the napkin. What do you have? Fuck. I don't, there's no bonfire.
There's a statue, but I'm going to lose 35,000 souls. No, I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing it. I have a, I have a level. What would I throw a level away?
That's an extra point in intelligence. Now I'm just going to run past everybody.
Do you have matcha today? Of course I do. Like there's, I would assume at this point,
there's more matcha powder fragments than red blood cells in my body. The last like two weeks.
Look, I'm in a public school bathroom. What are you talking about? Like right now? I don't know
many public school bathrooms that have like shelves with like video games on them, dude.
Okay. Does this actually kill you? I need to see because if it doesn't, then I'm just going to do
it. I'm just, no, it's going to kill me. Heat seeking missiles. Yeah. Then they shoot a thousand
of them. They're talking about where the game is right now. Oh, that seems what public school
bathroom. I swear to God, if that kills me again, crap, it was a chest here.
Scorpion stinger. Oh, that looks cool. Whatever that is. It's definitely not intelligence,
but it's probably so cool. I got to remember this for a future playthrough because that probably
would really like this. It's a, it's a dagger. Also Scarlet rot buildup. Oh, and it's got,
and it's got fuzz. This thing's hairy. This is awesome. And it does like, it's like stinger
flash. Oh, I like, want to use this. That's so cool. Scorpion. Very cool. Unfortunately,
that's the kind of character I'm playing. That's where it is. If you're wondering
the grand cloister, it's the weapon info. Weapon info is fashion from a great scorpions tail
glistening with Scarlet rot, a ceremonial tool used by heretics crafted from the
relic of a sealed outer God. Okay. So that's all I need to do there. Now I hope the flask
allocation is good because this looks like a boss. So we're just going to go, I don't care about
those souls. Who cares? Go get in the coffin. It's literally like a thousand shares. It's
literally just a thousand shares. It doesn't matter. How many shares of that do I own of this?
What do I mean shares? Stock Stanley. Okay. Here we go. Double headphones going in. Time for me
to pay attention. I appreciate everybody's help. I appreciate everybody's, you know,
Hey dude, you're doing pretty good. Hey dude, you're doing awful, but I'm going to have them
tuning you out for the next two or three straight minutes. There's a statue here so I can come back.
I have two, eight and two. I want, hopefully it's enough. I don't know.
Uh, in the astell natural born of the void. Why does everybody have one of those?
Can I, can I complain? Why does every boss have that move? Have they all have it?
They're like, welcome to the arena. Boom. This thing is great. It's like a whole solar system.
A lot of big explosive AOE. You have to jump and hit. Yeah. You're going to jump.
You're so big. I can't even. Oh my God. Okay. So that does one, two, three. Jesus. Okay.
You have so many moves. Do you have that too? Okay. That's not magic. That's not magical at all.
That's not magical at all. That was not magical at all. This is crazy looking boss though. Okay.
Well, very interesting. This is probably one of the cooler looking bosses. I think that they've
made, there was a tier list for interesting boss look like design a lot longer than that.
I think this guy would be up pretty high. That's oh man. That's hard. It does like it comes down,
but it doesn't hit Jesus. Okay. He goes like before he does it. Fuck. I was at a stamina.
Oh, maybe, maybe I shouldn't hit him in the face. Maybe I should hit him like inside. Oh my God. He
doesn't like that. Oh, okay. He's got like, like 15 move, 20 plus moves and counting.
This is going to be fun. He's just a nerd's rope. Oh yeah. Wicked coal dude. He's a nerd's rope with
like fangs. I think you can outrun it. Let me see if you can outrun it. Nerd's rope. Maybe like in
his back legs. I think, I think facing him head on is way too dangerous. Maybe I can like break one
of his little, he's got these like little crab legs. I should be able to break them. Maybe I can
stun him. How are you supposed to get the fuck away from that? That's an instant kill. Of course,
of course this is Elden Ring. Every major boss has an instant kill move. Forgot. I forgot what
video game I was playing. Okay. I wonder, can I dodge that when he does it? Like right before
he does it. Maybe. I cannot use the horse here. Unfortunately, I'm still going to go for the legs.
I think the back legs, he's got these little tiny little like lobster legs. I think I can probably
like hurt them or break them. I don't think so. Maybe not. It's definitely his head. It's absolutely
his head that hurts the most. That little right in his cracked skull. Jesus. Fuck. Couldn't see
where his arm was. I wonder how much, how much magic damage I'll do. Let's try it. Oh baby.
That's a lot. Shit. Fuck. We're going now? Hey. All right. All right. All right. Where?
What the fuck? Hey, yeah. That move sucks. I have that too. It's terrible. Shit. What the fuck is
that thing? Oh, fuck you. Oh shit. In my pants. Oh my God. It did it fucking three times. Oh my God.
It does it three times again. Get out. Get out. Don't, don't be over here. Get away from him.
There's no reason to be there. Okay. That's what I was talking about. We're fine. Holy shit. What?
Don't die from that. Don't die from that. I got enough. I got, I don't have enough.
He appeared fucking behind. I didn't know where he was going. All right. Well, I, here's the thing.
Here's the thing. I can get him. I should have brought an extra. I'll get him. I thought I,
I thought I had him. All right. I'm getting it, but that sucks. It's too fast. All right. Let's go.
I might, if I don't beat him in the next couple of tries, may. Dude, what the fuck are you doing,
man? Oh, fuck. Oh, those explode. Breathe. That shit took up the whole script.
Oh, fuck you, dude. It's so hard to know. I don't think I'm dead. I'm alive. Oh my God. Fuck that
move, dude. Like he just, he appears fucking somewhere behind you and it's like you lose
lock on and he's just right in your fucking face. That move is so stupid. Like, come on.
That's fucking dumb. That's stupid. Cause like where the fuck even is he going to be? He's
behind you. You lose lock on and then he's just right on your ass. Like, dude, I just,
did I just spam dodge? He'll, he'll, he'll catch me. It's such fucking horse shit.
I don't care. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. It's just going to come down to like,
when he does that shit, I guess just no matter where he is, just like instantly dodge.
I don't, I, I don't, I have no idea. Oh fuck. I did that twice in a row. Oh, I'm just tilting.
It's over. Yeah, I'm just tilting. I'm just full tilt because that fucking dumb grab move.
The gravity. No, the gravity move is not instant kill. It's just like an 80%.
The grab move might actually be instant kill or at least like 95% or something. I don't want to have
30 vitality. That was the one too. It's just so fucking frustrating. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Oh, I didn't even look and I fucking got there. Where are they?
Hey, where'd he go? What the fuck is that thing? Trying to bait out the face.
Fuck. Where the fuck am I? Oh, bro. I'm alive. I'm going to be alive. I'm going to be alive.
I'm going to be alive. What's happening? I'm against the fucking goddamn skybox wall.
I'm against this. I'm against the wall. This is wall. Oh, fuck you game. No.
Oh, the game's fucking easy. It's not even a hard game. Instant kill moves are stupid. Delete them.
Patch them out of the game. Instant kill moves are fucking deleted from the game. Instant kill
moves. You should never have put those in the game. They're fucking stupid. Nobody likes them.
Nobody, not one person likes them. You remember when Jay Leno used to walk around on the street
and be like, oh, hey, so what do you think about like this? Hey, what do you think about like Chevy?
Right? No, no, no. If it was like, oh, hey, I got a question for you. What do you,
in a video game, if something could kill you in one hit instantly,
do you like it? No, no, and I don't know. No, Jay, Jay Leno, I don't like it. Oh, well,
we got another person here. What do you think about instant kill moves in games?
I fucking hate them. They should never be in a video game. Oh, yeah, we're getting
interesting responses. I hate them. It's like one little move and it's like dad, dad, dad, dad,
dad. Even if it's not, I know that it is though. It is. Your health is just too low. He doesn't
have any instant kill moves. Okay, if I chop you up in a meat grinder and the only thing that
comes out and that's left of you is your eyeball, you're probably dead. You're probably going to,
not you, I'm just saying, like if somebody were to like push you into a meat grinder
and like one of your finger bones is still intact, they're not going to pick it up and go,
well, see, yeah, it wasn't an instant kill move. You still got like this part of your
finger left. No, I'm not going to put you into a meat grinder. I'm not going to put you into a
meat grinder. No, I'm making a reference to the fact that like if I, like if I were to get like
fucking killed, I don't know. You know what I'm saying? If, okay, if you were to, okay,
we're going to take humans out of this. If alien glob glob glob go one fucking shoots a disintegrating
ray at alien glob glow two, if there's only fucking teeth left, it's, it's fucking, you're dead.
You're dead. If I were to put you in a meat grinder. God damn it. That's so fucked up.
You understand what I'm saying though. I'm not actually saying I'm going to put somebody in a
meat grinder. God damn it. Let's go. What's the context? The context is if he does 95% of your
health in one move, it's, it's still the same because who I want you to find, you all do me a
favor. Find somebody that plays this game that has a hundred percent HP. No one's at 100% HP,
100% HP. Usually people are at like 80 or like 90 or like 85 or nobody. You can never get it right.
A 90 plus percent damage move is, is effectively killing you. It's you're dead.
MonkaS, I agree. I fucking, I had to use the meat grinder analogy, but it works.
Still not an instant kill. All right. Well, that was fun. I wonder if I should start doing this.
40. Let's play. Don't grind me up. No, whenever, okay. Whenever I say you, I mean like
collectively, like a thing, right? Like you don't like, let me tell you something. You know,
like I say, you know, like, you know, I don't actually, I don't actually know if you know,
I'm just saying you like, yeah, like, you know, you collectively, you know, you like if you,
you know, if you did, you know, if you trust me, no one's going to be cracked. I promise.
Now what do I do? He means you specifically. I can go, I can go back. So what did I get? This
is part of the quest or, oh, there's a place I can go. You're going to play the new destiny too.
That joke was like three months in the making and it already happened. So I'm sorry. You're
never going to see that ever again. Hey dude, like, um, it's actually not an instant kill move.
If I want to put you in a meat grinder.
Sorry. I didn't, I was just talking. I was like, I was speaking collectively, like just
like a thing that happens. Oh man. God damn it. I, I'm going to take this to the grave though.
Like 95, sorry, like 95 plus percent damage moves. I gotta move on. I gotta, I gotta,
I'm sorry. I gotta move on right now. I have to, I'm going to move on right now.
So we're going to continue to play. We're going to just keep playing. Elden ring,
Elden ring, no meat grinders. Nobody's going into meat grinder. Like I beat the boss. It was hard.
He was crazy. I got a little tilted in the middle there, but no, there's no meat grinders anymore.
Look at all these pigs. They're actually interesting. Stop it. Stop it. Okay. This is,
I actually wanted to explore this area. Why don't we explore? Let's take a quick look around.
Oh, look at this thing over here. We're going to mark some stuff on the map because that's what
we do in Elden ring. Let's check out some stuff. A new zone. There's a few places I think look kind
of interesting here. Uh, there's a farm over there too, but guys, I think we're going to check this
out first. I'm going to check that out first just to see what's over here. We'll start with, uh,
this one. I think this is a church. Potentially get a sacred flask. What the fuck? I'm not,
I don't want to fight you. I don't want to fight a glint stone dragon right now.
I just had a boss fight. Who did you just kill? Was that an NPC? I hope that wasn't an NPC. Oh my
God. Oh my God. That's a glint stone dragon. Of course, magic's not going to do well against a
glint stone dragon. What was I thinking? This is a really bad place to fight a dragon.
Actually, I don't know what's going to happen here, but okay. That hurt. Am I fighting this
thing? I'm still shook up from the last one. I do need my souls though. I want to see what's in
there. Put them in the meek rider. It's going to take a while for, uh, I think this community
to get over that one. Oh, it is a cathedral. Starlight shards. Starlight shards. Starlight
shards. Starlight shards. These are everywhere. These, these are rare. They're purple lights.
That means it's rare. Meat grinder apology. Okay, so let's get all these. Why not?
These are a pretty rare resource. Starlight shards. I'm going to look it up in a minute,
but let's get this. I already, dude, I wouldn't mean to apologize. I spent the last like 20
straight minutes apologizing. We're talking about me grinding people, but my point still stood
very solid, I think. Very cool. That was what was here. Ooh, wait a minute.
There are ruins under here? There is. What? Am I dead? Am I going here?
There's a ledge. There's a ledge. There's a ledge. There's a ledge. There's a ledge. There's a ledge.
And I have Starlight. I'm going to put that on. Okay, let's do it. What just keeps dying here?
Oh, thank God for Starlight. What is this thing? It's a hand. It's one of those fingers.
Clear ring. This guy, all that's left of this guy is his fucking hand.
All that a kill move? Is that an instant kill move? Or does his hand still exist?
All right, I'm moving on. No more talking about this. I'm kind of afraid of this. Should I put
the ring on? I don't want to put the ring on. All the ring rates will come get me. I feel like this
is bad. Wait, that's Rena. Oh, I thought I was going to take that ring that she had on and take
it off and put it on me. And look, this is so out of place. I look like I belong in like a fucking
Saturday morning funnies page in the paper. I don't belong in this scene. Oh, so Rena's back.
To the night sky. It is there. I shall find mine order.
Is this it? Travel the path of the Lord. And once all is done, we shall see each other
once more. All right, very cool. Where's my reward? Here it is. Dark moon great sword.
Dude, this is so but 16 strength. What is this? It's this. It's the from software weapon.
This is how you get the moonlight great sword. It's the from software weapon. We found the
from software weapon. OK, let's take a look at it. It's very pretty, isn't it? It is.
It is very pretty.
That does not use manna, by the way. How long does it last? Oh, looks really cool here.
I don't think you have an option here. I mean, I think I do have an option considering I need 16
strength, which I'm going to have the intelligence for it is the intelligence weapon. Yeah, but
intelligence weapon. Yeah, but but this is too. You can just two handed.
Yeah, but then I'm essentially obliterating all my sorcerers.
But on the strength talisman, this actually lasts a while. All right,
so what happens if it's just it's just a normal 200? OK, I have some decisions to
make because this is a big deal. I'm going to give you one reason why I'm not too keen on
using this item because for the entire video game, I have been I have these swinging patterns
down with the one handed and even two handed. It's a lot faster. I don't know. I'm going to
have to get used to this all new swing timing for the big two hander. It's very cool. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. It's a slow swinger. Yeah, I don't know. Well, let me finish this up.
Let me just continue to do what I was doing here. That also is that going to make me heavy?
This is important. Guys, I unless I don't have anything in my offhand, this is heavy. It's a heavy
load. I'd have to start putting points in endurance. I can't have an offhand unless I respect. I don't
think this is happening. I am more inclined to go into this than I am to that. This thing is pretty
cool as well. It does this thing. This thing's awesome, but I don't know because that's strength
into not decks in, but it does. It does skill with decks. It does. And it's frost. All right.
Well, we're going to have to do a lot of soul searching here. I think. Yeah, it's going to
take some because this is what I'm going to take into the end game. Whatever I'm taking to the
second half of this game is what I'm going to be using for the whole game. So this is going to be
interesting because I actually don't know what to do here. But in the meantime, let's do this.
Anything else down here? That was really cool. Quest line. In the meantime, I can go further.
I can go further down. Can I? I can. Wait, didn't I come from down? I think I came from this way.
Yeah, okay. I did. What if I go back to Ren's rise? That's a good idea. You're going to get
plenty of materials to spec several weapons really high. Yeah, but if this is like the other
from software games, and I'm imagining it is because instant kill move, if it's like the other
from software games, there's probably only like three or four of like the plus 10 or plus 20,
whatever item. So I'm imagining there's probably less than five or less than maybe even it was.
There was two in each playthrough of Bloodborne. I remember like the super gigantic plus 10 item.
I imagine there's probably two or three. There are more than four is four. Okay,
so it's not like the other ones. Because I remember the other ones. It was like,
you're going to find maybe two of like the super Titanite mega slabs. And that was it.
Okay, so there's enough. All right, well, then it then it's not and I'm not worried about it,
then. I want to keep exploring this area though. And that I didn't. Yeah, I want to check out some
of this other stuff. Because I'm probably not coming back to this island ever again.
But if you're wondering how to get the moonlight great sword, like you don't feel like looking at
a guide. It's Ren's quest line. That was a long winded journey. Get us to a spot that I'm not
entirely sure. I don't know if I wanted to use it. Okay, well, all right. Oh, golden. Oh,
is this one single person? It's one single person. Holy shit. Yeah, I did not take that seriously
enough. Why did I start freaking out? Where's this going to take me? I just like Don Shalani
just was doing that. Okay. Um, where's this going to take me? Should I do it? Was there a statue?
Or is this going to take me back way before? I don't know. I don't remember. Okay. Yeah,
it's here. Well, all right. No, do not do not just nonchalantly walk through that area. I want to,
I want to be in there. Ooh, that's pretty nice. All right. All right. I want to go underground.
There's definitely a dungeon here that I'm going to do. And after I do this island, I'm going to go
do a main story place, which I'm going to go to Caleb, I think, and go up from Caleb. That's my
plan. You don't like my plan and don't care. All right, let's take this more seriously.
Oh, my. Okay. I got stuck in the wall. Okay. You can't even be in the game. He's just like
fucking out and freaking out. Okay. Damn. All right. Well, let's try this again.
Let me get off the horse. I feel like maybe that's far better. Or is it though?
So many people spawn here. All right, let's go. Here's all right. Here's behind you.
Jesus. Oh, he's making the bird sounds by the way. He's making the from software bird reverse
suck in breathing sound. Holy shit. Dude, I don't even know when I should attack him.
Strobe into a fucking telephone pole. Fuck man. Where is he? I'm alive. But no, Jesus. Okay.
I want to kill this guy just because he's fucking irritating. Get off the horse. Oh, I think that
is guaranteed death. You see how fast this guy moves around and he like teleports. No way you
fight this guy off the horse. I'll dodge roll once and get killed. Dude. Oh, my God. This is
harder than some of the bosses. I'm parry him. I don't think there's anything to parry. Look,
get off the horse, please. I'm telling you right now. I'm going to die in literally one second.
If I get off the horse, but I'll do it. I can't even fucking take a second to drink.
I can't even take a sip of my fucking flask. I wish I could summon a friend here.
All right. We're going to stay on the horse because there's no way I'm going to reliably
and he'll teleport behind me and kill me and you'll have a complaint and I don't think you
want to hear me complain. He literally blended into the ground. I can't even get up. What the
how did he get over that? How did he get over the wall? All right. I'm, I'm thinking I'm taking
out my, I'm thinking my, my boy, my boy, all legs coming out here. No, you know what?
Let's bring out the boys. We can be annoying too. Oh shit. Where is he? Where is he? Oh my God.
Ah, I can't, which enemy is he? No, get away from me. There's so much fucking shit in the way too.
Like seriously, like how am I supposed to this enemy? Wait, can he get, can he get up here?
Yeah, he can. Yeah. Mother fucker. When can I even attack him? Fuck off. What an asshole.
What an asshole of an enemy. Oh, good thing I got the ghost glove or no, no, no, please.
Ooh, there's a, uh, one of those things. Wash your hands. I, what do you want me to do?
Okay. I'll wash my, I'll wash up in a minute. What? I'm, I'm, I'm sitting here.
Wait, you guys want me to go wash my hands?
Should I go wash my hands? I'm only, no one's touching this besides me and I'm going to clean
it with alcohol wipes after this. Don't worry. You must, should I go wash my hands?
What if I, what? No, this is where this is, this is where this goes wrong. If I go wash my hands
right now, I've grabbed onto this. I need to wash the controller. Did you get it? I have to
wash the controller too. I'm going to do that afterwards. My monitor is not covered. It's just,
it looks fine. All right. I want to do this. I don't know why this is here. What? What was that
for? What was that for? That took a long time. Why did that take so long? All right. Something
cool. Let's go. It's really an Amber medallion plus two. Holy shit. That's a hundred percent
more mana vastly raises maximum FP. Wait. Oh, 10. Why is this even in the game? This is the plus
two version of this. How many levels is 11 FP? So it's 10%. I mean, that's maybe one point,
maybe two points. Maybe I don't, I wouldn't consider that fast. About two levels.
That's three or four. It's three or four points. That's, that's really not a big debt, but how
good some of the other talismans are in the game, there's no reason to put that on ever.
I could see how that would maybe be okay if you were putting like more than 20, 30 plus points
in mind, but why would you ever do that? I can't think of a reason why you'd have more than like
40 points in mind. It's fine. I used to, I used to key for that. You said this fake wall is there.
Are you fucking with me? Yeah, you're fucking with me. Please. Can you do a quick
Seinfeld routine about the word vast? What even is vast? What's that supposed to mean? Vast.
Just say big, just say large, say big. Why do we need names for so why do we have so many names
to describe what is effectively big? Just say big. Oh my god, it's bear. That was horrible.
He screamed at me. All right, what was it? There was a couple other places I'm going to go. I'm
going to go here to, uh, he vastly underperformed. He didn't perform well. He largely underperformed
the vast ocean. It's a big ocean. The ocean's big. That's a good one. It really is.
As you know, he would like stay that way. He would move his hand, move his hand like this.
I don't want to fight this thing. I was going to look at the rooms. Is there something under here
that has to be, there has to be something here. That's not just look at. Yeah, of course.
There's something here underneath, under the ground, up above something. Oh, we already.
Yep. Yep. Nevermind. I already did this. I would do this. Oops. Sorry about that. All right,
we need to go here and here and okay. Yeah. One and four. Let's go. Oh, yuck. That's going to,
I'm going to die if I do that. Don't be stupid. I'll go to one and do it. It's Donald and it's
going to be. Is your shirt drenched? I don't think so. It probably isn't. I haven't been
playing for that long. Just de-aggro please. My shirt is not drenched. It's fucking fine. See.
What? Is this a different dragon? Why is he here now? What? Why are there two? Why are there two
of them? Is this a different person? Well, that, you're not fighting me. Is it a different dragon?
This one doesn't have a health bar thing. Okay. That's just an enemy, but what?
That one doesn't have. Oh my God. It is a different dragon. They're everywhere. What?
I'm sorry, but excuse me. Holy shit. Don't die from that. I'm fine. The island of dragons.
All right. Now we go this way. Not these guys again. No, you know what? Fuck off.
No, I'm not fighting any of these people. I do like the
they make a really cool sound. What are you doing here? This is the island of mini bosses. Okay. I'm
smithing stone. I'm safe right here. Oh, he's coming in. He's getting in. He's getting in.
Oh fuck. He got in. He got in. Okay. Now we can't get out. This is perfect.
What the fuck? This island might be too hard for you. No, that was not that sound. That was
a different one. There's got to be a better way I can get down here. I don't want to go all the
way around. That was not the dude. That was the crystal people. The guy with the spear that goes
wham, wham, wham. That's what he does. It's a different character. Grow up. Okay. Now I'm
going to wrap around. I'm going to be telling us to grow up. It should be you that grows up.
I'm already grown up. I'm a grown up. You're not a grown up. I'm a grown up. I'm just a
spell off the edge. I've got to go all the way around. There's no safe way. And what? Be old
like you? I'm not even old. You can say that in five years. Because then, you know, I'll be into
my early 40s. But I'm not old right now. I'm a young man. I'm into skateboarding. Okay, I don't
want to get killed here. That's 20,000 souls. I got to go get it. God, I can't just leave it.
That'd be such a, but like what a like fucking idiot that would be. Motherfucking idiot. That
would be if I didn't go get these souls. What level is the character? 74? 25? Why are my souls
over here? Didn't I die like way the other way? Oh, I forgot to get eye drops. There's other items
that I got to get there too. Remember, you're stuck in your ways. Um, I don't think so.
I thought he just jumped off the cliff. He did. Can they not jump off the cliff? Will he not fall
off? They like programmed that in. Don't fuck with me. I just want the stones. He's just right behind
me. Okay, now we go down to the church because there's definitely something there. I'm not
fighting this guy. Are you actually going to follow me down here? What's the Elden Ring? Does it let
you fly? I don't think you can fly when you put on the Elden Ring. I'm not even sure what the
Elden Ring is. The Elden Ring might just be a like theory or something like a myth. It probably is
no Elden Ring. How could something like that powerful be able to exist? Okay, I believe so
here we are. What is this? We have a Bobby Hill impression. I'll try. Yeah. Hey dad, I'm sorry.
I can't, but I tried. Seek three great wise turtles. Seek three wise turtles.
I hate having to face game one. Could they be anywhere on the whole island?
Because if that's the case, then I'm just going, I'm just going to fucking... Does this count? No,
this is not, this is not a magical turtle. It could be anywhere on the whole island. Are you kidding me?
They are everywhere. They can be anywhere on the whole island. Dude, there's not a chance I'm going
to do this. Three. Okay, I need to find three. Oh my goodness, I found one. What am I supposed to do
about it? I can't target it. I can't target it. That's so sad. Oh, there's one. If they're that big,
then they have to be around there then. All right, I'm just going to go around the perimeter.
What a pain in the ass. I also need to do this too. People are going to think I'm nuts, but I don't
care. There was one here. I'm going to just mark where I've been because I will just walk in circles.
There's nothing here. All right, where's this on the map? All right, there's nothing here or there.
Okay, nothing here. I don't see anything over all the way over here.
Yeah, that's nothing, man. You're stressing me out, dude. And this should be not stressing you
out because I'm actually marking where I've actually seen. Look at the other towers down
here. So why are you assuming that they're all on the edge? I don't know because they're huge
and that's really I can't think of any other place to hide them. It's one of these things.
Okay. Okay, so take a look at this. I can see this whole line. I don't see anything on this edge.
Nothing here. Oh my god. Fuck this. This is going to be such a pain in the ass.
I removed this. I don't want to individually. It's gonna be such a huge pain in the ass to
individually remove all these. I don't want to remove all markers. I have stuff marked that I
don't want removed. Okay, we're gonna go over there. But this thing is here. Let's go. What's
this? It's a boss, right? Electro black knife ring leader. Holy shit, dude. Jesus. Okay. Well,
that was interesting. Okay, didn't feel like didn't feel like he wanted to stop attacking.
I feel like this is a backstab encounter. Maybe like a backstab. 18k souls gone. They're right
here. They're right there. All right, this guy's got some moves. We'll try the we'll try some of
the intelligence explosions. It's pretty that's pretty good. I think I can get a backstab. But
holy fucking moly. Holy shit. All right. So when he jumps in the air like that, that's when you go
around. That's when you get the backstab. You dodge through it. And then wham. Dude,
he's a cool dad. This is cool. This is kind of like, oh, hey, look, this is a boss right here.
Well, I didn't get it. I don't think I was close enough. We're done. Wow, that that lasts a long
time. That lasts a lot longer than I thought it did. Dude, fucking stop swinging at me.
No, I got it wrong. No, I went for it. All right, I'll get it done. Yeah, you can't.
You cannot get the amount of iframes needed to dodge that attack. So you have to run.
Summon somebody. Not until I understand what this guy's all about. They don't seem to give
you very many opportunities to attack this guy. I can't summon. Oh, I think this is going to be
one of those fights where I just run away. Damn, but I had it. Jesus, what the fuck?
That's huge. That's a massive area. Okay. Yeah, I'm gonna try parrying a little parry shield.
What shield is the best parry? I'm not sure it matters. You need a buckler. Don't go there
without touching that. I'll try him one or two more times. Try parry him. He just he's very
elaborate with his moves. He does a lot of just regular swings. I wonder how effective it'll be.
Let's find out. That was weird. Cute. Time to do that. Jesus, man. He's just it's just almost no
opportunity to attack him. If I could get the parry is just whatever. I just want to get a
successful parry so I can know if I can do it later. You should just shoot him. Oh, yeah, I like
Elden Ring added like machine guns and like like handguns. Got that wrong.
Swing timings are so all over the place. It's like it's hard to even understand when to do this.
I could try the guard. No, the guard parry would be horrible because if I did I'm just he just
attacked me and kill me. I just want to parry him once and that will be my victory and then I'll
leave. I just need to parry him one time. That's how I win this encounter. That's a victory for me.
I thought I was gonna die. I thought he was gonna dash forward. No fucking way, dude. This guy's
unbearable. No way. Five more attempts. That's it. I just want to parry him. Five attempts to
parry him. That's not what you're betting on, I don't think. Just one parry. All right, get over
here. It looks like a parry once. That looks pretty good. That looks pretty good. Didn't it,
though? I don't understand. I don't know how you get away from that. I really don't get it.
What do you do? Good fucking luck. I didn't mean to press the button twice. I just did.
No fucking way. Okay, if you if you can parry this guy like three or four times in a row and
like not get hit, you're from a different planet. You have to be. I would actually like start to
contemplate like what potential alien species you could be. Now I'd be like I have fucking super
human intelligence. I must be from a different planet. I have to be. Yes, but what is your
reasoning for trying to join the Mensa Academy? The streamer said he was going to meet around a
bunch of people told me that I had a super genius IQ because I could parry this boss and Elden wing
three times in a row. Any mathematics or any English or any medical background? No. I just
got shit faced one night and was able to parry this guy three times and this streamer told me
who's the streamer? What are you talking about? I don't think you can. I don't think you can.
Can you parry him? Like, I mean, at some point you just like guess at some point. Jesus.
At some point just guess. I'm not even trying to fight the boss. Those are the bit what's he doing?
I'm just trying to parry. That's the only thing I'm doing and I'm leaving when I get
one. People people come to the stream and they see a guy like I don't understand what's happening.
It's like that's what happens. You give your friend the control. You're like hey play Elden
ring. They're going to be like what's uh what do I do man? What should I go? I'm telling you I'm
just practicing parrying. This guy's fucking moves are impossible to predict. What? I mean honestly
though like holy shit man it's fucking crazy. I'm gonna I'm not leaving until I get a parry once.
I'm not leaving this area until I like get it. I just want and then I'm going to alt f for the
game and then come back right with one eye. It'll be easier. Fine. I looked like I hit it.
That second one I think I hit it. I don't think I can parry him. He's a smaller shield. Okay.
Last try. Last try. That's it and I'm not coming back. No. Fuck you. No I'm going out. I'm going
out on my own terms. Hey wait where does it say my souls are? Wait why am I all the way over here?
I oh I chose the bonfire. Fuck. Oh well that's it. I'm not going back. I'm not going back to that
guy ever again. Jumping by past the stake. Oh that sucks. I still where just tell me what the
turtles are. I don't even care. I'm not gonna sit around for four hours looking around this
whole island for the turtles. Where are the other two turtles? Tell me. I just tell me where they
are. I don't want I don't care. No I want four hours of suffering. Just tell I just where are
the turtles? Where are they? Somebody said one of them's flying. That would be really funny but I
don't I don't think I believe you. Why are they throwing frisbees at me? Stop. One is literally
flying. No it's not. What is this? Is that gonna kill me? Okay I was supposed to be so upset.
What is that one? What's that for? Wait could I where was that? Why is it gone? What the fuck
is it for? Mark that. Where is it? Fortnite bounce pad dude. I just need to get down there.
I just need to get down there. Get down there. I just walked up the edge. I just want to go down.
Thank you. All right where's the turtle? Where is he? Tell me now. There's a shitload of turtles
right here. Why are there so many turtles here? Seal on the rise opened. What? What's the rise?
I did it? I did it. I did? Aren't there three? You broke the encounter. Oh all right what did I do?
It was no it was three. It was three turtles. It says find three wise beasts. One big or it's three
small turtles or one big turtle. Where was the big turtle? Wasn't the big turtle on the cliff?
I'm very confused how I'm allowed in here right now. It was in the air.
I didn't see it. This is kind of a spooky place. They were in the sky. Oh it's on my head.
Um a bug or something. I wonder what this was all for. It's gonna be for
or something. That's gold and he's dark moon. 68 intelligence at 45.
Uses the caster as oh it's the thing where you go into the moon. That um that caster boss.
I wonder how good that is. All right I think I've pretty much fully explored this island.
There's like three dragons here but I don't care. I'm not gonna fight them right now
or ever. So time to make a decision. Up from Kaleid or kind of up right from the uh manor.
Carry manor. I have two choices here. Up from Kaleid or right. You know I don't I actually
don't even really care. I would do either one of these. I'm gonna take a quick quick pee break.
Let me get a poll in chat. Right from manor. Up from Kaleid. Right from manor which is this way
or up from Kaleid. Get a poll going. I'll take a quick BRB. Gonna pee. Gonna refill my drink.
And I'll see you guys in a bit. See you in like two minutes. I got 50 subs an hour ago. Rock Lee.
Thank you. That's a lot. I still owe subs which maybe I'll try that again. Hopefully I got that
sorted too but we'll see. So where are we going? What are the uh what was the general consensus?
63% said up from Kaleid. Okay. Okay. Sounds like plan. 27% said uh hard to do do.
That wasn't an option so sorry. Right. Sound effects on. And we go. So up from Kaleid.
That sounds like plan. Very cool. Very interested. Also according to the notes,
the dragon no we're already we're there. That's just that's not gonna happen.
That's way later. Kaleid's not dragon barrel. I really hope this bowling pin isn't gonna be your
hat always. I don't know. I don't know. It's by far the best intelligence hat that I found so far
because specifically it does not reduce my stamina like the other ones do. All right let's go. I'm
just gonna go up from here. So this way which would be actually this way. All right. Okay let's
go. Swamp of Aeonia. Yeah really can I go this way? This is rot. This is another rot area. Okay
it's not. Oh I remember these guys. Yeah I was freaking out about these guys before.
He's dropping gold. Uh-huh. Okay. Come here. Mm-hmm. It's just like the rabbit from Mario 64.
What? Fuck. Oh scarlet rot. Wait. Stand over here. Where is he? What's this pattern?
Where this pattern is? So wait. Hold on. Am I stupid? What? Am I stupid? I'm going up here
is what I can actually see. I mean obviously right like come on. What the fuck happened?
What? Oh I had scarlet rot. I'm so locked in. Stop by the shack at the southern gate.
Okay. What if I like block? Where are you going? Where are you going? What? You don't go this way
anymore? Fuck you. What? I don't get it. Come here you little shit. Got him. Poison armament.
Uh-oh. Fellas. Hold on. Poison armament. Oh all right. I gotta go up that way I think right.
It's useless. Is it? It's useless? All right. I'm going kind of the right way but I almost
want to go that way. I want to follow the uh golden thing. Celia tower of sorcery.
What's wrong here? I can't go this way. I guess not. So this is like I guess progression but
I can't go in there. Why not? Why not? Shit. I can't go in here.
Are you firing at me? You can go up there. All right. I'm gonna do some rooftop jumping here.
Is that a hole? Oh yes. Hi. I'm Sigurd. All up there. My god. All right. Stop. Stop. All right.
Oh fuck. Get the fuck out of here dude. Stop. I just want to get up here. What's in here? Another
entrance I can't get in. You are such a shitty little enemy too and like I get out of here with
this bullshit and you disappeared too. I gotta get back on the roof. I want to go get those items.
Item Andy. Item Andy. Item Andy. I know. Okay back to the tree. Fuck. I think I can do it from here.
If I didn't have somebody up my ass I would be able to do it. I didn't have somebody constantly
up my ass I'd be able to do it. I can't stop. My god. I didn't fall off the fucking roof to
begin with. If the horse didn't have to make a gigantic 10 meter circle if he wanted to turn
around. Pain in the ass. I fucking hate these guys. I just want to get on the fucking roof.
I just get me on the roof. I'm just gonna go all the way back to where I was before
and just get up there. Like it's just I'm getting out of this foggy bullshit and I'm
just gonna go from here. Oh my god. Fuck all of you. Look you're a dumb ass little whatever.
I can't get up there. So I'm gonna don't even fucking think about it. Don't even think about it.
Hit him. Get off. Oh no no no. Thank you. I appreciate that you actually helped me. That
actually helped. That would have been very mad. Okay there's a ladder right there. I don't give a
shit about it. Never mind. Fuck the items. Nope. How dare you say fuck the items. Item Andy.
That guy's gonna fuck this whole thing up because he's gonna throw a grenade or whatever.
Oh nice. Worth it. Worth. It's worth it. Worth it. What's this? Oh light a fire.
Seal was broken in town. Ah. So that's how you do it. Okay so there's another one over there.
So I have to destroy the magical seal. I'm so impatient. Fuck it right? Okay. That's hard to
get up through. What's that? Red main painting. Oh shit. All right. Holy shit. What the? I'm gonna
just spawn a hundred times. It's you. Good. Now you get to die and you get to die too.
He's alive? All right. All right. All right. Leave. Leave. Leave. Leave. Leave. Leave.
I can get that. I'm certain of it. Hey. Well we're going that way. He's not enjoying this game at
all. You can tell. No actually I that's completely opposite. He's not enjoying the game at all.
Like he's just he's just desperately trying to fucking hold it together before like freaking out
on stream one day. As you can tell he's just holding it in. He wants to so badly fucking talk
about how he hates this. Hates what he's doing. He hates streaming this game. He fucking hates the
game. It looks like there's a lot of these so I don't know how many of these I'm supposed to be
doing. I have two. Oh I got it. Double slash. Seal's broken up there. There's one more that
I'm gonna go get which is over here and then I'm just gonna go in the front door. Easy snipe. Easy
snipe. Hell yeah. I'm not sure I can get this one from here. Holy shit that's a that's a face.
Holy crap. Um well a little awkward. A little awkward but whatever. I'm just gonna go in the
front door. Holy crap dude. Yeah holy crap. Would you guys rather I say holy crap or like say like
fuck. Which one's like you think more appropriate. I'm just gonna go in the front door. I don't want
to just be like swear guy you know what I mean. I'm gonna start saying like holy shoot. Oh my god.
Oh my goodness. Holy what the oh crap. Um there's a chest just sitting here.
Night comet. Holy crap. That was a genuine holy crap. That one was genuine I can promise you.
That was a genuine holy crap. Holy crap a night comet. All right well let's do this. I got this
one open. I got another one open too. Should I do the one that's lower? This one down uh downtown.
Why am I saying downtown. You know what I mean. I do need a map fragment which is
here. Why is my point pointing that way. Um excuse me. Go up this way now go that way.
What are you talking about. Please do your best Australian action accent. Uh no no I'm not gonna
no no. It's so funny accents like people just get so rage filled if like someone's doing an
accent and they don't sound like their neighbor. You know what I mean. Wait is he doing an Australian
accent. Oh he doesn't sound like my fucking neighbor mate. Get him. But it's just an accent.
It's just an accent. It's just an impression. What the hell. Okay pay attention. I'm getting
double attacked. Don't let him put himself back together. Did you do Jack Sparrow.
I'm done. Oh my career is over. I'm ending my career. It's over today. Listen I have two
headphones in. All right let me explain. The reason why I never have two headphones in is because I
can't hear myself talk. When there are two headphones in I can't hear myself speak and
it kind of speech jams me and messes up pretty much everything. So I don't I don't know how I
sounded right there but I know it sounded. I imagine a walrus with like a big mustache that
goes like this. Like when he's talking. Does that make sense? That's like all I heard and that's all
I saw. That's the only thing I could think of. Okay I can get on top of the building.
No. Yo grace from the last you grace. God he sucks. She's quiet. He sucks. I'm like
I'm trying to jump across the building. No I actually I don't suck. Excuse you.
What the fuck just happened? Okay I can't you can't make that jump. It looks like you can.
It actually looks like you can make the jump. What the fuck I didn't want to go to the statue.
It's probably another way around. I thought it was possible to make the jump if you did it like
perfectly or something. So there's another way to get up there which is probably I actually don't
know. You can't go from here. Maybe you can. Okay whatever. All right let's keep going. So
I need to go where do I go from here? That way? This way up around? All right let's continue our
trek through Elden Ring. Items though hold on. Maybe probably that way but let's just go. He
was dying in such comically avoidable ways. Well but I mean if you're okay but I'm exploring.
I am exploring the game. So of course I'm gonna fall down somewhere if I'm like if I've ever been
there and I'm gonna try to jump up there or something. Like what? I'm a huge Breath of the
Wild fan. One of the cool things about Breath of the Wild was like you could actually go wherever
you wanted. It wasn't like oh you have to go here you have to go there. That's why this game I'm
like comparing it to B-O-T-W. But um you can just kind of explore and that's what I like about this
game. So that's how I'm gonna play it. Okay what? That was very odd. Is it still there?
Why do I feel like it's still up there? Don't you feel like it's still up there and it's gonna
reappear? El Balo. I can't wait till it's actually a boss. If El Balo is really a boss with a health
bar and it plays like that. El Balo. Will you officiate? I'm not officiating any weddings.
Is it? Oh yes. One second. Oh my gosh. One second. I'm looking at something. Oh safe safe safe safe
safe safe safe. There's a person here. Okay hold on. Let me look. Let me see. What have we got? What
have we got? What have we got? What have we got? Hey hey I'm trying to hold on. I'm looking at like
what's I'm looking at food. Stop. No I have to just touch that thing. Okay all right. Oh the oh the
old girlfriend wants to ask what you want for food to get you killed in Elden Ring shtick.
Honey it didn't work. All right hold on. Give me one second. I want to actually look at this.
Yeah okay of course. Of course my usual order. Usual order. Five McChickens. Extra blue cheese.
All right there's somebody here.
He's pretending he has a girlfriend. Hold on guys. I gotta check. I gotta check in with the
girlfriend instead of making it up. Why am I just making that up? That's so fucking. That would be
weird. Okay so this person. Is there like a cure I can give this person? Oh what's this?
Okay well I don't think there's nothing else here. Is the mic audio fucked up today?
It shouldn't be. I don't know. I don't think so. All right that's good. Did I actually get enough
to do this? Four golden seeds. Damn it. Okay so you're infected with scarlet rot. I've actually
made my way to a road which is pretty pog. Oh spells right. Like I got. Oh no no no. I need 68
intelligence to use it. How close am I to actual 52 though? Would I rank Elden Ring? You mean like
on the the. What are we gonna call these now? Right? Before it was like Dark Souls. Souls like
or Souls game. Then Bloodborne came out and it became a Souls born game. Sekiro came out which
wasn't really a kind of Souls kind of game. It was close. But this one is. Are we gonna call these like
Souls brings? Souls Soulsbrings? All right what do I rank this on the Soulsbring
franchises? Soldenbring. Solden. Soldenbringborn. Soldenbrorn. Soldenbringer.
Ringborner. Soldenbring. I don't know. So soft. Souls. Souls. Soul. Soulbringborn. I like. Okay.
Soulbringborn is good. I don't know. Probably like one or two. I want to pass the time because I'm
curious if she dies. Still all right? Well you seem to be fine. Perfectly fine from this morning. So
you need to go to the shack. Oh all right well I don't know where the shack is.
Is it on the map? Find the shack. Oh that's a grave. What's that? Is that a shack?
Don't fucking die please. Oh not fighting you. I think there's an NPC here. South of the town.
You're screaming because you're gonna get hit by that. That's like what I do.
So there's an NPC here. That's not an NPC. Whatever. What do you got? There's something weird over
there though. What's that? Look at this game. This game's Drawstring Poison Grease. That was a fully
charged art too. Feels good when you hit that shit. What is? Oh that's. Oh okay. That's where the
festival was and then we fought down there. Okay I get it. This game's fucking. Never mind. I don't
want to be an idiot. I don't know what's going on here but there's butterflies. Your thinking face
looks dumb. Let's see your thinking face. I don't know why that got me. That got me. That got me.
Like I don't know. I don't know why that got me. That got me angry. I don't understand why but like
it did and it tilted me to a point where I got killed in the middle of that. For those guys dying
one hit. I don't know what's safe and what's not safe to fall. All right let's go. There's a clown
on the top right of your screen. Where? Where? Where? Where? Where? Where do we go? Where do we go?
Big guy. Oh big guy. No problem. Why is nobody spamming that? You guys get over that in one day?
You guys you guys got over that in literally 24 hours. Oh Omega Love. What an old meme that is.
That was yesterday. Something up here. I don't think so. This is bringing me just back to where
all the the dog man farming fighting is. Look okay that looks like a shack.
What else looks like a shack here? This could be a shack. I mean maybe one of these something
over here could look maybe be a shack. Something right here could be a shack. I don't see anything
here that's shack like. This could be it's a it's a shack like over here. Oh my goodness we're fine.
All right so you mean like right here? Like over this way? That looks like shack right there.
I think that's a shack. I think we found the shack. I think we found it.
I did everything. You didn't do anything. I found it. Not we. Me. I did. There are two of you?
That's weird. Oh you're invisible. Oh another goal. I gotta I can definitely level up again.
You know what this reminds me of? This reminds me of um a neverhood. Stuff like that.
Those big bulb almost like clay like trees. Okay so I gotta go up here and apparently the
shack is right there. I mean this looks like a shack. It might not be. Okay that that I thought
I looked like it could be an NPC. Who's not an NPC? I have no mana. We don't need it. Swamp
lookout tower. Eternal darkness. Oh that's right I did get the I got the uh the knight comment
and uh okay cool. What does eternal darkness do? Can I do anything else with this? Maybe I can. Hold
on. This might be kind of a weird thing to try but whatever. Like it looks like I can get in there.
Yeah look see on the tree. Can I climb the tree and jump from the top or does it just look cool?
All right that's not the shack. It's a cool tower. This I guess this is a good vantage point.
That a shack right there. That could look it'll be like a shack.
Just south of town it's in the canyon. But like here? Shack? Shack probably down here.
All right shack. Back. Stop by the shack. Is it even on the map? It's not. I mean it kind of is.
Sort of blends in. Wait how am I supposed to stop by the shack? You have a big dog.
Okay back time. What do you got? What's here? A pleasure to see you. A pleasure indeed.
I am Gary a great sage in my day anyway. I'd hoped to ask a favor when one of your ilk came along.
A strapping young tarnished able to cross the scarlet swamp of Aeonia. Don't fret.
Should you accept? We'll teach you the secret of Selya, the town you see there. Secret? What do you got?
Then you are willing to lend a hand are you? I need your help to heal a certain young girl.
I know where she is. Her name is Millicent.
The life I sent? No way. Resting at the church atop the cliff.
Stricken by the rotting sickness. Okay what about her? Rotting sickness that afflicts Millicent
has no cure. When the earth tree flourished even the demigods could not stave off its effects
despite their nigh godhood. Millicent's suffering can be eliminated. I have these like pink boogers.
You are to find a certain needle. Seek the deep scarlet swamp of Aeonia outside Selya's hands.
The needle made from unalloyed gold is lost somewhere. Don't I have it?
I actually think I have it. Bro I already own it. Here it is. Gold needle. First you must find
the unalloyed. It's hidden somewhere in the deep scarlet swamp. Then I will tell you as the secret
okay that's not the right one so it's in the deep swamp swamp of somewhere deep in the swampy area
okay cool let's keep going um i think i want to just pour it back here just go up add that to
the notes yeah deep in the what was it called what he said he said a bunch of words deep in the swamp
with the scarlet swamp of a whatever he said we all know we get it if you are wise you will my
flesh bride just rub these pink and purple boogers all over you and you feel fine i think i even have
one i will go into the mouth crazy these guys don't care crazy looking oh oh that looks cool
from far away almost that was close if i had spent even one more second caring about that view
nice try though very nice try all right i definitely can get to there from here can't i
another one just dropped and i missed it that's where i came from is there a way to go keep going
up i guess i have to go that way who's rolling the balls i don't know it's a magical ball roller
but this road there's no more road here oh there's a jumpy all right going this way
oh okay i go up i go that way this place is cool i just i like this place
more starlight shards but what am i going to use these for i didn't even look what they did
the game really wants me to do like a funny little go down here thing look at these platforms
or is it just one platform and my brain is stupid i think that's what it is no
why is this here you see i mean like what's the point of these i didn't gatekeeper for those
returning to the roots what i just do gamer statue what did these do what is that showing
you where john points to a dungeon uh-huh okay okay okay the dungeon down there okay
oh god damn it okay so this is what you want me to do no oh i don't know i'm gonna keep going
shit i gotta go up oh fall fall i'm not gonna fight i'm not fighting any of these guys for no
reason to be cool back over here just seeing if there's anything interesting there is not
beast blood wait don't i know this guy wasn't that the guy that was at the festival oh we'll
never know because i fucking killed him that i guess i'm gonna use it definitely go on top
of the head there's no way there's not something cool up here yep of course there is smithing
stones multiple smithing stones nice that's a lot of smithing stones up here oh fuck that alive
what's that what's that what's that all right let's do it i'm very intrigued oh is it alive
what's happening where it's going on this thing alive it is it's hurt though i thought it was
statue it's alive that is crazy five thousands 3,500 souls all right that what i need to go
examine that thing that's crazy there's so many dragons everywhere can i ride him can i get on
his back all right no no no no no i gotta get let's go we're going to get the map fragment
i'm not going to do that right now map fragment very important i'm not going to fight 10 dragons
at the same time and the omega dragon that's not happening don't fight me it's neat all right map
fragment and maybe a bonfire this is dragon barrel this is this is dragon barrel this is where the
other half of the um medallion is all right i need a bonfire now i don't see one i'm gonna head this
way touch grass there we go all right you can also level up probably once or twice perfect so
where dragon barrow far to the east for the other half of that resident evil coin thing
well it was called it was a fort it's like oh seek fort something right
fort fort fort for roth fort far off yeah all right that's where we're going i'm gonna find
that fortune i think i can level up twice because this might be 10 000 we'll find out
okay i might be a little short yeah i'm a little short okay although let me okay that's definitely
not a fort this could be that could be okay let me clear the all the shit i have out
this could be a fort this i don't think that's a fort this looks like it that's probably it right
there i'm gonna guess it's one of those two i'm also gonna mark this because i want to go to it
yeah it's definitely two there's no way it's not two but i'm closer to four
let's just mark all this stuff because i'm gonna be experimenting four is closer so that's where
i'm gonna go just to see what it is be careful there are dogs among us like a little chat wait
why is it why are you fighting me what well i didn't do why are they attacking me why are
the goats attacking get away from me i don't i don't want to kill these goats no animal in
the whole game is attacked besides these guys there's another bonfire oh merchant merchant
shack maybe i'll buy something since i've seen a customer now dragon wound grease gravel stone
jewel pot spiked cestus oh note gateway note imparting knowledge in brief didn't cave
let's get these i'm gonna read them right now
all right i'm gonna mark this and i'm gonna read those notes where they listed here right okay
note gateway port gale in caitlin houses a gateway that leads to red main castle okay there is a
hidden cave in the town of celia look beyond the graveyard at the precipice okay this painter is
said to have captured the landscape seen during the last moments of those welcomed into death's
embrace so the painter and the messages of the dead's last moments can be discovered by visiting
the location depicted even now these are cool because you have to go find this spot and find
this exact place find that exact view and it's probably like look down and hit a i think that's
close that seems close i'll look at it later didn't breath of the wild do this yeah i know b o t w b o
t w is one of the best games all right so that's that let's go uh i'm gonna go probably not add
let's go whatever this is lazy but i don't care any chapstick thank you for reminding me appreciate
that ow all right so now i'm gonna go this way we're just knocking out all the markers just
because i feel like it that's what we're doing that's what we're going really you got a lot of
health so what's this thing all right be careful oh he's so scary all the way up divine tower
there's epic loot tations in there and it activates a great room that's cool what you're saying is
let's go get up there why does this seem like the bird like the worst and best okay you're supposed
only shit i oh okay i just like dark souls i pressed the spring button geez this is so
fucking stressful okay it's gonna get in the way so get rid of it birthday what the 4000th birthday
where's lanya i've been looking for them the whole game right that is a one of these
is divine tower of caitlin
very very very very nice what's in the tower is the question oh let's do this door here oops
yeah this is going on yeah that's a that activates the great room that's intriguing
that's intriguing that's intriguing that's intriguing see it you see it i can jump halfway
into the thing how much longer till you finish the game a very very very long way
an exceptionally long way store the power of great dan's great ruin what does that one do
raises maximum hp fp and stamina um okay so this one is okay godric's gives you plus five to all
stats for dan's gives you increased hp fp and stamina but his five vitality better than the
max hp you get from this you know what i mean i feel like you get more from this unless this is
a lot because this is effectively bigger uh mind and endurance whereas this is all of them i wonder
how wonder how much it actually is to me that would have to be very significant to not use
the other one that's cool all right so the fort is definitely right there very cool hp is probably
higher dan is only good once you've hit the soft cap of stats oh that makes sense if you get to
40 vitality right 40 vigor that makes sense that would be better than not that useful maybe now
what about the rest of the tower oh there was another way to go you're right i even like
freaked out about it um let me do this part i mean i'm gonna do this first this has got me this has
got me hooked this part here there's also the huge dragon here too all right i'm gonna go kill the
huge dragon i'm gonna go stab the dragon in the face i wonder how much damage it does is this like
just gary am i gonna die here he he summons a shit load of dragons i'm just gonna die
so you sneak up in the face jump on top i don't know what to do um can i actually climb on top
oh that was that was another dragon why they just let me i'm stuck here i think i got the strat
get away from me oh this is 13 000 damage how believe so i mean i had a kind of a cheese
ball scrap right there but i wonder if it's maybe i should try how big is he
all right maybe i should go along his body he'd probably i guarantee it they probably got like a
big bulbous pimple on their back and i can just whack right it's probably a huge pimple let's go
find out why is he just why is he all head and neck he's just a huge neck with wings
where is his body i'm gonna go further up the mountain he's all head and neck his legs are
gonna be this big and he's gonna have like tiny little feet okay okay there's his head
he's lying down theoretically his tail should be this way where are my souls i need my souls
you're just sitting on top of them that's so dumb whatever okay i kind of feel i don't like
doing this i feel bad this actually makes me sad this makes me sad it's a lot of ruins
stop it i love it in the middle of stop it stop it dude what the fuck come on stop
literally ruining the game is come to brazil i'm not gonna stop i this is actually stupid should
i not be doing this for like storyline reasons is there actually a reason why i shouldn't be
doing this it's a story npc 14 000 damage on a bleed we're getting tired my guy's like all right
okay my god i feel like i've been chopping wood all day use the rune boost you're right
holy shit it's gonna be so much more how about both item discovery and rune boost just die
oh my god i feel like bad that was so sad 64 000 souls a new power is available though
all right i'm sorry i wouldn't be able to do this it would smell like rotten eggs right here
it would just smell like just rotting eggs this thing was lying down for probably like a century
this would kill you like the the power of the smell right here would kill you all right turn
around port right there unless is it was he lying on top of something right item or something
doesn't look like it i was seeing if there's an item here new power is available i wonder what
that is and here's the port all right now we're gonna be able to combine that coin once i get
it whatever's here or you can go kill stuff with that buff activated you know what you're
absolutely right but yeah you're right you're absolutely right let's go hold it still a minute
port harov yeah absolutely kill stuff hurry up this whole room is filled with fucking
dirt what is going on that's a beefy guy all right we're off i'm not gonna lose the souls
they're right here all the minus 120k omega lol it's not they're right here i believe we're at
48 i need a little bit more how much more do i need 52 gets me the new staff oh i can what am
i stupid all right i'm gonna get let's go here we do it i'm also gonna do this because why not
no reason not to so i can just see what's going on in this freaking room i'm dirty my eyes
god fucker how come i can't there's no critical there i feel like they should be there's no crit
he's gonna grab fucking soap soap i think the soap is bait i don't think it actually does anything
they'll oh look there'll be an enemy in the game that eats the soap there'll be a random person
that eats the soap and oh bring me soaps bring me 50 soaps that's the only reason why it exists
gamer doesn't know what to do with soap why is there a drop down here oh here we go
it's gonna be the coin nectis medallion right and now that i have them both what do i do with it
what do i do with it i wonder oh well there might be something over there
we craft them together yeah um left half is said to reside yeah right half of a split medallion
left half of a split medallion do you have to bring it to somebody
yep okay be the blacksmith that's what i'm thinking too maybe maybe the blacksmith will
say something about it now i'll go ask interesting i'm gonna go down oh we don't care i don't fight
you guys going down here read the middle part of the item description branching the medallion
with both halves conjoined will activate the grand lift of dektis connecting the atlas plateau
to larunia grand lift of dektis grand lift 12 that's i thought they stopped at 10 but where's
the grand lift of dektis i already got to the atlas plateau yeah grand lift an extra area you can
jump to i wasn't gonna just run away where over here in the rafters don't let a regular enemy
kill you okay so i go up here again it's chito off the dirty floor this floor is very clean
was vacuumed always it's been that put soap carpet soap on it okay so from here
i jump from here to there what do i just go around this way somehow save chito other ladder
there's an item right there it's so clean lick the floor then all right back in that rafter area
down here oh fuck okay let me get hold on wait wait wait i fucking fell down this guy's respawning
why are they respawning they shouldn't be this is not how this game works
eat spaghetti off the floor even if it was a clean carpet imagine eating spaghetti off a carpet
i was just like you know what i'm gonna try to jump to that because there might be something
there like an item on the edge and it looked like i really could get to it and i didn't think it
was gonna go that far down it's right here whatever hey there's a gold item in there
that's the one oh nice very nice the other one right okay so how do i drop down from there
there that was tough right over there it's over there oh shit i know don't make this joke anymore
all right so it's underneath me right now so i can just jump from here to there
i'm gonna get hit by bat in there no i need my starlight a lot of fucking health don't you
oh fuck all right so that was crazy i'm glad i had the light but what's this
this adagon's sore seal oh greatly increases attributes but also increases damage taken
that's a lot that's plus five to how come not intelligence oh because i'm looking at the
intelligence one right no int it's plus five to everything but not plus five to intelligence why
not no or mind i wonder what increases damage taken this legendary talisman is an eye engraved
with an elden rune said to be the seal of king consort radagon greatly raises vigor endurance
strength and dexterity but also increases damage taken by a similar measure solemn duty weighs upon
the one who beholden not unlike a gnawing curse i wonder what the damage increases because it's
a separate one for magic no i guess that makes sense but that was cool all right i cleaned up
this area a little bit there's a couple things i probably still do where is this pointing me down
here so i wonder celia deep swamp aeonia or do i try to activate that lift so the world ends here
so there's no more way to go up this way it's probably a place to go here this is a really
weird map look at how weird this map is so there's an area here and an area here nothing in the middle
nothing it's like a big giant like circle it looks like this land right here here right though it's a
big giant circle it's a ring it's a giant elden ring the the ring is the land it's not a material
thing it's the elden ring is the the world is really old it's the ring the world is the elden
ring all right uh like somebody say go back in the tower we did it we beat the game i do want to
level up one more time though almost there right 39 000 i need a couple how much does this give
thousand can't go wrong with vitality i just can't i'm gonna take soap off the bar because
it's kind of fucking me up and this thing is also fucking me up too okay so there's more in here
somebody said they were like dude go check i was like all right because there's another ladder
that way let's i'm just gonna go down there who cares because i can't it's gonna be tricky but
i'll try newman's ruin newman used to gain a multitude of ruins the newman are said to have
come from outside the lands between in fact of the same stock as queen marika 10 000 20 000
yeah how much is a multitude i wonder probably 20k or 10 all right well let's go down here what
what huh i can't walk across that but i could walk across it it looked like a lip i could cross
hold on i don't buy it i don't actually don't buy it i don't buy it okay what would why would
this ladder be here if you can't cross that there's no this ladder makes no sense unless
you keep continuing this way yeah what what did i do wrong now what now what what the hell
trick disappointing what's the hell what why is this ladder here that ladder doesn't even need
to be here there's nothing i can do here i drop down i'm gonna just i don't know i don't know i
think i'm dead if i drop the gap on the other side okay well i went that way last time right
let's go this way probably in inside the tower is it a room down here that i didn't that i ran
through or something i ran by okay it is right here i don't go off the fucking edge
oh fucking how much can you help you both to be copying each other's moves you're not original
oh so what is this oh shit i can jump around this but wait investigate does not open from this side
of course it doesn't from here this is such a far way down oh my god okay um now what a golden
rune i don't have to jump on that right i actually have to land on that thing i've got a jump onto
that little thing oh that was way off that was way off oh there's a bonfire down here
it's a bonfire okay at least i know i know there's a bonfire where there's a bonfire
that is so far by the way do you see how far that is it's gonna take me an hour it's gonna
take an hour to get down there what the hell i free fell i sky dove down this whole thing
that was very far they don't fall with me do they yes they do well then they're not gonna make it
oh my god what do i this way i panicked because he was following me and i forgot which way it was
here comes the big yeah this is that dumb tree area in dark souls one when we just fall down
the whole what's it called the route and like it was still only 2k rooms it's fine patience
it weren't even close oh don't move fuck maybe just a single roll just one singular roll
just and that's it just a single a single roll what about walk i'm gonna go for the one just
didn't i was waiting for someone to go right by the screen all right all right it was just walk
it was just walk oh my god that one was kind of hard and then this one is i don't think i
can make that one i'm not fucking with this guy i don't care how cheeseball this is
okay this dude lives on a ledge yeah what what is the point why is that guy here
it was longer i thought it was a lot i thought it was longer i've been trying i've been walking
off on all these all right let's freaking go oh shit i forgot i forgot it's uh it's this way
oh fuck oh fuck how do i get away from these guys god damn it i forgot it's not all the way
and then on the ledge it's on the ledge i'm gonna speedrun this i'm gonna get there now
i forgot to kill that guy oh don't he's too stupid to walk over here he died somebody fell off
there's a lot of items you're not gonna put an item over here from software yes you are why
wouldn't there be one in the corner right there right there it should be why don't even let me
go over here unless you're gonna put what a waste of wasting my time absolutely wasting my time
dude where are you getting what are you getting this half-price ganja you smoke half-price ganja
what's that i got i got bad weed so like i'm my brain is fucking slower what do you mean
i don't want to go up i want to go down i don't want to go up why is this taking me up it's a
lot wait where am i oh shit that was like a chad walk by the way this guy is just that this guy
what a chad male oh he killed me ah got him flame monk gauntlets what was he hiding
of course you were hiding an item of course you were and it was disappointing why can i do this
it doesn't make any sense i want to go up the ladder though i want to go up the ladder i don't
think i can get that from here i think i'm stuck down here i don't get to swing that many times
oh somebody got stuttered it's a boss see what it is god skin apostle fuck you i was healing
do you just wait till i fucking heal or you dickhead does that throw move you just literally
stand around until i put the fucking flask up and then you throw it at me i think i got it was that
a bug no it's a that's such fucking bullshit fuck that let's go fuck that we speed during the
potion he throws this thing at you oh i got the whole set odd skin apostle hood robe bracelets
trousers and fox that was crazy wood made by sewing together patches of smooth skin oh
ew overreaction for the youtube video yucky it's skin no bonuses to anything that's a lot
of magic resistance though it's actually just skin hair look at that poise that poise is awful
let's see what it looks like no gloves where are they oh my god i don't want to look at that
this is horrible oh it's so awful like it just looks i hate every second of that
let me back my fucking dunce comedy outfit wait maybe i'll keep the oh actually that actually
matches the helmet okay i like the pants they match the head i got a hundred thousand souls
and i gotta be careful here human skin versus comedy outfit there's a chest in here too
is this a joke chest why would there be a chest here don't put that in here god slayers great
sword what sacred sword of the dusk-eyed queen who controlled the godskin apostles
before her defeat at the hands of maleketh black flames wielded by the apostles are channeled
from this sword unique skill the queen's black flame set the set the blade ablaze with the
god-slaying black flame before delivering a sweeping slash additional input allows for a
follow-up attack black flames will continue to wear down hp for a while what this thing
is insane looking look at this thing wow that's probably the coolest weapon in the game like in
regards to how it looks i don't have mana to do it that's so cool looking i can't i don't have
any mana to do the thing but it still looks awesome this is one of the best weapons in the game you
should use the flame i imagine it's pretty similar to what these guys are doing to me up here
okay but that's not that only thing that's down i i like ran away i'll check that out in a minute
look at how many cool weapons are in this game you know i will say elden ring versus all the other
souls games there's a lot less at least maybe my brain is remembering this wrong i feel like
there's a lot of really cool items it's not just like short sword long sword a zweander claymore
right i feel like there's a ton of these unique weapons a lot more ninety percent of them are
suck though yeah but i don't think that matters i think it's fun to take decide on a playthrough
where you're gonna use you know what like i'm i'm using the raduvia in this playthrough i think
about that's very like actually interesting like the dismounter i'm gonna use this all right so
that was cool actually i don't i don't want to lose these souls so i gotta be really careful here
uh we're not gonna do this i can now put the staff on oh i need one more shit i got this thing too
i gotta go back to the town i got a lot of shit to look through hold on all right all right all
right all right here's what we're gonna do i'm going back to town i gotta go find it because
that's a boss soul weapon that is a boss soul weapon the cool int weapon or it's just another
level which i'll take either one all right what's what is this bastard stars what is this thing
what is this thing it's a flail it's a magic flail what oh my goodness it's a solar system flail
ash of war waves of darkness the big d and c scaling it's a flail it's dex int youtube reaction
for the youtube video look it needs 22 decks as well like this is this is this is an annoying
weird weapon to get right because you have to put like 10 to 50 you gotta put like at least 10 points
in decks to have this item and nobody's gonna do that like that's i don't i mean at least not
too late late game probably right it's expensive and i got it i just want to look at it what the
hell it's so weird it's actually a solar system i want to see what the i want to see what the power
does we're just gonna go to like land grave or something it's a baby rattle
it's a baby rattle all right i need to take the helmet off take the shirt off put a diaper on
okay does anything look like a diaper in the game because i will use the baby i will be baby character
okay let's see let's test it out on some sheep that does a lot of damage just like
in general it's not even leveled up that was 256 damage from the swing and it has not even
zero plus zero but it's but i have so many cool fucking weapons though that's the problem
does it have an l2 combo to try and try again l2 l2 i mean you're very vulnerable right here
because it's like one two three four it's about four full seconds all right it's decision time
this is a big decision i want all of you this is gonna we're gonna do this democratically
we're gonna do this we're gonna do this democratically now it's gonna work
where's the where is it okay are you guys ready we're gonna devote this one out of four items here
l2 r2 all right baby flail ab flail i want you to get a good look at it i'm gonna see
no okay people are gonna vote for this because of that people everyone's gonna click on this
because of what they're looking on the screen right now i need to put a pair of pants on so
people don't fucking automatically pick this because okay that made it worse that made it
way worse that made it way worse something that doesn't look like a fucking baby diaper okay
okay here we go baby rattle cool animation it's got the big explosion thing
it's pretty cool it's pretty sick pretty cool weapon i let's take a look at that again
without bang boom pretty cool we also have bug arm bug leaf so this thing is is like a scimitar
got a pretty good swing also has does not take intelligence to do this it has a big
intelligence scaling magic weapon also it's got its own version of the baby rattle although this
one is better i that happens faster it might not do as much damage we're not sure
bug wing that does not take intelligence pretty sick we also have moon veil now if you don't know
what moon veil is moon veil is the thing that has been uh carrying us through the entire mid game
i'll go we'll call this styrofoam sword if you want to get a good look it's styrofoam so styrofoam
sword boom take a look at this wham those thousand damage whoosh big intelligence move
unbelievably beautiful everyone's not going to vote for this because the katana and all katanas
are shitty loser weapons in these games from what i've been told so but it's incredible finally
we've got this
finally we've got the moonlit greatsword staple in from software and a weapon that is
in every single one of these games it can turn into a big bright night light which then has this
awesome beauty it's frost damage shoots out these cool projectiles also does not take
mana to do that very cool so what do we have ab rattle uh styrofoam katana bug wing moonlit
sword oh you want to see the other one yeah let me show you that one too somebody fucking weapons
there's so many weapons where is it right all right what is current i can't even look yet
i don't think i have enough ability to i can't turn it on the game won't let me turn the
cool thing on all right is it baby rattle or bug wing okay baby rattle is currently winning
bug wing is really close i can't even activate the power because i'm not
cool enough unfortunately you're gonna have to do a redo all right baby rattle one i'm thinking
this weapon better be fucking good the baby i don't think i actually i don't know if i want
to play as the baby should i not play as baby okay we're gonna do a vote between baby rattle
and bug wing because those are the two that ones and now everybody gets a choice baby rattle and
bug wing are now you get the real choice of real choices here pretty damn cool but what about this
one have you seen this one have you taken a look at what this one can do it's sick really cool
every time i take it up what about dual wielding them i need a staff in my other hand okay baby
rattle let's go all right this is gonna be close this is gonna be close i need something in my off
hand i need i need something small like a little like baby rattle it's like a little frisbee
okay baby oh what about the bug wing it's a pacifier
i have to get out of the frame but have you seen but have you seen buckling
redesign your character to look like a baby okay i'll be honest people are like saying oh no he's
doing a meme now and he was doing so well this apparently is one of the best intelligence weapons
in the game so how do i not have a regular somber smithing stone doesn't seem impossible
all right i know what i'm doing but i can't do it yet i can almost put this on which is going to be
a huge deal i can go back to actually casting sorceries again this is these better kind of
are yeah they just are i know boo boo boo i know it's no i'm not ready yet we're not ready yet
i need a regular somber smithing stone i'm using this thing neumann's rune 12 000 runes holy shit
this blacksmith sells those stones does he can't buy them the fat guy on the bridge has a literal
diaper are you being serious plus eight mimic by the way oleg's next there's gonna be two babies
running around the giant blacksmith all right where's the giant blacksmith he's over here
somewhere right he's like this way isn't he he's like don't go over to the manor you'd be foolish
all right what do you got name the teething ring and become the baby lord it would not have been
impossible without as lady rani's war counselor a childhood why express my deepest gratitude
talk or talk no talk or talk d scaling coming up we need a somber smithing stone four got them
what is that what is this what lowers fp consumed by skills i didn't see that the skill technically
okay i need 6000 souls shouldn't have upgraded that fucking all right let's just go get some souls
uh was the quickest place for me to get souls right now
i could go i could go fight the baby diaper lady where was that it was like here somewhere right
yeah oh get the diaper i'll try i will honest to god try uh not here wrong bridge where was it
well this is the right bridge right oh it's not this one isn't it i think it's this one
oh lady ron all right let's do it i'm a lot more leveled up now this should be a pretty
decent encounter it shouldn't be too hard the bug is way cooler it's too bad chat voted
thing is there's enough materials i could use in both let's kill but i'm gonna lean into this
for just a few moments let's go it's going way better it still hurts stop rolling
wow even with the bubble on that fucking hurt what the fuck Jesus man fuck off with this nonsense
swing no fucking stamina remaining in my inventory old skin noblehood noble robe
noble bracelets noble trousers what there's more of this shit hostile noble
no it has a bib let me look at this because i it actually the defense is really not that bad
defense is okay actually i'm not against it it's like baby birth it's like birthday boy
it's my birthday okay i need pants though dude i can't just run around like a fucking idiot
no no pants we're on the commoners trousers you can well you can see my ass wait you can see
that much he's naked you can see so much what the fuck that's fucking ridiculous why
but hold on what does that actually look like i feel like there's less when i have this on
is it like is it is it like he's an ass no i'm not ass inspecting i'm not i'm just i that was
weird to see okay i'm going back to the blacksmith where the fuck am i where is he i thought he was
a rock i don't think i have enough to level up doing all right this actually i'm not even
kidding around is probably gonna end up doing a ton of damage i need another thousand souls
we're gonna get a thousand so we're gonna get like 5 000 souls quick like very quick dogs down here
i guess i could just go but no they're only giving like 200 they sell some weapons and armor people
got mad at me when i did that last time i'm just gonna go to where i kind of like this area here
there's a bunch of random shit i can kill so did i is that it for caleb i don't think i did this
yeah let me let me investigate some of this stuff here because there was this thing here where is
this because this is like along this road all right i'm gonna go here i'll go do that dungeon
this is not upgraded all the way and this is not final but i'm curious how much damage this does
at like a plus four or plus five i mean for having a bunch of enemies you get surrounded by enemies
that's like a absolute oh shit button let's try it to be interrupted it's doing a decent amount
once it's leveled up it'll be better staggers it's really pretty it sucks stop it does
i wasted no i didn't i'm gonna i'm gonna wait until i level up a little more
it's not even leveled up wait till it's leveled up another super time look at that it staggers big
time the baby sucks it's not fair to it's not fair to talk about it yet i have no i'm not giving up
on it yet it seems like it's but it's this we're going up this is not leveled for the enemies i'm
fighting that's stupid i don't care instant kill moves are dumb instant kill moves are dumb
let me say it again instant kill moves are stupid all right you're not fully armored i know ratio
don't ratio me actually is getting a lot better 157 plus 148 it's starting to get actually pretty
good what's the katana right now katana is plus eight it's 187 plus 148 one seven plus one 168
plus 166 katana is so much better by by like an insane order of magnitude you want to try it with
the boss and give up after 30 minutes and rant about how much it sucks for 30 minutes yeah no
what the hell did you hear my voice yeah what was that fucking weird thing that i just did
all right let me take a look 157 plus 148 187 plus 148 is plus seven this is plus eight
i'll try it for a while i do need uh some more souls to get it to the same place
okay so i i how many plus nine smithing stones do i have i only have one plus nine smithing stone
right now and i am absolutely not going to use it on the baby rattle and until stars have
higher int scaling all right because i can get this i am willing to get this to plus eight
and try it but i need i need some more souls i'm gonna sell a couple of things that's
something easy i can't let's talk talk you get so many somber stones yeah i know
wait blight
hey what about blade
it's an underground
with a fallen star struck and make it yours what the precious treasure so that lady may tread
i already did that man i need 1575 so let me just go get like a thousand souls like in two seconds
if you kill one boss with a baby weapon then it deserves a plus nine why did i come here this is
my least favorite area in the whole game i've been able to swing why did i come here this place sucks
why would i why did i come to this area no it's not the weapon the baby rattle is it's gonna be
sick trust me it's gonna work out it's gonna work out it's gonna be good just out of spite i need
to i'm gonna i'm going to murder this motherfucker right now okay that's hitting for that's hitting
for pretty hard 480 that's actually not bad that's actually really good i did i baby rattle too hard
what's wrong with the baby what's wrong with what's wrong with the baby what's happening to
the baby um i can't even fucking run away from these things thanks for the thousand souls now
fucking eat my ass i need a little bit more just attack them add a forehead to your comment
because i just just i'd say forehead too junior cover your ears junior cover your ears he's
cursing again here we go i am willing to get this to plus eight it's there i am at plus 168
plus 166 that's in that's in this becomes c scaling here by the way xc int b this is doing
a lot of damage now i'm not willing to do plus nine on this i don't know what i want to do plus
nine now we're gonna actually play the game i've got some good shit i'm ready i'm all geared up
i'm ready i wanted to go check out this down here how do i get here let's start from here
no wrong this is wrong right yes this is wrong
so where is this dungeon i'm assuming probably on the road and go down from the road maybe
if i were to go get this way maybe i don't know what boss has been the scariest so far um
scary as in design or scary as in god i don't want to do that fight ever again which one yes
i need to go up here oh uh well i never want to do that fight ever again it's probably done
i just found that fight to be just a monster gimmick that it was just like a frustrating
gimmick fight that i hated i'd say that one if you're talking about like scary and creepy
and just designed really really it probably the big uh the thing where i got the baby rattle from
big astral like centipede bug praying mantis thing yeah the nerds were up astral yeah the nerds
were up possible that was just crazy looking had the whole solar system on its tail it was really
cool all right so now the idea is can i go where's this road that's not a road it's not a road what
is it so where's the dungeon down to the boss area so what do i have to go up this way from
the boss area because i can't get down there from here yes so interesting okay so it's this way
let's go big baby we're gonna go find it we're gonna go prove to everybody that this was not
a stupid idea to waste a bunch of somber smithing stones it's the painting it is the painting
is it is this just a painting dungeon so the painter so that's up though that's right there
is that up on a cliff but it kind of looks like it's right here maybe a little bit higher
it's like up there where am i right now yeah it's right here okay i'm gonna mark this like with an
actual marker called um yeah it's definitely right there dude much further down it is this
dungeon holy shit there it is look like such a fucking jackass i want the ones that match
that's right the ones that matched i think it was these ones yeah this matches war dead catacombs
let's try it this is very hard well great opportunity to try the baby rattle who just
hit me that you standing here like an idiot where'd he go where's the big guy i mean i'm
gonna die from the rot so what's the point just run around for a minute well there you are just
right there bro oh come on collapsing stars i got it i'll be able to put some of these new
insane sorcery moves on soon i got at least three or four that uh i need at least 50 which i'm
getting there i'm i think i need one more point intelligence i need one more point in intelligence
and we can get started with that sorcery shit okay don't think it's even worth fighting a lot
of these guys i got the chest there's probably something else down here maybe another time
oh grave bluff war if they're just gonna fight each other then they're just gonna fight each
other so who cares huh you shot me through a wall i didn't know the timing's on it but i
could hit through a wall hit me through a wall it was dumb oh it wasn't for yes it was nobody
argues with the giant baby i'm playing the perfect i'm playing the perfect streamer character this is
my punishment be like the big whiny baby character baby rage i can go that way but not yet holy shit
got a lot of help damn man get out of my way 155 damage omega lull it's not bad i just need
it needs a little getting used to okay you're getting used to sucking oh good thing i fucking
dodged that accidentally holy shit they should be able to get hit more than once with that
baby rattle would be a lot better if i if they could get hit by more than one of those
that would be actually awesome instead it gives them invulnerability you know the dead word
you got a spear i hate spears holy shit he's got a teleporter i thought i had time he's
punk actual punk can we get out of the fucking corridor get out of the corridor
oh fuck baby needs his i'm not gonna say that out loud it was just what there was just fucking
flowers in here that's why i fought all the way through that flowers i did that for a flower
those live those are alive hey oh through the window yep thanks yeah right through the window
oh shit i have no mana left i'm gonna pull them i'm down here fighting over here coward
coward come over here coward oh come over here coward come on that guy flipped me off
hey never leave your post somebody else can fucking deal with you man
oh don't forget about the glove ward of course that's why i came all the way down here
did i do everything there's probably a boss down here did i i feel like i didn't see everything
all right back to it so wait which way did i not go oh straight through i didn't go straight
through here walked by a contraption oh great fuck this game walk by a contraption
and they take so long it's like one two three then he lets go this game i'm not dodging i don't care
okay what the heck's happening here i see stuff does it matter what do i need to do
holy shit i didn't know he was fucking i thought he was shooting the bow and arrow
what why did he come over here what the fuck i hate you i don't know um oh we're going this way
uh i had that backstab i don't want to fight him anyways fucking don't care i don't want to fight
that guy so i don't care there it is no i'm farming for souls that i want to die at the boss the boss
are gonna be hard yeah well it's open but there's no boss bog hey there is okay all right this is
gonna be fun ah this is gonna be fun i'm just trying to throw a tantrum i mean it does a lot
of damage it just takes a long time to happen and it's cool when it hits it's really cool
i mean it's awesome it's really cool the move is amazing when it hits five that does like 900
damage if it actually lands 550 i mean it's good i mean look at that 600 that's a 1200 damage if it
hits i think i have enough was it 40 000 42 000 kill one more if it hits yes that's free
not fighting that guy try the katana again um i mean i love the katana 42 of course it is
i just walked off the weapon this weapons driving me insane why is this weapon why is it driving
you insane it's a cool weapon it's bad yeah it doesn't mean you can't have fun with a bad weapon
it's not even a bad weapon it's really not just got bad range yeah you know why the katana really
is better and why the katana is like one of the best weapons in the whole game because it has
bleed all right we just unlocked a very important milestone i have 52 intelligence which means
boys and girls got it you can actually use this thing actually use it look at the speed look at
the speed how much is the lung that does happen way faster if you don't know why i've been putting
points into intelligence not just for the scaling also because this thing makes all of my sorceries
cast speed way higher and new spells too that's right but we will play with those very shortly
what i want to do right now is just go get my ass kicked from a boss that's in this room
i don't care i'm not trying to i'm just trying to see what the boss's
moves are i don't really give a shit about beating it first time it's going to be really fun when i
start actively actively complaining about how bad this weapon is after losing to the first what
boss is going to do two moves and hurt me and kill me uh putrid tree it's another one of these
still hit me fuck wrong bus shit it's a little longer fuck wasn't bad okay wasn't bad it actually
did some pretty decent damage we're gonna do a test see let's see how this is the bit is over
go back to the real weapon i think it's actually doable because that was doing about 1200 damage
it just takes a long time let's see how much this does in comparison i know it's not even
fucking like that's not even a contest happens so much faster that and the stagger and grady
things fucking this weapon's unbelievable goodbye first try with the fucking katana
fucking fuck the katana is insane the katana is insane katana is staggering like a two-handed
hammer damn i think we're just spoiled by how good the katana really is and that's a new name
spirit too all right so here's the play here here's your here's your play i i want to play
with the baby rattle i'm very actually do want to play with it i don't think we gave it enough
chance by the way it's time to upgrade sorcery shit i got a flask upgrade i want to go back to
using sorcery so this is how we do it i got a bunch of new sorceries i can do and look if a
boss is giving me too much trouble then whip out the fucking katana and just let his head off
okay so i got a lot of souls it's time to leave i got a bunch of uh ashes too right there's a
casting speed talisman wow where is this right here a lid this edge here i mean that boss was
like kind of all right the reason why so that boss remember the first time i fought that boss
it was like 10 levels under level for it we've seen that same snake lizard monster enemy like
three times now so i kind of already knew the move set so i was pretty prepared for that
say that it was the same exact move set the only difference was it was
rot instead of lightning so there's a there's quite a few of those let's level up all right
uh it's time to examine some spells that i can now use this is a shit load now that i want to try
especially with this new incredibly better scaled and i'm going to go upgrade it again so here we go
first slot swift glint stone is is good it's good just kind of like oh i got comet now
that takes a whole fucking mana bar that takes so much mana i wonder how much damage that actually
does all right but anyways i think swift glint stone shard is good for just agro it's good for
chip damage i'll do comet after that and where are the other ones okay there's eternal darkness
forbidden sorcery creates a space of darkness that draws in sorceries and incantations the
sorcery can be cast while in motion okay i got another one too where is it there it is night
comet fires a semi-invisible magic comet the sorcerer can recast repeatedly okay collapsing
stars was another one and then what else magic downpour no crystal release crystal release
okay let's check these out right that's awful i can't move during this that's you have to
stand completely still okay what about i gotta know eternal darkness whoa what does this do
you only have one active wait this sucks up sorceries so i could literally just sit here and
cast okay that's actually good to have on the bar night comet what's the difference between that
and regular comet that looks good i like the way that one looks stealthier i don't have seeds
it absorbs spells it's harder to see in pvp this thing actually looks pretty insane
i wonder how much damage that does we get it tested on somebody that one looks good
omit with plus 60 with 60 plus intelligence and you never would have to melee anything again
yeah but the problem with that is i need way more mana it's tested on this person never you
i don't know if that was me hurting them or if he fell and he literally did that little damage
well that's fucking dog shit did i just stagger him though upgraded this is more than the other
one is hold on it's probably this enemy type yeah run on some normal guys yeah it's really
cheap to cast i want to see how much comet does not on these guys because these guys are obviously
beefy bulky bozos but i'm still gonna do it that's in actually insane for how much
you know what i mean 466 damage these guys are insanely resistant that's big all right
oh what else do i got this thing's cool this is cool but i don't think i want it
i think i keep on loretta's great bow it's been tried and true this thing is stupid so it's coming
off we're still barrage i remember this this thing was we laughed at this we made fun of this
i wonder if this is better with more scaling all right i need to go upgrade big time and i have to
go check out the dragon stuff too time is it how long have i been streaming for
what am i missing i probably need some more yeah i need smithing stone five for this i don't think
the giant sells five i have to go get them find them somewhere this goes to s scaling after this
i mean that's a huge fucking deal s scaling uh i'm gonna pee i'll be back we'll figure this out
drb three minutes i'm gonna get some water okay how are you how you doing good you're going
uh i need to figure out where to get somber smithing stone five i didn't have any music shit
oops did you beat the big boss in the desert are you talking about radan because i did it was
horrible all right let's come back now i think we're gonna have to i think we're gonna have to
i don't know i need smithing stones i could also probably do with another sacred tier or two
and another flask and that seems that's all right but
i have no more love warts
so what are we doing i got the coin to where where is that grand lift that's what i want to do now
no i don't i want to see what this is we're gonna do that north leonia i want to see what that does
spend all the time getting it first of all we're going that way that swamp outside uh cilia yep
let me do this first though this thing's really world shaking yeah in there oh but that's a
gigantic pot that pot's in fact as big as a building so you guys must be thrilled right now
sky shot uh i gotta go around haven't been here excuse me i gotta go all the way around dude
come on really this is gonna kill me isn't it oh come on look at all that's not that far
where's the fastest fucking way to get over there i don't from here that was so far no it's not
it's not that far it's not it's not far i don't want to hear it what if you fell from that far
i'm not a magical baby okay if i was a magical baby i don't think i would die if i fell from
that far no i'm not sorry contrary to popular belief i'm not a magical baby now we go this way
and from here i have to keep this in mind because i gotta go around but where's a safe place i can
go around that way no it's the best way to get over there from here it's a magical baby
it would have been bad all right i see a dungeon down there and i want to go look at it
oh i'm gonna take more machine things this is just a boss uh no no i want a bonfire what happened
here i want a bonfire what the fuck why am i like a rodent get what the hold on
all right oh my god press the right button for once in your life 700 fucking damage
that was crazy all right comet is good very good comet is very very good i need a bonfire here
there's got to be one right here somewhere there's one that one anything looks good compared to
crystal barrage i mean i think comet really is just a fantastic move though always has been
i want to go in that dungeon but probably you need to level up one more time but see if i can do it
but we'll explore a little bit let's check and see i do want to buy i do want to level up one more
time what the fuck what was that oh it's these guys shut up all right it's time for the baby
rattles to really show us why i got it in the first place that's it for here that's sick yeah
no it is that's some sick shit you're right it's very cool it's a really good ambush weapon
oh look what the internet taught me 31 000 damage the guide told him that no i saw i saw a gif
i've been avoiding everything elden ring but i saw this gift i was like that was fucking cool
that was a pretty sick gift it wasn't a gif in the guide there's no guide it's fun to do that
though all right it's cool to do this you all know it like that spin and i think that pretty
much wraps it up although i need myself i'll go down and it's probably something cool down there
oh there's so many of them i'm only getting 25 souls for each one of these idiots it's not
even worth doing that was that was like 30 people that i just killed all right i need to find a
little space to level up dungeon here uh was it just a boss though it looked like just a boss door
or am i stupid and misremembering the thing that i just looked at it looked like a boss door
not a hard boss so what you're saying is i should just get in here and kill this thing
and this shouldn't be a big problem and i i it's a probably pretty easy boss
all right so i gotta prove myself here then what are you saying i got 35 000 uh souls on the line
and i gotta prove that i don't i'm not just like a katana
roch andy is what you're saying okay i get it i could i could see how you could be you could
think that yeah i could see that i could understand that uh criticism all right fine
i'll go do it right now okay i'll go do it right now let's go what an opener oh that was like the
fight to you this is like the baby rattle fight that was actually the baby rattle fight there's
that was like the item to bring here oh my god some bronze shield depicting the face of a fire
giant several tongues leap from its open mouth tongues of fire really holy shit this thing is
big this thing is irritatingly large it's a dud this thing's a dud i'm too weak oh that's a crazy
item that's what i use that's the best parry shield in the game yeah and i two-handed try
it still doesn't work imagine how shit you could have a place root b if i mean like i know it's
like funny and shit but wow how unbearable would this be that i can't use it i know people do it
though people do shield they upgrade the fuck out of the shield and i mean it doesn't i mean that's
bad but it probably scales okay see the people running around with two shields
like this i remember this strat people used to do this shit he's like okay buddy you having a good
time it looks like i'm trying to make myself a makeshift 1910 flying machine that's what this
looks like i've got like the big puffy airbag i've got aerodynamic head i've got weird shit on my
back like a sail and wings this is this is the 1910 we have to get somebody in a personal flying
machine okay that's very cool that was cool all right now i just need to level up a little bit
let's get the comet out what do you say the 1910 cotton candy build it's got splash damage on it
too it's crazy what is that thing get it away from me rattle can't be good i can't believe it
is fucked well you better believe it because it's not it's actually not a bad item all right
what was the goal the goal was to get to this building up here right i'm i gotta i gotta focus
i have to level up but still i gotta focus on what the hell i was doing are you oh my god oh my god
oh my god i'm dead i saw that come from a mile away and i didn't do anything about it i just
i stood there i was just sitting there looking at him in my mind it was there's no way he's
gonna come this far there's no way he's gonna come all the way over here he just kept his head down
like this and just dragged it on the ground across what seemed to be the entire game that makes such
a funny sound all right stop fucking around and just leave i don't even need to be he just hit
his friend do i have enough to level up yet i'm sick of you why is it fire everywhere who's shooting
the fire dude you can double it up did you see that so you can go charge it wham wham and that's
13 1400 damage at least it's actually insane okay cool i need more intelligence and i need to get
this thing leveled up so it scales better it it looked like scrappy do in the scooby-doo movie
where they get all fucked up from the souls i don't know that's very specific i don't think i know
what you mean i don't know what that means okay one with mr bean you know what we're doing we're
doing sorcery again doing intelligence again i'm getting this shit to 50 intelligence before i do
anything else all right now the plan was i was gonna go there so that's what i'm gonna do
i need mind all right the next time i get like two or three points it's a lot of it's going into
mine there's really another one right here mine gets better as you level it up i think basically
the opposite of all the other stats really there is one of these trees over here too
usually aren't they usually like a weird tree boss well shut up get stop it just get out of here
i was doing something great sword just a regular great sword yeah i mean they it's got it got it
has to be in the game right so i have a question for all of you souls fanatics is there a reason
to use a great sword like that when all these other wacky fucking items in the game exist
horse iron lip of ultra great sword oh this is the gut sword yeah because i mean like but if you
i mean it's cool but if i feel like there's somebody there's tons of interesting weapons
it's almost hard to justify using just a regular weapon like for instance is any is anybody just
using a long sword just like this like who who's using like the dagger i'm just yeah i'm using
the just dagger it's the regular dagger so many cool things it's hard to justify you and they're
probably fine they probably scaled really well it's like holy shit the scorpion stinger the
redo via the mr record day like there's so much cool shit oh i'm gonna use the stock are you
because like there's so much other crazy shit in the game you can swap out blade arts on normal
weapons okay so that's a big deal that's a big deal that justifies a lot of reasons to use it
because you can put whatever you want on it okay all right that makes sense that's okay i get it
blade art plus infusion that's true yep okay yep you're right i stand completely corrected
you're right but there's gonna be one of those bosses here right isn't there always one of those
weird uh tree uh like death root or something i think there is yeah go find out hmm of a dungeon
point me into the direction of the dungeon there's a dungeon down i gotta go down that way anyways so
let's go and that's how you get down there is that a church is that an npc all right let's go
that is a church all right i'll get a tear from this this place looks so weird
it's moldering church there's cookbook another cookbook there's no sacred tear here usually
there's a tear right where's the tear no tear what kind of church is this what kind of church is
there's no tear didn't i already look at this the the guts right invaded by anesthesia tarnished
eater where are they oh would you look at you oh that hurts you a lot doesn't it easy sacred
scorpion charm godfrey at last at the end of his campaign his golden armies unvanquished and
unbowed it finds grace lost tattered and faded talisman raises holy attack ah that's not me
that's not me but i'm surprised there's no um there's no sacred tear in there
yes we need to go down that tree you just beat that poor man's ass yes i did yes i did very much
so where was the way to get down there this way there's only a couple exceptions usually
they're in the churches of marika okay well there's a boss i'm not gonna fight that while
surrounding me
fucking surrounded by idiots all right it's you know what i'm doing you know what at the time
what the fuck do you guys keep coming from stage left and stage right where do you people keep
coming from there's somebody just constantly behind me stop all right what do you got who's this
her tree appetite bad be better way better hello fuck i didn't know that they that that she was
i look they just blew up the fucking round you know what fuck the horse baby time what are you
doing why is it so much rot everywhere what's all the shit everywhere why am i running what
okay holy damage and rot damage okay please i mean that way i've got that that's this i'm
gonna destroy this thing get the fuck over here get this fucking puke off me it's a pot it broke
the pot it broke the pot okay it breaks the pot i didn't know it's gonna break the pot
maybe rattle is not bad it's really not talk a lot of shit about it but it actually is pretty good
that move is the only reason to have it on it's pretty easy to predict oh so okay it's one two
three it takes a while but if you get an opportunity okay if it didn't have the first
hit this weapon literally throw it into the ocean right the first hit makes this worth having it's
slow but it's good yeah if it didn't have that first hit it'd be terrible okay cool may have
been a little over leveled for this one but i have never i haven't been here i'm very curious
about what that is this flask i didn't even know i existed till fucking halfway through the goddamn
game where where is that flask shit okay barely boost stamina recovery speed barely blue stamina
so stamina or stamina recovery speed was fire attack i gotta go to all these trees because i'm
i guarantee it is like an intelligence one or like a magic one
ariel keeps pointing this way still there it is okay so here's the dungeon i'll get off my
horse we'll do this minor urtree catacombs it's one that gives you unlimited fp that would be
insane i have to imagine i could probably just come in here and clean up because although i mean
this is not this is seem this is pretty early okay if i if i would have it from limb grave
go up you know like three days ago i may have come across this area so i'm probably a little
over leveled for this stuff but it's free shit and i want it this is brought
it is oh those things are rot on the ground hey we're gonna do boys and girls very good
okay so why is it still building what's why is it still building i'm not even standing in it what
was that huh i'm not why is it building why is it building i'm not standing over here
how do i go up from here how do i go up can i go up soap doesn't do anything i don't see
anywhere to go up am i insane no there's no i got and maybe back up the elevator
there's nowhere to go here i'm going to all the way down the elevator for what for that
oh no right here don't i can't die in here that would be embarrassing even if you're
over leveled for an area imp cat head whoa this thing's awesome holds trace amount of intelligence
wait i lose one intelligence but that's so much more defense cat baby is that worth taking off
the intelligence i mean i'm so much more immunity robustness maybe it's worth just putting on keep
it on this is the worst outfit like i came out of the trash it looked like like dumpster melted
action figure baby like this is an action figure that you melted and threw it away just dumpster
dumpster action figure forked greatsword this is an action league now character
this is a rick and morty joke or or okay the costume for every horror movie villain from like
2002 forward every like scary person outfit heavy door is open i kind of like it though
it's a little too dirty i think i'm going to alter this and take the the bib off and i think i've got
my character a heavy door opened it's like burnt yucky skin dude what did you expect um where was
the heavy door after a heavy door no is there a heavy door down there let me i'm gonna alter
this let me see what it looks like oh i can't take the weird gross skin off of really i have to keep
the gross skin on i don't want to go through this do i have any more of those anti-rot things
okay okay first time crafting ever time to make some scarlet rot make seven of them okay i have
seven so there's a way to go this way this character makes so much noise now with this
baby rattle oh no grabs oh shit what do i i just i what's up here you're not real excuse me what
i could be a wolf head this is endurance endurance and okay so you can do endurance
or intelligence this is more kind of it's kind of more like an alligator than it is a wolf
i think i'd be a wolf sacramental bud this place is kind of big it's a ton more down there
uh that's just the beginning of the dungeon right yeah right i think so
i think of the jungle it looks like alf it did kind of look like alf
i don't know i better keep the cat away from me i'll eat the cat that guy fucking ate cats
right like that's kind of weird now thinking about that like 25 years later
oh i'm gonna eat your cat like you know you're gonna eat the cat at the household like our pet
he was always talking about like eating their cat like alf fuck off you live here for free you
stay in it for free if we feed you you don't have to do anything you run like a weird like ham radio
fucking station out of the basement you're not eating mr fluffy it's not gonna happen boomer show
can't relate plus old and maybe one day you'll binge it on netflix if it ever goes there the
dated reference all his references are dated yeah yeah yeah yeah sorry sorry i'm 36 sorry i'm 36
i remember alf your boss down here or what there is and that's a long run so i better be able to
one-shot andy i better be able to one-shot andy this it's probably very easy encounter
don't say that because if you lose you're gonna look like an idiot it's two of those cats
oh shit oh my god i did so much damage hey let's watch what do you guys say you want to watch
let's watch all right don't okay let's watch go get him come on baby he's plus eight he better be
good just do something he's drinking a potion okay is he all right he might do it no you can do it
come on drink another potion drink another potion another potion you got you got another
one drink drink drink drink drink drink drink what is he doing that's the worst move in the game
that's the worst move in the game fuck off mad pumpkin head ashes okay that's kind of cool
mimic has your genes i'm sorry i would not cast collapsing star at this enemy he was just sitting
there getting pummeled his brain couldn't figure out what to do this charge r2 does so much damage
yeah this thing is actually good we just been we gave this way too much shit because the katana
is just like a broken unbelievable weapon it's the best weapon probably in the whole game
so everything else by comparisons like wow that thing sucks but no this thing's actually really
good if you can get this down especially during boss encounters it's like 1200 plus 1500 damage
when you do it this thing's really cool like eight out of 10 pvpers are using that katana
yeah i mean that holy shit i like it i think it's actually really cool i think it's it's fun it's
really cool looking all right so now that i did that let's head back to the entrance striking
damage yeah that's what i'm saying if you can get both if you hit the cat part and the explosion
will just is an extra especially when i and you know what all right all right decision has been
made let's go plus 10 plus nine i think this thing this is going to carry us steak i don't
think so because i honestly think that that left trigger is arguably arguably better than the
katana's l2 for one reason because it gives you more than one opportunity to hit it
this is a one trick andy weapon that's fine this is going to scale well with int it's already
doing as much damage right now as the katana i'm going to stick with my decision to get the
baby rattle to plus 10 let's do a little bit of an examination here 179 189 we're at
what we're going to see this okay 553 545 this has bleed it does which makes it ridiculous
but this is starting to fall off with magic scaling if both b and c this would be like 5
like 80 maybe with plus 9 you can compare it okay here we go so why is it lower what b
is it a lower b is like a b minus this is a plus 10 no it's plus 9 uh plus 9 versus plus 8
oh it's because of yeah right i mean this is a this is obviously a better weapon right let's be
obvious but i think this thing is gonna really shine somewhere okay what time is it let's get
we're getting close uh we're getting close to the end of the stream not quite yet i want to do a
couple more things i didn't even go to the area that i wanted to go to why is this marked no i
wanted to do this yeah i want to go to this urn tree because i want to do that painting thing
so i need to go i need to go this way just mark it i want to see the painting and there's a there's
probably there's an urn tree avatar that i didn't do here you don't die if you do this right i
thought you didn't you jumped into those things i thought you didn't if you jump into the wind thing
like if you jump down into it really i missed i wasn't close enough oh well i made it what is
what the what's with all the pots there's so many of them but that's accurate though right if i land
in that i don't get that's accurate right okay yeah i just thought i was losing my mind for a
second all right go oh very putrid too putrid holy shit okay well not uh i think we were on
the horse for this one this seems like a horse one what all right watch out for this holy shit
get that rod out of here all right again friendship friendship again yikes oh not a third swing i'm
fucking paranoid there is a third swing putrid you kill it by hitting it you don't there's no
time limit a hundred thousand souls what are you doing there's no time limit to beating a boss an
elder ring you want me to get in there and act like an idiot and go to overconfident hit him
like five times wrap around him five times and get killed no that's a lot of souls okay
what do those do makes attacks more likely to break enemy stances that's really good
rarely boost all damage negation uh so this is like this this takes one hit this is temporary
for a while this one's kind of cool but i feel like this would be actually the meta something
tells me you drink this before a boss fight you go fight a boss and you'll be breaking this stance
every five seconds i was hoping for a magic one but that's not it's not what we got let me go see
the painting all right this is it right here this is it i'm too high down there i got a hundred
thousand souls dude i got a hundred thousand souls that it right there that's it right there
is it safe is it safe to go down here that's literally it right there right there uh i don't
know how safe this is to go down this way i might have to go to that can i drop right here please
god please teleport mark it and come back please all right i'm gonna get into 50 and then we're
doing mind and vigor the rest of the game actually might all right i want to do that that looks
really cool that's a secret difficult parkour to get to this little thing and there's a teleporter
there you bet your ass i'm gonna go do that right now oh right i could just do that let's go
right here wait what was it where was it like right here right where was that wait where was
that oh right there okay get off the horse i can't get off the horse oh i didn't want to fall through
the middle nice aim the one the one spot that i couldn't do that on is where i fucking did it
way too cautious fuck at least it wasn't 100 000 no it wasn't all right i'm not hesitating let's
go where where even are the souls are the souls down here oh they're okay they're there oh they're
there what what happened there what was wrong with that what happened there i gotta land on
the branch what kind of fucked up masochistic sadist made it so you had to land on the branch
and not the pillar otherwise you die what kind of sadistic fucking masochistic where am i going
honestly what the fuck am i doing where am i going there's a bonfire down here don't jump are you
fucking out of your mind i didn't get this bonfire i guess not well that would have made
this a million times easier all right so now i gotta go to the alzheimer's ice what is my goal
my goal is there's a very very big deep super large on sale valuable secret that's down here
i just have to get it i just have to get there there's a very super valuable interesting secret
super cool and it's not this way it's over here watch and learn i'm so mad
i know and that's not like oh watch and learn here's a funny clip hi i'm not gonna do koto
no get out of there get out of there i'm too old for that i'm fucking 36 years old man i'm
not gonna start doing like koto leo way too old i'm too old for that actually too old for that
like i okay like a decade later i would have if someone i would have looked at that clip of
me being like i am koto leo and i would have been like fucking come on dude
i was walked off the edge i can't do i can't do koto leo
no don't go up this one i want to go on that branch i'm sliding get this shit out of the way
okay we're from here right there okay i did it i think i actually did it that branch right there
don't fucking die fuck
i can't wait for this to be just a smithing stone you know what
you're probably right it's probably a somber smithing stone core but i'll be damned if i'm
not gonna do this i'm gonna get to the bottom of that i'm gonna do it don't overshoot it
i got it let's go fuck yeah what's up here all right the plot the person is that because
like they that's an enemy that's an enemy why is there an enemy here it's a fucking ruin arc
what the fuck go off the cliff what is this guy what is this dude is steven spielberg
that guy just nobody died what happened did he kill that guy what just happened
why was that guy doing like a steven spielberg thing i think he killed that thing
fuck you break his legs maybe it's the sword no it's his arms it's his arms
i want to kill that guy i'll try one more thing plus nine rattle by the way yeah i know i mean
that guy's you're not supposed to be you're not supposed to fight this guy this guy's here
as a joke thank god i'm like i got the katana katana will the bleed work he's not that bad i
get it he's not that bad i just got speed around this part all right wait big axe he lands on the
ground hit him hit him in the hands how many souls is this not that much right all right he does the
big axe the the beam thing is not a big deal just bait it out give him the hands he's got a weak
rest his wrist is his wrist is weak no i i just got too greedy to hit the arms shit
shit that's such a pain in the ass to get down there there's nothing more down there he's down
there and i want to kill him i got him yeah the new spell was that the secret the guy like doing
the you're on camera routine there's a tp that's here that you can use so you don't have to jump
wait really how would i get up there how would i this thing is like on top of a building saved
hey there's no tp tp what are you talking about there's no tp if i think this guy's on a ledge
okay don't get greedy you need tp okay only a few times ready get out get out get out get out get out
all right i can just run from this can i line of sight oh shit there he goes
no he's not putting his hands down i guess i could get i guess i could i could maybe i
guess i could i can't go through him dude what the fuck what the fuck what oh my god the bait
bullshit like oh you're gonna hit me in the arms no you can't oh fuck you you swing so slow speed
it up fucking grandma break his fucking wrist he's so slow with that one no no
fuck is he gonna shatter his wrist and fall down i vote just shut your wrist and fall down
but he shot his wrist and go down i don't i don't understand charge charge him charge him
charge attack all right charge your doctor i missed i'm gonna go off the edge
fucking in a goddamn Disney ride why won't his arms break why won't he yeah that's like his boom
boom boom boom the red bar represents your health ban that guy for five minutes
i'm not doing physical damage with a staff all right i'm good i gotta put on i gotta put on a
fucking anime theme song i gotta put on an anime theme song oh it's gotta be attack on titan which
season season two season three all right i'll put on season three attack on titan intro i'm gonna
fucking die if i'm not fucking careful here slow it down a little i got it i'm everything's fine
we've saved it we're good to go nothing's problem stop moving season three intro no this one no not
this one and four he's in two this one this one this is a minute long guys this is literally one
minute long this fight's gonna take like six minutes one two i can't even hear the music
it didn't work it just made it louder and more annoying than usual what you're about to hear
is encouragement and praise with cheering applause i'm bringing out the big guns for this one
acknowledging you for a variety of reasons if there's a situation that does not apply to you
just listen and see how you feel so sit back get ready here it comes
don't be loud i'm just warning you we want to thank you for all your hard work you're the one
who steps up and gets things done around you keep your word deliver what you promise and then you go
the extra mile you're doing a great job a great job if anyone asks we'll tell them
we want to tell you that we have faith and we know you can do it we know you've got
great thing it takes to accomplish whatever your heart desires that dream the career you want
that recognition you're seeking it is yours just listen everyone agrees
we're on your side we're here for you we believe in you you can't
has ever happened in my life you've always been there for me and that's the greatest
gift anyone could ever receive the greatest gift anyone could ever give
you've got the biggest part of anyone i know dictionary and there's your picture
here
thank you my friend it's too funny it's too fucking funny it's seriously too funny like i
why did i put it on oh oh you know my friend what does he say it's fucking funny as shit
it's funny as fucking hell man it's so funny there's one line he says in particular and it
gets me every single fucking time no matter what i'm doing anyone could ever get no matter what
has ever happened in my life have always been there for me no matter what has ever happened
in my entire life you have always been like this guy doesn't know me at all i've never met this
guy before ever like i understand like encouraging cheers like oh we believe in you right but like
no matter what anything's ever happened in my life you've been there for me like this is just
a random guy on a cd all right last try let it play no matter anything whatever's happened in my
life it's so funny they used to charge for this i wish i remember watching the ads on tv and it
was the funniest fucking thing i know you know this but i want to say it again i'm so glad we're
friends that's the other one that's the other one that i he gets leans in really close to the
microphone no matter what has ever happened in my life where's the double jump fuck you i'm done
i'm done i'm done and that's the greatest gift anyone could ever where was the double jump i
would have got under there you saw that where was the double jump i would have nailed that where
was the double jump side we're here for you i'm so glad we're friends i don't know why i didn't
have a double jump what i don't need the horse fuck it want to say it again what the fuck are you
glad we're from software what are you talking about what the fuck i wasted two flasks no matter
what has ever happened and therefore you were received the greatest gift anyone could ever give
no you don't thank you my friend he's lying the wrong way you piece of shit
you fucking locked me in congratulations you did it you didn't let anyone or anything stop you
i didn't actually all your hard work has paid off i actually didn't do it you knew where you were
headed and you kept walking a straight line toward that goal you took the obstacles and made them
rungs on a ladder and now success is yours and it's all because of your commitment to yourself
you've earned it you deserve it feels good doesn't it i didn't win yet success is yours
all right thank you thank you for believing thank you for a million things
for your love and your support and your persistence and your patience and your courage
when life was the craziest but i didn't have a clue when i kept going down the wrong road
you were all
you stood nearby prayers and you knew the truth and it worked
i wouldn't be who i am today if it were not for you and together
because wouldn't go over again all this is for you there don't stop now just keep going
the finish line is closer than you think we can see it
drop is out please shit the rocks can hit you i thought it was a cosmetic
i know 60 years over it's more than half full you're smart and you're creative and you're courageous
so the truth you stand up for what you believe you learn from your mistakes and you laugh easily
often at yourself when you dream you inspire others to dream
no please please please oh my god i thought that was the other one oh my god he killed me in one hit
he killed me in one fucking hit he killed me in one fucking hit he killed me in one hit he killed
me in one hit i thought i got under his legs i didn't i don't know how he hit me with that i was
between his legs i was between his legs wasn't i the fucking axe didn't even touch me the thing
didn't even fucking touch me what the fuck fuck you what no no no way no way no way no way
is a blade on the hilt no no way no way i'm all right fuck this guy no way how i was i was
literally in between his fucking legs i'm pissed you weren't completely healed so it did ninety
seven point fucking five percent of my hp you've got to be fucking kidding me that's so fucking
annoying time for the meat grinder there's time i like fuck i could i couldn't stagger
you can only stagger it seems with this all right i can't fucking believe he killed me that would
have been such a great end too you annoying little fuck didn't stagger i wouldn't i would be very mad
if he didn't he can't believe it that's why i was so desperately trying to keep at full health too
because like god damn it man that the fucking move and it's just i i want to look at that clip
because i want to see how i got hit we're on doom music fuck this enemy he's gonna drop he's gonna
drop a smoldering butterfly but i'm gonna shove this sword down his throat and just twist it
around in a circle i fucking this guy sucks he's in a shit area he's got instant fucking kill moves
no it's not it's he's got he's got one hit kill moves i don't care who you want
before i go again people saying hit his legs i i don't think you i don't think it staggers him
i think you could only staggers with with a molten smoldering molten is right
it's like you you have to break the smoldering stuff you can you can do his legs you can stagger
anywhere this version he has his legs covered no legs don't no no no you have to do the arms
you don't have to do the arms it staggers but it's weaker his wrist is weak yeah whatever how loud
is this gonna be no i want like the from the first age from the first dagger from the first
there it is gonna be loud gonna be loud warning gonna be loud i'm not kidding
music get the music pumping what's with this low moment come on
get it get it get it get it get it i missed i tried to dodge the second one it's up there
what the fuck my right trigger my right trigger got fucking stuck i swear to god i'm not making
that up i swear to god what's happening why is that happening oh my fucking i'm dead
it's over it's bad news my right trigger is fucked the fuck did i break my controller
i got the golems halberd i think it's just really sweaty and i was slipping on it
seems overly sensitive right now though like literally look at this pretty like like weird
all right nice it was nothing what i already had one of those
oh dude but i can do dual wielding that was not worth doing at all there's no reason to kill that
guy there's absolutely no reason to kill them unless you want to um that was cool that was
kind of cool all right so is there anything else here yeah but now you but now you're the one person
that killed that guy i am am i how come this is not achieving for it i got the spell yeah
there's nothing else here how do i teleport you're not gonna put like a magical gigantic giant
golem over there and not have this something be pulled that he drops like a giant golem magic
sword all right well what did i get yeah i i'm not streaming for the next couple days so
we're gonna keep going not for long not for long not for long not for long only like 20 to 30 look
at how red i am only like 20 to 30 minutes tops i there's something i i want to go to that hot
i'll forget about it the one that i was gonna do before this is my voice holy shit i'm all fucked
up okay it's an ash of war grants affinities and skills brain of arrows archery skill this is an
archery skill this is the bows not seeing any of these yet uh i want to do i want to do this
from here probably how do i get there i forget i think it's from here over here because i gotta
go down to that way going this way let's go i gotta go to see off a river the gargoyle locked
elevator is that the place that uh for my notes the offer has a stone sword key elevator is that
what it is oopsie look at that guy that was crazy i'm off fighting that one the elevator is required
looks like i can get here from here i can't did i do this tree yeah i think i did right i do this
tree yeah you can jump up the crystal but it's probably not intended um all right
i have tons of those keys i'll do it look at the swamp there's an exit to the north
oh shit i can't get there i have like 12 of those keys i'll do it let's see where this goes
this game looks so pretty it is pretty this is gonna take me up i'm gonna be inside that building
okay
long elevator okay ah very very interesting okay so this is how you have to get here and there's
one of those things over there we're just gonna investigate this line here and then i'm done
and then we're gonna figure out what to do with this game going forward i'm gonna play mario golf
i don't know which one i don't know which one do you want me to play i don't which one do you
want what do you which one was that person talking about the new one don't these guys
usually hang out around the um boss wells whatever they are i don't see one anyway
i don't think i was gonna miss that rune the newest one he can't shoot me he just shot himself
again did he not just shoot himself he didn't who did he shoot i thought i could i was going
to be an absolute badass right there why couldn't you have been why couldn't the other one have been
that easy what's the name of the weapon you're using uh uggie baby's baby bonnet what's the name
of the uh the actor from barney baby what is the name of the what's the what's the what's that
dinosaur's name what's the what's the dinosaur's baby baby bop yeah baby bops uggie baby baby pups
uggie baby bonnet thought he was going down what just died all right what's in here time is it all
right i i actually have to like go i gotta get up tomorrow this is it how do i move them need to go
to 6 a.m mass no that is not what i'm doing why what do i do i'm back someone's on the ground
there are summoning signs well all right i i i i i i'm out of gas oh shit these these okay
these are red knight of the great jar and wait i'm running adversary i don't get it what's this
fucking camera okay i like that just fucked me up so bad i'm like why are we stuck i like was moving
my i had the wrong spell equipped like i i i could have beat that guy in literally fucking five
seconds it's not bad time no no no oh my god that's far away and like the weird invisible wall that
was behind me that just threw me off and then like i had i just like i don't even know why it's on my
loadout i don't even why three of these are on my loadout what's the point let me just kill it
just kill it please i'm not streaming tomorrow i'm not streaming tomorrow and i'm not streaming
for like a couple days and i'm gonna play mario golf for like 30 minutes to like just to like do
something else so people don't think i'm like a fucking one game andy and then i'm literally
gonna play this game we're gonna open the menu of mario golf and i'm gonna do my settings and
then i'm gonna go back in ellen ring okay where are those signs right here no that's not gonna be
bad is it what i deserved oh nice guard counter
all right are you happy are you happy doulus knight of the great jar has died are you happy
you're gonna let me in now you gotta kill them all don't you of course you do fuck all right i'm
being greedy stop being greedy stop being greedy actually stop being greedy in play we're three
last one this guy looks to be the strongest of the three we'll find out no cheese i'm wasting
time don't attack yet that's a lot of stuff don't use magic don't use magic don't use magic
i jumped over his fucking head he actually hit me fuck you he's getting closer gravity well
whatever this is i'm dead fuck you i don't have any heals left i'm fighting him first
the eternal darkness is a good idea i just we're going one three two because the second
guy is the easiest dude get that shit out of here you're a righteous little shit
okay one three two i'm gonna get eternal darkness ready i should absorb the spells
actually fucking amazing i was too busy marveling at how cool that spell was that i'm gonna die
damn it it's like it's the all the buttons you have to press to fucking do it
i just gotta keep the
out of gas i'm i'm at the tank's empty these guys really aren't paying that much
pay the ass but the tank is literally on empty this guy is the fucking worst of the three of
them without a doubt he just has so much shit to do he's just he's like five times faster than me
and has i don't know this guy is the fucking worst the other two like literally just go home
like why would you why what's the point of having the other two guys you are you are not even close
to being as good as this guy is like not even close not even fucking close both of you go home
oh don't come back either he doesn't we don't need three bodyguards we have this guy we have
we have dualist that's not all right it's time it's time for bed his name is it dualist right
not duelist not do you list he's a dentist i made it up for fucking content relax this
guy's just the hardest of three use the katana i feel like the katana is cheating at this point
all right i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done it's over it's over it's
over it's over it's ending precisely 60 seconds one not night now don't count yet
okay they they just doubled at the same time sure all right we gotta get a confidence boost fight
confidence boost fight that's this guy right here confidence boost fight bring him up this guy's a
piece of shit he's a chump awful at everything he's not very good and i'm gonna get a backstab
right now three two one idiots oh i would normally dodge that you always i i have to
unplug the fucking internet i would normally dodge that without a problem at all i gotta
unplug the ethernet cable good enough sloppy these dodgers are this is bad this is ugly
oh yeah there's no way i missed that in any out any other scenario there's no way i missed that in
any other scenario all right we're gonna summon the fucking great gatsby whatever this guy's name is
i will say though i'm really glad that i fixed the internet thing it was the server it was the
twitch server unfortunately it is i don't know what that means though because the server that
i normally stream on i don't have any fucking mana really that was great this will though
all right so what i was gonna say was
um i've been streaming on a server for like two years and i can't stream to it anymore
i don't know what happened all right just dodge and swing and attack i forget about dealing with
the black hole thing that doesn't matter just kill him yes we're good let me in great jars arsenal
that hit i can't be it axe equipment load can i get in now oh did he move out of the way
just start smacking them really i can't get in here well i'll have to figure this out another
time pretty cool though looks interesting over there all right pretty cool there's there might
be something else i can do there but uh i am gonna just go back to the town we're gonna do
one quick little thing to wrap it up actually i'm gonna put the credits on the screen that makes
sense right doesn't it thanks for watching everybody i appreciate it i'll see you guys
guys i will see you guys oh i need to go down here i'll see you guys in two days so monday
tuesday i'll see you guys on wednesday for mario uh i'll see you guys from mario mario golf
see a little face cam i'll see you guys mario golf and then uh this is me talking
uh i can't even speak well that'd be technically technically technically three days but it
technically is the next day right now oh it is technically sunday so that would be three days
technically right two and a half whatever it is thanks for all the subs there were a lot there
was a couple of major gifted subs thanks guys appreciate it i still can't upgrade this i can't
upgrade i need a five which i don't know where i can even get one let's figure that out in a few
days but it's awesome i'm having a bunch of fun i haven't done really any of the main campaign
stuff really besides obviously the rena stuff which was really difficult i'll see you from mario
golf thanks for watching sunday wait sunday oh shit yeah you're right that's true that would be
three days right because it is the next day so yeah i'll see you tuesday i mean yeah right right
my brain was just trying to figure that out because it's the day is already here right right
right right right i'll see you guys on tuesday the eighth at four p.m pacific yeah i i meant it to be
two days not three days see you guys on tuesday mario golf and probably more elden ring great
evening great night thanks for watching bye good night take care take care of yourselves
uh raid who is even live right now how many who is even live let's see raid bob ross let's see
there's a few people i could do it too
no not bob ross i'm not gonna raid bob ross
you just go to bed cat go raid whoever tell him germa sent you
uh xqc is live yeah boxbox is live um moon moon is live i don't you know what just spread out
i don't know how to do this too and i got i am fucking dead and i need to leave now
because everybody's just spread in five or six different directions some of you go to box box
some of you go to xqc some of you go to moon moon some of you wherever you want to go just
iron mouse is doing yeah the subathon so yeah there's a lot of places to go i just can't decide
i can't pick i'm too tired good night we'll do a proper we'll raid somebody proper um next time
good night guys we'll do remind me to do a proper raid tuesday at four o'clock that's correct pacific
see you soon good night guys