Okay, so guys, welcome to Binding of Isaac, my playthrough, or my first one, I guess.
Ooh, I got the eye, the pinky eye. I forget what this thing does.
TF2 would not work. I couldn't get it to- I couldn't stream it for some reason.
It was all laggy and glitchy and crazy, and I couldn't do anything about it.
I'm gonna have to figure out why that's happening, because that's not good at all.
Not at all. You have nothing for me. I didn't really find anything besides the
chance to do poison. That's pretty sick. I don't have any bombs or anything. Looks like we're just gonna go fight the boss.
Kane versus Pin. All right, Pin, what you got?
You ain't got nothing on me, buddy. I see the one that just kind of jumps out. It's, uh, it's that agreement right there. Cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
Bully!
Ow!
No, I wish Burger Boy was in this game as a playable character.
Whoa!
Why am I not hitting him?
He just killed himself.
What a stupid bastard.
Ding ding, ding ding, ding ding ding ding ding, let's go.
The basement, too.
You know, how I'm not playing as Isaac? So I don't have the bomb, the luxury of having like, the bombs.
Get out of here. Get out of here! Boop boop boop. Actually, I gotta plug my headphones in. That's one thing I didn't do.
Headphones, you're in. And, oh, are you sure you want to do this? Yes, I'm sure. I'm as sure as I'm gonna be.
Aren't I? Let's go!
How do you record games with fraps? F9, I think, is by default.
The Book of Shadows, I love this thing. This gives you a shield when you hit space.
Any bombs? Envy! Oh, Envy.
Envy's got nothing on me. Envy's got nothing on you.
Oh, and for future reference, if you're watching this on YouTube,
and I'm responding to random questions on the stream.
So I'm not talking to Burger Boy, or he's not here with me.
Otto's not in the room with me.
So, Otto, what do you think about fraps, like in F9?
This is Wrath of the Lamb. Wrath of the Lamb DLC.
Excuse me, sir.
I love the noise those guys make.
TF2 is not going to start, unfortunately.
I have to do some bug fixes, or find out why the stream was lagging, like, incredibly.
X-Split, it was X-Split. I have no idea why.
It's something I have to spend some time with.
Question is, actually, can I put the Book of Shadows on and walk in here?
I bet I can, let's find out.
Oh, absolutely I can. Oh, baby, look at that.
And pills, I'm Kane, taking the pills would be good.
Tears up, hell yeah.
And what's this going to be?
Health up. Look, and you know what? I'm going to get hurt right here.
It was worth it. Totally worth it. Totally worth it.
Yeah, the YouTube chat is not really ideal.
When you write a message, let's say like five people write a message at the same time,
it kind of puts everything in a queue, and spams it after like two minutes.
It's very weird.
Da da da da da.
Secret room, baby.
Oh, that's a dime. That's a dime.
Okay, now I'm going to go in the coin room.
Going in that coin room.
Let's see.
Alright, this is a bunch of pills, I think, isn't it?
That's the coin purse.
I think that's the coin purse.
Yup, oh my god, and look at this.
I'm going to buy these pills over here, too.
This is going to be insane.
Bombs are key.
What's this one? Health up. Health up again.
Oh my god.
What is this?
Balls. Look at this, guys.
And I'm going to buy this, too.
Whatever this is, it's going to be good.
Oh, we're going to be teleport pills.
Yeah, Kane, if you have any pills when you're playing with Kane,
then you'll never get bad pills, ever.
There's health in that room, I want it.
And I want this, too.
What? What just happened?
What the hell was that?
Alright, I just put a bomb down right here,
moved over and put up, and then looked over at the chat,
and then I got hurt.
What just happened?
Did the bomb come up with me? Did the fly hit it?
What the hell was that?
Oh.
I looked over at the chat, like, what are people saying?
Dang, I get hurt.
I wanted to open this. Oh.
Come on, now.
The reason why I'm not streaming on Twitch anymore
is because I get 720 on YouTube.
I'm not partnered on Twitch.
Because I have a contract with Machinima
that makes it so I can stream on here.
I can't believe I didn't get that.
I can't believe I did not get that item.
I'm an idiot.
Get away from me.
Alright, so it looks like we got some fruit punch right here,
some Hi-C ecto cooler.
If anyone knows what that is, you get plus 20 German points.
Yeah, that right there,
that green stuff right here is ecto cooler.
Hi-C ecto cooler.
The rest is fruit punch.
Let's keep going.
Pinkie eye.
Oh, God.
Why do they have to have such big tears?
Okay, I got the book of shadow again.
I got the book of shadows.
I need bombs.
I need bombs bad.
Get away from me.
A nickel.
These guys can't do anything.
I don't want to get myself hurt.
Curve the bullet like in wanted.
Oh, come on.
You're better than this, Jerma.
I miss you every single time.
Oh, God.
Where's Boo?
Boo.
BooMan61 is my binding of Isaac.
My binding of Isaac buddy.
He tells me all these things I need to know.
Pinkie eye or match stick?
I think I'm going to stick with pinkie eye.
So wait, the 720 stream is bad?
Is that what you guys are saying?
The 720p stream is not good?
That doesn't make a whole lot of sense.
I don't understand why.
Whole lot of weird stuff going on in today's stream.
I don't know what's going on here.
Boom.
Yeah, you got nothing, Sloth.
Sorry, Sloth.
But you dead.
Favorite class in TF2 is the engineer.
Yeah, I just want...
No, I don't want that.
The book of shadows, because the book of shadows is really good.
I got my fly buddy
flying with me.
He's going to bend the knee and...
Wait, where is he? Oh, yeah, that's right.
He comes out randomly when I shoot people.
That's an amazing item, by the way.
Me and my fly
going to fly away
to the end of time.
Oh, no, mini greens. Book of shadows.
I had to. I'm not losing all my money.
These guys are shooting at me.
Get out of my face.
Ha ha.
Well, the resolution has nothing to do with
the chat.
It's just the YouTube chat is
bad.
I'm not going to sugarcoat it.
The YouTube streaming chat
is not so good.
Ugh.
I hate these enemies. When you get in a room with these guys
and there's more than three or four of them,
say your prayers,
because they are so annoying.
I don't have any money.
Test tomorrow, dude. I forget your name.
I went by way too fast.
Good luck on your test. Anybody who has a test.
Good luck on your finals.
If you already had them, I hope you aced them.
And if you haven't had them yet, then
go in there and sack them silly.
Metaphorically.
I'm going in here.
Get me some items.
Ooh.
Oh, big problem.
Triple shot, baby.
I killed plenty of birds.
Look at that.
This could be a good playthrough
if I'm not an idiot.
Oh, like that.
I thought I could hide behind the thing and move.
But there was a rock in front of me.
I need to open this.
There might be hearts in there.
I need to.
No, but there's a nickel.
Across the pond in Wales. That's a far away.
That's a far away away.
Ooh, the battery.
Look at it out of my head. How gruesome.
Alright, I got a lot of good items,
but not a whole lot of health right now.
I cannot screw this up.
I really need to, like, pay attention and not die.
Because that would be so bad.
Alright, I got everything I need.
Can't get to the secret room.
I don't have any bombs.
I am not going to do TF2 again today.
Because it's just...
I don't want to have to do the headache.
I'll have to try and test it out later.
Alright, husk.
This is not going to be easy.
Try hard mode.
Have to, like, pay attention to only the game.
Just for fun, I'm turning it on.
I don't want a chance to bump right into him.
Come on, bump across, baby.
Alright, we're good to go.
What is this? Eight ball?
Oh.
It gave me, like, a rag on my head.
What the hell?
I am the magician.
Alright, doesn't the magician take you to the secret room?
No, he doesn't.
This game is not free.
It's pretty cheap, though.
This game is only
five dollars on Steam.
Actually, isn't there a sale going on for it right now?
Or is the sale over?
Yeah, the no damage achievements, I don't know, man.
I don't think I could ever get those.
Because you'll get so confident,
you'll get to the end of a level and be like,
I got this in the bag.
And then you just die.
Oh my god, I got rage now.
As long as I play this safe,
I will beat this whole game right now.
I can't be stupid about this, though.
I gotta be smart. I gotta be smooth.
Oh, god.
The liberty cap is a random
mushroom
every room.
And this is a chance to have poison.
I think I'm gonna stick with the mushroom, guys.
Because I want those random mushroom achievement thingies.
Achievement, what am I talking about?
Yeah, I see I got a massive, like, speed increase now.
And, like, I'm kinda just little.
Is my mind playing a trick on me?
Or is this just damage?
I think it's just damage. I'm not going in there.
Screw that.
Exam tips? Well, good luck on your exams.
I actually made an exam tip video.
Did you, uh,
did you check that out?
Look at how little I am.
Hey, look, I'm tiny.
Get away from me.
There we go.
That's what I'm talking about.
It was a spy video from, I think, like a month ago.
How you see damage? I wish you could see damage in this game.
It'd be an interesting feature.
Little numbers popping up over everybody's heads.
Oh, what's that?
What's that do? I don't know.
Whatever. I don't want it. Pride.
Get away from me, Pride.
Oh!
He's doing it too often.
I can't, will you do the other move?
Wow, he didn't do the
he didn't do the other move once.
What a son of a bastard.
I forget what the Emperor card does.
Boo! Boo!
I need your help, Boo!
Anytime I'm in a Skype call with Boo, I'll just say an item
and he'll go
Oh, that does
plus 25 damage.
And I'll go, thanks, Boo.
I don't know what it does.
But I'm gonna keep it.
I have faced Super Greed. He's a pain in the ass.
He's a super pain
How did I not get hit right there?
Don't ask me how I did not
get hit. I have no idea.
I need that heart.
Take that and I'm gonna get this
heart because I need it.
Woohoo!
Boo does have quite a sexy
voice, I will tell you. It is true.
I can't get these bombs!
Teleports you to the boss room.
Good to know. Thanks a lot, dude.
Good to know. Oh, I'm turning
this on because I need it. Do I have
enough money for anything? Let's find
out.
I'm gonna get it. It's always good to have.
And Steam Sale, I...
Probably should
have tried to find the secret room to get the
Steam Sale. I think it's gonna be
right here.
Oh!
Yeah!
99 bombs.
That makes me happy.
Now I'm gonna go blow up every
damn thing in
the item room down here.
Well, not the gambling room.
Hey, what's going on?
I love your little casino here. Everybody
is gonna...
I'm gonna kill myself.
I just tried to make a joke right there
and my brain is too dumb to be able to
make a joke and do my joke at the same
time.
Whatever.
Let's go boss room.
bossfight.com.edu.
Cain versus Fistula.
This can...
You know what? I need to start dropping some tactical
bombs. This guy can
be a real pain in the butt.
Oh god! That was some dodging
right there! Oh my god!
How did I do that?
Alright.
Okay.
Juicy juice. Jesus juice.
Pretty cool. I'm good to go.
Ah!
I apologize for the coughing.
I'm still sick. Full health.
You know what that means.
Oh, get away from me.
That was a collateral right there.
Oh god!
Thank you for saving me.
Book of Shadows. Appreciate it.
Okay.
That's another situation
where I hit E
right here to drop
the bomb. I moved over here, looked at
the chat, and I would have just gotten hurt
because I wasn't paying...
Alright, let's not do that again.
What? Oh.
Why did...
Why did that not work?
Okay, that's good to know that
that's here.
Why did that not work? Flies, get out of the way!
You're ruining everything.
Thank you.
If I find one of those blood donation machines, I'm going to
use the hell out of it.
There's nothing I can do to get away from that.
I hate...
I hate these enemies.
If there's one enemy I hate in the game...
Okay, I gotta be quiet. I need to try odd now.
Oh, I'll take it for sure.
It's a trap!
Let's go. Another room with these stupid
brain bastards. I hate
these guys. You know what?
Everyone just blow up right in here.
Thank you.
Some might call that a waste. I call it
a journey. Oh.
Okay.
I think the secret room is... Oh, no!
No!
You know what? Everyone, come here.
Let's all have a family picnic. Come stand
right next to me.
That's how I deal with those guys.
I got plenty of bombs. Oh, great.
Greed. It's alright.
It's just regular greed. He's a wuss.
It's just regular greed. Don't worry.
Give me that money, and give me your key.
Oh!
Get away!
I'm not going in there. Those rooms always
give me trouble. I always die.
How do you shoot at an angle?
So, when I hit up, and I move to the
left a little bit, it kind of like
curves it. So, if you hit left and up
kind of at the same time, you'll curve
your bullets. Like, bling, bling.
You can do it any direction, too.
It doesn't have to be up or down. See, I can do
it left and right, too.
I think I'm going to be alright. If I can get some more
health up, I should be able to kill Mom's
Heart. For sure.
Oh, oh, okay, okay, okay. I won't do
this. Don't worry.
I promise you, I'm not crazy.
This room, if you don't know, because this is Wrath of the Lamb.
This is Added in Wrath of the Lamb.
When I walk over this, it hurts me.
For a heart. But, it has a chance
that it's going to drop something good in the room.
So, I'm going to keep doing it.
Come on, keep hurting me.
I know you want to give me something.
Oh, fine.
Because now, I can just go all the way over here
and go back to that room where all those hearts were.
And...
I'm fine.
What? What? What?
What? What? What? What?
Okay.
Oh. I almost
just had a heart attack. I thought I could not get back
into this room.
I would have just been so bad
right there.
I don't have enough for the ladder.
I'll probably get it later. What is the Sword
Room? The Sword Room,
when you go in there, you can only go in there with full health.
And it's a...
You fight a wave of enemies.
Three waves of enemies.
And then after, you get to have the item that's in the room.
It's pretty cool. I don't...
I just never go into it because I always end up getting myself
killed in there. Troll Bomb,
get away. Now I can get the ladder
if I want it. No!
Stop it. You
bad pets.
I'll go get it. Might as well
have it, right? Might as well own
it. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go. I'll have you.
Thank you very much.
Oh. I don't need the heart.
Because I can go up here.
Blue hearts are spirit hearts.
So when I pick up a spirit heart,
it lasts
only as long as it's there.
See how the red hearts are there pretty much
permanently? The spirit hearts
are only there until they get... If I get
hurt right now, it's going to take that spirit heart away and I don't
get it back. Even if I get health.
I'm playing Bomberman right now. I feel like
I'm like spelunking. Ooh,
the rock. Oh, I
must be doing max damage, am I?
Yeah, I'm doing the maximum amount
of damage you can do in the game.
So that's good. That's good.
I'm stuck.
Oh, I got
stuck on the rock.
I think I have my book of shadows.
Okay, that's Epikac.
I don't want it. Is that
Epikac or is that Chemical Peel?
I don't know. I don't want it.
I hate Epikac. Epikac
makes you shoot like those green balls and you can
hurt yourself with it. I always kill
myself, guaranteed, with it every time.
Cane versus war.
One of the four horsemen.
Oh my god, I am destroying
him. I am absolutely
destroying him. Wow.
Usually this guy takes a lot more hits than this.
Okay, see you later, man.
And I got a cube of meat.
And that's Chemical Peel? That's Chemical Peel?
Alright. No deal with the
devil. I don't want the deal with the devil.
Chemical Peel.
If that's Chemical Peel, then I will get it.
I'm so scared, but what if it's Epikac?
Alright.
At least a dozen people have said it's
not Epikac.
Oh, thank god.
This game is
so worth it.
Somebody just asked if it's a game worth it.
Yeah, it's worth it. Absolutely.
It is probably the best game
I've played for under
twenty dollars ever.
This game is only five bucks.
Without the sale,
the expansion and everything, I think
it's eight dollars with everything.
But, I mean, I've spent
more money on games
that I've never played than I have
on this. I bought Deus Ex
for sixty dollars, and I
played the game for an hour and ten minutes.
I didn't like it.
I never heard this music before.
Actually, no, I think I have. I hate
these enemies. These are the worst. You have to kill their hearts.
Die!
Oh, thank you. Yeah, this game
is four dollars and ninety-nine cents
to buy it.
I have the expansion, though, as well. I think the expansion
is three bucks. So it's going to
cost me eight dollars for everything. But
there's a Steam sale, I think,
still going.
You know what? I'm going to quench this once
and for all. I'm going to just look
and see how much this is.
View store page.
Binding of Isaac.
Okay, so, the Binding, yeah, so it is
four ninety-nine for the Binding of
Isaac, if you can see. And then
the Wrath
of the Lamb DLC is
three bucks. So there you go.
The Steam sale is over on it,
apparently. It was over a while ago, I think.
It's a very good price.
The last time I spent
less than five dollars on a game,
or five dollars on a game, and
I'm using this.
Under twenty dollars, last time
I spent that and actually, like, really enjoyed
it and played for a long time, was probably
Orcs Must Die.
Orcs Must Die, I got a lot of playtime
out of that and the game was only fifteen bucks.
So it's, yeah, I'd say
it's a steal at this price.
You'll put at least thirty to fifty hours
into this game. If you really enjoy it,
you'll put at least thirty hours into
it, at least. Oh,
Otto. Where is Otto?
My dog. And
oh, I didn't want to open that. I could have just blown it up.
I could have just blown the damn
thing up. Flatpenny.
No, I don't want that.
I do not want you.
Go! Ah!
Ah, what a bad place for these enemies.
At least I have this.
I would have taken so much damage right there.
It's not even funny. I would have taken
a thousand points. I would have died.
I probably would have died right there. Geez.
Oh, get away from me, you
jumping frog freaks.
Ah, damn it.
There we go. See you later.
Ah!
Yeah, you know, I looked, I was looking
at DayZ. DayZ
looks pretty cool. I just, I thought it was
a standalone mod
or a standalone game.
Arma 2 was like fifty dollars
for the whole package, isn't it?
I need to drop some
cash on that.
You need Arma 2 and then you need Arma 2,
one of Arma 2's expansion packs
or something to be able to play it.
I think Arma 2 was thirty-nine or forty
or something. When I saw that
I was like...
I'm going this way. So Arma 2 is thirty
and then you need an expansion too, don't you?
That expansion.
Let's go, you...
Oh, you egg burger.
You know what? Let's go.
Let's fight. Come stand next to me.
We'll talk.
I keep thinking
that...bad, bad. I can't even hit
this guy. Get out of the way, you son of a...
Ugh.
This guy is blocking the way of me shooting him.
Stupid son of a B-I.
I-I-I.
Capital I.
Everybody in this room blows up.
Arma 2 is free? What?
Arma 2 is...last time
I looked at it, Arma 2 was money.
Diablo 3's real money auction house,
I have not even used it.
I don't
even care. I was mad
about it at first and I was kind of like
that's a little weird, but
it's got to help
drive the game for years.
So I'm not really
all that concerned about it.
Open sesame. I think I'm going to fight mom
here in a second. Maybe this
next room. Number dime.
Alright, let's go fight...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I need to get some...
I get some coins.
I got coins.
Operation 2033
Metro.
That game's coming out with a sequel soon, aren't they?
I'll get the compass just cause I'm not
going to be able to buy anything later.
Alright, let's go fight. Let's go fight
mom's big, fat,
disgusting leg.
Follow me. I don't want
to go in the sword room. It scares
me. Cause if I lose health
and I die to mom,
I am going to be
PO'd. Let's go
mom. Oh, what do you say
mommy dearest? Come on,
step on yourself. Oh, she
is...I'm killing her so bad.
Ugh.
Alright, that's fine. Go ahead, swap me. I don't care.
And she's going to do it.
Isaac.
Hahaha.
Let's keep going. I only got
two more rooms. And then maybe
I can go...I don't know if I'm going to be able to go to Shoal.
I don't think I've beaten the game enough times to go
to Shoal every time.
Ugh. What's that?
What's that? I want to look at it.
Cursed skull. Oh, boo.
Boo, what does this do?
Ugh, I don't know.
What does a cursed skull do, guys? Does anybody
know? Does anybody know?
I need to know what it does.
Cause if it's good, I want to keep it.
Alright, we'll come back to it. I'll come back. It's going to
be there. Cursed skull is bad.
Okay. Alright, good to know.
Do not get this.
Okay.
Chest inside of a chest. Chestception.
Get away from me.
Health up. Exactly what
I was looking for. Oh, it's me.
Go get him, flies. Yeah.
The Book of Shadows is the thing that's
making this playthrough possible.
It really is.
Oh, go, go, go, go, go! Yes.
Um...
Lord have mercy on me. Geez.
Health up.
Health up again.
Oh my god. You're going to be
kidding me. Teleport pills. Let's just take
them. I'd like to thank
the Book of Shadows for making this possible
because without him, I wouldn't be
receiving this award and I want to thank
my mother and my father and my parents.
Alright, I'm not going in the secret room.
Let's take a look who's in there.
My buddy Greed.
The name's Greed.
Oh, gad.
See ya.
If Isaac's health is brought down to half
of a heart, Isaac is then teleported
to the last room completed.
Um, that sounds
pretty incredible. That sounds pretty
ridiculous. Actually, but to be
honest, even if you complete the last
room with half a heart, when you get to the next room
after the last room, you're
probably going to die.
That's still pretty cool though. If I did
not have the mushroom, I would absolutely be taking
that. Get out of here,
you spider.
I never liked spiders.
Creepy-crawly. You want to thank your
mother? She tried to kill you.
This is true. This is very true.
But I have a short
term memory loss. I forgot that.
I forgot those things.
Get. I hate these guys.
These guys are annoying. I stick
my head up and then, no, I joke, bye, you
don't hit me. Yes, I will take
that. Every single door is
now open down here.
What's the game from E3 you're looking forward
to the most? Um,
I, you know, the Wii U.
The Wii U is actually
really, really cool.
It's, it's very, very interesting.
It's kind of like when the Wii first came out.
It was like, what is that?
I think I might just get it.
It looks like it could be fun.
Because the coolest thing in the entire world
with the Wii U, let me, I'll explain this.
This is the coolest thing ever.
So if you're playing on a TV
that's, and then you're like, let's say you're in your
living room. And
somebody comes in and they say, oh,
I want to, I want to, I need the TV, I want, I want to use
the TV. And you're like, dude,
I'm playing a game. You want this?
No, no, you can't take the TV. And
sometimes, I mean, back when I was younger, it
didn't matter how much you complained.
Or how much you wanted to, oh my
god. Or how much you wanted to
stay in the room. You had to get kicked off the TV.
With the Wii U,
it's going, they're going to make it so
when somebody kicks you off the TV,
you can just, I'm using like
my hands right now. I'm not even like, my hands aren't even on the keyboard.
You can, it goes to the screen.
You have like a, it's a mini TV
on the screen.
So let's say you get kicked off, you can
just play on the Wii U pad screen.
Like, okay, fine, you can take it. I'll go in
my room and play the game. That's insane.
That's unbelievable.
That is one of the coolest things, I think, of that
system so far, is the fact that you
can like, take the system
with you around the house.
Go to this last room. And plus,
I mean, this might sound kind of like,
kind of disgusting, but
like, how, how awesome
would that be if you were just like, you know,
playing Super Mario 15,
whatever comes out.
You know, I gotta take like a dump.
You can just like, take it
into the bathroom.
I know, I know, I'm gross, I know.
But still, like, the possibilities
are, are endless.
Somebody should actually
grab those teleport pills.
I will. No, I, no,
I won't. I don't have any, I don't, I'm gonna hurt
myself if I go in there. Let's just go
fight the boss. Bang, bang.
Bang. The Wii U.
I don't like the name.
That's, I wish they would change the name.
Imagine if you dropped it
in the toilet.
I can imagine that would be one of the worst
things to possibly happen.
But I guess
why, how would you drop it in the
toilet? Like, oh, whoops!
Chup-plunk!
I just
thought of the noise they would make.
Chup-plunk!
It's a big thing, man. It's a pretty big device.
Let's go kill
Mom. Let's go fight Mommy Dearest.
Oh,
God.
Get away from me. You know, I'm not
even gonna go item hunting. I'm just gonna
try and kill Mom.
Ah, a heft!
A heft! Yeah, I'm
not going item hunting. I'm just gonna go try and
go for the kill, I think.
Tears up. I think I'm at max
tears, too. How am I not at max
tears? Does it make any sense?
Oh, you know what? You only live once.
Yeah, you're gonna kill me. Sorry, buddy.
Neither is your friend over here.
I live.
We you.
Oh, God!
The noises I make when I play
this game really surprises me.
I got back to 99 bombs. Are you kidding
me? Everybody blows up.
Boom, boom. Alright.
Good to go. No, I did
not take the brimstone from the devil.
For a very important reason.
Because brimstone,
that would have taken two hearts away. And if I
get to go to shoal,
I'm gonna want those two hearts.
And I'm doing so much damage
right now. It doesn't even matter at this point.
I have a very, very, very, very, very
good setup. So I think I'm okay.
I'll get hit by a big
rotten tooth. Double
gluttony. Double gluttony!
No! Get away from me!
Get away from me, gluttony!
Will you just die?
That's all I ask.
I just ask of you to be dead.
Get...
Oh, that guy. I almost got a tooth collateral.
Only in The Binding of Isaac can you say
the words tooth collateral.
And have it make sense.
You know what? I'm going the other way.
I'm ending this. I'm literally
ending this right now.
I'm going into the...
I'm ending this like I'm going into...
Oh god, I can't even talk.
Go! Go!
Alright, I'm not gonna go the other way.
I'm just going to fight her.
I'm going to fight her.
She's got nothing on me.
And... who's in here?
Get...
Dude, what's the Super Meat Boy challenge?
Ooh, I can...
Alright, the real goal here is to...
Oh god! No, I'm gonna kill him!
No!
I always do that, man.
I do that way too often.
Hold on, I gotta text.
Alright. Text complete.
Jerma, turn around. The treasure room
can only be one room away over there.
And... let's...
Oh, that has to be right here.
You are absolutely right, my friend.
Good eyes. But I guess at this point
if I kill Mom right here
then... and I don't go to Shoal
then it's over anyways.
What? What's this? What the hell is this?
What is that?
It lives?
Who is this guy?
What? What?
Is that like a different version of
Mom's heart?
Oh no.
Oh no, I can't fight those things.
Oh, okay, I'm good.
Oh, did you see that, like, ricochet?
Let's go, it lives.
Don't you know it's impolite to text during a live stream?
That's true, but...
Oh my god!
It was my mother!
Oh god! I'm so scared!
I'm freaking out!
I'm gonna do it! I did it!
I did it!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah.
Hey, yeah. It was my mother.
Alright, um...
Looks like I'm not gonna be able to go to Shoal.
A poop!
Oh, I finally
unlocked that guy.
Took me long enough. Cause I played
Isaac. What? What?
What's going on? What?
What? Oh dear
goodness. I made
it to heaven.
Okay.
Um...
Oh god, I am scared right now.
This is the first time I've ever done this.
No!
No, no, I gotta blow...
No! No, I'm freaking out way too much!
Slow down. Alright.
Oh my god, he's gonna kill me!
I gotta get rid of all this stuff in the room.
This is the problem right here.
God, what a mess.
I can't...
What's... There's no health bar
left. Get out of here. Get...
Get away from me!
Oh, a chest inside
of a chest. The citadel.
Give me whatever's in here.
Okay, I
have a feeling. Yeah, right.
Say goodbye, guys. This is it.
See you later. Oh,
if I did not have the book of shadows,
I would have been done.
Again, I'd like to thank the book of shadows for
making this all possible.
Geez. Again?
Again. Again.
Is every single room like a boss?
Oh, get that bomb
placement. Every single room
is a mini boss then, huh?
Wow. Oh my god.
Hmm...
Two sloths.
And a spirit heart. That's okay, I'll take it.
Oh my god. I'm actually...
I think I'm actually gonna be... I'm gonna do
this, guys, because I have the book of shadows.
I can... I can be incredibly
reckless because I have the book of shadows.
Look at how just reckless I'm being.
Ooh.
Okay. Red patch.
Don't remember what red patch does.
Stream? I need
your... I need your help.
I could go to the secret room.
Don't get too reckless.
That's a good... Good advice.
Red patch.
What does it do? I don't have
the time or the patience
to look it up.
I'll stick with it.
I'm gonna stick with it. Okay.
I gotta use this to my advantage.
Use the guard
to my advantage. It's just like shoot
mania. No, it's gone.
Oh my god.
Gotta get rid of one of them.
Go away! Get away!
How much life does this
one... Oh my god.
Really now?
It increases your attack when you get hit?
Okay, I don't want that because I have max damage
right now. I'm gonna take the
mushroom still. Let's go.
Hmm. Yeah.
Forget it. I'm going this way.
Give me that heart.
Secret room already was there.
I'm gonna go up and then down.
Oh, why did I waste that? I didn't
even need it. They just scared me.
Oh, Monstro, you ain't got nothing.
You ain't got nothing, Burger Boy Mastro.
Oh, get hit
with a tooth. Get hit with a tooth.
That was lucky.
Alright. Is there more than one
secret room? There could be one right over here.
Maybe? No.
You know what? I am not messing around
anymore. I'm going right. I'm going there.
I'm not gonna do any more bowl
snip. Going to fight
whoever's in this room down here. Oh
my god. Book of Shadows.
Can say it a million times.
Well, I just...
Might as well go in here. I opened the damn door.
I'm gonna use it. And...
Doesn't this do something though? That's the book of Balaam.
There is no max damage in this
game? Well, isn't
that an indication of how much damage you do?
I thought that's what it was.
And... Two Greeds.
It's gotta be
two. They gotta have two of everything, huh?
It's like double mint gum.
Double... I don't even... Money doesn't
matter. That doesn't matter.
Double your pleasure. Double
your fun. That's a statement of a
great mint. Double mint gum.
I'm doing it. Here we
go. Kain versus
Isaac?
Ah! Ah! He's...
God.
I gotta utilize this as best I can.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. I gotta use this as best I can.
Come on! Okay.
Book of Shadows. Come on.
I got the power. I gotta be quiet now.
Or else I'm really not gonna do this.
Damn! God!
God! No!
God damn it!
Oh!
And I gotta text.
I can't believe that.
He had
no health.
He had zero
health.
I should have placed bombs.
I know. I just...
Oh!
Oh! I
was so close!
I was so close
to beating this... the entire
game. Like, that's the end of the entire
game of Wrath of the Lam.
And I didn't do it.
Well, at least I tried.
Yeah, if I got
the 20-20 hindsight,
if I had done what I should have done,
I didn't know it was gonna
be like that, though. Oh, well.
That's gonna be pretty funny
video.
Hey, here's a full playthrough of Binding of Isaac,
except for the very end when
I die when the boss has one health.
Oh, man.
The death animation started.
Oh. Well,
at least I tried.