Hey what is happening guys, Jerma here with a gameplay commentary. This is a
one-life gameplay with one class. Not with two classes, this is the same class.
Two gameplays, one class, one life. In both lives. If that makes absolutely no
sense to you, you'll get it in a second. First headshot is on that heavy, this is
the Huntsman sniper on Hightower. The first one is gonna be on Hightower. The
second one is going to be on Gold Rush, it is, with the default sniper rifle. So
two different ends of the spectrum. Huntsman sniper and default sniper, so you
get to see both ends of the world. You get to see China and you get to see...
what's on the other end of China? America, right? America! You get to see China and
America. What a terrible analogy that was. Anyways, payload race Hightower is the
map we're playing on right now. And real quickly, I want to give you guys a tip on
how to deal with a Huntsman. Never get that close. See how he got right up in my
face? When you do that, you are increasing your head's hitbox by a
astronomical amount. You never want to get that close to a Huntsman. How to deal
with a Huntsman? Stay as far away from them as you can, because you will get
luckily headshot in your face. If you get within five to ten feet of a Huntsman,
you're pretty much dead. Sneaking around those boxes, luckily get the headshot on
that heavy. Good thing, because these dispensers would have gone down, and the
engineers, and they would have had to build it all over again, and that just
sucks. So I'm glad I could protect those engineers. Long-range headshot on that
soldier right there. I love when that happens. There's one thing in this game
that I think is the most satisfying thing. It's either an engineer crit from
the Frontier Justice, or a long-range across the entire map headshot from the
Huntsman. Hands down, I can't think of anything else that's more awesome than
that. Trying to time when that scout was going to come out of the door. I didn't
time it right, but it's okay. I ended up getting away. He's coming after me guys,
and here we go again. The same thing I said before. Watch what happens here. I'm
gonna die, right? I get in this little corridor, and look at how close he gets.
Now he's dead, and I am completely fine. That could have been the end of my life.
Can't stress it enough. Never get close to a Huntsman. Pick off that Pyro right
there. A soldier coming around the corner. I miss. He misses. I miss. He misses. This
is where it gets a little funny. He gets too close. Get him right in his face, and
now it's time for round three with that scout. Dun dun dun dun. Here he is. Jumps
over the arrow. Misses me with the ball, and I wonder, you can probably guess on
who wins this round. Probably he was getting a little sick of getting shot in
the face from two feet away. I think he learned his lesson. Good job scout. You did a
fine job. Now before we get on to the next gameplay, I want to show you this. I
was pooping my pants because of this by the way. Think I'm gonna headshot him? No. I
go for the taunt kill. I get it. I can't believe it. I'm so sad. Oh well, get over it. Time to get
on to the next gameplay. This is the default sniper rifle now, and the Darwin's
Danger Shield, and the Tribalman Shiv. I do very, very well here. Very, very well.
Unfortunately, something else ridiculous happens at the end of this gameplay. Not
gonna spoil it, but I wanted to, again, poo my pants and then shoot myself in the
face because of what happens. So I saw that spy coming around the corner there.
I didn't end up going after him. I really wanted to get the headshot on that pyro,
and now me and this huntsman sniper going toe-to-toe. We can't seem to kill
either of each other. It's really, really funny, and that's it. Dude, what are you
doing spy? Why did you do that? So me and that sniper just say, forget it. I'm not
gonna deal with you. You're not gonna deal with me, and we go our separate ways.
Headshot on the engineer, and his sentry goes down. Looking good. Sitting pretty.
Headshot on that medic, and a headshot on the heavy, but it doesn't kill him. Turn
around running away. Don't get yourself killed in these situations. Try to get
the upper hand. Try to get the advantage. He sees me again. I turn around. I get the
headshot just in time to protect that other sniper. Now I start doing a whole
lot of missing in a row. Miss that soldier with the headshot. Miss that
engineer with the headshot. Miss his sentry. Doesn't matter. It got destroyed.
Anyways, this pyro's doing the smart thing, which is if you didn't know, he
stood up. That was the mistake he made. If you don't know, ducking behind the
cart is a very, very good way to protect your head of getting headshot, as long as
you are right behind it. Specifically the part with the huge bubble, because I can
still get you sometimes if you're right behind the cart, right to the side. But
he had the right idea. That sniper was coming after me, I could tell, because he
was scoped in, looking straight ahead. Get the headshot on him. Get the headshot on
that pyro. Bang, bang, bang. We're doing pretty well here. Looking out for that
demo spam. Trying to find a situation where I can shoot somebody in their skull
cap. A spy tries to backstab me right here. I just barely get out of the way.
Now I look in the obvious spy places and that's where he was. Get the kill on him.
Coming over here just to resupply my health and my ammo. This is something you
never want to let slip your mind, guys, because as a sniper I have 150 health.
Usually you have 125 if you're using the, not using the Darwin's Danger Shield. And
the big problem is a lot of people forget about going to resupply their health and
you can get killed by a sniper that's counter sniping you in potentially one
body shot. So you always want to make sure that you have full health, or at
least very close to full health, anytime you are sniping. Otherwise, like I said,
you could potentially just get one shot by some dude that just goes counter
sniper and just murders you. Not having very much luck with the front end of the
gate here, so I turn around and go to the right side. Ends up being a good idea
because I end up getting three or four headshots in a row. There's one. Here
comes two on this heavy. Doesn't kill him, but it's okay. Watch what he does.
He's like, no! He jumps in the air trying to avoid me. I get it. Soldier coming
around here. I get the headshot on him as well, which makes it three headshot
kills in a row. Just briefly now I want to talk about one thing really quickly
before the end of the gameplay. Coming up to a close here in the next minute or
so, I just want to let you guys know how to play with sniper. If you guys go back
a couple of months, go back to my Uber update video. If you watch my Uber update
video, you will see I was an atrocious sniper. I said in that gameplay, I'm a
terrible sniper. I'll never be good at sniper. I'm awful. And I kind of swore
off the class for a while. Just recently, the last maybe month or so, I started to
really practice sniper and get much better at it. And that's really what it
takes, guys. It's all about the muscle memory. It's all about keeping your arm
and wrist in check and not flying all over the place just relaxing. Go to a
couple of orange maps or go to a sniper specific map. You will get better. You
just have to practice. It takes a little bit of time, takes some effort. That's
all I have to say about that. The gameplay is coming to a close here in the
next 30 seconds, but the most important part of this gameplay is coming up right
now in the next 15 seconds. Get ready for this so you see the spy right here,
right? Okay, I'm aware of him. I know he's there. So I come back around here
going up to the top of this corridor up here, and I figure if he's going to come
up there, I'll see him and I'll probably bump into him. There he is.
Oh my God. Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. I
will see you all next time. Take care.