Hey, sorry I'm late. I had a couple things I had to do that I wasn't aware of until like 45 minutes
ago. Let me just get a tweet out there. Hey, a tweet? What a coincidence. Tweeting out a birdhouse
stream. I mean, there's something funny there, I think. Rvem just gave out five community subs.
Thank you so much, Rvem. Right off the bat. Didn't even get started yet. I'm making a gaming bird...
Like, this is going to be the worst stream you've ever watched. Hold on. Let me just...
I'll be right back. Give me one second. Okay, so yes, tonight is more proof that all you need
to do is just kind of just be the one guy sometimes. Maybe like five or four or five days
ago, somebody in the recommended channel just wrote, build a gamer birdhouse. And I was like,
that's really dumb. And then I bought a birdhouse kit. And that's where we are right
here. That's what we're doing now. One guy. More proof that eventually, if you stick around
long enough, you probably be the one guy. And I was thinking about it as I was unpacking
this thing and just looking at it and taking a look at the directions. This is going to be
really bad. This is going to be bad. I just want to make sure right off the bat,
your expectations are very low. Okay. We're talking like, think about where you could put
your expectations. Like a scale of a 10 point scale. Okay. One is... Oh, let's get like
this off the screen here. So expectation one at a 10 point scale is a guy turns on a live stream
and he's asleep with a black screen, right? It's tiny. What do you mean it's tiny?
SheXOXO, thanks for the five community subs. Oh, and I'm already dropping stuff. That's super
glue. Don't want to get, don't want to get that on your lips. Hey, here's like the funny
joke for today. I'm going to pretend that this is chapstick at some point. I'm going to
put super glue on my lips and I'm going to go and then everyone's going to laugh.
Ripped shirt? No, it's old. This is like a shirt from 1981. Is it ripped shirt or is he
wearing a choker? No, this is a ripped shirt. I'm not wearing a fucking choker.
Anyways, let me just get a sip of my delicious fucking tea. Oh, my tooth. That's
good tea. All right, my train of thought. Thank you to the five community subs. Thanks for coming
out. And so here's what we're talking about here. So if you talk about a point scale for
for streams, one is guy turns on stream, black screen, sleeping, you just hear him snoring
and that stream is on for 12 hours. Nothing changes. It's just black screen, guy snoring.
A two would be cam on guys sleeping and snoring, not just black screen.
A three is this stream. That's what you're about to watch. You're about to watch a
tier above the guy sleeping with the webcam on. Let's see what we even got in here. We
have to work with this like nails in here. So I got to be actually careful that I got this.
I could get hurt. Somebody just broke joke incoming. This is the joke. This is it. Like
somebody told somebody to build this on stream. It's gonna be so loud. This fucking
hammer is going to make like loud noises. The neighbors are going to fucking hear me.
So let's take a look at the pieces we've got in our fucking bird house.
No, it's too early for that. So this little, this little guy right here,
that's what the bird sits on when he's outside, outside of his house.
Let's go over the pieces. So we've got front door, back door. I don't know what these
are. Side panels. Okay. Well, this has like a, why is this like a tombstone?
This is like a bird tombstone. Okay. This looks like the floor. Where's the roof?
Where's the actual roof to this thing? And I got, and paint. It came with four paints.
So I hope you're ready to paint this because you only get to choose between yellow,
white, red, or blue. So is this the roof? This comes with instructions,
but should I try to build it without the instructions? Maybe that would be
more fun. I don't think fun, I don't think fun is the right word. Without the instructions,
but I don't know how I'm going to do this. I need the instructions. I need the glue.
All right. No, no instructions. I can fucking do this. All right. So here we go. So it's
going to look, let's, let's just, let's block it out. So we make sure we know what
we're doing here. Like this, right? This is a fucking small bird house. What bird is going
to fit in here? No bird's going to fit in this. By the way, I don't think there are any birds
in Las Vegas. I don't think there are birds here. All right. Let's go. I don't, I'm
using the fucking instructional manual. All right. Sort the pieces, find the hammer,
ask an adult if you need to find a hammer. Are they labeled? Don't use it. Fine. Here you go.
Okay. This is, this is the, this is, this is the top. This is the roof because look,
it has to go like that, right? Cause there's, there's that like chain that comes over.
So this has to be the roof because there's a chain in here. So this is the floor.
Is that the floor? I don't think that's the floor. I think this is the floor
because then, ah, look at that. You guys didn't think I was going to figure it out.
Well, this is the floor right here. Here's the floor. How do I, I have to like hammer
the nails in here. But which way do those go? So that's the floor. Here are the side panels
like that. That's not the, what about the sides? Are these the sides?
Give me the instruction. I don't care. What did I get? I crumpled them all up.
Let me just get the, let me just get the base first and then we can, who cares?
These are the side walls. How the fuck are these the side walls? I had it right. So how, what?
So this is the roof. So that's, that's the floor. I had it right the first time.
How are these, how are these the walls? Those are walls. Look at this from this angle.
This is, that's not a fucking wall. That's very clearly not going to help.
They go on top of the wood. Okay. Wait, what am I doing? I'm doing the first two steps.
The floor. What do you mean the floor? Do you like to have them like that?
There we go. I have to glue this shit on top of the floor. Wait,
I'm going to stop reading this chat room. Okay. Just let me, let me just read this.
Select perch B and house front C, which is this these two. Okay. I'm doing it one at a
time place. I can't do it. If I do it in the wrong order, I'm not going to be able to get
it right. And then the, and then the no birds that are in Las Vegas, they're not going to
enjoy this. I need a small amount of glue on end of perch and insert small. All right. So
I got to glue this thing on. Just, just relax. See, it's got to go right there.
I don't even need glue. No birds are going to enjoy this. They'll be, they'll be fine.
So this is the glue. I can't, I'm not going to fucking be stupid. I'm not going to eat
this. Although it all, it is tempting though. Frosting, frosting. It's like frosting. It's
not frosting, Jeremy. Okay. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Okay. Whoa. Okay. So this is glue.
What kind of glue is this? Oh, that comes up fucking fast. You guys want a good shot of the
glue going on? Perfect amount of glue. Look at that. See? And then that goes in here
like this. I don't want to see the glues go out around the edges though. I already
fucked it up. It's already ruined. Look it. It's already ruined. Already I fucked it up.
It's already fucked up. I already ruined it. I already fucking ruined it. See? No, don't.
Whatever. Who fucking cares? Okay. Done. Let's take a look at what the next step is.
Place floor on flat surface. This is the floor. What? Like this. Just wipe it. No,
I'm not going to wipe it. Once, okay, I will stop after this and I'll throw the
directions behind me in a fucking fit of rage and you'll think, you'll think it's cute, right?
Okay. On the inside bottom edge, I got to run glue down here and then glue it
to here like this. So we've got glue again. Oh, fuck. I need like four people for this.
Okay. So like this and then I have to hammer this in. What happened? Ask your mother for
help. I'm going to have like sticky fucking hands. Look at the instructions again. That is the
floor. Place floor on flat surface. That's what I did. Take the front. Place against floor edge,
matching up nail holes. Don't you understand? I had it done right. Like I did that right.
Like this. That was correct. Why is everybody freaking out? That's what I was supposed to
do. Because see, look. See? See the holes there? Like something else has to go in there.
Because this is the floor. On top? What do you mean on top? Like this? How am I supposed to
hammer this in? How am I supposed to hammer this in? I can hammer it in this way. Why do
I even need to put the glue there? Just fucking hammer it in. God damn it. Now I don't know
where the holes are. He's pretending. Yeah. Yeah. Got you. All right. So then like this
and then the nails. Look at that. All right. All right. I don't want a bird to go in this.
They're gonna, they're gonna like die from like the glue poisoning. Okay. We're gonna hold it
there for 10 seconds. All right. Now I need to hammer the nails in. How am I gonna do that
though? Is it? Oh, what? Disgusting. There's a fucking worm in my fucking drink. Don't step on
those. You didn't. Whatever. Don't step on that. Watch it. Hey. Watch it. This is fucking
dangerous now. Watch it. I don't think this is possible. All right. I got an idea. What?
Okay. So if I just like make it land on the spikes, I'm gonna put a nail through my hand
on this stream. I'm taking my fucking time, man. All right. Here we go. Ready?
You gotta put. All right. It's in. Now I gotta get the other one. Oh, look. Like coddled,
soft hands man. Scared by, scared by fucking hammer and nail. Oh, well,
I don't touch those things. That's it, right? That's going in. Let's get it in one hit.
Oh no, don't do that. This is dangerous and you could be, you could get hurt. Don't fucking try
this at home. Uh, yeah. Don't build a bird house at home. That's, they're fucking dangerous guys.
Pretty sick. All right. That's good. It's in there. It ain't going anywhere. Nice. All right.
Now we're on the right track. Now I don't need, I don't, I, I know this is the back.
So that's going here. How loud? That's probably really fucking loud. Table dented. Where?
Right there. Where's the table dented? Right there. Right here. Stop. This table is.
All right. Listen to me. This table has seen a lot of work. I've built every labo on these
tables. Uh, that's a lie, but some of them, this was thrown in as a last second in the
moving truck because it was just a random shitty table that I still had that my mother
gave me like 10 years ago. So look, it's going to be fine. Don't worry. This is not
expensive table. This table was like probably four and a half dollars 12 years ago, 20 years ago.
It's an heirloom. No, it's tested. Look, it's tested with the test of time and it can take
anything I want. This is my like fuck you table. You know what I mean? Like build a
bird house and paint on it. All right. We guys relax. How are these? Wait a minute.
Look at how small that is. A bird can't fit in here. This is a wall. If I were a bird,
I would throw up in here. I'd get claustrophobic inside of this place. All right. Where are the
holes here? There's a hole here. So these two holes are designed to go in. There's holes on
the edges here. So that's like this. Okay. So they'll have to connect that. Let's glue it
first. I don't understand what the glue is for if you have nails. Okay. The wasps are going
to appreciate this nest. I'm done. I'm done using the glue. Look, okay. Here's the glue
will be the icing on our, it's going to be like a gingerbread house. I'll just put like
icing swirls on it. Fuck this shit. Get this out of here. Don't do, don't get that on the
nice desk. Don't put that over here. Don't fuck up this desk. I don't care about this
one. This one, they might look the same guys, but they are not the same. They are very much
not the same desk. I'm so paranoid. I dumped a whole coffee on here the other day. All
right. That was enough time to load it in. Is this shit blurry? Is this blurry? No, you're
good. Basically the same desk. No, it's not the same desk. Well, I'm just realizing
right now where the web with the face cam is. This looks like I'm like fucking huge.
I got like a tiny head and a huge fucking arms. Yeah, this looks easy enough for me.
It's like a mech suit, the body type of a fucking Megazoid.
All right. Uh, nail right in the front, right? Right there. Huh? I'm not using
glue anymore. There's no reason to do it. It doesn't do anything. It doesn't fucking do
anything. I have to hold this and hammer the nail in. I should have put these on
first. Why did I not do the walls first? Fucking gamer bird house. How can I think
of this with physics, right? Cause you know, cause phonetically speaking, I have to
connect these two together, but the, the centrifugal force of the glue is not
holding it. So it falls off. So I gotta go like that. Oh yeah. I got it. I got
it right. Fucking here. That lined up right? Yeah. Fucking just squeeze it.
Just get it. Here we go. Now it's in. Now it's in. Just get it in there. Got it.
Hmm. No, there's a fucking little gap. There's no gap anymore. Get over there.
Mother fuck. Am I hitting this into cement or I don't understand. I'm going
to break it. I'm going to break it. It's in. No, it's in. It's in. Oh,
look at how red I am. We'll come back to that later. I got to get the other
one in. No, how am I supposed to do this? How are you supposed to
actually do this? I gotta think of what color I want to paint my bird house.
Oh my fucking God. And now it's like bent. The nail is bent. I bent the
fucking nail. No. All right. It's an extra perch for the bird. You know
what I mean? The bird, one daddy bird can go here, right? And then baby bird
can go here. And then baby bird too can go over here. I'm like knocking
out other nails. There's no pulling this out. I'm already committed. I've
got to just really get this in. This, I've become too completely
committed. But how? I'm gonna need something to wedge this up against
like a wall or something. I'm gonna like push it against, no, but I can't
like, I'm gonna put a hole in the wall. Use the side of the table.
Yeah, but look at it. It's all wiggly. I think that was a glue on my hand.
No, that wasn't. I'm just panicking for no reason. Okay.
All right. What's next on this? It's not even written. All right. So now I
gotta put the other wall. No, I gotta put the other nail in.
God, this is, are we having fun yet? You know what I mean? We haven't
fun yet on this stream. No. No. No. Hey, fucking one guy
wanted to do this. Do you understand? That's what we're doing this for.
One fucking guy said, hold on. All right. That wall's on. This feels a little
not secure at all though. All right. You know when you're sitting at a
dinner table and if you put your elbow on it goes
and then you have to spend the entire evening trying to not put
enough pressure on the table so you don't knock everybody's food
around and knock everybody's drinks off and shit.
I hate that, man. That's the absolute worst. You know, don't you like hate
like fucking weird shit like that? Do you just hate stuff like that, guys?
Relatable. All right. Now other wall. I don't even know if I'm going to get
this correct. It's gonna be, this is gonna be so
fucked up. So then this goes, I need it. I need, I don't, the glue is not
gonna, is not doing it for me. Forget about the glue. That's the
decoration on top. I dropped nails on the ground.
Don't, let me forget those. That'll go through my foot in like three
days. Don't forget those. Don't forget them.
This birdhouse is like such a simple stupid little shit birdhouse.
Yeah, what's the point of the glue? It's just there to make
like little, little Timmy think he's like working on something.
Because you bet your ass that's why that's there.
You think them parents are gonna let little Timmy pick up the hammer and
fucking hammer this thing? No. That's what dad's for. That's what
I'm for. You know what I mean? Oh, it's gonna go on the bottom one
first. Get that in there. Okay, same deal as last time. I
gotta, I gotta be careful because it's
it's not flush. If it's not flush here, that means it's not gonna be flush up
top either though. Fuck you, come on. Get over here. Like this.
Get on the edge of the table. Get on there. This doesn't feel right.
I don't know what that was. I'm sorry. All right, we're almost done with the
construction. Actually, no we're not. We have a lot of other shit to do
with it. That was cool. I love those muscular
items. Hey, thanks. All right, one. Don't, every time I put my thumb
here. Okay, I'm gonna like, I'm gonna line it up real quick.
That's how, that's cartoon goofy from fucking the Disney channel. That's how
he like hurts his hand every episode. Oh, didn't go in. Uh-oh.
No, we're good. Oh, maybe not. I think I may have actually
broke it. No, I didn't. We're fine. All right, come on. Don't, don't goofy
this. Do not goofy this. It's in the perfect spot to get
goofy and I don't want to do that. So we're gonna be very gentle, very
careful. Okay, now I can move the thumb.
It's going like this. Whatever, I don't have to fucking live here.
So then hammer it in there. Almost got, it's almost complete.
I can't, this is, it's almost complete for us to go to the top and
just baseball throw it down into the ground and watch it explode.
We're not doing that, I'm kidding. Jesus, he's not very smart, is he?
It's a fucking birdhouse. These things, do you think, do you think, do you
think that, do you think that these things are cut correctly?
No, they mass produce 500 fucking million of these
and they're all at random specs. They're not cut correctly. They're not all cut
correctly. They, yes they are. It says who?
Do you work at Birdhouse Factory for? It's just, it's just some credentials.
Oh, you see, I work at the Birdhouse Factory. They're all cut to spec.
They're in any room for error in my Birdhouse Factory.
How is this gonna stay down here? No, I gotta go through them. No, I have
to go through this one first. I can't go through the bottom
because I have to connect it first. Yeah, all right, what side of the
Birdhouse Factory did you guys wake up on today?
Fuck! No, it's all right. I thought it was really wrong.
Mmm, that's moving a lot. I don't like how that's moving around so much.
These pieces of wood are near flawless for a quarter of a penny.
Really? Didn't that sell? Did that sell?
He's the same piece. Would you look at that.
Oh, would you, would you look at this? That's not exact, is it?
Oh, listen, it's a little, what happened here?
What happened there? Factory? Hmm? What happened here?
Yeah, get fucking, get the Birdhouse Factory exposed.
I don't even know where these, where were these plugged in? I don't know.
I gotta move this way though. I'm stuck over here. Not in the
Birdhouse. I'm talking about in, in this life.
There we go, all right. Of course, Mickey!
Whoa! Almost did it, Mickey! Don't fucking do this at your house.
It didn't do anything. Fuck! It's still, the Pinocchio nose is in the
front. That's why it makes it impossible to do this.
And the leg. Oh, I just broke the table! Table broken up!
All right, looking pretty good. I'm gonna do the outside first.
I don't know why anybody else feels like this when you're working with
tools, especially with wood and nails. So, this is getting very tight
right now. To a point where I, it's like, oh, I gotta pull it and then
hammer it in. Don't you feel like that the wood's gonna explode?
But isn't that, can't that happen? Can't there be like enough pressure
being pulling and pushing and crack, crack, crack, that the thing just
blows the fuck up? I don't want that to happen, so I'm
being very careful. This thing's gonna explode. All right,
I'm missing a nail somewhere, right? Thank you for reminding me about the
nail on the floor. Okay, they're still gonna put the
roof on. Oh, shit! There's already a bird in here!
He like, found his way in! How does this even, I'm really fucking
reaching here, huh? You can see it better that way, right?
Oh yeah, I'm very proud of myself right now. This is an accomplishment.
You know what I mean? I'm gonna go to sleep tonight and I'm gonna be going,
just having a couple of nightmares, like fucking nightmares, like Jason
the chainsaw, like chainsawing me! And then I'm gonna scream, wake up, and
like go back to bed. And then I'm gonna have like a pretty decent
dream about like birds and, you know, I built that. That was fun.
I don't think that's in. It is actually. All right, the general construction is
complete. No, it's not. Not yet.
Are you stressed out? No, I'm just kidding.
Bird lands and the bottom fall. Yeah, all right, so we make like a bird
trap door. The bird lands and like falls out.
And then I'll build a bigger, better house, right?
Connected. It's an, and this thing has cushions and it's got like
cable tv and it's five times as big and they go into that one. And then
this is just kind of the entrance. So then the people don't know
what the bird has. I mean, this is like the fake house. Like I just have like
four walls and a fucking front door, but they don't know. Like they come
down, the trap door goes whoop, they fall through,
and then there's another exit out the back of the tree. So
they can have as many nuts in there as they want. Bird tax evasion.
I did it. Now I'm just gonna put these two on. Now how the fuck does
this work? Because this little, little slot here,
so it goes like this. Oh wait, hold on, I see.
I get it. Do I? Yeah, because the chain goes through there,
because this goes like that, because there's the slots on top.
You should really pull your pants up. I'm wearing pants today.
I had to. Fuck, no, it goes like this.
Because then the chain goes, how the fuck does this work? It goes
like that. How does the chain go in here? The
chain has to go up and through there. Like that, because the divot, I don't
know if you guys can see. I'm pretty sure it has to go like
this. I have no fucking idea, because the
chain has to go through. The chain, see, the chain has to go through. So
you know, it's like that. Got it. Bingo. But this might have to have to
turn around like this, because the chain goes. No, no, I had it
right. Bingo. Okay, so like that. So this
one's gonna go on first. Oh shit. What? How the fuck does this go on? There's no
holes here. I don't have a guide. I don't have any hole guide.
The holes are on the top. I think that's how,
I think this is how it goes, and I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna deal with
it. I think. Don't get angry,
because there's no, the only holes are on the top here. Nail it with the
chain already attached. My neck is too thick for this. Somebody
mentioned choker earlier. You can like see this digging into my
skin. Hey, uh, what's up? Do you like my new look?
It's just like digging into my body. Yeah, I'm gonna do like accessories now.
What do you think? Now here's the worst part about this. I
might not be able to get this off. See, it didn't even leave a mark, but
very clearly it did. It's like, it's like a fucking red
line. My like neck just drank kool-aid.
Whatever. How do I do this? I'm about to go get
alcohol. I don't, I'm done. I don't care. I was hanging. Look, wouldn't it be better?
Okay, listen, hear me out. Hear me out, guys.
Just wait. Don't you think it would be better if I put like water in here
and it looks like a bird hot tub? You know, like a bird bath.
Look at how perfect this is. They come in here, they could put their
towel over there, they go right through, they could be in the water,
bird bath, take a bath, come out and leave.
This is not a house. This is a bird. This is a shower. This is a shower that
goes in your house. I don't think the seal is good enough
though. There's no birds in Vegas. I slowly came to the realization about
this. All right, give me the instructions.
Who ripped them? That's what I want to know. Who ripped them?
Which one of you guys ripped these? Because I wouldn't, I,
one of you guys possessed me. I saw like
ripped paper and my eyes fucking turned red.
Why am I, what am I sitting like? Okay. Oh, it's just the old treasure map.
How do we build the old fucking hot tub, mate? All right, so
take a side wall piece E and run a thin line of glue on either edge.
That's not where we are. We already did that.
Lay roof panel F flat on working surface.
Place roof panel G at a 45 degree angle on top of panel F,
matching edges and nail holes. There's only one way to put these pieces
together. This will ensure proper alignment once you've lined up the
nail holes. Remove roof panel G and run a thin line on the length
Okay. Get out of my head. Stop it. Damn it. No. Okay, I'm back.
I'm just gonna, I'm just fucking connecting the damn thing like this.
There's only one way the thing can go. This is the way it goes.
Like that. Nail holes are here. I'm gonna do it off
camera. It's bitter. It's the shoe. It was the goblin. Okay, so here,
like right here. All right, the instructions weren't clear enough for
me. Like that. How the fuck am I gonna do this?
Do you see how impossible this is? How would a six-year-old do this?
All right, score check. I want a score check of the string. I told you it was
gonna be a three. Four? You can't, Jeremy, you can't
hold it and put it down and then hammer it. Why does that hurt?
Almost, this is gonna end bad. It's the only way I can do it.
Imagine if I missed. I would just hit myself like right in the chest.
My stomach is too malleable. It can't, it's not gonna work.
I have too much of like a jiggly stomach. I gotta like rock hard abs this.
Why is this not going, it's so loud. I'm sorry. Ready? I'm gonna try to talk over
it so it's not so loud. So sorry, it's loud. I'm, I didn't,
that's, that wasn't even funny. This is just
Nintendo Labo but dangerous. This is gonna be loud.
I'm gonna meet the mic because you're not gonna want to listen to
this. Trust me, you didn't want to hear
that. That's a little fucked up but that's
fine. All right, here comes the moment of truth.
Don't do it. Don't do that joke. Don't do it. No one's gonna think it's funny.
Castlevania, just pretend I did a Belmont thing.
Get in there. Get the fuck in there. Get in there.
Get it. Oh, get in. Oh, I'm just gonna put it on the ground, okay?
Why do I need to hang this? I'm just gonna put it onto the,
on the dirt. Fuck you. How did this even happen?
Birds fly? So they can land on the ground. They go to eat the worms in the ground.
They can't go in their house. Oh yeah, a squirrel will just go in
there and like take all their stuff. So add a security system, which is what
I'm gonna add. Okay, the chain is in. So how the
fuck do I do this? I have to connect these two.
How the heck am I gonna do that? What the heck is gonna happen? What
the heck? Okay, I need the knife.
What the heck, man? No, I need to paint this first. Get out of here.
Get it out. Get it out of here. This has to be painted
before the chain goes on. There you go. There's your little bird house, guys.
There's the fun little bird house. Okay,
now I need, how do I keep this on? Do I have to glue this?
All right, so do we want the bird house to have like a Sonic the Hedgehog
or like a visor? Well, balding. I mean, that's like balding or Sonic
because that's too typical. It's got to be like somebody's
blowing a hairdryer in the bird house's face.
Oh, that's right. That's a lot of shade for the bird.
That's a nice shade there. That's not bad
because then they can hang out. But what bird is, I don't know. This is what I
don't understand. The bird is supposed to sit here.
What bird is this big? This is a bird. A bird's not this big.
Is this a replica? Is this like not supposed to be held anywhere?
This is a bug house. This is going to be filled with fucking
cockroaches and beetles in like six months.
I'm going to look in there and it's going to be like
that X-Files fucking sound effect is going to play that like weird fucked
up violin. I'm going to cause an infestation.
Yeah, I know what a bird house looks like but, I mean, lots of birds have
nests that are like this big, right? They're like huge. A fucking
condor ain't going in there. A hawk ain't going in there. Uh-oh.
This is not good. That's not good. Oh, that's not good at all. This is not
even going to fit. Oh shit. How did that happen? Oh,
that's not good. But during the winter time they're going to get cold.
That's raft. All right, I'm just plugging it in.
I'm hammering it in. Where are the nails that I dropped?
Because I need both of them. Do you see it?
I have no idea where they are. All right, this is one.
I'm gonna have to glue this because I only have one. Wait, hold on a second.
Did I only drop one? I think I only dropped one, right?
Because how does this stay on? That was a disgusting, gross,
under-the-breath burp. Hold on, what are these?
What are these? These little hooks? What are those for?
Use the glue? But this is the fucking icing.
We're going with the shade because I want the bird to have a nice shade.
Let's get the glue on there. I don't want to use that much of this though
because I swear to god this is really icing.
And then I'm going to paint it. And you'd better believe that we're not
going to spend very much time on that shit.
The bird won't fit. Don't put that over there. I gotta think of a good color
scheme with the four colors I can choose from.
This is important. Yeah, but the bird. Yeah, maybe the bird. But then,
look, no, I'm doing the bald head because if a bird can't stand up, if a
bird's this tall, right, then it'll bump its head on
the ceiling. We're doing the bald head.
Ruined it. How did I ruin it? And there we go.
All right, this needs to be hammered a little bit. How can I do this in a
way that it's not going to? See? Look at that. It's perfect. What
happened up here? It exploded. I told you it was
going to. I split the wood. All right, so now it's
time to paint. This is going to be a joy. What about
this last nail? Not an extra nail. All right, let me show
you. Can I show you the utensil that they gave
in the box here? The utensil that they gave.
Are you ready for this? Here's how you're supposed to paint the bird house.
It's a fucking carrot brush. What am I supposed to do with this?
I'm supposed to paint with this fucking little carrot.
All right, important. Red roof, yellow roof,
white roof, blue roof. I ain't gonna, it's gotta, I'm gonna, it's gotta be one color.
I think, I think I like blue roof, but that's just me.
Because then we get blue and then blue,
white, blue, then sonic, and blue, yellow. No, I'm not making a sonic the
hedgehog birdhouse. Smart click. All right, fine. You
want to play that game? We can play that game.
Enhance it. Here we go. What have I selected here? Hold on.
Wait, I can rip these off, right? No, I can't. We gotta get even closer.
Fucking god damn it. Hold on. Okay, you ready?
Go for it. Ah, it looks like blue is, get, don't click my face.
Blue is winning by a lot. Yeah, yeah, I'll click.
Fuck! No! He distracted me! Why was, I'm such a total, I'm
looking at the, get away from me! Get out of here! I'm
not afraid to use it! Don't, I didn't hit myself in the fucking
face. All right, it was blue. All right, stop. Stop it. Everybody stop
it. Stop. All right, so the color of the
fucking roof. Okay, so the color of the roof is
gonna be blue. Please select the color. Please
select the color of the front panel here, the front.
What color is the front going to be? That was
blue. Blue? Is it blue or white? This is tough.
If only, if only like a massive amount of you guys weren't clicking
this spot right here. All right, it's gonna be white.
Why am I, I'm gonna hurt myself. Put that down. All right,
so we got blue, white. What would you like the back
panel to be? Don't vote yet. Back panel.
What do you want the back to be? Go ahead. I mean jeez.
Blue? Really? That's gonna fuck, that's gonna fuck it all up.
Blue? So it's gonna be, so blue up top,
blue on the back, white in the front. So then what about this, what about the
side panels? Side panels. What are the side, both, they
have to be the same. Side panels. Really, the whole thing
is gonna be fucking blue. The whole thing is gonna be blue
except for the white. Okay. What would you like
the bottom, the base to be? What is the base?
Oh, we're getting a little bit of a different story here.
Red. This is just gonna be Spider-Man house.
Oh no, it's red shoes for Sonic the fucking Hedgehog.
All right, bottom is red. What about the, most importantly,
the little tip. What's the tip gonna be? Sonic does not have a fucking
red nose. Yellow? Okay. I think I get what you guys are
saying here. So we got blue all around, blue, blue,
blue, blue, white in the front, yellow tip, red base. Okay, thank you for,
thank you for playing. Let's try to get this back to where it was
and begin painting. Fucking Sonic the Hedgehog.
Okay, so let's get this a little closer.
All right, that's good. So let's begin.
So how do I do this reliably? We have to start from the top.
No, we can't start from the top. I have to do the bottom first.
But how am I gonna, okay, bottom first. Red bottom?
Do I have to, are these concentrated orange juices? Do I need water for
this shit? No, I like this cup. Hold on.
Okay, so I got something to do this with.
I got like a machinimish mixer shot glass. I don't even know
where I, I don't know who this gave this to me.
Well, we're gonna use it to fucking dirty our brushes in.
I think I got that like, so I don't know why.
It was just in the group of glasses. Maybe you got it from machinima.
Probably, whatever. Let's just dirty our
brushes in there. All right, so we go with red, right?
Like this first? I have not painted in a very long time. Okay, so
I gotta be careful here. I gotta do this correct, because if I
don't do this correct, then the whole thing goes to hell.
I already started. You don't need water to paint it?
Wrong side, what are you talking about? This is the bottom. This is the bottom.
The bottom of the device. How could this be the wrong side? It's the
bottom. I don't, it's, this is not the top of
the birdhouse. You think I'm fucking dumb? I do need water for this.
It'll make it spread easier. Like, could they have given me anything
besides like the bridge cleaning dental device?
You know what I mean? Like, oh, I'm gonna clean into my dentures.
This is one of those fancy flosses that nobody uses.
Am I doing this right? But I can't be done after, I have to like, I have to
decorate it. I have to write like sayings on it.
Like, a couple of, I've got a couple of frags. You know what I mean?
Because it's a gamer birdhouse. This is already drying.
Give me that house. No, this is for the birds.
This is not for you. Not for me either.
It's for next week's recycling. I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, yeah, birdhouses.
I don't like the way this looks. I need like a brighter light on here. Give me
this fucking sun. There we go. Now you guys can see.
Look at how much better that is. You can give me like some tips
and some pointers. Get over here. I thought that-
Don't drop a fucking expensive light! Why are you like this light?
Stop! Oh my god, will you please just fucking stop?
There, that's better. I mean, I'm like blowing up my face huge, but
this is for you guys to be able to see the the colors here.
Was this- what? Hold on. I gotta like change the settings here because this is
blowing me out. That's better. Hey, look at that.
That's better. Now I don't look- well, I don't-
I don't have paint on my hands, right? I already have enough fucking hair
problems. Okay, here we go. So what did that guy-
jerma985? Is it j- is it jeremy985? What's-
what's his name on Twitch? Yeah, yeah, no, you had it right, man.
You watch that guy? Yeah, I mean, I check his stream out every now and then.
Like sometimes he's playing something cool or he's doing something.
I'm like, oh yeah, I'm like a fan. Oh, really? What's he doing now? Oh, dude,
probably something really fucking cool. Like, have you never heard of him before?
No, never. I did, but what is he- yeah, I'll check him out.
Yeah, right now he's uh, he- oh, I just saw what he was doing.
Uh, no, you know, man, like uh, you know, let's um, you want to like get in
the lobby and like play Overwatch or something, man?
No, no, I'm gonna check this guy out. You're like a fan of him. Yeah, I
want to see what he's doing. Yeah, no, but no, man, like we should
like go- I gotta go though, like uh, hey, just-
do you want a free Steam game? Yeah, dude, free Steam game. What are you talking
about? Yeah, uh, just pick a game that you want and just like don't open that
page, because like I think Twitch is fucking broken or something. Twitch is
fucked up. Yeah, man, I'll have to check him out
some other time. Yeah, some other time, like give me- he's live,
he's live like sometimes and he's live, he plays uh,
he's like, all right though, it's not today,
not today, Dan. Look at that, perfect coat of fucking paint.
You know, it almost makes me want to just grab it and fucking smear my
hands on it. All right, so now, uh, how do we- how do we wait till
this dries? I didn't think this through. I'm gonna do a second coat.
No, I gotta get the edges. This is kind of relaxing. Sometimes-
listen, listen to me, okay? Sometimes, you're like, we do a little
relaxing, fun little relaxing streams, you know? Not every stream has to be,
you know, something that you share with your friend. Sometimes we're just
gonna relax and then build a bird house on stream,
right? This is just one of those relaxing streams
that you'd refuse to tell your friends that exists.
Why do I have this shirt? It's alf, it's an old alf shirt.
It was a gift. I can't- I thought if I
even get one touch of paint on any other place but this is not
supposed to be, one push up. Then I'm talking about
over the course. If I do it once, it doesn't matter, it doesn't stack.
Whoa, dude, one push up. Yeah, one. No, fine, we'll make it 100.
Almost done with the base. No, I'm not. Okay, I gotta be very careful
because this- oh no, oh no, no, no. How am I gonna get
in there? This little bit here. Don't touch it.
All right, have we gotten to a point in the world?
Right now, I'm sitting here thinking, man, I have to like do all this shit by
hand. If this was just like a building
video game, I would put my cursor over this and it would go red
and I'd be done. I'm just thinking about, man, if I only had like the
paint tool and like house flipper or something, this is
gonna look really nice when it's done and then you guys can all say that you
helped pick out the colors because I made this. No, I did. No, I
did. No, I did this. Okay, I need a little bit of water
here. How am I gonna switch color? That's why I gotta get it all done
in one go, whatever color I'm using. Don't rush it.
This is not a video game. This is one of- this is one of those
experiments, guys, where we have to have patience, okay?
Sometimes you gotta bring yourself back to reality. Not everything can be
done by opening up a Google Doc. Google Doc painting. Well, you know what
I'm saying. Not everything can be done with a
fucking Google Doc. You know, back when I was a kid, if we
wanted- if you wanted to like say hello to somebody,
you know what our Discord chat was? The living room!
And I had to call up on the phone. Hey, what's up, man? You got- all four of us
want to get in the room and play Ninja Turtles?
Yeah, it was the living room. The arcade. Yeah, the arcade was awesome.
The crazy thing about the arcade, we're- we're in this- like, hear me out on
this, right? So it used to be back when video
games were just becoming very, very a popular thing and arcades still
existed. Think about, like, think about the original
microtransactions, guys. You used to have to pay like 50
cents to play a game. You'd go in and play Mortal
Kombat? No, no, that's 50 cents and if you lose,
go fuck and see you later. Give us another 50 cents or you can't play
again. What do you think they got the idea?
Not wrong. I mean, just think about it. And I would go into that arcade
with my allowance and I would spend- I would put 20 dollars in that
machine and out would spit for just 20
bucks and quarters. And I would spend it all in a
couple hours. All right, hold on, I gotta be careful.
Make sure there's no bubbles. It's gonna be hard with this little toothpick,
though. Yeah, it was an entertainment vending
machine. That's a really good way to put it.
Okay, now I've got all the edges done. Now,
how- how am I gonna do this? I think I can go underneath like this.
All right, this is where I gotta be actually careful because
as you see, I gotta get right in this little edge.
But it's okay, I can paint over it later. Play- play Christmas music? It's
not- it's not Christmas yet. It's not- it's not
Christmas yet. It's all right, I'm gonna paint over it.
Not bad, actually. Not bad at all. Spider on the wall.
Ah, let me get in a better position here. Spider on the wall. There's a
fucking spider, dude. What are you doing?
Stop what you're doing. But yeah, I mean, I remember arcades.
Arcades. I was gonna just say something but I forgot what it was.
Can you guys see that? Okay, looking good.
Looking good, Jeremy. Have you been practicing
off-stream with a paintbrush to make sure you didn't make a fool out of
yourself? No. No, I didn't buy five bird houses and
build them all five times to make sure I knew exactly
where the pieces went. You know, I'm not like that, guys.
I'm a genuine streamer. I wasn't even paying attention and
I didn't fuck it up. You know what I
could use right now? A piece of toast. Do I want toast
because this is reminding me of toast? These pieces. This is just bread. I'm
trying not to eat bread though. I'm trying to stay the fuck away from it.
Original Doom OST. I'm not putting on fucking do- oh my god.
Do you want to put on Doom for this shit? You want me to put that on?
Is that all you guys- do you guys listen to any other- I thought that
was an animal on my camera. I looked over at the
OBS preview and I thought this. I thought this was an animal in my
room. Anyways, do you guys listen to any
other songs? It's just, hey I got an idea. Doom
OST. Yeah, that's just what's always on repeat.
That's what my alarm is. I cook to it.
Although it's kind of like that with a lot of things.
Like I can tell you right now there are some songs on YouTube especially
where I am absolutely at least 10% of every single play.
Absolutely. The little hairs are coming off of this fucking toothbrush.
Is the bottom dry enough for me to put this down? I think it is.
We got a good coating on it. Filled in all the cracks. Just this last
little bit right here. See it? Don't worry, I'm gonna get it.
And then we'll put on the Doom OST. How many times have I caved in and
just put on the Doom soundtrack? I wonder how many times that's
actually happened. Doom OST. All right, looks good, huh?
Bang. So can, that shit's dry. No it's not, fuck. This is the edges are
like, I gotta spread the edges out. I'm bleeding. I cut myself accidentally
on the, on the wood. That's just, that's not, that's dry.
That's just blood. Should be a little more alarming.
Okay, I gotta, I gotta pass out. Don't do that. Okay.
Uh, I think it's good. Look, I don't cut all day, okay?
It's good. Wash it off in the machinima. Oh yeah baby!
Oh, look at that! Oh, I got this cool, awesome new drink idea.
Dude, check this out. It's the machinima slammer. Martini, man. Oh, we got,
we got triple sec, uh, rum, some watermelon juice. It's the machinima
slam. Yeah, you won't do it. I need another
color now, right? No way, I'm fine, right? Is this, is this gonna be dirty?
Because that's, we're done with the red. I see one little spot right there.
Let me just get it. Should this be in
arts and crafts now? Am I in the wrong category? This is just like,
I need to be in like, arts and crafts. How do I do that?
Arts and crafts. Art. This is not art, though. This is not art.
Uh, this is like, this is like offensive.
Oh yeah, I'm an art streamer. Look at me go like I'm painting a bird house.
Uh, crea- creative? There's no, creative? Destruction.
Go under body painting. I'm not gonna go under body painting.
Crafting? I just, uh, I don't, uh, what about like bird houses? Is there a
bird house category? God damn it. I just have to go into
art. And, okay, how about building a bird
house in parentheses. Don't watch this stream. It's not,
don't watch it. Don't tell your friends about it. No, that's like a
reverse psychology. Like, oh don't watch this, man.
Whatever, building a bird house. I was in just chatting before, but what's
like just chatting building a bird house?
All right, here we go. I did not forget about the Doom OST.
I can't fucking believe I'm putting this on. Give me a second.
Don't drink that! Welcome to the fucking Satan stream.
Whoa! Why have I made it a plastic? I swear to God I don't look like
this. I don't look like this. That's so
strange. I, this is something to do with the
lighting, I can promise you. I'm not like greasy. This is, I didn't
just paint my face. I just painted my face. That's what I did.
I painted my face red. I can't even see. I need to do paint.
Hold on, just hold on a minute. I'll be right back. Dude, it fucking stinks in
this room. I don't know why. It smells like old,
old like rubber mats. I don't understand why that is.
All right, back to, back to our Doom bird house.
So it was all blue, right? Blue everywhere on all the sides,
down the back, right? Or should we just do fucking
red? All right, let me close red. We don't need it anymore.
Give us the old boom. The old Doom. Doom, you know, I'm not doing all red.
We already voted on it. All blue up top. I can't fucking see
though. This is hard to see what, I can't
read this. This is the, it doesn't, it's messing with my brain. It's the
wrong color. See, you guys, we can't, that looks like
black. I'm gonna change the, the screen back to normal in a minute here.
That's right. We'll build a fucking bird house. I need more than that. I gotta
get like a lot on there. Not doing more than one coat. Just
get it on there. This actually is kind of working like
a black light, so I can see exactly where I haven't painted.
You want to put on the boom Doom? Boomer Doom?
Yes, I'll put on Boomer Doom in a little bit. Let me get one panel with
the original Doom new boom soundtrack.
The new boom, you know what I mean? It's all right if that's,
I got, I splattered it a little bit. What if we did like a cool thing where
it was like, never mind, shut the fuck up Jeremy.
Whoa. I say anybody that comes in from like the art
category, just, we need to just tell them that I did all this by hand.
Like I, I crafted the wood myself. I like cut it, I like did it with my
bare hands. When this is done, I know a lot of
people might be taking a little bit of jokes and talking shit,
but you are going to wish you had this birdhouse when it's done.
Which won't be very long from now. All right, this is, okay,
can I stop the boom joke? The Doom joke? All right, hold on.
I'm gonna like move out of the way so I can make sure I, because I need
to see it from afar so I can make sure the lights are correct.
There we go. Hey. Now we can actually see what we're doing.
It's purple, but we're on Twitch who gives a shit. That's my excuse.
So original Doom. Original Doom OST. Okay.
This is from, this is the original Doom soundtrack. I'm gonna put it low in the
background because I don't want it to be, I don't want it to take over the
stream. Not like it matters. What, what happened
here? Why is it yellow? Sonic the Boom House. Sonic the
Birdhouse. Sonic the Boom House. You guys got me
saying boom and boomer and shit. I don't know
who came up with that. Some television show.
Of course, bring it, we contribute it back to TV shows.
Someone just says stop. Stop doing what you're doing, Ralph, please.
I got, I don't need any more paint than this. This is a little too much.
This is a cute little bird house. Don't you think so?
What's wrong with you guys? Calm down. I feel like I've been doing the
same motion for five minutes straight. Fucking just move on already, man.
Squirreling in the holes. Look, it is perfect. It is perfect.
Ohhhh. I'm not doing it again, don't worry.
I had at least a thousand people just fucking clicked mute wicked fast right
there. Somebody was, I had a sandwich and
they like fucking dropped this shit. Fucking, god damn it, dude.
Jeremy, what the fuck? Like a food all over the floor. Right now they're
cleaning that all up and it's my fault. And it is.
Somebody's on their hands and knees right now because they dropped like a
fucking bowl of macaroni and cheese on the ground
because they thought I was gonna be really loud again. Okay, this is turning
into more of a Super Mario house than it is a Sonic the Hedgehog house.
I'm gonna have to finish it up by drawing his face on the front.
Right? All right, that looks good. We're completely coated on the front.
Same thing on this side. Just get a little bit of water on there to
loosen it up. You know, you know what I could
really go for right now? I should have a slammer. Triple
sack, rum, watermelon puree. I'm really craving one right now. I
could probably do this better with my hands
but I'm not going to because then what do I do with my hands? What am I supposed
to do with the hands after that? Paint. I'm okay, so if I if I dunk my
hand in here and smear it all over there and do it in five seconds.
Okay, that's great. Then what am I supposed to do with my hands?
I can't leave the room. I would have to sit here until
so I would have to scream for help. I'm gonna grab the doorknob with
paint all over my hands. Wipe it all over my nice shirt, you know?
Like, all you guys that are talking shit right now about this shirt.
Keep in mind I put this shirt on because it's like a shitty shirt
and if I got paint on it I wouldn't be it wouldn't be the end of the
world. When you paint you wear painting
clothes that you know you don't care about.
But I care a lot about this shirt. This is like a this was a gift
from my mother and it means a fucking lot to me.
So I'm not getting paint on it. She gave it to me a long time ago and
it's a really great fucking gift and I don't want to ruin it.
So was the table. But do you understand I-
No. Don't go that far. Your shirt is amazing, sweetie. Thanks, Mom.
Thanks a lot, Mom. I appreciate it. We're running
running out of blue paint just to let you guys know.
We're getting down to the bottom. God, oddly satisfying.
Like, yeah. Watching him paint that. Oddly.
You know what I'm saying? There's a dev in the chat? Dude, love your bird houses, man.
Can you uh confirm for the for the viewers here? First of all, yeah I mean
I think the release went really well. But can you confirm? Just I just was
curious is is there something about the in the factory
the way that they cut the pieces? Because some of the pieces weren't
matched up correctly but I mean but you can't- Come on. It's day one. Bugs.
You can't get over bugs on day one. So I understand but is it
going to be- Yeah. Day one bug. Like there was a
bug in here when I put it up on the first day.
Because I've had bird houses from the same company before. But there I
mean it's still a problem I think. All right so this is almost done here
and then we can do some finesse work. And then I'm gonna add the icing. I don't
give a shit if this is supposed to be a Sonic the Hedgehog house. He's
getting icing all over his head. What am I- What else am I supposed to
do with the glue? This is Christmas Sonic the Hedgehog.
I gotta really thin this out. The blue is going away.
I don't have very much and I have to do the whole rest of the house.
Any art people in here that know how to do that? How do I like make this
go further? Can I put like olive oil in there?
Paint thinner. Easier said than done when you- This wood
eats it up. It drinks it up man. Yeah something about- Your walls are just
drinking up the paint. That's why it's gonna take us a couple more days.
Yeah we put a coat on and your walls just fucking drank the thing up.
You know? We're gonna give us like four more coats.
It'll be like $425. It's not a big deal but you know your walls man
they just fucking drink it up. All right it looks good. Pretty decent.
Now that we have- We're missing a little bit down here.
Paint- Put less on your brush at a time. That's a good idea!
But you see what I'm saying? Look at the edge here. I mean your fucking walls
just fucking drink it up though. All right that looks fine. Let's see if
we can get away with this. Not getting away with it. This is
the hard part because this is where the little divots are.
Shit! I gotta go underneath. Can I- Can underneath be white?
Guys, do you care about that if underneath is white?
No. No it can't be. Why? Why can't I have the underneath be white?
Because it's Sonic but whatever. Doesn't Sonic have like white
frosted tips or is that his like- No that's his like weird cousin right?
Who's the Sonic the Hedgehog with the frosted tips? There really is one.
Silver. Silver the time traveling hedgehog right?
He went over real well. Didn't see him in another fucking game.
All right. Why didn't everybody tell me that I was dripping? I can use
that later though. I have to wait till this dries to do that part.
The front is white. All right. We let- This is going a little bit further than
I thought on the edge here because this is a smooth edge.
Looking kind of good. Looking kind of good.
Looks good. It worked. Now I'm just going to do that on all sides.
Thankfully the blue is gone after this. I have plenty of yellow too. Can I
just make his whole body yellow? You guys are not really going to
care that much. No one is going to care that much if
his body is fucking yellow. No no no no. All right my god.
And why do I care? Like the bird that's going to live in this house
is not going to worry about if his house looks like Sonic the Hedgehog.
I didn't know what that is. He's a bird.
Birds don't play video games no matter what Falco
tries to tell you. It's Falco's house. No it's not Falco. Well it could be.
Guys are you starting to realize that every fucking video game character is
the same color scheme? Are you figuring this out yet?
Think of a video game character right now in your head. Are they
are they red and blue? Yes they are. No no uh Doomguy. Doomguy is red and blue.
Look it up. Somebody said Link. Uh the the the game with on the DS with the
four of the links and the one was blue and red.
Metroid. Samus is blue and red. Pac-Man is yellow. Donkey Kong. His tie
is blue and red. Red tie with a blue
decay on it. Oh I'm almost out of fucking paint.
Oh this has got I gotta make this go longer.
Captain America. Blue and red. Spider-Man.
Blue and red. Thor. Blue and red. Iron Man.
Red with a little bit of blue and a small by orange for his eyes.
Heinz tomato ketchup. The weird blue bottle.
And it's red. And they did a blue they did a blue version of it too. Remember
the gross blue one that nobody wanted? Blue and red. What the fuck was that
noise? German 985. Well you're probably thinking
German your colors are not oh wait they're blue and red.
They're like teal and they're like a version of that.
Okay it looks good. Did I get some on me? No. All right we're
getting to the point where I need to I still have blue. I still need to do
blue. Just gotta do the back. Wait hold
on wait wait wait wait. Only the front is white right? Front is
white the sides are blue the back is blue.
Is that correct? Right he's right okay right right right.
I need to spread this out a lot because I did a heavy heavy-handed
coats on the top. And this children's toy only gives you
two teaspoons of paint. There we go nice and liquidy.
Who is white? Yeah white's in the front while blue's in the back.
It's not a big deal like I didn't just get what the fuck is wrong with me.
I can fix it later. That was a horrible jump scare in a horror game.
No I painted blue on the red. Whatever will I do? Okay I think I might
have just enough just barely. Gonna get underneath here. Good thing
the whole thing is blue. You guys really didn't make it that
hard for me. If you guys had made the sides yellow
the top blue the corner red you guys really just said
blue house. Do whole house blue. Made it pretty easy for me. Thanks guys I
appreciate it. Pay up with those push-ups baby arms.
What did I say I was gonna do one? I can't put this down.
Don't you realize this? I cannot put this down. You're gonna have to wait
a minute. Just remember that. They won't. Now
is the top dry? Not really. Gotta spread that shit out man.
This blue paint fucking everywhere. Thanks mom for the fucking desk.
I have to put this down. All right now I gotta do. I can't hold it.
I didn't think this through at all. Get out of the way machinima.
That table is now fucked up. No it's a memory that I'll never
I'll never lose. I always remember the day that we all built a birdhouse
together. You know what I mean? Remember the
time that he built a birdhouse and we were all there screaming and
cheering him on. You got to the finish line. I'm just
okay I gotta just pick it up. Just get just rip off the band-aid. Pick
the fucking thing up. I'm out of fucking paint.
Why wouldn't they give me like triple the amount that's in here? Who made this?
I did. I made this. Me. I did. I did this. Me. I did this.
Me. I did this. Change the OST. Hold on. I just gotta fill it in
good enough. It's a whole other side that I have to do and I don't have
any more blue. We're gonna have to desperate times call for desperate
measures because this is not going to work anymore like this.
Thing is fucking empty. Blue. Everything has to be blue.
I'm on the desk right? All right okay good. The top is so good
and the fucking god damn it. Mix the other colors.
I can't make blue with yellow and red? I can't make blue with white and
yellow. How do you make blue? Go buy more
paint. Use a blue marker. I don't think I even have a blue
marker. No. I can I can work with this. Just
wait. This soundtrack sounds like shit by the way.
I can't. It's not my headphones aren't in but all I can hear is like
and I'm does that that must sound fucking terrible.
Almost. And then we just deal with the consequences.
Oh I got it. It's over man. I got it. I'm gonna be good to go. What? That
was so unnecessary. Just put just add water and then swirl
it up and that's perfect. We're good. I can touch up
Bullshit later. Just want to make sure it's coated. Look at that. Doesn't that make you feel fucking great?
Okay, is a robot singing right now? I can't tell. Is there lyrics to this song? No. Okay, dude
Oh, man, you know what I'm craving right now? The new fucking drip from machinima
Bacardi 151 top it off with a little bit of rum chata underneath that a
layer of fucking orange juice and then blue food coloring
All right, almost done. See we stretched it out. We stretched it out guys. We made it
We stretched it out and we did it prices averted nice and blue just have to take care of the edges, but that's fine
The touch-up work can come later because I'm gonna use the white to do little touch-ups and I did not think in a fucking trillion years
That the birdhouse stream was gonna be more than two hours
not in a fucking
Million years I would have taken the bet last night if you said this was gonna take 15 minutes
Nah, dude, that's gonna take like 15 fucking minutes
Alright good gotta get the underside here. What do we really even need to? Oh
Fuck you, Jeremy. You touched it and it's ruined now
How am I ever gonna win the fucking birdhouse contest?
Just gotta get a little bit here and then the blue is done and I can finally it's empty empty empty
Actually empty actually literally physically literally physically fucking actually empty, you know, this is a pretty good Splatoon song
What's wrong the roof? What's wrong with the roof? The roof is a design choice
No, well, it's the reverse of the design choice
That looks a lot cleaner. So we're supposed to be shade for the bird
But we ran into a little problem where looked so cool if it was wind blowing against the house's hair
So we just said cool man. We decided to do that instead
Needs to be a thicker amount of paint here. And then we move on to the white
I'm gonna take the nub out that looks like shit
I'm not happy with that at all. It's this goddamn art, man. It's got to be the way that I want it
It looks fucking horrible back here
What what like fucking pizza delivery music is this is this actually doom?
Okay done
All sides are done
Blue blue, it's not perfect over here
See that you see look at the faint done. There it is. Now we just need to I need to wash my fucking hands
I can't see this the problem that I knew was gonna happen. Why didn't you why did you let me do this?
Why did you guys let me do this? Because now I can't leave the room
I can't touch anything over here because I don't get paint on my fucking mouse
Beck, okay clothes this weight. This is paint all over this. I'm not touching that ever again
Just open the white. All right front. This is this still is drying so I can't really touch it
Is there an OST still playing? Don't touch your mouse. You're fine. Okay, what other OST something like relaxing?
Something we could just chill to
Sonic OST
Sonic Mania complete soundtrack playing. Okay, Sonic the Hedgehog Sonic Mania OST
Sonic Heroes OST guys, it's so hard to decipher because this take 400 Sonic games
Okay, I have to hold it by this thing right there
I gotta use a lot because it's not showing up. This just looks like glue
Paste this looks so fucking bad. What's with this color opacity here? What's with the pigment? This pigment sucks
Dump the whole thing on there. No, cuz then it'll never dry
How am I ever supposed to draw Sonic the Hedgehog's fucking shitty face on here? I'm so mad right now
This was looking kind of good and now the white paint just ruined it doesn't even show up through the wood
I'm gonna have to do like five coats
Mix it in the glue
But I need this for the adult not not yet. That's
This is absolute last resort. This needs to dry and then we can figure out a fucking absolute last resort plan
If it doesn't work, how come all the other paints were so good, but this one was terrible
This is not even trying to be paint. I actually I'm pretty certain. This is not even his paint. This is not even paint
Absolutely not paint
Fucking bullshit. This looks terrible. Why haven't put this color in here, you know me why do what what instead of white?
why don't give like orange or
Brown or green whiz green you put up not a white that just doesn't work
I need layers, but I don't have enough to do that many layers
I really should just put fucking frosting on here. That's what it looks like
Are you fucking kidding me? It is frosting. What color is Sonic's eyes? Look at this up close
That's not even that's just powder
Baking soda on the front of this thing. I guess we could do the nose and then paint over it again
It's got to dry and then we'll do it again. Alright, so let me do some let me do some little bit
Alright, so this now that I have a minute here
Let's do the icing
Because this is this is done up top here. So what do you think like or horizontal?
vertical
What do you guys think? I would say probably horizontal like this just a little bit because it's so it's festive
What do you mean? Those are the spikes. That's spikes
How have you not figured this out yet? I gotta go like spikes
spikes
Don't ruin it. Oh, yeah, don't ruin it. Don't ruin this fucking great piece of work here
But don't ruin it
Hey, why was I saying? Hey
Hey, oops, that was I accidentally just turned off from Sonic the Hedgehog
Sonic was it Sonic Heroes you wanted Sonic Heroes
Ost. All right. I gotta dry this quicker. I fucked it up. I was gonna sing it, but I can't hear it
I was gonna lip-sync it
Whatever. All right, let's try another
I'm gonna see if I could fit something in there afterwards
Sharpie have a sharpie that'll do that
Let's try another coat
No, it just clumps up. You can't even see it
Whatever it Sonic's face is a little patchy, right? He's gonna have like a fucking goatee. Anyways, this Sonic has like a big goatee, right?
He is an animal. He is a hedgehog. Why would he not have a fur there? This is fur. That's perfect
Okay, that's fine. I'm okay with this
It's not gonna get any better than this. I mean the stream by the way fucking goddamn it
This really doesn't do anything. Okay, I'm gonna have to it's time for glue
I'm gonna see what it looks like. I'll try it in one spot
Doesn't seem to be helping much
But here's the what I'm gonna do with the glue. I'm gonna draw his face with the glue
That's right because I'm gonna mix in some blue into this bottle. I'm gonna shake it up and I'm gonna draw his face
This actually is working somehow
It's almost forcing the paint to clump together. So it makes a an actual patch
Like don't you remember that you guys have seen the videos where the guys make the pancake art
It's gonna be like that
except just forget about the pancake part
figure out what was wrong by the way, everybody everybody's gonna freak out but I
I should have painted the whole thing red and then I would have painted over the paint white
White over because look what's happening with it. Look look down here. See how this is actually coming up
It's coming up white
Rather than this weird fucking puke
I can't even say it
Started over and no, I want to get to the design. That's the best part
So I need to put
blue
Like I need a picture of son. Okay, turn the shitty fucking music off. It's not shitty. It's okay
For like a 2003 game. All right, um sonic
sonic
What does he look like?
What does sonic look like?
All right. It's
You guys made me do this all wrong. Why did you make me do it like this?
I it needs to be blue down to here eyes and then it's a yellow here. All right, so I need yellow
Might as well paint the stick here
We're so sorry
Don't be sorry. I'm just kidding. All right, white doesn't matter because it doesn't stick to anything. So
We just need to paint this thing yellow
This one sucks too
Whatever. All right. Look at that. Would you look at that? It's almost completely done
Just got here. How shit faced is jerma?
I mean not really I had um, i've only i've been drinking these machinima drinks
Like the latest one
the fucking moo machine
This is vodka cream
Heavy cream that is and then two droplets a fucking hot sauce
It's called the crazy fucking cow from machinima. All right, i'm done with this and we're gonna put the chain on
And i'm gonna hang it
You won't be able to see the hanging
Because that's not gonna all right. Well, there we go
I gotta fix the red down there
Do the face the face is gonna be very very much last
And then I gotta do push-ups. Yeah, don't worry. I'll do them. It's fine
All right, just need the red to get the bottom because that's all dry and then i'm gonna paint the sonic face
A bird's is what is it? What is this lead paint? What is this based off of this acrylic?
Can birds even like touch this stuff? I feel like a bird can't touch this
I feel like the music will hit them so hard when they land in here that'll make them say oh my lord
And then if they go to bird church, they'll be blessed
I'll take the minus twos for that. That was fucking horrible
All right. Hold on nice coat of red
Almost done. You guys won't let me put on the icing. I'm just gonna do it off fucking camera. Anyway
Anyway, thanks coming up the stream guys. That was a lot of fun and see you later
I'm gonna fucking drench it with icing
All right. I'm above bob ross right now
Jesus christ
All right one more little coat
And I can say that this is ready to dry while I do the face
We're ready
Seems sturdy seems like a good fit for any sonic the hedgehog bird
Let's do the face
So let's see if my tactic is gonna be worth doing
We'll just do yellow. So I need to put yellow paint in this glue jar
How am I gonna do that?
It's got limoncello
And it's apple cider. This was called the shooter
No, never mind. I wanted that
He's breaking down. No, i'm fine. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Here we go
I'm gonna get this
Into there and then we're gonna stir it. This is gonna be hard because take a look at the little hole there
But man if this works, I will be a fucking genius
It's working. It's working
Everybody thought I was insane. That's not gonna work. Jeremy. Oh really
Take a look at my science almost there and I'm gonna put the gap back on
Don't just i'm why am I showing this to you guys it's not that important. There we go
It is a nice dyed yellow
Put the cap back on and here we go. Check this shit out. All right sonic's face
His nose is inside of his mouth
I can fix it. Hold on. Oh, well if it wasn't safe for birds before it's definitely not safe for them now
What'd you use for the paint there? Oh glue
Plank from ed ed and eddie
I can't put my hands on this
I need to put the chain on and I still need to figure out these fucking two hooks or four
All right, one last be right back. Hold on. Fuck. Why did I even shut the door that tight? I almost just dumped this
I almost got it open. It's close
I tried to get it open with my foot and I couldn't get it. Okay, so
Uh, we're good, right? It moved it moved, huh? Listen closely. There are screams coming from the bird house
I don't think I want this in my house. You know what I mean? No shit. It's a bird house
Yeah, but I don't think I like want this near my house. All right. There you go. There's bird house. Let's get these hooks or four something
Finishing touches and then we smash it
It's a treasure map three pieces
Three pieces. That's all I got three pieces. All right, so you've created a okay. This is a very hold on
Wait, this is a very specific bird house for very specific birds
Get out get out of the fucking way dummy
All right, so this bird house is for somebody look this up and see if these are in vegas
Uh, you've just created a perfect home for chickadees
Nut hatches and finches are any of those in las vegas. I don't think I don't think there are any
The only birds that we have here in vegas are scorpions
Okay, so connect
I can't believe I have to use the fucking treasure map to figure this out
Lay roof panel on flat surface
match up the help
Lay roof panel flat on surface
place roof panel at 45 degree angle
proper once you have lined up the nail holes remove
roof
Remove roof panel g and run a thin line of glue along the connecting edge play
Connect one end of the chain to a hook
Run it through the bottom
Of the roof across the top and back down again attaching it to the other hook
Where's the chain? I know I my mother took it from me because I was playing with it too much
All right, so like this
Okay
Hold on just like the crane game. I can get it
This is just one of those tense scenes in a movie
Where I have to be very quiet because like the weird pig guard over there like the guy with a pig face
He's snoring and he's fat and he's like he ate a bunch of same shit before I came over
And i'm trying to get the key from his fucking side of his pocket here
Oh, he woke up. Oh, hold on. Hold on a second. Hold on. Okay. He's back asleep. I gotta get that key
Just fucking karate chop him in the back of the neck and then take the key. That's what I would do
I'm stuck. All right, so I need to feed this through here
Like this
Wait, hold on. No, no, no, no, this has to go the other way put the hooks down
For a second
Jesus jason
Oh real name. Fuck
Get in the fucking hole
It's really just too it's too thin
It won't go through good and
Hey
I'm getting paid. Oh, that's stupid
Fuck. No, i'm getting it everywhere. God. Damn it. This stupid face
It's a glue
That's not gonna dry i'm wiping it off. Oh, it's ruined. I've ruined it. Look at the side of the fucking house
I want to show you that i'm trying it. Do you see what's happening here?
The shit it don't want to work like it don't work it doesn't want to okay got it now
What does this want me to do?
You know what I mean?
How does this want me to actually do this do I have to I have to hang this I have to drill those holes somewhere
What labo is this?
This is pretty much a labo stream
So then it wants because then you hang it like that. Okay, so this has to come out here
The hole is just not big enough for the chain to be in here. It's a problem with this device
All right
We're almost through completely
So that's that's through
like this
So, but am I supposed to have these connected?
So it's like that
You feel like it's not that hard
Sure, it's in
Now these get connected
And then it hangs somewhere now. The question is how the fuck am I going to connect these?
Who needs it?
Perfect. I need to test it though
Got it. Look at that
It's ready. All right. Now we need to like put stuff in it to pretend there's a bird in there
Here I got an idea
Get wait get in there
See, it's like a little bird
Um, okay. I gotta make a family and see how they like it in there. Okay, there's one
Gotta get the baby bird
See, it's like a little baby bird, right? See
I'm gonna make the papa bird
Um, whatever this is
Yeah, so now there's a family in there
Close this shit up. Let's take a look. How does it how is it pretty good? I think so
This is sturdy
If it was just hanging on the side there, see that's what's gonna look like when it's hanging
Smash it with the birds in there. I need to connect this though because this it seems
I can't really bend it
It looks like I can but it's I need like a wire
I need a like a wire cutter or pliers or something
Well, whatever. All right
There's your bird house
No, it can't fit in there
I can't put any more birds in here
Now un-paint it
What do you mean? I can't un-paint a bird house
Make the hole bigger with the hammer
No, this is perfect
Okay, it's good
Now burn it
Wait, how how how am I gonna get that out of there? Oh that that stuff is just in there
This is bad. I gotta I gotta get rid of that. The wood is split here. Why is that not doing anything?
Come on get in there. All right, we're good
What is with the scooby-doo nails like I smash one and the other one opens up whack-a-mole. Oh my god. It's stuck in here
Jesus. All right. We're good
Okay, it's all free in there. See I need a little bit more of this to put this back on
This is like hey you Pikachu
The hell are you talking about? I used all the glue to do the stupid face. Didn't I? Nope. We're still good
Just need enough to put it on there and so it stays
Perfect. All right. Come on just a little bit more. That's like you never saw a fucking thing
Got it
Okay
Back to normal. There it is
Eat the glue. I'm not gonna eat the fucking glue
Glue your fingers together
That doesn't work guys. This isn't a cartoon
There we go
There's the bird house. The chain has been the hardest part. That's what broke it the first time. Just do it very carefully
Glue your tongue to a lamp post. It doesn't work. I've tried it
All right
There it is. There's your bird house done
I can't wait to this fucking chain. It's just whatever
It was it looks fine. It looks all right. It looks cute
What do I mean pull? What am I doing a pull for?
A pull for what for this?
The roof is backwards. No, that's sonic the hedgehog
That's what we decided on a thousand volts. Where do you think i'm gonna get a thousand volts from?
Look at the paint
What I mean this paint is some paint here, but that's okay
As long as I don't get it on my desk or on my mouse or on my face or on my body. I'll be fine
Have we has has sonic heroes been playing the background this whole time? I hope it hasn't
Under the roof
I don't have any I don't have any blue. There's no more blue left. It's gonna have to be red
To my i'm not gonna smash it. This has been almost three hours
This has been three hours to make this fucking thing. Perfect. Okay, the roof is so bad
I'm not gonna smash it. This is a this is a piece of memorabilia. It's a memorabilia piece
That glue is actually pretty good
Fix it with the hammer. I'm gonna get this away from me. Don't put it over there because it's paint on it
I have to look at it
All right. What am I doing with the treasure? I gotta like clean up
Sell it how much would you help? Okay, let's start it. Start the start the bidding
Start the bidding start the bidding at 30 cents
Well, that was fun
I pulled it off the auction. Okay, i'll give you i'll give you six golden rings for it
I'll trade it for a better one. I made myself
The back does look a little fucked up, but it doesn't matter. We tried our best
The resources that we had four dumb shitty cheap paints
A little stick of don't eat me glue a treasure map
And badly cut wood
Never mind. This took him four hours. Don't add time for no reason. It was three
This took him four hours. This would be three hours
Okay, not four don't add time to make it funnier
It was three and by the way an hour of that was us just chilling out and talking and playing in our irl stream
So it wasn't a complete and total build that I left. I washed my hands. It probably took like
Two and a half hours and we were just hanging out. We that's what we were doing today
I'm gonna smash it. Don't smash it. This didn't take nine hours
I look like kind of dirty today
It's because of this that's right. I forgot
Face cam you putting it up. Where am I gonna? Oh, I have to do a push-up, right?
Here
I can't touch anything. Just let me be right back
Let's just like we're gonna chill and hang out for a little bit longer
I need to like clean the fuck up, but I can't do that yet. Hey, let me i'm gonna move this
To somewhere safe
Just move the whole fucking thing. Hold on
It looks like a torture instrument
It's very clearly a bird house
Oh, hey birdot
We've got a bird coming in right now with five community subs. Thank you birdot
See, I told you birds love this thing
All right. Let me at least like hold on. Let me at least wash my hands and i'll come back and we'll just hang out
For a second. Hold on. Okay
So whoa
Hold on. That's
hold on there
Naked see I had to wear clothes today and that sucks move this back to here
Actually, let me just go like this. All right. So, uh, that was that thank you for joining me on that
Let me move
Do I have?
Yeah, I should be using the other camera, but it's all good
It's all good
So that was kind of the plan today and i'm going to give you a couple of things to look forward to
Uh, oh, that's disgusting. That was not a bug around my hand. Okay
So many people are gonna freeze frame this image
It was like this
And people are gonna be like what the fuck is that on his thumb? There's like yellow green boogers on his hands
It's paint. Oh freeze it right there dude. What does he have in his thumb? Is that like fucking schnauz?
No, so, uh, I want to go over a couple of things while there's still a lot of people here
Thanks for coming out. That was just a stupid
Uh one guy said to do that and that was that was the stream was the one guy said to build bird house
Proving yet again that you could be the one guy
Uh, but what i've been doing the last couple of days and today and i'm going to continue to do today
And probably tomorrow and for the next few days
The christmas eve stream is is there's two things that are going to happen here
Uh, I can't really talk about them yet, but is that if I can get
studio time
On christmas eve watch out for that fucking stream because it's going to be insane
If I can do what I want to do on christmas eve i'm going to try and that's why I took the last couple days off
Um, not green screen part two something completely different
uh
If I can get in there
I'm gonna have a lot of fun
So it's something i've been trying to plan
And something i've been spending a lot of time recently trying to get it to work
And if it doesn't work if I can't get into the studio on christmas eve
We're still going to do something
That's going to be very very fun. I'll give you more details very soon
I've only got like another couple days to plan this really before knowing if it's going to be possible
In studio or out of studio. So it's kind of what i've been doing over the last uh,
No, not ipad game something different something that you haven't seen before on the channel something different
Something a little different but let me uh move with this
I need to I need like the better camera because after this this camera like sucks
But it does i'll tell you what it does involve. No, I can't i'm not gonna do that
There's like five different segments that are gonna be on that stream if it happens and it's gonna i'm gonna put a ton
Of time into it. Well, that's as good as i'm gonna be able to get because I can't put the other camera in
It's an incoming joke. No, no incoming jokes
Well, actually incoming joke potentially on the 24th because that's christmas eve gonna play alf shirt. Yeah
No problem. This motherfucker used to eat cats. You know that right?
I thought he was a cat. He's a cat with
Look at this like pompadour haircut. He has
You sure? Yeah, I know we've talked about the hole in the shirt. I need to get off of um
I need to get off of this because i'm on art right now and i'm just kind of sitting here
So let's go back to just chatting for a little bit
So plan over the next couple days like oh what no no title just chatting. No that I build a birdhouse complete
birdhouse
done
and then in brackets
Pretty decent. Okay, and then this is just chatting
Because that's what we're actually doing now
Oh, I think I got the push-ups. Fine. Here you go. I can't you can't even see this
This is what's this tv?
No, that's my chair. I thought that was like a giant fucking tv. Get out of the way
You can see here. Okay. Come on. There you go. I don't care green. Where's green from?
I thought there's a person behind me. What the fuck is wrong with me right now? What's wrong with me?
I thought this was a person
Like standing behind me
I'm losing my fucking mind
I just caught it in the peripheral like who the fuck is that guy?
Too much paint. Yeah, I'm like breathing these fucking fumes
But anywho, yeah that so let's go over a couple things one christmas stream
Uh incoming
And it's gonna be fun and whether it's in the studio or not in the studio. I got two different plans
Tomorrow, we're probably gonna play hotline miami 2
And i'm just gonna play it all day and all night. That's the plan tomorrow
uh
and then
so monday
I'm probably going to take
monday and tuesday off
Because I desperately want to try to get this stream to work for christmas eve
And it's gonna take a lot of off stream work where I can't really be live. I have to be making phone calls and hiring
people and
Without giving anything away. I have to really really give it an honest try because I think it's gonna be a lot of fun
So that's the plan over the next couple of days tonight. We had this tomorrow. We're doing hotline miami
I don't i might try to beat all of hotline miami tomorrow
Try to give you guys like a good like eight to ten hours stream tomorrow
Just fucking beat the damn game just play it and fucking engross into it
Nervous streamer. No, I don't think so when I talk about
I'll give you a little
Uh in depth into my life here when i'm just like being me
It's like hard to just be me i'm gonna be with a camera on like if i'm doing like a character or like
Voices look at how easy i'm not nervous at all, but i'm like, hey, i'm just like talking to you guys
I'm like a camera on it's like wait, hold on. I gotta be me
So guys, uh, hey, it's me and uh
Is there a guy i'm kidding i'm not nervous. I don't know why I would be why would I be nervous right now?
I don't have like a reason to be nervous
Just kind of I just talk too fast
Stop shaking speaking of shaking. Is there any coffee left in here or tea?
All right. I had a panic attack in my brain for a second. I thought there was paint in here
I thought because remember I reached over to this and I was like, oh, yeah dip that in there
I thought like it was like three hours ago now. I thought I did that
There's nothing even look at it's like empty you want me to drink that gross dirt at the bottom
He's flying off the handle. No, but that's the plan
I really hope I can get it to work because it'll be
If I can do what I want to do on christmas eve
It will be the most intricate stream that i've ever done by far
By a fucking million times so it's gonna be we'll try i'll try i'm gonna try as hard as I fucking can
But if I can't get it
Then we'll have plan b and plan b is not as elaborate and intricate as the studio stream is
But it'll still be a lot of fun
This is not something that i've talked about before this is just a christmas
Themed stream that's all you need to know
But let me let me hammer out some of the details before I really like announce anything because it's very easy to be like
So this is what's happening on christmas eve and I hope you're there and it's gonna be a lot of fun
And this is exactly what's happening and then some of it just doesn't happen. So I'd rather why are you guys adding push-ups?
What what what what what's this command that we're adding from push-ups somebody adding plus one push-up
Why I didn't do them all. Oh, it's being deleted. It's being deleted. Okay, I get it
Why would you be counting those in the first place?
christmas eve present
maybe
Keep your ear to the ground over the next few days guys
hopefully I have something interesting to announce but
Uh speaking of that it's still early enough where I can go work on it
So i'm gonna i'm gonna get out of here now short three hour stream
Sorry that this is where it's ending but tomorrow
Tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow hotline mayami 2
We're gonna just we're just gonna go as long as I can so tomorrow we're gonna do hotline mayami 2 i'm gonna
It's gonna be a fun game. Can't wait. You're so ominous
No, this is not something that's ominous. It's something that's very fun
See you tomorrow. Okay
Got you
All right, let's do the bits
and the subs
What time tomorrow? Uh, probably around the same time as today probably around
No, no, no not the same time as today. I I I had a phone call
I had a couple of phone calls actually that I had to make
So that's why I wasn't here at where I was supposed to be but probably three o'clock tomorrow three pst
and we'll go
Probably all night should be a lot of fun. Hope to see you there
See you tomorrow if you're leaving. Thanks for joining us for the uh, the bird house stream, which
That's what it was
That's what we did
And thank you to double d. Thank you double d for the one dollar
It's a youtube link. Let's go ahead and click it
I didn't even have time to to silence that
Thank you. Uh double d
Thank you has named for the one dollar if this stream isn't a 10 out of 10
I want my money back. I told you this is gonna be to chill three out of 10 stream
I am monk. Thanks for the one dollar tier three stream germa venus hashtag charity
Thank you. I am monk
Appreciate that
Etroop. Thank you etroop for the ten dollars etroop
This jeremy guy is a real jokester. Will you marry me? I'm mailing you a ring so you can't refuse
um
That I don't think that's how it works
But thank you etroop for the ten bucks
Appreciate it. Thank you for the ten dollars and the ring that you're sending i'm gonna have to send it back
He's rejected
Thank you. Thank you divas for the four dollars divas
Hashtag charity
Awesome. Thank you divas
Uh virian. Thanks for the one dollar. This is already my favorite stream
PS your hair is looking really good today. Did you do something special with it? I use a couple of products
I don't here here's tip number one. I don't put any
product in my hair
Right. I use products in the shower. So i'm in the shower and I use good
Shampoos and conditioners and then I don't do anything else to it
And I let it do what it's gonna do and make sure it's nice and fluffy
I don't put hair gel mousse. I don't do that at all. Never
Your hair is fluffy in the shower when you get out and you fluff it up
I get I fluff it up and then I leave it alone
Moose hair what?
How often do I comb only after the shower? So I get out of the shower. I brush my teeth
Sometimes I brush my teeth in the shower to save some time
Sometimes I piss in the shower
To save some time
Uh, and then when I get out of the shower
I just go live with a comb not a fine tooth comb because you know, you don't want to rip out hairs
You go back with it. You know what I mean?
You just kind of get it nice. So it's not all crazy and
Flip it up a little bit make it do fluff it up and then leave it alone and make sure it's it's been combed
And then I leave it alone
Why we all yeah you all everybody pees in the shower. Don't ever anybody that's weird
Why do people say that?
What the fuck you what's wrong with you? You did that today
I know you did
I know you did it today
did I ever tell you guys the story of when I was in college and somebody was peeing in the shower and
Everybody was upset about it. It's like dude. Somebody's like pissing in the shower. Somebody's peeing in the shower, dude
I don't know. Who is it? It was like 10 of us
Like almost 12 of us that lived in this place and there was detective work
Everybody was trying to find out who it was
And huh, here's the punchline all of us was doing it
It was like pretend we were pretending that we were upset about it for some reason
Nobody wanted to get caught
It was at least like four or five of us that were doing it and I remember sitting on the couch being like who's fucking
Doing this man
That's like really messed up like stop doing that like we go in there and I was doing it
There are people who piss in the shower and then there are liars
Do you pee in other people's showers guys? I don't piss in the shower every fucking single time
Okay
Please be clear about this
If I come over to your house, I'm not gonna pee in your shower. No, I'm not I wouldn't do that
I'm a liar
Don't invite him over your house man. He's gonna pee in your house
Why are you showering at my house? Because because you invited me over there and I like stay the night
What do you mean? Why am I this we're talking about if I was invited to sleep over and I stayed there and I agreed
And we both were like, yeah, that would be fun
Do you shit in the shower too? No, it's a polar deal
You gotta open up the drain and it's like a pain in the ass. I haven't I don't do it anymore
I'm sorry anymore
No, never I pee in the shower like three times a year
This is all this is all just smoke and mirrors
Anyway, thank you to sprite 37 for the one dollar. Hope you're enjoying las vegas and it's treating you better than it did
Me before I moved away several years ago
Be safe and I hope you have a chance to check out
Excalibur's tournament of kings if you decide to visit the strip
There's a lot of interesting stuff on the strip
But yeah, you do have you do have to like just be careful
You can get really sucked in
to the vegas culture
so
actually, um
I wanted to go to the esports arena at some point here
To check it out because that's on the strip. I think we were talking about that
A few weeks ago in the luxor. Yeah, did you move to las vegas? Yes, I did
Uh just about a few months ago now
Back in october
Well, I don't think you're ready to compete
No to watch
And i'm gonna go to evo this year
Because that's right in vegas. Oh
I've always wanted to go to evo just because I feel like it's an interesting thing to watch
I want to go watch like mortal kombat 11 at evo. It'll be held by then
What the hell is evo?
Uh evo is the fighting game tournaments
But yeah, I I kind of said I wasn't gonna do any more
any conventions for the next probably six to twelve months just because
Moving was very expensive
and
Spent
We spent we've spent a lot of money so far just on getting this place livable
So I kind of like yeah, you know that
that expensive trip to
Like twitchcon or the the expensive hotel rooms at packs east going back it's I just I don't think I'd be able to do it
but 2019
Somewhere in the halfway point in the summertime. I'll probably be making my way back to conventions and stuff. So
Anywho, uh, thank you sprite. I've been enjoying vegas so far. Thank you
Joey fedacini. Thank you for the 27 dollars and 50 cents
No message. Thank you. Joey. Thanks for the 27 dollars
Appreciate it and there is no message here put all your money on red. No
No
Thank you to uh, jinxibo for the 10 dollars here. We had a big nearly 30 dollars
From joey and then a big 10 dollars here from jinxibo
Jerma is like that weird uncle who keeps telling the same fucked up story every time you meet him
And you're still not sure if it's real or not
So you sit there nervously contemplating whether you should laugh or not
I got you right where I want you
It's like anything could be real
Anything could be real. You know what I mean? What does your reality look like? Huh?
Hmm. Tell me what does your reality look like?
What does your reality look like? But you can't even see it. You're gonna turn off these monitors
It's a this ball. It's a glow-in-the-dark like squishy ball
I don't know why this is in here
Hold on. Can you see?
I gotta
Let that sit there for a minute. It's I fucked it up. It doesn't matter
I he could wait down. All right. Whoa
See, it looks like this. There we go. It's kind of glowing. I gotta get all these monitors turned off
Hold on. All right. Ready?
Well, don't drop it. What the fuck does your reality look like?
Let me get let me get like a little bit more juice on it. Okay, that should be better
Nice
This thing is fucking powerful. What the fuck?
Whoa, what the fuck turn the fucking lights back on man. This is freaking me up. I can see you guys again
I've got a slimy face
Nice joke idiot. I don't have a slimy. It's a contrast
You see goes if you see me if you those of you see me in real life
You know that I don't have a slimy face
Uh, thank you slimer. Oh, thank you slimes for the five dollars. That's a really
Perfect name to read right this second. No message. Thank you slime
Thank you freudian weapon for the dollar 30 germa heart. Thank you
Sloth jones. Thanks for the one dollar streamer builds house for himself
Lol, that's me laughing
out loud
For those of you boomers in here
Hey, awesome. Awesome alec. Thanks for the one dollar. If you were a bird, I think you could fit in that house
back to back
Back to back. Hey dubski dude. Thanks for the one dollar
The act of you turning on your webcam is the equivalent of taking a sledgehammer to my already
fragile heterosexuality
Well, thank you dubski
Thank you so much for the one dollar
Although I don't know I have like weird days
I have days where I look in the mirror and I go. Ooh nice
And then I have days where I look in the mirror and I go. Ooh
I think we all have those days though
But thank you
Thank you
Thank you. She xoxo for the one dollar. Hey germa. Where did you get that pac-man mug?
Looks really neat. I have secret locations like amazon.com
Now you can get it. There's a lot of places you can get it get it online
You can get it. There's a lot of like novelty gift stores. You can get it at if you have
One of those weird novelty stores near you
Sponsored by amazon
Now this whole website is sponsored by amazon
What are you on about the entire this whole entire platform is now sponsored by amazon the whole thing
I didn't that's not my decision
But thank you for the one dollar
Hey logan. Thanks logan for the one dollar. Hey germa. I've been a big fan
I've been a big fan since tf2 days and this is the worst thing i've ever seen
Thanks god bless hashtag charity. I told you guys
I've made sure your expectations were very low today. Thank you logan. Thank you. Novi for the one dollar
This is more embarrassing than the raptor hashtag charity. Nope. What?
Me building a bird house on stream is more embarrassing than me putting on
A dinosaur costume and making dinosaur noises
No fucking way absolute there's no way that I can agree with that they're about equal
Thank you, thank you hans beats for the two bucks
He's still going to do the do the music stream
In fl studio love the streams. Thanks for the laughs. Yes
That's kind of in the back pocket right now
In fact, that will probably end up being the next large stream
after the christmas one
Because I have quite a few ideas
And now that I have access to that studio and I told you pretty much like once a month
I want to get in that studio and do something
And we're talking about potentially hiring like a real band
to like record and
Make terrible fucking music
I mean
There's I have access to stuff now that I never had before
Hire like a hire like an actual audio engineer to mix together songs
This this goes way beyond me just fucking around in fl studio at this point
Make up the band name make a whole album
God, we'll see though. I'm i'm i'm into it
So but now that'll happen after the christmas stream because if the christmas tree does happen
The way that I want that will also be a fairly large stream. So
Got to spread them out once a month or so once every like 40 30 to 45 days. That's what I want
Uh, thank you tingy for the one dollar. Remember to pick up the nails you dropped ps. I'm really glad you're not
a contractor hashtag charity
Yeah, if I I did I did kind of make a fool out of myself trying to hammer those in didn't I
That's all right
Thank you butter dirt for the one dollar. If you really want to do this. Well, you'd use wood glue and clams
German moon
It was whatever came in the kit. Oh clamps. Okay
Ferotian weapon. Thanks for the ten dollars ferotian looks like you don't skip arm day
I never used to and it just stuck with me
I I did so many arm workouts guys that my arms still look fucking sick
It uh, I don't even do it anymore, but thank you for the ten dollars ferotian weapon. Appreciate it. Thank you so much
Extra cheesy. Thanks for the one dollar
I was on break at work and showed someone your stream while I was watching it
They looked at me with a mix of confusion and judgmental contempt
Also, if you had to pick one, would you rather be stranded somewhere really hot or really cold?
Uh, really probably really hot. I mean they both have awful consequences really cold you freeze to death really hot you dehydrate to death
Which one of those things would you rather do probably hot because I feel like I could like
search
While it was hot
You can't really search when it's cold for stuff because it's your body locks up and heat you die slower
Yeah, but that gives me more time to search
for like
I don't know i'm stranded on a desert island. We're like the fucking bananas and coconuts and
Strawberries and carrots and shit. They might be on that island. I can that gives me more time to find them
Thank you irate gamer screen cap for the one dollar germa you'd look really hot in a choker
I don't know why I just read that
Thank you for the one dollar demonic cucumber
Thanks for the one dollar considering the large amount of predatory birds in the vegas area
Are you sure that by encouraging smaller birds to stay in one place you aren't just building a bird feeder for a larger audience?
We're making just like a live feeding den for vultures
Thanks for the advice
Thank you to par follow eel for the one dollar. It's a youtube link. I'm not gonna make the mistake by clicking it again
Uh, it's a guy like putting a bird in his mouth. I want a fun fucking thank you for the one dollar
extra cheesy
Thank you. Why is the game cube intro playing? What the fuck? Okay, here we go
Thank you
One dollar extra cheesy the judgmental man was some old crotchy guy who wouldn't understand the antics of us
Fry young streamers such as yourself. So don't worry. You're still cool. Also, i'm the place you're stranded on
Would you rather eat a razor death adder or a logitech mouse?
Well, a razor death adder would mean I would have to have it with me and I would not want that with me
So I probably want to take the logitech mouse
Thank you. Demonic cucumber again for the one dollar. Hey jeremy back again
Wanted to clarify something about my bits from earlier this week
What I meant was you are a very attractive man regardless of your age not in spite of it
I'm crushing pretty hard to be honest
Well, thank you
No, that's very very kind of you. That's very nice of you
um
I don't
Thanks. I don't
I don't know how to I don't even know how to react and people give me compliments like this
because I don't know
I like sit on the couch
And like shit my pants and stuff and like don't get up and like then I I I get like fed
Fed
None of that's true. None of that's true. I'm just
I don't know where I get fed comes from i'm serious
I get fed it's because we're talking about the vultures and that just jumped into my brain
I don't know what I was going with that
See, I told you I don't know how to act when somebody says things like this. Thank you demonic cucumber
again for another dollar here
Also, my mom wanted to threaten chat for implying that she was old
But I can't post what she said because i'd get banned just be warned chat. She's a scary lady
Yeah
Don't talk about somebody's mother like that
She's not old
Kim and italics must have their hands full with you
No, i'm very good
I'm very good. Don't worry
Just put a face cloth on while you talk. Why would I put a what a face cloth?
Dr. Clay, thanks for the one dollar fun fact. This is the fourth stream in a row
Where you've made the hey peter joke. No, I did not when did I say hey peter this whole entire stream?
I did not go. Hey peter. No, I didn't when
I did an hour ago. No, I didn't
You actually did you literally did?
I need to have this proved to me because I definitely do not remember doing. Hey peter
There's no way
Time to go vod diving
All right, somebody can get that to me because I like okay we talking
Because there's two different ways to say peter
There's hey, uh, hey, i'm joe swanson from family guy and uh peter. Let me tell you something now peter
Peter right then there's uh, don't tell harry peter. That's not the same thing. You definitely said peter
I did not find it
You combined them. I definitely didn't
Yeah, i'll be proven wrong if I need to be
But that's a pretty good fun fact dr. Clay. Thank you
Yeah, it apparently was about three hours ago because
That's when this bit message that but that's what dr. Clay wrote this
Hawkeye of mine. Thanks for the 15 dollars hawkeye of mine. All right, somebody has it
All the towers have been unlocked. This is not even the right stream. This is the end game. Uh, hey, but uh
Peter uh peter we're at the end game now peter
That's like a week ago
I can't have it. I can't help it. I just can't i'm, sorry
Uh hawkeye of mine. Thanks for 15 bucks hawkeye of mine. Make me a hawk house
jerma venus
Well, just you can come get the birds that are in the house because you're a hawk
No, no birds are gonna i'm gonna make sure the birds are safe
Okay
Dark star 700 000 games. Thanks for the one dollar. Is your shirt collar trying to become a choker?
Yes, it is
Double d thanks for the one dollar. Hey jerma, what keyboard do you use? It looks very nice
this is a
I believe this is a walmart logitech
15 dollar keyboard
I add that's actually what this is
And guess what?
Works just fucking fine works just fine for me. Yeah, it's the one in the green box
You'll know what i'm talking about when you next time you go to walmart look for the one in the green box
It's this one it comes with a mouse too
It's wireless
Is it the k12? No, hold on. Let me see
this is the
uh
This is the k540
Let's see k540
logitech
We're gonna okay. There it is. No, okay
You gotta go to like walmart like k like walmart
Okay, it's actually like 30 bucks
Yeah, I think it's like 35 dollars
Maybe not. I can't I don't know
It's it's it's in like the realm of like 40 something dollars
Oops, i'm just closing windows
all right, so
uh
Yeah, it's a logitech 540 whatever it was it's like 40 bucks comes the most it's all you need man
Unless you like you do do you really want to have like
I don't like mechanical keyboards because it sounds like it's raining in my house. I don't want that i've had them before
And it's just no
Especially streaming. I got my mic right here like okay. Let me go this way
Okay. Yeah, he's over here. Yeah, let me get him
Okay, I just missed that shot
fake e3 voice
Don't get a blue switch. Yeah, I know there's like the cherry red and the the with the o rings. I know i've had them before
But i've dumped sodas and and like beers in them and like they're too much money
And i've come to the conclusion that I cannot be trusted with anything
so
$40 keyboard and mouse from walmart
Like if I dump a fucking beer in here, like i'm it's not gonna be a huge problem
If I dump a beer in $180 $150 piece of machinery i'm gonna be upset about it
I've had i've had really nice keyboards before but
I don't know. I really am turning into like an old fucking van. I want to go back. I like the old keyboards
The ones that just that's all you need. They don't need anything fancy
It just needs to have the letters on it and you press the letters and then that's all I need
What's wrong with that? It's nothing wrong with that at all
Boomer calling what you want
But that's your answer. Uh double d. Thanks for the one dollar
Thank you smelly boy for the two bucks
Please let us make shitty germa creepy pastas and let bugleberry read a few of them. Hashtag charity
Thank you. First of all second of all
um you
be seeing
Bugleberry a lot sooner than you think let's just put it that way
Some would say very soon
Some would say
They would appear
on a certain stream
upcoming
soon
Not tomorrow
But thank you smelly boy. Thank you rvm for the 10 bucks. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you rvm
I bet your favorite pokemon is mr. Mime you nerd hashtag charity
No
my favorite pokemon
is
Uh, what's his name?
He's the top. He's like a spinning top and he screams his name and he he what's his name?
Hold on the the top pokemon
pokemon
top
Yeah, hypno top he like hypnotizes people when he spurs his name
Uh, yeah, hypnotop is my favorite
Hit no hit what hit?
hitmontop
Yeah, hitmontop is my favorite pokemon
mainly because
Yeah, he's cool. It's a cool pokemon
All right, let's move on. Thank you rvm. That's my uh, hypnotop is my favorite
Thanks for the ten dollars hawkeye mine. Thanks for four dollars gamer bird house. All right
Hashtag charity. Thank you
Gaming hash. Thanks for the dollar 82. You should play house flipper again. They're coming out with a new gardening dlc
And they redid the graphics
um, maybe
maybe
We have gone back to that game a few times
And I don't know. I feel like trying to squeeze out the last remaining bits from that game
If there's enough there if there's actual a lot of content for the gardening then maybe i'll go back to it and do it again
bird house flipper dlc
But thank you for the suggestion. Thank you dark star for the one dollar. Oh my god, the red light exposed germ is true identity
sluggo the melted action figure
Thank you
uh sand draker for the one dollar
Long time watcher first time caller. Have you thought about getting a p.o box that people can send stuff to
I imagine there's a lot of traditional fan art that people would love to send and share if not
It'd probably be motivating a lot of people to make some
There's a few streamers I watch that open their public p.o boxes every week and it's really entertaining
Uh, love you and give auto a pet from me next time you see them
I have talked about this a couple times before and unfortunately I have to say no
P.o boxes because number one they have to be maintained
I can't i'm so
Scatterbrained you guys all know that that p.o box would fill up and I would get calls from the post office
Like can you fucking come down here and pick this shit up?
Um, whoa shit, right? Okay. Okay. Okay
and then also there's like the the chances that people send really fucked up stuff and
Uh, i've thought about it in the past before
People send terrible shit to yeah, I just
I mean if
For for some streamers in some communities like yeah, it's like a fun thing you do and I get it
I think it's that's like a funny interesting thing to do
But I am not like ready nor prepared
To like open up a box and have there be
Like throw up in it
Because i'll just be like uh, uh, and i'll like have to i'll have to leave the room and like end the stream
Yeah, maybe like one day
But no, I don't even want to like pretend like that would be a reality probably not
Your viewer base is very wholesome. I can't imagine that happening
I know but
Just don't want to have the opportunity for it to be a thing that could happen
Hold on to it though in the future. Maybe i'll lighten up a little bit about it
But not now not now not me in the immediate future at all
But thank you for the one dollar sandrager. Appreciate it. It'd be like five people that actually send like blood
And ruin it for everybody else
Yeah, I made like a whole video about getting like blood in the mail
Are you trying to tell me that you don't think that five of those packages the first day would not be?
Like red liquid in a box
Come on now
Okay
But thank you. It's time for slime for the two bucks
Congrats on becoming the number one art streamer on twitch
And i was building the bird house
Was I actually number one there
I think there are people that are spending lots of time and energy and effort on their
Pieces and artworks and stuff and then look at me like look at me. There's a hammer
But thanks for that. That was um
Thank you
So our bird house is your side business or yeah, man, I sell them for uh 20 bucks a piece
But thank you. It's time for slime for the two bucks
Uh, thank you suedo lane for the one dollar. Please pee on the bird house
moon to dev hashtag charity
What please pee on the boot on on the moon house on the fucking bird house god damn it
Oh, that's what that is. Okay
Dark star, thanks for the one dollar. So where do you fit the joy cons on this one?
Thank you, sweetie swanky for the one dollar story time when I was seven
I wanted my dad to make a bird house with me. It was a special time because he was never home
Being a truck driver
however, shortly after the bird house was finished, uh, a
Starling did try to go inside it but the hole was made too small and the bird's head got stuck
And couldn't get out
It's only until a week later that my dad had to throw away the bird house
With the body is still attached and vowed never to make anything with me again. Oh my god
That's fucking horrible
Oh no
No, that's so sad
Yeah, how do I like unread that story?
Well, i'm sorry to hear that. That's not that's that's terrible
But peter is it is it peter? Hold on
Peter but does that actually count though?
That doesn't count because i'm not doing
It doesn't count
That's clearly not a b that's a p that
Peter
That's fucking b, whatever
But i'm not doing joe from family guy. I'm doing
Willem Dafoe from
Spider-man
Those are two different peters
And that's a half i'll get that's a half. That's a half peter the fuck i'm like looking at this image right now
Imagine that's like the that had to have been the thumbnail to the stream at some point, right?
I think i'm making a fucking little lunchbox
Just a hammer and a shitty little lunchbox next to me
and then my magic
Magic wizard wars mouse pad
I've had this mouse pad for four years
I don't think the servers are even still turned on on this game
But anyways, thank you
Swiggity-swanky sorry to hear about that horrible story that horrible traumatizing awful story
Thank you. Smelly boy for the one dollar
How would you feel if you walked outside one day to check on the birdhouse and a full
Seagull was stuffed inside it like a looney toons character with its beak poking out the front
No, not right after that last story
No
You mean what you mean to say you mean the bird is in the house
Arms like the wings are sticking out the side beak out the front feet out of the bottom and he's pretending like he can't see me
And he doesn't think I can see him
That's the trope you're talking about
That I would first of all laugh
And then I would be like I would try to help the bird
By taking the top off
I would I would take the top off
And then the bird would
And get out
But this is the looney toons universe. So it would be all right, but thank you for the one dollar
Thank you zazzasalt for the one dollar finches and chickadees are both native to las vegas
You could actually put it out somewhere and make a home for birds
you
Ornithologist what the fuck is or an or what you do what orthodontist you orthodontist fuck hashtag charity
Orn
ornithologist
Ornithologist orthodontist
Ornithontist
the study of bird's teeth
Okay
Thank you to
birdot for the
two three four
Five dollars here
They say am I winning?
Uh, should I pm you my address to collect my prize?
What what prize?
Oh the bird bird, that's right. Okay
birdot
Talking about the bird house
He was auctioning. I mean, I mean, yeah
It's for you
Just fly on over to vegas
I'll know it's you
Just wear like a german 985 like a wristband or something. So I know who it's you
Just don't get stuck in it
Demonic cucumber. Thanks for the one dollar. We need those push-ups. All right did him
Uh scoot shaco. Thanks for the five dollars
Dude, you're nuts. We're hanging out charity hashtag charity
No, that's not even possible with these pants. Sorry, they're completely sealed
Thank you for the five dollars though scoot shaco
Garfield the monday killer. Thanks for the one dollar tweet tweet. Come here woodstock. How do you do germa?
You got germa you got me while I was inviting everyone's favorite avian
Over to your bird house. Remember when woodstock had that terminal illness and you cured him with your fuzzy bear impression live on stream
That was really something
Woodstock's real thankful through his savory and wants to give you some popular tune publicity. He's
Buying the bird house for a hundred bits. What a historic event in streamer tune relations
Say cheese
That was something
What what did I do? I can hear it's pain. I'm in i'm not in pain
He said his pants are sealed. It means that there's no way
for
There's no way for my beaters to
Do anything like that?
It's sealed
Thank you garfield the monday killer again two more times for a dollar each. So three bucks here total. Thanks garfield
I can't say I care much for alf. He's threatened my life on multiple occasions
Now forget to send the alf threatening my life bits
You get an extra garf buck
Thanks garfield
This guy okay alf is just the sans and barney rubble voice. That'd be a pretty good sans voice actor
What the fuck does that mean? Okay moving on
Okay
Thank you timmy tim tim for the one dollar don't eat italics's brownies
Well, i've seen this
Making you a plate of brownies. Okay
Here's your brownies. I just made a whole tray
I've got it all right here fresh out of the oven
Um, but I just put one percent poopoo in each brownie
Why would he do that to me?
That's disgusting. Why would he ever do that? Why would he do that to me?
Why is he doing that to me? Did I did the brownies he made like fucking three days ago do that?
Did he do that? Did he shit in brownies for me?
He was so adamant that I eat them
Hey, it's russ gara. Thanks for the one dollar. Hey jade
You've done an emote contest in a movie night and he plans for an art showcase
I've been working on some drawings of germa carriages and I got wondering about it by the way
You pronounced my name wrong again
No worries though. I get that you can't read
Love you. Hashtag charity
I think for some reason my my brain
Is saying that your name is like
Russell gara
That's your that's your name. That's your first and last name russell gara
Like hey, it's russ. It's like russ gara, but that's not it. It's not like russ
Is it like it truce?
It truce gara it truce gara
Correct me. I need to know
like it russ
It russ gara
So it's not russell gara
Well, thanks a lot russ
I appreciate it. No, thank you
Hey agent pigeon, thanks for the one dollar. I love you germa, but can you please tell this girl
named
X to go out with me. I'm hoping you can use your streamer powers to convince her that your boyfriend material
Thanks, man and eat my ass. Well, I don't want to say these things
I don't say these things to people. I don't know
I'm not going to tell somebody to eat my ass and i'm not going to what
Thank you agent pigeon for the one dollar
Hey
Sniper. Thanks for the one dollar. Hello germa
Smaller than average bia here. I just got evicted from the dumpster
I was living in and now i'm looking for a place to crash. What's the rent for the birdhouse?
I've got a half-eaten cheeseburger and a very shiny penny
But the birdhouse is for birds. It's not for it's not for people
Dude in the bia place
Smaller than average bia
Streamer wants his viewers to eat his ass
No, I was correcting myself to make sure you didn't think that that's what I was trying to say and that's not
Even what he was saying. He was he was telling someone by direct first name
To eat their ass and i'm not going to participate
Can't even do the voice anymore. I uh small than average. Yeah smaller than average bia here
You know, I just got evicted from the dumpster
Now i'm looking for a place to crash
That was a what's the rent on that birdhouse?
I got a cheeseburger half eaten. Don't worry about it and a shiny penny
That's gonna be enough for me to live there. I don't think I still fucking got it. Come on, man
Arthur from red dead
I just got evicted from that dumpster
It actually is
damn
No, no, it ain't any lad none of that here
Dutch I just I need I gotta get out of here dutch
All right, I'll find out I guess i'll do it whatever whatever you say. Hey mister
That's the yeah arthur arthur
What a fun what a good voice acted video game. All right
I got a plan
I was gonna just scream and do the dutch scream, but not right now after doing that
Hey, thank you suede elaine for the one dollar. I poop in the shower and stomp it down the drain moon two dev
hashtag charity
Well, that was a fucking revolting thing that I just read
In a just stone cold voice
Uh, thank you tune
That's 94 shit
I read it but thanks for the 94 bits
Thank you graveyard ghoul for the five dollars, how many streams did we get the roast of germa 985?
There's too much material there
You give me watch a roast and they're just like trying to reach for like weird shit to say about somebody
Well, you know, let me come up with something. Oh man, let me tell you this one story and the story's just like who cares
That's not even a big deal
Dude, you prefer let me tell you something about x
They prefer
I i'm not kidding. I listen to me
They one time I was sitting on the couch with them, right? So we're sitting in the couch for gaming
we're playing fortnight just like we always do and my goodness if
He doesn't pick up a controller and plug it in
And it was he wasn't even kidding and he only eats red and pink starbursts
Why does he only eat red starbursts
This guy's fucked
But for somebody like there's so much fucked up material
That would be actually embarrassing for me. It happened like two nights ago
when we were playing edf they're talking about like i'm naked and shit and
How like i'm an idiot and like it's embarrassing when i'm like naked
That like if that was on a roast that would be real and it would be actually embarrassing for me
You never responded about the art showcase. Oh shit. I'm sorry
Uh, yes
Yes, yes. Yes
I think something like that would be very fun
I know that there's a
there's a few uh streamers
That I know of and particularly that do art showcases and it seems really really cool really fun
Really great way to show off stuff from the community and i'm all about that
Just not immediately
Once we get to the new year
I'm going to sort out a few things to try
2019 i'm going to come up with a couple of things to do
For either the end of streams or once a week or once a month
That we just kind of hang out and do
Yeah, vinnie does it. Yeah, I think there's there's a few other people that know that actually that do like art streams
But yeah, Vinnie's been doing it and it's really really cool
But that's not something I would do
On like a day to day or a week to week basis. That would be something I'd want to do once in uh
You know, I feel like once like I said every month or two
Is it going to be a death of the memes on new year's eve?
Not this year they get to live
You saw what happened when I when I killed the memes. They just came back stronger obi-wan style
but
Thank you to why?
Am I small no, that's the will that's will I am small for the one dollar
When I visit vegas
Uh, I can invite you to my hotel room and you can piss in my shower
I will probably respectfully decline
Thank you. Uh will I am small for the one dollar and the invitation?
Hey syruk syruk. Thanks for the one dollar. Hello jerry
I have one question that will only take a minute to answer but you can spend as long as you need
Elaborating on the answer if you feel the need to
How have you avoided capture?
for your crime
of
Yut da da da da last year
because
I didn't do anything
I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything
That's how because I didn't do anything
Vegas is a cover-up
Thank you for the one dollar, but I didn't do anything
Where are the pikachu socks?
I didn't do anything. Okay
Uh the pikachu socks and the whale
They will be here soon. Don't worry. I will make sure to show the second those come in the day those come in
You're going to see them the day they come in
Uh will I am small. Thanks for the one dollar 10 out of 10 ball tricks. Thanks, man
Hey serrano
Thanks for the 50 cents and I read it. Why i'm i'm i'm breaking my own rules
But they say hashtag charity and you know, it's worth reading because it was for charity
Thank you serrano. Thank you will I am small again
for three dollars
Ever since I watched germans tutorial for the tommy slov. I've been a big fan
Gotta go now, but enjoyed the stream. That was a long time ago
Holy shit
The tommy slov tutorial
Wow, thank you. I'm being corrected here. It's william
William thanks for the three bucks
Well, if you if you're not here anymore, thanks for watching
Hopefully we see you again soon
Don't waste your talent come to the uk. Wait, what?
Oh, let me see this. I'm gonna see this
130 000 100 over 130 000 total raised so far for like for direct relief
12 more days to show support cheer and include hashtag charity
130 fucking thousand dollars
damn
I just saw it pop up on the screen
Hashtag charities
If you want to include it in that
Which that's awesome. That's a lot of money. But anyways, uh, thank you. Dr. Clay
For the one dollar you're the only streamer
I know if we can build a birdhouse on stream and make it watchable still
Take care. Hashtag charity. Well watchable or not. It was something I was going to do
And I don't know. I kind of had fun
That was fun for me
In quotes watchable
You you bastard
Uh s dog man. Thanks for the one dollar. Hey germa
If you ever did a holiday if you ever did a holiday to australia, would you consider aligning it with a con of some kind?
So we could meet our esteemed streamer
I wanted to donate
5,000 last time but 5,000 bits costs over a hundred fucking dollars
You deserve it. You're an idol to me and many more. I love you, man
Holy shit. Why is it? Why is that so much money?
Why is 5,000 bits over a hundred dollars?
in australia
That's an insane
That's an exchange. That's the exchange rate and like the tax that's fucked up
but anyways, um
Yeah, don't worry about that. Don't worry about
Wanting to give me like a hundred dollars or fifty dollars
That's not important
Thank you for even considering it
But yeah, if I ever decide I mean australia that's a long ways away
australia is
That's a trip. That's like a two week long trip
You can't really just go to australia. Yeah, I live in the u.s. Let's just go to australia for a few days
I would want to spend at least a couple weeks there
Maybe one day but if I was going to go there it would have to be for
I'd want to line it up with at least a couple of particular reasons why I would go
Three months in a balloon
But thank you
That's dog man. Appreciate it
Maybe one day i'll make my way over to australia. Let's put it on the list
Agent pigeon. Thanks for the one dollar. I love you germa if you could please tell this girl
No, i'm not doing that. What?
Also eat my i'm not i'm not naming these two people
Thank you s dog man again for the one dollar. Oh, also I use fl studio a lot
If you need help getting the hang of things message me on the discord or something would love to be able to contribute
Yeah, there's a lot of talented fucking people and I definitely would
Before that stream i'd probably hop into a channel
There's also like I want to make a game
Design channel on the discord eventually here because I want to see how many people are interested and how many people uh,
Because i've seen people making games i've seen at least two instances three instances of people making
playable video games and it's it's fucking really cool, so
It would be nice to have a place
For that and somewhere down the line. I would love to I don't know
I always have trouble
Saying stuff like this because it's not necessarily true
But I have a lot of things that i'd like to do a lot of things that interest me have a lot
Of ideas that i'd like to try to have happen
Now how many of these things are realities right you watch you watched me over the course of four years
Talk about how badly I wanted to write something write a book
I started it. I tried it and every few months i'd be like, yeah i'm trying
And then like a year went by and it's like I I don't think I can do this and then like a year ago
It was like um, that's never gonna happen. So
I don't want to do that anymore. I don't want to be like hey, uh, yeah
So i'll see you like next year when there's a video game that's released and that I made
These are ideas that I just want to see if they're possible, but the channel
on the discord
Would mainly just be for just general
game dev talk because a lot of you guys are interested in it, too
You know, it's not just
Me that eventually that'd be fun to make a game at some point. Wouldn't it?
Wouldn't that be like fun to do in like a few years or something, right?
The bullet hell thing was a game
There's somebody else working on another game
Somebody put like made a whole mugen template for me. There's a lot of you guys that are interested
So it might be fun to do
To have like a place where you could go talk about it
But yeah
Uh getting close to the end here
Thank you dinky duper for the one dollar. Hey, did you see that jeremy guy on twitch?
Yeah, man, he went ballistic over a bird house. What a boomer
He started smashing stuff and then sniffed a whole jar of paint and pooped a blood vessel
It still doesn't live up to bill crazy though. I mean, how are you gonna beat him?
Thank you kairatobi for the one dollar
Uh rats rats with rats
Celebrating it another milestone bash
jeremy 200k this week
jeremy venus coffee and cheez-its are on the way and jeremy's been such a good streamer this year jerma heart
Open up your bits while we all cheer
There's a lot of emotes in there
Yeah, I went I got past
200,000
Not 200,000 beaters
Well, sure, whatever
200,000 uh followers happened, uh, I think yesterday
Offstream
2000 200 500 so thanks a lot guys
I think we passed 100,000 almost exactly a year ago today
That was back last year, right beginning of last year
It's been about a year and a half just under a year. Maybe
That's 100,000 followers in a year. Thank you. That's fucking awesome. You guys are too good to me. Uh, but
Thank you kairatobi
Thank you double d again doubled for the one dollar. This is not a gnome this time. I swear hashtag charity. Thank you
Why did that work so well
Thank you boba fet wars for the one dollar been around since the old days glad I started watching again
Love you, man
Right back at you boba. Thank you boba fet wars for the one dollar and for sticking around as long as you have
Means a lot extra cheesy
Thanks for the one dollar bake a cake on stream and then threaten your neighbors into eating it
If they try to refuse say 4 000 people will know
How they failed?
Uh boba fet wars again four more dollars from boba fet wars. I don't know if bits went through
Oh, they did they did
Well, thank you so much here
Boba fet wars for the five total dollars
Thank you so much
They did go through mostly lost. Thanks for the one dollar. Here's where you set it
Hashtag charity. Yeah, we saw it already
Thank you ken dandy for the one dollar
Long time watcher just quick. Thanks for all the laughs
Recently moved to palm desert and been feeling a bit lonely. So thanks for the entertainment that helps me get through it
thank you ken for the one dollar and
i'm more than happy to
hang out and
Keep in mind. There's plenty of people here too
a lot of people that hang out in the discord and just chill and talk and play games and
Give uh, give it a look. There's a lot of great people in this community for sure just hanging out
But thank you ken for the one dollar
Good luck to you
demoniccucumber. Thanks for the one dollar as much as i'm glad to hear that you're
Did you have regular bowel movements? You've completely ruined it. Maybe i'll try my luck crushing
off
No, I that was a joke. It was a joke and it was just for fun
Sell the logitech keyboard and buy these keyboard pants
Extra cheesy, thanks for the one dollar. No, i'm not gonna buy keyboard pants
How would this how would these even work?
This is just a joke, right?
Those don't actually do anything
Although that would kind of be kind of good
I am not even fucking kidding. I think I would want to use those
Because your hands think of where your hands are naturally resting when you're just sitting in a chair
WASD is right there. I don't know those kind of those kind of cool
Maybe i'll do a stream one day where I just hook up a bunch of elaborate
Gamer gear all over me and do like the gamer android man stream
All right, put that on the list
of things to do
Uh, thank you art van delay exporter of another 25 center
I've been reading a lot of these
If you have stream plans on christmas eve
How are we gonna go to star's house?
i'm not going
That's it. Hey kyra toby. Thanks for the one dollar forgot to charity the last one
Thank you kyra toby
by all means
Use that hashtag
Absolutely. Hey dark star 700 000 games. Thanks for the one dollar hashtag charity
Forgot to add the hashtag to the other bits
Just want to say that if you're able to make painting a birdhouse into a hilarious hours long event
And you certainly have something special
Uh, yeah, you know, you know, yeah, I do I do I do have something special. I got something really special in my life
I got I got something special. You know what it is
all you guys
Because you thought that that was worth watching
that's the special part because
You know like i'm very lucky
That we can just have fun doing that. I'm grateful to have a fun
laid back
a little bit on the loose cannon side, but
Community you guys make this
Even more fun for me. So
Absolutely
Why is sub and donate time without face cam?
Well, that's because I uh, I I don't like face cam
Oh, whoops
I don't like face cam. I don't like having face cam on
Because i'm a fucking weirdo
And I do a lot of weird shit with my face
I've gone back and watched
mods
where
I I let me take a look at how that went. I want to see a particular section to see how that went
And i'm like this
It's just like I don't
What are you doing, dude? Why?
This whole sec there was a whole like 25 minute section of a stream one time where I had my mouth my lips
Just going like this
It's just like are you gonna eat it or are you gonna spit it out?
I did the wrong. I if I clicked I
I clicked the I thought that was connected to this but it's not
I thought it was fucking connected
Hey, thank you timmy tim tim for the one dollar was your pizza good on thursday?
It was
muy
delicious
Yeah, it's very good
I'm trying to gauge whether or not how I feel and I feel kind of bad
I've had bread the last couple of days and I do I do feel a little worse than I did a few days ago
I don't know. I got a fucking laundry list for this doctor because this is gonna this is a new doctor
Right. I moved across the country. So i'm gonna be like, okay listen
Let me tell you all these fucked up things that are wrong with my body. He's gonna tell me to leave
I'm gonna get the music at the doctor's office. The doctor is gonna pretend to get a phone call
Because I we're gonna be talking about this for so long
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah like didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't. Oh, sorry. I gotta take this up man
That's sorry to hear about all that like just go down to the lab and we'll take some blood. All right. Bye
But thank you, too
Uh, thank you to drosophilia for the one dollar get exposed. You just pronounced my name wrong, too
it's
Dro
It's drosophila
Though at this point I might just let it be our little thing
Uh
Yeah, there is no i.a
Drosophila
All right. I got it
drosophila
Have trouble reading. Thank you
Appreciate it. Yes. No. Wait, what do you mean? Yes. No dro drosophila
I'll go with dro. Hey dro
It's quicker
Nice snap didn't fucking turn back on got the delayed magic. Whatever. Thank you to
spuds
Spuds for the one dollar hashtag charity. Hey germa. Thanks for the stream today. What's a good dad gift
I need ideas
a nice pair of
Memory foam slippers
The good ones get a nice pair of memory foam house slippers
Your dad's gonna fucking love them. That's a guarantee
Timmy tim tim. Thanks for the one dollar was your pizza. Good. I already answered it. Yes
I don't know why that I read that one again. Thank you marty 20k for the two bucks. Hey germa
Just wanted to let you know
Uh, my feet smell real bad right now party. Okay party party
That's wonderful. I'm really glad to hear that that's fantastic
Oh, thank you
Uh dark prime. Thanks for the five dollars
I love your streams. Would you care to check out a green screen video I made
It's called the germinator
Uh, well
I did say a while ago that we weren't going to do them
uh in like bit messages
but
I think what i'm going to do I think what i'm going to do
Is there may be
There may be a movie night encore and what I mean by that is
Not like a five or a six hour long stream. We're talking like a end of the stream kind of deal here
Hey, here's like movie night encore and we're talking like maybe 30 to 40 minutes of
Other ones that have come in since you know what I mean?
Because there were a lot of submissions that I've talked about. Hey, it's not just gonna be for one day
Maybe we'll do it again and we probably will because i've already seen at least a dozen
That were not on the movie night that were very very good
Just do it every couple of months
Yeah, but if we were gonna do it every couple months i'd want to give more material
because there's only so much you can do with like
Like a fucking raptor I would need to do more if it's gonna be a regular thing
Kiwo up to upload of like six already
That's so funny
Six
I actually saw I I actually saw one on twitter. It was fucking funny
But if I was gonna do more of that, I would want to do more
So maybe I would do another green screen
appearance
Like the green screen bonus pack one thing at a time. I got this christmas stream that I need to get ready
And one one step at a time
green screen dlc
But hopefully that answers your question dark prime. We will probably see it very soon
Hey superintendent chalmers. Thanks for the one dollar. Hey jeremy. How many bars of soap have you stolen from hotels?
I know it's a lot hashtag charity. There's no such thing as stealing soap from a hotel. It's free
They put a bar of soap in there for you to use it and take it
You're supposed to use that. So
Dr. Clay, thanks for the one dollar and here is you doing it last stream. I got proof right here
Hey, uh beater
Nobody said it
Hey, uh, can I go one stream without doing that?
You said it, but I didn't say it everywhere's closed. I just there's no food
Okay, i'm not allowed to say that tomorrow
Whisper it well, i'm doing hotline miami too tomorrow. I'm not allowed to say beater tomorrow call me out on it if I do
Because i'm not going to
Hey, thank you marty 20k again for one dollar hashtag charity. Uh forgot. I forgot what to say
Oh, man
What were you gonna say?
uh, thank you
Isner for the ten dollars
Thank you so much for the ten dollars here. I'll never be the one guy if I only lurk
Checkmate jeremy. Oh and hashtag charity
And never be the one guy if you lurk. Well, you have to be the one guy
You have to be if to say something
But thank you for the ten dollars and thank you for that putting the hashtag charity there as well
Thank you
Dark prime again for five dollars. Thank you. I appreciate your streams. Would you care to check out the green screen video?
I think you might maybe it didn't go through the first time
Maybe that's ten dollars total here
Uh, I was late to the party, but I think you'd love it. Hashtag charity. Thank you for putting the hashtag charity there
Hopefully I answered your question. Hopefully you're still here
Uh, hold on to that because we will probably put it into a small compilation
On green screen encore night
At the end of another stream at some point over the next probably the early 2019
after the christmas stream
because that gives some more time for people to get some and we'll do another little thing and
You hang on to that. Thank you. S dog man again for the one dollar on the bits thing. Yeah
a udt usd
Plus gst and I guess there's the online tax
Entertainment tax shit. Yeah, it's an it's an around the world thing traveling here
I've wanted to go to america, but likewise, it's a big commitment to make and a lot of travel
Yeah
Travels hard no matter how far you go
You go
an hour
You know to another state
You go
Yeah, i'm going. Uh, i'm gonna go up to i'm gonna go to maine for the weekend, right?
When I was in massachusetts, that's like a four-hour drive and that like that sucks. It's a long way so
Any type of travel is stressful, especially going that far
Five minutes to mcdonald's. Yeah, it's like it's fucking a lot
I can't mcdonald's just deliver
but yeah, and it's if you get like on an airplane or you travel by boat or
More than four or five hours in a car
It's always a pain in the ass
Yeah, maybe one day you'll come over
uber rats what?
Thank you marty20k again for two dollars. Hey germa985. Where's the ocean?
the deepest
At the bottom
I threw up. I just puked because I read that
Hey novi, thanks for the one dollar. Congrats on the 200 000 germamites. Hashtag charity. Thank you
200 000 of you guys timmy tim tan thanks for the one dollar i'm running out of these daily tv videos
I think are funny very quickly
I'm running out of these. I love how you can run out of them
Like you've had a supply rules, too
Excuse me. May I see your license? I'm afraid i've left it at home
In that case, you'll have to take it to the police station within five days
But why you were speeding ma'am, but I was only doing 75
There's a 70 kilometer hour speed limit on this road ma'am. Is there I didn't see a sign
Well, ma'am, we've been following you so you were doing 75 too
No, ma'am, we were doing 90 kilometers an hour and we couldn't catch you
Wait traffic 90 kilometers an hour. Isn't that like
That's like 30 miles per hour. Well, isn't it like 40 miles per hour?
Boomer can't do math. I don't work in kilometers. I don't work in kilometers
I work in miles per hour
Thank you timmy tim tan. Thank you chubby funster for the one dollar. Hey germy you make me laugh
So I guess you're funny or something
Trug uh, jess for confirmation your fursona would be a rat, right? I'm sure you'll answer this and not laugh nervously and move on
from it, uh
No, hashtag charity. No, my fursona would be
If I were to have one like an alternate look there's a haven't you seen that spider-man movie where they're all different spider-mans from different spider-man universes
There's a bunch of you already
The one germa that is a in a fursuit right now somewhere
That exists in some alternate timeline
Is probably
In a big slippy toad costume this one. No, not this one
or uh
I was gonna say goblin
But that's not a that's not an animal. That is a mythical creature
Can a goblin be a fursona?
It can right like a goblin is is that that's that's technically like an otherworldly mythical animal
Goblins don't have fur
Who cares?
Well, that's yeah, that's that's two different alternate timelines
one of them's a frog one of them's a
A toad and one of them is a rat
One of them's a goblin
One of them is a wolf
And then in this timeline, it's uh, it's a a leopard so
Whatever. Okay
I really gotta like put this to bed one of them is one of them's a human it's this one
Thank you moist n
For the one doll i've been watching your youtube videos forever
So glad I finally started to watch your stream keep doing what you do and love your stuff
Thank you moist. Thanks for the one dollar
Uh cook thank you cook for the one dollar germa. You rock my socks. I hope you're doing well and keep us smiling
I'm gonna just keep doing what i'm doing
If you like it, then you do thank you
Thanks for liking it
Thanks for hanging out
Socks rocked confirmed. Hey demonic cucumber. Thanks for the one dollar
If you don't title the gamer gear stream the bionic boomer
It's the bionic boomer i'm gonna get one of those eye trackers and track the screen and shit
I'm gonna be so plugged in there's gonna be so many cords all over me
Boomer
I'm gonna look so shitty too
A heartbeat sensor i'm gonna oh my god
Don't tell me to do all this. I'm gonna do this like soon
I'm gonna get so much fucked up shit. I'm gonna get like a virtual boy
I'm gonna take my blood sugar in the middle of the stream. Although I don't think I can do that
Can I like take my can I like read my blood sugar in the middle of the stream?
I don't think i'm I don't think i'd be allowed to do that. That like breaks t. O. S
What if it was really fucking bad
Oh by the look it's been long enough
Can I tell you guys the the thing that I that i'm so pissed off that I didn't get a chance to do
During the lie detector stream
So I purchased a bunch of medical shit
I've bought one of those blood spinning machines
One of those things where you put all the blood tubes in and it
I purchased one. I actually fucking bought one
And the thing I was gonna do is I was going this is too bad. I'm so sad that this didn't happen
But we were gonna do an elaborate thing me and the doctor
where every question
Instead of just asking a question and then like reading and saying oh that was a lie. That wasn't a lie
He was gonna take up he's gonna drop blood from me
every question
So he's gonna ask a question and then draw blood
Put it in the spinning machine and then put it under a microscope and then determine if it was a lie
And the whole joke was over the course of the stream. I was gonna be losing so much blood that like okay
Yeah, it takes a while. We're gonna do like 20 30 questions
And at the I was gonna like go get like water and come back with like like blue skin
Like I was getting I was draining all my blood and then I realized
Um, that's like breaks a lot of rules here
That would be like I bought like a like a fake syringes and shit and I'm like wait
I don't I can't do that
I don't think I can do that
but I was like laughing my ass off about it me and uh
The guy that helps me do most of the videos and stuff
We were just like
Oh, and the doctor was gonna look up every now and again
He's gonna look through the microscope and be like, ah, this is the most full of shit blood i've ever seen in my life
Like how why would you need that to determine if it's a lie or not?
There you go. There's that's uh
There's some insight on on that stream. I couldn't do the
draw blood from me until I like am fucking turning into
like I was gonna be like
Falling asleep and shit and he's gonna be like waking me up to ask more questions and draw more blood
And then we were like, no, I think that might I think that's a little too much
I'm gonna need a piss sample
Because we were trying to think of like ways that if you took a lie detector
What would you not ever have to do?
But yeah, that was that was part of one of the ideas that just never ended up and I still I fucking
Had the machine up until I moved
I was trying to think about some another way to use that machine
And I couldn't it was just not enough time
No, he wasn't really gonna be drawing any blood from me. It was gonna be all fake
How much did it cost? It wasn't that expensive because I don't know somebody was like getting rid of it weirdly enough
Bionic boomer we have the technology
Yeah, now that I think about it. What the fuck was all that shit?
How much was it? I I I I I can't say
I can't say
What can I say?
I don't still have it. I'm not gonna look there was only a certain amount of stuff I could put
In and when I when I moved right?
So when I was like stuffing up boxes and shit
The big spinning blood machine is not something that it was a priority to bring to vegas
How do you come up with this stuff?
I don't know
You still took the machinima shot glass. Um, excuse me
Uh, the machinima shot glass is like an inch tall
The blood machine was a fucking huge machine. It was giant. It was a big heavy clunky machine that made a loud noise
All right. Let's finish this up
But uh look forward. I look forward to the bionic boomer stream
Put it on the list
Thank you. Uh, lulamore for the one dollar found you on your old layers of fear youtube stream
Where you were dying laughing when the baby was hitting the wall
Been hooked on hooked on you since love you stuff. You always make my day
I hope you're well and merry whatever is you celebrate. Thank you
That was the hardest that was one of the hardest composers i've ever had to because that had a face cam on
I was desperately trying to keep my cool and not look like a weirdo
But how do you keep your cool when something like that's happening? I don't know
Back when I had short hair. Yeah
But thank you lulamore, uh
Right back at you as well
whatever, uh
Merry whatever is whatever you celebrate
Thank you. All right. Only a few more extra cheesy. Thanks for the one dollar. You could wear these with the pants
uh mouse belt buckle
Hello, why is there?
A craziest gadgets dot com. What the fuck is that dumb website?
Well, is this is that website just the in the back of the seat on an airplane?
Like that mall whatever it is like the weird shit that that used to be in the mall
Not the mall in the in the back of an airplane
The sky mall
It's going to be all it is going to be a joke
If you think that the birdhouse stream was just like oh he
So like somebody said look at these pants and hey build a birdhouse
This is gonna i'm taking this to 100 now
The bionic boomer is going to it's gonna happen and i'm going to be decked out
head
To toe
There's not going to be a fucking inch of my body that does not have a peripheral attached to it
It's gonna take hours to go through them all
bionic boomer
I'm gonna attach you know those little claws those like robotic hands like those things that you can reach up like grandma users to grab
stuff
We're gonna like pour a drink
I'm gonna have a robot on me like moving an arm and shit
Oh spill drink joke incoming
You're gonna spill a drink
Not on this desk
I love this so much
But thank you extra cheesy for the belt buckle
Thank you marty20k for the five bucks hearing you read my messages is making me regret
Giving bits while drunk
Sorry, and thank you. All right. That's it up
No more bits
Uh, no more bits anyways because the stream is pretty much over
But thank you marty20k for the five dollars
And no more drunk bits. Okay, if you spill a drink on the bionic boomer, he dies
I actually want it to be hard to move
Is it gonna take like i'm gonna need help here
I'm going to make an elaborate suit that is going to be physically difficult for me to actually move
It's gonna it's gonna be very hard
Thank you, uh wind thank you wind windar for the one dollar
If we do a movie night encore will there be limitations on what we watch?
Like is it possible to avoid 15 to 20 vids of jojo stuff? They're fun to watch but they took up a lot of
uh the first movie night
I would probably say
It would be
um
I don't know. I don't know
I can't really I can't say
because
I haven't thought too much about it until right now
So I don't want to give rules and guidelines on something that I haven't even personally thought about yet. So
Uh, we'll talk about that at a later date when I can get a more clear idea of what I would like to do
But we'll see
and then finally, uh
Solomon the squid thanks for the two dollars. Hey, germa love the stream was wondering if you ever had made progress on that book
You said you were writing it you're back
It's no big deal to me if you decided to cut it all together or put it on hold
Uh, I just wanted to know if there was any cool details you'd like to share on it. Well
uh
I actually uh, i've talked about the book
Not only tonight, but I put the can on it probably like a year or two ago
Remember we were streaming. I don't know what we were playing but I like actually put the nail in the coffin
Like a couple years ago, didn't I it was gonna be a choose your own adventure book of rote with this engine that I was
Learning tell this the end of the book now that it's dead. How far did it get?
I didn't I copy and pasted like a bunch of shit in here. Remember that was how long how many you guys were here
For that I copy and pasted
Probably like 1500 words in here. Was it twine? It was not twine. It was the it was the ink
the
Inkling writer, no, they were not inkling the ink ankle ankle writer. What is this? What are you guys doing?
Weren't there like a dozen pages that got pasted? Yeah, I just like copy and pasted all the shit that was there
Oh, okay
But that's it talked about it. I i'm surprised that people were asking about it
Was anybody asking about it? Did I just go off?
Because I thought I did kind of put the nail in it like a year or two ago
When I copy and pasted everything because we like your stuff. Oh, okay
It was a lot of fun to try to make but here's the next part of this that needs to be addressed
To do something like that you that's what you have to do
You know what I mean?
I can't like unless I like wrote that book on stream
It would never get done because that's what what am I doing? That's what i'm doing right now, you know
There's only so much time in a day
Where if you focus on something
That's kind of what you're focusing on
stream making an adventure book
Yeah, but I don't that's as much as everybody says that that's something fun to do I I don't work well that way
I have to be like silent just staring at a screen when I come up with something that I want to try or write or
Talk, you know like uh when I came up with like, you know
They're getting blood taken from me and putting the uh in the spinning machine for the lie detector
I mean I was silent just staring at the screen
Smart click so you guys write it for me
No
Anyways, that is going to be it
We got a few more here moo means moo one dollar lego's bionicle boomer the mask of light
Thank you
cool 42
Thanks for the one dollar. By the way, the name is pronounced coal not cool
And for some strange reason I watched like five ads and didn't get any bits for them which caused this message to get delayed
Anyway, now that i'm here. I'm not really sure what to say other than you're a great streamer
And i'm looking forward to future streams and future biomic bionic booming
Hashtag charity. Thank you col
Thank you tippy tim tam for the one dollar. Can you get some money out of your money bath and order me a pizza?
Be there in five minutes
Uh fgw. Thank you for the one dollar. Hey germ. I recently got my first car. It is a compact suv
So my friends and I nicknamed it the streamer mobile
All in fun. Love the stream
Man, that's a pretty good car
Compact cars are great. You can get them anywhere. You can fit in a lot of spots
Uh, and then here is from extra cheesy. Here's another dollar. Here's a wearable tv
A fucking wearable tv
I'm probably gonna get all right. You guys ready? You guys ready for like this is like the stream where like jeremy gets sued
I'm gonna have like qvc on that fucking tv
the whole stream
This is the wow the credits roll. Uh, somebody just linked to this
Thank you for all the subs that came in
There were a lot tonight. So thank you guys so much
Oh
Why there's so many of these heartbeat sensor gloves eye trackers, yeah
I'm
I'm picturing the way that i'm going to look in my head
That is making me laugh every time so that's how you know that it's a that's how you know that it's worth doing
A thermometer sticking out of my mouth
Picture the robot labo. Yeah, but way more for the actual
Dude, i'm gonna be careful fucking electrocuted
Imagine if I had like a toaster or something
Like a some type of
Like an easy bake oven
Ha ha
Make food. Okay, put a whole chicken in like a rotisserie
And have that like on my back is like a backpack and then cook it the whole stream
He's the ultimate weapon
And then eat that at the end
Do you remember that will kill you?
No, i'll be careful. If it's if it's too dangerous, I won't do it. He just wrote you will you're gonna burn
I'm gonna get like a burn
Internet streamer burns down
Pretending to be a robot on live stream
Imagine the write-up of that article
Going by his fake superhero name the bionic boomer
Anyways, i'm out of here guys. Have a great rest of the night. I'll see you tomorrow
for
A hotline may i be too?
I can't promise we're gonna complete the whole thing but we're gonna we're gonna play for a while
So we'll see where how far we get
See you real soon. Thanks for coming out
Take care everybody
Thank you extra cheesy for the one dollar. Oh, how'd you get that nasty burn?
I cooked a turkey in a backpack while wearing it
See you tomorrow