So I'm setting up VR. Let me tell you something about VR. I don't know why you would ever
fucking buy this. I don't know why you'd ever own one of these. It's a thing. Yeah, I'm kidding.
Start it off with a rant. Let me tell you something about VR. Should every VR stream
start with me being mad at VR? No, I'm fine. I'm good. The mic is quiet. Well, it's because,
hold on. It shouldn't be now because it was loud yesterday or the day before.
Hold on a second. Okay, I just don't want it to peak. Anyways, how you doing? Welcome to another
two to three hour VR stream. I have a bunch of games. We're gonna roll through them. At least
30 to 40 minutes in each one. I have two back to back here that I want to start with. What's that
thing behind you? What? Oh, let me just let me just grab a water. And we'll start in like
one and a half to two minutes. Be right back in a minute. Oh, the first game. Let me tell you.
The first game we're going to play is the arcade, the peer, peer arcade,
peer arcade two. I don't even know if the games I even have loaded here. It's like a VR arcade
simulator. It looked interesting. I'm gonna try it. I'll be right back. Okay. You guys ready?
That was five minutes. That was not five minutes. All right, let me get over here.
I did. I got a chair. So if I need to sit down, I can sit down if I have to.
All right, we get in here. Yes. All right. Can you can you guys hear it? All right,
the little low for me. Oh, so this game's got skeeball. It's got billiards. It's got,
I don't know, we're about to find out. What was the other one? Let me get my hand here.
Make sure I can see all of your lovely faces, which I can. Please. I have no idea what you said.
All I saw is please. Okay, this actually has index controls, which is actually pretty cool.
All right, press up and aim to teleport. Let me get hold on. My eyes are not in the right place.
Hope everybody's having a good day. Hope you're taking care of yourselves.
All right, here we go. It's a teleport game. That makes sense. That's okay. Why did you do
it? It's a VR game. Don't do that. This is virtual reality. You can't do that. Stop
jump scaring me. It's those need to come up very, very slowly. Wimp. But as if it's,
it's scary. All right, this is how you turn out a snap turn. Yeah. Okay. Sure. All right. All right,
I'm ready. Those got to come up if they're in the so this is my peripheral right here,
right? Can you do middle finger? Oh, you can. All right, cool. So this is my peripheral.
If this, this has to go like this fast. You can't in VR have to be like it's scared. It scares the
shit out of people. All right, how to grab and throw squeeze grip to grab and release to throw
squeeze. Okay. That's pretty fluid. That was fluid. I'll be honest. That was very fluid over here.
Can I do it with the other ones? Insert coins. Wait, what the hell is this? That's how you put
a coin in? Why is this? Why is there like a bomb in here? Oh shit. Really? How's the how's the how's
the audio? We good? How's the audio? I can't see so I need to know. It's good. It's good. It's all
right. It's good. It's good. Sounds good. Freddy Fazbear. All right. What about capitalism? I don't
know. I don't I don't want ambient sounds in my head. Should I smooth turn for you to help you
guys or is this all right? All right, single player. Is there story? Okay. It looks kind of
weird. Does it look weird for you? It looks kind of weird for me. What's this? How much money do I
have? Oh, shit. Are you kidding me? This is awesome. This is like coin game, but I get to actually do
it in real life. Well, in fake life. All right, let's try it. What do I do? Oh, what is this song?
Am I doing it right? I got it. I got one. Turn it. Turn turn. Okay, now come up. What? All right,
bring it down. Got one. This is too hard. This is way too hard. I'm just gonna leave this. I don't
care. I'm just leaving it. Some five year old will come and get a free life. I don't care.
Some some like 10 year old could go over there and get a free life.
Oh, I know this one. What do I do? I was gonna just fucking just load the goddamn thing up with
coins. You know what I mean? 26 credits. I'm gonna be here for a little while. Do I have money?
Where's my money? Do I have like a money indicator? He's a rich kid.
Instructions. Press the button to swing the crane arm. Okay, I didn't get any. All right,
there's like this like $30 in here. Right? Wait, am I trying to get it down here or over there?
Down here, right? No. There we go. That's five. I'll take it. Oh, there's coins. This like has
zero value to me right now. Do you know what I mean? If I know if I have 50 attempts and like
put like $100 in here or like $30 in here, there's no risk. There's no reward. Like I don't care.
There's no there's no stakes. I can just do this as many times as I want. Go harder. All right,
one more. I'm gonna get this hand over here. All right, some 10 year olds gonna be real happy
when they come over here. Like you're welcome. There's like $30 in there. Oh, I love this one.
It's me. It's me like the tooth fairy of the arcade. Like what am I doing? Oh, I gotta be I
gotta be much gentler. That's how you know the person that every time that they're at the arcade
and they play one of these and they're way too aggressive and they're way too rough with it
and they go oh let me try one boom boom and it like goes all the way over there
these things are designed for you to go like this people that like shoot the basketball and
they like shot put it it's like dude relax just do it gently you don't have to go so hard
he's gone mad that's me no it's not hey go kids i'm like paying everybody's parking meters
this is stupid i want this as a prize where am i can you see me where am i can you guys see me
oh this one's a rhythm game i'm trying to get hold on a second wait a minute
i have free rain i gotta try to get it on top of that you know what i'm saying i gotta try to
ring toss it on the top of this pier thing come on i'm gonna get it eventually piece of shit
oh it's close what am i touching all right we're good you couldn't do the ring game
see you in an hour oh my god it's gonna take so long stop just that's the one whatever
fuck it who cares i'm getting kicked out i'm gonna get thrown out all right what is this one
let me get recombobulated here okay there we go all right how does this one work i don't get it
okay i'm not sure cats not playing right now how long is this here you go kid
oh no way i can get it
can i play get out of here
you can play when i'm done with them
um whoa all right yeah all right the pier we're gonna oh these i can buy these prizes
what's a frog one i'm so excited for this the frog frenzy this is the this is the game with
the alligators right the one that goes like ouch do you guys know what i'm talking about
it's like we are the alligators and we'll come in
and ouch oh don't what i'm not doing this right there's like two of your friends are here
two of your friends are here and each of you has one frog or one alligator to deal with
and you get the maximum score possible this is not how this is played
oh
i don't care oh what's this one alpha adhd oh i know this one you have to hit the button really
okay all right hit it button dude you gotta hit it one two three four one two three four
one two three four one two three four i can't hit it fast enough what's this one oh i know this one
this one's all in every arcade too much dopamine okay here we go i know this one you gotta try to
hit all the you gotta light the whole thing up come on come on almost there right there
right in the middle come on come on come on how much time do i have 30 seconds oh shit come on
there it is can i get them all of them all the greens oh shit rainbow
go 18 seconds i can get it oh i just moved it that was weird i don't that was like puke inducing
that's 35 000 points that's pretty damn good oh what's this one nice nice yeah how is it
possible to be good at this game that's right all of you should be afraid all of you should be
afraid of my power all right this is just throw throw the shit i get it these are the ones where
they bounce back you know that one went what the whatever that one's there's a lot of games in here
i didn't expect what's this oh shit you can cheat with those rings oh i'm not allowed yes i am this
is such bullshit no don't there's a wall right here that that you that would have been on the
front page of all the reddits that i've ever been on i would have i was about to just literally
baseball pitch this into the wall and go through the wall thank god for the chaperone
holy shit that would have been awful how many tickets do i have 170 all right okay i mean this
is it's hard to shoot a basketball like this do i have to use both hands i think i have to use
both hands do it again oh no now we gotta call the attendant the guy the guy in the uh in the
shirt has to come over and be like oh so you got it up there huh yeah i don't know what happened i
don't know what happened i i don't know sorry sir sir i'm sorry sir i have to get no don't just
don't do that what the fuck this is so embarrassing you can't even do it standing on the edge oh my
god dude if you saw an adult in here doing this i have to get one oh my god what the fuck no do
it again where i gotta be careful i don't hit a wall okay bye where are you guys okay you're
over here what's this one sumo wrestling how does this work what oh i have to like throw them out
200 another 200 200 200 200 200 that's way too much time i don't want to play for that long
oh nice this is like curling okay curling is actually kind of fun
oh fuck come on do it again i let go too early oh shit come on it's why am i going it's not i'm
not doing it that hard i'm i swear to god i'm not doing it that hard all right there we go finally
yes all right what else is there how many tickets do i have 178 what can i buy at the counter
oh i can get a ball in the cup thing i can get a little ring toss set a dartboard what's this
little little pop gun let's see oh that thing the thing that's at like the doctor's office for all
the babies okay i want i'm gonna do i have 218 get the cock ring that what get the cock ring
oh a little xylophone oh i thought i had to confirm it i thought i had to confirm it i just
used all my money no give that to me i want i want the drum all right i gotta play what's the best
ticket per machine because i want to get more of these toys i'm not done yet well wait what's
over here ostrich run oh i remember these you gotta put the ball in i'm number one what number am i
holy shit that was right in the middle red red red red red that's all right red nice
it's my first place okay i'm number two dude let's go oh i'm weighing the lead this is fine
get in there oh shit i'm choking so bad there it is how many tickets is that that's a lot this is a
two-player game yeah but i should get tickets shouldn't i where are my tickets what kind of
arcade machines i don't get tickets from this one that's kind of horseshit nothing wait what's
down here what neon bowling and coin pushers is way more point let's go okay i'm gonna be stuck
here for like three days oh kid you gotta be kidding me oh yeah yep don't do it look at this
this is awesome all right i'm thinking golden galaxy yep that's what i'm thinking this one
has like the gun okay how does this work oh i got into the ufo where are you guys okay
you want to get it okay there's the indicator what i get i'm just gonna get flooded with tickets
oh bonus oh did i get did i did i see you i don't know if i saw you or not oh i need more hold on you
guys are you guys are right here okay i need to be aware of that so if you're right here that means
i need to turn because if i want to do that right into the camera like right here i'm gonna go like
this right okay so if i go like that and turn okay am i like really close to the camera like
am i am i like close right here i'm like right here okay this is important here we go i've been
trying to hit this for so long god if i can only hit the bonus guys oh hold on a minute we've got
something here oh no way oh almost oh we got something no way oh almost three alien heads
looking for that bonus oh re-rolling again i can feel the sweat going down my ass crack
that's kind of embarrassing nothing oh oh this could be the one guys what do we got
alien alien oh oh shit oh damn it i i'm gonna stay here as long as it takes come on get in there
i'm getting tickets for this right wait what is it guys oh oh close i wonder what the hand is
we got something here that could be big i just have to hit the bonus i don't care about anything
this is embarrassing this is worst joke actual worst joke yeah you say that now but just
but just wait come on give me that do we have a bonus here guys i think we might have something
here alien head alien oh oh fuck you fuck you relax this is like this kids jam oh i got it um
excuse me what the fuck uh dad dad what the hell did you do i i just tried i just did i only had
two tokens left i didn't get stuck in this shit but seriously that's what's going on triangle
triangle that like hurt i just like pulled my eyelids up my like eyelids hurt i like scraped
my eyeballs worth it oh god i do the jim gary all right let's go this way i gotta get the fuck
away from you by the way because like i don't want to go near you oh this one's fun where's
the i i don't i probably look so fucked up and sweaty and my eyes probably look so screwed up
where's the thing for this wait it's it's this big oh my god okay i guess i'll try it
where's the thing to put the coins in i don't see a place to put money in you guys see a place for
me to put money in up left the here why are these so comically large wait a minute but
all right i'm not kidding around i truly mean this i have gone to the arcade where these exist
and i'm i'm fucked up you know what i mean like i'm so screwed up like i will go to one of these
coin machines that have the slots like this and i'll get two or three people to all stand at one
of these and like just just have like 15 dollars worth and everybody just at the same time is just
going like this until i've run out of fucking money this doesn't this feels unfair this doesn't
feel fair yeah yeah yeah yeah oh guys no way we're about to get the number three pink coin
are you serious we're about to get another three pink coin oh there it goes it's about to fall
it's gonna fall guys it's falling look it's gonna go wait it fell it already fell
wait a minute this is the number three i'm so sorry i'm sorry
i'm not gonna i promise i will never do that again everybody hates that what do i do with these
oh wait a minute five four three guys oh we need the two we need the one guys
i can't i promised you i wouldn't do it again and i mean it i won't i i'm apologizing right
now you're getting it but i do want to fill the whole thing up what oh wait i'm doing this kind
of wrong it's got to go down the middle i need one and two this is god damn it this hurts they
got to go down the middle finish the joke there there is no joke i'm just doing i'm just being a
weirdo that's got to go that way though wait hold on is that two all right two is coming down
one i'm not going to be able to get one shit come on at least i'll get the two
all right there's the two bingo guys here we go i just need the one all right just turn my volume
down for like 60 seconds just turn turn my volume down for 60 seconds here we go
go this one right there got it let's go what do we got what the fuck what you have to put them in
the hole yay what's this one this one looks really fun this is the same one all right who cares leave
no don't you dare do that okay so how does this one work okay this one i like this one's really
cute it's balls of yarn all right let's load it up
train coming i've played games exactly like this and i'll be honest if you guys want me
to prove to you that i have played a shitload of these make no mistake about it i have physical
proof of that kind of system dozens and dozens and dozens of those cards that i just didn't know
what to do with if you want me to prove it i will and it's embarrassing you're gonna laugh
your ass off me holly and italics went to round one if you want to see the proof i'll show it to
you prove it i i swear to god i swear to you show us now you want to see right now give me a second
let me see oh my god this is so embarrassing okay you guys ready this is so fucking embarrassing
like this is bad you're about to think you're gonna everyone's gonna think so much lower of me
are you ready to see this shit it's from this machine
okay put the cam a little bigger for this just because it has to be
but those of you that think that i am fucking around that that think this is a big gigantic
stupid joke that i've just said none of this matters here's the stack of cards that i have
can you see that can you see can you see this this is from a machine
it's like 150 cards it's a stack as thick as like an entire collector's box
what's this one oh from marble carnival that's that's what it is marble carnival i have
hundreds probably at least 50 to 100 what do you think
like this is here's your proof just to make sure that i oh he must he maybe he like just got these
so i went to duplicates no no what do you think about that one interesting huh i've been this guy
a hundred times you're such a weirdo i'm i'm telling you the truth why would we not believe you i
don't know people thought i was full of shit for a second scalping well the idea is okay listen
the idea with those stupid and they're fun okay it was just fun it's just so addictive just sit
there just cash them out all right like i gotta get back over here hold on the whole thing is we
couldn't get that we needed one this is how rigged all these things really are so to be able to cash
those in like the full set you need i think it's like a set of come in like a set of 12 or something
reset at 10 and we were missing one out of the probably 70 to 80 times that a card dropped
this one just wouldn't fall so we just have all these duplicates what am i doing with the
headset i feel like it's like playing the mcdonald's monopoly game i got like
50 park places does anybody have a boardwalk we'll be able to get a playstation 3 at the
ticket counter god all right i think i messed the eyes up yeah i did see three was it what it was
back to it i had to prove i had to prove that though people didn't believe me do a giveaway
boardwalk was a one in 36 million chance i wonder and you know you scope out all the other machines
of the same exact one to go okay does that have any cats in it oh no i don't see any cats lined
up any cats here anyways this is bullshit sign them and sell them i don't i don't think i can
resell those i don't they're not like i don't own the copyrights or whatever why did my headset get
uncomfortable okay well this one didn't have any cool cards i don't care all right let's go do
bowling i got 18 stars i can go bowling now everybody wave goodbye to the coin room i think
there's another room down there there's a lot more in this game than i thought there was this
is great yeah i need 18 okay second hall dlc hall what dlc hall there's a whole nother hall
what oh my god there's so much more this is crazy i didn't think it was this big
this is awesome all right here we go let's get over here do i play against computer there's
nobody to play oh one player all right let's go what i'm just gonna use my fucking hands
ow am i standing up what happened i gotta score at least once
let's see if he wins by the time i get back good luck all right we're gonna start over here
oh hold on hold on hold on that was based thanks what do i do i have an idea this why does this have
detection what what why does this fire over here this shouldn't be able to fire over here
can i hit that from over here oh okay hold on i got an idea my head hurts a shock
these guys just had a different game oh shit hold on oh fuck hold on wait
i come from the future you fucking idiot how do i shoot this is there an arrow that i'm missing
where's the where's the arrows where's the what the hell was that where's the arrows in certain
money oh somebody needs to work on the safety practices at this place you can't i can't be
shooting an arrow what about this one this is real it's shooting actual projectile i was just
like yeah look at oh accident what's this one i'm just trying to get banned for life this is so
weird to control how do you 200 200 300 points that one's fun uh what's this one oh i just once
i'm just gonna do it one time oh where is it right there okay that was a really bad i don't
know if that was toad or what i don't know what game that was from but it was a bad impression
what's that from okay it's like okay mario party one mario kart 64 mario party 64
i want you to scrub that that was that was really awful i could tell because it's it's like pushing
on my nose so like the okay like pushed it makes it sound weird and i just commit it anyways but i
want that scrubbed i did it in two tries i win wait they have the sniper game oh yeah this one's
awesome in the arcade as well i'm actually pretty good at this everybody they all met everyone that
omega lulled in the i'm talking everyone that omega lulled in the first five seconds i want
them to be timed up for uh never mind they can stay here oh no tickets though sniper
this shouldn't attack oh just wait attach these oh this hurts
can you guys even see like it's so impossible my neck do you know it's fucking hard to do this man
because i can't hold it with two hands i can't like put it down either i'm gonna bullets gray
gunner oh all right oh got you in 0.7 seconds that's not bad oh what did i didn't i thought
that was part of the set i would that would have been such a good one i thought that was part of
the set right one more time leave me alone what the fuck get away from me good i'm a pretty good
shot if i if i was in the the real one the real one i can do pretty good too
ski ball of course right can't skip this one not gonna skip ski ball oh shit i got a lot of tickets
right into the purple you gotta be kidding me first try all right i gotta go in the purple
it's okay it's all right oh come on dude come on i'm being so gentle with it it's so stupid
try the other side why is that so hard to do i'm being so gentle 500 i'm just making sure
there's no wall right here i'm there is just whatever don't who cares it's not funny uh i
gotta spin this is kind of creeping up on me here which way do we need to spin this way i think i
gotta go this way i think so yeah yeah one more two more okay that should be good that's better
do i have enough to go bowling yep there's one more thing to do here
shock attack i'm pretty damn good at shock attack that's it i just have to feed him oh no it's his
teeth okay i have 25 seconds slow down fuck take the tickets give me the tickets do i not get
these come on i got 500 tickets i'm ready to go bowling what do you guys think stop pretending
do it sidearm he's pretty bad get the drums bowling bowling bowling bowling
all right i'll go let me go bowling this game is cool this is pretty fun all right bowling is
over here there's something over there too whatever it is bowling's all the way down
oh it's a crunching inside of my brain wow all right this is pretty sick i'm ready so how does
this work is it like roll oh i guess it's that easy oops oh the speed oh fuck no play it like
a normal human for god's sake no overhead yeah just give me just start over give me another one
what happened give start over oh i'm trying to like just throw it down the middle fuck do it again
okay i can't move where am i oh it's the cord okay i think are we still live am i not unplugged
or just do it like a normal person and just play your pants have fallen down it's all right
me angry another caveman joke in vr i'll take these for a minute wait wait wait oh no oh no
this is not gonna end well okay get over here it's gonna take a second but it'll be worth it
stop moving all right i think this is enough maybe that maybe one more two more no fuck all
right these two that's it yeah don't walk into the wall too immersed okay you ready wow whoa
whoa dude i i have to leave now that was awful i can't i uh i didn't get anything okay prize
counter let's go what do i have 541 dominos that's kind of cool rubber band gun the ball in the cup
thing that's that's pretty cool i want the ball in the cup thing no don't lose it already
what hey i i need that i have another one i just buy another one i did didn't i all right don't
all right what else what are these little tins there's an airplane wait that's a that one might
be cool blue gun drum get a noisemaker get the drum how much is the drum uh there's a big frisbee
there's a radio what about the horn is that dynamite why is it dynamite okay i need a place
to sit down to do this where did the right here i need a flat surface on the ground i don't even
you guys might not even be able to see me but whatever this is not what a drum sounds like
that's not what a drum sounds like upside down it's not upside down it makes everything
everything makes the same sound get a hold like this so you go like hey i don't care
that didn't work i've got 100 141
how do you shoot the oh it's just an annoying sound maker i don't even want to do it it hurts
why is this just this is just the sound that the drumsticks were making but worse and pitched up
oh i don't want to do it everybody turn your volume down and i mean it i'll turn it down for
you just in case everybody opens this and fucking gets their head like blown off from like the
loud bullshit do it louder no i'm not doing it louder okay i turned it down here we go
that sounded like i was clipping like some physics was clipping into a wall
gary yeah gary's mod prop collision exactly yeah that's too loud now excuse me
all right i think uh i think we've seen pretty much everything i want to see in this game it was
fun i think we can move on to the next one i got a lot of random shit i'm just going to kind of
open something but i'm going to take this opportunity to wait what's this wait wait
wait wait my brain is so weird i thought this is a guy hanging upside down why is it moving
all right is it why is it alive why are they moving why are they moving in here i don't like
that that was really weird damn it i have to get the monkey you're right this is so cursed please
get away from this how do i get this game this game is called peer arcade two it's a vr game
i play a lot of coin games so i figured i got i have to play this one i'm thinking right there
that looks all right what do you guys think that looks all right get it right by the base of the
head that kind of around the neck there it is see right around the neck oh what was the swing that
was stupid this is underwater please get a parrot i gotta get the monkey i can't grab it too much
motion it's moving too much no too much motion i'm gonna get him around wait that actually might be
kind of good get it what is it a bungee jump what was that why did it do that what was that shit
that was unbelievable it's not a bungee cord keep moving that's not it there we go right around the
neck in the head pick it up move it that way what the i don't know if i can get this thing
please turn the music off stick your head in there and see if you can just grab it
no the game like pushes it away i tried doing this but like this doesn't work it doesn't work
that's it that's it i want to see pogs in the chat stop i'm not doing that
why is it shaking around so much stop i'm not touching that anymore what are the other ones
there's balls there's cows there's zombies oh i kind of want one of these um stars
where am i i'm just gonna run into something that was weird i can't take this music anymore
i'm gone wait i can't pick up my friend huh oh well trophies bowling trophies i'm assuming
fantastic flush that's all right it's time to move on to the next game
button let me buy a soda first this was cute i like this this is really fun free drinks for
everybody how about a max go how much is in here there's a lot in this can there's so much in here
it's infinite quick before before they understand before they get what happened take them
wait why is there yo-yos in here what hey kids soda nobody move nobody move i'm gonna crash
myself out of this one uh anybody thirsty we have to keep going how many cans are in this thing
i i'm sorry who are you i just i gotta go double somebody tell me when it's been all right i need
you guys to count collectively to 60 seconds and tell me when it's been 60 seconds it's been 30
okay 45 my fingers are getting kind of tired okay here we go how am i gonna we're gonna have to do
one at a time this is gonna get out of control really quick all right how long do you think the
39 is gonna handle this how okay do you think i can fill the whole restaurant with these
do you think i could fill the entire fucking restaurant with these all right just give me
a minute i feel i at least want to get him to be like 10 feet tall wait there's another one over
there too this looks like this looks like somebody like took a baseball bat to like the soda section
in the grocery store this is fucked up all right i'm in for the long haul i don't care how long
this takes i'm probably gonna lose 5 000 viewers this is a scientific approach to see how powerful
the 3090 is this is a project now and it has to happen i'm gonna have to all right i'm gonna
do this for five straight minutes just here's what you can do ready go open up another tab
okay open up another tab like maybe there's another stream going on that maybe you want to
go check out open up another tab maybe some music maybe do some like work that you've had going on
and just like kind of come back in five minutes i'm gonna be doing i'm gonna be doing the same
exact fucking motion i'm gonna do for five straight minutes so like just just go relax
maybe go take a break i'll be here i'll be here and i'll see you and i'll see you in five minutes
just turn the just mute the stream too like you don't need to hear this
somebody you gotta let me know when it's been five minutes though
just just an agent of chaos this is so stupid nobody tell them nobody tell them
tell me what you gotta go faster it's been one minute okay i'm not gonna need to do any like
wrist workouts for the next two years and all my all my stamina is gonna be gone for the rest of
the day am i gonna be able to even play okay if i need to play a vr game that has like a shooting
mechanic i'm not gonna be able to do it don't tell him black's critical information huh don't
he doesn't know what do i don't i know you gotta tell me he's unaware keep going
okay i'm starting to lose my mind how long has it been two and a half minutes they cap out
where do you see that that says zero zero man where do you see that it caps out they're
despawning no they are not they're all still here with four minutes in they're making shit up all
right ah okay one minute left all right all right all right all right all right 30 seconds
here we go
it's starting to lag it's starting to lag out i actually can't i'm starting to get sick i think
i'm gonna get sick i'm at like 20 frames a second
okay oh boy oh boy oh boy i think i've gone too far
okay there is i can't touch that i can't touch that yeah i was gonna just say jump into it like
a pile of leaves i was gonna say the same thing oh all right this i have to say a very fair warning
here this is gonna make you sick it's it's starting the motion is starting to get fucked up
so just be aware of that it's it actually might make you a little sick so just kind of maybe
minimize the window a little bit don't look at it head on there's so many more in here
wait do i have anything heavy that i can throw over here like a chair
oh local weather says we're gonna get two feet of cans today make sure you wear your make sure
you wear your good boots uh-oh uh-oh open what jump into the pile oh no it's gonna break i'm
trying to move very very slowly and steadily because i know it's gonna be motion sick for a
lot of you guys the end game here is i'm gonna go get a really heavy object i'm gonna throw it
over here oh jesus man okay this one's done oh yeah holy shit oh my god did that okay did
they remember the old jerry lewis movies there was a scene where jerry lewis was like he always used
to run into shit and crash and stuff would break and this exact thing he like runs into a giant
display of soda cans or something in one of his movies he was like a wacky guy he's kind of like
jim carrey before jim carrey and like this is what the aftermath would be i want to see what
this looks like from far away that just looks so awful all right i think i'm actually gonna crash
my whole computer let me just tell you if my stream turns off that means my computer probably
fried so just be aware that this these are heavy oh goodness here we go can you grab a bench wait
can i grab one of these chairs no you can't here we go one two three not heavy enough uh-oh
um you need to get some the fps is going down yeah a bowling ball i don't i can't bring a bowling
ball out here they despawn at the door shit shoot at it what about the drum throw the drum
all right i hope they don't despawn no they're definitely still there the whole game feels like
it's underwater right now i don't think they're gonna despawn hey wait wait whoa whoa did you
hear that that was that was a drum sound you heard that right you need to get the dynamite
you're just trying to break my computer i mean you're trying to break my computer but
i i'm i'm i'm for it how much is the dynamite 500 where can i get 500 tickets quick the coin
pusher i can't i don't want to leave this area just steal it the sumo game does it well okay
okay still don't understand how the sumo game works you have to pick up balls and toss them in
all right not bad what if it goes in that one just lose points
nice no no times one shit this is a long time is this worth it
oh 15 seconds all right times five 500 oh all right let's go how much pick them up this is
bullshit there were only 70 tickets they did not despawn okay 500 70s a lot i need more tickets
though something that would give me more than that that takes too long maybe one of these oh
this if i just spam it and who cares about the timer i wonder how much i get all right i just
ran out how much did i get for 34 this is way way better like a million times better just keep doing
it please stop it hurts my eyes i'm sorry i know we'll get we're almost done i'm throwing the
dynamite over there and then my computer's gonna crash and then i'll see you in like a week i'm
trying just to keep like my head down i'm just gonna keep my head here good again again okay
almost there halfway there you're just grinding in ruinscape it won't take that long i want can i
can i skip this and get the tickets okay yep almost there check on the cans oh they're still
there all right i wonder what temperature my gpu is at right now probably like 110
what's the highest that 30 30 90 can go without like exploding you know the funniest part about
me having a 30 90 is so i get a 30 90 and i don't play any games on it really i play like
fucking fart simulator 2013 a few times a couple of 2d games and then i try to break it with
overloading it in vr why do i have this at this point i probably better off with like on board
graphics all right we're almost there we are at 3 45 we have to do this like three or four more
times i promise we're almost done i'm gonna take a break after this too get some water we'll come
back playing another game 379 okay i got 40 let's see that what's that what's that what's that
379 all right i'm gonna get i'm gonna go 40 again 44 nothing but net you're going to blow on your
computer last one this is it and then i'm gonna leave this game all right this is where it all
comes down to it this is it 500 slowly gonna make myself over here there they are okay
how does this work how do these work how does this how do i turn this on right here lighter
how do i use this go to the cans they're still there don't worry how do i do this do these do
anything it's a flute no it isn't it's not a flute throw it that's just cosmetic it can't be
i have to like flick it on something i need a lighter where would i get my hands are purple
i don't get it don't start them it's a flute it's not a flute that's a wick right there
look for a lighter prize they're not gonna sell lighter at this arcade huh oh fuck you
it's 250 tickets i lost the hand oh my god okay come on i don't even care anymore i'm about to
sleep again i'm losing tracking on i think the vr is starting to crash yep oh yeah this is bad
oh boy oh boy the left hand is not having a good time i gotta do it for science for scientific
purposes what if my stream turns off that sucks this would have been such a huge
okay don't i need those what's going on with the music did you hear that last one okay come on
that's it i'm done i'm done get me out of here 250 get out you i can't even press the button
really got 12 germans destroying the metaverse my god dude this is it this is the last one just go
why are they all missing excuse me excuse me i got four what how is it possible something's wrong
they're coming out of the machine do you understand like something's wrong with this
something's wrong here the metaverse is breaking i drank too many sodas is that enough
i gotta get out of here now i gotta get out of here now i gotta stop freaking out
okay i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done go get the fuck out now get out get out oh god
you guys ready um here we go oh shit oh shit this is bad actually be careful this might actually be
flashing lights and stuff i'm not kidding ah i'm gonna take a quick break gonna get some uh some
water use the drum all right i'll use the drum and then i'm out i'm going to get a drink of water
what is the what is okay wait hey vr josh what does purple hands mean because they weren't purple
before nope nope nope honest to god don't look at that nope i ain't doing that that's gonna like
that that's gonna cause motion sickness for sure nope no no i'm not gonna cause motion sickness
for everybody purple means what move your hands around everybody close their eyes
let me see what my what temperature my gpu is at right now no i'm just leaving it i'll be right
back we're gonna open up another game i have to bring my computer cpu down to like at least 10
degrees i'll be right back somebody said wait crash it you idiot all right i'm gonna give a
really strong warning here strong warning i'm this is about to be unbearable to look at
i'm not kidding if you're if you're sensitive to like motion sickness and like flashing shit
this is gonna happen be careful i'm dead serious if you don't think we can handle it then just i'm
serious be careful i'm gonna drag the drum around i'm serious this is gonna be very very painful to
look at please be smart about this here we go
and that's the bottom line because stone cold said so i'll be back i'll be back game didn't crash
it's okay i'll see you guys in two minutes okay i'm gonna be loud you tell me tell me how loud
this is how is that what the hell is the name of this game i forget the name of this game i think
it's called legendary tales called legendary tales i'm quiet yeah i'll be i'll be loud when i put
this back on volume is low yeah don't what once i get in the headset it'll be fine don't worry
not played either the last game or this one really okay yeah all right am i still quiet
because this is me with the headset on probably not i'm ready let's do it this is called legendary
tails how you doing this is like a sword and magic and skeletons game when you're gonna play among
us vr oh maybe next time okay i'm gonna have to do some calibration sus guy plays among us vr
50 000 viewers and i have to have the sus image at the top right of the screen the whole time
right like i don't even have a face cam it just it's just the sus cam let me get in the right
spot okay we're back we're good i think the gpu is fine that's a catastrophic event the
gravitational pull is gonna probably be bad right all right calibration spread out your arms in a t
pose press the trigger button then move your hands down by your sides what the fuck okay your current
controller is not the oculus it's the index it works so he said yikes all right tutorial oh this
is a lot of info um legendary tales come over here how do i do that oh i can just walk point your
hand welcome to legendary tales i am a guiding wisp that will teach you about the features of
legendary tales the basic controls are shown on the side left track pad move press left track pad
right run track pad i just read that like a fucking weirdo okay run right track pad turn
i mean yeah it's just it's just the movement it's grip okay two-handed grip stop it two-handed grip
changing hand position you can change the position of your hand on the weapon by holding it
grab the weapon with both hands probably moving one of your hands along the weapon by holding
the indicated button rip wait what trigger grab weapon track pad change hand position what track
pad's a little thumb thing right oh okay i see it's kind of weird though that feels weird i can't
like uh point your hand add a holster get out of here there are a total of three holsters on
your body one on each side of your hip and one at the base of your spine put the shield in the
back holster and the sword in one of the side holsters trigger pick up trigger at holster
position so that's okay that's in all right so then now what do you now now what do you want to do
so put this here oh okay cool items can be moved directly from the field stop doing that move your
hand over the items of the status window appears and use the key shown at the side and the item
will be automatically added b um press downward on the right analog stick oh okay interesting
inventory the menu screen can be open whatever okay press up on the analog stick
press up right analog stick press up right analog stick press up right analog stick
oh that was weird okay that's me this is really actually kind of cool equipped yeah there's the
equipment close it again nice interact with trigger so equip that put it in a slot i think
probably unequip okay cool i've had enough open the menu screen okay i've had enough
it was a menu this is the menu right i've had enough skip skip i've had enough skip i've had
enough i've had enough i'm done i'm done help point all right really interesting stuff yeah
i can see my inventory lip i'm just leaving just leave press press it it's a button this is the
menu what can i pick this up how to use item crystals when you kill an enemy or destroy an
object a crystal may appear in the treasure chest if you attack throw or crush the item it'll be
destroyed and a random item will be dropped there try these different item crystals oh shit what's
this oh cool all right yep i get it navigation doors left analog move right stick turn so what
do i do point your hand i don't even know what that is guiding wisp the door will absorb more
of your health and summon a guiding wisp bro i don't even care have you played a game called
real life before um yeah a few times climbing ladders all right grip you just grip and go
trigger grab all right good all right i think i got the tutorial down rope climbing same way grab and
and go wait okay oh this is i don't like this hanging place your hands on a nearby surface to
climb hold the object with your hand and pull the controller down to elevate your body okay
place your hands on a nearby surface to climb hold the object with your hand and pull the
controller down does everybody understand what's going on the video what's the video is just
showing me like he's going like this grab push where's the shortcut hang oh we got more than
one rung here we got more than one rung that's how you know hey excuse me i'm just gonna skip
that's fucking this that's that movement is is i don't want to say it i'm about to i don't want
to say it i'm about to say it okay you fucking chimpanzee shit get me to the game i just want to
play wait i'm supposed to go down there whatever damage type damage all right i want to play the
game now like right now sky room dungeon uh-huh there are three types of attacking weapons
slashing piercing and bludgeoning slashing is done with the blade piercing is done with point
bludgeoning is using the blunt each weapon has a different damage multiplier for different parts
compare the damage by performing different attack types of the weapon provided okay that was good
to me let's try it this feels like it's gonna be fun it's fun i just want to play it light attacks
yeah yeah oh i get it okay good heavy attacks uh-huh check the damage value this is a heavy attack
trigger i just broke my hand very cool goodbye thank you wait archery whoa holy shit that's fun
that's intuitive bow and arrow present hold the trigger to take an arrow out this game's fun i
think i understand the basic concepts of the game you're gonna shoot your eye out i'll be fine
defense yes with shields you can defend who who would have guessed when i don't have a shield
anymore when enemy is attacking knocking into the enemy's weapon at a certain somebody will knock
it away and you can parry oh now let me jam it into his head parrying when enemy is attacking
you can hard parry them by hitting them at high speed uh-huh i don't i can't understand this this
side go like that way maybe i got it when they swing to the right i don't get it you're doing a
great job thanks so much terry thank you so much you might be dead but you still got it still got
it terry i know it was you by the way oh magic select the magic you want to use in the summon
there's many magic slots activate the magic circle by pressing the button
a open the magic circle okay in the skills tab oh fire arrow okay cool i'm into this by the way
press up on the stick and we're gonna go here the magic tab there's the magic tab magic here okay
fire arrow what do i do that how do i do that again fire magic tab there are too many rules
where's the fire magic tab that i don't have that on my list oh oh god okay fire arrow learn
thrust your hand forward and release the button to fire an arrow they're gonna go like that okay
let's put it up here uh-huh can't close that so summon a magic circle select the fire arrow
okay when charging is complete thrust your hand forward that didn't do it is it going behind me
i'm not that's not working it's a blowtorch you can combine spells fusion magic all right
we're almost gonna play the game i promise you don't you guys remember the rule of thumb said
this 100 times every vr game is just a tutorial you just like hey by the way like your fingers
can go like this all of them do this all of them make sure you put your hand down here try it i
mean there are some there are some lots of things in this game that you have to know i get it all
right fusion magic you need to what are you saying use fusion magic you must learn the spell it is
made from as well as the fused version you will also need to place it in a fusion magic slot
along the bottom so if i go like this and i can i like put it down here what does the video say
all right you like he's like i have to learn whatever this is ice arrow what does it want
me to learn acquire the fuse magic lava axe what the fuck okay so where's this where's a lava axe
okay learn summon lava axe what does this require fire arrow and fireball what does it have to do
with an axe okay um i got i have it now use it try using the magic spell i have to put
um okay put this here equip it cast hold trigger i've been i have to i have to put it up here
bro give me a break what equip fireball okay equip fireball so i have fireball but fusion's
down here how do i how do i do this fusion fire axe put it up i cannot put it up here
do i have to like put them my hands on both what is this video trying to show me
okay so i have to put it on both hands so that's selected that's selected right selected
is it what the fuck why is it not on here and then mush your hands together all right please
let me get out all right eat you eat orbs to heal i got it how do i exit the game okay fill your
hp potion try filling up the hp potion take several recovery orbs why did i even do the
tutorial i probably could have just been fine so fill one all right so that's how you fill up
potions you currently have very low health use the previous if you go to open and b press right b
use stored potion is that what i just did press top right trackpad open inventory change potion
type i need to leave the game now okay change potion type fun recovery orbs can be used i okay
why did i do the tutorial this is so stupid point your hand take the weapon and shield
and hit b press down on the right stick now acquire all the orbs while your hands are full
all right the you know when you go into like a disney ride and they play the video before
you get on the ride and it like the the video to get on the ride is like 20 minutes sometimes
and the rides like 15 fucking seconds okay you can equip stuff this is too much info
just put it on my hand what okay you can wear helmets okay awesome this is sick i this game is
going to be really fun i know it that has to be the exit right there this money really open the
menu open the menu open the menu okay thank you yep got it and i got the bow cool got it sick
this game's awesome go thank you please i thought i was going to get the controls okay get me out of
here i just want to play this seems like so much fun too why did i even click the tutorial
uh-huh yep pick up your sword you get it back what else what else you got for me anything else
thank fucking press the fucking button let's go come on press shit that's all i needed to know
that's the only thing i needed to know where's my shit where's my shit all right let's go i'm
ready let's do it i'm ready play i'm fucking ready we're ready to play the game now this
game's gonna be i swear to god this game is gonna be fun i promise all right i want to do what do i
want to do for a character what do you think max luck i don't think i can put any points in it
okay i think i have to start with strength decks okay bows dad i'm gonna do decks mad that this
could be fun i want to do like like ten points in decks abby i guess is my name whoa normal
abby let's go you guys ready welcome to legendary tales okay what do i have on me open up the
inventory i saw the tutorial i know what i'm doing nothing in my inventory i don't have any
spells here we go oh shit this actually looks good we talked a bunch of shit about the tutorial
but this looks like it's gonna be fun and i mean it any weapons are there boss fights like that
that'd be awesome if there was what do i do
what's happening you're doing it that's what it is oh whatever it is you're doing it oh nice here
we go they said look for coins they said look for coins crystal oh shit this is too big for me
pretty yeah this is too big for me there you go this guy right here this guy right here that
thing's too big for me yeah remember i'm dex manna they're not be what i think it is i hope not
whoa that was cool what thanks good to know what do you got helmet money all right we finally got
enemies to fight does somebody already play this level i feel like somebody played this already
i kind of don't like the health meter it's fun it's fun i'll tell you items it's fun resident
sleeper i'm not gonna read any of those i already know what to do shield i'll take it nice what the
oh give me what's up oh what's that something small what's the difference three to five what
is it yep this is this is short as well look at that nice what is this oh it's even smaller three
to five three this one's smaller i'll take it why is he swinging so wildly i'm not swinging wildly
it's finesse think about how many times i just hit you that was like seven times in a second you'd
be carved up like a christmas turkey okay let's keep going why is he still playing dizzy bird
i got a lot of mana potions i don't care oh i can buy this how good is that so this one is
two to five three to five three to six no i think i would i got better stuff i finish and move
hey oh why would i throw my dog right in the face oh shit where are my sword oh what oh no oh no my
confidence is gone all my confidence oh give me that you can't shoot yourself how do i take this
with me he's doing it how do i take this with me okay here we go good let's get that confidence
back let's get that confidence back all right open the doors all right we gotta go this way
this way i hear somebody somebody's behind me somebody's walking behind me what's going on
i did it my head's wicked edgy yeah thanks for the weapon buddy oh a save point map gimmick
okay that opens up over here what am i going i think i fucked up i think i screwed up you're
missing oh sorry i'll be back where are you okay i'm coming back here i am uh where did i where
am i going the other door in the cell like back here like this way oh my god see you later what
is that wait what is this it's like an ironing board what it's like a fucking panini press
it's like a parry shield because in dark souls i go like this right like oh okay you can climb
lots of things in this world can you oops there's a chest over here what's in it that's a lot of
money what oh my god these are blue these are rare these are rare gems these are rare gems
it's the same exact thing that's the same thing i had before okay i take the coins i just get did
i get them it's got better stats though that's cool this game's actually pretty fun can i die
from this if i fall it's dark down here oh nice okay so now what oh by the way so the next time
i play vr uh we're gonna we're gonna play that blair witch vr game we're doing a horror game
go back go back come up okay so i gotta go back through here i think am i doing this right or is
this wrong oh shit blair which is now also vr yeah it's like i guess they made a blair which vr game
you need to put a green screen behind you hey can you twerk yeah oh i need to weigh that down
what do i not care about all right i'll be right back sheesh oh sheesh no don't drop the fist no
souls no i still kind of don't know what i'm gonna use the wisp you're a zoomer i'm not i just heard
that a lot where's the wisp okay we're following this thing where do we go from here man where do
i go from here where do we go oh the ac just turned on it's a wonderful look up there's nothing
there do the map gimmick thing um didn't i already do it i thought that opened up this yeah like i
pulled that didn't that open that dude go kill a bigger monster bro go back to the climbing room
and open the door are you serious i want it there we go okay go back to the climbing room wait you
mean he's literally shitting i'm not i'm not shitting what what resource pack is this open the
door that door wait that door look i didn't even know you could open doors oh boy look what's in
there oh legendary items healing orbs yeah i know i know all about them i have a criticism about vr
every game just wants you to know that like you can use your hands to climb look i can climb i
like i'd rather just have it just do it by itself i just hit up get up here i don't need magic i'm
not a magic user i have a bow and arrow i'm a bow and arrow user but i think the game really
wants me to use magic where's my bow all right let's pick these guys off can you climb god i
feel like i'm playing pubg again there'd be a guy that had no fucking idea that i existed and he'd
be walking around picking up frying pans and looking out windows and i would just be missing
him over and over and over and over and over again and then finally this guy down here notices
that i'm shooting at him turns up and goes tap tap tap tap tap and i'm dead instantly like how
will people that go to video games i don't how are you that good how could you hit this from here
oh my god you little shit he's a skeleton it's going through his bones he's going
eat this motherfucker i hit him with that but i don't hit him with the bow and arrow i that's
impossible that's not i that's not even possible i'm going down give me that oh that's not what
i'm used to so my specialty but i'll use it let go of it i don't care extended range actually this
is kind of this is not bad is it gone oh shit free glove oh boy fight portals you've just learned
how to use a portal portal boy this lightning why did i not use this how many points i have okay
can i should i do lightning that was probably stupid but i don't care that's left yeah okay
abilities strength dexterity general critical damage increase yeah oh yeah let's get that this
is kind of cool fuck cool all right portal all right so we go in that was kind of fun your ass
is in the camera oh i made it out of the tutorial this talents people why is it just tristram
oh this is cool we are why are you so big how much is that bow oh can you steal how much is this
257 bucks i don't want any of that armor i don't need armor armor is for what's this two to five
what's that three to six tower shield that's not bad just kill them i can't attack a townsperson
oh that's my stash this is just diablo 2 all right i'll go punch a guy oceans i can't it's
not gonna happen guys no i can't all right so let's go i'm ready i talked some shit in the
beginning but this is actually kind of cool it's a slow burn it seems but it seems like
it's pretty damn good i'm just gonna go and see what happens oh you have quite a treasure there
in that herodra cube somebody asked for that i did it probably doesn't sound very good my nose pinched
according to the herodra a speed yeah okay what happened here people were killed something must
have happened okay so what when i was a young boy over the ocean this is where the part in the
disney movie where they get over here and they start singing out to this jump that just made me
almost puke i think i maybe i'll come here later all right i'm giving this 15 more minutes and then
we're gonna move to another game 15 more minutes incoming i don't know what i'm supposed to do
go into the church not the portal do the stat points send invite oh wait you can play with
people magic all right one skill point i could do lightning didn't i already buy this what's
going on here i already did this 10 crit damage i thought i'd already i did it already play among
us vr i i'll probably play among us vr on the next vr stream i don't even want to play that game
though all right go to the church i don't really even want to play it because i i don't know i
don't want to like sit there and be like oh so where were you man oh i was here i don't like
know anybody i don't want to play vr i don't want to play among us with like a bunch of random people
that i don't know isn't half the fun it's like trying to find out if your friends are lying to
you i don't i don't like really have that i don't really talk to that many streamers there's like
three people i would be like are you ready among us vr i would have to get in there and like
just get into lobby and say i'm the sus guy eject me and even if i was a crewmate just get rid of
me and then i'll just leave the game i don't have any items i need a weapon don't move what is that
oh shit here he comes give me that give me that whatever it is give me give me
he just ran into the wall
why is he still alive fucking beating the fucking shit out of this guy
oh good block i need the weapon that's on his hand what the fuck dude no no give me this
this i have to buy a weapon all right let's go i forgot that dude in the face like at least
15 times all right give me this guy writer it's all i need let's go you died in the cathedral
level one i died in the yes i did because i don't know i didn't i didn't have any items
okay here we go no more fucking around now i actually have items i can actually play the game
now jeremy relax like it's not a big deal you heard the guy like yeah i don't even know why
i did that all right where's the little goblin some shit in vr just really does it to you i don't
know why that was a block i'm gonna go for a thrust oh what the fuck oh my god this game is
called legendary tales yeah no it's good it's actually kind of fun i did i i tutorial talked
shit but that was i i think i jumped the gun there this kind of feels like blade and sorcery
where are they what is that what is it it's a bat where is it behind me it's just sound effects
that's not even nothing here there's nothing here oh my god it's a bat hey i got a frying pan
oh shit the scariest enemy in the game so far there's nothing up what is even up here
why would i come here stay back hey there's nothing what's the point of going up here there's
nothing here at least i don't think so i'm okay surprisingly shit what no put that away where'd
you come what i don't know how to punch him in the face fuck you that's a bird that's not even a bat
there's nothing even there i'm sound like winded give me this thing i don't even care what it is
i have no my weapon i've i'm winded i'm a little winded when i'm going back in there i batwheel
that's it's scary they like swarm your head and there's all the sounds are inside of my head
there ain't nothing getting by me now nothing getting by me now where do i go i can't do
anything down here oh my gosh this is tom and jerry cartoon i don't there's nothing here
this way maybe let me touch the wisp where am i going where's the wisp
oh god he took his head off those are three perfect swings oh yeah yeah okay fine sure thing
i think i got him i didn't lose i'm there's no bats in here the deck i don't have enough
strength to do this to use that well no nothing this way wait boxes take it i'll take it rest
away sometimes i what what game is this half visible i'm sorry i i'm just trying to stay in
frame all right i haven't opened this yet i wish there was a map because i'm kind of walking in
circles all right this is new all right dead dead money i'll take it shit where's everybody
you look at what i'm not gonna let you kill me you little shit no it's not gonna happen
i'm not gonna let you kill me no pick it up pick it up pick it up pick up what is this oh shit
why am i so bad at fighting these why does it turn into a mr bean movie i don't understand
why does it turn into like a comedy whenever i see a bat they freak me out i don't know why
okay i can't get in there leave me the fuck alone that way i could do it that would be so cool if i
just like okay you know did you guys ever have the the rope climb in gym class you guys had that
right that was a kind of a fucked up messed up thing to have it just did they still do that
i remember they had the ropes come down and you climbed the rope all the way to the ceiling and
it was just like oh yeah that's just what you do you just climb to the you just climb to the top
of the ceiling without any like help they still do that isn't that dangerous i don't remember any
safety harnesses it's just like holding on for dear life being like what it's fine that's a boomer
thing it's been 15 minutes oh okay they're like four feet tall no they were not they went all the
way up to the top i remember that yeah i would loathe seeing those ropes hanging from the ceiling
and you'd i don't know you'd always kind of go up like a quarter of the way and just pretend
like you just like can't do it i'm too weak i'm way too i'm too weak like okay fine i really
want to get up here so please right here i oh god do i have weapons
all right stop making a dark souls joke and play it's all right all right all right it's been 15
minutes all right all right i hear you i now i hear you all right we're moving on that game was
kind of fun though i'm not gonna lie all right we're gonna take one more brb i'm gonna hop into
another game i don't know what it's gonna be it'd be a weird one that was legendary tales actually
pretty fun that was actually fun final brb i will be right back and get some water the final game
that we're gonna play today a game called vr workshop making some things out of wood
woodworking game kind of cool how's the tea it was good that's some water
at 330 yep this is we're definitely getting to that point where i'm uh
flowing down this game is gonna be way too hard for you what choose the board that yeah this is
gonna be easy i'm gonna have a good time all right let's do some woodworking this will be
where we end it today and then the next stream uh i don't know how long the blair witch vr game is
but i'm gonna start with that and that will probably what's today because i have to have
enough time to make sure the big stream on the first is good to go so i'll probably what's
today the 23rd 24th 23 i will probably stream next on the 27th because then that'll give me
plenty of time to get the rest of the stuff ready for the first so we'll probably do cooking sim vr
blair witch vr and if i have time for one more maybe maybe among us vr would be a pretty pog day
but yeah let's let's get in this and see i'm back on thanks for sticking around by the way
kind of slowed down a little bit the tutorial there but i'm having a good time happy birthday
to that person whoever you are all right so this is a woodworking game wait can you guys hear is
this sound i don't know this sound is there sound no uh hold on okay choose wisely instructions
okay choose the board that corresponds to the board represented in the drawing place the chosen
board on the x ring the bell receive judgment contemplate your actions go to sleep sleeping
pills what do you mean sleeping pills why would i take sleeping pills what i didn't even make
anything i just took drugs and went to sleep all right choose wisely begin begin okay so i just
quit the game flipboard workshop guide okay where's that where's that chair all right workshop guide
movement decides using your feet you can teleport smoothly and rotate okay press and hold the
teleport button well i don't know what the teleport button is okay press and hold the
teleport button look direction present hold bulb left and right hand teleport buttons
okay what else you got tool belt use the tool belt to keep your tools and other items closely
switch interact near the belt buckle all the tool belt follows you around i just never could do i
could never do anything in school this wasn't gonna ever happen all right here's the wood
okay here's a piece of wood i see is there a dog auto what are you doing over here
dad daddy's working okay what are you supposed to do oh whoa it works what's that thing's name
from ed ed and eddie okay so i need to i got my tool belt here i need tools that's where i sleep
okay what do i need to make choose wisely materials total score i'm ready to submit in a second here
choose the board that course i'm gonna this is gonna follow the board represents what get back
in frame i'm coming that's a wall i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming okay so what the fuck am i
supposed to do all right so here's the thing that i need to grab this is the thing so this goes over
here choose the board and put it in the x i did it i didn't do anything is everyone supposed to do
complete okay uh now what one out of now how do i play welcome to the workshop begin a new project
what's going on change on the projector measure oh it's a tutorial ah okay oh instructions saw the
board to the correct length using the drawings as a reference submit for judgment okay so i gotta
take that piece of wood and i've got to saw it 24 inches long so it's gotta be 24 inches long you
got it 23 okay there needs to be so i have to saw it from here so i gotta saw it to that line
because that's like 20 that's like just about 23 inches so now i got a saw
that would be so scary grabbing it by the blade not a great idea by the way so how do i do this
how does this work holy shit i just did it this is fun okay so this is 24 inches long
get it on the x that's it right 63 percent how i thought it wanted to did i get it wrong
that doesn't make sense i did it wasn't good enough what do you mean 24 inches long how does
that make any sense 24 inches long oh a vice so what the hell use a pencil mark where 24 inches is
23 that's 24 right here that's literally 24 inches that's off of the table okay that's 23
no it ain't 23 24 yeah i had it right what is that all right i got it 89 what's next make the cut
oh this one's gonna be fun please use the tape measure okay what do we got saw the board to the
correct length using the drawing as a reference submit for judgment sleep tight okay but to make
a cube that's easy that's easy okay that's i made a cube that's it it's a cube a cube is a cube
hold on that was a shit cube you cut it diagonally no i didn't maybe a little but what does it matter
can i do it again oh shit it is diagonal all right i had to get a this is the wrong way stop
this one's worse i think you need to measure i don't like oh i don't like measuring i don't care
who needs to measure all right get out of this chair i'm gonna fall down if this chair keeps
getting in the way all right fine i'll measure it i'll do the stupid thing we go like this
okay look sure here we go here's your edge here we go take a look here is it gonna be a perfect
line wait how does it this doesn't matter if i draw a line it doesn't matter what if i go like
this i don't get it read it this is i can't do this it's impossible measure how i've never taken
a woodworking class please he doesn't know what i don't understand i don't know what to do no shit
it's just geometry the last time i was in a geometry class class bill clinton was the president
okay i don't remember anything from that class i don't know anything from that class all sides
are equal oh i see what you mean by that it's perfect goddamn cube if i ever seen one what
happened here i wonder if it's gonna be fucking right i'll tell you that the teacher doesn't even
check anyways you go up there with a cube and they go yep that's that's a cube all right that's a
passing grade i'll take a see whack whack he's pretending he has to be pretending oh wait nail
the two boards together oh this is gonna be fun okay does it i don't doesn't matter how do i have
to do anything weird pick up the whole thing what the fuck okay that's pretty nice like little lip
for the shelf it didn't say i had to just it just said nail them together yeah i mean nail them
together that's it you're a caveman 240 this i like this game a lot this is fun 24 inches long
they both are 24 inches long okay 24 inches long what if i just double them up that saves a bunch
of shit a lot of time right the 24 inches long tape measure 25 24 25 20 i need the pencil 24 25
25 okay i was saw if you picked up a tape measure you're reading centimeters what no what are you
talking about why am i in the way okay get right there oh okay now they got these perfect now they
have to be this has to be put on here like this i have to put this in the in the vice again what
am i what am i making okay so this goes in here cool then how do i glue i have to glue this where's
the wood glue finishing nails common nails do i have to glue this there are grips under the table
oh i think this is okay that's good that should be at least a b i don't even need a tape measure
look at that perfect that go in yeah it's in this is solid one maybe like one more i think
that should be good that's solid that's solid that's it that's solid that's a that's going to
be at least a 70 or 80 that's definitely going to be good that's a 98 percent all by the way i need
a tape measure you sure almost almost 100 percent all right well now what stool sample i have to
make a table now oh boy this is going to get weird okay what is it i have to use bread 18 everything
is it's an 18 inch long table 18 inches so the whole thing is 18 inches 18 what is all that
what i only have two pieces of wood 18 inches long and then these are 10 inches long so i need two of
these two 18 inches is this whole thing to double 18 what is the measure how long is this whole thing
stop this is like 27 47 this is like 47 inches long what's 18 plus 18 oh 36 so i need two pieces
two pieces two 18 pieces of this one right no of that one um two 18s of this right next to each
other or two 18s of that right next to each other this one that one the bread get back in frame i
hold on the narrow one is 18 so 18 twice but then what about this one is this the back i these like
i'm sorry but these like little dumb ikea drawings they're not that clear what what is this
what am i looking at here what what am i looking at these are not instructions these are caveman
paintings this is the caveman painting instructions i i can't decipher with that what the what they
want me to do the width of the whole thing is 18 but there are two see one two cut but this 10
what's that the width of the whole thing oh the bread's so crusty listen to this when it comes
out of the oven you can just hear crunch of the bread do you need a hand saw to cut through a
piece of fucking bread that would be the toughest most disgusting bread ever all right i don't get
it i don't get it i'm not i don't really work with my hands i'm more of an idea guy you know
i'm more of an ideas guy this one needs that one needs to be two pieces of 18 hammer a nail
into the bread i love how you guys are giving me tasks that you know that i'm capable of doing
like i'm like the i'm like the weirdo that just comes here and does this oh yes i hammer a nail
into bread that sounds easy i do that right here oh hey look what i did daddy no i don't want to
bite into this what if somebody bites into this they hit the nail hold on let's as you see we had
that flavor injector and add look at that look at the peppercorn we put in there is it gonna cut
through the nail one peppercorn one peppercorn in the whole piece of bread all right i need to
help somebody get somebody help me just help me nobody does this shit alone anyways are you serious
who does this shit alone you like have three people all looking fanning through the instructions
i don't know dude what do we even have those nails be my person that's here helping me
make a sandwich with wood
i can't i can't that's what i'm capable of doing oh okay fine oh there's mold on it okay
okay okay i'm gonna slice the bread real thick oh yes absolutely delicious thinly crusty slice
bread no that's too thick just make a i'm gonna make a sandwich with nails get off of me oh this
is so dumb i want to make kind of okay what if i just make my own thing can i make like a chair
out of this stuff should i just dump the whole bag of nails in here nail it to the calculator
can i even do that no wait let me just give me a minute i need at least two pieces of bread
what happened to the saw wait this paint what this game is so cool why can i be smart enough
to enjoy it fresh mayo or ranch doesn't matter coat it each and every pore it really will absorb
the tuna okay where's the saw is there any mustard i don't we only have white paint right now
we only have white paint god damn it dude this whole stream has just been like do the weird thing
today can i just dump it over okay where's the wood what happened to the saw okay give me a nice
slice of this a nice thick wood burger okay we're gonna do a double a double patty need another
piece of bread top it off with some nails and let's get another piece of nice thick cut bread
all right what if you walked into dad's workshop and he was doing this what would you do would you
be like dad what the fuck are you doing dad like what's okay i can't have the nails on it actually
went through it actually worked and who could get the mayo it looks like it's lined up okay
all right that's done and then somebody said nail it to the calculator submit this all right if it's
more than five percent i win that's how this is gonna work holy shit what 24 percent okay what am
i supposed to actually i'm skipping this one i don't get it i don't get the caveman drawings
i'm just taking my i'm taking pills and going i don't get it i have to beat it shit all right
give me some help just give me just help me just give me some help which is tell me where to start
first go to sandbox mode what are you kidding me begin load backup quit where's sandbox mode
nail a board to your forehead cycle through the entire projector this is a million slots
free play all right what do you want to make what do you guys want to make build a sailboat a house
all right i'll build a um a rocking chair chair i'll try a chair i don't i don't i'm gonna just
give me one of everything like how do i get more than one okay i'll make a chair why are they all
the same size okay all right that should be enough to make a chair i need a few of these all right
let's go i'm ready what does a chair look like chair there's a seat we're gonna have to probably
double it up or triple it up so let's go like this there's a seat obviously oh look i have a reference
right here okay there's a seat i'm gonna i'm gonna like double or triple this up by the way
i don't need to measure because if you see what i'm doing here just eyeballing it i'm gonna double
it up okay so you triple it up you think it'd be a big seat i'll make sure the seat be i don't think
it should be that thick easy stop do i how i need some bigger nails now that's way too thick all
right so this is gonna be the back of the chair like this i need a glue or something options table
of contents okay no no i need materials that scared the shit out of me that was like a jump
okay give me this give me these so first thing is first this is the seat so the seat's gonna be
two double patties try to get it flush if i can it's two double patties on top of each other
like that doesn't have to be perfect close enough i can and i can just i can shave off the edges too
i can shave off the shit that it doesn't make sense once it's nailed i can shave it oh shit
it's all right no no no it's okay it's okay that i need a leg um all right this can be a leg
leg should probably be pretty not huge but all enough i need four of these they have to be
relatively the same size i'm gonna say like here because then that'll be is that that's okay that's
that's kind of weirdly huge okay hold on i need to keep this still just make it the same length
it's kind of huge just give me okay come here i'll do two at a time do you guys know they make wood
i just found this out literally like three days ago so they like squish it together they like spin
it and have this long they take a tree trunk and they essentially shave it and they shave shave
shave shave shave shave shave and then they like wet it and like press it together it's it's weird
how they do it plywood yeah they spin the trunk and shave thinly these like puff pastry pieces
of the wood and then they like wet it and like squish it together it's weird how they do plywood
yeah no way dude yeah no seriously it's weird you're not using plywood yeah but i'm just saying it
i didn't know that but we can't learn things here together ban everybody oh wait that's perfect
that's actually not a bad thing one two three okay let's get this at least hammered in here
hold on i just like pressed a button on my keyboard i have no idea what i just did
um i have to get it in there first shit i feel like this is a chevy chase movie i i feel like
i'm not even that's so dangerous that's so dangerous that's so awful so he's gonna get hurt
okay whatever it just has to work so that's that do this now at least i have one leg
don't make a mistake this time okay let me put this over here get it started but don't go all
the way okay no more yes okay pretty much halfway there how do you um never mind i need one i need
another person to hold this you know what i mean somebody else has to hold on to this oh no what
do i do how do i do this vice stop relax bingo check that out oh god where am i going all right
all right not bad not bad okay shit it's okay it's okay it doesn't look awful i'm almost i've pretty
much got it where i want it but not really though just everybody relax what was the piece of this
is it right here i need a long piece for the back this is too long i gotta cut this i gotta
market with a pencil whiz pencil okay i think my pants are falling off this is like you know
those services that are at like home depot it's like oh we can get a professional in there and
help you i don't i feel like i'm how do you return me you know what i mean like if i was doing this do
you return me is like hey man this is like not working out like i'm i'm gonna return you how
does that work that's the power of doing at the home depot what if they do something like this
you just go like hey uh home depot um there was a little bit of a problem with uh the person that
we had final leg going in boom easy they pull a nail out how do you pull a nail out i'm gonna
leave it i'm not gonna touch it i'm not gonna touch it all right so i need a back for the chair
which i'm gonna say one of it could be like this right is there a thicker one than this that's
let me not think of a wider that's not even that bad i'd maybe just take a little bit off the top
here you make it a trojan horse i need to okay i'm gonna cut a little bit off the top it's a
little too long i think i think it is too long excuse me that kind of okay that works so i need
i need to hammer it from this side so the nail has to go in here be driven there was a hammer
hammer was a hammer what happened to the hammer stop using the power tools while you're so high
i don't what happened to the hammer what oh it's over there no it's not what it's in your tool
belt what is it doing how did it get in there am i even in frame probably not i probably now you
can probably see me okay where are you there you are hi all right i'm back i'm ready i need like
one here and then one here on the other side make arm rest too i'll try jesus workplace hazard
they've worked okay and now i need to have that does not okay you guys know you guys have to see
the like the when somebody is on drugs comparison it's like we gave woodworker steve four hits of
lsd and like that's his normal work and like this is what he made on lsd okay well it's i need to
arm rest how are you supposed to sit in this chair this is allison wonderland shit yeah the mad hatter
sits in that one okay it's modern art it's a car seat it really it really does look like a car
seat play the home depot theme it's a tim burton chair yeah yeah i don't don't you just hear like
panning around okay i need to add arm rests so if arm rest would come up from they'd come out like
here up and then out so i need a small piece that goes like this how am i going to nail it in here
a tiny piece that comes out and then out this way ain't it i will it's so bad okay i need a little
piece yeah just like one of these that sticks out a little and then one that goes kind of up and
then that way i just need a few a couple of little pieces not very much there'll be a head rest too
okay let's attach these make a head rest okay yeah like that so then it was like you'd come up
and then this way all right so i can do that give me some nail hammer where is it i keep losing the
hammer right there okay okay now i gotta have a piece that goes this way that's so low you're
gonna be like going like this to like put your arms on the on the arm rests you're gonna be so
slumped down to even touch them they're right next to your ass okay well it's all right these
are such small pieces why do i think this is a good idea they're so small oh that's that's
actually gonna hurt somebody they have to come they have to be higher all right i'll just i'll
fix it i got it i got it just trust me everybody just trust the process trust me i'll handle it
where am i okay give me the whoa give me these where am i where are you okay i think i can do
this how do i get this to attach to this i have to go in like sideways is there no glue can't you do
um wood glue jermis stop go outward wait i can like bang these in oh no no wait wait wait wait
these nails are too long but that fits all right it still works i got it i got it i got it same
exact thing okay and then they need to come out like that that actually should be fine yeah that's
gonna be fine these are long enough what oh that's my i don't know what it is about this
since goddamn headset man okay this is way too long i gotta shave at least what fell off i have
to shave this a little bit and then i'll paint it yeah at least that much has to come off like
right there okay let's get here mark that it's good then now all i have to do is the head rest
and then paint it and that should be good look it's all about post-production those of you that
think a movie is made when the actors are talking on set nope it's the editor actually
the whole movie is made in editing this is what a movie looks like before it goes to the editing
bay it's just an electric chair should i just make like a thing that comes out and just put
it on somebody's head this is this is an electric chair head rest doesn't it needs to be really
small like right here right there don't need to be that cool with it just yep there we go oops
nails coming out the back oh i can't stand up on its own i need another piece down here i need like
bird feet down here hold on like that okay i'm not telling you to do this i can just do it like that
yep i haven't looked at what are people saying i haven't even been paying attention what anyone's
been saying you can make a torture chair i'm gonna say right kind of at the end here all right i need
one in the back same piece like that simple you know what fuck it man well i should just do the
whole board why you probably going why are you doing it at an angle so it can spread out yep
right here it's so close it's so close to standing i need one here and this i gotta have one come
down a little higher this game is fun this is actually really cool this is one of the
cooler vr games i think i've ever played it's just cool it's just really neat this is very neat i
like it no that's gonna come out i need one more here but it's gonna be hold on are you saying i
can paint this fuck you what is happening all right it's not long enough oh god damn it wait
it's okay no it's not it needs to be longer oh i got an idea i have an idea this is gonna be
a pain in the ass but no no no no get out of the way please don't break it stop we're gonna have
to add three at a time i think should do it what's happening what's going on okay this is a disaster
i'm done i'm done with it i'm i'm fucking done this is an absolute disaster yes yes i don't
can i paint it slender man's chair hammer some nails through the seat
you mean like going that way oh my god okay fine let's see one like one like
marv nail from home alone but that's twisted that's twisted man this is i don't this kind
of feels like this i feel like i got this out of like a serial killer sketchbook or something this
is weird give him a face he's so heavy on the right oh my god that's gonna break something
i think i'm good i'm good i'm good i just like smashed into something over here paint it i would
still sit on it i don't i don't think i would what do i get for a rating you know today i got a much
bigger appreciation for people that are good with their hands uh hold on let me see if i can fix
this for a sec if i take these off and i take these off it should be okay i don't care i'm done
this is just the chainsaw sound you hear when you're tied up in this thing
how come i don't get a score how come i don't get a score all right let's see if i could beat the
hell out of this thing with a hammer nope it's pretty it's solid it's solid this is not a bad
piece of furniture all right all right i'll see that's it that was fun how's my face look
do i have indents all over my face does that even count as furniture probably not all right
i will see you guys on the 27th want a hair check sure we're gonna play some more of the
major requested games but i'll play among us vr i'll do it fine not terrible
vr face you look like a soccer mom all right i'll see you guys on the 27th we'll do
glare witch vr cooking simulator vr and then i'll do at least one game of among us
in vr i'll finally do it i'll do the meme and i'll see you later thanks for sticking around
uh what time is it right now seven it's not too too late but we'll see you again soon after the
27th that's gonna be the last stream until the first take care of yourselves oh hold on wait
guys guys guys guys among us vr doesn't even have an announced date yet what are you talking about
it's not out huh okay well i'm still gonna play cooking simulator and i'm still gonna play um
glare witch it's not even out yet all right i'll see you guys later thanks for watching as always
appreciate it we'll see you again in a few days get pranked there's a vr chat version of among us
yeah but that's not the same thing i'll never i forgot i was twerking earlier that's right i
did do a twerk well i did a fake twerk i did like a comedy twerk now the games are fun today
i actually really really liked the um the coin game kind of one that pier arcade that was actually
really fun i'm surprised i was in there for more than two or three hours the second game was really
good too it just took a while to get going beginning of that player which game is slow
and kind of trash huh really do skyrim vr i'll look into it how long you're gonna stream on the
27th not probably not that long less than five hours all these vr streams are gonna be all less
than three to five hours get a bunch of mods maybe i will i'll get a i'll get a good lineup
on the 27th yeah i'm going right into the bath uh right now why are you so into vr right now
um it's not that i'm into vr right now it's just setting vr up in a room scale takes a lot of it's
it's hard to kind of go back and play another game because i have it set up completely like my chair
is not here my computer is pulled out um like i don't i don't have a desk right now so anytime
i play vr i always do it and just do a bunch of it and then put it away for six months so that's
kind of how it works do i expect you to die i expect you to die too came out i played the first
one on stream years ago all right good night guys i'll see you on the 27th take care of yourselves
thanks for sticking around as always see you guys soon good night goodbye take care