Hello everybody. My name is Hill Joe Gullum. I'm Jeremy's, um, his, his grandfather.
And today we're gonna play Insane Aquarium, Zootilux mode. It's the best game you can ever buy.
And it's loading it right now. I don't really play video games, they hurt my brain.
And I wish this noise, we gotta click here to play, okay.
Gee, I play casual games, because I'm an idiot. I'm just...
Okay, what am I doing here? Um, I wanna do challenge mode, because I, I'm,
know I want a new game. New fucking game. Okay, let's try tank number three,
because I still can't beat it. I like to use the crab, and I like to use the other crab,
and I like to use the floating crab, well, you know, to get the money in the beginning, you know.
Okay, so it starts, you click to feed these little fish-faced fucks, and then, you know,
they drop the dog shit, and you click it, and you get money, and you click again, and you get more
money, and then my game is lagging really badly right now. Click that money right there.
The whole point of this, by the way, folks, is you wanna try and get as much money,
so you can pay for your daughter's wedding. At least that's, that's what I pretended is.
Okay, so we got four fishies here, and they're all dumping out dog shit. And I got my little
friend Steve over here, I think that's his name. So the whole point is you wanna give these guys
the delicious worm cakes, and hold on a minute, I have to diarrhea. Okay, okay, I'm back from
diarrhea-ing, and uh, I got a big fishy here now, and this is uh, uh oh. Oh fuck, somebody
fucking died, and I got an alien, oh this is bad. You're gonna shoot these fucking aliens! Oh my god.
Oh Jesus Christ. Don't worry everybody, I got a fucking diamond. So that means we can buy
extra food. $315? Are you fucking kidding me? $318 for food? Oh, you gotta be shitting me.
Whatever, I'll just let it keep going. So I'm, I'm doing pretty well here, I got a big fish here.
Like I told you, like I told you before, I'm making lots of cash. I might wanna upgrade
my food quality. Oh shit, gotta pick that up. And the silver ones too, remember,
silver's worth something too here, you know. I don't know what this fucking face is for,
I don't know who the guppy is, guppy cruncher. But uh, okay, time to figure out, I need another fish.
What the fuck? Hold, hold on just a second! You, what is this? This game is a, is a bunch of
bullshit! Oh my, you gotta be, whatever. You know, I'm returning this game.
I'm gonna return this game today. And oh, hello there Susie. What's your name? Never seen you.
What was I just saying about, oh yeah, um, I think I was saying I was gonna play challenge mode and
I needed to beat tank three because I didn't beat tank three yet. Okay, okay, I like to pick crab
and other crab and this crab. Okay, uh, the point of this game is you want to feed these fishes
and collect the dog shit. And the whole point is you want to try and feed them. And uh, and like
you gotta be careful because aliens come up and uh, what is it? I'm playing a fucking video game!
I don't care! You can go to hell!
Oh, okay, I'll be up for dinner in a minute, okay. So like, okay, like I was saying,
oops, all of your fish have died.