We good? Alright, it's time for us to do the greatest video game of all time. Tear List.
This is gonna- oh my god, this is gonna take a while. And I'm too red! This is gonna take all
fucking- I- I just was looking for some stuff to do real quick. That better? That better. Alright,
let's uh, let's start with- okay, this is- so this is the best game that I've ever played, right?
He's played like five games on this list. More than that, at least eight. Or ten.
But what actually have I played? Alright, let me get the ones that I'm certain of. Alright, Team
Fortress 2 is- is- is a masterpiece. It goes up here. What else is on here that's an absolute
masterpiece? That I know for a fact is like up at absolute masterpiece level. It's Resident Evil 4?
Resident Evil 4 is up here pretty close. Not- I wouldn't say the whole way. I'm not done with this
yet. We're gonna- we're gonna go to great. Um, Battlefield 1. I don't- I don't think that's-
I don't know if that should be on here. Battlefield 1? On the greatest video games have ever made list.
Okay, but if it's the gr- okay, if every single game on here could be the greatest game ever made,
they're not necessarily horrible games, are they? I'm gonna put it- I'm gonna keep it here. It's
gonna go down. Okay, um, XCOM 2. I've had never played it. Oh shit, Smite's on here. Smite on here.
Alright, but here I'm gonna be fair. It's a Smite. I think- I think Smite's more fun than Battlefield
1. I am- I am certain of that. Which one is this? Is it Smash Brothers Brawl or Smash-
Smash Brothers in general? I think that's Brawl. Hold on, I just gotta get this situated.
I don't- War- I don't wanna say Warframe is horrible, but I don't think it's the best game
ever made. I don't want it to be horrible, though. Okay, alright, let me ask you this.
If I have less than, like, two to three hours in the game, should it be under have not tried the
game? Because if I have less than five hours in the game, they're going down here. I don't even
think it's hor- okay, I'm just gonna- I'm just gonna leave it here. No. I think it's better than
Battlefield 1. I think everything's better than Battlefield 1 for me. I don't think there's
anything on this list that's worse than Battlefield 1 for me. We'll find out. This is very early.
This is League of Legends. I- I don't- I don't play it. That's gonna be at the bottom. God of
War 2. I didn't- I never played it. Fallout New Vegas. It's- I know people are gonna- This is-
Right now, I am just making myself out to be the ultimate hated person. This is more- This is way
different than doing cereal box tier lists. If Fallout New Vegas is not on Masterpiece, I think
a lot of you are gonna be very adamant that I'm- You're gonna want to, like, be mad at me.
I don't- I'm scared to put that idea- This is- Okay, this- Should I do an on-stream one and an
off-stream one and then tweet out the comparison? Oh yeah, Fallout New Vegas is, uh, it's definitely
an A-plus tier on-stream, Andy. And then off-stream is, like, down here. No, I'm gonna- I'm gonna do
this real. This is for real. This is what I actually really believe. I'm not gonna have anybody
fucking tell me what I- I'm not gonna- I'm not gonna have you influence me at all. I think
Smite is more fun than Fallout New Vegas. I- It is. I'm sorry. Everyone's gonna be mad at that,
but, like, I've had more fun playing- I- I don't know. I just think it is. I like that video game.
But this- But is it though? What- Did I- Maybe. On-stream, off-stream. It's close- Hold on. I
gotta get more up here. Until Dawn should not be on this list. Why? Half-Life 2 is also not gonna
be as high as people want it to be. I don't consider Half-Life 2 to be, like, up at Masterpiece.
It's- It's great. It also made me very sick. I don't know why. The boat level in Half-Life 2,
when you're in the boat, I had to stop playing every- Oh, this is Half-Life 1. Okay. Well,
hold on. Hold on. That still belongs up here. Half-Life 1, you idiot. All right. Half-Life-
Is Half-Life 1 more fun than Smite? Careful. Careful. Uh, Castlevania? I don't- I- I don't-
I didn't play the one for PlayStation. I'm sorry. Bioshock 1. Bioshock 1 was very good.
It's not better- It might be better than Half-Life. Oh my god. People are gonna hate me.
But it's kind of not fair though, because it's so- It's like years later.
You're gonna stop. Based. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. All right. Well, I'm gonna hold
on. I can- Once I get it to where I want it, then I'll be all right. This is Crash Team Racing?
I don't know what that is, but I didn't play it. Uncharted all- I've never played an Uncharted
game. I don't even have one second in them. I can't even put them on here.
Mourninghawk's Pro Skater 2. That's not a masterpiece, but it's up here.
Wait. Hold on. Am I allowed to put this up here? Didn't I talk a ton of shit about this game when
I was playing? Wasn't I raging? Like, constantly being whiny and annoying when I played this with
Dreamcast? I did, right? Okay. Then I can't put it up here. I was- I just kept complaining. Over
and over again. Over and over and over again. It's down here. Uh, Call of Duty Mad World 5-3.
That is- is not very- it's not good. It's not a good game. It was a fu- it was fun, but it wasn't
good. Look, every Call of Duty game can be fun, but it doesn't mean they're good. Like, it's fun- I
could just sit there and just, like, be on the phone with somebody. Just like, yeah, yeah, man,
yeah. Just playing a little bit of Kill Confirmed. Yeah, what are you up to? Yeah. No, I'll be over
in like fucking 20 minutes. Like, you just don't even fucking care. You just like the sound.
Actually, and it's something I really actually truly believe, I believe that the Call of Duty
hit sound is the only reason why people play the game. I truly believe that. That sound effect is
what brings everybody in. Something about it. It's- it's like this- it's this perfect, like,
scratching that itch on your back that's right in the middle that sits between your shoulder blades
and the middle of your back that you just can't barely get. But the second you get your middle
finger up there and you- without that hit sound, that game is a three. With that hit sound, it's
about a seven- it's a 6.5. Dark Souls- is Dark Souls one? Is Dark Souls one better than Smite?
Yes. Of course it is. That would be outrageous if I thought otherwise. I'm not done with it yet.
It's- I don't- hold on. Let me- it's not- don't say Masterpiece yet. I'm only putting things in
Masterpiece that I truly can say belong there. Like, right off the bat without even thinking.
Some of these will move up. Just wait. I have not played A Hat in Time. Red Dem Redemption 2 was
very good. Was it more fun than Smite? Yes. Mass Effect 2? I didn't- is it- okay. I don't like
those games. Is that- can I say that? Is it okay to say? I like- I like- don't like Mass Effect.
That's okay, right? I don't hate Mass Effect. I don't think it's a shitty game. I just don't like
it. That's okay. I can say that, right? That's okay. All right. Yeah. It's definitely better
than Until Dawn. But I didn't- I didn't even play it, really. I didn't- why are you asking us?
Because sometimes, if I say I don't- you know, if I said I- that Mass Effect 2- remember?
If I say Mass Effect 3- if I say Mass Effect 2 sucks, then I'll get tweets about it. People
will be like, fuck you, you're an idiot. You don't know anything about video games. I gotta be careful.
He's being hacked. I haven't played it, really. I don't- I'm not into the series.
Sonic Mania. It's probably- is it- I kind of feel the same way about Sonic the Hedgehog that I do
about Modern Warfare 3. The sound effects. Like, I only play Sonic to, like, hold down and go
I don't- I don't really care. And for the-
And then the-
I have trouble playing Sonic the Hedgehog. I feel like I- I have, like, ADHD and it's hard for me
to concentrate on a lot of things. So I'll be running very fast and it's just like- and I'll
hit like a fucking spike. I can't even pay attention to it. It's better than Smite. Of course it is.
If you guys would like to see the definition of recency bias, this is the only video game I've
played off stream in the last six months. The only one. But it's fun! It's better- it's better
than Warframe. It is. All right, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. What else we got? GTA V.
Ah, it's close. I have to come back to this. I think GTA V is, like, one of the better games
to come out in the last, at least, like, 10 to 15 years. The GTA V story is, like, all right,
it's all right. It was cool. But just- hold on, now that I can give my reason why. The- the world
of GTA V is so- it's just peop- it's just people are alive. Just like the pedestrians and the
buildings and the mountains and so much time went into that city and that world. People have tried
to do that since. Remember, GTA V came out in fucking 2013. 2013. Name me a game that's come
out recently that really kind of badly wanted to have that same vibe and it was a disaster.
It better not be on this list. What is this doing on here? This definitely was made before
the game came up. This list was created probably, like, a couple weeks before that game came up.
The Avengers. It's- it's not on here. Okay, it's- I don't think it's on here. Somebody said it's on
there, but you don't even know which one I'm talking about, but maybe you do. Is it on here?
It's not on here. It's- look at these little icons. I can't even see. Is it on here? It probably is.
This was probably made before it even came out. Bottom left. This is the games that I pre-ordered,
thinking they were gonna be the best game ever made. Uh, the list. This is unfair because I'm-
I'm just, like, bandwagon jumping Andy, right? And I know you're fucking sick of me saying that,
but it's- look, that's how- that's how we communicate in this generation. We say Andy.
I haven't played Cyberpunk. I just- it's bad because to- everybody told me it was bad.
Cyberpunk's bad because everybody told me it was bad. And I saw a clip of a car, like,
flipping upside down and, like, deleting. I can't rate it. I can't. I didn't play it.
It sucks. It's actually really fun. Well, there's two people right next to each other. They got-
it sucks, but it's fun. All right, so it's like Modern Warfare 3. Are there- wait,
are there sound effects in this game that- like, is it Modern Warfare 3? Like, when I really load
the gun, does it go like- so I could just be like, yes. No? Okay, then it stays down here.
I thought this said Bugleberry. What is that? Jungle Party? Is that a good game? Is this,
like, a game I've never played? Played Jungle Party. It belongs there. It does? I don't- I have
no idea what it is. It's a masterpiece. It's a masterpiece. It's a masterpiece.
This is a paid ad to let it be on here. It does look like an old cereal box CD that was taped
to the back of the box. I don't- I have no idea what it is. All right. Okay. I only played the
first four hours or five hours of God of War, the new one, but my goodness was it
beautiful. It was fantastic. And I've been told that the first three or four hours of God of War
are ten out of ten, but the rest of God of War is like eight and a half out of ten. That's what I
have been told. I had the first, like, six hours is like a full ten out of ten, and then the rest
is like an 8.6. Is that fair? You know, I don't play video games. All the games on this list,
I think I've played, like, for three to four hours. Dota 2, I've played for, like, three hours.
Yakuza, I've played for, like, four hours. Street Fighter, I've played probably a total of, like,
two to three hours. Halo Reach, I played an hour and ten minutes with Joel. Batman, Arkham City,
I played for, like, two hours because it was on sale for, like, the eighth time. Watch Dogs,
I played for about three hours on stream. Star Wars, Lego Star Wars, played for about four hours.
Ooh, Shadow of the Colossus is on here. Now that's a great, yeah, that's amazing. Borderlands 2,
is this the good one? German, none of them are the good one. Uh, what the fuck, dude?
Borderlands series, to me, is Overwatch Ultimates with the entirety of the time that you're playing
the game. That's how I felt. I just kind of felt like I was constantly in an ult in Overwatch.
Holy shit, he's lost it. I didn't say it wasn't fun. I just remember, like, pressing Q every,
like, minute, and it was just like, and then I guess we won. Everybody in, like, Borderlands,
especially the later ones, they have, like, super moves that you can use every minute.
Get the super moves out of games. Can I say that? Get, take ultimate abilities out of fucking video
games. It makes them annoying. It makes them stupid. I don't like them. I don't like having
ultimate abilities that you just press a button and just, and everything dies and you do it once
every minute or two. No, let me have to fuck, I want to play. I don't want to just press fucking
Q and have colors light up the screen. That's why Smite deserves to be a little bit higher than it
is. It's a bad take. I don't think it is, though, because it makes it, look, I know I'm not, like,
that good at video games, but when you have ultimates in games that just, just level everything in
front of you, when you play with more than one or two people, you just, you might as well just be
hanging out talking in a Discord call. You're not even playing. When, like, three of you have a
fucking Q button to press every two minutes, you're just hanging out and talking in a call
because it's like, all right, let's go in. You guys ready to go in? Just, like,
wipe everything out. Oh, we all pressed Q. All right, like, pick up the items, I guess.
There's another one. There's another fight. This one's a boss. Everyone pressed Q.
That's unironically correct. Thank you. Going off script now. Just wait till they add an ultimate
in the next Mario game and then all everybody can come back here and be like, man, you know,
you were kind of right about that. Just wait till you press, wait till you press, like,
fucking right bumper in, like, Mario Odyssey 2. And he goes like, and fucking spins and stars
go everywhere and, like, and everything gets fucking dies around him. Wait till it happens
and then you tell me I was wrong. You're a psycho. So, I mean, no, I'm not. I didn't play Uncharted
3. I didn't play fucking Uncharted 2. I didn't play fucking Uncharted 1. Ooh, this one's good.
That's very good. Whoa, I even said it. I have to put it up here. It doesn't, is there a doesn't
deserve to be on? I guess this is doesn't deserve to be on the list. All right. I'm changing.
Horrible is not horrible. Horrible is doesn't deserve to be on the list. That doesn't mean it's
a bad game. But when you're talking about the greatest video games of all time, I just don't
think they belong on the list. You got to put, like, you got to put Doom on here somewhere.
I don't even know what to put it, though. I think I played it for, like, wait, this is the remake.
I played the remake on stream. Somebody get the exact time. Somebody get the exact time of how
long I played Doom. Is it more than four and a half hours? Four hours. It was four hours and 27
minutes. No, I'm way more suited to watch movies. Coming to this realization, if Doom was a movie,
I could give you, I could give you a good review. After four hours, not even TV shows either.
TV shows last whole seasons and hours and, like, tens of hours. I'm a movie guy and I'm coming to
the realization here. Fake Doom fan. It was good. Hold on, let me just mute so I can get rid of this.
Whatever is wrong with me. Oh, Far Cry, Far Cry, Far Cry 3, dude. I didn't. Wait, is this Far Cry 3?
I played this on stream for four hours. I played this one off stream for one hour and uninstalled
it. Mortal Kombat 11 played it for like two hours, three hours. I didn't play Wind Waker. I know,
I didn't play Breath of the Wild. Finding of Isaac goes up high. No, I don't know if it's,
it's definitely an amazing, definitely. Final Fantasy, I don't even know which one it is. I
didn't play it. Watch Dogs 2. Both are bad. I'm sorry, they just are. That's how I, that's what I
feel. Mario Odyssey. I played for like three and a half hours. I got to the part where you walk in
the, I got to the part where, like, you walk in the pipe thing and it's like a do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
It's like all nostalgia and then I uninstalled the game. Don't ever listen to a thing I say about
video games. I have no experience. I am the best indicator for if you've got a good, if you got a
big first act, a really good first act, you'll know because I'll play the game. Everything that's
up here, notice how they all have really, really fantastic first acts, with the exception of Isaac.
Isaac and TF2 are sm- You okay? Oh my god, I'm so sorry. Are you alright? That was probably really
bad. I'm really sorry. Oh, there's like 16,000 people here. I'm really fucking sorry. I'm really
sorry. But these, you can do Binding of, you can play, you can beat Binding of Isaac technically
in 30 minutes, 20 minutes. TF2, you just jump in a server and just walk around with a flog and just
burn people, light them on fire and crit them and get them to yell fucking swears at you in chat.
It's, you, it's, you don't have to do anything. You know, it literally takes five minutes.
All these have great first acts. I'm, this is a complete eye-opener. I don't, I didn't play any
Assassin's Creed. No, I don't play FIFA. I don't play Fortnite. Oh boy, what a first act this had.
The cinematic cutscene, getting into Dun Moro as the, as a dwarf, getting the, the voice lines
and collecting the stuff and getting going and going to meet, uh, Anduin Wynn at Stormwind.
What a first act. And, uh, don't give me shit for this. World of Warcraft, not the one that they,
like, resurrected and redid it again. No, the original one back in like 2004, 2005.
That was, it was really cool. It was insane. It was unbelievable. No one had ever done that shit
before. I don't know, EverQuest, EverQuest, EverQuest. What about EverQuest? Did you play
EverQuest? I did. And I, I, this was, I liked World of Warcraft better than EverQuest. Fuck you. Why?
This is going to be hard a little bit later. I knew this was going to take a long time. Overcooked
2 should just not be on the list. It just shouldn't. It's a cool, it's a, it's a cool game. It's, it's
fun. But it's not better than, like, Resident Evil 4. It's not horrible. It just shouldn't be
on the list. Pac-Man, all right. Pac-Man might not be better than Resident Evil 4,
but it might be more important than Resident Evil 4. That doesn't matter? What do you mean
that doesn't matter? How can you compare, like, to the first, like, the first act of God of War?
But you have whole generations of technology. Of course that matters. Yes, it does. Only Dark
Souls is only at very good. That's not true. I have to get this in the, I have to get it,
all of these are within one or two tiers of correctness. I need to go and fix it,
but I need to get them up here first. Pac-Man's more important than God of War. It just is. I
could, I could look at that later. Metal Gear Rising. It was all right. It was okay. It was
fun. Metal Gear Solid 3. Is that Snake Eater? This is the best one. This is the best Metal
Gear Solid. I will die on that hill. I think this is the best Metal Gear Solid. I think it is.
Metal Gear Solid 2 was fun, but they had this, like, crazy, like, AI-generated script that you
just, they pumped it into your brain over the course of, like, 12 hours. I like Metal Gear Solid
3 the best. The first one was really good, too. That's a great series, though. Fantastic series.
Unbelievable series, but I think the third one's probably the best one. I didn't play The Last of
Us. That's a lie. I did play The Last of Us. Let me make sure I get this correct. Let me make sure
I get this correct. I might have some things missing and misremembering here. It was either
MLC Stealth or Italics. The PlayStation had a feature where you could screen share to somebody
and they could take control of the controller and play, and they did that for me with The Last of
Us for, like, 20 minutes. That's my entire time of play. It might be missing some details there,
but it was one of them. Maybe 30 minutes? Oh my. Thank God it's on the list I got. I was starting
to get a little concerned. And they've got the remake coming out. Please don't fuck that up.
Please don't fuck that up. Please. Blizzard, give us one thing. Diablo 4. Diablo 4 can suck
total ass. I don't care. Just, don't fuck with that one. Don't fuck it up. I would rather play
this than Diablo 4. Oh my God, didn't even see this. All right. What's the absolute masterpiece?
Where does it go? For a second I was like, I thought this was the Magic School Bus,
and I was like, this is a TV show. Why is it even on here? Original Counter-Strike. All right,
my enjoyment from this game was not very good because I was terrible at it and it just made
me angry. I hated Counter-Strike because I was terrible. Does the game pissed me off factor
work here? I got so sick and tired of just turning a corner and watching a guy just go like this.
And I was gone. Like, crouch dad. I didn't even know what happened. And then it's like, okay,
I guess I'm going to wait. And I don't like the waiting either. I don't like waiting around.
So somebody would just, crouch dad. And then I would just be waiting for the, for what?
No, I don't want to do it. No, I just, I don't, I didn't like it. I, I played so much Counter-Strike
and had just negative kills to deaths every game. It's definitely better than Smite. If you were
to take a screenshot right here and zoom in and put it, like, I would be an enemy of PC video
gaming. It's not accurate. I don't know if this is it. I have, I can clean it up to do it. All
right. Phantom Pain was very good. Did I pretend to like it more than I did to make sure I could
have a fifth game in my top games of 2015? That's the real question. That's the tough one.
Cause I did really like it. And by the way, I don't, I know I talked about it, but I don't
even remember giving the list. I woke up in my bed the next day. Like I remember starting that video.
It's not, no, it's, it was decent. It was, it was not better than three.
Tetris is fucking horrible. The game sucks. Only, and only, oh, listen, only smart people
put this high. Us dumb fucking idiots hate this game and think it's stupid. Yeah. You can tell
if like how smart somebody is, how high they put Tetris. Oh, Tetris man. Oh, amazing. I love Tetris.
Super. I love like the equations and no, no, no, no, no. I get this. I get, I fucking,
us idiots hate this game. I don't like Tetris. I just, it's the forward thinking and what piece
do you have next? And like, oh, get the, do the math problem. Like, oh, which can that fit there?
It's like, it's a big, no, too much, too much visual. Get it off. And there's no blood in this
game. So like, eh, eh. I fucking hate Tetris. Overwatch is not better than Smite.
Overwatch, is Overwatch, is Overwatch better than Smite?
Metal Gear Rising should not be this high. Hold on, I'll go back to it.
Was this Omega LoL? I don't play Soul Calibur. I have not played any of the Assassin's Creed
games besides the first one for guess how much time? I'll give you a hint. It's not five hours.
Call of Duty Modern Warfare? The original one. I'm one of those posers that started
playing Modern Warfare and Call of Duty at Modern Warfare 3. The original Doom. The original Doom.
Why am I saying it like that? Doom. The original Doom. This is unfair because all these old classic
video games are just automatically just placed up on this first or second row. That's kind of
unfair. Tetris. Tetris is stupid. Excuse me. Blood. Oh, what about, excuse me. Pac-Man dies
and he goes inside out and fucking disintegrates screaming. And you eat fucking people in this
game. You eat them. You crush their bones and stuff with your mouth. Arkham, I only played for like
three hours on a Steam sale. Dark Souls 3. Here comes, and here comes the never-ending debate.
Every one of the, okay, this is the worst part about doing a game list like this.
Every single Dark Souls game not only has to be right next to each other, but in the correct order.
Or I'm in trouble. You can't have this. No, no, no, wait, wait, wait. Dark Souls 1, Dark Souls 3,
Dark Souls, Sekiro, Dark Souls 3, Dark Souls 1, with the brackets. They have to be right,
it has to be right. No, no, no, no, you're doing it wrong. I actually, I like Dark Souls 3 a lot.
I don't know if it's first act. First act is pretty good. What was a better first act?
Dark Souls 3, Dark Souls 1, Dark Souls 2. Dark Souls 2 is the worst one. I think we can agree on
that one. All the Mario karts have been zero out of tens since Double Dash. Making a correct
statement here. After Double Dash, they all became zeros. What is this? Life is straight,
all right, hold on a minute here. This, I like, this was, I liked this. Better than Tetris?
Is Life is Strange better than Overwatch? Life is Strange is better than, I know you, but you
can't say, oh, what, Life is Strange is better than Tetris? I cringe. I don't like Tetris.
I don't like Tetris. I think the game sucks. I didn't like Tetris when I was 12. I was like
nine years old playing it, eight years old on the Nintendo or something, on my Game Boy.
And I remember just being like, this game's fucking stu-, I didn't swear. But I was like,
I hate this. I don't like this game. Where's Bonk? By the way, if Bonk was on here,
he'd be up in fucking Masterpiece. Bonk is the best Game Boy game. And who talks about that?
Nobody but me. Final Fantasy VII. The only experience I have with Final Fantasy VII was
watching Burger Boy scream at his TV, jumping up and down, because he couldn't beat the last boss
over and over again. And this is like, like 19 years ago. And I think he got so mad. I remember
like, he got to the point where he was so mad moving around that he could unplug the controller.
And that made him even more mad. And he was jumping up and down, like jumping up and down,
controllers out of the port. So I'm, and that was my reasoning for never playing this.
I've never played Final Fantasy VII. I've just seen the final boss and an angry friend. So I was
like, well, fuck this game. Why would I play this? It's my only experience. But a great soundtrack.
And I've, I've seen the movies and they're good. The movies were pretty cool. I never, yeah,
I know. I'm the person that didn't, I didn't, I watched the movies. No, they're not good.
They literally aren't. The movies aren't good. Advent Children. Yeah, that's the one I saw. That
was bad. Advent Children, Omega, lol. He doesn't know. Well, I didn't understand anything that was
going on, but I like, I like Katsith and I like, I think it's cool. But wait, but Katsith, those are
terrible. The only reason why I wanted to play, I must have Metal Gear Solid VII, which was wrong,
is because Katsith has dice and don't you like gamble to play? Don't you, he like throws dice
into like it could be anything, right? That's cool. That's cool. I like that character. What
am I talking about? We're talking about Final Fantasy VII. What is he saying? What? Let him
enjoy something. What? Katsith was on screen for five seconds total in Advent Children. Yeah. And
that's the part where I stood up in the fucking theater and I screamed and clapping. And me and
one other person that thought Katsith was cool. And I pointed at them and I was like, you get it?
You and I get it. Ow, my elbow. And then he was like, holy shit, are you okay? And he ran over and
he like held my elbow and he like wrapped it up. And I was like, and then that's how I met
Exoskeleton Bug Millennium Boy. Anyways, Inside was good. No, no, get this off of really bad.
I don't like the word bad for these. I have no, I don't play video games. Pokemon Emerald version.
I've never, I don't play it. Oh my God. The only experience I have in Super Metroid
was renting it from Blockbuster and somebody else's save file being there, right? And then opening it
and just hearing the
thing. And running around and shooting stuff. And I had no idea where the fuck I was going
because the map is all over the place. And you had to have known what you did before to do what
you're doing in the future. And I didn't want to start at the beginning. I did that for a lot of
games, by the way. How many of you guys rented games like RPGs, especially turn-based RPGs?
I did this all the time with Earthbound. I think I was too stupid to like really want to play
from the beginning. So I would just hope that there would be a save file that was more than
halfway through the game. And I'd be like, oh, nice. They're like halfway through the game.
And I would just walk around and fight stuff and just play on somebody else's save that they had
on the Blockbuster one and just enjoy maybe like 30 minutes. And then I would just stop. I just
wanted to enjoy somebody else's time in the game. Like I didn't want to start at the beginning.
You're a fraud exposed. That's weird. Earthbound street. I don't know. It was definitely because
I didn't get it. Especially turn-based RPGs. They were like too slow for me. They would be like,
wait, what do I have to do? I have to get the stick and equip the stick and then like walk
over to here to the town and buy this and then walk over here and fight. No, this is back when
pressing A as fast as I could was my skill, my skill set. So pressing A as fast as I could was
like a half of every Super Nintendo game. And if that wasn't in a Super Nintendo game, then I might
as well head back to sort of return to the Blockbuster. Papers, please was very good.
But again, I would always start Papers, please and get to the point when there was more than
three or four things you had to do. And that's where I would stop because I couldn't do it.
It'd be like, okay, you have to check the ID. I got to check their work order, where they work
and their passport. And this is too much. I don't want to do it anymore. The game is incredible
until you get to like the four things on the screen. It's very good though. It's up here
somewhere. Outlast 1, I actually really liked. But you can't put Outlast in front of Doom,
can you? We'll see. We'll see. I'll fix it later. Hold on. Is it going to get in the right place?
Persona. I've never played Persona. All I know is that I saw someone, I watched somebody play
Persona 3 for like 10 minutes. And it was a part where they were like just shooting themselves in
the head with guns. And I was like, oh, okay. Like that's how you fight. It was like, wow,
that's crazy. Sekiro was better than Dark Souls 2, but was lower on the list for Dark Souls games
for me. And no, it's not Dark Souls. I know. I know. I know. I didn't play Yakuza 4. I've
never played a Fire Emblem game. GTA 4 probably deserves to go in front of GTA 5 because
technologically speaking, when GTA 4 came out, it was insane and never done before. And by the time
GTA 5 came out, open world games having that much going on was pretty normal. So they kind of
started that. They did that really first. So I think it belongs in front of it. Even though
the video game might be a little bit worse than GTA 5, like the engine of the video game. I like
GTA 4. It was more, it was kind of crunchy, you know what I mean? It was like crusty in a way.
I liked it. It's like Breath of the Wild if you like open world. I will one day. Apex Legends
have never played it. Wait, the first Walking Dead Telltale game. I almost just like spoiled
everything. The Walking Dead Telltale game had a few really, really fantastic moments.
There was a few, and they were not short. They were, it led up to a lot of, there was a couple
things in particular. I was like, oh, that was, it was really cool. I don't think it was like,
whoa, amazing. It's the best game ever. It was good. I liked it. It belongs in the good to very
good. Was it better than Doom? Well, I have to fix that. Red? Oh, Devil May Cry. No, I haven't
played it. None of them. I have no time in any Devil May Cry. Yakuza Zero, I've played for like,
oh, I know, but I can't rate this because it's better than Tetris. It's better than Life is
Strange. It's better than Metal Gear Rising. Overwatch is worse. Overwatch is way worse.
No, it's not. It's better. Modern Warfare should not be over here. Modern Warfare should be,
actually be down here. Like, let's be honest. I'm just thinking, if Until Dawn is down here,
does Life is Strange deserve to be up here? I don't think Until Dawn was horrible. I don't,
honestly, I, this is cut off at the top. I don't even know what Far Cry it is, but it doesn't
fucking matter because every single one of them is the same game. I have no idea which one this is,
but all of them go down here. Is it three, four, five? I don't know which one it is.
Okay, Portal 2 and Portal. I'm gonna make a lot of people upset with this. I know,
first of all, there's a method to this. Hold on. Portal 2 was awesome. Portal 1 made me almost
throw up every time I played it. Portal 2 was spread out enough with different stuff in between
that I could get over how much I wanted to throw up. Portal 1 was just puke, puke, puke, puke,
puke. Just throw up puke, puke, puke. It was just puzzle puke, puzzle puke, puzzle puke.
It made me sick. The game Portal actually makes me ill, even in Portal 2. Portal 2 was more going
on. It wasn't just like go in this room and do a puzzle and then lie down on the ground,
which I did many times. I would complete a level in Portal 2 and be green and then I would lie
on the ground in where my computer was. I would lie on the ground and just wait till it passed
and then I would get up and do the next level. I couldn't handle it. That didn't happen in Portal
2. This would be up way higher if it wasn't the way. I do think Portal 2 was better than Half-Life
1 just because it's, I don't know, it was newer. I liked Cave Johnson. Life gives you lemons. Get
some limes and half a sprite or whatever. He's had funny lines. Yeah, it belongs up here. Maybe
even a little higher. Put God of War down here. You just ruined my night. No, I'm just kidding.
Somebody, can I do this? I don't know why. I want to like make two cams. Have one of them be blue
and the other one be red and put them right next to each other transparent and like give you like
a 3D show. Can I do that? Color corrector. I need blue. Where's blue? Wait, color.
All right, that's red. Let me turn the brightness up. Is it gonna work? Okay, so there's that one
and then I need blue. I'm gonna, this is gonna be 3D. Oh, I can't, why can't I duplicate it?
No, I want to, I want to duplicate this and make it blue. Why can't I do that?
Paste duplicate. Why not? Is this a virtual boy? I don't think I can do a dupli- yeah,
I had this problem before. Yeah, because I can only paste a reference. I can't paste a duplicate.
Why? That's really annoying. Let's do a virtual boy. Yeah, I can't. Why can't I paste a duplicate?
Does anyone know how to do this? Because I haven't been, I've been trying to do this for years.
Can I just add another source, which is this camera or is that not going to work?
OBS can only take one camera. Like, hell it can. I'll be right back. Sorry, sorry, hold on,
hold on. This is so fucked up. I broke it because I plugged a camera in. Hold on. You see? All right,
this one works. All right, all right, all right, all right, here we go, here we go, here we go.
I got it. I should have it. This is gonna be fucked up. I can't wait. All right, now I'm almost done.
You see? Here we go. They gotta be in the same spot. This one's, this one's focus is fucked up.
Is it like grease on here? There was grease on it. There was a layer of grease. Oh, that's
disgusting. Okay, here we go. This one has to be blue. Did it work? I'm coming at you in 3D.
Okay, hold on. By the way, I gotta make this, I gotta, I gotta say this real quick. This is
probably, which camera do I look at? This is probably gonna hurt your eyes. This is probably
not gonna be, this is probably gonna suck to look at. So, I just want to make that really clear
right now. Like, just if you have like sensitivity, this is actually probably gonna be horrible.
Okay, so, make this, like you do it a little bit off to the side, right? I gotta make these
close to each other. Can I get it? Hold on. Red needs to be brighter. I'm gonna, I'm gonna like
throw popcorn in your face. Okay, brighter. Better? All right, here we go. It's time for your 3D.
You ready? I'm coming at you. I'm coming at you. They're off sync? Does that matter? Coming at you
live in 3D. Yeah, this is just, okay, when, you know when you go to the movies and you go to the
3D movie, and you realize that like halfway through the fucking movie, you really don't want
to watch it in 3D anymore, and you take the glasses off and you're just like, oh, Batman's
like punching the guy, and it's just like, and you're just like, I don't, can I, can we just go to
the other movie? This movie's fucking three hours long of this. Hold on, wait, ready? Just hit my
fucking monitor. I'm fine. It's not a heel. Hold on, wait, wait, wait. I need to.
All right, now we'll get your 3D glasses on eventually and watch that. I think, I actually
think it's probably gonna work. Okay, I'm fine. I think it's gonna work. All right, back to what
we were doing. I was doing this. Let's go. So, hmm, more how? I mean, look at how many are still on
here. Well, this is the last thing we're doing, except something else. There's something else to
show you. In fact, why don't we go over this now? I have something to show you. I came across
something very interesting. You know, turn this off for a sec. So, in my hand here, I've got,
I've got a little thing. Now, it's not Catboy. I saw my uncle recently, and at a little family
thing, and he was shit-faced, and he told me that he had something, a family heirloom, that was very
important. I had no idea what he was talking about. I thought, it's not a carrot. It's not a carrot.
It's some kind of important document. So, he told me that it was probably worth a lot of money.
It was grandpa's secret. So, the curiosity got ahold of me, and I said, well,
can I see it? He said, no. He said, you can't. It's just fucking safer. Remember, he was shit-faced.
So, I said, listen, I'll trade you a trip to McDonald's. I'll take you to the drive-through.
And he thought about it for a second, and he agreed. So, I got, I got whatever this is,
grandpa's secret, and we're going to open it right now. Are you ready? All it took was a
trip to McDonald's. What have we got here? This is a map. A map to what? Well, I mean,
that's obviously Las Vegas in the background. There's a treasure chest in the middle.
What is it? Is it a teaser trailer? Teaser is a bit, I mean, there's no information on here.
This is supposed to be Las Vegas. Vegas is landlocked. I, grandpa, I, there's no,
there ain't no water in Vegas. I don't think that's accurate. Anyhow, I'm gonna, I'm gonna
get some experts involved, and I'm gonna see if I can figure out what the fuck this is,
because there's very obviously something here. I see, first of all, I see a hamburger up here.
I think I'm, I'm gonna look into this. I'm gonna, I'm gonna look into that. Oh, I, hey, hey,
drunk Uncle Frank, you may have made the biggest mistake of your life, because I'm gonna get
whatever the fuck that is. Forgot about the wink. Why are you so red? All because of this. I'm
wearing like two, three layers. Porn acting. I've been that guy for a fucking year.
I felt, whoa, hold on, let's redo it. A treasure! I just like fucked up my neck.
I just pogged too much, and I just put a kink in my neck. Oh, holy shit, that fucking hurts.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on. It hurts. All right, we're good. Oh, we're gonna figure out
what this means. Very, very, very soon. I'm gonna go do some exploring. I need to find out what that
is. What's your porn acting? Fucking neck hurts. That was a YouTuber acting? Oh, what did I do?
What did I do to myself? I pogged so hard that I just like, it was like,
I gotta take a bath. That's the hardest I've ever pogged. On camera, for sure. All right, let's,
let's go. You know, you know, you know, I'm thinking, you know what I'm thinking?
You know what I'm thinking? I'm thinking a good, I'm thinking, I'm thinking Saturday afternoon
sounds like a really good time to go maybe look for this. That's what I'm thinking. And if I were
to give a time on Saturday that I would be doing that and exploring and trying to find grandpa's
secret, whatever it is. Gosh, I would probably put the sus at 1 p.m pacific on Saturday,
this Saturday, what I would do. What is it, nobody cares? All right, Mario 2. I always put Mario 2
in really bad. This two, all right, there are too many games on this list. There are way too many
games on this list. I can't do this. Dead Rising 2 was awesome, but was it better than Dead Rising 1?
Although I complained every single time I played it. I didn't play Deus Ex. I, where was, I played
Bully. I don't remember how good Bully was. I remember being, I remember it was good. I think
it belongs up here. Super Mario Galaxy 2, I didn't even play one second of it. Shadow of War
belongs up here, somewhere in good. I'll fix it. Crash Bandicoot, I never played it. None of them,
all three of them. I didn't, I just saw the demos at like the GameStop. I remember watching people
play them. The one that's like two minutes long. Only the PlayStation disc, I never played them.
Mario Galaxy, this is really good. That goes up in amazing. It's very, very good. Probably the
best Mario game that I've played in probably the last 10 to 15 years. I didn't play Factorio.
Is this Superman? I don't know what it is. What is that? Is this one of the, I don't think,
I don't think I played that Monster Hunter. I didn't play the Indiana Jones one. I didn't,
I played Lego Star Wars. I mean, it was all right. It was decent. Yeah, but it was not,
probably not better than Portal, though. Maybe. I've never played Roblox. I played this. This is
the Super Nintendo Zelda, right? That belongs up in great. Can we just, can these be free spaces?
Is this Ocarina of Time? Oh, okay. Yeah, okay. These have to be free spaces, like Bingo.
You can't, listen, you can't put on the greatest video games of all time list,
Zelda under good. These are free spaces. Zelda, Pac-Man, and Doom are free spaces up in amazing.
Yes, you can. It sucks. It does not suck. Resident Evil 7. The first act was amazing. The rest of
the game was not very good. I'm going to put it down here. Terraria. I, I just don't, I'm not,
I just don't, I just not a big fan of Terraria. It was, I played it. I beat the game. Me and
Ster played it. I, it was all right. It was, I don't really like, I, I, listen, how do I word
this without having like a rock go through the window right now? I like Terraria. I think it's
a really cool game. I just don't like the way it plays. I just don't like the side scrolling like,
it's fun. Let's get myself watering eyes from that. Play what? I'm going to sneeze. Am I? It's
coming. Rocket League. No, I never play, I don't play it. Skyrim. I played for four hours. Three
and a half hours were making monsters. So no. The Witcher 3. I never played it. Celeste was very,
listen to my voice. What's going on? Celeste was very good. Would I put Celeste somewhere over here?
Where do I put it? I didn't even play Doom 2016. I did for like three hours. Why is it even up here?
Where do I put the games that I've only played for four hours? Where do I put them? I can't say,
oh wow, it's like, it's one of the best games ever when you play it for three hours. It's going down
here. Make a new tier and call it four hour Andy. Okay. Let's make a new tier. Add a row below.
Okay. Four. There you go. And that, it can be just like, I don't know, grayed out. A lot of games
are going up here. Oh my god. So many games are going to be on here. What actually? No, I haven't
played Fortnite for more than 10 minutes. This is so bad. What else have I played for the four hours?
No. No. Batman. Modern Warfare, the original. Maybe because I downloaded it one day because
I wanted to try it. That's good. What about up here? Battlefield 1 is a four hour Andy.
Mario Kart 8. I, I, I'm not going to put it for our last of us. Watch Dogs, Watch Dogs 2. I want to
go, I want to go to bed so bad. Four hour fart. I've seen a lot of trans pride and I gotta make
something really clear. Please, for the love of God, I support LGBT rights. Full stop. That's a
full stop. And sometimes you look over and you see people very, very upset about that.
And I just gotta say, I gotta make it clear again, I don't want to see any, like, awful
shit. And we've seen, I'm gonna be honest with you, I've seen some really awful shit in this chat
about that. And there's the idea that, what about the spam? Spam is always taken care of. We have
a rule for spam. So there's no reason, there's no reason at all to, if you see the trans pride
emote, to automatically start to just throw awful shit into this chat. Spam will be taken care of.
Please, for the love of God, don't be such an asshole. Because I hate to say it, I really do.
I've seen stuff in this chat that I'm not, does not make me happy. So let me make that really clear.
I, I have to. Because, what about, thank you. Well, it's, I'll be honest, it's, it's hard to
talk about on stream. Because for some reason there is a percentage of people that just really,
really hate the fact that it's talked about. And I gotta make that really clear that I,
wherever you stand socially, politically, it doesn't matter. I don't bring that shit here.
Don't bring that negative shit here. I don't want to see it. And if I do, I'm gonna be,
it's gonna be taken care of. It just is. You don't have to explain yourself. Well, sometimes you do.
Sometimes I do. There you go. That's, I want to make that clear. Get back to the, get back to this.
Yeah, we will. It was a good transition from the fart joke. Is that, is that how,
that's not what happened? That's not what happened. Yes, it is. No, it's not. What fart joke?
I didn't make a fart joke. Or our fart. Oh, I did say that right before. Whatever. It doesn't
matter. I, doesn't, all right, let's, let's fucking go. You're the master of the segue.
It's so fucking hot in here. Like, and I, I just so badly want you to know what website I'm on.
You're here right now. I don't have to fucking wear this. You, I, why do I have to wear this
right now? Let's show the Andy Mark t-shirt. It's too, I don't know why. Like, hey, I'm on
Twitch.tv. You see this shirt? Like, this isn't a doc. I don't have to wear like the lab coat.
It's not a doctor's office. Like, oh, I'm a doctor, you know. Twerk, please. Okay. That is so sweaty
and disgusting. I can't even tell you. Twerk. And now, hey, I'm almost as like red as the t-shirt.
It is so fucking hot in here. Why is it so hot in here? All right, let's go.
Lego Star Wars 2. I have, I have no idea. Uh, did I, I played Limbo on stream, didn't I?
It was for four hours. That's four hour Andy. That counts. Did I beat it on stream?
Wait, it's a four hour game. Oh, okay. It was, it was all right. I liked it. Monster Hunter World?
Uh, I remember streaming Monster Hunter World with italics and getting so angry at the game
that I never played it again. So I'm going to say four hour Andy. That's a lie. I beat the whole
thing with italics off stream. I thought it was all right. No More Heroes is a good game,
but a terrible video game. It's in, it's somewhere in here. Uncharted, never played them.
Chrono Trigger, thank you very much. We're going up all the way to Masterpiece. Thank you very much.
Chrono Trigger's a masterpiece. It is. Uh, I never played this. I didn't play any of the Pokemon's
Jackbox Party Pack 6. That, that shouldn't be on here. Why is Jackbox Party Pack 6 on here?
Jackbox Party Pack 6? Hearthstone is on here? No, it's not. Oh my God, it is. This is decent.
Firewatch, I, all right, it was decent. It was all right. Beat Saber, I don't, four hour Andy.
Silent Hill 2, four hour Andy. I only played it for like four hours. The Sims 4, four hour Andy.
Getting over it, four hours. Half-Life 2 was, show the photos. Go watch the video. Half-Life 2
is not a masterpiece for me. It's not. There's a lot of subs. I missed all these. Uh, Mega Cheese
Nips, thanks to the five subs. James Morris, five subs. Volco, five. Ten from Lenny the Person.
Twenty-five from Wiggly Joe, which is a lot. Thank you, Wiggly Joe. Ten from Mega Dial, again.
Uh, five from Nice to See You, Nice to See You 2. Thirty-five from Frogman. Frogman 5078,
gave thirty-five fucking community subs. That's a lot. Mega Dial 5, Dad Jeff 10, X Sparta 5,
8-Bit 15, Matt Reyes 5. Oh, actually, it's Matt Australia. This is still coming in. Justfin 5,
Julie the Fooly 5, and then Gearbroth 5, and then another five from JWY. Oh, okay, we're going.
Vinsmoke 5. These just kind of come out of nowhere. I'll just look over here and it's just like
bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, sub, sub, sub, sub, subs. You guys just load in.
Uh, thank you, all of you, though. Seriously, thank you. Uh, Jamie, thanks for the five.
Boston, thanks for the five. Boston Game, let's fucking go. Let's fucking go. But, but stop now.
You don't have to do this. You especially don't have to give me 50. 50 community subs from Captain
Nemo. That's 50. Thanks for the 50 subs. Thanks for the five. Artichoke, Electra 5, Apples 5,
JBNKY5, Greg Sash 5, Willy Plays 5. I just told you to stop. This is insane. Um, thank you,
though. Easy Ice, please. I agree. I actually agree with that. I always get Easy Ice. They put way too
much ice in drinks nowadays. It's serious. Ike, this is still going. Uh, um, thank you, Victor
for the five. Ultravirus for five. Captain Dark for ten. Toaster of Doom for five. Bug Eyes five.
Wacky 2, ten. Pool to music, five. Uh, Kool Kack, five. Hakun, five. Hype Train, this is way past
the Hype Train. I look like, like, I have like fucking skeleton skin. What's with this white
balance? I don't like it. I look weird. Hey, Ballistic Burrito, five. Robotic Rogue, five.
Wiggly Joe, another five. Cosmetic, five. Hype George, five. Stimpak, ten. Takin Mosh, five.
All right. All right. You've done it. You've given me too much money. Thank you, everybody.
Uh, thank you for five more. Red Sauce and then 25 from Soda Cat. Thank you, guys. Thank you.
I really appreciate it. But we don't have to do this. All right. That's it. That's it. No more.
Yeah, you get just too much money. Thank you. I will take it, but it's a lot.
Uh, Cotton Canyon, five. Phi from Funky Lesbian. Phi from Labster. Start crying.
This is not gonna make me cry. This is gonna make me go, holy shit. Silent Sturm, thanks for five.
Silly Moose, five. Chrissy, five. Daddy Good, five. Poetic Psycho, five. Phi from
This is, what do I do? Phi from Risen Slash. Phi from It's Noy. Castax, five. Keep stuffing him.
No, don't stuff me. Delete that. And don't ever tell anybody. And don't ever talk about that.
He doesn't care? No, of course I do. It's just a lot. No, I, of course I do. Um, Miss, hold on.
More coming in. Five from Marshmallowy Ghost. Phi from David Cage Official Twitch. Something
telling me that's not David Cage's official Twitch. Emperor Zant, Mindizel, Little Pretzel,
Bugwiki, and AB Joe. Thank you Bugwiki for ten. This is a money stream now. This is just a collect
money on camera stream. I'm just sitting here collecting money while I just sit here and talk.
Thank you Gaw for the five. Spicy Pepe's for the five. Ten from Nocturnal Turn. Wild Card
Soldier, five. This is almost, it's almost a thousand subs by the way. I don't even know
what to do. How do I turn the faucet off? How do I distract you guys? I think I know what to do.
I think I know how to distract you guys. Quick, refund, refund, refund. Uh, 808 thanks for the
five. Uncle Joe, five. Fourbugs, five. VGB, five. Feline, five. Evasive Milk, five. Somewhat Bleak,
five. Ten from Megaboob. Oh, ten from, it is Sky. Five from Slinkerton. Five from Yurt. Five from
Wild Card. I can't even read these. Five from Peaceful Hailey. Ten from Labster. Five from Nep.
All right, I'm going to continue with the tier list. From here on out, any community subs are
going to be appreciated, but I gotta move on. I gotta stream. This is insane. This is over a
thousand gifted subs. Thank you everybody. This is unbelievable amount of subscriptions.
And it's over a thousand community subs. That's fucking crazy. Uh, I hopefully, hopefully I can
put Warcraft 3 in the right spot, otherwise I'm gonna lose subs. Uh, thank you guys, really.
Completely unnecessary. Thank you nonetheless. Hopefully I do good. Hopefully I can use your
money wisely. Thank you. Among Us Andy. I'm the person up for ten seconds, because then they'll
have a full tech of ten seconds to really go over what they did wrong. Uh, Warcraft 3 was amazing.
It belongs up here. It does. Not the remake, the original one. I think it deserves to be up there.
Battlefront 2, never played it. Street Fighter 2, I've really, I've watched people at the arcade
play it, but I never, I never played it. Second Son, never played it. The Spider-Man game, that
should be up here under, under good. That's under good. Path of Exile, this is a four hour Andy.
Uh, Dishonored, that's a four hour Andy. Yakuza didn't play this one. Need for Speed didn't play
this one. Assassin's Creed didn't play it. Didn't play the Dragon Ball game. Minecraft. Do I put
Minecraft in, um, I don't think I put Minecraft in Masterpiece. I think it goes under great. High
rate. Doom 2016 is not, seriously, why is it even up here? It belongs down here. Spider-Man
belongs probably up here under very good. I really liked that Spider-Man game, it was really good.
Spec Ops The Line, I didn't play it. Crusader, I didn't play Crusader's Kings 2. I don't know
what that is. Um, Gmail? What is that? Oh, that's Gar, that's Garry's Mod. That's Garry's Mod. Is
Garry's Mod really like a masterpiece of a video game, or is it like a cool toolbox? It's good,
but I don't know, it doesn't belong high that up there. Hi. Uh, Superhot. The original Superhot
was cool. Superhot VR was better. It's not on here, which is disappointing. Mordhau's not really bad.
It was, it was good. It was, it wasn't better than Portal. Civilization. Didn't play any of the
Civilizations. Spore. Uh, Spore's gonna go up to good. Fallout 4, that's four hour Andy. Maybe six
hour Andy. What just went in my eye? Super Seducer on greatest games of all time? Why? I never played
it, but why? Uh, this is another Far Cry, who knows what it is. It could be one I played, I don't
care, it just belongs down here. I may as well have never played it. Uh, Far Cry 5 is four hour Andy.
Guitar Hero, is this a mobile game? It's like a Facebook game. Hotline Miami. This goes up to good.
Actually, very good. No, it's, I'm gonna keep it at good. That is a mo-, it's a Facebook game.
Fallout 76. I don't, why would I ever play this? Is this Pong? Pong is definitely four hour Andy.
I have probably played it three times. Yeah, absolutely. I didn't play Deus Ex. Didn't play
Dishonored 2. I played For Honor, that's also for four hours. Metro 2033, I played the whole thing,
and I did like it, but I don't think it was that great. No, I'm thinking of the next one. I liked
2033. Actually, I actually really liked 2033, it was great. Deus Ex. Yeah, I didn't play it.
This is Persona, I've never played it, didn't play it. What? No, yeah, I did. Back in like 2013 or
something. Wii Sports? Um, it was good. I don't even know what that is. Guitar Hero 3 is four hour
Andy. I may have like in college or something played it once, twice maybe. I played Rock Band,
I played Rock Band a lot. Not Guitar Hero 3. Stalker, I streamed it for four hours. Ooh,
Cuphead. Cuphead belongs up here. Probably up at very good. When's a DLC come up for Cuphead?
Never. Oh no, what? It wasn't bad news or anything, was there? Postal 3 on greatest
games ever, four hour Andy. Sniper Elite 3, four hour Andy. Undertale, uh oh. See, some of you took
a screenshot when I was doing this. Like when I was moving this up and scrolling. Screenshot!
So you can like link it to somebody that you know loves that game and now they hate me.
It's up here somewhere. Shadow, that's way too high. Shadow the Colossus has to go further down.
I'm okay with this so far, but maybe not. We'll see. This is a Fallout wallpaper
for your computer, for desktop. I don't know which one it is, so I'm going to say I don't know.
No, it's four hours. It's probably Fallout 3. Wait, no, I played Fallout 3 on stream for
four hours. Six hours maybe total. I've never played a Pokemon game before. Does it count
before hour Andy if I tried to stream it but it didn't work and I tried to play it? Not really.
Logic 2. Never played it. Um, which Hitman is this? Uh, belongs up here somewhere. I'll
figure it out later. We, something Play 2? Just Dance? No. Counter-Strike Source
is just going to go right next to Counter-Strike. One slot above because it has better graphics.
Let's Counter-Strike Go. Oh, well, whatever. It doesn't matter. Dead by Daylight, have never
played it. I actually played and beat this whole game and I had one incredibly major complaint.
This, the DuckTales remake was good. The music was great. It was awesome reimagining. Um, they,
there were way too many cutscenes. There's a cutscene every other screen in this game.
I, it was like come, just let me play the fucking game. It was like cutscene, cutscene, cutscene,
cutscene in like the remake of DuckTales the game. There's too many cutscenes. It was decent.
Why is Tetris in bed? Because I hate that game. In fact, it's going down because you just reminded
me to rethink of what I, why I put it here. I hate Tetris. I don't, I do not like it. I hate
this game. I know, like Tetris 99 came out and it's, what a cool idea. It was such a dumb, stupid,
horrible, shitty video game. And then they came out with the Super Mario one and that one was
really good. I'm sorry. I know people, some of you probably really like this Tetris and it's,
I just hate it. I hate it. I've always hated it. And it's because I'm not good at it.
I'm not good enough to play it, to be good at it. And that angers me and it makes me not like it.
So take that as you will. Mad because bad. That's yes. Yes. Mad because I, I, I hate Tetris because
I'm not good at it. At least it's better than the Avengers game. Don't you feel like the Avengers
game was a dream you had? Wow. The Avengers game so hyped up for the Avengers. Like that's the
dream where like you think it's real, but the thing it wasn't real. Wow. How awesome would it
be to have a never ending like action adventure, like kind of you, you watch words, an action
adventure game where you play as the Avengers and you go and fight stuff and it doesn't end.
And it's like a game as a service kind of thing. And they keep adding stuff and there's like boss
fights. It's like multiplayer. We've wanted that for so long, Gordy. We've wanted that for so long,
Gordy. And yeah, yeah, I know. But I feel like I dreamt that and then it wasn't, it didn't exist.
Hold on. Somebody said, somebody just said this. Is Genshin Impact a better Marvel Avengers game?
It is, right? It has to be. I would love to play it. First time I downloaded Genshin Impact on my
iPad, I got a black screen. I could walk around with the character, but the entire environment
was black. Couldn't play it. Uninstalled it. Two or three fucking months later, I go back and I
reinstall it. This time, I can't even get to the actual main menu of the video game. I sure would
have loved to have played it on my iPad. So I uninstalled it again. So maybe like another two
or three months after they do some more bug fixes on the iPad version, I'll try it again. I'm not
going to play it on PC. No, I want to lie in bed and just run around and hit stuff until I pick up
loot cases and stuff. I don't want to play that on PC. That's not a PC game to me.
That's a like in the bath game to me. That's a like sprinkle in some bath salts and like light
a candle and just play Genshin Impact for like 30 minutes and then get out of the bath. That's not
a PC game for me. You're a crackhead. Stop getting sidetracked on the most random shit. Take every
stream I've ever done and pull out the times I get sidetracked and if it's less than 60% of everything
I've ever recorded, you win. If getting sidetracked is not like at least 60%, then you win.
I don't know why you don't really win anything. You win the thought. You win knowing that you
were right. No, don't triple the debt. No. Lance vs. Zombies. This is the first one, so it belongs
up here. The second one, I would love to just like snot rocket it out of existence on here.
It better not be even on here. Mountain Blade Warband. You know where that goes. Last of Us
Part 2 didn't play it. Journey didn't play it. Um, this is, this is Near didn't play it. Kingdom
Hearts 3 didn't play it. Rainbow Six Siege, 4-hour Andy. Death Stranding didn't play it.
Animal Crossing, 4-hour Andy. System Shock 2 never played it. Divinity never played it. Dying Light
was, was okay. I wouldn't put it in like best game ever. Untitled Goose Game was better than Dying
Light for me. It belongs somewhere up here into good. We'll figure that out in a minute. Oblivion.
I streamed it like two or three times for what? Three, four hours each? That's not 4-hour Andy.
It was all right. I had fun. I can't believe this is even on here. It's like honestly,
I'm 4-hour Andy. Yeah. Dawn of War 1? If it's Dawn of, if it's Warhammer 40k Dawn of War, then
it belongs up here. I loved the original Dawn of War. I thought it was fantastic. It belongs up here.
We'll figure it out. Turkey Sandwich. All right, so I got, I've gotten to the point where I haven't
played any video games in my whole life and I thought this was the list to choose from.
No, we're almost done. I didn't play Sly Cooper. I never played NBA 2K20. No Pokemon games ever.
I never played Persona. Never played Grounded. I don't even know what this is, so I'm gonna say
no. No More Heroes 2 belongs up here. No More Heroes 1 is better. It's not, in a way.
Oh, Tsushima. I really wanted to play Ghost of Tsushima. Metal Gear Solid. I think this is,
Metal Gear Solid is fantastic. That's gotta go up to amazing. Okay, I'll find the play
sport in a minute. Didn't play Yakuza. Didn't play Call of Duty Cold War. I didn't play Doom
Eternal. Didn't, no Crusader Kings. No Bayonetta. No Super Limital. No Wasteland 3. Oh, Hades.
This goes into, this goes into great. Where? We'll find out. I don't know what that is.
Payday 2 belongs in 4-hour Andy. Half-Life Alyx. I talked about this when I beat Half-Life Alyx.
Half-Life Alyx is better than Half-Life 2, and that's recorded now. I think it is.
That's wrong. I don't think it is. Where is Half-Life 2? This is a lie. This is, this is a lie.
This has to be up here because I, I game on PC. It's not true. That's not true for me, and I have
to break out of the, out of the deceit and the lying. I don't think that Half-Life 2 is like a
masterpiece. I think Portal 2 is more fun. I think I enjoyed Portal 2 more than Half-Life 2. I'm
sorry. I still find it to be very, very good. I just, I think Half-Life Alyx is better. By a lot.
I'm calling Gabe? Yeah, call him. Sure. And tell him that the next one in the series was way better
than the last one. I'm sure he's gonna be really happy. Imagine knowing that you tried to live up
to Half-Life 2 and somebody said it was better than Half-Life 2. He's gonna be real fucking
happy to hear that. He's gonna be ecstatic to know that because they were very concerned about that.
Like, oh, how do we do another Half-Life? Can we live up to Half-Life 2? Oh, you, oh, you,
you guys did. I thought it was fantastic. Where is it right now? That was Game of the Year last
year too. That was the best game that came out last year. And Hades. But Half-Life Alyx is better
than Hades. This shit wasn't even, it wasn't even nominated. This wasn't even nominated for Game of
the Year. And it was the best game that came out last year. Are we gonna judge things based on how
good they were? That was like the most fun I had in a video game last year. Yeah, there are some
movies that get nominated for awards that are in select theaters. So what's the difference? It's
VR. VR is expensive. Viewers are dropping. What do I do? Hold on. Uh, make noises and make sounds.
Uh, how do I get them to stay? Make, I gotta make sounds and make noises. Quick, do doi doi doi.
I, I don't know how to do it. I broke it.
I don't, I don't know how to do it anymore. I think I fucked it up. Of course I know how to do it.
Shovel Knight. Didn't play it. Not even 4-hour indie. I think I opened it on Steam
and like jumped around for like 10 minutes or something and then was like,
I'll play this later. And I played it. Don't know what that is. Don't know what this is.
Didn't play the Batman game. Hollow Knight. That's, that's more than four hours, right?
I streamed this like two or three times. Was this four hours? I really liked it.
The reason why I could never go back to Hollow Knight was because I got halfway through the game
and then didn't play it for, what, like four or five months? And the game is a,
it's one of those, you have to remember where everything is. This huge map with all the
different areas. And this one, you have to have the jump. You have to have the dash to go over here.
And I just forgot everything. And I would have had to restart the whole game. I didn't want to
restart the entire game because I already did it. And it was like four months ago. Maybe I could,
maybe I, I don't know. Should I restart it? I will help you. I thought it was really fun.
Oh, I think it's too late. I think it's too late. I did like it though. Uh, never played it.
Didn't play it. Uh, I don't know what that is. I think it's Final Fantasy. Subnautica. That's,
you know where that goes. Warzone. Didn't play it. Titanfall God. This is Titanfall 2. I didn't
even play it. Orion the Blind Forest. Didn't play it. Mega Man? No. Is that Mega Man? Samurai
Warrior. Oh, um, I don't know what that is. Saints Row the Third. I didn't, I didn't even play it.
Maybe for like 10 minutes. Flight Simulator. Didn't even play it. Hitman. This is Hitman.
Okay. Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah. This goes up here. Okay. Before I get this completely done,
before I do this and fix this, I want to tell you what my favorite ice creams are because I
got to get that out of the way really fast. Vanilla. B. Rocky Road. I'm going to, I'm not
going to think about it. Rocky Road. C. Peanut Butter. D. Pistachio. A. Birthday Cake. Way too,
it's kind of good, but it's way too sugary, way too heavy. Cheesecake. Strawberry cheesecake. A.
Eggnog. D. Cherry. D. I don't know. Peppermint. C. Bubblegum. D. Rum Raisin. D. Mint Chip. B.
Brownie Batter. That's somewhere, that's up here. Hold on, don't even think about it. Lemon Custard.
D. Coffee. You have to be in the mood for it. C. Uh, Creamsicle. Like a cre, like Creamsicle. Creamsicle.
B. Peach. C. Mango. B. Neapolitan. Moostrex. B. Beer. D. Blue Moon. Don't even know what it is. D.
Chocolate. B. Superman. Don't even know what that is. That looks like fucking Play-Doh.
This is Play-Doh. That's not real, that's not ice cream. Cotton Candy. D. Black Raspberry. B.
Coconut. C. Raspberry Ripple. I don't even know what this is. Grape. C. Cookies and Cream. S.
Chocolate Chip. Basic. Strawberry. S. Chocolate Chip Cookie Dough. S. Butter Pecan. Without the
pecans in it. S. With pecan, if I, I, I put the pecans in my mouth and I get the ice cream off
and I spit it back in the container. Until, uh, this is just ice cream. Reese's Peanut Butter Cup.
Alright. No. Peppermint is, Mint Chip is just way better. No, it's not done. Now it is. There you go.
Alright, back to what we were doing. Alright, this is important. We're gonna start from the bottom up.
So, of all the games that I have only played for four hours, what's the one I think is the best?
Probably Odyssey. It's not, not Dota. Not Borderlands. No way. I've played The Sims for
longer than that. But The Sims 4 is not even the best one. It's like The Sims 2 or The Sims 3.
I should play The Sims 1. Alright, mark this on your calendar. I'm gonna play The Sims 1. Like,
soon. In the next week or two. Like two, three weeks from now or something. It's alright. Okay.
So, definitely not. Probably not. Probably not. Probably not. I put all these games I put in,
like, the same category. Like, I just, I've only played them for, like, a few hours and I don't,
like, all the four-hour games have to be in the same place except for Mario Galaxy. Horrible.
Uh, Avengers is probably the worst game ever, right? Like, it has to be. Mario Kart, I don't
like the Mario Kart. It's not overcooked. This doesn't belong here. Four-hour, Andy. I only
played it for, like, three hours on stream with, like, italics. Alright, that's perfect. That's
more accurate for me. Alright, um, Until Dawn, I just don't think that, I don't think they're
bad games. I just don't think they belong, like, really on the list of best games ever,
but we'll just keep it here. Modern Warfare 3 better than Warframe? No. Is Far Cry 3 better
than Modern Warfare 3? Is Until Dawn better than Modern Warfare? Yes. Yes. No. Okay, that's,
that's fine. Alright, now this is really important. Is Warframe better than Far Cry 3? Yes. Is
DuckTales Remastered better than Warframe? No. Warframe moves up. Is Mordhau better than
Hearthstone? Hearthstone's better than Firewatch. I mean, what? Firewatch was cool, but it just,
it did, it was, I liked the experience, but it was just, alright, let me just tell you. I was one of
those, I was one of those, I, look, the game's been on for, like, fucking seven years. I was one of
those people, I, I didn't like the ending. I didn't like the end of the movie. Is it? And
I felt like the entire thing was building up to the end of the movie, and I wasn't a big,
I didn't really like the end of the movie. I liked the movie, I liked the experience. I did,
it was a good, it was fun, it was, it was decent, it was good, but I felt like the whole thing was
leading up to the end, and I was like, well, I didn't really like the end. If the whole thing
was leading up to the end for me, then I wasn't a big fan. The photos were, yeah, it was alright,
it was fun. For those of you that don't know, The Photos Are In is my favorite video that I ever
made on the channel. That's my favorite video. I get asked that all the time, and it's hard for me
to pick, but that's, like, that's my favorite video I ever made. Derma Rumble Live was awesome,
but I, I don't know, I still think that that's, like, my favorite video I ever made.
That's the video I show people when I introduce them to you. Well, that's a weird one to pick.
Anyways, Portal is better than Counter-Strike, Counter-Strike's better than Dying Light,
Dead Rising's better than Dying Light, it's just a, it's just a better version of the same kind of
game for me. No More Heroes is better than Dying Light, all these are better than Dying Light,
all of them. Smite is definitely, no, it belongs here. Dying Light just really kind of belongs all
the way down here. Yeah, it was alright, it was good, yeah, it was good, but, alright. Name me one
character's name from Dying Light. Any character in the whole game, name me a character's name.
You understand? Kyle Crane. If you just, you can't just go to Google and type in
Dying Light characters and just pick one, you know what I mean. I can't, I can't name you one,
they're all just a, just blank face. I can't name you anything. All I remember is me and Sterr
chasing this weird zombie around and he ran into a fence and killed himself. That's the only thing
I remember, that's the only thing I pulled from that game. It's on, sorry, it's on, it's on Sterr's
video. It was really funny. And I remember Sterr throwing an axe into somebody's head.
Somebody was like standing there like we were looting somebody and like an axe just hits him
in the skull. Oh my god, what's with my eyes? And then, oh, that's where the meme is from,
that's where Coffee's Cheeto, that's where that's from. But that was a secret video, that was not
in the main video. That's a secret video, that's not the main one. Alright, let's continue. I think
I like where this is all standing right now. Whose is better than That'll Get Rising? Is it
Limbo's? Okay, Star Wars, this has got Star Wars in it, it's better than Overwatch. Alright,
now it's going to get tricky. This is where it becomes hard. I really did like Shadow of War,
I thought it was fantastic. This goes down, this goes down, this goes down, this goes down,
this comes up, this goes down, this goes up, this goes down, this goes down, this goes down,
this goes down, this one goes down, this goes down, this goes up, actually, this one goes way up,
way, way, way, way up, this goes up, that goes down, that goes, this goes up, this goes up,
that goes down, that goes down, so does this, this one does too, to here, this one goes down too,
that one goes down as well, this one goes up. We got it? Yep, this goes down.
Prairie was like more fun than Metal Gear, no it wasn't. Close. Level up for Shadow of War. Shadow
of War is better than Plants vs. Zombies. God, yell at me. Metro, is Shadow of War better than
Metro 2033? That's very close. Say 2033 33 times. 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033,
2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033, 2033,
doing that made me realize it's better than Shadow of War. Thank you. Oh, you know, you guys ever
look in the mirror and you get terrified, not of losing this, not of having like, like get crow's
feet here. No, no, no, no. How many of you guys have fucking horrified at the notion of eventually
having this? Like, I don't want that. Like, I don't, I don't want that. And it's going to happen to
everybody. Just that like sagging, weird fat pocket that's under the chin. I, I get,
make me bald, have me have crow's feet, wrinkles everywhere. Do not give me the turkey neck. I
don't want it. It's, I, it's one thing I really don't want. And it's already kind of happening.
We're gonna do like exercises. You like go put your chin up, right? You have to do exercises.
Uh, Plants vs. Obvious is going down and Hotline Miami is going up. So is Celeste.
Spider-Man was better than, oh, that's tough. Sekiro was not better than Cuphead. Sekiro was,
this is hard. Now it's really hard. Um, Sekiro was good, but Dark Souls is leveling up.
And so was Dark Souls 3. Left 4 Dead 2 was very good, but it's going down. Red Dead's leveling
up to great. Fallout was, mm-hmm. Yep. This is leveling up as well. The losing viewers.
Well, it's because every time I move a game that's your favorite game up a slot or down a slot that
you didn't agree with, you leave. So when I just put left, when I just went from Left 4 Dead from
two, from great to very good, this is somebody here's favorite video game. And they went and
they fucking click the X. And it happens for every single one of these, because statistically
speaking, if there's 14,000 people here, somebody in here has a favorite game on this list. It's
every single one of you. Like this is somebody's. This is somebody's. This is somebody's. All of
this is somebody's favorite game. So when I take Cuphead and I go like this, two, three, 400 people
just collect X. That's how it works. All right, let's go. Is Mario 2 better than Left 4 Dead 2?
They both have two in it. Level up. Level up. Level up. D level. D level. No, no way. You know
what? D level. Resident Evil 2 was more fun for me than Dark Souls 3. Is Minecraft better than
Dark Souls 3? Half Life 2 is. The Half Life games are better than Dawn of War and Hades and Cuphead.
Yeah, they are. They are. BioShock is definitely. Oh, this is going to make people so angry.
Me even, me even remotely considering scrolling my mouse this way. Put this in front of this.
It's not good for a lot of you. I'm considering it. It's close. I played way more. It has to go
down there. That's fair. That's accurate. Like it has to be down in 4 hour ante.
Because I only played it for like fucking five hours. None of these other games that I played
for four hours, right? No, I've played a shitload of all of these up here. Yeah. All right. This is
good. I'm happy with this. Minecraft is better than Resident Evil. Minecraft is better. Minecraft is
better than Hitman. Hitman is. Resident Evil. Yeah, Hitman got D leveled. Sorry, you got D ranked.
Oh. Oh, how far is Hitman going to fall here though? Is Cuphead better than Hitman? Yeah.
Hades better than Hitman. Close. Yeah. Isaac. Yeah. Here we go. This is where it gets much harder.
I think that's where it stops. Look, if Pac-Man gets to be up here and Doom Classic gets to be
over here, Minecraft, like Minecraft is one of those games that's going to be the Pac-Man when
you and I have 50. Okay. I'm done. Wait, Half-Life 2 better than Dark Souls 3?
Yes. All of these are better than Dark Souls 3. All right. Half-Life 2 better than Resident Evil 2.
No, it's not. Not for me. I loved Resident Evil 2. I loved it. It was like my favorite game of the
year. I thought that was fantastic. I loved it. Like when I finished Half-Life 2, I was like,
wow, that was awesome. That was unbelievable. When I finished Resident Evil 2, I said,
that's one of the best games ever. I said that kind of, maybe I should just level it up. Yeah,
it's leveled up. And by the way, Fallout New Vegas just got leveled up too. And guess what? Doom is
going down here. I don't care. A game came out in the fucking sixties or whatever. I don't care.
It's classic. Sure. But what's it doing up here? These two have to be next to each other because
they're about to fight each other. Mirror. That's fair. Pac-Man does not go down too. I love
Pac-Man. It goes down here. Because that means Half-Life 2 is like the best in its category for
like a great game. But the other games up here on this list, I need to just triple check and make
sure I had more fun in them than I did Half-Life 2. Because this is now the barometer for like a
great, very, very, just great experience. Find out. Pac-Man. Fine. Fine. Resident Evil 2 stays up
here. Minecraft that's staying up here. Ocarina of Time. I put the nostalgic glasses just on.
Ocarina of Time. Dark Souls 1. I got to find the one that's like, what is my fucking favorite game
that's not quite masterpiece. What is it? Or does one of these get leveled up? It does.
GTA 4 is a, is a fucking masterpiece. One of the most revolutionary games ever made.
It had so much going on. So much to do. It changed everything. It was a, it was one of the first true
real living open world games. It's a masterpiece. GTA 4 is a masterpiece. It is. I think it belongs
up here. What about San Andreas? San Andreas is not on this list. Resident Evil 4. Okay, hold on.
Metal Gear's got to go down here. It's an amazing game, but it's not, it's not quite up here.
Where would I put San Andreas? Honestly? Probably right behind GTA 4. Or right here. I, I, GTA 4 is
like one of my favorite games ever. I like loved this game. It was, I loved it. Maybe down here.
Like right here. Okay. Was Resident Evil 2 better than Mario Galaxy for me? Yes. Was Mario Galaxy
better than Warcraft 3? Yeah. I think so. Was Undertale better than Warcraft 3? No. Was Shadow
the Colossus better than Undertale? Wait. I think I actually broke a controller with Shadow the
Colossus. I think like the, I, the grip was, I couldn't grip. Like it was, I hated the control
scheme. And I think I literally like broke a controller in half. Like 15, 20 years ago. True.
Is Metal Gear Solid better than Undertale? Yes. Is Metal Gear Solid better than Warcraft 3? Yes.
Is Metal Gear Solid better than Mario Galaxy? Yes. Is Metal Gear Solid better than Resident
Evil 2? No. Is Resident Evil 2 better than Ocarina of Time? Is Ocarina of Time better than
Minecraft? Is Metal Gear Solid better than Dark Souls 1? We have to go back and take,
we have to go, we have to go back here. It is. Is Half-Life Alyx better than Portal 2?
Yes. Is Portal 2 better than Minecraft? Is GTA 5 better than Ocarina of Time? GTA 5 better than
Resident Evil 2? It's, no it is. Yes it is. Is it better than Minecraft? Yes it is. Is it better
than Portal 2? No. Yes it is. Wait, isn't this, this is where it just was. Wasn't this just where
it was before? Is Resident Evil 4 better than World of Warcraft? No. That got knocked down.
Is Half-Life Alyx better than World of Warcraft? Think, think really hard on this. No it's not.
It's not. I had so many wonderful memories in World of Warcraft back in like 2005.
This is, nothing will be able to cross this. This is not going up here, but nothing will cross that.
Portal 2 better than Resident Evil 4? No. Is Resident Evil 4 better than GTA 5? Yes. I think
so. It's so close. It's by like 0.01%. Alright. Team Fortress 2 or Diablo 2 or Bloodborne. Let's
see. I think this, I think I'm done with this. Wait, is Undertale, it's Undertale better than
Warcraft 3? Is Mario Galaxy better than Metal Gear Solid? Is Zelda better than Dark Souls?
Let's find out in this video. I feel like I'm making a fucking like top 10 list. Oh, I hate
to do that, but I'm gonna. I'm done. This is, this is it. I really believe that Team Fortress 2
is the best video game ever made. It's the best game ever made. It just is.
Now, it might not be that supported right now, but holy shit, back in like 2010, 2011, 2012,
this is the best game ever made. Ever. Is Bloodborne better than D2 though?
Yeah. Is D2 better than GTA 4? Yeah. Is Chrono Trigger better than Bloodborne? No. I think this
is accurate. 2013 was peak TF2. Nothing can come close. I have never cared about a video game more
than I did TF2. 2010, 2011 to like 2015. Oh God, nothing will ever come close. If this is a barometer
for where a video game has to cross to be better, like a best game ever made. Oh, you've, it's,
you've got a long way to go. So here's, look at, see these two. I find Bloodborne to be one of the
best games ever made. I do. This is not even close. If we're talking about a scale, okay, this is like
the best game ever made for me. And this is like a second best game ever made. You're talking about
like, like 50 points to go to cross from here to here. If TF2 is like a 100, Bloodborne's like a 60
and like everything else is underneath it. It's so impossible to cross that threshold.
Somebody has to do something insane. TF2 is on its own tier. That's yeah. Now that's,
that's accurate. I really, that's true. It belongs up there. It does. And literally everything else
will never come close. Like maybe one day somebody will make something that is.
Where's Stardew Valley? Cause that's like, that actually like belongs up here somewhere.
Okay. So Stardew Valley is not on this list. Hay Day a Facebook game is. That's weird. Okay.
Can I pretend this is Stardew Valley? Cause like Hay Day, like farming or something. All right.
This is, this is Stardew Valley. Stardew Valley better than Resident Evil 4. I think so. Hay Day.
This is, I got 5,000 hours on Hay Day, man. I'm number one in my Facebook group.
Now it's perfect. All right. There it is. There's, there's your video game. Tetris sucks. I hate
that game. And that's it. That's going to be the stream. Um, so I've got to figure out,
I've got to figure out what this is. I can figure out what this means. I wonder,
I wonder what he wants me to find. Grandpa. I will see you guys on Saturday. What are you
going to do? Tetris stream? What about Slime Rancher? Uh, Slime Rancher is like up here
somewhere. No, it's not. It's like here. Where the fuck is Dark Souls 2? Do you really think
Dark Souls 2 should be on this list? I mean, it could be. It may be, but it would be down here.
Oh, this, we'll do the same as one after the stream on Saturday at some point,
some point. We'll see. I will see you guys on Saturday. That's the next time you're going to
see me. I'm going to look directly at you because I'm telling you Saturday at 1 PM Pacific. I might
think about figuring out where that, what, what this is. I'm going to go explore. I'm just going
to go explore now and just see if I can find anything. It might even be in the same damn close.
Yeah, we'll see you on Saturday. Uh, that's been the stream. Just wanted to hang out for a few
hours and just say what's up and hang out with you guys. Uh, didn't I say, I said the stream was
going to be 45 minutes, didn't I? Well, that was wrong. I've been here for like three and a half
hours. Have a wonderful rest of your evening. Take care of yourselves. I'll see you guys on
Saturday at 1 PM Pacific. Look at how, look at that. Oh my goodness. That's so many subscriptions.
Oh my God. Uh, but all in all, I hope that Saturday's fun.
It seems to be that there will be a lot of interesting things to do.
We'll see. See you Saturday. Take care of yourselves. Archaeology. Wonders of archaeology.
Uh, raid? Uh, yeah. Who's, who's, let's see. Who's live right now? Or maybe we,
maybe we picked somebody we've never raided before. Maybe. Let's see who's live. Uh,
hmm. Time for, time for networking Andy.
Or somebody we haven't raided. You know, we haven't, we've not raided, uh, critical in a long
time. What are you doing? The big man is here. It's been a very long time. Go say hello to moist
critical. And no raid song, no raid song shit anymore. No more, no more raid songs. Charlie's
going to look over and he's going to be like, what the fuck are you guys talking about? He's
going to be like, shut up. He's going to be like, what are you talking about? So many people have
no idea what you guys are talking about. And then I, and then I have to figure out how am I going
to like cover for you guys. Oh, hey, uh, yeah. I mean, uh, we're just getting around. Uh, we're
just like funny, you know, having fun. I told you, I got a DM one time that was just like,
don't you fucking ever do that again. Now go, go say hello to, uh, critical. I just type slash
moist slash moist. It's not what I want it to slash raid moist. Okay. I'll see you guys on,
uh, let me make sure I get it right. I'll see you guys on Saturday. Have a good day. Have a good
night. Goodbye. See you soon. Why is it going so fast? Why is it going so fast? Why is it going
so fast? Why is it going so fast? Oh, I thought it was about to count. I thought it was counting
down. Did you see that? That was like a five second timer. That was weird. Maybe you guys
didn't see it on your end. Maybe I saw it on my end. I'll see you later. Get this rate to 8k. Come
on. Get this rate to 8k. Come on. No, I'm good. Just 8k. Come on. I'm not clicking it till you do
it. Don't embarrass him. Don't embarrass me. All right. Goodbye guys. See you soon. Take care
of yourselves. Goodbye.