Hey, what's going on everybody? Uh, Jerma here with a Terraria gameplay. Hi! Uh, we're gonna finish
Terraria tonight, today. Knew that was coming. Yeah, I'm pretty predictable. Uh, we're gonna finish
Terraria. At least the base game, Star and I. Uh, this is, might be a shorter stream. I wouldn't
lock yourself in like the last couple streams for eight hours or so. We're gonna finish the game,
chill, and see what happens after that. We'll see. I will give an update on the activity book,
which has been pushed because obviously I wanted more time people to do stuff. We'll talk about
that after Terraria. Gonna be a chill stream. I think he's trying to talk to me, but I told him
I do a full five minute broadcaster intro. I can see the thing lighting up on, uh, on Discord. He's
trying to talk to me. What is it? I saw your thing lighten up. I thought you were trying to
get a hold of me. Oh no, I was talking to the people and telling them that it feels like I
threw my left arm out, but I haven't used my left arm for like a year, so I don't know what's wrong.
Sleep on it wrong? And then you told me to take some glycycerols. That's not what I said.
Hypoglycerin? No, that's not correct. That's incorrect. What did you tell me? I told you.
Glucosamine and chondroitin. Oh, what does that do? Where do I get it? You get it anywhere.
It's good for your joints. It's good for your cartilage. Oh, it's not even that. My chat's
telling me it's cancer. I don't think I would just always take care of your health. It's important.
For your health. But we're going to beat this game. Are we? Yeah. Didn't you tell me this is
going to be like... Are you stuck in the room? No, I'm doing my intro. No, you're stuck in the room.
What do you mean stuck in the room? You're stuck in the room. You'll know when you get to the game.
I'm in the game. You're stuck in the room. How did I get in here? I don't know. Well, I know how to
get out. You would destroy that house for your own gain. You're free. You're free. Get out quick.
This is your chance to get out. He's a fucking monster. Get out quick.
Yeah, that's why I cut their ears off. You're a sick fuck. All right. So where do we go from here?
What was the last thing we did three years ago? Where are we? I don't know. Last thing I remember
is you built an entire teleporting around town tunnel system. Oh, yeah. Hey, welcome to episode
number 74 of Let's Play Terraria. I built these teleporter pads to give us a little bit of an
easier time getting around. You just stand on top of the teleporter and you right click the switch.
Hey, look, and we're at the dungeon. This is actually the next boss. Oh, nice. So I helped
with this if anyone's curious. Oh, yeah. Jerma did this one. He gets full credit. I was about
placement. I was saying, hey, we should probably put them in different places. I looked up some
stuff about Terraria. I wanted to be prepared for this stream. So I said some of the teleporters
should be in front of the new bosses. Some should be in other areas that are involved in the plot
of the game too. So we can see the story play out the plot. Yeah, the plot. What's the plot so far?
Just to catch everyone up. So you get dropped off outside. Are we going to fight it? We're going to
and when you dropped off outside, there's you have to use an island situation, I think.
Yeah, because this is an island, right? I mean, it could be. It could be. I mean, the whole goal is
we're just trying to figure out why we're here and how to get out. Yeah. And you have to build
the spaceship to get off. Yes. Because we're about halfway done with the spaceship. But first,
we need to kill the cultists while the Martians invade. OK. OK, that will make this harder.
Oh, I remember this. Remember when I went, whoa, what the fuck, dude,
something just happened, man. So it's been like three weeks since we last played.
How do you keep asking? Like, oh, my God, I clicked out of the window.
You keep asking, like, when are we done? OK, well, we kill this boss and then there's one
more and then we're done. So hopefully we can end this stream in 20 minutes because this.
What do you mean ended in 20 minutes? I think that's what the fans want. Oh, shit. Let's heal.
I got it. H. I mean, I've played this game before. Am I missing him?
I know you guys are your guys are all getting them. All right. He's almost at 28 percent. I see.
He's up. He's that one. Oh, I can feel the DPS. Three percent, one percent dots.
Game's over. We didn't do this. No, what's here? Here's what here's what you're going to look at.
You press anything on the map. Yeah. Uh huh. You see on the on the top of the map,
there's these icons for the nebula pillar. There's these different pillars.
Actually, there's one in our base. Everyone's dead again. Everyone's dead.
Huh? And we go home and everyone will be dead. That's just a fact because the pillar spawned
on our base. Once we destroy all four of those pillars, you immediately fight the final boss
and then we're done. It doesn't take like a while. It could take a very long time to do this.
You know, got any like side tracking stories and like what happened moments
we could do while we dig down for an hour and 25 minutes? Well, they're supposed. Oh,
actually the Martians are also at our base. Here's let's say let's take this teleporter
if you're ready for like pure chaos. Is it going to be pure chaos? Uh, if you fly higher than like
six feet, you'll die. What? Because of this pillar. Just on that. There's these things that fly around
in the sky that don't want you to fly. Oh, okay. Going good. So don't jump in the air.
You see like the worms in the sky? They like one shot you if you go too high. Oh, God. What if I
I don't know what fucking heal is. Turma. Turma. I tried Z. What if I rebounded like a month ago
and I don't even remember what the fuck I bound it to. Oh, God. That is over here, isn't it? That's
scary. So, oh, and the Martians. So what do we need to focus on here? After you kill like I think
it's 150 of the solar enemies, then you can destroy the pillar. You kill 150 enemies? Yeah.
Mage one trick the wizard. What the fuck?
Okay. Mage one trick the wizard. Is one trick their nickname? I don't know. Apparently,
he's only good at being a mage. I mean, that would be good enough for me. Get out of here. Get out
of our base. And as soon as we destroy the pillar, like a UFO is gonna show up.
I don't even know what's happening. Dude, I'm about to drive through today.
You never believe what happened. What happened at this drive? I had this dream.
I had this dream that I was at the drive through. Just so you get the full terraria experience.
I'll let you pick those up. Yeah. What is it? What is it? I'll allow it. Pick up what?
Where the pillar was, there's a whole bunch of solar fragments and they wow, dude. Wow. Do they
sure? Do they craft some stuff? Actually, can't we not do that yet? Because they don't have the
ancient manipulator. Well, I mean, to be fair, you did like delete a mod or two from the game,
so I don't even know some items don't exist anymore. I'm getting like chunk errors.
Are you though? Yeah, I am. No, I'm picking them up. You guys thought that was a joke. No,
I have like errors in my inventory. Well, German didn't summon all these Martians.
And some angels. Oh, yeah. Oh, he's playing the playing the fool. I see. What the hell is it?
What is this thing? Where does this teleporter go to? Which one? The one that's like underneath
the Marsha. All right. There's the saucer. OK, attention span for that teleporter gone.
One of them goes down to the midway point of all the shitty NPCs and the other one goes all the
way down to hell. Oh, you really did like do all of that, huh? Yeah. And then one of them goes to
the jungle and one of them goes to the dungeon. Game's over. Not yet. First, we have to kill
Naruto and then Bardo comes for revenge. Oh, a lot of help. Watch out for this UFO. I see it.
Watch out for the UFO. Close the door. Let my minions do it.
I want to fight. Was that with UFO? OK, by you. It's dead. Nice work. Dang.
Oh, there's a bunch in the background. You can shoot those for me.
All the UFOs in the background? Yeah. Dude, this is like just I'm burning so much
mana with this weapon. I need to get rid of this thing. It's good. But did you did you get the
the ice frost summon staff that I told you to get a good boy?
Before the screen started, I was like, hey, German, you're going to need to get this.
It's very good at this stage of the game. I've got the frost staff on right now.
Use it.
Oh, they're all dead. No, they're not. Oh, I thought it was going to drop by everybody.
What's not fighting me? What's it doing? It's over here trying to shoot me desperately.
It's dead. All right, we got it. Is there going to be another one? There's two.
This one is smarter. It's holding down left mouse button. They don't understand.
Get the car key. Yeah, get the car key. I got a swimmer. That guy, he knows what he's talking about.
I got a key. All right. Use the car key. Do I get to go? Wait, you tell me I get to fly
and get the fly in a car. You stole an UFO. Well, hold on. Once he's done,
he just spawned right on top of those. Oh, whoa. He just one hit killed me with that.
Yeah, that does a lot of damage. Now, you know, it's for next time. All right.
For next time. Yeah, because we're starting a new run, right? It's been a while since we last
played. I think it's just better off we start from the beginning. I already have 380 health.
Oh, yeah, there's in the storage, there's life fruits and you should be able to get to 400.
I don't remember because I took off the mod where we died.
How did I just click out of the window? Why is that possible?
I feel like I'm getting hit and it takes me like two hits to die here.
That shouldn't be happening, right? Well, you do have summoner armor, so maybe
that's that's kind of is what happens, but it's unfortunate, but my summons are so cool
that it's worth it. There's so much random shit on the ground. I don't know what any of
this does, but I'm going to get it. I guess the there's like, use, use your UFO. Okay. Well,
hold on. Are we safe or where's that car key? Okay. Cosmic car key summons a rideable UFO.
Yeah, use your UFO. I'm going to keep saying it until you laugh. So like just laugh and get it
over with. Oh, what a nice UFO. Wow. This is last forever? Yeah. Really? Yeah. So I just get to be
Bowser the rest of the game. This is great. All right. I'm never taking this off. You can't drop
any Koopas though. That's all right. I'm never coming out of this seat. I'm going to be like
fucking crank for the remaining times we played this game. All right. What about your old
case? It's a mouth slot. What does it blessed apple unicorn? It's not a UFO. So who cares?
That's true. All right. This is important though. There's a lot of so many things that are
overwhelming my brain. All right. I'm going to get um, is the staff anti-gravity anti-gravity hook?
Does that ring a bell? Anti-gravity hook. I think it's just a hook. Is it a cool hook? Is it better
than what I think I have? It's the one I think I have. I don't know what I think you have.
Come on. I can't get in here. Bullshit. Let me, let me do this. Where's Mr. Craft?
The German has finished telling the dream. What dream? I don't even remember you saying
there was a dream. Alpha ray and two wingman, 15 dark sun fragments, a genesis and a galactica
singularity. Yeah. Damn it. I can't do that. I already told the dream story. I told the whole,
I had like three, I had a full dream thing like two days ago. I already told it. Oh, I was doing
a, I was like running like the previously on German nine eight five, like two or three streams
ago. All right. Let me do the thing that I always do. And that is just, I don't care.
Tell dream or riot. I'm sorry. I have to, I just, that's what I do. I deposit all.
I mean, at this point, at this point, who gives a shit doesn't matter. Doesn't matter. And I gotta
say, I played, I told you, I played through a game with Ashley and she really wasn't better than you
about sticking random shit right in the storage. I thought she knew better. And yet we had like
40 slots filled with banners. Look, we don't know what's good and not good. We just want to make
sure that we have everything we have at all. All right. Did anything, what was I trying to do?
I was trying to make something. I'm trying to make something for
someone's, the legendary valor for to assault enemies and blow them away.
Well, you're going to want the legendary valor for what the fuck is the valor for
what the fuck? I didn't know I had this guy. It's a Pokemon. I think I gave that to you.
Why can I, I'm a, I'm a, I'm a summoner. Why can I not have like five of these?
I think it's only one for that one item. I told you to get the, the ice frost thing from this guy.
Look from, yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Get the ice frost. I'm not the cryogenic frost cryogenic staff.
I need some money. I got plenty of that. Like 20 platinum in there. Okay. Is this better than my,
is this better than my like Lovecraftian guys? Someone's an animated ice concert to protect you
fire and why do I know what, why do I want this annoying cryogenic staff? Yeah. So I have to
reroll this because it sucks. All right. Okay. So whenever you want to, whenever you want to beat
hurtful cryogenic staff, let's go. Fuck. I said, I wasn't going to make that a thing on the channel
and it's like too late. So what the fuck is this? This is, this is like, this is not a summon. It's
a century. I like all this stuff. This is cool. This thing takes too much mana. I don't like it.
I'll like have to switch to it randomly. I do like this thing though. All right.
Um, I'm ready to do whatever you want to do. I know. Let me get all my summons and let's replace
this. Then I could go, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing. Okay. All right. What do I got for potions?
32, 14. Oh, where's the, uh, you said there was, um, something to heal me to give me more health or
something more max health. Is there something in the inventory? Oh, I pressed the letter L so I
muted. I'm sorry. Um, what's the, uh, in the inventory? What? Uh, you said there was something
in the inventory. I said there was something in the inventory for max health. Oh, life fruits,
life fruit. So I just take, take all this. I can just take all these you're saying I'm going to
take them all. I'm eating all the fruit. Is that all right with you? Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Use them.
Oh, why is it not working? Don't throw it. Oh yeah. Good job. Way to go. Take one first.
You're looking healthier already, buddy. You muted again. How is that possible? I didn't press L.
Well, you know what? You know, if you don't want to talk to me, that's fine. I need to have 400
health to be able to eat these. Oh, you need life crystals? I think because I turned off the other
goofy thing. You turned off the mod. See? Okay. There's, there's 23 life crystals in here. You,
you've got it. Oh, it's cause I'm pressing L. Yeah. I'm pressing L for life crystal.
Oh, that's, that's funny. All right. So take these. Now I'm at 400. Can I? All right. Now take these.
There we go. That's better. That's what I'm talking about there. I'm good. I'm ready to go.
Ready to go beat the game. I'm ready. It's ready to go beat the game. That's it.
Okay. On the map, let's uh, hey, hey, let's use the new teleporter system. Wait, I want potions.
Where's the potion guy? Is the potion guy dead? Is it Howard? It's Howard, right? No.
I don't think the potion guy's alive. Hold on. I think there's a different one
because I got a better potion mod, but I think he's like way downstairs. Oh, did you move somebody?
Getting to the bottom of this. You made all these teleporters on my instructions, of course,
but you made these teleporters and I don't think you remember what you did.
You talking shit? Yeah. All right. I'll just delete the teleporter. He thinks he's at the end.
Oh, hello. You think we care for him or not? I didn't, I didn't talk about, but it's like funny.
So like a few weeks ago when we were trying to figure out like, hey, when do you want to do this
again? You had already played through like a full another time, like on expert. Yep. Me and me and
Ashley, we had a, we had a hankering for some more Terraria and we played on Revengeance Expert and
beat like the whole thing. And then it like that same week, he was supposed to play Terraria with
me on like baby mode. And you were like, do you still like want to do this? And I'm like, yeah.
You're like, you sure like, you don't want to like, you're not sick of that or anything. And I'm like,
no, I like this game. Fun. Well, you know what? Yeah. I don't know if the NPCs on didn't yet
with the potions. This is good because I can't die. I can no longer die from fall damage. So what?
I don't have potions, whatever. Screw it. Let's go. Have you played Super Mario RPG?
Uh, a long time ago. Stream it tomorrow. Oh, that teleporter goes right into the other one.
Dude, I planned this so well. Whoa. What a God. He knew. What is this thing here?
Isn't that a pillar? Yeah, there's four of them. I'll have you know throughout our entire
Terraria playthrough where me and Ashley beat the game together. Uh, most boss fights we quoted
a classic drama quote. Isn't building this platform cheating? What do you mean? What is that? What do
you mean classic? That's the one thing I took away from us playing together is that building
platforms to fight bosses is cheating. I didn't know. I think you would, I think you would really
think it was funny. The one thing that we built, there's a, you remember the giant mech head,
the skeleton head with the big arms swinging around. So we made a giant railroad in the sky
that goes on a diamond and it goes too fast. So he can't catch you and he just stays in the middle
spinning and actually had so much defense. We can only do one damage to him. So he AFKed
until it was dead for like 30 minutes.
That's so stupid. Why am I fighting ice with ice? Isn't that a mistake? I don't know. Yeah,
I think you're healing them. I love being Bowser. This is great. I would have died like three times
by now. Ow, don't kill me. Come on. Dude, heal. What's the heal button? Press L. I do. I just get
hurt. I get killed so I get hurt. When anything touches me, it does like six hearts. Maybe you
should get armor. This is your doing. You said be the summoner so I can have constant DPS because
I don't trust you. You can focus on dodging because you don't have to attack. David, I want to attack.
Just dodge. Just dodge. I died. Or you can just always use that teleporter to get right back.
Which teleporter was it? I forget. The one on the roof. Yeah, I get confused if my enemies are not
projectiles or if they're my projectiles. Whose projectiles are who? It's almost over. You can go
back to your Mario RPG. Don't even talk shit about Mario RPG. So how many times do you jump on an
enemy's head before they die? You do the chain combo jumps when you attack. You just sit there
and hit a 20 chain. Everyone else is doing the sleep phase. You turned the stream on for five
minutes when I was trying to do the ultra achievement. Why do you know that? Because
I said I played it a long time ago. Did you ever do the 100 super jumps in a row? I don't think so.
I think I actually didn't play it and I watched my brother play it if I had to guess. I almost
had a meltdown trying to get it. I got to like 38 without like save states. You ever play Vagrant
Story? No. Very good game. It's the Dark Souls of before Dark Souls was a thing. For the PS1,
I would recommend it. I mean, you like old games. I do. It also has the Super Mario RPG mechanic
where if you hit and you attack, you know, you can do another attack. Timed hits. Yeah. Very good.
Very, very good. Cool. You know, I'm just going to wait 30 more years for the roadmap and we can
all enjoy it because it's really awkward. There's like no sound in the game. There's no sound.
There's sound, but it's it's like PS1 era and everyone has a square face and there's no actual
voice dialogue. It just everything's really quiet and claustrophobic. Anyway,
we're going. We're going back to the base. We got to go the other direction for the other pillars.
How many more pillars are there? Two. And then after we do the two pillars, we then combine them
all. Your mind goes blank. You're not sure what's coming. But the stir told me it's the Moon Lord
and he then you got to fight him. So I teleported back within the thing and yeah, I can't get out
now. I'm stuck again. I need to rebuild this. Oh, don't worry. That person has a clone.
We just made them meet for the first time and look at this. They're like, oh my God, are you me?
What was in the prison cell next to you the whole time? How long have you been here for?
God, I've seen maybe two or three years. They got a lot to talk about. So that I'm okay with that.
No, unfortunately, they don't count as rooms anymore and they're both going to escape. Good.
Good. They'll have their own like fucking Nickelodeon TV show. All right. You ready?
They'll be on Cartoon Network. All right. I'm yes, I'm ready. How about for Moon Lord? Like I don't
attack him. I just like let you do it. No, that's not fair. Oh, easy. He jumped. Just I'll just
I'll play support. No, I'm going to do the technique where I just don't. I just run around. I
just don't try not to get hit. Actually, I think Moon Lord, I think you outrun him with the UFO
like very slightly. I can't remember. I can always build a railroad for space, but I think that's
cheating. Space railroad. That sounds kind of fun. Yeah, I'm just trying not to get hit. If I get hit
three or four times, I'm dead. What is that light steel? Is it life leech in this game?
Oh, there's one really dumb accessory that I'm using that for you, man. It's really easy to
get item and it's the best item in every mod I've played. You take you take like 50% more damage,
but when you take 25% more damage, but under 50% health, you have 25% light steel.
As long as you're shooting, you don't die. That's pretty awesome.
Yeah, it's like if you just want to like vegetate out. Whoa, whoa, get off me.
It's really the go-to. Somebody said fighting Moon Lord with ancient ice chunk and they said
not like this. What is that? Why is that a bad thing? They seem to think so, but it's normal.
Okay. Before we do the last pillar, we can actually go do a boss and we'll get you a better
summon. Oh, what? Watch out. Watch out. All right. I'm going to dodge. Am I like shut off? Why can
I not do anything? What's wrong with me? Some enemies have a debuff that'll disable your UFO.
This guy might have it. I have my summons. I'm just trying to avoid it. No. Oh, please. No,
don't kill me. They're like in the background. Thank you. They're in the background of my game.
It's funny. Like I'm pretending I can be hurt. It's for the stream. Wait, how did I end up this
far away from you? Oh God. Where's the closest teleporter? Uh, you can open the map and teleport
to me. I can be hurt. What just happened? Uh, and then you click on me if you have the potions.
Why did I end up here in funky town? How did I end up in funky town? I'm just going to fucking
fly to you. I'm coming home. Am I not gaining? Okay. So you press the M. I don't know. I don't
have a port to me. I don't have the potions. Are you teleport to funky town? I teleported to funky
town and that was like the checkpoint for me to get over to you. What is this? Another one.
Okay. There's another guy over here. There's a, I just, I think I just, I'm gonna, I got bad news
for you. Um, bringing over the last pillar. Uh, the part of the move. Oh, I don't kill it. I'll be
there in like 10 seconds. Just dodge, dodge, dodge. Don't kill it. 0.1. If I stop shooting,
I can take damage. Hold on. Hey, can you see my fire? Am I getting close? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You got it, dude. That hit it. Did I get it? Yeah. What are you kidding me? Oh my God. I'm making a
montage just for that. I hit it from all the way back here. Dude. That's fucking awesome. Are you
serious? That's probably, I mean, has anyone ever done something like that before? Are we
summoning a boss here? Are we going to fight the, um, the teller? Hold on. Um, we can, we can also
make, hold, hold on. A lot of things are happening right now. Here. Okay. Here. Here. Now that guy
can stop laughing at you because you have a new summon staff. Say they left. They're gone. Oh,
that guy. They're going to, they're going to find themselves. Oh, that's great. No, not the guy in
chat. The two people. What two people? You don't even, how do you not remember that thing, that
really weird, fun thing that happened like less than five minutes ago? The thing you sent me?
Yes. Okay. So I started a cell staff, so I'm replacing this. Let's check this out. Oh, this is
the, uh, this thing that I gave the materials for last time, right? What? You have to unsummon your
other things. And where are they? All right. So I'm just a bubble guy now. Yeah. Now you're a bubble
guy. Yeah. Last time we played, I looked up some stuff on the Wikipedia and I said, like there was
some summons that I thought were cool. And I was like, what materials do we need? And I got some
off stream and then I just like, I'm just going to leave them in the box and next time we'll figure
it out. So you just, you just made it for me now just to kind of speed things up. So
all right. What else did I get? Astral Bulwark. $10 to kick Yerma from the server. It's not enough.
$10 to kick me from the server. You're going to have to add like five zeros. Yeah. How come
all of my donations are to ask Yerma things? That's what all mine are too. I don't even,
I don't even like this guy. Boy, that wasn't me. All right. So I want to, I want something
else besides the snowstorm staff. Maybe I should just put the zealous thing here and just use that.
I'm going to give that a try. That sounds like a lot of fun. Shut up. Shut up. What? It's in my
brain. What is in your brain? What are you talking about? Do you have any meld blobs?
Metal blobs? Meld blobs. What do they look like? Purple blobs. I should have way more of them.
Purple blobs. Oh wait, no, that's right. You have the thing that's like,
Hey Star, just wanted to ask you a question. You have one of those, don't you? I do. Star,
don't act like he doesn't have a name. Oh, you have one of those? That's very disrespectful.
I want to look, what can I make? I want to see what I can, can I turn this into something?
Yeah. What can I turn this into? All right. I can make Kevin's catalyst, which is
rogue damage. Now this is all melee damage and shit. There's actually a lot of things we can make
right before the end here because now we also get astral ore. You know what astral ore gets you?
What is that? Okay. Wait, first of all, I am going to get potions out of that inventory.
Inventory? Okay. I gave you $25, now kick Yerma. No, that's, he said like three zeros,
wasn't it? I mean, that's like, you're going to have to give Star like 10 grand to get rid of me.
Yeah. I mean, that's how much he's given me to play with him. So competing against a lot here.
Oh, here's $15. Okay. All right. So I want to do, what did I want to do? Potions.
Right. All right. Did you use the life fruit after you used the things you did, you know that?
I got 425. Yeah. One of these give me no mining potion. No, wouldn't have potion. No,
archery potion. Don't want it. Water walking, night owl, shine. All these potions suck. What
are you putting in here? Um, um, um, um, um, um, um, I wish we had a potion person so we could do
this. You told me that the guy was a new potion mod guy, but I don't think he showed up yet.
Excuse me for you adding and deleting mods. Fix those rooms. Actually, I think there's enough
empty ones. No, just fine. I'll fix it. Thank you. There's enough. Wait, don't be in it.
Shit. All right. Bubbles, get out of the way. All right. I fixed the room. Well, let's go here.
I've got my bubbles. I wish I had those potions. The potions really did help me so much. Um,
you know, we're just going to sit around and wait and tell some stories.
What stories do you have for me? All right. My arm, my shoulder really hurts. Well,
you have any recommend what I could have for this? Yes, I do. Well, I'm being dead serious now.
Is it like your like, like rotator cuff? Or I don't know what that means. Is it your shoulder?
Is it the like the joint inside your shoulder? Is it the muscle? Is it?
How did you sleep last night? If it helps, I can also dislocate the shoulder like on command.
You might have something. There might be something going. You might need to see. Um,
you might need to get, take, get that taken a look at. Oh, well, I've been able to do that
since I was like, like four years old. Oh, okay. But still, some, uh, the other kid,
he dragged me across my porch because we were playing a game and it pulled out of the socket
and it hurt a lot. But now I can just like pop it out and it's like whatever. You were playing a
game. Yeah. And it was what the fuck are you talking about? I was playing a game when I
was like four years old and the other kid was dragging me by my arm. What game requires you?
I can't remember. I was like four. I don't remember the game. It was some stupid game.
Okay. Checkers. Yeah. We're playing like checkers. Yeah. Yeah, it was checkers. I think actually.
All right. Oh, but anyways, um, now if you haven't like joint problems, joint pain,
I would, I would see a physician about it, but you might consider taking that. Then you might
consider taking some glucosamine, chondroitin compound. Should help a little bit. Okay. Yes,
I am not a doctor. Can you spell that for me? It's just like it sounds. Uh, try to spell that
for me. Okay. Okay. One more time. Glucosamine, chondroitin. What the hell is this? Strange plant.
Nice. What is the strange plant? That's like a, you turn the game on and you can find those
in the dirt like at minute one. Hey star, you should tell Jerma he don't need to pick up strange
plants. God, he's so dumb. No, they're not mean to you. Star. I don't think in your whole life,
no one's ever been mean to you. I don't know how you do it. How do you do it, man? What the heck is
that? That's just your Trump. No, it's not.
That's just, no, it's not. You guys need to get your ears cleaned. Yeah, guys. Come on. No,
I was wondering what's going on here. All right. You ready? Um, not yet. Cause I think it might be
a huge problem. Where is my, he's ready. I'm ready. No, I'm not. Where the fuck is my staff
that summons these things? Did you put it in? Did you auto-stash it? No, I got it. Here's a random
staff. Wait, no, where the fuck is it? Why is snowstorms staff here? I didn't do anything.
What the hell is this? No, what happened to my staff that summons the bubbles? What is going on
right now? What did I, did I do something? What did I do? You probably, okay. No, no, no. Yeah,
I did. I did. All right. We're good. Okay. We're going to, we're going to skip everything. Skip
everything. Why everything? We're going to, we're going to skip everything. Come up here.
Actually, I need potions for this. Don't you wish you could have potions for this?
Hello. Hello. What are you doing? Hello. Star is going to carry Jerma. I hope you guys understand
that this entire Terraria, Jerma, and Star play. Yeah, that's right. I'm on the front of the ticker.
This entire Jerma and Star play Terraria has been Star showing me this game while I sit behind him
in the chair and watch him play. Yeah. He just has an in-game point of view. And it's been great so
far. We should totally have this NPC by now. It's this, no, it's not this guy. This guy sells life.
Here, Carl. It's not Carl. I mean, you've been doing a whole lot of just interesting things.
No, get away. Get the fish. Wow. I just saved that goldfish's life.
Oh, this is Lucy. This is the person. She was here the whole time. You're the backseater while
Chad is the third guy across the room playing Fortnite. Jerma, get over here on Lucy. Lucy.
Time to get them all. Thorn's potion. Get two of them. Who cares? We got platinum.
There is a server crash if one of us is talking to her and you change which shop it is.
What? I'm not going to touch anything then. I'm just going to buy the things I know I want.
Okay. Okay. This is just, okay, here we go. Max number of minions. Get a few of those.
I need more money. Don't touch me. There's a bunch of platinum in there. Yeah. Yeah, there is.
Here comes the crash joke. Are you talking to Lucy right now?
Okay, you're not. Whoops. What? Are you? I just, I'm in, I am in Lucy's menu right now.
Don't do anything. This place is crazy with all this fungus. You know what I'm saying?
Hey Jerma, you know what I'm saying? City and skin. I want mana regeneration. More than that.
Titan. Battle? No. Hey Jerma. Max life? You're muted. I must have pressed L. I apologize
profusely. Do you know what I'm saying? Say it again. I don't know what you said. No.
Okay. I am ready to do whatever it is you want to do. I'm ready to see the end game.
One second. Okay, so this boss is from Thorium Mod and it's supposed to be fought after Moonlord,
but for some reason they decide it like, if you die they don't want it to despawn,
so it's really easy because it just never goes away. Okay. So it gives ridiculous absurd items
where you don't have to think anymore. You just put all the items on. Nice. So if you don't want
to think, all you got to do is beat like a three-stage boss. Okay. Was that it? The Simon says that
you just put down? Only usable at night. I think it's about to be night. How good are you at Simon
says? I'd say I'm Simon, right? How good am I at Simon? Yeah, the thing with like the five lights
and it goes, Oh, red light, green light. No, you have to like stop when the person says red light.
No, you have to listen. And then you put your thumb up. You have to match it.
I win. Okay. So I'm pretty good. Okay. Fine. You think you're so fucking hot. Here we go.
Okay.
It's getting harder.
Not bad. You got it.
Hmm. Somebody's a little smarter than I thought.
All right. Close. That was it. Let's go. I win. I messed him up. I win. No, you ripped the
batteries out of the machine. That doesn't count. Oh, come on. Oh, come on. He's broken. It's broken.
What's going on? I think it's broken. I told you, you broke it. You pulled the batteries.
You can't pull the batteries out. Where'd you go? Do you just have like a notepad full of like
time fillers that you can do in any game? Like just in case something goes awry. I got it.
I got to fill some time here. Yeah. Yeah. You're very good at it. I'll give you that. Okay.
What one's nighttime? Is it 6 PM guys? Is that when mom calls you in for dinner? I don't know.
That's not on my notepad. I only know what's written down on my second monitor. Okay. Well,
what's next on the script? Wouldn't you like to know? Magician never gives away his script.
Okay. Ma says we can stay out till 7 30. It's a five of 43 PM right now. You mean secrets.
That is that's a script. I'm going to just walk somebody here. What are we doing?
We're waiting for nighttime. It's almost nighttime. Is that another hour? Time goes by fast. But not a
real hour. There's a there's items to like switch it tonight, but I can't remember. What are your
computer specs? I don't know. I got a Dell. I have a gateway PC. You know, those like $245
cow machines. They didn't even come with a fucking CPU. I don't know what's up with our health. I
don't know why I have 540. I don't know what happened. It is now 7 PM. That's nighttime,
right? We need it to be 7 PM. TTS. When is sundown? Star. Sundown is at 7. Hey, how could you even get
in on the wow classic thing? You have like five seconds to answer before like an end game.
Okay. So I, okay. I already did it. Here's your answer. That's a really good answer. I'm glad that.
All right. Here we go. Oh my God. All right. Pay attention to this.
You're gonna have to do this back to me. It's Simon. You're gonna have to do it back to me.
Okay. Okay. Just do something. I don't think you understand what I'm saying. I'll try.
Was that good? Oh, I dropped 32 gold. I'm sorry. 32 gold is not a lot. It's a lot.
Well, that is not good against enemies that move quickly. Oh, these aren't moving fast.
Surely you're getting eaten alive down there. I know. I can't do it. I'm like, I'm just like,
who? I may as well just be walking into the towers. I'm surprised you're not writing in chat right
now. Oh, dude, I almost got my adrenaline meter. I've almost got revensions. I'm going to stay in
here. What are you doing over here? He's being useless. Ooh, that was a pretty good setup there.
I'm probably shouldn't, maybe I shouldn't go in the air. I'm like, they hit faster than me.
UFO has a little flow in some spots, but this is also, I think you and Ashley, I want to build
the thing just to show you the stupid circle mine cart that confuses every boss.
Get out of the fucking baby trolley. All right. Oh God.
This is the expert level. And you know, there's a YouTube video of a guy doing this
and his hands are just like around the whole Simon. Can they chase you for a second so I
can switch my arrows? Sure. I'll go like this. Thank you. I am very pleased. I'm very happy to be
the rock that you threw to distract the enemy. I don't know what you did, but it worked for a
second. I didn't think it would be possible. It's like a ghost in here. What is even fucking in here?
Stop, leave me alone. Get it again. I spawned, they spawned in here.
What was that? So that was like a car accident. Is it safe to come back? Don't worry,
Jerma. It's not much longer. There we go. There we go. There we go.
I love your one little Pokemon still blowing wind down there.
I just get hit and die. I can't avoid damage. I just get hit three times and explode.
This is really my fault. In the past, for like most other streams, I would have prepared you for
this. But it's like the finish line is right there and my little brother just tripped and it's like
I'm looking back, but I'm still running forward. Yeah. And I'm really hurt too. No, brother,
little brother, give me that back. Not only did I fall down, I got very seriously injured.
There's another phase. I don't think it happens. My leg is going the other way and you're all just
like, ah, okay. No, but seriously drop those. All of it? Yeah. This is a stick up. And then,
okay. I'll give you what you need. We're at the finish line and I just saw you trip,
but I don't care and I didn't prepare you. Hey, hey, hey, come here, come here, come here.
Didn't that- You're taking one of these. Didn't that happen like three streams ago, by the way?
I think I've had a broken leg just sitting there since like we fought the fucking plant boss.
A broken leg? Yeah. You know, I'm bringing up your like running the race joke. No, I agree.
This happened like two streams ago. We hit plantera and I was just like, okay. Like I have a-
Oh, fuck. I pressed B for backpack and I'd B for drink all potions.
Yeah. You did just drink all your potions.
Oh, my leg. Big butter. Big bit of my leg. You're going to have to pick me up.
And that's, that's for you too. What the fuck is this? This is like the best item I've ever seen.
Yeah. What is this stuff? It's like I said, that's supposed to be the final boss of thorium
and it's not that hard and it just keeps- It's like, here's the end of the game. Here,
have some goofy end game items that you can craft immediately. And-
What? I can have like 10 of these? Yeah. Now you turn into like a superhero.
Where are the armor? No. Okay. Where are the armor? I'm- I know.
I- I- It also makes you bind a special key that I don't think you have bound or you'll
have to check in the options if you have it. Molten banner. I'm holding this banner. What the
fuck? 25%. What do I get for this? Set bonus. Pressing the special ability key will unleash
an echo of slag fury's power. It's like a bonus stationary summon that shoots a million missiles.
Do I even have special bound? Keybinds. Special ability. Where is special ability?
Uh, it would be under thorium. Oh, it's like a mod. Yes. Uh, controls all the way down at the
bottom. Thorium special ability. Thorium special ability. Um, like, I'm gonna, I guess, just,
I'm just, jeez, is that okay? How long- What's the cooldown on this? Uh, it's like a minute.
I don't know. I don't know exactly. I just pressed it. It didn't do anything. It just like
looked like- No, that thing right there is- Oh. Well, there's nothing, there's no enemy,
so it's not shooting. Oh, I see. Cool. All right. Nice. Well, now we can just like sneeze on moon
lord. You want to just sneeze and kill moon lord? Yeah. Ooh, let's go get it. Right. Into the UFO.
Yeah, where's that guy? He's laughing at you for using astral chunks. Where's that guy now?
Yeah, where's that guy? Yeah, my big bro killed Ragnarok for me. Where'd that guy go?
What's your favorite 80s comedy movie? Ignore the pink blocks. 80s Ghostbusters.
That's not a comedy. Is it 80? Was that 88? 89? Was that 90? Might be 99. 91 maybe. You're debating
the wrong thing. It's not a comedy. Yes, it is. What are you talking about? There's not like a
single funny thing in that whole movie. Every single actor in that was a comedian. Wait,
wait, hold on. What did you just say? Quote one funny thing from Ghostbusters. What the hell are
you doing? Okay, I just did that. Anyone laugh? Were there any lulls in your chat? That's an actual
quote from that movie and it's a really funny part of the movie. Those who get it will know.
Are we talking the one where the Ghostbusters were all women or like classic? Dan Aykroyd,
Bill Murray. That died instantly. Yeah, we have really good items now.
Am I not using this? Somebody said use the fire staff. Isn't that the fire staff?
Superior ancient spark? Oh, there was a different like magic attack I could have gotten you. I don't
think I crafted one. Use the molten banner while holding this banner. Wait, that's not like a
Diablo 2 charm. I have to actually hold it out. Watch out, dude. Moon Lord's coming.
Is Moon Lord coming? This is going to be the hardest fight because this is like
end game content. This is Deathwing. That's end game content. Okay, I'm ready. Does he go...
Holy shit, that's actually way crazier than I thought it was going to be.
He's got me. Is he dead? I think so. Oh no, no, he's half. Now you're going to shoot his heart.
Go for the hot. I can't get in close enough. Oh no, he's dead. That was rough. Hey,
give me the freaking Luminite. What are you doing, little bro? Congratulations. You have just beaten
the base game of Terraria. See you guys later. That's it. What do you want? Luminite or Luminite.
Do you want one of my huge... Never mind. Luminite or Celestial Onion. What does it look like?
Shadow Diamond. Yeah, I'm going to give you a hundred beats. Where is it? Luminite or...
What does it look like? Is it portal gum? It's ore, so it looks like a little blob.
Yeah, there's a portal gum. I don't think I have any of this shit. Oh, Luminite. You keep
little brothering and picking it all up. This doesn't look like ore. This looks like trash.
Oh, thank you. Thank you for giving me the trash. Okay, so what's going to happen now, I guess,
is you can tell funny stories and I'm going to speed run the post-Moon Lord content.
What? This is cool. Quick, do the thing. Hold on, I got to do the thing. I got to do the thing.
Wait. No, hold on. Oh, shit. Is he doing something funny?
Yeah, I'm doing the thing that you do with the portal gun in the first 40 minutes of portal.
You figure out you can do that. All right, so you want to speed run the rest of the game?
Yeah, I'm like, I'm just, I'm not going to clue you in.
Well, I'm just going to teleport to you. I'm just going to buy wormhole potions and then teleport
to you. Oh, there's the, there's the original music. It's been a journey. Why are there snowmen with
guns up here? Snowmen, gangsters? It was in my inventory, so I had to get rid of it.
Oh, they're dead. Oh, did I? Oh, that's awesome. That's such a cool enemy. Okay, I'm going to buy
some, I'm going to buy some pots and then I'm coming to you. Did they sell wormhole potions
or do I just have to make them? Right. Do we have any? Well, you can buy them from Lucy,
but you have to send it to store one. So when you talk to her, she says, which shop?
You need it to be classic, like wild classic, you know what I'm saying?
Okay, that's weird, I guess. Strangely enough, I don't know what you mean by that. Reeses.
All right. How do you eat it? Who cares? You sound like someone, but who do you sound like?
Who was that? I should know that was Will Arnett, the Reese's commercial. I thought you guys would
have known what that was. I would make, I would make quasars flair. It's very good. But I gave my
Daedalus Stormbow to my other character. Where the fuck is this wormhole potion? Because I didn't
play for three weeks. I don't have one right now. $50 just came in right now. $50. Thanks for the
$50 AV Joe. And this is for Star. Hey, please tell, uh, hey Sturm, tell, please tell Jar that he's
doing a good job. Glad to see you playing one of my favorite games. Will you be playing it again
when they release mini golf? Is that real? Uh, I will. I don't know if I'll stream it, but I'll
probably play that. Oh yeah. Yeah. Now the answer for me is no. Make sure you catch Star Stream.
Are you said to? All right. Hold on. Shop changer. You said vanilla, right? Yeah.
On Lucy. And what color is the wormhole potion? Um, blue water walking feather fall. Why is there
like a triceratops in here? I'm looking for triceratops. Uh, is that me? I don't know what
that was. Okay. Invisibility, gills, flipper, hunter. I have no idea what that is. It sounds
like I live. I'll be right back. Is that thunder? It sounds like an airplane in my house. Yeah. Go
take a BRB. See what's going on. That sounded like there was like thunder. I don't think it's on
here. Yeah. I think it's, uh, AC one 30 inbound. Uh, excuse me. Yeah. You've got a UAV. All right.
This is way more important. Where is this potion? Oh my God. Am I going to have to like, it's not
on, it's not on vanilla wormhole, wormhole, wormhole, wormhole, wormhole, wormhole, worm, worm, worm,
worm. Oh, you're right. Um, do you see in the underneath way at the bottom, bottom left,
the like bottom, bottom NPC Severus, the alchemist he has. Okay. All the way down there. You have to
make a full metal alchemist reference. I'm not sure. No, I was going to just that was funny for
20 episodes. I was going to scream out, but then I don't think I could do it. I could
What was this guy's name? Severus found an alchemist. Hey, there they are. Good here.
You can have this. All right. I'm ready. I'm not sure.
Very good. I'm hiring you. That was the test one.
That was an elbow chop. All right. So I'm ready. Let's go.
I'm going to be able to do this one more time. Deposit all. Yeah. Nice. All right. So what's the
next thing we're going to do? I teleport to you. Well, I bought 10 of these. So, oh, you must be
rich. You know, for 10 of those is at least five platinum in there, man. No, I didn't get rid of
this stupid thing. This thing's causing me an issue. Is it having an issue right now? That's
better. Now I can do one, two, three, four, five. I can do five of those. Damn. What was I doing?
I need to make the unholy shard. What am I doing? Can I turn this into anything? This staff?
No, this is the ultimate ability. And do something with this? No. So is there any
reason at all to even have a pickaxe at this point? Do we need any? I made the really good
one that we need because there's new or that one, but I'm not making you one.
Don't worry about it. Do I have to activate this or can I just hold it?
Hold what? The big ice cream. You have to hold it. It's very clearly states while held. Yeah,
but I don't know. You don't know what? When I click, it goes, you don't know what? When I click,
it goes, I didn't know if I had to turn it on or something. I don't know. Is there any reason for
at all to have German stars for area speedrun? I don't know. Is there any reason at all for you
to go on like a road trip with your friends or are you just going to go on that road trip by yourself?
Exactly. When you click on an enemy with a banner, it makes your minions target an enemy.
Okay. So there is a point to click. I mean, I didn't know. What am I supposed to know everything?
I don't know. You have, you're the one with like 200 days played in this game.
I didn't, I didn't make a summoner ever. What am I supposed to know these things?
What the fuck was that? That was maybe a real funny guy. So what's the next boss?
Profane guardians. And then we got to kill the profane goddess and we have to kill, um,
uh, the marshmallow man. If I see your sound is muted one more time in this chat, I will,
I'm going to swallow a whole egg. Me? No, mine. What? Oh, what am I doing?
Where's the thing I'm looking for? Tell me where it is.
Oh, I'm sorry. Uh, celestial hill bomber.
Didn't I make the fricking onk on this character? I did. Right?
Before we played the game, you did mention I have too many characters. I don't know who is who.
You did say I don't, but I swear I like farmed and made an onk the last time we stopped playing
and I know, and I just like, don't have it or is, or is this it? I don't know. No.
Why does the music keep getting funky? Oh, because of the mushroom biome that I made above us.
That's onk town wings. I don't feel like making all this stuff. Like I could,
but I've already done this with, I'm just going to, I'm going to go fight things.
So you're going to go fight, we're going, where are you going? To the teleporter?
Oh, he's during the daytime, dude. My God. Like now, now. Hey, I keep forgetting to sleep in the
bed. This is awful. I really am just a little kid in the car. I just have an ice cream in the car.
Don't get it on the seat. I'm getting ready to fight a boss. We got to fight it during the day.
So I'm going to craft the thing that lets me skip the time of day, but I don't remember what I need
to craft that thing. Let's go. Let's go. I'm assuming, I'm assuming souls of a night.
So let me ask you something. We, this is, we've done a, we've beaten Terraria, the base game.
No, yes. What has been your favorite moment from the Star and Jeremy Terraria playthrough?
I told you. What was it? It was when you said, isn't this cheating when we were making platforms
to fight a boss? That's easily my number one takeaway and favorite moment. Cool.
My favorite was learning how to alt click items to not deposit them after 16 hours.
Cool. Mine would be when like for some weird reason, you knew the recipe for the like day
changing item and you told me like how to do it. I did? No, like, no, like right now, if you told
me how to do it, that would be my favorite part. How do I do it guys? How do I do it? How do I do
it? How do I do it? How do I do it? How do I do it? How do I do it? How do I do it? How do I do it?
I'm muted. How do I do it? I'm looking at chat. Someone says it's called Cosmo light. Like how
the hell does that help? If it was me, I would say I'm going to take a guess here. It's a hell stones
and light souls. I don't know. That makes sense. I'm looking to be held by the hand here. I do
have to make moonlight and then I have to make daylight. Moonlight and sunlight, right? Three
sun stones and 22 of the fire spirits from the moon lord. I'm just taking a guess here.
You're wrong. You're wrong. You guys are supposed to get my back here. You're supposed to have my
back. 720 damage. Get you baited. So where are you off to now? I feel like the last like 12 minutes
of this playthrough has been star remembers how to summon things. There's a lot of things
to summon. You're going to fight a boss? Yeah. What the fuck have you not told me this for?
Alright, let's go. Holy shit. This is fun. I like being able to destroy things and then they drop
the profane core which I don't think you can make this like non consumable but I don't think we need
to do. Pretty sure it will be the first time. I'm feeling pretty good about that. So are we fighting
here? Yeah, we're going to fight here. The things that we just fought are adds for the next boss.
Oh jeez. Okay. It's a pretty rough one. Alright, I'm ready. He's fast. He's fast.
He's like flying around in the dirt and I can't shoot him because they're up that high.
What are you doing?
What happened? My little brother shot up and just made it harder. God damn it. I'm just
I don't know where I am. I've lost a dinghy world. Help. Watch you win.
I'm just like I die. So I just I spawn. Hey, I'm going to spawn to you.
How was it? Did you do anything fun? He's dead. Nice. Good job. Thank you.
That was a tough one, huh? That was a tough one. Now, what do we do? When you show up and like take
all of the items again, which is my favorite part and then and what happens next, you know, go on.
I'd like tell you to give it to me. He's going to do it.
Uh huh. I don't even remember what he dropped. I just remember it. It's it's important and you're
just going to like auto stash it and I'm not going to remember what it was. No, I'm going to throw
it to you right now. Oh, this one has summoned damage. Summoned it. Nice. Oh, poop. You're
supposed to fight him in the other area to get the other. There are two items up here. Oh,
shit. Then you get the rune of cost. Look at this. But some say cost them. Get those. I'll wait for
you to get it. Divine Geode. OK, I got a divine unholy essence and a divine. I keep forgetting
to sleep in the bed. And you make fun of me for making mistakes. Yeah, well, that's because you
are more. So is this any good? This Divine Geo. What can I do with this? Let me talk to the guy.
Uh, I think you can chop it up. Yeah. I don't remember. What did you just say?
I didn't say nothing. Hey, defense absorbs 25% damage on players on your team. Only active above
25% life. OK, so it's like you can make armor. 10% increased damage. Any summoning stuff?
What? I'm just thinking if there's anything for summoners here with this Geode.
Unholy Essence. Let's see if I can do that. Profaned Crucible. Oh, we never fought the
Ravager. And now he's buffed because we killed that boss. We had to do the Ravager.
How come you didn't remind me? I don't I don't know what that is. Did you did you get this stupid
snowman staff? Are you snowman? Hail bomber summons kamikaze snowmen that will blow up upon
hitting enemies. I mean, that sounds like I did. All right, I'll try it. Is it a sentry? Does it
replace my cool thing? No, I think I think they're just spells. What? Yeah, they have like a
duration. Oh, OK. That's kind of cool. All right. Where are you off to now? Going to the dungeon.
Going to the dungeon. Why are you going down here? There's a there's a boss down here. There's a lot
of new stuff in the dungeon. There's two bosses down here, actually. Are you snowman? I'm not
snowman. Never dig straight down. I didn't know that. What? You don't take fall damage
because of lava. Oh, I wouldn't see it. You are going so fast. Holy shit. Cool.
Oh, wow. Why are you going that way? I'm clearing space for in case one of the bosses show up.
Oh, hey, German. I need you to just stay here. Stay here. Yeah, I'll be right back for real.
He's never coming back. Is he? Well, how is that not working? OK, I guess this item is dumb.
Now I'm going to go. I'm now fully protected. Fuck. Just kill. OK, are you dying?
No, I just got almost insta killed. Why is this guy so bad? The guy playing, not the character.
That's what I mean. All right. I just almost died instantly by like a fireball. Should that be
happening? Oh, I mean, this this area is a little bit buff, but no. How is it? Yes. I mean, see,
that's understandable. There's a lot of things going on. I just get hit twice and die. That's
what I've been doing for the last like hour and a half. Oh, I died. Shit. That was a that was a big
oof. You know what they say? That was a big oof. That's what they say. You know what I'm saying?
They talk about it. Stop it. Where are you going to the dungeon? I got to pick up all the things.
Wait, how did you go fast? Shit, you're like, oh, I'm just teleporting to you at this point.
Why would I wait? I'm going to get down there. I'm going to get down there when I get here. Finally.
Hey, don't matter how you eat it. It's okay. Okay. Um,
this is scrumptious. What are you up to? No, I don't know. I did. I picked up. Look at all this crap.
I don't even want this stuff. They won't leave me. I don't want it. There's a boss that summons
here, but you have to get like 50 ectoplasms first. 50 ectoplasms. That sounds like a lot of
ectoplasms. Like pink skulls that fly at you. I think appear after you kill enemies sometimes.
And then it's kind of a tough boss and it might kill me, but I kind of want to fight it.
Either that or I can. Oh, hey, you got the portal gun? No, you don't have the portal gun.
I deposited that what seems like a decade ago. Um, go home right now, little bro, because
I need you to get that portal gun for me. Okay, I'm going to get the portal gun.
Make sure you heal up, you know, buy your buff potions. Okay. Okay. What did you need? You need
the portal gun. Anything else while I'm here? I need the portal gun while you're there, bro.
Some people consider using it during a boss fight cheating. Do you? I don't. Why is it? I don't
understand what you mean. How would that be cheating? You know, forget it. Did I already use all my
fucking potions? Well, I'm sorry. I'm coming. Hold on. Let me. I need more potions. Let's get some
magic power. I want some more of these. Okay, that's fine. I want to get. I think I'll put the four.
Whatever. All right. Yeah, I got what you need. Okay. Come give it to me. Portal gun incoming.
Thanks, bro. Here you go. Oh, okay. I was going to entrust the portal gun to you.
No, don't trust me. The damn thing. Okay. Now we find a boss right now. Uh, not yet.
Okay. So you, you go, you go on this side, come out that side. Okay. We might need to make this
wider. You can't go in the portal if you're on your UFO. Right. But what's that? What is it? What
are we doing this for? Why do we have a portal? Because we're going to fight a boss and it's
undodgeable. Undodgeable. It really helps to have. So what you mean just like go in portal and you
end up over here and then do it again. Just run around a circle. Uh, yeah. Like once it comes
towards you, you go in the portal and then when it comes back towards you again, you go to the
portal again. Uh, it's not foolproof. You're, you're going to die, but it'll help. What if I just stand
protected in a manmade house? No. What do you mean? No. I mean, they all go to the walls. Uh,
fantoplasm. No warning. Okay. A like three, two, one would have been slightly helpful.
You know, 2020 hindsight, you should have made it be the guy that has 50,000 HP. Not the guy that
died. It would be really easy to switch to it if you want to. The, um, the armor that we got after
killing Ragnaros, not Ragnarok. Uh, it gives you an armor set for melee and the special ability
button makes you immune for like a couple of seconds. And it also like gives you shields as
you attack. Uh, and also you should have made me blah, blah, blah. Like I didn't make you anything.
You said summoner, you should do it. It's so much fun. And you, you entice me with like fun,
cool little pets. Well, little bro, if you want the melee set, I can make that for you and get you
the life steal item so that you can just swing at things and press the immune button when you feel
scared. Just kidding. It's fine. I'm fine. You sure? That's very good. There's no shame. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Okay. He said no. I lasted a lot longer that time during a blink
twice. Are you actually having fun? I think Terraria is a good game. Does illuminate? No,
illuminate is irrelevant. That was blinked twice. So having fun. So Yolo bloom. And I
forget the other one now. Um, I was rocking on chair. I want to get the other boss to someone.
I just got to kill things. Just kill stuff. Get down there. Get down there and attack that.
You guys are stupid, but when you get down and you finally do something,
imagine being called stupid and it's stupid. Why are you digging? Why can't you just go down?
Why are you doing that? I really like the sound digging mix in Terraria and you got to make
things like, like once you can dig this fast, you got to make things like symmetrical and even.
I just realized you're doing like 700 damage every quarter second. Yeah. No problem, bro.
Yeah, kind of. There's no water candles here. That's what's going on. There's no water cannons.
Also, I'm getting spikes off the walls. Stop touching. You do that per fireball per quarter
per second. You can equip the DPS meter and see what your DPS is. Let's compare it on the next
boss. Do you have one? You should have it showing up on the right hand side because I have one.
Yeah. What do you got? Well, you can also make
target dummies so you can shoot the target dummy. Let's find out. Read this. All right.
Looks like you're sticking around. Oh, no. The little ghosts can kill me. I am just such a little
shit wanker. What are you looking for exactly? Dungeon enemies. I think we got rid of all the
water candles though. Unless I use another zerg potion. Hey, bro. Hey, bro. Yes. Go back up to
the room we cleared out and I'll be right back. Go back up to the room we cleared out. Yeah. That
big square room where I was digging a lot, you know, where there's like not a room. The big square
room. Okay. Got it. There's an alien here. What are you doing? Attack this. Kill this thing.
Attack it. Oh, it's not real. An illusion. Okay. I'm back. You're not even back up at the room yet.
I thought I had an issue. All right. Come on, little bro. The thing is, the funny thing about
this is people don't even know. I'm like older than you. He doesn't know, Pepe. Die. He doesn't
know. Okay, don't die. What? What the fuck? You can't just do this to me. I said don't die.
Oh, that's some slow down. Okay, here it comes. Not plantara. Hey, but there's no,
no potions available. I can't believe this boss is not plantara. Okay, what's your GPS? I'm dead.
Oh, oh, you're still shooting at it. Why do I die so fast? I don't know. Star, why do I die in two
hits? Because the summoner armorers throughout the entire game provide the least amount of armor.
So you're taking more damage than any other class. Oh, and also you're just getting hit a lot.
It's a combination of those two things. How many times do you, how many times do you have to hit
before you die? You? I don't think I can. You can't die? Yeah. It's almost, it's like impossible
to avoid damage in this game though, because shit is just on every pixel of your screen.
Oh, that's not true. Not true. You literally can't die if you just go melee. You really should.
All right, I'm going melee. Let's go. I'll come back and buy this shit for you. I think I still
have it in my inventory. Melee is so boring though. Yeah, but I've been playing this the whole time.
And if I really am just going to go like, oh, dead. I'd like to play the game. Okay. You're
ready for me to hand things to you? Nope. Not yet. Uh-huh. No. Now I am. Take that. Wait,
was that the right one? What should it be? Yeah, that's the right one. Take that. Nice. Nice.
Take that. Nice. Take that. Ooh. Uh, and I'll go get you the, um, the, uh,
I don't care anymore life steal item. Hey, thanks for boosting me to 60.
No problem. Yeah. How come everyone in wild classic right now is like, oh, first to 60,
dude, just wait, wait until they add the buy a S level 60 account option.
Do you know what I used to do? And now I am, I'm, I'm, I'm not ashamed. I'll tell,
who cares? That was, this was years ago. I used to, this is back before you could
purchase any of that shit. I used to have like the three characters, right? Yeah. So I'd have
three or four characters, like accounts, and I would multi box those accounts. And what I would
do is I would bring like level tens into the front door of a dungeon that they could get into level,
like 10, 15, 20, depending on what the requirement was to get in. I would sit them at the door.
So three people in the dungeon would just be standing at the front door, going into the
instance. I would then have my main character aggro the entire instance, every single enemy.
You could not get hurt. And then I would do one move once the whole dungeon was aggroed
and they'd level up like 15 times. I think I told my chat was because I brought up
a few times the pressure. I told you, I used to multi box level accounts and sell them on
D2Legit.com in Diablo 2. It was a very short time of doing that. You'd have to like rush
like a whole multi box room full of characters to like level 80 and not use a single skill point.
We've all been there, Jerema. All right. Let me see what these things do. Very weak note.
Throws a hyper dense water malibut rains upon hit enemies. Holy shit. Okay. So the other one gives
you like bonus shields as you hit things. So you'll have bonus max health. You become
invulnerable to damage when you use your special key. You get like a bubble around you. Look at
this. This is so cool. Those all go homing as well. All right. So then and the accessory I gave you
is a is a big plus. Throws a hyper dense water malibut rains upon hit enemies. Raindrops shield
your life. Life regeneration by five produces a floating globule over five seconds. Pressing
the special ability will develop you within an impervious shield. While the bubble is active,
all damage taken is converted into healing. I feel like I'm going to need this stuff. All right. So
let's try this again. So now, did you give me an accessory too? Yeah, it's like a black glove.
Increases the damage you take by 25%. That's a lot. Yeah. All right. Let's try. It doesn't matter.
All right. Hold on. I'm going to try and make you some melee items because I think we have all the
stuff. I'm just going to do that really quick because I you still have like plus to summon
items on. Yeah. Accessories. Yes. Oh my God. I just realized I got a gift sub. Thanks a bunch.
Jerma sucks. Why am I wearing these boots and these old ass wings? I don't know. This is these
bad frozen. I never got different wings. These old ass wings. And he's right. Any wing and then
angel treads. Should we make this? We can make angel treads, but I just don't. I don't feel like
doing it. Oh, I know you don't even have. I have frozen wings. You have angel treads, right? Yeah,
you can upgrade them to serif tracers. I just do not feel like. I have frost spark boots. Oh,
and yeah, you're a step behind. Then you should like not even wear them. Also, did you use the
celestial onion? Did I use an onion? I don't. What do you mean? Do you have six accessory slots?
One. I have four and one of them is empty. Okay. You put this in the storage. Here, take this.
You put that in the storage. You use that item and it gives you an extra accessory slot
and you'd want it to store it for a better day. I'm going to hit you. You've been speed running.
It's going too fast. It's going too fast. It's going too fast. You know, to be fair, I didn't
explain to my little brother what he should be doing. That's my bad. It's, you're going too fast
for me. We, this is not just, I started playing Terraria. This is, we just got to Disneyland. I've
never been to Disneyland, right? And you are sprinting to fucking like space mountain and I
have a blindfold on. You're just like, let's go. And I'm like, I, I, wait a minute. I, oh, oh,
I want to get a corn dog. Fuck the corn dog. Get in line. I mean, that's, that's what's happening.
And then you re we get, we go on space mountain and we get up to the top of space mountain,
the big drop. And then you rip the blindfold off and go look down. And I'm like, what happened?
Yeah. That's what it's like playing Terraria. But it's really fun though. After I got off that
space mountain roller coaster, I'm just like, that was, that was really fun. So it's, I'm all right
with this. All right. So what are we doing? I mean, what do you want to do? Do you think
Jerma would play Terraria for like a hundred hours required to like learn it for the first time?
I'm, I'm, I'm doing the community a service of showing him this great game and like a bite
size, the family size pack that he can enjoy. And it's, I, it's great. See, like I, I wouldn't have
built it. I wouldn't have built like a big giant compound to have all these people. I don't even
know what have these people do. I don't even know what have these people do. I just know they're
here and it's all right. Cool. Okay. Okay. Hold on. I gotta remember how to build the ravager.
Replace the emblem, the guarding Avenger emblem, 12% increased damage to defense.
Is this sucks? I mean, this thing doesn't do anything. I have so many better options than
just 12% more damage. Let me see. What can I turn it into? Mechanical glove,
melee speed. So I need to take this, take this and figure out how to upgrade that.
Cause we should have all this stuff to upgrade it. I was working on that, but I'm getting sidetracked
by like 30 things. Mechanical glove increases melee knockback, 12% damage and melee speed.
That sounds pretty good to me. Let's make it. We do have to be like one of these special
crafting benches or something. Um, it should be right here. This anvil,
I think either that or it's way over here. The tinker is table instead. It's a tinker.
Actually, what am I doing? I know what I'm doing. Mechanical glove. There it is.
Okay. So now I can, I mean, that's a lot. That's very fast. Okay. Looking good. Now
people are still yelling at me for these wings. What are those? Is that what they're saying? Um,
a little meaner, a little meaner than that. Uh, the one comment in particular said, um,
you are the stupidest person I've ever seen play this game. And then their name is not in chat
anymore. And so they're gone, I think. So, I mean, that was kind of like really like unfortunate,
like, okay. Uh, Chris may well knock back and inflict fire damage and attack.
I need a magma stone. Do we have any magma stones? Yeah. Here you go. Nice. All right. So
I'm just going to make this like super thing. I think there's one more step after that.
All right. My major is another step. Holy shit. Okay. Fire and consider this item.
What the fuck is that? Okay. Let's go here. Fire gauntlet. Elemental gauntlet. Do we have a
Yharnam insignia? Uh, no, I think we're very close to having one. I forget how to make it.
I'm doing my own thing. Okay. So what you gave me this Aegis thing. Yeah. It's immunity to fire
blocks and knockback. 40% max life. Increase health. Supreme holy flame dash. Activate buffs
to all damage. Crit chance. Any fan activities. Your movement speed. Increase enemy aggro.
Okay. I forget this. What was that? Why did I just did that in a turn tonight? I did that.
I thought it'd be funny. It's my gauntlet. My gauntlet versus the giver to the wings,
right? Because I don't, what's the point of having this if I have the flying saucer, right? Oh yeah.
True. Do you have a melee? Which is broom, which is better.
I'm forgetting how to actually make the good wings. Oh, we need luminite bars.
It's pendant. I don't need this pendant anymore either. I have like a useless pendant.
I got a couple of useless things. Oh my God. Let's just see how it goes. I'm willing. Let's
just, let's give it a little attempt here. I got more health, like a better armor.
So let's do some, let's go attack something. God damn it. I had to do this the long way.
I mean the long way. I think I turned off that other mod. I'm not using minions,
so why are you using the amulet? Is it, do we have anything that's better than this in the stash?
Better than what? Just, I have a useless slot right now.
Just look through equipment and there's a couple things. There's an item that's 15% damage under
50% health, which you'll be at because the other item. There's, there's some other things in there.
Um, uh, there's a lot of toys in this toy box. What am I doing?
15% increased melee damage. Here it is right here. And more, oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
there's the fungal spore. Look at that item. It's like a mushroom head. Your weapons don't count,
but you'll, you will get a weapon that will count. True melee weapons emit mushrooms when swung,
boost true melee damage by 25%. So what, what do you mean? True melee is like when your melee
weapon actually hits something and not the projectiles that make, okay. All right.
Does that, that includes the axes too, right? Uh, no, I don't think the axes count.
How you doing? Need help? Uh, we got to do the pillars again really fast.
Yes. We have to do the pillars again? Huh? Yeah. There's a, the only way to get luminite bars is
to kill moon lord. And I had a mod where you could like buy moon lord packs, but I think I turned it
off and forgot about it. It's like the only way we can get luminite again to my knowledge is by
doing all of the pillars to summon moon lord. Okay. I guess. Unless there's some other way to do it
that my mods enabled that I don't know of, but now that we're big strong boys, it goes really
quickly. We are pretty strong. All right. Uh, the number one thing that that's going to need to
happen though, is it's going to need to actually swan the enemies. Uh, Hey, you wait here. You're
going to do another wait here, please. Jeremy. Oh my God. Bed. I got to pee so bad. My God. I'm
going to pee my pants. I'll be, I'll be right there, bro. Um, dead. Okay. I'm getting off the
fucking thing. I don't, I don't even know what hit me. He's dead. They look gone. The super boost
accessory. Well, how did we get that? Super boost. Yeah. There's an item that lets you like run
as fast as you can see. It's ridiculous. Oh, why is there sand elementals coming out here?
Oh, the Ragnarok boss dropped it. It might be expert only. Well, that was very easy. That was
a very easy boss. I got it. Forbidden. I got to forbid something forbidden. You can craft it. I'll
see if I, maybe I picked it up or I would have to kill Ragnarok again. Or apparently I can craft it.
You guys might be thinking of something else because there's a couple of mods that add
similar things. Forbidden fragments are outdated now. That's okay. Astral ore. I got like orange
shit. This thing's dead. So I'm coming back to town. Okay. All right. Um, I have to pee.
So I'm going to go pee for the first time in my whole life. Go take a pee pee. I'll be right back.
Um, I'm just going to kill Ragnarok again. I'm getting, I've got my adrenaline. It's a joke,
by the way. You're supposed to laugh when I say that. Oh no, that boss doesn't drop it. I'm thinking
of the second phase that drops that. Do you remember the name of it, Ashley? Because I would
just go to our other server and like grab it. Or you could do that and you could join me. You could
like bring it here so I don't have to shut the server down and explain to Jerma how to join again.
Joining. He like despises joining Terraria servers even though it's like a steam invite.
I don't. I'm sure you could find it though. I would appreciate it very much and then we could
do your, your joke and then we can give it to him and I could, I could play the rest of the game
with it. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. You'll get the fee. We don't need to tell him about that boss. Oh dude,
does this thing drop Luminite? Is that what it was? Does this thing give fragments you don't have to
do? I remember that now. I'm going, I'm going to. I know he doesn't drop Luminite. I got some water.
I'm back. Hey, here. Maybe if you have an extra slot, there's that. Extra slot. That's right. I
do not, but one of these I think is useless for me. Yes. He won't pick up the essence as will he?
We have like 80 of every essence. Don't, don't worry guy. He doesn't know. Is there something
I should know? Sorry, is there something I need to know? No, there's nothing you need to know.
All right. Uh, chat, congratulations. You have just made, you're now on cool down. I will not
look at chat for five straight minutes. I want like an on screen chat, cool down, read-o meter.
That would be awesome. We're like after five minutes to your stream would even say streamer
must look at chat now. And then everyone would get their thing in. No, that would be a terrible
idea. Cause once I get the countdown, it would be like streamer look at chat now. And it would be
like crazy spam and everyone would get out of their system. Then you could just like in good
conscious and look away again. Like, okay, that I'm right. I've read you. Do you really want the
only thing that you looked at ever to be like, Oh, W O or like streamer sucks or like a bunch
of coffee pasta? What else are they going to say? I see some really, really good shit in chat.
Sometimes. I don't know about you. Oh, well, it doesn't like, it would just like make you feel
good inside though. I'm going to pretend I didn't hear you say that. I mean, like when a cute girl
looks at you and it's like, Oh, right. What are you saying? Uh, anyways, that's coming out of my
video. You can keep that in yours if you want. I make one video. So that's coming out of it.
That's not going in my video. You can put that in yours. I'm not. I've never made a video.
I get that clip. God, it's so easy with the challenge. By the way, while I was peeing,
I decided that during the course of the P I was going to have a rating for Terraria.
Didn't we do this though? We're done. This is the final Terraria stream. So I have to give my final
score. And I, yeah, but before you were saying that you couldn't do it properly because it was,
it was what you said, like you, you thought Terraria was like messy and like too chaotic.
But I said, it's because there's mods and you've never played like basic Terraria and it was skewing
your, your review. Yeah, that's fine. And you agreed, but now you're going to review it. Well,
I have to say like my final thoughts on the game. We just get up behind the podium. The floor is
yours. I'm going to give you some, uh, noise crowd noise here. Uh, sure.
I think that was fun. I think I deserve something for that one. I really do.
I think I deserve something for that. I don't know. Here, do it one more time.
Click, click, click, click, click. Okay. Yeah, that was spot on. Thank you. But I
have no preparation at all. And you just do that on me. I come on. I think I deserve at least
like an extra letter grade higher on my, um, test for that one. Uh, people who missed this
joke from before are really confused. That's all right. Uh, no, I worry about them because
when I have to look at my child, I worry about them. Why haven't you ever just worried about
the one before? So we have to, uh, defeat moon, uh, the moon. I have to defeat the moon. Uh,
oh, oh, who's down there? Who's down there? That was me. Well, they're dead now.
So what's going on? You, are we, are we, uh, summoning? Do your best. Like the S like
simplest thing. That is awful. No one wants to hear that. That was pretty good. That was really
good. That was so good. I've never been like happier that I've said something there. That
was perfect. I can't do that again, but just this time to say something, say like something, uh,
why he's following me. I'm too far in the sky. I can't help you. You're like leading him away.
Okay. Now I get to be the big brother. How do I hurt him? How do I hurt the moon guy?
The brain go for the brain. How do you hurt this guy? You had a chance to be the big bro.
What was that? Not hitting him in the right place. The brain, right? His right hand had a,
a little bit left on it. I need that. You don't even know what to do with it. Yeah, I don't.
Fair hurtful angels. And I need the Luma night moon Lord trophy, portal gun,
reckless terraria, which what is this? This is cool. This looks kind of cool.
Here. You want, should I take this other onion? No, you can't use them again.
Sorry. Invite me. I, you can just join Ashley. You don't need to be invited here. Uh,
what did you actually want? Luminate. I don't know. Is, is, is, is that a, uh,
I'll find it eventually. I'm never picking up anything ever again. Thank you. Did you get it?
No, I don't think so. You want to do all the pillars again because you picked this up and
like, you can't find it. I promise. I don't know where it is. Luminate, Luminate or I got there.
He did not drop it. Oh my God. He's a good, this is a cool house. Did I just do all that
for a pair of wings? Did you think so? Yeah, I think so. All right. So I've got this,
this can be upgraded. What should I upgrade that to? That's the question that I have.
The yo-yo. Oh, I want to see this insane knockback. Ruthless. This to thrower class
somebody who uses it. You'll have this like save file from like five years.
You'll have like some friend eventually that like it gets to this point and you're like,
oh, I remember this. Actually, you saved a frog leg and I have no idea where you got it from.
I had to like when me and Ash were playing come here and steal the frog leg because
I don't know what, where it's dropping in the mod, what's happening with it. You don't get those.
All right, I did something. I think it's from fishing, but no one was fishing. It's like a
mod added a different way to get a frog leg and he had it and it was in the storage and I don't
know why. I couldn't figure it out. I did something. All right, so what's happening now?
You tell me. What do you want to do? What's the next like milestone? You tell me. I mean,
this is all extra. We already beat the game. I mean, you tell me. I don't know where we go.
Can I talk to Lucy or are you in the, can I get in there? Can I get in there? Yeah, you can get
in there. She's all yours. Let's see. I like this. Just get five of everything. Fuck it.
Archery, summoning. I don't need that anymore. I need like damage. Is it like a melee damage
potion that I haven't been taking? There's a crumbling potion in the calamity mod
potions. That's really good lowers defense when you melee hit. Oh, that sounds cool.
I'll go do that. All right. Calamity mod pots. It's not going to let me connect.
Do you have the item, Ashley? What is it called? You wouldn't have it. Can you put it somewhere
that I can just like shut the server down for a second and go get it? Or what's the name of it?
Crumbling, crumbling. Right, right, right. Oh yeah. Ashley, what's the name of it?
I'll just look up how to get it. It's cool. Yeah, I'm just gonna get all this shit.
This stuff looks insane. Does Star have VR? Yes, we mean Star played VR before.
We've done a multiplayer virtual reality stream. We played tennis. That was that was a hoop.
Oh yeah, it has to be expert mode. So I'm going to change it to expert mode.
What? Why are you doing that? So I can get an item from Ragnarok.
An item from Ragnarok. Oh, we have the stuff for this. It's in one minute. He's going to read the
chat. Get your oo's ready. Get them ready. Yes. Where are we going? Hold on. I'm doing shit.
So guys, donuts next to me. What? Let's go fight stuff. I'm going to test my might.
I like really specifically need a thorium anvil. I'm going to like punch someone in the freaking
mouth. If I like a soul forge isn't good enough. Okay. It's the name of my mind. You gotta have it.
No. Jarrah's bored in his own stream. No, what? I love doing that. Like turn on friendly fire and
get him. Okay, here we go. Hey Star, turn on friendly fire for a second. I don't want to
just take to lose nothing. Wait till he turns it on. What the fuck was that?
Okay. Why is Chewbacca in this game? 30 years later. Okay. Jarrah, I'm tired. Can I go to
sleep please? Yeah. You can go to bed. And now I can't make the Ragnarok emblem. What am I missing?
And now I will do a series of voices while I drink water. Here we go.
I can't believe it. I know. Absolutely amazing. Start up. We don't have vortex fragments. What?
When did that happen? Everybody. Jarrah stole them all. Nobody likes that one. Well, that was a
board joke. That wasn't a real joke. You want a real job. Jarrah, did you steal all the vortex
fragments? Uh, yeah. I walked by them because they were on the ground. Oh, give it to me.
What the hell are you doing, little bro? I just picked them up. What just happened?
Yes. And here's the other ones he dropped. I promise I didn't just try to throw them down the
well. And for my next drink. Okay. Uh, you have not seen this boss before. Ooh, new material.
Oh, did you even make good wings, did you? You didn't get good wings. No. And here comes
dying reality. What's dying reality? Oh, the Ragnarok. Where is this enemy we're fighting?
It's the circle with the health bar that's right next to you. And because every enemy
follows you for some reason. Whoa. I insta died. Like I had full health. What happened? Holy shit.
When you say you had full health, you mean you had half health? No, I had like at least
like 80, 70% or 80%. I got really at least got to see the fireworks. Okay. I got the thing.
You got a thing that you were looking for? I got the thing that I was looking for. Nice. Now my
wife is happy. I got a Ragnarok treasure bag. Should I open it? Yeah. And then you're going
to want to put on the Omega core. Whoa. The Omega core raises movement speed beyond comprehension.
What do I replace? Are you wearing boots? Wait, it takes the place of boots. You don't need boots
anymore. Um, I don't, I don't like this. I can't use this. This is why I can't play Sonic the Hedgehog.
This is Sonic the Hedgehog levels of speed. Well, you have to play with it until the game's over
now. That's what Ashley says. And I mean, does this work in my spaceship? Who runs the world? Girls,
does this work in the spaceship? No, it doesn't. I don't like it. I don't like it at all, but it's
okay. I will deal with it. It's cool though. Nice. You sound like entranced. What about the
master tides? Here, I'm going to make you good wings. Do you even want wings? Are you going to
be in your like a dummy? I mean, the UFOs, these wings are faster than UFO. Just take this stuff
because I don't know what it does. Yes. Give me the wings. We're done with this horse shit.
Thanks for making me throw up. I'm sorry. I didn't want to do the Sonic the Hedgehog
super speed thing. Here's wings. Angry Stardust wings allows flight and snowfall. Great value.
Okay. What should this replace? What should this replace? I don't know, dude. True melee damage.
More. I'm exploring the world. I keep hitting planets. Place the shroom. No, I want to place
this Omega core. Is this faster than the spaceship? It is. Yeah, it is. Okay. Thanks. Thanks for trying
it before asking the question. Okay. You're ready. Um, hold on. I can take the shroom off.
Okay. Oh, I got to take off my dash. My dash like very randomly throws me
in a, this is, I would, I would quantify this. I would quantify this as not fun. I'm gonna take
them off. I'm dead. I just ran into the side. So did I. The dash is what's getting me.
I would quantify that is breaks the game to a point where it's, it's, it hurts me. It hurts me
to do this. I can't even pick up this stuff on the, can we take this off? I don't know.
I don't know what's giving me the dash, but now I'm really slow. This one. I'm so slow now though.
Man, I'm too fast. I'm too slow. Put the boots back on instead of this room. Baby rage, baby rage.
Make the angel threads. Star, can you make me the angel threads? Yeah. Thanks. You already made them.
I mean, yeah, I've been wearing them. I took them off for the Omega core. Oh, that was dumb.
I am the alpha and the Omega, right? Is that what you always used to say to me?
I don't think I've ever said those words. No, like whenever you're making a video and you want it,
something to be a certain way, you just say, I am the alpha and the Omega. And then you always got
what you want it in a mean voice or in like a, just like telling you that no, like a holier than bow
kind of thing. I am the alpha and the Omega. Okay, hello. There's more light. So what's next?
Ravager. Ravager. I love shooting the bubbles. So hard to control. It's funny. Like I, I,
I fly up so slowly and yet if I tap left or right, I'm gone. I almost just whacked it. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. I was saying it and he crushed my God. And my next trick,
I am going to drink a glass of water while Star does voices. Be amazed.
Don't make mouth noises into the mic, Jerma.
Well, it was close. I added an extra one. I did the part after that. I was, that was the next part
of the, of the, I'm proud of you that you could admit that you did it wrong. Why is everybody
blaming me for the gross noise you made? I was just drinking water and you did the gross noise.
I didn't do that. No, you like prepared noises for your drink because you thought it would be
funny. And if it didn't go, like your joke didn't stick. I said you to do voices, not go like,
I said Star is going to do voices while I drink out of this cup. And then you just made a bunch
of mouth noises. That wasn't a voice. What? So it's my fault. No, it's both of our faults.
Yeah. You're really fun to work with. Hey, anyone want to do any like work with Jerma?
We'll throw you under the bus. Yeah. I've like read, I've read a bunch of shit about Jerma.
Like I like his streams and everything, but he's apparently really, really hard to work with.
He's like notorious, like throwing tantrums on before broadcasts and everything. He's really
hard to work with. You wouldn't believe the things you said to me before we started today.
Like even I bet I've met him at like events and parties and he's like a super dick.
Yeah. I know why we didn't play for three weeks. Broad, bro, mega low caster.
I swear to you, I made an onk. Did you? I think you did. I do remember that. No, you weren't here.
I'm just trying to, to seem like we're working together. I'm just trying to make it seem like
we're, Hey, we're doing this thing. I remember you made the onky. You weren't here for that.
He just threw me under the bus. Well, I'm not going to let you lie to everyone.
Here it is again. Jerma like wants to look good in front of everyone,
even if it means his friends have to lie for him. Okay. And we're going to kill the ravager.
Oh, again, that was fun when we died both together. Like we didn't do it. Dude, I can't,
I can't control. All right. I'm ready. All right. Come on. I'm getting, I'm getting
damage reduction. You just said to do it. And I activated my pots. It'll be like two seconds.
I only have three minutes. It takes longer than three minutes. I'm setting up my minds.
Okay. You ready? Who is that? Let's do it again. Oh my God. He just disappeared because I went
too far. God damn it. I can't not go that far. I can only hear this in my one ear. How far would
you go? I need to hear this. I'm right here. That wasn't that bad. That was nothing. Are you
fighting? Yeah. Oh shit. I'm sorry. I feel like a snail when I, when I fly up. Get the fuck away
from the guy. Get away from the guy. What's this guy? This guy following me. They come through the
fucking goddamn things. I'm too fast. Don't die. Don't run away. Nice. Nice. The ravager.
You do 20% more damage. Take 20% less damage. Do 20% more lifesteal. Take a hundred percent
more damage when you are not standing still. Fucking cool item. Gain an increase to all damage
reduce light wing time. All right. Whatever. Oh, he drops blood stones. That's what it was.
Blood ocean. Blood orb. And the phantom heart. Ravager is pinwheel. We don't have blood orbs?
How do we not have blood orbs, Jerma? I can't even get in this hole. Is this,
is this a joke where I have this in my inventory and I don't know? I don't think so.
Nah, I bought a bunch. Is stir going to fight the four celestial towers? Nope. I'm sorry. I'm gonna be,
I have to, I gotta butt in here and fix that. Is stir and then in parentheses after that
and watching Jerma and parentheses going to do, I just want to be, I want to clear up what you just
said. Okay. Stir and parentheses and Jerma's eyes and then, and parentheses. I mean, I am watching.
I am seeing it happen. Is stir and then parentheses and Jerma's respawn scream
and parentheses going to continue to do the celestial? That's so funny. That's a good one.
Typically I would fucking time you out for something like that and making fun of the
streamer. But I mean, come on, that's pretty good. Are you using that 25%
intramally thing? Uh, no. Would you like it? No, I'm just, you might want to.
I have the angel treads, the fire gauntlet. Here, take this weapon. Okay.
This thing is too, all right. I will have to reforge it. Seven,
17, was it 1770, 1662. Is that the year you were born?
Just give out your password on stream. I don't have 39 gold. What the hell?
I, I dropped a lot of my money. So did I. Do we have any platinum left in the bank? We don't,
we don't have any money. You know how to fix that. Sell, uh, something I have. Honestly, like sell
all that. No, I don't want you to do that. Nevermind. They just called this a pleb house.
We use a Zerg potion and just kill everything. Okay. They know it'll get in here.
Oh, it'll be able to get in here. I didn't know this was like a artillery thing. Doesn't,
I can't remember what bow I was using in the other game, where I got it from. Anyway, we got
to go to space. Space. That means I get to be in this. I think we need cosplay. So we'll just
hurry this up and, ah, okay. So the storm weaver has awoken. Hopefully he doesn't instantly run
away. But he's a two faced worm that comes up to space to fight you. Why am I, why am I still in
that? I, what am I, get out of the, um, I was trying to get out of the fucking UFO and like,
I got, uh, I was in the UFO, which was slow as shit. I'm, I'm throwing it in the trash
so I don't do that again. I heard that burp. Hey, did you come up here and pick up items?
I'm going to scream at you. I came up. Why, what did I do? What did you pick up? I don't know. I
just came back up here and I ended up coming. What did you pick up? Armored shell, storm dragon,
Mag, uh, Magnum rounds. Drop it off. Just drop it off. Do you think I'm not going to take care of
you? I think that's pretty much it. Is that what it is? I don't know if I got that now. I don't
know if I got that too. Okay. We've got to go to hell. Okay. What the hell was that? You can't hurt
them. What's that? Oh my boat does not even work here. You're gonna kill it. I'm trying. It's a
ghost. I thought you were like a fan of that movie. I'm not afraid to know ghosts. Remember
that one? Should I go, should I respond and pick everything up again? Did you? No. Okay. Okay. So
now where are we going? So that you can summon the other boss and then this is like the boss
before the boss. Hold on. Let me just, let me die again. Waiting for you to die. Okay. So what,
what are we doing now? I'm trying to remember how to summon the boss. You just made a pizza.
Want some? That just doesn't sound bad. Armored shell, twisting nether. Did I get twisting nether?
I should have it. I don't have the drops from the boss. What? I got a hellstone brick. Yeah,
I got an unholy essence. Twisting nether. I don't know where that is. Yeah, the boss we just fought
should have dropped twisting nether. Did you pick it up? I have it. Okay. You threw it to me.
I just did it. Thank you. Thank you, little bro. You're welcome. I need potions. We didn't get any
money, did we? Not really, no. We're gonna, we're gonna need them. This is a tough fight.
When I say before, like, oh, he's setting up. Listen to me. This is a tough fight. Sounds fun.
We do need money, though. I need potions. I don't have any. I have healing potions,
but not anything else. I mean, like, does it matter? I'm kind of, you said this is the hardest thing
we've done. Yeah. How am I supposed to do the hardest thing we've ever done without my, like,
15 potions I drink before each boss? The devourer of gods made me bite my desk, and there are several
bite marks. He's right. He's right. Insane chat. Let's get you some money. Insane chat. I just
imagine the front of your desk with just, like, teeth impressions from the dentist office,
just all over the front. How do you explain that to anybody, by the way? If anybody comes over
your house and goes in your room and goes to your desk, there are bite marks all over your desk. What
are you going to tell them? Come to me. That's what I'm going to tell them. That's what you can
earn some cash. You can tell them you have a flavored desk. I mean, that would be, you could
say that. But would they believe you? Then they'd want to try it. You getting money? Yeah, I think
so. I'll be honest. I have no idea. This is a better way to do this. All I know is there are,
my screen's full of things. I don't know what I think. Things are happening. That's all I know.
There's a better way to do this. Hold on. Get in there. Please don't spam the chat.
I think I have some money now. I've got 17 gold, which is not a whole lot, but it's something.
Murray, where did you go? How much do you have? 17 gold. 19 gold. Yeah, it's on the down.
Hold on. I've got a plan. Have you ever wanted to eat something non-edible, like nice smelling
soap? Yes. There is a store that sells soap. If you guys have ever heard of Lush, there's a
chain of, they've got all kinds of weird, like cheese soaps in there. And by cheese soap,
I mean, they have these gigantic wheels of soap cheese that sit on these mantles and they have
to carve off of these giant soap wheels. You know, just stuff for your shower, your bath,
or whatever. There is a lemon zest candy smelling soap cheese wheel thing in there.
I feel like if you ate it, it would be okay.
Probably. You'd probably get a really bad stomach ache, but that first bite would be like,
hmm. But then you, yeah, after about five seconds, you'd be like, wait, no, no, no, no.
But they have like a honey. They've got this like honey smelling soap. It looks like a honeycomb.
It looks so delicious. When's the last time you ate one of these?
I've never because that's a bad idea. You shouldn't do that. Nobody should do that.
How do you know that that's a bad idea? Because it's, oh, you had the electro
Roombas in here the whole time. You fucking god. It's chemicals and you don't eat chemicals.
It's a stupid idea. Don't do that. German doesn't even know that the electro Roombas
give you like 40 platinum. Add that to the list of things that I don't fucking know in this game.
12 platinum for selling these like, come on, dude. Come on. I got so mad at my apple. I gave it bite
marks. Biting my desk. I can't imagine. First of all, what kind of desk do you have?
If you don't have a wooden desk, that's even more concerning.
It's a grape desk. Oh, I know that. I know those. It's a cheesecake desk.
You know, there's some fucked up billionaire in the world that has like a food office.
This shit doesn't even work. He goes in there and pretends to go on his
like hamburger fucking mice, his cheesecake desk, his monitors. They're made out of like glass candy.
He doesn't do anything in there. He just goes in there and just goes, yeah, I could afford this.
And like it takes one bite and then somebody goes in there and replaces it.
Come on, dude. Come on. Oh, I can't believe you know the platinum thing.
Help, help them. These people, they mean nothing to me. Holy shit. That guy just shot that dude in
the face. Damn. I don't mean anything to me. What fucked up thing would I do if I was a billionaire?
Okay, get up here and then you can tell us all about German world. No, um,
it's all there. Wait, we don't have a money problem anymore. What? Why are you summoning
plant? I'm going in. There's a view somewhere. I don't, I don't know where. Why are you sending
plant arrow? Oh, they didn't drop anything. I was just summoning a bunch of them so that we could
sell everything they dropped for money. And then they didn't drop anything. I would put it into
like dragon egg research, try to like hatch a dragon. I know this doesn't even work like,
oh, that guy didn't even get a chance. What am I, what am I doing with myself?
This is all so that you could buy potions. Come here, son. Take six platinum. Wait.
Wait, that's not what I want. And then we're going to fight the God worm. God worm. Nice.
Uh, so what, what is the best, what's the best potions I should be buying and like having
actually, uh, the Yarnham stimulant, the crumbling potion, yarnings, titan, crumbling, invincibility,
wrath, endurance, Yarnham, Yarnham stimulus, calamity. What else? The photosynthesis,
soaring. Just get one each. One of each. Get one. I'm just going to buy one of each.
Nevermind. Um, what's going on with chat? I accidentally, oh, okay. What? That's not,
that's not going to happen here. All right. Uh, fortitude. No, non-calamity.
I want my regular potions now. Where's the old guy?
What's this? Wrath. Max life. You ready? Um, hold on. Titan. Okay. I'm gonna like see how many
laps I can do around the fucking planet. Cause I'm the flash before like my friends, right?
Who also mutes himself. I hit L. I hit L. All right. Okay. Now let's do it. I'm coming to you.
You're already here. Yeah, I'm here. Okay. Let's do this. So what are we doing? What's the,
what is this thing that we're currently doing? It's, it's a worm. The worm. All right. It's the
worm. I'm ready. Let's worm it up. Holy shit. It's fast. I'm scared. I drew, I brought it to
the other side of the world. What? By accident. It was fast enough to like go the whole way. It's
coming. I haven't, I haven't seen it. I have, I don't even know what it looks like. Oh, there it
is. Okay. This is phase one. Phase one. Yeah. This thing is long. It's too long. I'm trying,
I'm trying to let my little brother fight it. So I'm like staying still near this area. He was
covering the whole ground. That thing was long. Holy shit. My brother, I haven't even seen what
it looks like. Okay, boy. Oh, all the guys are dead. Oh, I kind of needed potions. Whatever.
Ready? Hold on a second. Okay. Does it like gain my speed or something? Cause it just suddenly
jumped like a million miles an hour when I flew up. Doesn't this thing match the speed of the
player? Yeah, I'm noticing that. Oh shit. Wow. I'm noticing it. I forgot to get to it.
I don't worry. German's muted again. You don't have to listen to him. How is that possible?
I didn't do anything. I didn't press L. It's head and tail take normal damage. Its body is
resistant. I mean, I still did all right damage, but he just kind of, he just did the snake thing.
He just wrapped around and went. Oh shit. Somebody just gave a fucking hundred bucks.
Uh, amnestic. Oh w thanks for the a hundred dollars. Turn up the music.
I know I'm thanking somebody, but thank you so much. Sorry. I'm sorry. Fucking bucks.
But I brought it up. Turn up the music. Do what? Turn up the music there. I like need the potions.
I have eight of each like decent one. You want some, you want me to split them with you?
No, actually I have good enough ones. All right. So I think low now.
So he matches the speed of the player. Is that what you're saying? He might.
Okay. Well,
wrapping around.
It's like my flight time is lower than it should be. I still have the ravager thing in my inventory.
He's coming. Oh no, please. No dear God. I ran out of juice. Stay alive. Now I'm mad.
Holy fuck. I just almost instantly died. Can we do it? Does he not have a phase two or is
this phase two garbage on normal? Or wait, no, he summons all of these guys and then you get phase
two. What do you mean then? Leave me the fuck alone. I'm trying to eat this thing. Zero point.
Jesus Christ, man. It's fucking this is like intensity. The video game storm weaver.
Okay. Now it's now it's this guy that we fought before and then it's the guy again.
Yeah, where's he going to do this again? Yeah, except this time more. Oh Lord. Holy shit. I
just got fucking air shot. I'm dead.
Yeah. I think I saw this ravager shit in my cotton inventory. I can fly for like a second.
I'm going to bite my desk. You were warned. You're going to I'm going for it. Hey,
don't worry. He's at 80%. Oh, boy. I've really done it now. I've really done it now. I've done
it. Oh, now you've done it. Clicked out of my window so many times. Let's play.
I did it too. Fuck. I did not want to go into space. Please don't die, Jerma. Oh, no. I just
clicked out of my fucking window. Don't give me this counter responsibility with the giant worm.
I summoned the ravager by accident because if you hold down your mouse and you shoot at the top
left of your screen, it will click the things in your inventory. All right. Explain to me why
I just clicked out of my window again. Why in the name of fucking God is that possible?
Just playing full screen dummy. I almost just turned off my VPN accidentally and would have
like my stream were turned off. Lock the hot bar. How? I can't believe I actually summoned
ravager. What do I do? Oh, I never know. At least ravagers like these ones.
Jesus, I'm dead. Oh, where are you? Oh, I thought it was following me. Are you good? Yeah.
You've managed to go that way. Are you? Are you? Are you guys going that way?
Yeah, we're going this way. Going that way. Okay. I mean, sometimes life gives you lemons
out of the fucking window again. I don't know how I pressed like a different. I didn't even.
I pressed like a different mouse button. Are you doing this way? Okay. Why is he in the background?
He's too good for you. Jesus, man. I'm going to die again here. You want to bite your desk?
Not yet. No. Don't die. Oh, duh. I'm okay. I really wish I had those boots I gave to
Jerma right now. Are you good? Are you coming? I'm respawning. You good? Are you good? You back?
My lord, I'm going to die. I'm dead. And I am. Spawned again. Oh, I almost had a holy fire or
whatever. Oh, my fingers just hitting so many buttons. It's too intense for me. Did we lose?
Yeah. This loss seems very not fun. It's fun. It's just too much health. And I couldn't have.
I think we could both have much better weapons and accessories by now, but I've skipped so much
stuff. It's too much for my brain. I'm down close though. Yeah. Yeah. Actually, our potions
probably ran out. I didn't even realize. That takes forever. I usually take another one after
I spawn back. You want to give up right there? Is that the I give up in Terraria? I mean,
or we sit here and wait for all the NPCs to respawn and do something else?
Oh, they're all dead. No, they're all dead. That was our one chance to kill the god.
Here, let me get my main. Go get your main. Do it. Go get my main. Go get, okay, go get your like,
your decked out in full raid gear character. Are you actually going to do that? Yeah. I don't
remember the items I had. I'm like curious. I lost connection to you. Yes, I had to leave.
You killed the moon lord. So technically you did it. Yeah. No, it was fun. Yeah. So that
was the guy who beat Dark Souls on stream that devour of gods. Right. Is that is that like one
of the last boss two more after him. So there's two more bosses to end the whole thing. Yeah.
Damn. One of them is a there's one hard boss after that. That's a dragon yarn.
And then after that is like that. I have fuck you. You put this way that I'd like I didn't even
feel like crafting shit for. I was just like, I don't I'm not interested. That's cool, though.
There's a lot of content in this game. There's a lot of stuff to do.
Are you actually going to get your man or is that it? Yeah, the server is up.
I should be able just to join you, right? Yeah. I'm using this. Oh, this. Oh, true. Oh, yeah. This
was like crashing my computer because I had to replace my way when I had to replace my power
supply, I lowered an underclocked all my hardware and shooting this bow was bringing the server
down to like 10. Yes. Let me see. Where are you? That's you. All of those are homing arrows.
So like the game just kind of freaks out one up. Also, you can have. I know you can't use that.
Yeah, you can't use that. It's too intense for me.
Well, your character looks really cool. You ready? I guess we have. I don't have any potions.
We need them. Are you just going to know? I do have them because they're in my piggy bank
and it uses my potions from a piggy bank. I'm remembering. All right. So we're going to we're
going to go for it. You're going to kill everything in a second. No, it's still a
really hard boss. Oh, all right. But what are you writing? I thought that was a unicorn.
Is it a you? Oh, I'm a brony. I'm going to tell you that. Oh,
I'm ready. I'm going to get I'm going to get in sticky. I swear it's going to happen.
All right. Show off. Show off. Show off. Show off. Show off. Show off. I mean, I can't hold on.
Oh, this is hard. The game's hard. I knew it was going to happen.
Only seems to happen on this boss because it goes to the edge of the screen and you like follow it.
Remember when you said that this was hard? It is phase one. Well, you just killed that without even
I think slowing down a little. No, I'm good. I'm kind of waiting for the next health bar to go down.
OK, next part. All right. Here comes the destroyer of worlds, the eater of the gods.
Oh, that's all right. I'll just be tails. Now you're definitely lagging bad.
Yep. That it's it's when all these homing projectiles start going off at once,
it slows the game down and makes it easier to dodge.
It's helping a lot. Holy shit. There's so many arrows.
Also, you can see the arrows staying inside of them because there's like a hit delay on the boss.
So not all the arrows can hit him at the same time.
That's so stupid. OK, is this part? Well, it's easy to dodge when it's like slow mo, right?
No, I don't have slow mo, though. You don't know. That's just you.
I got a fucking beast of a computer. I'm going to die.
I'm not going to get to see the end of the movie.
Jerma has left. What? What do you mean have left?
I think I deced you. Oh, no.
I was going to see it. I was going to get to see the end.
Damn it. Are you still in there? Yeah.
Is it dead? It's like it's frozen.
Is it killable? I don't think so.
It crashed. Yeah.
Where is it? Where is it?
You press M and open up the map. You can see it.
This is not crashed. Its head's running around.
Well, kill its head. This is my chance.
I'll use the other bow.
Where is its head? Zoom your map out. You can see it moving around.
Oh, it's over there. It's dead.
Did it. Did it.
Where did it die? Right here.
Oh, and that sword's really good.
The power of the gods.
Excelsis.
I'll confirm to Jerma beat a Terraria except for the other bosses.
Whoa. I haven't been this happy.
Oh, yeah. And you can boost your melee damage a lot.
And that weapon is super good. All right. I'll keep it.
I have to have an asterisk because Star had to go on his big, cool character.
Wow. I just wanted to see what happened when you died.
Let's go over to the jungle real fast.
I beat the moon. Moon skeleton. I was there for that.
All right. Where are you? You're just flying around here.
Where are you? Going to the jungle.
Actually, the teleporter just takes it. I'm going to do that.
Jerma has joined the red party.
Does the jungle teleporter?
It's on my roof. Here, I need to.
Hey, I want to show you something real quick.
Show me something else cool.
That was kind of cool.
You can always teleport back to me.
I will. I won't yet.
Jungle dragon Yaron. He's killing me in one hit.
He does that.
One hit. You're up.
We need actual platforms in the jungle if I'm going to do it.
Are you just flexing right now? Are you just trying to beat this hard boss?
What else are we going to do? What do you want to do?
I'm just curious. I'm all right if you want to do a big mirror flex.
Ask Star to make a drill containment unit for me to play with.
I forget how to do that.
What was that?
I feel like that would be the Christmas present where you give the kid the present.
He's like, oh, this is so cool. And he plays with it for like a day
or like 10 minutes. And then you never see him play with it again.
Like, wow, you went through all this work and you made him the drill containment unit.
And that's all right, though.
Yeah. And do you have an axe?
Oh, a pickaxe.
Hold on. Oh, everyone's dead.
That's why I remember when like cutting down trees.
I do remember when cutting down trees.
You help make a platform.
We need a flat little.
My my friend, I have not carried around platforms in probably two streams.
Well, yeah. What can you like mine some stuff, daddy?
Sure.
All right. What do you need? You want platforms?
I got platforms like dirt.
And I just need like a flat surface.
So when there's a dragon making giant firewalls and you land like in a puddle,
you don't instantly die.
This guy can reach you.
What?
This looks like it would be you.
What would what would be me?
I don't know. Like a guy was walking over here.
I'm not a guy and I'm not walking over there.
I'm the guy on the my little pony.
I hate these things.
All right. So how much do you need?
How much space do you need?
Oh, this is probably good enough.
Is that all right?
Are you Brad?
No, I'm not Brad.
No, that's okay.
Three, two, one.
I wasn't ready.
God damn it, man.
I swear this fucking click out of the screen.
Bullshit.
Get on my nerves just a little.
I need to go into full screen mode.
Dude, I don't even know.
I'm just going to sit here.
I'm just going to watch your stream.
I don't even know where you guys are.
You're throwing swords at them.
You're doing all the work and I'm just like, I'm happy too.
I was lagging because last time I was doing this, it wasn't.
We also don't have a party.
So like, I don't even know where you are.
Damn it.
Oh, he just went.
He just killed us both in one go.
He just went through you and through me.
Laggy dash phase.
That was a laggy dash phase for sure.
He's such an annoying boss.
So where is he on the scale of Terraria bosses?
There's one harder than him, I guess,
which was Supreme Kalamitas after that.
Can we see it?
I never made the summon item for it.
Oh, and the item is also annoying to me.
That's why I made it.
Yeah, I don't feel like it.
Well, I'll just look at a screenshot of him.
Oh, and you need Yaren's soul fragments.
It is Supreme Kalamitas.
Supreme Kalamitas.
Okay.
That's it right there.
All right.
Is Terraria stealing other people's content live on stream right now?
What?
I'm looking at an image of...
I want to see what it looks like.
You know what I need to do.
What are you talking about?
I'm looking at like an image of the boss.
This bow won't lag because it doesn't home anymore.
So are you going for this again?
You got like a bone to pick here, huh?
Also, I'm not sure how much harder I'm making this on myself for being on a pony
and not having a dash for when he turns into instant kill dash phase.
Is it a certain health that he gets to that he doesn't?
I like the part where he goes...
...and he like teleports back and forth while he moves forward.
Those are my favorite parts about this boss.
I'm holding a piece of fucking wood.
We're not sure if he's trying to go forward or backwards.
I love that.
I fucking clicked out of the goddamn window again.
Why do I keep doing this to myself?
All right.
Here we go.
Did he get you?
Yeah, I don't have like a Crimson whatever chaos.
I can't remember the name of the rod that teleports you.
German muted?
Yeah, of course.
Uh, I accidentally did.
Yeah, and I tried it when we and Ashley are playing.
If you kill the slime god on expert, he gives you the stupid potions
that like actually make you immune for six seconds that we just swore off using.
Rod of Discord.
Yeah, there's something in Calamity that Rod of Discord upgrades into
that is better for teleporting.
I can't remember what it is.
The Rod of Discord.
That's cool.
Oh, do I have the thingy?
Is that what we call Terraria?
We got to seal all the stuff except for the last final boss, but that's all right.
Well, actually also you kill that boss, you get him to 10% health and then he runs away
and then you have to better chase him down.
No, no, like he actually leaves at 10% and then he's like, haha, you'll never beat me later.
And you do it again later and he's different ish.
Oh shit.
So technically there's two more bosses.
Yeah, and then after you beat that, you restart the whole game and play it on Revengeance.
Which actually, I hope it didn't like delete an item.
Well, I was absolutely thrilled to follow along and enjoy Terraria.
Did they already beat Moon Lord?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, that's it.
I don't know if you have anything else planned for today.
I didn't even expect to stream that long and yet here we were four hours ish.
Yeah, no, that's good.
I'll probably just hang out for a little bit.
Okay.
Maybe I'll do some random stuff for like an hour or so.
But yeah, you ready?
You want to do the outro?
Hey everybody, it's me OnlyUseMeBlade.
Check me out on OnlyUseMeBlade on YouTube
and fake hair everywhere.
Well, I would say to follow me, which is Jerma.
Oh, follow Jerma.
Okay, bye.
Follow Star too because he streams and that's it.
It's Terraria.
Thanks for watching Terraria, Star.
He's gone.
I was going to say, Terraria is Saturdays.
What do we do?
There's no other video games.
Never mind.
I forgot.
There's like no other video games to play.
I'm just imagining that guy as his Twitch streamer.
Well, okay, guys, I did it.
It's 2028 and there's no more video games.
I did them all.
Thanks for watching.
We did every console.
I've played every PC game.
I'll see you when the next game releases.
Hopefully one comes out on Tuesday.
Family Feud.
Yeah, you know, I could load up the Xbox Family Feud.
Not Kinect though.
All right, I'm going to give you guys a choice.
It's going to be up to you.
Either just Xbox, just Family Feud, no Kinect.
Just play it and hang out for like an hour or two.
Or, or we can do Talk to Transformer or Tier Lists
while we just hang out.
Those of you that are just out of here
or you're like, all right, that was it.
I'll see you later.
The next stream will be on Tuesday.
So I'll be off for a couple days here.
I'll be live on Tuesday.
But let me get a poll in the chat and I'm going to go P.
Come back and see what you guys want to do.
Let's see.
Talk to Transformer Tier Lists or we'll do Family Feud.
Again, thanks to Star.
That was glad that he got to show me all those things.
Terraria is a really, really fun game.
Got a little overwhelmed throughout it,
but that happens.
It's a lot of info to take in.
But no, it's cool.
I enjoyed it.
Otherwise, why would I have wanted to stream it all the way through?
8.6.
All right.
Strawpoll.
Talk to Transformer Family Feud, Xbox or Tier Lists.
I'll be right back.
Vote.
And I will see you guys in a minute.