What's, uh, what's happening? How you doing? Yeah, supposed to be live tomorrow, but good life today. Felt like it. Hope you're doing well.
Got a plan tonight. Uh, I was going to play Dark and Darker Tomorrow, but I saw everybody playing it and I got, I got FOMO and I didn't, I was like, okay, it's out right now. It's only going to be up for like five or six days or something.
I was like, I don't want to waste it tomorrow. I want to play it right now. I did play a handful of rounds just to get the controls because there's not really a proper tutorial. I understand how the game works. And boy, oh boy, is this game easy. My goodness. I've won every match. I have a ton of cool stuff. It's actually very simple. It's probably the easiest game I've ever played in regards to difficulty. And by that, I mean, um, it's hard for me to get
past the first two skeletons. And if I do that, I usually die in the next room. So yeah, I think it'll be fun. But I was, I was, I was like, what the fuck is going on? What is this game? What is this game? And then I decided to read the developer, um, little manual that's here. And in that manual, it says that, uh, 90% of our internal testers died to the first monster.
Now I don't feel so bad. I don't feel so bad now, but that's just the way it is. Yeah. How come you're so zesty? Why is the microphone so close to my face? Hold on. There we go. Uh, yeah. And I know this game is about, I, I join a party. Don't do it alone, but whatever. Maybe we will. Maybe eventually. I don't know. I let me just see if I like it first, right? Let me just see if I like before I like hit up a bunch of streamer friends or YouTubers, whatever, or the people in the community or whatever. What I, let me just make, let me just make sure I like it.
Surprise stream. Yes. That was easy. Where's Gunnu? Hey, Gunnu. No, no, no, no, no. People haven't, people didn't potentially watch the VOD last night. I don't want to give any spoilers. All right. So let's go. I'm just going to go. I do have a question. And I know a lot of you, this is my first time playing this. I didn't participate in the alpha first two alphas, whatever they were. So I'm going to have a lot of questions and I would like them to have them answered. If you could please help me.
Question number one, this new map, this goblin caves map, put it in the emote only. What? No, I don't do that. I need help. Is this goblin caves map something I should be doing solo? Because when I went to it and I opened it, it looked like a ton of really hard monsters were just walking around. Yeah. Because as of this update, I think it's there's a solo only map. It's only solo. The goblin cave is so hard.
Yeah. It's really hard monsters. Yeah. It's solo, but way hard. Okay. All right. Well, let's just, I'm just jumping in. Look, and I, you look, people are going to give me a lot of help. I'm sure there's going to be people that are trickling into this stream that like are going to ask, hey, I'm just like curious. Can, can this guy tie his shoes or is this like a normal thing? And I know I'm, I'm ready to, I'm prepared to look over and see so bad omega low. And I'm going to make sure it doesn't get to me. I'm going to look over. I'm going to see it probably every 10 seconds.
I've just, I know it. I, I'm in the mirror. I was, I was doing nice, relaxed breathing. I was going, all right, you can do this. We're going to be good. It's already bad. All right. Are you guys ready? I've got my drink here. I'm ready to play some games. Let's go for it. You'll be doing well. Don't make fun of me too much. I'm new. So, uh, I'm just going to do the regular mode. I made a couple of characters. This is mead one, not to be confused with mead.
Three, mead four, mead five, or smush. I have smush one, smush three, smush seven. Well, sorry, smush now. Where's mead two? Yeah, I skipped over two and I skipped over like five. I don't know who to play with.
Barbarian seems dangerous. Fighter seems like the thing to start with. I'm going to start with fighter. I'm going to start with, I got a shield. Is this a good stream to fall asleep to? Um,
ask that again in 20 minutes after I've screamed for the first time. Probably, hopefully not that loud. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to stay with the fighter. This is just the default class. It's just the fighter.
You can use most gear. You can do most things and you have a sword and a shield. I'm just going to go. I don't know why. I must have said hi at some point with the other character to nobody. All right, let's go. Let's go. I'm going.
Am I going to get stream sniped? Oh shit. I probably am. I'm going to get, I'm going to get stream sniped. Oh, it's open mic. I turned it off. I made sure to turn voice chat off. Don't worry. I put, I put stream remote on and I turned off voice chat. I don't know if that matters.
Okay. Here we go. Both headphones going in. It's time for me to try this game out. All right. It's time for me to try this game out. That was kind of E3, I will say. Okay. I already hear something. Hold on. Should I worry about people hearing my footprints?
Pick it up. What is that? Is it loud? It sounds kind of loud. Oh, a gem. Does that mean anything? Is it good? Okay, good. There's a lot. Okay. So for those of you that don't know, this is a PV, PVP, PVPVPE. Okay. I can't make any, I can't like talk. Is that a person? This is, that's a player. Is it a player?
What the, what is that? Ow. All right. So I'm dead. All right. So I died. That's, it's a good test run. I'm dead and I lost. It is kind of loud. It's too loud. All right. That's it. That's game number one. I'm trying to think of what I might have done wrong there.
I got, I got, there's too many people in that room and I met, I messed up. Is this a VR game? All right. Is the audio, how's the, how is the audio? Is it actually too soft? Like that? I wonder if that's better. Music can stay there. All right. So the whole, what can you, can I, can, what did I do wrong? What did I do? I can't do face cam. I don't have any clothes on. I literally don't have a shirt on. I can't. I'm not doing that. So should I just wait and slowly walk around and open chests and stuff?
Only engage one enemy at a time. I mean like this mother fucker right here. All right. Well, there's two enemies now. What? I didn't block it. Excuse me. Why is that not blocking? Hold on. That one doesn't count. Why did it not block? You went right through the fucking shield. It's loud. It's a timed block. Wait, it's timed. So I can't just hold it up. I have to like, oh, boom.
Okay. I'm learning. Hey, the developers of the game couldn't even get past the first run. So easy. Easy. I'm not going to uninstall the game. What are you talking about? I'm not going to uninstall it. Yeah. Well, I guess I'm going to uninstall the game. That's enough. I've had enough. Oh my God. That probably hurt. That was my blood coming off of my hand. That was nothing to do with his head. Aim at the, at the attack. I'll figure it out. Okay.
No, I'm not uninstalling it. The only way you can get good is if you get good. Nowhere in the get good manual is it uninstall the game after 10 minutes. That's not get good. I thought that hurt me. Ooh, a ring. I'm not going that way. I'll deal. I'll deal with the spiders. One hit. Okay. Look over here. Can I break that? Okay. You can break it. All right. All right. All right. Not bad.
Okay. Not bad. Not bad. Didn't take any damage. I got to move here. Actually, I don't want to go this way. The thing's coming. Look at the mini map. Should I cover the mini map? Is that what streamers do? Cause you know where I am. What is this? Why are you in this room? So is somebody saying it's a physics based block? All right. Give me a fucking diamond. Give me some gems, some jewels. Thank you. All right. How do I get out of here? I want to leave now. I got three gems.
I'm done. I want to leave. How do I get out? How do I get out of here? I need to find a portal. Where are they? Is there weight in this game? Okay. I got to go over here. I got to wrap around. I can't get this way. Head towards the middle. They only spawn near the end of the round. Okay. And the round is eight and a half minutes left from what I understand. You're looking at that, right? Watch out. I got to go. I got to go. I got to go.
How do I get through this? Can I open this? I got to go now. Is there a lever? I don't, I don't see one. I don't see one. Is there one on the wall? I don't see. I'm just going to go this way. Oh shit. I'm dead. Or the side of the door. Uh, hold on. I got kind of screwed here. I got screwed. What the fuck is wrong with me? What happened? What? Where the fuck did all these people come from? I got screwed. I got screwed. That's what happened.
I couldn't leave. And the thing, I got screwed. Is this harder than Elden Ring? Um, I don't know. Maybe it was a stone by one of the doors. I'm getting it though. I'm understanding it. Yeah. The game is meant to be very difficult by design. Well, I kind of, that was kind of a bad spawn. I got trapped behind that wall with the lever and I didn't, it was on the other side. Best to play it in a team. Well, I would like to get to a point where I see another player first. All right, let's go. I get it. This looks like a much better spawn.
Am I poisoned? I'm already poisoned. Shit. Come on, man. Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. Two movement speed. Those are pretty good. I actually am a little faster. All right. All right. All right. Campfire kit. I know this heals. Somebody shooting. Make sure to close the doors behind you. Yeah, that's true. Shit. What have you done? Why'd you aggro everybody? Oh, what have you done? What have I done? What have you done? I got him. How do I heal? Fuck you. Oh,
oh, Jesus. You can't get in here. I'm going to heal in here. All right. I feel pretty good about that. All right. So can, can rogues go invisible? What happened? Oh, I'm okay. Oh, it's only like a half heal. All right. I got to kill. I'm happy about that. I got to go loot that body. Your E is a heal. It is. Oh my God. I thought it was like a power up. Where'd that, where'd that guy die?
Oh my. Oh shit. What is this? An, a sacrificial altar. Oh, okay. I'm fucking, I'm fucking out of here. Like the whole instance aggroed to me. Okay. What was that? How do I throw this? Oh shit. A portal appeared. Did they show up on the mini map or no? The hell? How do I put, how do I equip that? All right. I'm kind of safe here. It's like three.
My friends, those, they're friends. I ain't going over there. Oh shit. It's three of them. It's three people. It's three people. I killed somebody. Shit. Holy shit. There's an omega chest. Guys. There's an omega chest right here. Oh, I can't, how do I get out of here? I hope I, I need to leave now. I'm safe right here. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. This is so much. I can take everything. Oh my God. Look at all this gear. That's all. This doesn't look good. Does anybody have anything? What a battle that came. Look at this battle that happened here.
This stuff, it's all just default shit. This guy's going over. Oh, that's like a whole party. That's a whole party. That's an entire party.
I got nowhere to run. How'd I get out of here? Use your invisibility potion? How do I switch to it? How do I switch to it?
How do I switch to it? How do I switch to it? How do I switch, how do I switch to it?
How do I switch to it? How do I, what button? Tell me. Quick. Quick. Quickly. Quick. Four. Quickly.
I'm invisible. Fuck you. I'm invisible. He can see me. Why can he see me? What's going on?
Shit that hurt who from where from behind? What are you talking about? Oh?
My god, what did I do? What happened who killed me? What's going on? What was that press E?
What was a wall trap? Oh
I gotta fight against three people he is your oh, no, I rebound it. That's why where are all the portals
That was like at the very end. There was only one little circle. That was okay. That was better
That was a pretty crazy three piece was it do you mean that you played well all right nice cool?
Oh my god. I feel like pretty good. He's blushing
Okay, well I have to apologize that all of you are about to
Completely resend those statements when I die to another trap in about
All right, give me some
So these like Diablo 2 kind of style do I put these in stuff or is it just do you just sell them very?
Interested what is that? Oh?
I'm dead run run run run. Oh, okay
I keep forgetting I keep forgetting about the heel turn the volume down more okay. Oh, it didn't even I thought I did it
There we go and change your abilities. I
Gotta get out it like I get out once I
Have to at least escape one time, but at least something
It resets every game. Oh does it yeah? I have the streamer
The streamer mode on if it's resetting the audio. I'll just do it through OBS. I'll do it right now
Just dropped it a little how's that that better? Okay? That's this is I'm in like a library all right hold on okay?
That really hurt okay. What do you have anything?
What's a quick way to scroll between the items you have in your three and four slot they added solos it seemed like the solo was
Harder like the enemies were harder. It was like five or six enemies in each room, and I was kind of overwhelming
You press them multiple times. Oh, right. It doesn't just drink it okay get out of here
Okay, free stuff. It's a friend. Okay. All right. Let's work together. What about this person never mind run
They're all decked out. They have like the look at it. They have uniques. They have like fucking purples
No, you know what fuck it. Let's get them right now. They're gonna think we're scared
We were hit two squires
To rogue squires
Going up against like the greatest knight in the kingdom what the fuck was I thinking you just got your friend killed
Oh, I'm sorry heel I keep I gotta get I gotta burn that into my brain
We were just like to like farm farm workers to like farm boys
Podrick's you were trash mobs. Yeah
Okay, this is I'm gonna get out of this one. I'm gonna get out of here
Look at all look at this room. This is the room to spawn in there's tons of shit here. All right
What do you got gold coins?
cool
22 oh shit
Is it better?
Nice, I should probably just throw this shit away now. I'm gonna put it in here
I'm gonna make somebody's day really bad. What's that 23 22 movement speed movement speed armor pen
That's kind of cool. Should I do that? I feel like that's dangerous
I don't think I have the I don't have the skill to do that right now
Wait, what it's an off-handed web. Is it an off-handed weapon fucking this is weird. What's that? What's going on here?
Is it only an offhand? Oh, that's unfortunate. It's stupid. All right, easy actually kind of cool
All right, give me another one. Yeah, do a welding. I gotta start to move. Oh, hell. Yeah. Okay
I've I've got shit on now. I just have to get out of here. How come it doesn't swing both sometimes
We're still ball. Don't let's swing. Oh, I have to swing this and then this I can't do it the other way
Okay, heel. Yep. Thank you. Appreciate it. I gotta move looks like a way to go this way. Can I go that way?
Yeah, how do I get there's like a tunnel or something? Oh shit. Nice. Holy shit. I lucked out another one of these rooms
Oh, okay. Don't don't don't don't I'm freaking out. I gotta stop freaking out. Oh fuck off
It's so easy to be greedy. Do I have a stamina bar? That's a great question. No, okay
I think I got another second or two. I need a health potion or something. Yeah
Um, I have too much stuff. Oh, come on. It should have hit I gotta dump some of this junk
What is this thing horseman's axe? Somebody's been here money. All right, let me get give me a portal get me out of here
I need a portal. Come on. What do they look like? Is it very obvious? Somebody's coming. There's a hat
Oh, I can't put it on. I can't put it on dude. You're a walking loot box. I know I thought I'm so nervous
I just want to leave
Why are you a point-and-click adventure game protagonist that's not come on somebody coming give me more money
Okay. No, no. Oh, I can get out try to stay in here. I'm just gonna sit in here. Just hide heal
I don't have a heel left. I used it already and the torch is off. Well, no, this shit is closing in
I have to leave. I think somebody just came in here. Yeah. Okay. Give me a fucking portal. Give me a portal
Is there a portal up here? Nobody right here. What did I just do? No drink it drink it. How do I drink it?
Why am I using it as a weapon? How do I use it? What's going on? Oh
What the hell is that thing? Oh, oh my goodness. No, no
Shit oh shit. Oh shit. I couldn't get it. I couldn't get it. I couldn't get it
I couldn't get it. I couldn't get it. I couldn't get it. I couldn't do it. It was too long these
They were all right behind me. Oh
That's so sad. Oh
Wait a minute open it open it open it open it open it open it open it open it open it open it open it open
It open I'm dead. God damn it. Should have just done it. I didn't know how it worked
That's the first time I've ever seen one. I in my brain
I don't know why I figured it was like press E and it just you just go in I didn't know it was like
For like 15 seconds. God damn it. That wizard was in the same position. Did the wizard get out?
Did I I let that wizard get out? That's what happened. Oh man
I took all the aggro away from the wizard or the wizard. Oh, he died. Okay. I don't feel as bad anymore
That was so close, too
I didn't know I thought you could just like go into it
I didn't know you had to sit there and open it like a treasure chest wizard was helping you
It's one portal per person. There are one time use. Oh
so
You want to be first to the center? That's one of the reasons why god damn it. Oh
All my stuff that I got
Alright, I'm getting I'm going to the center right now. I'm just trying to get there immediately after I touch this
Never mind. Oh my god. Stop
Yeah, this is the demo. So this is available right now if you want to try it if you want to play it
It's a free demo. Oh, you're behind. Okay. It's not like a beta sign up or anything. It's just you can just do it
It's good. Okay. No, I need to get to the center. Even if I leave here with one health potion, I don't care
I'm trying to I can't right-click always take out the healer first. That's what you taught me. Mm-hmm. Something's wrong. Something's wrong
God damn it 2v1 fuck your swords too short. All right
So I have two things to ask that was that a healer or am I just wrong chain your attacks together?
I mean, well, there's somebody behind you and somebody in front of you. I'm just getting fucking beat up
That was a cleric. So the cleric that green
Beam was a heal. How good is it? It's good. Okay
I was I didn't you know, I was thinking like this game is kind of a hard game and like oh, I'm a healer
I feel like it would be like a shitty heal, but it's good. It's really good. Okay, 35 on others 15 on self
It's pretty good. Okay, so sprint and second wind adrenaline. Ooh
Well, yeah, why is everybody saying I wasn't but I was being I was like BMing
Cuz I've started attacking them. Uh, all I'm saying is I walked in that room
I walked in that room and
That I don't I don't know what the moves are that caster looked at me
And then I saw like I saw him cast in a spell and I'm just like, okay
This is an aggressive spell. It was green. I thought it was a poison spell
I thought he was casting his poison spell at me. Some people are friendly. So I was just like the
crazy guy
Okay
There was even an opportunity for me to leave and I just like chugged a bunch of heels ran back in swinging
Okay. Yeah, but I don't know in a game like this. You don't expect anybody to be friendly. There's a taunt. That's kind of good
I feel like I need to use these more often. I'll be fine though. Yeah, PvP is the point of the game. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, that's true. It's like oh this guy is attacking us. We're just trying to loot. Oh, all right. He left
What's that? I hear he's he's just he's okay
I hear him doing a bunch of drugs in the other room and then he screamed her aloud and came outside
Okay, cool you need to spam crouch to say you're friendly there's yeah, there's this VoIP. Yeah, I don't I don't want to use it
I like silent protagonists. What's the whole time? They were like dude, bro. Stop chill. What are you doing?
Come on, stop man. Are you can you hear us? I don't hear anything. I just have all my ears are closed
I'm just a kill people
Rabbit animal
Bro, please dude. I'll heal you just stop. Oh, I got poisoned
Alright that poison kind of hurts. Oh, there's a tomb. Let's use it. I'm sloppy right now. Oh
Oh, all right. I can definitely I can definitely I can definitely trade this. This is some good shit
I can't lose this. I have 22 max health do a welding again. Let's go. What is this thing?
I touch this it's not gonna spit like like acid at me or anything, right? Okay. I'm gonna move here somebody
I'm ready to left. That's multiple feet. That's multiple feet. I gotta get out of here. That's multiple feet. Ah, oh my god
Didn't even I didn't even realize. Oh fuck off your bullshit. Oh my god
That was a bad. I that was a bad start. I got kind of whatever it was a secret entrance to he's getting worse
Um, I don't know if I'm getting worse. I'm just kind of getting bad starts. Can you roleplay as the silent protagonist this round?
Yeah, sure. That sounds fun. I will defend. Oh, I'm supposed to be silent this. Oh my god. Stop it this
What another shit start I even saw you do I saw you I knew exactly what was going on over here
You're not making this any easier
The sword is made out of styrofoam all it is just bad for the environment and I didn't do anything else
Oh my god, this is fucking awful. Like can I is the whole are we all right now?
Can I can I get some stuff? This thing is cracked. What does that mean? Somebody's walking?
Your feet make penguin slap sounds. Okay, not anymore. I got shoes on now
Oh my god
Fucking doc and DACA dude. All right. I'm gonna go this way into the bullshit in here. Oh my god
I died to the Sioux. Okay, everybody relax. It's doc and DACA
it's fucking hot and you got to relax because you just have to be aware of your surroundings and
Feel like an orc and orcs must die. It's just kind of whatever it's all right
It's uh, oh and I was doing pretty good there. No, that was not good
I'm I'm just going again. Oh
My hand stream snipers don't even have a chance. No, they kind of don't I'm probably pissing off the stream snipers right now
because they're spending all this time desperately trying to get over to where I am and
They they're spending like 15 to 20 minutes sometimes getting precisely to where I am and I just die in the first five minutes
And they're just like what the fuck maybe that's a deterrent to stream snipers interesting. All right, this is this is a this is a good room
Just watch out for that in the middle. Oh, come on
What the fuck is that sound? What was that? What was that? Nice green boots
plus one strength
candy oil lantern
Okay, that slows me down. I don't know if I like that. Holy shit. I gotta leave now. I just got a blue sword
Okay, get look at all that shit over there. Oh my goodness. Who's there's so much stuff over there, too
How many fucking arrows can you shoot in a row? I'm so dead. I do what?
What?
What he does that sometimes he didn't shoot two in a row the last time
Rapid animal you have to block the arrows. I mean I you watched me you watched me do it
Yeah, I went to kunk kunk and then one time he did it
He didn't do two in a row that last time and he did two in a row the next time
I couldn't to dunk it. This is the one. This is the one. This is probably not the one
You have to go into it saying it's not the one. This is no way the game's impossible. It's not the one
This game is literally not completable
Okay, so that's how we're gonna go into this one. Look at look at look at this
Look what I just got in the very first second. It's impossible. I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna do it
It's not it's impossible. I'm not gonna do it. Yeah, it's not gonna happen. Go in with that mentality and yeah, it's just not possible
Okay, it can't be done. Yeah. No, you're right. Yeah, I'm looking at Chad and I'm seeing the yeah, man
I just it just it just can't be done and I agree with you. All right
Okay, this is good I still hold on to it trying of power cool trying of protection, okay
28 better it's just not possible right like it's not gonna happen. What's up 29 good nice get me out of here
Can I not go through this? I'm hitting the ceiling. I didn't change swords. I did I can't pick the lock
All right, you want any lock picks that a player portal you see a portal? Oh, oh, uh, uh, the secret room
Why you're not doing too? Oh my goodness. All right. I got some good shit. I gotta get out of here. Don't panic
Don't panic. I still have a heel too. Oh my god. Look at all this shit screens
Do I'm rich if I get out of here? It's not I can't be done. Give me a portal. Where is the portal?
Oh get that shit away from me. What's that? Oh my god. I want nothing to do with you, man. Excuse me
I see blue. What the fuck is doing that? He died something killed him. It was a spider stupid fucking wall traps
Where are I don't know quiet? Why just leave there's no portal
Get me get me get me get me the fuck out of here
Give me the fuck out of here. Give me the fuck out of fuck that spider if that spider bites me
I'm gonna be pissed. Let me out. Let me out. Let me out. Let me out. Let me out. Let me out
How do I go in how do I go in how do I go in I made it?
I did it. I actually survived once. Holy shit. Now what how many people are left just two
They're kind of away from each other though. That means I get to keep all that stuff, right? Okay, that's it
Now you play another one and lose them all you can also go into a level two portal keep the useful loot sell it
Yeah, there's that you have a stash right the red portals will take you deeper. Well dark grows darker. So now what?
Oh, look at this. I got some good stuff. Look at this. It's a training sword
Okay, so it's a stacks of their quick way to put it in the inventory alt-l
Divide alt-r drop shift R. These things are pretty damn good. Okay. Okay. This is a rapier
I can use this but why not? Why can't I use it? I've been damaged 20. Oh, no, I'm not a ranger
I'm a fighter try. I hope I could hold on to this for other classes though, right? That's into the whole point 813
Yeah, no each character has their own stash. You can trade it. Okay stashes per character
So there's no real reason for me to hold on to this to sell it to the does the jewelry do anything else like this?
Rare piece of or a uncommon jewelry. Is that me? Is it just sell? Is it just money? No, I just sell it. Okay. Um
So what like treasury gold and silver is my language
How may I help with your financial needs the wrong person collector sell?
I'll pay you top price for any unique trinkets you can bring back three. Ooh, this one's five eleven three
Okay, 25 gold shift right-click. We'll put him in. Hell. Yeah. Wait, hold on. Oh shift right-click moved it to my stash
Look at this. I already got a stack going right now. It's a shift left. Click. Okay. Okay, so I'm gonna just sell this crap
The tailor the armorer right so there's zero I get this third 62
I'm gonna buy this how much do I have I have I got money. I'm buying it. Let's go. Do you want this?
Service this is this is all this is all completely just foreign to me. I don't even know what's going on here
But quest coming soon. Okay. All right. So what about um
Weaponsmith, what do you got? This thing's 29. I got 60 gold 29 move me move move speed
1.1 physical damage thing. I have now is pretty good. Wait, this thing's 34
I'm keeping this one as a backup. You can have this get the better shield too. I will
22 though, that's kind of expensive. It's a two-handed shield, huh? No, okay. I'm good with that. All right surgeon
bandages, oh
45 gold how many three that's it. That's a bunch of shit 45 gold. Hmm pickaxe
Oh, this is how you get the or I don't want to go too crazy because I don't I'm not gonna go too crazy
Unidentified, uh, it's keyed. I get it. You could wait. I don't I have silver didn't I pick up
Oh, no, I probably died at some point collector. Okay
Valentine before the big bag these sweet colorful treats. I have some of these. Holy shit. I have it
I have like ten of those. Oh, no, I died. Well, thanks for the raid raid came in from J6 J6
Thank you. Welcome everybody playing doc and DACA. I think I got I think I'm ready. I'm ready to go again now
Wait, no, I'm not I want a helmet. There's so many interesting things that tavern master ale. Oh, I want potions
54 I found that would you get this?
54 that's so much money. Why is this one so much better three? Yeah, but alright
I'll take one. Oh, no, what 15 versus? Well, I just got ripped off gathering hall. Okay class. Ooh
Level I guess someone else Reese's a are acquired from armor by 10% I think this is this is new. That's good
Okay, worst. The worst thing that could happen is I got 23 bucks. Wait, I have an empty slot
Oh, I see what you mean. Okay, I'm in a defensive stance. The defense rating is increased physical attack power temporarily increased by temperatures
Successful defensive mule speed dual belting. I kind of want that. I'm wearing heavy armor. Okay. Am I ready?
Okay, get destroyed. Am I good? Let's go. I've got items the goblin caves. Am I ready for the goblin cave? It's done
Yeah, I got armor this time bring me it's over. You're gonna lose everything. No, I'm not. No, I'm not dead in three minutes
I bet you or ban me. Is that what you said? This is a new enemy
I'm gonna pick up the gear on you. What the heck? Oh my what the fuck is this thing? Oh
Okay, I'm just gonna hide. I'm literally gonna hide in the corner. This is this is insane
I just got like I got a fucking blue. I got a blue
I'm gonna hide in the corner the whole game that person's gonna get banned just bro escape now escape escape escape escape
Leave now. I don't know how I don't know how to leave. How do I leave now that hurt if I leave now leave now, dude
I don't know how to get out of here. Oh now I'm nervous. I'm actually very nervous. This seems like a really good weapon
I gotta get a I gotta I'm gonna go very slow. Goodness bandage. Nice. Is that a portal down there?
Do you have is a fall damage? Yes or no this I think there is how do I get down? Don't lie
They didn't lie. Thank God. I think there's a portal right over here. See that blue. That's not a portal
I hear somebody screaming. I gotta go back up open the chest. No. Oh my god. There's a lot of people in here
Thank God, he's got a blue he's got a blue that was a paid actor
No, it wasn't is this poison is this poison just go cuz that sound give me a portal get me the fuck out of here
Give me a portal
Good luck, dude, I don't even want to fight you. I don't even want to fight you don't close that door
Give me out. Give me out. Give me out quick. Oh
Everybody follow me out here. There's a bunch of fucking adventures get out of the fucking way
Where is a portal? How is there not a portal here? Do you look there? Oh, well, there's no else to go. Oh
Fuck you run run run. I got nowhere to run. Where is a give me that fucking thing on your back. I'm dead
I'm dead. I'm dead. Where are they? Yeah, this sucks
Where I did look at this. I'm literally running around in circles. Oh
My god, you mean to tell me that there's only there was one portal up here somewhere. Oh, that's such a pain in the ass
We're running around this little fucking circle and what one of the two dickheads is gonna find it
This yeah, there was a big ramp. Yeah, I'm being followed by this whatever that guy is
He could he completely fucked me over when he closed that door
Oh, that's so fucking sad. I had so much good shit too. He stopped you from going the wrong way
Well, yeah at 2020 hindsight. We all know the portal is up here. Was it two portals up here? Well, I lost everything
I still believe another one spawns in the end. Is that right? Well, we go we go for it again
Sad I was right there too. It's just like where fuck I had such a good weapon
Portal bullshit. All right now I'm pissed off. I'm go. I'm just going in I'm killing I don't know friendly
I'm not gonna crouch with a sandwich in my hand. Everybody's dead everyone. I'm going in
All right, you are you have a whole combo. I'm dead. I can't move. I can't fucking move
Don't fight these why not? I thought that was a naked player. I thought that was a nude player
That's a boss. Oh should have just crouched with a sandwich. Yeah, I was gonna say where the hell am I?
There's so many people in this in this solo area
Am I am I crazy or is there like three times as many enemies in solo than the team stuff?
I'm sorry. This guy has the whole dungeon on him. I know what it's like man. Trust me. I know it's
I'm getting out of here. See you later. I want nothing to do with this. I help him. He's got seven
He's got seven ghouls on him. I
I'm not gonna help. Oh my god. Everybody has the same problem
Okay, there's a potion here. Hold on help help. I hold on
Yet now I've got the aggro
I'm gonna drink this. Hey, let's go. Let's team up on voice command. Oh
You had that did oh, no, no, no. No, it did not it's in front of me. What is in front of me?
What the fuck is this?
Jesus are you talking Joe? What are you talking about?
What?
Do this one is way harder. All right, you know when this shit is fucking hard and
Just a little much when each person I saw I saw two different people had a an
Absolute just there was a choo-choo train of enemies running after
Single person dude. This is laser tag on steroids. That's funny. I was fair and better in the team stuff
Alright same spot. I need you to test it. That is hit myself with the sword. I'm hitting myself with my own weapon
I'm already in trouble. There's a player. Alright, give me some stuff. Alright way back. I just got a green ring
That's gonna be worth like 20 bucks. What was what is that? Oh, I might say that they can't fire eight eight
Oh shit. Okay, I'm going in. What is that? I got okay. I'm gonna set it. I gotta move. No, I got a bandage
No, no, no, no, I don't want to swing. Why is this what I'm not pressing any buttons?
I'm I might literally my hands are in the air guys. I'm not pressing any buttons. Stop swinging
I'm not pressing any buttons. I probably just looked like a fucking crazy person comes to the campfire
Look, that's the dumbest thing in the game. There's literally should be removed
They literally they should take it out of the game tomorrow. You take all this stuff. Ah, you missed this thing on the bottom
Oh stop. That shit is way harder. I'd rather fight the three players. You can see traps on the map
Really? I can't believe you're dying to level one goblin enemies. Yeah, pretty rough. All right. There we go
Look at this already getting started with some fucking wines of olive oil. You holy shit. That's not bad
Can't use it. But okay. I gotta go down. Oh
Okay, that's a good start take my time here
I'm kind of in the middle so I don't really have to go that far that on nice. Oh, yep
Those better 30 25 now, I'll hold them though. I get this whole area to myself spell book longbow
You go in the hole. Maybe ooh surge full heel. Oh my goodness. It's a full heel
Okay, I got no excuse now. Where's the actual circle right now?
I feel like I'm very far away from it. There's a lot of shit in here. I'm gonna hang out it for a minute
I think it's pretty quick too. It's a lot of money. Okay, let's go
Loot so many chests. I gotta turn and run in a second here. Okay time to move
I got a lot of money to one more chest and I'm gonna go I promise
Yeah, I think sucks a lot of shit here. Look at all this stuff. No, I want to pick it up
I want to pick it up. I want to leave leave. I am going I need a portal. It's up man
What the fuck is that? What just happened? What was that something just exploded? Oh, I got okay. Oh my shit
I thought he was alone. All right. What what is what is that? What is this bullshit right here?
Why are there two here? What is this bullshit? How come there's two why wasn't what?
What's going on with the weather three portals in the same spot, dude?
I was running around like an asshole when I had all that shit and there was only one there in the middle
I was it directly in the center. What look at all these there's so many in this spot. Oh
Come on
You don't start spawning till late
You should get near the center early then camp out till you see the prompts about a portal the caves I guess
We actually might have a friend here. Hold on a second. I
Want it? I was gonna play with other I'm definitely into it. So I'm down to party in random places. It's all good
I gotta make it I gotta make it out with something. Oh
I thought a piece of glass like burnt me or whatever. You know, I mean at least sharp stab pain
Oh, look at that. Don't go near that. Are they red fuck you
Come on
way, I
Gotten a lot of gems and jewels. I picked solo, right? So what were they guarding? Can I open this? It's locked
Hold on. Well, I have a second. Hold on typing my attack went right through him. Ooh
What's resourcefulness? What does that do? He's sending he's sending emails to Gunu. My whole inventory is
Stuff that okay. I gotta get out. I'm getting out of here now. I have to escape. I just get so obsessed
They're supposed to be dead. Dude guy you stink how many spiders are in this cave, please leave
I'm I'm right now. Um, um, yeah. Okay. We're good. Okay. All right you you good. We good, dude
Why is this thing still alive? Why is this thing still alive? I hit it like seven times. We are we cool
We're all cool, right? Oh my god. This is how you play
You don't just like you just don't act like a rabid animal
Wow, what's that? Oh, thank you. I thought he's gonna hit me. I am NOT going to kill it
No, I need I you know how many you know, I'm not gonna say this out loud. I don't have shit on me
I have nothing on me. I don't have a bunch of jewels or anything. Did you crouch? Did you crouch yet?
What's this? What the fuck is that? Oh my it's a red spider. No, that is not happening. Uh, uh-oh
Is there a way to go? No. No, what do I do? I think I've just got I don't know
How do I how do I how do I fix this? How do I fix this? I have to run through it
Bro, where are the freaking portals?
They gone why is there not one here?
I thought it would spawn in a circle where I was they were on the floor above me, bro
With all that verticality, how can you tell where one ever is?
They're all first-come first-serve. They always seem to spawn on the top floor
Is that is that for real or is that just so they're always on the top floor? I made it up
Oh, I'm just a day win motherfucker. Not that easy. There we go. All right, we're back in it now
We're back in it. You just killed your friend
You get hit once dude, you're fucking it's over god damn it. What the fuck I'm already dead
Your health is low. Do you have any potions or food? I don't know what's up there, but I'm not going over there
Sorry, I read that from chat. I had to do it. What you there's no way you hit me with that
Get out of town. I'm in so much trouble. No, no, no, I'm in so much trouble. There's a fucking plate right there
What's going on? Ah, what? Where are they?
This is so hard, I got decapitated
God damn it. I got a but I got I gotta buy something. I have to buy something. I'm buying
I'm gonna lose all my money buying buying this longsword. No, I'm not 34. I'm buying this
I gotta give myself a chance, right?
47 this one's 13 the believers are filing for bankruptcy
At least I have some armor and more than 20 damage. We're good. Everything's good. Does he make it out alive?
2.1 to 9 point Wow. Well if I win I make a lot of you really really rich with channel points
That's for sure. I was just a lever. This thing is huge. You just put two that that's what's in here
I was stuck. It was so loud. Patch it. What is this? What did that do? Secret? Stop it. Stop!
Throw a torch at it. Yes. Ooh
A spear. I don't know how to use this. Is it 34 versus 39? I don't know
It's where I got a lot of reach though. Okay. So the last one is a swing down
Looks like it has a block at least or the parry at least. Okay, cool. All right, let's go. What do I?
Why this is a maze but that was a player that's shit away from me. Oh
Portal up. Holy shit you oh my god. How'd tell me how to tell how can you tell?
Yeah, okay. Okay
Okay, I'm not look. What do I do? What the fuck? There's no pressure plate
They just they're just little blended into the walls. The map will show that's so teeny tiny
I ain't looking over there. What it wasn't on the map. I'm looking at the map right now. What am I standing on?
Excuse me. What what is happening? Did you see the mini map? It was there was two behind me
There was one what my my indicator was on top of it my little indicator
It's so teeny little tiny my characters arrow indicator was covering it
You can crouch crouch. I didn't know you could avoid it by crouching this
How was I supposed to know that?
It reminds me of
Darkest dungeon when some you just walk in and all of a sudden it's just like yeah
Like the thing just fucking the trap on the ground just attacks you I'm fucking angry now
You I know, you know, I was that me or you well, I thought that was that I thought there's a mage
I thought that was a player. This is not a player
Man I get
What fuck get him kill him with this shit die
That was such a shitty spawn. Oh, well swing at it. I'm good. That thing's like a super hard thing block it
I think it goes through the block Otto. What it's Otto
Dog needs Otto. It's Otto. That's cool. That's cool
Remember that was a cat. Everybody loves Otto. You're dying too fast for mods to be able to put up new poles
Dude, I'm sorry. What am I supposed to do?
back back
Good I get poisoned. Oh, come on. That's a big deal. That's one knowledge. I'm so much smarter with this on look
Oh, I want to mine this so bad. That's where you get the crystals. They're more than one. It was two burning eggs
Agility and action speed nice. Okay, not bad. Can't put any of that on try to dodge it a lot of boots down here
18 pretty these things this is all crap. I don't even this is not even worth selling. Yeah wizard shoes
Who's gonna buy that? No one's gonna I know I was gonna want to even take that from me. There are some
I'm gonna try to get out of here. Did you come from? Where'd you go?
What did you come from? Got Nigel the group over there. Boy, I'm mashing. I'm mashing it. That means I'm a friend
It doesn't care. It doesn't care. It doesn't care. He doesn't care. Oh my god. I had 50% HP
Crouch and people will be friends that first was a rabbit animal just like I whatever I had didn't have very much help
I had like what half health I tried to do I pressed control too many times
I sticky keyed myself as somebody that was just easy to kill control control control control
Kill that one. Oh nice. I'm so addicted to this game, but I can't win
Frustrating get your ass away from me
Just restart
Fucking pissed trying to the class. I want I need to get it at least one more. I need to get out one more time
I'm not turning the stream off unless I survive again. I don't care if I'm here for ten straight days
I'm not turning the stream off until I get out again. I don't care if it takes a hundred years
I don't care if I turn to dust in this chair. Okay, we're good. This is not a bad place to spawn
Explosion bottle. Why am I not doing the strategy? This is impossible. I'm never gonna do it. Everybody accepted right now
It's never happening. I will never do it. It's just I mean they pack it up. This is not happening
It's never gonna happen. I escaped last time I said that
Look at how much stuff is on that fucking goddamn cupboard. Oh hell
That hurt a lot
You didn't hit me you swung around my body you look at all this stuff. Oh my god. It's so many things
I'm taking oh my god. That was a blue. I'm taking the I'm taking the whole entire antiques roadshow with me
I have to get out of here now. I'm just gonna I'm gonna run to the middle. I'm gonna hide
I'm literally gonna hide in a corner. What the fuck? Why do I hear so many noises? What is that? Oh, I'm so fucking jumpy
Hey, hey, hey, they back fuck you
You piece of shit, no, I wasn't ready I wasn't ready I wasn't ready. I wasn't ready. He scared the fuck out of me
Oh my god, it's just like he appeared behind me and he my heart started to go fuck
I had a full heel how but I am I gonna be like done
How long does it take to heal every other heel in the game besides the health potions?
Is it like an instant heal? I'm thinking like it's a bandage
It probably takes a long time and he's doing this like or back forward for back for back for back stab forward back for back
He swings so much faster than me. It takes a good 30 seconds to heal with the surgical kits
Yeah, was that a poison dagger too? I feel like it was it was poisoned. Oh, there's three things here
Never mind. You'll do an attack chain
Yeah, but I feel like though it's me holding down the attack button
He'll stab me four times and I'm dead like I have to block so much shit in here
Alright, why does out played by the AI the AI stopped moving and just sat there looking at me regardless of the loss rate
Well, I mean it's the first day I've ever played it. Give me give me a break. I've never played this before
This is the first time I've ever played a video game as I'm an actor. I'm an actor. I don't play video games
I'm an actor stop. All right, let's do it. I'll change classes after this. I'll try the I'll try the Ranger Ranger rules
Did I get it? I did. Okay Ranger is snooze
Um, I would want to try it at least once Rangers not great solo
I feel like this is a great solo class to be wrong. Is that incorrect rogue is wizard is crazy
Solo really you like spaghetti. This is my only question. Yeah, I love spaghetti. I'll be taking that one. This looks like a trap
I'm wait. It's not on the mini map. It's not on the mini map. Where is it on the mini map?
It's not on the mini map. It's not on the mini map. I think I'm all right
I'm
Help help. I won't fight you. I won't fight you. I won't fight you. Let's work together
I'm not gonna fight you. Look see I haven't swung at you. I'm protecting you. I'm helping. Let's go. Let's get out of here
Yes, I feel like he's gonna hit me. Well, I keep like I don't know
I feel like he's gonna hurt me. We should probably be Wow. Okay, cool. All right, we need if we gotta find a portal
We gotta get out of here. It's bugleberry. Should we try to kill the boss? What is going on here? Hey, stop hitting me
Why is he hitting me? Why is he hitting me? Wait, who's wait? What was a different person? It was a different guy
What do you mean? That's a different guy. It looked exactly the same. It was the same person. That was a different guy
They had the same exact clothes on it was the same person
All the classes look the same, but yeah, but they had the same robe on they had the same staff
No, they didn't he had like a club. I don't whatever I he was behind me. I turn I turn around he's right there
I'm thinking that's my buddy with the fucking magical shit. Okay, maybe it was a trap. Maybe he lured you into it
Damn it. I need to I spent all my money. I have like five gold. Yeah, I I kind of just I see a
Bugleberry walking towards me. I'm like, oh, that's bugleberry because he was just he was right there a second ago
And then I get hit in the head with a fucking mace. It's like wait, what's happening?
Why is everything going dark my head hurts?
So bad there's a diamond
Just leave right still alive run now run now run now run now
Okay
Bugleberry, okay. I've got a diamond good work. You could take that loot. I'm a fucking good guy like that. Yeah, I know I get it
See, it's not just me. Don't make you make fun of me. It's not just me. It's not just me
Everybody gets hit by that shit. He's dead
Right now
I can't do this right now. What happened? I feel so bad
Oh
He's got like fucking jewels on him though. I give me a portal get me out of here already. I got I have like stuff
I'm okay. I'm just I'm gonna find a portal. I'm just going to the middle. This is gonna be awful
Look, we're in this room this huge
Look at all this verticality all this bullshit camp in the middle until the circle closes in in the portal spawn
That's that's kind of the goal right now
I'm just gonna sit right here and no one's even gonna fucking see me. I need to go over here
Okay, I'm going in here and I'm gonna hang out in this one
This is where I'm gonna just sit turn all the turk close every door and turn all the torches off
One person has escaped one person escape portals appeared you fucking piece of shit. I would die. Yeah, that's how he died
Where is it? Come on. Is it above me or something? I'm gonna go up. Oh, I can't I can't do it
I can't do it. I can't do it. I'm gonna die if I go up
I don't have any more healing potions you have to this game is so fucking hard
the fact that you have to find one of these portals and it could be anywhere and like
Go so that so there was one portal somewhere in that area
Somewhere I mean I was just down I went up but the thing is already there
If you waited another portable to spawn you were the last person is there any way I can see that or is it?
I just keep track of the kill feed. How would I know? I'm the last person does it tell you?
I kind of just want to die so I can just start the maps. Oh, I'm wearing them out
I see the timer does it show player count? I'm done. I'm dead
I'm just trying to see like where is there an indicator? It's on top now that one doesn't count
So let me I got a question
So even if everybody is dead you're dead too if you don't go in one of the random portals
Everybody's dead. You still have to leave the same fortnight focus on just finding a portal, you know
Yeah, I'm not gonna find one till late game
So is it a certain minute wise or a certain how big the circle is the one the one thing?
I'm getting confused at is so I was the last person left there
How come the oranges portals everywhere in that because remember like three or four games ago?
There were like five portals in the middle at the end. It's just based on time. It was map size
In the goblin caves only three portals open up every time only three people could leave my god
That sucks. It's based on how many players are there is this well somebody's walking not that person by the way
I heard something. No, I'm telling you. It's not this person. Okay. I got a pretty good helmet ten goddamn minutes
I get it all I'm kind of in the middle already. So now just go up
Where is up? Somebody was here. There's something is anything on the on the mini map look like a staircase
Like what does the staircase look like on the mini map? I don't think it looks like anything. Okay, I'm up now
I always make a habit of crouching in hallways not a bad idea nice alright besides my weapon. I've got I'm alright
I've got some pretty good stuff. Why am I going down? Oh, okay? Never mind after this. I'm just going for survival
This is a huge chest come on. Give me something give me something. Just let me hide. It's alright 49 pretty good
23 33
Get rid of that crap get rid of this bow to fuck this thing get rid of this tunic. Okay, all right all right
It's time to escape with the jewels and the gems. Oh
No, okay a portal is out. There's a magical sword in there. Can it jump over? Oh?
Goff I want whatever that is. Oh
That's pretty good. Oh, I'm so bad at inventory management
We friends if you careful be careful. Whoa, that's dangerous up there. I don't get through this
Why can't I get through that equip the sword? I can't on I need a portal look for the portal
That's what I'm doing. I'm telling you. I'm looking for one right now. Is that one right there might be get me out of here
Get me out of here. Get me out of here. Get me out of here. Get me out of here
Get me out of here believers. We made it second time tonight
Oh, that's so stressful needing to go find one of these fucking things
It's so stressful because you just don't know where it is and there's so many people that are trying to kill you
Okay, I did get some decent stuff. I should be able to sell some of that
I'm gonna put sunglasses on so many emotes. Yeah, you earned it you earned it
Did a fun game it is it's very addicting. It's very very hard though. It's a game where one
Single mistake will just delete all the stuff you have and I am very prone to mistakes
So take that as you will
Yeah, I was gonna maybe party up with some people but I wanted to make sure I actually liked it first
rather than get into a game with two or three people and it's like I actually really don't really like it and
20 minutes into the game be like, well, sorry guys, it's not for me and leave I think I can just exit right?
It's not gonna hurt me. Oh my god. All right. Look at all this. I got a big battle axe
Okay, but I haven't clicked on a merchant in four hours or whatever. It's been nice nice Jesus
76 bucks actually have money now. So the real question is is it worth me taking that perk to use this?
No, so I should just sell it shield is better. Yeah, uh, I'm gonna hold on to these. All right
I got 94 bucks. I get rid of this thing
3323, okay, so we're gonna be conservative Andy if I have a decent one
I'm not gonna I'm gonna take the worst one
we're gonna be conservative Andy here and I'm gonna take all my money in my inventory and
Just cuz I really want to like flash my wealth around you know, I mean
Yeah, I feel like that would be like I like somebody's little brother if you killed somebody in the head like a hundred gold
On or something if they go you just don't you don't understand what's happening right now. It's gotta be nice
I refuse to have a stash that doesn't look perfect. Okay now I might take some of this shit off depends
All right weapons see those blue letters and it just makes me sad. Uh
22 I could buy a
Bowshian things pretty good don't buy weapons. I'm gonna buy it armor
Can I serve button I can do to compare or is no I just have to mouse over
This is the same thing which is a little higher. Is there anything that I'm missing? Not really. Yeah by healing supplies
NHP 15 HP this just way worse. Hold on three of these versus three of these that's an extra 15 health
45 gold 15 HP over 20 seconds
15 HP over 20 seconds
I feel like the bandage is just better but you can drink that and move around this one's cheap six now
It's the same. Let's just do only one gold. I'll take it Taylor
I want to buy this so bad, but I don't have enough money now. I need a hundred. Okay. All right. Here's the here's the plan
Here's the plan going for it going for it. I'm scared to take most of my good stuff, but you got to do it
Okay, here we go survive perks you fool if you see a party of three run
How much longer you're gonna go tonight at least another couple hours?
Already blew it. See the problem is my I'll talk in a minute. All right. The problem is I
It's really hot in this room and I'm wearing a big ass sweater. I mean it's open
I'm I it's just like a it's like a it's not even it's not a sweater. It's just like a it's like a sweatshirt
I'm there's nothing under here. It's just I'm kind of bare chest and bare belly and I just have this thing on
I don't know why I put it on. I was like, why did why did I put this on?
I don't have a webcam on anymore. Who gives a shit. Why are you wearing a sweater? It's not it's like a little
How do you even describe it's like open?
It's like an open sweatshirt. I was like what I thought you I thought you will
I thought you said you hadn't didn't any clothes on why'd you lie to us and world ain't fair. All right
Was a cardigan no, it was not I would not wear a cardigan right now. Ooh, was it better? Oh, I'm sorry for lying
I wasn't actually lying though. I was like shirtless. Sorry didn't know you were doing that
Shoot your buddy in the back, please
Lot of stuff in here use your heels you bought I'll save them 10. Well, okay
That was a lot. Is there already time to leave? I don't need two shit leather caps. Do you forgive me?
Can I pick that up somebody was here? Okay, relax. You already clean this place out whomever nice
What if I'm a friend you probably have friends. He's probably screaming over discord right now. He's probably like hey, hey
There's a guy here. There's a guy here. He's got good gear man. Good gear. No, I ain't fucking with that
He's literally probably in voice chat right now with two other people that you imagine looking at this guy
You look at what I got you're coming for me the portal. Oh, I can't use that
Somebody said hey, dude, this dude's gear is ass. Let's ignore him
Hey, this dude's gear is ass. Don't worry. No, no, no guys. Everything's gonna be fine. I've been watching this dude stream
He's literally only escaped twice and he's been playing for four hours. I mean, he's probably gonna die
Anyways, I kind of feel bad killing him. He's like one of these shitty streamers that like does not have play
I feel kind of bad. He's lighting something on his hand
Everybody has you have friends. Don't you I'm gonna go the other way. There's portals everywhere now where I'm sorry
That fucking scared the shit out of me. I thought they were behind me. I really thought they were behind me
There's so many portals. How have I not run into one? How have I not run into one actually hit me?
I need my fucking torch. Oh, what's that sound sound? I heard when I heard it. Hey, hey, hey
I heard I said, where is it? I heard one. I just heard it. Where was it? I hear them. Where are they? Where's a portal? Oh
You
That's more money I didn't think you could get any louder, I'm sorry
All right for one second. I thought this was a three-part story like something
This is like a cards on this character like he was eating something
He ate it and it was gross and it hurt him or something. It looks like oh like I'm testing this and it's like
Ah, I thought it was like the read for some reason for one second
I was like, oh, he's like poisoned. He ate something story in 3x not bad. Nice. All right. What do you do with silver?
All right, like silver. What do you what do you do with it? You got more perks? Yeah. Oh, check it out. You sell it
That's pretty good. Nice 20 more bucks. Um, I'll keep the bear trap now. I have a really important question
Do I buy this should I do it? It's gonna be a blue weapon
I'm gonna lose it all of my money, but it'll be worth it cuz I'll have a blue in my inventory
I'm not gonna equip it. I'm not equipping this. I just want to make sure I have a blue
So if somebody comes to this stream and they see me at stash they go, all right, he's got a blue
He's fucking all right. He knows that he's done. He's got a blue up there
I was gonna I was literally just gonna leave the stream, but he's all right spend on utility so you can survive
Do I sell this to him not interested in buying what it's a way again. Explain to me
What it do with silver sell to the treasurer?
Golden golden silver is my language by the one. Oh, wait a minute. Oh
One is free five is 15
Is it my getting scammed or is this just the exchange rate by a coin purse notice? It's just always three to one
Okay. All right. This is really good much more money now
120 bucks I can't even use this I should just sell it. I actually can't use it. Let's go again
All right. Hold hear me out on this. I'm just going in naked because I don't know how to use this weapon
I'm just going to naked. Okay. No. Yeah, why not? Yeah. No, fuck it
Is it true that you spent a hundred dollars on the family guy mobile game? What year is it right now?
Asking that why are you asking that? Why are you asking me this? Do you want me to answer the question? Yes back in
2013 or 2014 I may have spent
$75 on the family guy the quest for stuff mobile game. I don't know. I just did it
I didn't I did that didn't do it ever again. It was stupid. I did I I'm very
I'm very ashamed. Well, no, no, I'm not it was no, I'm not I don't care. It wasn't a joke
I doubt yeah, it's the only time I've ever done anything like that. I don't I don't care. We think I care
I don't care. Yeah, I spent 70 bucks on a family guy mobile game. Okay, it was fun for it wasn't even it was just like
It was like dopamine or something. I don't know. It was an iPad toilet game
This is like this is like nine years ago, by the way
I can't believe you spent $75 for toilet entertainment. Well, hold on
It was like it was like five dollars at a time and then after I got to like near a hundred
I was like, all right, I'm done
And I uninstalled it
It just I uninstalled it five. Yeah, it was I did five dollars
Sometimes it's $75. So you wasted money. Yeah, I mean remember that's so much
This didn't this didn't happen like a last weekend. Oh, that's a weird first swing. What this is really weird swinging pattern
So what? Yeah, what let me ask you this what dumb what dumb things have you bought over the course of your life?
I'm sure we all have stuff bro guys, bro guys, bro, guys
I was gonna say guys. I'm naked like it's very cool. No, I'm not naked anymore. Let's go
You want to fight you aiming that bow? Oh, I see you aiming that bow. Oh that hurt
You get the whole fucking Wizard of Oz behind you. Come on, man. And that's why we did that
What was that? Hold on people were betting when I went in there with a weapon. I've never used naked
I don't know that was not. Oh, what a that doesn't sound like a sound investment to me. Hmm
I think that's on the level of family guy
Mobile game purchases, don't you think? All right, we're going for a real one this time
Yeah, I I know how much people spend on mobile games
Do I don't think I want to take everything like it's always a mistake to do that, but we got it
We got to go. We got to go in right? We're gonna go all in I have money. Yeah, we're going in
This is all junk. I just like delete it or something. I am I want everybody
I want ever I want everyone to raise your hand in here. Hold on a minute
Let's let's break this down very quickly. How many hearthstone card packs did you open get out of here?
Get out get out of here. Get up. Just leave now. Get up. Get up. Get out of here. Get up zero
Dude give me a break
I'm not gonna I'm not gonna get fucking do you want to know something funny? I know I did
I may have spent more money. No, that's not is that true. No, I don't think so
I don't really spend that much money really don't okay. I think I'm ready to go
I'm gonna take some of the good shit. Let me do my perks kind of like that
I've spent over two hundred dollars on Pokemon cards
Yeah, I I mean that some of the mobile game stuff is just clicking on a house to collect coins
So that's a little different. I'm going in I split I spent over three hundred dollars on planetside to cosmetics. Yeah, whatever
Hey, whatever. Yeah, it's hey you hey, what whatever you want to spend your money on it's up to you
You've based just don't go overboard with everything spend you buy whatever you want
You got if you've got some money that you want to spend on something go for it. Don't go overboard. Yeah, I
Somebody just said it. I it's people are acting like I spent 50 grand in the family guy
Mobile game a lot. Oh, I gotta get this shit before the look
I'm right in the middle so many parties of free you're gonna waltz in here
I gotta get everything and run away. I can't believe you spent
150 thousand dollars on the family guy
Mobile game you all right. What do you do? Are you doing that? He's everything. Okay. Hey, I told you that I knew it
You play with a party where you get jumped by three people
Well, you play solo and you fight the fucking goblin horde and lose everything's gone
At least I have I still have money you didn't use II. I kind of was like not even any time
I think I would have died well before the hill over time happened
That rogue just got right up my face and was just like bap bap bap bap bap bap
How do you how do I how do I what do I do about that?
I feel like I feel like I couldn't do anything about that
He was just like right in my character's character model just going step step step step step step dad dad dad
What do you do hit him back?
All right, just run just kill
Hit a fucking mage with him. Did I cut my finger cooking any tips?
Go to the doctor. How bad is it? It's bad. Go to the doctor get stitches or whatever
Elton if there's gonna I'm telling you there's gonna be some Eve online shit with this game when it eventually is done and everything
It's already and everything that comes out. They're gonna be people decked out in all
Legendary fucking uniques and they're gonna lose and it's gonna be an Eve online moment
There's gonna be one point where you're gonna get all decked out. You're gonna go into a lobby. You're gonna lose everything
It's gonna be so sad
I'm actually kind of happy that I'm not really doing that
Well, and I'm not just keeping that many things
Because I'm gonna get really attached to like a blue or purple and I'm going to literally stare at the wall for an hour
If I were to lose it, there's a high roller mode for that. Yeah, the hundred goal to go in
Sucks I would okay. I would definitely watch people do that. That's way too scary for me
I'm just gonna pretend like I don't see this person. He's trying to get my attention so bad
I watch this watch this, but I'm doing this for the joke. I don't care. He's probably like this kid sucks
Like I guess I just saw him right like wait. Oh, are they watching the stream?
Thank you. I appreciate it. I'll drop the spiders working together
Hey, do you mind if I get all the jewels? Hey, thanks. Hey, do you mind if I get all the jewels? You know this guy?
I'm just kidding. You can have it. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Have it you can take it
You can have it. You can have it. You can have it. You can have it. How do I drop it, dude?
I used to play Diablo 2. I don't fuck around. How do I do? How do I get have give back just drink?
I just drag it out. What's he doing? All right. Well, I'm taking this wrong with me
Oh, I find our way out of here. I think this is a different person. All right, let's go loot this shit
We're definitely gonna get a portal. Oh, you're mining. Nice. Oh, it's friend, right guys
It can be hard to tell all right portals here portals here
I'm gonna go up right up portals are up portals are up portals up right you need to get out get out get out
I don't know where like where's a portal down down. I don't see anything like wait
Wait, do you actually mean that like I actually can't see it. Where is it? I think we're in trouble. What do we do?
What do we do stone ramp? Well, these guys don't know where to go either. I just heard something. I heard it
Where is it? Where is it? I dude everything has fucking collision. I I don't know where to go
I just heard something up the ramp. I I'm gonna die. I think I'm alright. Hold on. You mean like up here, dude
I like this mode. Where the fuck are they? Why did I wait so long?
Dude, this this level is like seven thousand feet tall. Well, okay, I got trapped
If you're outside the circle for more than like ten seconds, you're just dead. I thought I thought they were alright
So apparently I have this incorrect they do not spawn directly in the middle
I thought that it was like a ton of them like two three of them at the end will spawn right in the middle right in
The middle of the circle right in the middle. That's not what happens. Never it's just RNG
There's so many up and down in this level. How do you reliably know where they are?
The regular mode is almost it's pretty much one level
It's not like fucking a ten-story hotel
Hold everything the awful start. I might just die and restart and poisoned just kill me
This room is like a fucking million people in it. I was doing fine
I just got somebody said I got so salty I uninstalled laughing my ass off kind of par for the course
I think don't you think with this game? He was laughing his ass off. I
Got so salty uninstalled
I
Thought I could kill him in three hits in the head. It's too magic
He's already damaged boys. Let's go. Come on. Oh, you're gonna make my confidence go to zero or mage. Ooh
Not a hurt. This is not a horrendous start somebody here. Oh
Skeleton. Oh fuck German. Just go play slots
What
This is the one this is the one hey, I have made character progress I have like a hundred bucks
Well, I mean I'll have 25 at the end of this after I you know
I a little bit of family guy gold I would have walked into that trap
Oh, I've completely forgot to play one of the other classes my bed
I'll do after this a lot of money the penguin walking you can play this with some friends at a later date
Probably I'm very I'm addicted to it. I'm addicted to it. Even though I can't do it. Oh
My god, that guy threw a fucking bomb at me. What are you gonna do now? What are you gonna do now wizard?
You're dude your nose got cut off such a shitty thing to be in what the fuck you hit me right in the fucking eyes
He hit me right in the eyes
Is there a hole in the shield fuck was that sound that was a mistake wasn't it? Oh, no, it's these two
Powered shield on new class new class. Hold on one more try and I'll switch. Please. I'm losing everything
Hey, I gotta tell you this is a casino tip or if we're here
If you're at the casino and you're at the roulette table, and it's red hundred times in a row
Just bet with the trend you're gonna be like, it's gonna be blitz gonna be black this time
No, it'll be black this time. No, I think you should I think you should bet with the trend at this point
That's a fallacy. Of course it is. Oh
Gambling is just a fallacy. You missed one again. He hit me right in the fucking hair
No, I'm not fighting this room. Well, this is a lot of stuff. I didn't see I can pull them individually might be alright
That
Get you have wall hacks like how would you even have?
There are three more skeletons in here focusing you're dressed like your character
I am NOT so there's a pretty decent amount of money. Okay, let me just loot bro. That garb is whack
Uh, I've been here to this to you're to all this now find a portal and leave
Um, I don't think they're even spawned in yet clean this up. There it is
I'm going mess somebody up with that. This is it's such an interesting PvP
PvP PvP. Okay, decent shield. I'm too junk junk. Alright, there's a portal you alone. You're not alone
Goodbye. I hope nobody saw me. Oh fuck. Oh my god. Fuck off. Wait, are we fighting?
I thought they were being non hostile
They were kind of standing around for a second
It was a full three or four seconds and I was like, wait a minute
I I didn't hope they were like stream friends or you know what I mean? I didn't alright
Let me ask the believer something I can't fight three people. Are we fighting? I know I was just whatever
I went into this room. I thought I turned the light off. They all just barreled into the room
I could have probably thrown down. I know I was just stuck
It was over the mage is just enchanting fire sword on the barbarian and you got a
monk
Doing something else some type of shield buff. I don't know
I'm just a guy with a fucking bottle of liquor in a lighter new class
I'll do it after this is what it feels like to root for a losing sports team
Yeah, but eventually they're gonna win the World Series and you're gonna be so happy when they do just might take
70 or 80 years. Yeah, but that's also not a fair analogy considering
Okay, it would be like if I was playing a basketball game and I was the only player versus a whole team
They're like passing the ball back and forth
They like slap in five and I and I'm running around in circles. When is that stream?
Do you guys think that if I hired a professional basketball team to just go just versus me only?
Would I score one point in a full regulation game? What do you think? I didn't know you don't think so
I think I would do it. I think I could actually do it
What scoring one basket?
Can you just see in your head a team of like seven foot tall basketball players and me as like five eight Andy
I would go to shoot the ball and they would just just
Absolutely, just spike it down. Yeah, I would have to get a foul shot. I would have to get
I would just be flopping. You know what I mean?
Somebody would get it. I would run up and do go for a dunk and I would flop and be like, oh
Well, I was too that was too hard and then I get a chance
Your five eight was shoes. You don't think I'd be wearing shoes. I'll be wearing like basketball shoes
What?
No, no, that doesn't count either. I want that health back. I'm gonna wait. I'm gonna wait till that health is back
I'm waiting. I'm gonna wait till it's back. It's going in the review. What's happening right now?
Can't even leave do you think if I just stand here somebody will eventually walk by like what if I'm just a prisoner
This are paying as a prisoner. Oh, I'll tell you in locked in here all this time
I just wish I'm able to rescue me or something. All right, give it out there
Yeah, I sound like it's locked in here stuck in here
Unbelievable. All right. All right, mate. All right, mate. You know key you got a key
Oi stuck in here. I can't get out. Hey, you got a key, right?
They locked me up six to seven years ago now can't get out. There's no way out mate
I tried that already. I tried they gave me a torch and that's how they gave me you got any you got a key
You only didn't get me out of here. All right, don't just walk away from me. I'm trapped in here
I got money. I got I have two or three coins. I got I've humbly say how many coins I have I have free coins
Oi
Can't find reliable help anywhere these days seems. Ah
Ah
Now that's a mate right there. That's my mate right there. Thank you. Thank you very much
All right. Now who's in charge here? Who's the one leading? Oh forgot about the coin
There you go my ten coin split up over your one
What happened I dropped a few coin for you there on the ground for letting me out of there
I was stuck in there a long time, mate. You know how long I was in there for seven years. Oh, wait
Me mate George. Is he still alive? Oh, no
He's gone probably died a long time ago. They replaced him with a chest. I don't want that
Junk, so what do you do for a living? I was a thief stole. Hey, and I killed I killed too
I killed case you were wondering. It's Martin by the way, but how are you? Thank you
What was that something felt kind of hot? All right, boys. We've got a fight here
It's just a mage not a big deal. So why I'm going in ah
Fire that's how you get through that door
Sorry, right. Just trying to get a little bit extra coin. Well, we have a few spare moments
Over that trap mate, I don't know where he went. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, I know what that means mate
I know exactly what that means. Don't you?
Yeah, the May it out the mayor didn't like me very much from a small town
Accidentally, may I burn his house down and didn't really mean to is kind of a misunderstanding
I got tried they wanted to hang me and then I want to zombies in it. What's that mate? Oh
Are you look at that every gauntlets gem necklace pearl necklace blue sapphire
The bandage of some coin. I don't know whatever that is and some of that some of this a little bit of exodus
A little bit of gold you anything on you. Yeah, how the way might we're going to tell you I'm a backstabbing cheat
Sorry, sorry. Sorry, but I'm a lot of drugs
Oh
God damn it. That probably looks so stupid. Holy shit. You're a jester
You started using a funny voice and your survival rate
skyrocketed
Said peaky blinders. All right, let me get another one in can I get another real try one in your last words?
Yeah, clout. Yes. All right class class class class. I'll play is a different class. So Ranger everyone saying what about wizard?
You know, I got to turn my mic off. Yeah wizard you want to do wizard. Trust me
I'm an ice and frost and fire and oh it resets every time. Okay. I don't know how to play with the wizard
We're just gonna walk around so I have a staff you have to stand still when using spells
Okay, it never turned on they couldn't hear you good. It was the little indicator down the lower left
Yeah, they were like they were answering questions. Did you do a wizard voice?
All right, let me see here. So this is a swing
We select a spell from your memory to cast fireball slow haste invisibility magic missile
Okay, so I fires pretend home. So is that on? Okay, do a Deckard Kane RP
Maybe maybe another minute or two. They've been a minute. Does the mage does not have a torch
Oh, yeah, I can't wear any of this, you know, just throw one down easier that way. Ooh, what's that ancient scroll?
That was a wizard thing. I'm doing this wrong. Oh wizard battle. That's actually really fun
What happens if you run out of spells? Oh, that hurts me. Oh, this is a trial run. This is a trial run fuck
Using everything I have here
I'm in trouble now. Is there a heel? Oh, that's the other that's the other caster. What does haste do faster?
You don't really tell you meditate to recharge. Is that a certain button combination? Oh really vulnerable here really vulnerable
Oh, it's only one recharge
Your headshots matter with that or no, they do. Oh big pog move the big chest. I don't think I can
All right, I'm just gonna try to get out. I'm just gonna try to survive
Okay, the goal is just just try to get the hell out of here portal. Get me out. Oh fuck
Don't mind me. I'm not sure they saw me. I'm just running around looking rooms for portal. Oh, I feel like there's one in here
Thank God, I didn't see what it was. It was a ranger 15 armor plus two magical heal. Wait, I could I can wear it
No, I can't so okay if you find a good item like this for another class
I can't it's not a shared stash, but I can trade it to
Myself or just trade it you trading post it to others
Do not sell blues to NPCs trade them to the other players in the market really you would that's so cool. That's so cool
I'm gonna fill my inventory with blues
I'm gonna sit in the fucking trade server and just drink like six Mountain Dews and just trade like hats for refined and shit
All right, made it out alive
We go all this other stuff is kind of trunk trunk trash and junk combined
Are there other spells besides the one that they're more spells?
This is the coolest part of this whole game by the way, but this is by far the coolest thing the menus
Yeah. All right. Let me look at my spell
Here was zap. Wait, what is this? I don't get it. Good night skill one skill two
Spell memory priority, you'd have two sets of spells equipped, but it sucks
So just keep it on this keep it on one. Oh, I see the cost limit
Actually haste is good for trying to run around and find stuff. I'll get rid of it. I just want all offense
Let's try his app magic damage bonus melt. Oh, I want yeah this for sure 20% cast speed. Hell
Yeah, can I get a hell yeah in the chat, please? All right, let's keep going. I made some money. That's cool
Hell yeah, are you addicted yet?
I've been addicted since probably the first hour this game does this thing where it lets you keep stuff and there's rarities
It's it's just kind of scratch that itch for a ton of people addicted but bad
Hey, where does it say that you have to be good at a game like this to enjoy it? I've done I've done
Okay, I didn't mean to do that. They're not allowed to make fun of me
It's my stream that count as a spell this wizard sucks, dude. You kind of stink at this Jesus somebody die
Holy shit, that was a weird 3d movie
Um, okay
So that takes a lot to kill things if I had voice chat on I was gonna be like don't fucking do that
So what would some of us are trying to look at our menus and we don't want sounds to have be in our ears
Don't fucking do that. That's BM majors PvP. Do some more RP. All right fine. Oh
Goodness me. No, if I say so myself, I seem to be
wild world of
Monsters and demons and goblins and oh dear. Oh me
Please find a way out of here the circle of hell it seems. Oh
bastard
Ah, oh dear. Oh, no, let me cast it. He's already gone. Never mind
Oh
It's all you here
I'll try it again. Fuck. Well, he heard was oh me. Oh dear
Oh my all these demons of me and that guy's just gone most short-lived wizard
What was his name? We didn't even get a chance to do that died too quickly scramble scramble still skin. Oh, oh my goodness
Confounded door there's anyone out there
Geez, there ain't anybody around yet. That's fine. I'm just warming up. Oh
dear
Me. Oh goodness gracious. Oh
Can you?
Anyone out there? Is anyone out there?
Here and out there could help the great Kenneth height. Oh
Entry grant me I'm not even fucking all my audios not even on what why am I muted? Oh
Oh, that was it he took a chunk out of me it seems. Oh my goodness
Adventure a please if you could lend me a small hand
I've been chased by demons and ghouls and goblins and they're following me and be careful over there. Oh
Dear the life of an adventure. I sure is full of wonder
Watch out. Let me
Accidentally aggro the entire room. Whoops a daisy. Let me just find a way viewed adventure if you would please
Over here. Oh
No
No more death more death and destruction in this vile world
Ha seems to be my last stand
Defeat me you vile
Disgusting future demons on my way out of there. That was very terrifying
Goodness, I'm need some type of healing potion or
Something like that. If anybody can hear me. I'm just I'm just a lonely wizard
I'm not muted look at the bottom of here. You know need some potions or manner
I seem to be running out. He's a nice wizard shoes. Oh dear
Adventure. Oh
If you have a potion or two watch out a skeleton behind you. There's a skeleton here. Oh my goodness gravy
I could help I could help you. Let us work together
I'm just a lonely mage trying to find watch out for the skeleton. Oh
Little sticks. Hey adventurer. I know a few tricks little faster now now, aren't we?
Now this I believe there is a gigantic diamond hidden in this cave somewhere
I saw it one time 25 years ago. Yeah, let me help you out with the more haste. Let us go back up adventurer
Fireball incoming nice swing now the fireball coming out here
Excellent work. You sure do know how to use a sword
I know quite a few people that would be very interested in how you are using that weapon
I'm from the adventurer's guild up north very far north
It's very chilly where I'm from as you can see I'm wearing all these robes down here and close that door
Even wanted anybody to be sneaking up on us. What is your name? Ah, Mike, I'll get this one
Would you mind if I meditated for just one moment, please? Ah
Refreshing adventure. This is probably a bad way to go. Oh my skin hurts. Yes. Yes, of course
We need to go this way all the way looking for a diamond a crown made out of jewels
emeralds rubies
Adventurer, have you ever held a ruby before in your hands? Oh
You've had it the whole time
By gravy. Well now we can leave I don't need to stay here any longer not exactly what I was looking for
I do feel awful though. Make sure I have a power spell just adventurer. Where did you go?
Adventurer, I might have something for you adventurer. Holy show
Grisness of adventurer. I'm gonna give you something and I want you to make sure you understand
This is a very expensive item and that's what you get for being on my team
I'd venture up this way if you see a portal by any chance, please. Let me know. I'm so old
I should be the one to go first. Yes, of course. Yeah, what a nice young man. You really are
Oh, they think that they can use magic on us. Don't they how does that sound?
I hope he gets out with that blue. I really do
Failed that guy fucking hated you. I don't think so. He's got a blue. He's got a blue. He's getting out of there
All right, one more RP and then I'm gonna go back to plan this time
I'm gonna be a dark wizard. Well, that's when you that's when you turn it off
Well, let's play
Unfortunate fireball. What is the range for this to actually hurt me? Am I in a cell? Oh my goodness
I went into a cell. How did I back into a cell? What was that? I didn't hit apply. It looks like it was off
That's pretty good stuff. Is there a heel that way? This is oh, this is a heel. Is it a full heel?
Somebody kill me. What's that? Did I kill him? Did I just kill myself because of the magic missile? Oh
Dear oh me oops
Accidentally magic missile to ground. All right, this one's for real. Let me try. Hold on. Let me try the Ranger
I feel like the wizard is really really awesome, but I think you really have I think you need to be like a little
More familiar with the whole game range. Yeah, range. Yeah, it seems really cool though. This seems like the the kid is really fun range
Yeah, no range. Yeah free. How does this work detect recent enemy footsteps? That's cool
Forage food light speed projectiles a greatly increased in addition physical attack powers increase. Okay, that's cool. That's pretty good
That's pretty good too 15% more headshot damage. I'll try that was the loadout the bow
All right. Let me try it. The multi shot one is super good. How does it work? It's I get six shots you hold it
There's a lot of drop on it though. Okay, that's a lot of drop
I gotta be ready for that range of voice probably something like this if I were to say something like this
You think you're so powerful waving around that two-handed axe. Okay, I don't like this
Where why am I in vents? I don't have a melee weapon. Do I just eat wood off the ground? Oh that's okay
Oops, how do I get out of here? Do you have infinite arrows? Oh, fuck you. Oh
I kind of like it. It's kind of fun. Can I break this with arrows another pick lock?
I don't seem to have any close range. This one's open pretty good. You can get a sword. Maybe I'll try it out
Walk over here wizard shoes. Get him. Ah, ah
Oh
I'm to go holster the bow to go faster. Oh
No, I want that chest. Oh
Never mind. Goodbye. So the sacrificial altar. What do you do? What is that? Oh, no, this is bad
I'm in a lot of trouble here. I gotta I gotta just drag them this way
The teammate revive, oh, that's pretty cool. Okay, cool. Holy shit just run. What is that? I don't know. I'm dead
Thousand there was so much shit. I'm dead. Yeah. Goodbye. It was like a thousand spiders in that room
There's just so many people. There's so many things close the door behind you. Yeah. Yeah, I know I know
Honestly, I just trying to get used to how to shoot the bow
Triple shots amazing. It's gonna land some headshots on some people. I want some garlic bread. Um
You know, what's really weird and I've never said this out loud. I don't think anyone's ever heard me say this
You know what? I want a steak. Is that weird? I want a steak right now
I haven't eaten a steak. I mean when we're talking about like a fork and knife. I want a steak like
Steak, I think it's been probably 10 to 15 years since I've said that I don't really eat steak
Yeah, I'm not sure what put me in a steak mood
Yeah, no, it's been probably at least at least 10 years since I've wanted to eat a steak
I guess I could just sit up here and just sniper. Ah
Oh, that's good, but I'm gonna have to wait
I was saying it a lot last night because the eternal cylinder. Yeah, you're right. All right, you look ridiculous
Can you die already if you got low iron? Hmm. That's an interesting theory
What's the netcode like on this? How much should I lead people pregnant cravings?
Um, no pregnant craving would be if I were to say I want a steak
But I want you to marinate it in cool whip first somebody else here they together who you shooting at who you shooting at
Are you shooting me? Yep. Oh god. Damn it. Um, okay, so
People are fighting. It's I think that I think one's dead. Oh, you're coming after me, aren't you?
I don't know how I survived that and really don't I got no arrows. I'm in trouble here. Yeah
No, this is not getting out of that
I mean, honestly, you should have just started killing the stuff
We were both dead was like four or five enemies behind like right next to us first PvP kill of the night
Well, that's not true
That would be oh, I don't know how I'd feel about that if that was a accurate statement
That's at least the third or fourth PvP kill of the night at least five
I missed some raids didn't I shit honey Goblin came in with a raid honey Goblin rated last night, too
And that's where if you're still here from that raid, which I see I think that was hours ago. Thank you
All right, caught it like three and a half hours late. You did not hit me with that
What is it going for your wing? It's horse shit, dude. Why are there so?
Many of you honest to goodness. What the hell I know I'm supposed to close that door, but I had to
What's going on? Okay. I'm fine. It's a little sloppy, but whatever what's going on
Welcome to odds right in the face a wonderful word of odds that class seems
Unbelievably good rogue is a hard time with mobs Rangers. Not a solo class
I probably shouldn't be playing it then the fighter I think the fighter is probably the class
I could try barbarian feel like that would be my speed big heavy swing hit head P break
Um, I'll probably I want to keep playing but it is getting kind of late. I want to get out one more time
I want to escape one more time shoot. Oh fuck
Terrifying. Oh shit. Somebody's here how to go just in case somebody follows me down here
Somebody's asking if there is a proper solo queue. There is there is a solo mode now. It's very very hectic
It's very scary. That's I would say it's very difficult. It's the game. That's the way they get the name of the game
It's not called easy and easier. It's called fucking hard and harder. Please. Let me loot these chests in peace, please
I'm still alive. That's a good thing 15. Wait, is it faster seven bow? Oh seven. Okay, I'll try it
That damage is pretty bad though. Your mom's sick. I gotta go to bed. I hope you feel better. Oh, this is bad
Yeah, I'm in trouble wrapping around. Give me a good bow. Give me a blue bow 29
Better. Oh my god. I thought I had an extra second. All right, give me a portal. Give me out of here
There is a person portal. That's way too that room is way too dangerous. Oh shit. I'm in trouble
I don't think I have any potions or anything. Do I could be worse. This is a good stream
Oh, I'm glad you think so. The game is very very fun
This is gonna be one of those games
I think that it's gonna have a lot of fans
There's gonna be a lot of people that are gonna be playing this very very frequently. I'm just gonna go
Oh
Very bad everywhere. I just leave another archer here. Oh, yeah. Come on. There's a portal somewhere
I don't really have very much. Yeah, I have some jewels. I have some stuff crouch. I step in my own trap
What just happened? I didn't know you could do that. I didn't know you could do that
I thought it was like it's mine. So therefore the game doesn't I didn't know you could do that. Ah
Thought it was mine. Yeah, and I even still tried to jump
All right, it's a fun class but I feel like it's a classy where you need to have like support, okay
I'll try but I'm gonna try barbarian for two times co-op with somebody
Um, that'll be probably something that has to be planned because it's um, it's very very late around almost the whole world
So I think that's something that hey you want to do this on
Thursday or something, right? I think that's got to plan it up a little it's 6 p.m. In Australia
Hey, hey ones in chat if you if you're if you're from Australia, where am I? Where are my Australian friends at? That's a lot
Wow, okay. I get it. I feel it. They're different swing. It's a sideways swing. Oh get out of here
This is a really bad place to spawn. Yeah, a lot of the it's a lot of people that are around right now. It's a lot of
Australia
Asia too, right New Zealand. Yep. So I'm yeah, but you're up to because you're probably waking up right now
I like the late-night crowd you guys you guys have been really really not like it didn't don't get me wrong. Hey
Thanks, I don't get me wrong
every time zone has
You know this this perks to every time zone. Well, this is the first time I've ever streamed like this
Somebody's coming. Oh, okay. Yep. Ow, you got it. Oh
Yeah
Yes, you lied to me you lied to me that is that is be a way this different person
What'd you lie? Why would you lie to me? You're the two. Oh, why would you do this to me?
Why would you do this to me trader trader? What the heck you lied to me?
You did the squat squat. I lied to was it a different guy. They would look like they were together
He was waiting for backup bunch of bastards. I'm telling you to a man party. Only one was friendly
Would you ever visit Australia?
Australia seems like equal parts one of the most beautiful remarkable places on earth while also being one of the most terrifying places
I would never want to go like I would want to experience Australia in a in a helicopter
You know what I mean? Like holy shit. Wow. Look at this. Look at how amazing this is. This is so beautiful
Don't let don't land though. Don't land. I hear there are spiders as big as two fists. I
Thought we'd fly over
Now is there a parry or no, is it just power all jokes aside though?
I would I would it's definitely on the bucket list the places that are interesting to me
Dude, you got a really wide swing. Yeah
Maybe barbarians not for me. This is a little harder than I thought it was gonna be
Japan's another one a lot of places in Europe to like you guys know
I've never left I've never left in North America for like any reason ever don't trust anybody. Oh, no. Oh, yeah
Probably eventually I imagine I'll do a kind of a world tour at some point
Maybe into my 40s or 50s or something world tour announcement. No
That's why I'm gonna be going to every major city in the world a
Hundred cities in a hundred days, you know what I really want to do
I just I just want to go into a bar in Scotland
Just like sit down just get whatever they have on tap and just have somebody just talk to me
You know what? I mean, I just want to sit there on that stool and just look over to the left and right and just like
What's what's your story? What's your story? Let me hear it. No bar. Yeah a pub. That's what I mean. It's very profound, dude
I'm serious though. I think that's like would be nice dude. Yeah, I just like said that's everybody be like, oh my god
He's he's so well traveled and he's so he just wants to like have a conversation
You won't be able to understand them, but I could nod I could nod
Don't cast a spell at me. Did you miss the legendary ancient scroll? I don't need that shit
Do you think I need the legendary scroll? No, give me two packs of cigarettes and a fucking axe. I'll be done in an hour
Get your whole fucking crew, huh? Get your whole crew out of here. Ah, ah
He was one hit I'm alive just so dark bro, you died to a friar
Hey his buddy jumped on my back and when it wasn't hey that was I that was 2v1
But yeah, I think there's a lot of cool places to see the thing about the United States if those you bet
It may not have ever been here. The United States is very very different across the whole country
It's almost like four or five different countries. There's so many wildly different climates wildly different people
It really does sometimes feel like a few different countries. Yeah. Oh, yeah, we got multiple Star Wars worlds stole that from chat
I don't really understand how to play barbarian. It's like I swing and then I just like oh fuck
Is there am I missing something here like I'm getting hit way too much
I'd rather eat 50 hot dogs or travel the world. Why can't I do both of those things?
You're thinking too limited here. I have to choose one. I would want it. I would travel the world
Yeah, you can get a hot dog whenever you want to get a hot dog traveling the world something
That's kind of a big deal. I could eat a hot dog every day for the next two months
I mean, I wouldn't want to do that, but I could but it's 50
Yeah, the 50 hot dog sounds like a punishment not a reward. Hold on. Ow
Alright, I'm gonna hurt. Alright, so I oh shit my bleeding. No, that would be unfortunate. I think I might be
Hold on. Yeah, give me a sec. Okay, so the issue that just happened. Damn, okay
So let me explain. No. Yeah, I am shit
Give me one second. I'm fine. Don't worry. So this is actually kind of funny
I'm a bloody nose right now and it's because there was a really hard ass booger in my nose and I just went to like
Kind of rub my nose and this really hard booger just hurt me. It's kind of funny in a way, but like fuck it sucks
I'll be right back. That's unfortunate. You're back. He ripped his own brain. I'll be right back. I'm back
So I didn't realize it wasn't at a BRB screen. I'm good. I have
Tissue paper stuffed up my nose. Hey booger boy. Yeah, can we see no?
I I got a I got a some I got some liquidation here. It'd be hard to drink this in my nose though
That's hard to do. Did you at least eat the booger bro?
What do you think? No, shut up
Time that person out for I don't know that few days. I don't know. Shut up. No, I didn't it's disgusting
That person for a week. Okay. Let me try I
Want to try let me go back to them the thing I was doing before even gonna play scorn. Let's go prepared
Let me just take all this stuff. I got plenty of money. I'll try this one more time. This is so hard though
Yeah, I don't really know what happened. It does get very dry out here. It's very cold and it's very dry in Vegas right now
I'm not really prone to nosebleeds
But I think there was just there was a one a little too hard in there and I rubbed
I got I do this thing a lot. I don't know if it's just something. I don't know. It's a call it like a
kind of
Compulsive thing that I do but I a lot of times I will pinch my nose and like kind of pull down a little
Just I kind of rub like pinch pulp. I do it all the time
You probably see me do it on camera a lot where I kind of like take my my index finger in my thumb
And I go like just rub pulp. I do it all the time. So I did that and
Caused a nosebleed somehow
That does sound like a really really suspicious way to tell everybody that as a nearly 40 year old man
I was picking my nose when you couldn't see it. Well, you see
All right, let's go I'm fighting the boss one two shit three hit combo. I got that
Against the wall
Don't even I'm fighting this don't hurt me not again fucking die. Oh my god. Damn it
I can't I can't back up back up back up bang into wall. Now you're in trouble
I have no idea if I was even close but whatever. Oh, yeah, I forgot I got attacked
75% just started aggroing stuff in the room and at that point it's just over. It's late
It is late, but I'm a late-night Andy now. Oh, I'm just gonna leave
Let's just go back in here. He's dreaming of that Scotland pub
You think it's the earwigs in your brain that are making you slowly nocturnal or earwigs nocturnal. Ooh
Okay, pretty good
Diamond back here or something get back here. Can I just hide here the whole match?
Unfortunately, I am NOT near the center. I want to take you one at a time, please
Don't you dare come together? He seriously hit me in the fucking head. Oh my god. Oh my god
I can't I I died in two arrows. Did he headshot me twice in a fucking row?
I died as I shot 15 arrows at somebody and hit him in the head 15 times and they didn't die
I got hit to a two arrows and I'm dead aim really high with the shield. It's awkward. Jesus
Crouch and aim stupid high. I like this comment you muppet. You keep costing me a thousand points
What's the statistics here? How many bets have there been and how many have actually how many have I won?
How many have I you know? Oh, I made it out for three
Like 30 those odds are very bad
You can't put it on double zero every time with the rule of table and when the dealer is like, oh, sorry
It's a it's a red 20. Yeah, you fucking muppet. Why is it not on the green one the one in one out of 35? Oh
Shit, I just blew my snot thing. I gotta put this back in
You're betting
Against the edge. There's an edge here and you're betting against it
Stop trolling it. I
I'm this game. Yeah, fuck you fucking muppet. Oh
I'm telling you stop that in green stop betting zero and double zero. It's not gonna come up
You need to you need to be betting a strategy bet, right? I'm gonna damn it. This one's so hard. Okay
I'm gonna do this one. You didn't even put a an English accent on while doing the muppet
I didn't I don't know if that person's English
So many people have lost money. We're okay right now. It is 270 K 4 million
It's not good. It's not good. The believers have been drained
Completely 200 K to 4 million. It's we're kind of bleeding out all the believers
I've actually kind of feel bad. I need some of these believers to get a big win here
Otherwise only gonna be doubters with them with the with the capital. I can't have that
I'm trying as hard as I can know. I can't have that. It'll just be all doubters. Let's go. I'm gonna turn it here
It is somebody's close. Oh
I'm in the left. There's still many archers in here. No, fuck you. Give me all your stuff
Give me everything you own. Stop rolling. Stop rolling. Stop rolling. What do you have? I took okay
I got everything actually don't need this shit
17 no, I have a lockpick which can get you fuck this up. I'm gonna be very pissed off at you
I need health though. I can't use the fuck. What's that? What's just why did the clock just appear whatever?
Okay, I I just I looked away for one second
I was like, oh, that'll be fine and cool lockpick. All right potions this I actually I have to get out from this one
I do look at all these trinkets and shit. I got to get out of here healing potions or something
Come on, they live. Thank you. What the fuck? Oh, it's a mage
What a little bubble time to go in a minute in a minute in one minute
There's one or is it to loot loot loot nice worth it. Oh, I'll take it something
Wait, did you make sure you fight as many monsters as you can? Hey, dude, I see what you're doing
Look at this little fucking place
That doesn't really help me. Nice. Okay, don't want to fight that. I'm just gonna go this way. Okay. All right portal portal is somewhere
We've got some dead bodies portal. I just heard one. Where is it? I just heard one. Oh my god
Yes
Believers believe it. I'm gonna call that and I'm an unbelievably clutch
Molotov to buy me the time to open the portal to get the heck out of here. Yes
Look at all this shit. Look at all this and I left I got it. Didn't I get out with something pretty nice?
I swear I got a oh the blue is the last round when I yeah, that was unfortunate huge payout
I'm actually so sad. Oh, well, the odds weren't that good. I would have oh no, I feel bad
You didn't win. Oh, oh no, everyone's sad. Well that that worked. Okay, let's get some money
Hmm. There's gonna be a lot nice nice nice nice nice
Ooh, ooh. Oh, yeah, this is big money now. Look at this
Gold who wants to buy this thing? I'm gonna actually hold on to this like a crystal ball is pretty good to have for a wizard
Hey, well, what if I play with a wizard? Who knows? Hey, I'm saving this for Holly
She's gonna play a wizard. Um
Only four gold and I feel like yeah, whatever those worth a lot
I've got a pretty decent amount of money now. Do I dare gamble it? Of course not
No, I'm saving it. Why do I have multiple torches? I will buy a weapon though
22. Hmm. None of these are any good. I got bandages. I'll buy potions though. I would why these here
health
54 that sounds just that's just like awful. All right, I'm gonna do another one, but I have perks
I have stopped bleeding. So that's good. Do a high roller. I am NOT ready
You want me to go into high roller looking like this?
I'm wearing an elf costume with a fish tank on my head
You want me to go into the high roller zone and get fucking one shot by somebody's legendary weapon
You just want to see me lose a hundred gold. Hmm. Yeah guys. I have a serving tray for a shield
It's gonna get attacked the legendary ice sword of the mountain and it's gonna crumble and it's gonna split me in half
All right, I'm just gonna do I'm just gonna go again
Actually like last one probably for the night because I mean I do you know, I am very very into it
He's never gonna say hi to smush. You know, the worst part about this is I really like this game and they're about to take
It away from me in like five days. They're gonna take it away from me
I wonder when the actual just kind of beta just like it's open and it's gonna be there for a while
I wonder when the beta actually will be because it's supposed to be coming out at the end of the year
Is that full on 1.0 right? This is just a play test. Yeah, I think it's in my personal opinion playing this
I feel like it's almost
At that point where I think they could probably slap a beta on it, but that's you know
Okay, I have to win this but that's also just me being selfish and
You know, I got I want to play it so that's you know me being selfish
What is that spider don't play Tarkov Tarkov is like this right same kind of idea but with machine guns
I actually prefer this than that. I prefer the sort of dungeon kind of medieval fantasy. He's here
I don't know what the hell he's doing. Oh, come on
There's no getting out of this I
Can kill your fucking priest? I'll be happy you have the best take sometimes
But then you ruin it by talking about drinking your own piss or something. All things must be balanced
What if I talked about drinking my own piss? That's I've never said that. Oh
I whatever yes, right
I said I was people gave me shit cuz I had a water filter and I was like, oh, it's great
And they were like, oh actually that water filter sucks
And I was like I'll piss in and drink it and I never did it. Yeah, I remember it's like
Oh, man, that water filter dude, it's like a scam
I'm like what he did like I could piss in this thing and drink it and it was like to do it then I was
Like I will and then I just got called out and didn't do it
I hate that you just hit me. That's so unfair
Somebody's shooting me with a bow and fucking arrow and I don't know if it's a person or if it's a monster
That's just not gonna happen
This guy's buddy just died and I'm just gonna absolutely
Scared this shit out of him here. Oh my god, your friend had nothing. Your friend had nothing. What the fuck?
Well, good luck cuz now we're both fucking dead. What was he invisible?
He's invisible, wasn't he?
Invisible, how long can they stay invisible? Are they actually invisible invisible? Or is it kind of rogues can go invisible?
How long does it last? It's until that way is it it's like shadow meld from Warcraft every day
I you know every day I just see how good this class really is about 20 seconds if they're stationary
I remember when a rogue used to kill me in wow, I would have a fucking mental breakdown
I remember just questing in like Stranglethorn Vale and you would hear that
Kidney shot of whatever wasn't just couldn't move and then it was like
Who and you stunned again and then that person would just sit there for like an hour and I would just get my body
And they would just do it again
Just like log off bro log off. I was that guy were you you're a real piece of work. I'll tell you
I just said the ceiling that's very good believers. Are you there? I'm proving my usefulness
Start is this is he just running around the circle turn the brightness down. No, I can't play it
I can't play it unless the brightness is up like 20 30 percent at least my eyes are so bad my you know
It's crazy my eyes when I'm looking at a monitor or worse than just real life
I don't know why that is boomer eyes. Oh shit. What happened to this person? Oh, sorry, man
I'll take this I tried to help him I did but this game this game is
This game is pretty pretty hard we leave me alone for one second. Oh my god, you fucking little shits. I'm gonna wrap around
I'm over here, man. Hey, it's a little slow. Dude. Where's Mike? Oh my god
I thought this is gonna be so much easier. I thought this is gonna be so much easier. Holy shit
That was a disaster. No, don't even please don't please please not right now getting kind of just destroyed at every turn
This is so bad. This is bad. I'm in trouble. Holy shit. You saved my life
Thank you for the love of God close this door for the love of God closer, okay
Okay portal. Oh dear careful. Careful. There's a monster behind you. I gotta be honest. Oh shit
No fall damage, right? Okay. Wait, I need a portal. What happened the mage act the goblin mage killed me
Well from that far away. I got sniped from that far away. He jumped down
Well, I hope you get this these items. That's sad
Alright, this is the last one. This one counts. This is the one that
Really counts this one counts. None of the other ones did I've been playing for about seven hours
These were all tutorials leading up to this
Exact one right now all led up to here. Hmm. What do you got you two are together?
What about you?
That means you need to refund all previous bets. Unfortunately, I'm sorry to say that's not gonna happen
I'm getting out. I'm gonna leave here with like 300 gold. Let's do it
You should turn the monitor off for this one. That'd be actually really funny. The gas following me. Okay, I got some replacements
This is just junk, but I'll take it. Alright, let's keep going. I'm gonna actually go around your time
Is this poison somebody else's down here? It isn't poison. Thank goodness. Somebody's down here
You better not be full of shit. Nice the code. Yeah. Alright the the adventurer code. Alright, let's get out of here
Oh, he's meditating whoo you you coming or do you need help? Why am I talking like you can hear me?
Yeah, I got full health. I don't know if you can hear me. No, you can't I got you. Don't worry
I'll protect you. Okay, then go over here. Be careful. This is really dangerous a wizard like you. He's hallucinating again
This isn't even a multiplayer game. I don't understand what what Jeremy's talking about
He's been playing Scrabble on stream for the last six hours
Against the computer. I don't what is he talking about like swords and stuff
I'm just like taking everything and stuff sucks friendly. There's a boss down there. Can we kill it together?
Well, we're gonna have to figure that out. We're gonna have to go. We're gonna have to do it. I think it's mine
Holy shit. Oh my god
That's a fucking purple. That's a purple bro. I'm leaving. I'm out of here. I'm fucking out here. It's mine. It's all mine
Oh shit, we slept we separated. Is this cool? Wait, could he use that? Maybe I could give it to him
Hold on. Hold on a minute here. Hold on a second here. Hold on a minute. Hey, hold on a minute
Hey, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Hold on. Everybody's relaxed. Everybody relaxed for a second. I'm freaking out
I can't jump that wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait. What is who is it for?
Warden Ranger is do we have a Ranger anywhere over here?
I I actually would give it to the Ranger if there's a Ranger here give him the crystal ball
Oh, hey, can you use them? Should I do the Diablo 2 thing where you like dropped it on the ground?
I picked it up really quickly just to make piss everybody off
Please to do that and any time it got grabbed it was they would just leave the game. They were just an exit
I'm not gonna dump kidding
I would never do that but like if there really was a Ranger with us, I would absolutely give it to them
Because like that's fucking cool. I just too bad. It's not for a wizard. You probably should go over here
I used to do that in fucking tibia
Oh
See you later. See you later. See you later. Have fun everybody. Have fun. I got a fucking purple
I got a purple. I got a purple
I wish there was a Ranger in our like part of that little group because if you drop that for somebody that's actually using that
Class and they would just it was like holy shit
Did really like if somebody dropped me something for that could use quick end the stream
I will probably hold on to this because I will probably I'm not gonna I'll probably give this to somebody
Oh, by the way, let me like ask like an actual question here
Like I know I was just kind of fucking around was that like BM. I don't want to be like that guy
I know we're just kind of fucking around here
But is that like is that BM or anything like was I like a dick for doing that like be honest with me?
Cuz I don't I don't want to like, you know, yeah, who's it? Yeah, the wizard was the one who killed it
I just I just saw it die like I just saw fucking red and it was like a purple
I just picked it up and I freaked out leaving him stuck. There was meaner. It's true. Is there any way to do recent players? Oh
He feels bad. Well, I just I like don't know the etiquette and even if there is not I mean here's the thing
It is like it's just like a demo. So it's not like
But I don't be like a dick you would leave in a heartbeat if you if you were German
Is there actually like a recent players list cuz I will just send it to them. I really don't even care
I don't want to be like an asshole. It was like funny for a second and I'm like, wait a minute
That is actually really good and somebody could probably sell that but it is like five days left on the beta, right?
You're thinking too much about it. Yeah, I probably am it's a beta. There are no rules. That's true. That's true
Maybe if it was a legendary should I should you use the gathering halls be happy about it? Yeah
Trade what if I went into trade? I was like, hey the wizard that I just took that purple from did please DM me
The DM for BM he gave you the gloves you drop you have the odd that and 2020 hindsight
I should have just dropped that for him. I feel bad, but it's all good. Don't forget to stash it
Yeah, I got it right here. Dude. You gave him a magical globe. That's right. I did dude. Don't worry
What if he's a terrible guy in real life? That's not the point. That's not the point
He he probably thought the orb is what you got. Yeah, I should have just gave it to him. It's all good
All right, one more I'm gonna keep this. Where did I get this from? Oh
My god, this is for a wizard. Oh my god. How did I not see this?
I did I get that too. I gotta get in contact. I got I gotta fucking hit that guy up
I took all of his stuff. I gotta give him that fucking dagger. I have to I have to find that person
Fucking terrible. All right, let's I'm gonna play another one stash it for you
Screaming it's all mine and then I feel bad
I get my brain just like didn't piece together like what I was doing and I'm just like, oh, yeah
Wait. Oh, right. This is the people here. That's fucking
Well stash the shit. I did I did is anybody hold on. Where's the and I everybody remember their name
Nobody has to remember their name. Oh, you have stream remote on steam recent players. I don't have I'm not really maybe I can see
Recent game now one of the things up top wizards. There's only 18 wizards in the whole game name and karma
It'll show you oh that I knew it was somewhere
Oh, there was no there's no there was no teammates because we weren't technically in a team together
All right, let me sell this stuff and we'll we'll do one more. He's gone forever
How many more one more is a good question gotta be extra generous next time to make up for it
Yeah, I will atone for my sins. I will it's so funny cuz it's
Calling with the ring or something. I spent the last seven hours playing and like I've haven't been playing very well and all of a sudden
Like oh my god amazing. I don't take it
Yes, like it's right
Pretty good pretty good. You see your recent players. I just looked
There's nothing there. You were like a little raccoon. I know that's I got it felt like my god. I'm gonna die
Oh my god, I'm fucking sloppy right now dirty
I really do want to make it out because I have a lot of decent stuff. He said it's okay
It wasn't malicious. Yeah, but I still feel bad about it bugs
Yeah
Why is Bugs Bunny Peter Griffin the same character? Why is that they aren't it's just me
Yeah, my impression. Yeah, that's always scary every time it really is
All right, I'm just gonna move cuz kind of far away. I actually didn't his revenge. This is revenge for uh,
The Wizards revenge I was not altruistic enough. I can see names unless they're just scrambled nonsense. Are they he's addicted?
Yeah, I am somebody's behind that door. No
They were friends everything was going so well until you blinded by greed
Shit and he said hey, dude, does the stolen equipment work better? Oh
Okay, we laugh about this and it's like really not that big of a deal
I shit you not a couple hours from now. I'm gonna be lying in bed
You're talking to Holly and it's gonna be like I feel real bad about that wizard
I wonder if I can like reach out to him and give it back to him. Ow. Oh my god, don't even vote
It doesn't count. Don't even vote. It doesn't count. Don't even vote doesn't count
That's not that that one doesn't count up. Don't know that one doesn't count
There's been a few stinkers in a row it now that one doesn't count I walked out and I I was looking at chat
Well, you're gonna bet anyways, so this just pretend it's this one. All right
I had to pay I had to pay it forward over here. You shot me so I hit him
Hey, my buddy Eric just got his loot stolen by some jackass. Be careful. Damn shit
I'm gonna be on the lookout. I was waiting for you
I knew you were gonna do that and you still got me with it somehow
These are some really dog shit spawns the last two times, huh? I can die
That's pretty cool
Get this stink out of the way. You can't have any more in there. I can't believe this
I can't believe you still alive like I hit you a hundred times Jesus. Oh my god
I just want to leave but I can't walk up there. What is happening? What's happening? Let me help
I need that I need this and you're in the way. I got a plan. Come and get me now with it
Oh, you gotta be kidding me. You weren't even aiming at me. It's better than a player
What's this deal? Oh, I'm in trouble now. I'm dead. I just there's three people just fucking chasing my ass
Like you're doing great, sweetie
So here's the plan. I'm gonna do this one
I'm gonna do this one and then one more solo goblin world just for old times sake and that's it
And then I actually I have to go eat. I haven't eaten seven and a half hours. So I need to eat
I'm getting like brain fog. I'm just gonna I'm just gonna you know, I mean, I'm just gonna try to get away
I'm just gonna try to get out if they're red
Does that mean that they're stronger or have more health or something? Yes. Okay, that would explain the damage
How why am I not swinging to wait what what the fuck happened why oh you have to you have to hit right click
Then left click it's backwards. That's what the fuck. I come
I forgot just to do the swing to go one two with the swords
You have to do a right click then left click and not left click and right click you have to hit right click first
Now that was annoying that laugh. Yeah, so if you have if you have two swords, you can't press left click first
You'll just swing the left side. You can't do left and then right you have to hit right click first, which is come on
Gwen the heel. Okay, not bad. I have to get out of here though. Yeah, this is that this is truly the last one
Where the fuck are you? Oh
Just trying to get out of here without getting hit once. I actually have to get out of here now surprising that that did not kill
Jesus I got so complacent. I just was like, oh, I'm just like walking around just tacking random shit Jesus. No
No, no, no, no. Oh my goodness. What a disaster
Oh, come on, there's no getting out of that that one sucked
That one didn't count that one that truly was just stupid. That just didn't count
I escaped that shit turn around guy the bow and arrow. You just I'm just dead. I wouldn't count. I don't shit spawn. I
Just have to what is this a red bug what I can't move no matter what happens. This is it
Mmm, I could die in the first 10 seconds and that's it. I'll come back to it
Yeah, this is the final match no matter what happens next time. I will be in a party or maybe I'll play so I don't
I do but up you'll I'll be playing this again 100% this week
You bet your ass play it with stir play it with Vinnie. Yeah, I mean whoever wants to play out
I know it's probably a whole crew that can get cycled in and out. Okay final one. This is it
I'm gonna actually I'm gonna just quiet down. I'm gonna focus. I'm gonna try to win way too many nice
Very good. Very good. Very good. Hello. Let's work together. You have a pickaxe. Oh shit. You get a bow
Oh fuck every friend I get dies or I steal from them. That was my fault. What did I do?
I think he just gets shot in the head by an arrow. They're sad. It's unfortunate
I shouldn't be laughing at that
But I mean, I feel like I've discovered people's bodies a handful of times here. Okay, I gotta get out of here
I'm not this open-ass room. No way. See you
That's pretty good Eddie. Why is my name Eddie? Careful. Let's get him. Let's get him. I need to atone for my sins
Let's get him. Who's a week takes fighting together here or as I'm people just kind of walking
What? All right, somebody fall back or oh, please. I don't have any healing left
Why just people just walking around backstage? We're not fighting this anymore
It's so bad I wanted to do it so bad
No
Wait the shield I thought I blocked it. No. Oh, that's so annoying
I thought I fucking had it. I was certain I like a purple was gonna drop and I was gonna it was gonna be a whole
Thing I was gonna turn the voice on I'm gonna be like, hey take that you've earned this. Oh, I had a whole thing planned
Shoot why am I a loading screen?
Loading screen. What's happening? I can't just moving my spectating the heck swing man. What are you doing?
I'm telling your mother don't I'm not messing around in this room too many spiders too many goblins
Actually, I think I'm gonna have to do this though. Okay, I'm in the center and chill out now
Just relax pick up some stuff and leave do not aggro more. That would be a huge mistake the red one. Oh
Oh
Don't lose this. Oh, it was me. Fuck all that shit. Good. What was that?
I gotta go one final chest for the road for the road for the road for the road for the road for the road for the
Road for the road for the road for the road for the road for the road for the road for the road go go go go
Go, I think I'm lightning fast
You have a bandage. It's okay. He's gone. Whatever
You Muppet that big chest. I am NOT gonna do that. I needed a lockpick moment of truth right here
How the fuck are you still alive? I have this
45 gosh darn damage. You've got to be shitting me. All right. All right, all right, all right
I gotta go up right up where I guess it's on the top floor
Fuck that like up here discount. Oh my god. This one over there. Come on. Make the jump make the jump make the jump
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Everything's fine. Everything's fine
I'm relaxed relaxed relaxed relaxed give me I'll give me I'll give me I'll get me out go on
I'll go out on a high note go out on a high note go out on a high note. Thank God
Jesus only you left one person
So what's the strategy here? Well, what was he? What was he waiting for? He's just afraid of the Archer probably. Yeah, nice
This is my sin corner. It's the guilt armor. All right, that was very very very fun
Oh, it's offhand. This is the comedy run. This one is not even real. There's no betting or anything
It's nothing about it's just a comedy run. See it's already funny. They're already really funny
This is such a bad spawn to new law. No, there's no way. All right. I'll see you tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow
Or no, no, not tomorrow what's technically tomorrow technically tomorrow
So Thursday because it is technically no no no no no Wednesday because it is technically Tuesday right now
So I'll see you Wednesday. We're gonna play more of this. I want to play more dark and darker
There's only six days in this test and then they just wipe everything and they put it back in the oven for like another two
Or three months. Yeah, I'll see you guys on
See you guys on
Wednesday the eighth have an awesome rest of your night. Take care of yourselves. Get some sleep. See you later
Okay
Now that they all left everyone that wanted to go to bed that really needed to go to bed was like, all right
I'm going to bed. See that person's doing a comedy run. I can't do one more. It seems good. All right, it's confession time
What a terrible place for that to spot
No, get get me out of here. Let me out. Let me out. He's a rabid fucking animal
Like pretty good comedy run I would say peak comedy run
What was the confession in the first 30 minutes of playing this game? I thought it was fucking dog shit
Like in the first 30 minutes. I was like, wow, this game is fucking absolute dog shit. So this is awful
well
I'll play this for like an hour or two and then I'm fucking never opening this again and then um
And then I realized what what it was and and realized that it was fun
Now I am telling you this is probably going to be my favorite game of the year
This possibly could be one of my favorite games for the year
It's just it just grabs a hold of you
Yeah, I mean that's obviously a really bold prediction, but I I know how I am when I get in a game
And this is really fun. Even if it's like kind of a it's it's it's kind of it's rough, right?
But rough in a kind of a good way
Um, I know it's it's literally february and this game's not even out yet
But I could see myself jumping in this and just playing it and bashing my head against the wall. Oh shit. Sorry
Yeah, I lowered this accidentally. Thanks for watching. Thanks for staying up. Um, we'll play this again
I'll see you probably i'll ping some other streamers and see who wants to play it. Maybe on um on wednesday
Have an amazing rest of your night. Get some sleep. See you soon. Thanks for watching. Take care of yourselves
See you soon. Good night guys call your mother call your mother
Call your mother. There you go. Good night