What he said, the lame title.
Well, I'm retired now, so I don't have to worry about that anymore.
How's it going?
You're gonna play armored core.
Yeah.
We need to talk about armored core because, uh, I have some, I have some
thoughts, I have a few thoughts I've heard.
Uh, I've heard it's very, very, very difficult.
I've heard it has a very, very large learning curve.
And I mean, I would be jumping into, uh, return to the Jedi without watching
any of the other star Wars movies.
So, I don't know, maybe this is not true.
I heard it was really hard.
I heard it was okay.
Here's what I heard is that I love from software.
I love dark souls.
I love Elden ring.
Oh, yay.
Here comes another from software game.
It's just, this is not Elden ring, dude.
This is a different game.
This is a completely different experience.
How about this?
I'll maybe I'll open it.
I'll try it.
But if it's clear that I'm just like completely have no idea what I'm doing.
And it's just like, Oh, I'm having, I'm having a lot of trouble.
And we might just move away to something else that day.
You'll love it.
I I'll give it a try.
I will.
But I've never played any of the armored core games, any of them.
I don't even know if I like this genre.
You know, I'll try the new food, but I will be honest with you at the restaurant.
Oh, Hey, try this.
It's, it's got, um, cilantro.
It's got a, the squid in it.
And it's, um, it's got a potato mash on top.
I'll try it, but I'm going to tell you, I'll take a bite.
And I'm going to go, it's all right.
Not for me.
Or I might go, Oh, nice.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, I don't, I I'll try the new food, but I can't offer it.
I can't promise I will love it.
What kind of freak doesn't like robots?
I, I like robots.
I just don't know if I'm going to be good at playing as a robot.
Uh, but anyways, let's talk about the next, uh, week or so.
First of all, we're going to play viewfinder tonight.
Today.
I have a plan to play bouncing duck simulator.
If not today, then be on Monday or something.
We'll see.
Also at the end of this coming week, I want to continue sorcery part four.
And I will try.
Uh, I almost just said assassin's creed six armored core six.
That's the plan for this coming week.
Probably streaming and streaming today, streaming Monday, and then probably on
like Saturday, Sunday, maybe like Sunday this coming weekend, but for today, let's
play viewfinder of a Hilux two.
Yeah, I know.
We have to play the assassin's creed now.
He's never going to play Hilux.
I definitely will.
What about mine?
Quack.
I don't think so.
What about the Smurf cosplay stream?
I never said I was doing a Smurfs cosplay.
When are you going to reveal your balding?
Um, somebody in pre-stream chat said, Oh, Hey dude, like have you started balding?
And I was in the middle of typing reply to this person, but I stopped.
And I deleted it all.
I deleted everything because I'm not going to even talk about that because you know
what I mean?
Like I, I'm not going to type or, or, or address like anything about me, my hair,
my balding or anything.
I'm not even going to talk about it.
You know what I'm saying?
Do you know what I mean by that?
Like, I'm not going to even start talking about that because I'm not, I
ain't manifesting anything.
So I am going to, uh, have no comment on that.
I, my hair is great.
I'm not making any comments besides that.
I've, I've got, I've got pretty good hair right now.
The only comment I'm going to make, you address it constantly.
Yeah, but I address it jokingly constantly.
It was a, that was a real question in pre-stream and I was like, Oh yeah, well
here's the thing, man.
Like, let me tell you about, no, no, no, no.
I'm not going to, I'm not going to sincerely address it.
No way.
How many hotdogs do you think you could eat in 45 seconds?
Let me think.
Probably two, maybe, maybe full one.
I don't know.
I've never tried.
I would say one, one sounds like fine, maybe, but that's not something that I
something, that's not something I would recommend trying.
Yeah.
Uh, how about this?
How, how long do I have?
All right, give me a number.
Give me like 10 minutes or like, what's like the, um, how long in a hotdog
competition do you have to eat all the hotdogs that are out there?
What's like a typical hotdog competition timer?
10 minutes, 30 minutes.
Okay.
Uh, I would eat one over the course of 30 minutes and I would eat it with a
fork and knife during the competition.
Be like, here we go, everybody.
Welcome to the hotdog contest.
Let's go.
Three, two, one.
Let's fucking, everyone's freaking out and I just slowly take one and just
start cutting the end off and choosing which dipping sauce I'm going to put it
in.
No, that's what I'll do first.
I will make sure that, that there's 10 different dipping sauces and I slowly
make a little pool on the plate with each one and I will like make, oh,
exquisite faces every time I take a bite.
That was a Malcolm in the Middle joke.
That's a good one.
That's a, what a, that's a good episode.
That's real.
That was Malcolm in the, all right.
Well then, yeah, it's a, that's, that's a funny joke.
I like it.
I should watch that episode.
I don't think they even have dipping sauces past the water jug.
Once I get my headphones, it's over for you hoes.
I don't know how yet, but it will be.
What are you talking about?
That person is really excited to get a new pair of headphones.
And I'll tell you, I've been there before where you're just like, oh man, I'm going
to be powered up once I get this new thing.
You ever get, you ever just feel like completely energized.
There's like a new thing coming up.
Soft retirement, soft hair loss.
Do not out.
I actually want you to time that person out.
I don't want that message to be like recorded into history.
I want that message deleted because I don't want to manifest that.
I want that to be deleted.
And then here it comes here.
Everybody say it.
Here it comes.
I'm doing just fine.
I'm doing all right.
Manifest some fucking hair.
Yeah, it's luscious right now.
I've been manifesting it since I've been drinking green tea since I was fucking
19.
All right.
That's how you manifested.
Can I have your comb when you're finally gone?
Oh, that's gone in the museum somewhere.
Such like an ego.
That's such egomania.
I know.
All right.
If you wanted to see like the signup sheet or the museum of history of
entertainment history, I would bet out of all the things in that museum.
The German nine, eight, five comb in the glass gets the least amount of signups
for that part of the tour that they may, they might even have to move it to a
different room.
Eventually, you know, that's going to get moved three or four times before it just
gets put in storage.
And then I get a call asking for me to come get it.
All right.
You guys ready?
Uh, no more Stalin.
I'll put the baseball on display.
Oh, they will not.
Don't you have a copy of your face?
Yes.
And I don't like it at all.
Okay.
The reason why this thing is weird is because there's constantly a mirror when
there is no mirror, we all know, looking in the mirror, you see your face, being
able to see your face when there is no mirror is some, I honestly, I put a towel
over it, but I don't want to see it.
It's weird.
You laugh like a gnome.
That's fine.
It's kind of cool.
Show it.
No.
I don't even have it.
I lied.
It's not even here.
Turn on face cam one and just have it be the mold.
Now that would be really funny.
Except the problem with that is somebody would like, would like get it and like
zoom in and like with AI generated fucking knowledge, it would hit every
single point and they'd be able to make one.
You can do that now.
Oh, nevermind.
Who cares?
You should sell it or something.
No, that's very weird.
He's obsessed with himself.
All right.
Let's go.
You should sell it, but attach it to a life-size stretch Armstrong.
No.
Hey, speaking of things that are going on sale soon, uh, on 28th and a couple
of days, as YouTube is going up, it's not my, a mold of my face, but that,
that is my likeness.
Pretty cool.
All right.
Let's play bro.
Play the game.
I'm, I'm just chilling.
Relax, bro.
Don't play the game.
I won't.
I relax.
I I'm not gonna.
Okay.
Uh, let's do it.
I'm gonna move over here.
You should be able to hear the game now.
Viewfinder.
If you guys remember that we played this during the demo demo, whatever
it was, the steam demo thing, whatever it was, it was fun.
It's a game where you take pictures and the pictures become part of
the world that you can place.
It was very fun.
And let's, uh, let's freaking go.
Right.
We're in time to explore.
You'll get it.
If you don't get it very soon here.
How's the audio?
Is it good?
When are you going to finish breath of the wild?
You know what?
I will.
It's not right now.
Is there a sprint?
I don't remember.
I don't think there is.
How's the audio.
Can you hear good?
I've seen this much overgrowth before.
It's okay.
I already, I did that before and it scared me again.
I guess we know now that falling doesn't hurt.
That's some good news.
At least.
Oh, that's right.
There's a rewind to get back up there.
That was sick.
Yeah.
It's a rewind time.
Should I say that every time?
What's an old photograph doing here and just hype it up for a full minute.
That's going to be so annoying.
If you're like a new viewer, this was like, shut the fuck up, dude.
And play, stop.
Just play.
Why do you have to do like this weird thing every time?
Can you do something with it?
Oh, that's right.
Okay.
I can place this over here.
So check this out.
Watch this.
Check this out.
You ready?
Did, did you just shift reality?
Let's go.
Put the phrase on a soundboard.
That's kind of funny.
All right.
Hold on.
What should I say?
Like rewind bros.
Can I get a countdown?
We're going into rewind.
Ah, I fucked it up.
Hold on.
Hey, I can't even do it.
Why not?
Why is my GoXLR fucked up?
I can't even do it.
I think that, I think it's broken.
I can't do it.
Oh, it was funny for like five seconds.
We got it.
All right.
The batteries.
I remember the batteries.
Have confidence in yourself.
Yeah.
You would, when you, when you do, when you do acting, if you do voice acting,
you're going to do a few takes sometimes.
You can't get it perfect every time.
That just means you're a bad actor.
That's fine.
Shut up.
Oh yeah.
Soft retirement stream.
Let's go.
No, I'm not going to talk about that every five seconds, by the way.
It's almost working.
We need one more.
Looks like we need one more.
Does this mean it works if it's black and white?
Cool.
Hey, can you say hi to my cat?
Yeah.
Um, come here.
They work.
Hmm.
That doesn't look right.
Oh, you know what I'm going to have to do?
This is just the tutorial.
We're good.
Is it true that you're moving into a nursing home?
I have an, I have an idea or I, you know what?
No, I'm not manifesting this because it's funny.
Thank the jump.
I care.
All right.
Now this is where it's going to get pretty crazy.
It looks like the ocean.
Didn't we talk about this on the hit man stream from like years ago?
I wish I could be like, if you threw a car battery into the ocean, like what
happens, you know what I mean?
Like we've talked about this, how much electricity needs to like
electrocute the water in the ocean.
How far does it spread?
Electric eels are so weird.
What a wild creature to have organs in their body that hold charges and then
discharge.
It's like two or three different organs that do different types of charging, right?
It's so wild.
It must be a security measure, a structured path we have to follow.
Well, let's find the next magic.
Yeah, I, they kind of are.
You know how many times I've made a joke about shooting electricity out of my
hands?
There is a creature on this earth that does that.
No, sit here and think about that for one second.
Just bear with me here.
There is a creature on earth that shoots electricity out of its body to hurt stuff.
Excuse me?
That's not a TV show.
That's a real life.
All right.
I got to pay attention.
Where am I going?
Oh, this is like a hub world.
Okay.
I get it.
Are you high?
Be honest.
No.
So you can revisit levels.
That's cool.
Okay.
There's another one that's going to be active.
I can use them.
I think.
How do I turn?
Oh, here we go.
You answered way too quickly.
Now this would be an awful game to do that with.
Are you kidding me?
That'd be so bad.
Do you understand that if that were the case, I would be sitting here like this
for like 10 straight minutes and people would be like, what, where did he go?
BRB.
And then eventually it would just move.
They go, sorry.
I was looking at that mountain.
All right.
Where's this gone?
Oh, I need the, yep.
For the bridge.
Yep.
Go.
Sick.
Well well,
the surface you can use to climb up there.
Chicken wings.
Definitely high now.
What do I, what does it want me to do?
Oh, this.
Yeah.
Check this out.
Cool.
this game listens to your microphone I don't think it does everything is so
beautiful it actually is though all right I need two more I remember this
part this part's cool watch this ready I gotta make a whole painting on future
skies are bright that is a treasure in the making well that looks like shit I
made look at connected I connected these clouds and then I put this up here
where's the Sun oh oops can I have that back it's like why am I in a vacuum
cleaner it's just there for fun it's not supposed to be you I'm I doesn't matter
okay I need that how do I get that one give me them both back okay wait do I
have to do it like this oh shit okay um I think I did it nice give me this
painting we're taking this over here oh wait it's one more I just got an
achievement for dropping a battery off a level I don't think I did that right
yeah you have to like carve it out that's cool all right what if I do this
how do I get in here there it is he loves this game it's really cool I don't
know how many I don't know how many sleepless nights the coder it's just
like sitting there looking at the code and just going holy shit I feel like
after a certain point I would just be looking at this and be sitting there
going okay I'm I'm a genius at some point right like you have to give credit
where credit is due like you they need to take a lot of credit like this is
look at this at some point you have to sit there and like look at all you call
and go holy shit I did a great job and you absolutely deserve to say that I
destroyed the teleporter what did I do wait what did I do that just oh oh oh
god oh my god I'm gonna puke what do I do uh what the fuck is going on that was
really weird way too dank is it too loud seems like the simulation had some
difficulty maintaining itself we might need to reroute our power sources to
keep it running that's what we get for messing with old tech genius
this tricky to get ancient tech back in working order all right
computer please load Star Trek the next generation engine room please I got
pretty good oxygen have you guys noticed this is a just as something that I've
observed I have noticed that since kovat a lot of these are still everywhere
and I keep trying to put my hand under them and they don't do anything anymore
they just don't do anything anymore I'll be like oh cool what hand sanitizer let
me try it there's nothing there oh oh shit there's nothing in this I think
these have just been not filled for like a year that bad registered and I get
embarrassed every time I don't I okay I have absolutely been in a field of view
going from one that didn't do anything to oh there's one over there to the
other one that doesn't do anything either and then I kind of just put my
hands together and go like clap clap like okay um I'm gonna keep walking I'm
just gonna keep walking looks like we're back online ready when you are
all right let's go it's too bright these panels should be like gray hold on let me
see okay but the public sanitizers smell like the cheapest vodka and have the
consistency of saliva that's yeah that's kind of true
let's get our bearings and find where we left off the foaming yeah the foaming
ones were awesome if you if you had a foaming hand sanitizer it was just like
like a little moose oh it was perfect it's all you needed okay so do I go back
to that other hub that I was just in because that was corrupted right yeah
there you go you're just like spongebob on spongebob was fucking awesome okay
spongebob is awesome I'm being compared to who I would determine to be a
literal God I wouldn't be surprised if you know at the pearly gates it's
spongebob there okay I might be overdoing this a little bit it's fun
cool oh I'm here oh I just arrived at the gates oh it's the gates of heaven
huh spongebob I came over here okay spongebob I think I did a pretty good
job I did I make it into heaven yeah he pulls a fucking lever and you drop
straight to hell no you did not make it that's a family guy bit that's fine I'll
take it repent repent Patrick it's Roger from
American Dad whatever Roger for American diet they have the same kind of cadences
Roger from American Dad it's Roger from it's spongebob from American Dad what do
you want me to say they kind of have the same cases no they don't they kind
of do they're not even close somebody said I just sounded like somebody from
from so like from like Hollywood Squares wait what now look at that this is that
kid this is the cool part this is the part I like the most
anything any secrets yep this was my favorite now what did I sit on my balls
or something like what are they what do I do oh shit I remember I remember this
one I got this is from the demo this is what sealed that I was gonna play this
game it was at this exact moment that I said yeah when this comes out I'm gonna
play it he'll say anything in his retirement whatever like that's cool
Tony said when did we enter the Nintendo DS I was reminded of watching Joel's
perspective during the house slipper stream that's what I was thinking of
that was a lot of fun yeah already starting to think about when house
slipper 2 comes out already the gears are already turning on doing that again
so should be a lot of fun second time okay this one has a battery right here
so that's easy get it right over here give them more time yeah we learned a
lot from that first one so the second one's gonna be I think a little bit
improved oh I can't like put my face on this I don't know if like this is
another like funny dumb meme then like you are gonna photocopy you like the
photo the photocopier joke I think still works even though people that
doesn't really exist anymore right but like I think that that joke still makes
sense it still works there's something inherently comical about like oh I'm
gonna put my face to this is squish my face down to me it's quantity to me it's
like okay more than five to ten versions of like your smooshed face I don't know
how dangerous that is all right all right all right everybody relax what do
I need to photocopy oh definitely this I don't say photocopy too many whoa look
it's all pixelated oh guys it's just like the sunflowers oh that didn't look
right okay so what am I actually supposed to do here wait I know that it
that's it right I have three that's kind of work right yes how did you like
playing tf2 again it's fun I'm really surprised that that group that MVM group
did as well as we did we talked for about I want to say at least 15 minutes
before the stream like okay it's gonna be kind of hard this is difficult it's
really not easy yeah we destroyed it if Ludwig was going hard all right I need
some brainpower for this one no whoops should I just say wait is there any more
pictures over here oh wait a minute I'm gonna use three because I don't know
what exactly is going on here I make this jump ah I don't need more than
three probably let me just get them all get the get the duck oh oh this duck I
need two more ducks and I win is this water doesn't need to have a smell I
couldn't stop thinking about this while watching a ray attend to her plants
today there's an addictive quality to this place that makes up for the
inaccuracies that surround us when we come here out of thin air we create
beauty that tickles some but not all of our senses I read this as like I'm
reading sorcery strictly speaking the code we create is a technical marvel in
designing these structures throughs me like nothing else
averages every character in sorcery but the novelty of it makes it too easy to
forget what a real flower smells like and I don't want to forget sorcery
coming soon this coming weekend one voice yeah okay I might have one voice
but I have one version of one boy I have oh fuck never mind I'm retired who
cares where do I go um did I miss a picture oh wait up on the roof maybe
yeah there we go whoa wait give that back oh boy hold on I need to get up
there all right wait wait wait wait wait wait I need to come on I need to build
this first I don't know if you like I make it from here
okay got it yes I could go higher you play Gears of War
oh very briefly train just coming who's is open now teleport to optional
challenge can you recite the Gears of War lore mmm I can try what was the song
in the commercial it was like do do do do do do do do do do and they were
drilling down into the earth and they were all sitting in a pod drilling down
they were all sitting there and it was just drilling down down down down down
they had to go to the center of the earth to fight the aliens or something
that's the only thing I know about the whole game it was mad world was it it
wasn't the that it wasn't a rock song it was mad world it didn't didn't it did
it kind of that's that kind of it go listen to what I did and imagine that
this is something you haven't thought of in ten plus years that was kind of close
for being a memory that I haven't thought of in a very long time all right
so this is an optional challenge I don't know what it wants me to do but let's
find out I'm gonna put it right here here's a war to the last day this is it
this is not mad world this is it this is the one this is the right one this is
the right one yep I told you I told you I had it right it wasn't mad world
that's the one where they're sitting down and they're shaking in the pod and
it's going down that's gears it that's the Gears of War 2 like trailer oh
goodness what do they think that was gonna work
yeah Gears of War 3 is mad world all right well knowing that that means I
have to go like this I'm smiling the average bro what about this there a
picture up there yeah there is all right I need to get obviously get up to that
and I go from here I did there I do this that no not really oh I need to get up
there what's a maze I know what to do I know it well I already won I was gonna
say I'll just look at it from above okay now oh shoot oh crap you're cheating
there's no such thing as cheating in a game like this it's called using
different parts of your brain to solve different problems all right this needs
to be much closer I have the right idea this needs to be like over here from the
table that that should do it right yes it will do these mashed potatoes have
been going a while I'm getting worried what are you just stirring mashed
potatoes oh wait doesn't seem right this is not right oh how do I need to
rotate it okay but if I rewind is that gonna I'm gonna lose all my am I to lose
progress if I rewind hold on what is on this one did I oh shit okay wait ah I I
what the hell is happening what's the goal is there like a their goal I don't
know what the goal is is I don't see a teleporter anywhere up there wait a
minute I don't get it I missed a photo okay how do I wait hold on I have an
idea is that the one where's the one that I need to get right there I this is
a challenge mode this is not our where do the stairs go I just think I might
have gotten it it's right there can I crouch shit it's right here hold on I'll
get it this is gonna be puke wait what's that I got it I actually just got it I
think I can't climb these stairs why what are you talking about what get up
the stairs what what was wrong with that jump backwards all right this is an
optional hard mode that's why I'm gonna puke if I stay here for more than like
10 more minutes why can't I go up these stairs do it again just stop where do I
need to go do I have to go up there if I have to go up there then I mean I have
to have to go this way which gives me this picture which then let's go over
here there's this photo and I need to get each one of these so let me get this
photo we bring it back here so what if I go like this now I'm just here I just
wanna see what happens so if I get this this brings me here this gives me
another one of these which gives me another one of these which gives me this
which then allows me to I don't know I mean is this bait is this picture is
bait this has to be what if I go like this and just keep picking up the same
picture just over and over again I just don't I just don't get it am I am I
supposed to eventually make it up to the top of here does this do anything for me
which photo is the teleporter in I didn't I thought okay I thought that I
was look I didn't have the right context I thought I was trying to get up on top
of the other buildings that's what I had to do in the last couple times I only
did one more duck and I can take a bath all right so that went over here
Oh surprised you made it this far cat pause in a while since someone's
wandered around this place and it's good to have you there's plenty of things to
do here have you finished exploring the train will take us to Horia station a
place where science and art meet am I done with this section I think I did
everything I don't think I'm missing anything I
think I got it all you missed a duck ah yeah please man I don't have time I need
your skincare routine um he's a gentle cleanser on your face do this in the
shower and use a use a decent moisturizer when a few minutes after you
get out of the shower have to dry on your face that's it that's it
moisturize it moisturize your neck too people forget to do that and I'm not
talking about a little glob in your hand it's like a little pinky amount just get
it on your cheeks forehead your chin tip of the nose work it in easy this is
pretty let's go was that whoa hold on I'll never take the art of walking into
your work for granted I have to make the picture with my face there it is okay I'm
ready to go in what no that was that wasn't the Tasmanian devil that wasn't
an orc that was me puking you think I was doing like an orc rage charge that is
not what that was that was I just puked because that was weird whoa hold on let
me do it again oh it's so stupid okay and there's the teleport I think I have
to be I gotta look down I gotta get up there at the cat I like that this is
okay I'm gonna like these levels these are fun I'm gonna get even harder and
it's gonna be more fun to do that hello you do it I'm not doing it it's me I
don't know how it happened but somehow I lost direct communication with you live
comms don't seem to be working where you are that should be fine though we can
talk using this method as long as you pick up I'll try to leave voicemails if
you can't I've been monitoring your vitals in the system so I'll keep you
posted as you wander along good luck in there bring these to the planning
session what oh I get it whoa cool get out of the way I'm having fun there's no
crouching either shit okay I have to uh this needs to go all right I need to
take this out here's what I need to do check this out there we go now I have
enough space put my back against this wall and get it right there yeah we
listen to the Omega phone I just cut that off but it's okay all right I'm
gonna have to line up like three pictures here oh I I've seen a Disney
World documentary about this okay uh is there another lever I need a painting
for sure all right breathtaking paint me next always a pleasure to watch a master
at work thought provoking go there a painting how to use our screen printing
in mural successes your little orchids urine dream big but remain practical
strawberries are pretty good something I've been noticing this is a that's
gonna make me throw up looking at that all right my graphics card when the fan
turns on now kind of goes like this I think I'm gonna have to replace it oh
oh but it's not it's not that the fans loud it's making a different noise did
you okay when it would when the thing when the fan would boot up we all know
you that's fine the pitch has changed instead of it goes what does a pitch
change mean bearings might be cooked hmm it's not dirty I usually I usually dust
it out there's a change when the FPS changes oh it's only when I think that
it starts to heat up a little it's gonna do a sick drift stare at a wall no it
doesn't I know I know you were you talking about where if you look at a
certain thing or if a certain thing it's rendered it's like yeah I know I've
heard that I know that this is the fan kicking on yeah this is more like a fan
sound but okay let's see use camera okay I turn this I like does that help me at
all I'm assuming probably no but I'm gonna just see what happens now I can
rotate the photo what am I doing uh let me take a look around first why would
you need two photos if it's just right here excellent show you had coffee yet
yeah I'm just showing all right two batteries there are four photos I can
take here just just take them right I'm just gonna let's just see what's the
cat's name oh I don't know all right battery right there let's go like this
name the cat I don't know Joey that has a name it's Kate that's right yeah I was
not paying attention I was half my brain was and then it just buried it
somewhere all right one more we're probably up there
but I have a solution to this I hate this mess of my own making. You must know what Mira has been working on, squirreled away in her own little maze, so I can find a way to help her.
Mending relationships often felt harder for her I have been tending to her plans
I wonder why she didn't just put in the effort oh I think I just got her hold on
sorry all right I'm gonna go back here this is on the battery oh shit there it
is it's right there is that it is that not it I want a good bird's-eye view
okay where where is it it's not up there okay so is this one right here where is
the other battery I would imagine to be like around the corner right here but no
or up top on one of these but it's not where's the other battery huh I have an
idea oh I know what to do I know what to do there we go
nope oh I figured it out I got it I got it I got it everybody everybody chill
everybody chill how do you feel when all your fans can immediately know that
you are high well you're not very good at it because I'm not no I told you
since the analog clock I incident I have not been able to do that no I said I'm
never doing that ever again since the analog clock incident you also admitted
the analog clock thing was a lie to save face if it that was a lie no no no no
the cement level in hitman was the lie to save face you're mixing it up but we
have to make sure we get the record straight the cement level in hitman 3
was the lie to save face come on you gotta get it right what is this yeah I
think I distinctly remember looking over at chat at being like oh my god dude no
no way like what is he all right what's he doing and I was like what am I doing
I don't know yeah that edible must have just kicked in everyone's like oh of
course I was like I have to say that otherwise I look stupid you already made
this joke yeah but you know sometimes we recycle content I play them oh I do play
it wait wait I used to be really far away doesn't it go working read that
clock right now that clock is that exactly 3 p.m. I'm not sure about a.m. or
p.m. that is 3 p.m. I I said it that I said it after I said it after I said it
after I said it after I said it after it happened after what an accomplishment I
went out there and did this to the sunflowers went out there and singing to
them and I got stung by a bee I was like lying I thought I'm fucking around it
didn't happen no he killed it no I don't you don't play music to make a plant
grow I do this shit in real life all right I I know how to take care of a
goddamn plant have you seen my blooms have you seen my blooms have you seen my
blooms then I don't want to hear it you killed it again it's not dead yeah when
you don't even get your fucking hands dirty you don't press a button on a
computer screen all right and this is inaccurate I won't have to do this for
what do you have to say now and it's a sunflower to my favorite all right is
it done I gotta be I got an achievement for that wait oh oh that's not good I
think I was supposed to take a picture of this oh shit it's gonna sting me oh
okay cool I won five cool okay that's fun now what this is stupid what I'm
doing yeah how do I I have to take a picture of this guy can I move the
camera well that changes everything uh-huh ah now yeah yeah yeah yeah yes
oh oh don't Luigi me right now I know what I need to do it it's taking a
second um I don't I mean I guess I doing it is that right I got it I got it I
got it I got it I got it I got I'm fine everyone relax it's a puzzle game it
takes a second bro you are clinically goofy that's it that's kind of okay well
whatever it's a it's alright red hi now is that those actually like shark or
fish heads or is that like a cake or something they make it look like ice
cream or something I don't know what we got here dried mangoes that sounds
actually kind of good all right two batteries you got it
there's one is it gonna be a camera somewhere right don't do anything yet
that fix it we'll land now on this Wow get this man some prunes some prune juice
undeal the telephone hey I've been trying to look ahead but the simulation
is a bit of a maze you're the only one that can navigate it simulation is a
maze what remains of all their research should be scattered around you this is
gonna be a hard one machine that could solve climate change I'd be deep in a
lab somewhere anyway I'll do my best out here find that machine all right I'm
cheering you on find the machine delicate machine something to do with
climate that sounds familiar you got it Joey all right this is gonna spawn that
which that's fine keep that there a picture of it and that's it wasn't too
bad one two oh shit I ran the court over oh I really really ran the court
over so okay I get it I get it I get I know to do just watch I know exactly
what to do watch this hey that's mine I can say like that I didn't even need to
I had it I didn't even eat I didn't even need you that I didn't even need to do
that that was I got it I got it I got it I got it again I know to do is watch
watch this I did it backwards wait wait everybody just I know what to do I'm
I'm just doing it in the wrong order.
Okay, just get me in here.
Start over, watch.
I need to take a picture of this while it is intact.
There we go.
And then, now, it doesn't matter.
I got it, yeah.
That was a tricky one, but it was fun.
Now, ooh, but hold on.
This is where it gets a little weird.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, wait.
Take another picture.
Now, here we go.
You have to take one before and then one after.
Oh, okay, I bit it.
But this is the optional challenge now.
These are gonna get progressively harder and harder,
and I'm gonna tell you,
I don't think I'm gonna do all the optional challenges.
I'm gonna try them for five minutes each.
Start the timer starting now.
Complete them, you wimp.
They're hard.
All right, so what's going on here?
I was gonna take a picture of it,
because I don't know.
I imagine I could probably use this
as a platform to jump on.
What's the goal?
Let's find the goal.
The goal is to flip this thing sideways.
I got it, I've already got it.
You better start betting,
because I got it right now.
You better bet correctly,
because I just beat it.
Hopefully, you got 10 seconds to get the bet right,
because I just did it.
I know what I gotta do,
but I don't know how to get up there.
Wait, hold on.
Check this out.
Watch this.
It's the lowest point.
I need to see where it is.
It is, which side is it on?
All right, it's on this side.
So it's like,
I know what I have to do.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got it, I got it.
Come on, I got it.
Is that it?
Fuck, you know I'm gonna get it right now.
It's so close.
Got it.
Oh, sorry, doubters.
You just absolutely got destroyed right there.
I mean, just decimated.
I kind of feel bad for the doubters, don't you?
I kind of feel bad for the doubters.
The first time ever.
Usually, I'm internally swearing at them,
but not right now.
We're heading towards the workspace
of a masterful engineer.
See, Leon, much like the others,
settled in quickly here.
I got that one.
I caught that one.
I caught on pretty quickly on that one.
Oh, hold on.
Okay, there we go.
It's okay, the points don't matter since he's retired.
I'm sure you'll find something useful here.
I always believed in you.
Well, thanks, Joe.
Really important, Jerma.
What is your sleep positioning?
I am a side sleeper, usually.
Usually.
I got the, usually I'm on my right side,
and I've got a good pillow to support my arm and shoulder,
like my arm and forearm,
and I'm like right at the bicep meeting the forearm area,
is under the pillow,
and I'm kind of propped up right side, lying that way.
My legs are sort of down on the, you know what I mean?
I feel like most people sleep like that.
That's probably a majority.
Filter select.
Do you sleep hanging from the ceiling like a bat?
That would be really weird.
What does this say?
Information?
Dude, you guys have no idea.
It's gonna be, I, okay.
I'm going to commit to one bit this year,
and it's gonna be a good one.
I promise.
It's not a big bit.
It's just a small bit, but I'm gonna commit to it.
Pauly and I were laughing a lot about this,
and it's, it just, it has to be done.
It must be done.
Where's the level?
They're all staticky.
Don't say, I won't say, I won't say.
Will it be on YouTube or?
No, it'll be stream.
Probably just easier that way.
How do I unlock these?
Uh, excuse me?
Is there higher up that I didn't see?
It's gonna be really hard not to laugh,
but I will go into actor mode,
and I promise you, I will see the bit through.
By the train.
Right in front of the train?
Yeah, okay.
Ooh, I love the teal.
It's my favorite color.
Did you guess?
My entire channel is based around like these three colors.
Do you hear that?
Freeze.
Oh, another one of these.
Oh, all the levers.
What are we looking for?
All right, mountain.
Okay, need to watch this.
I was hoping I could just do a weird hop around it.
I probably can.
That's pretty close.
It's definitely doable.
Someone else will do it.
I know you will.
Don't hold W while you air strafe.
I feel like that was screamed at me
so many times over the years,
and I just never was able to not do it.
Just always press W.
You're just so conditioned
to be holding the move forward button.
I don't see a picture anywhere.
Jerma, I'm a dumb animal.
If I can let go of W, you can too.
I'm not even sure that's a possible physics ability
you can even do in this game.
I did let go of W though, I promise.
Okay, well, there's the teleporter.
Hey, look at that.
Air strafe is a Source thing.
Yeah.
All right, so very clearly,
I, oh, I thought I had to get four.
One, two, three.
Ah.
Well done.
Thanks.
It's a shame things crumbled.
Cake.
I don't like cake.
Can we get a poll?
I actually, and please answer honestly.
I know sometimes people mess around here,
but standard cake.
A standard birthday cake.
No, not ice cream cake.
Not a tiramisu.
Just a cake.
Just a regular cake.
Do you rate that higher than a C plus?
Is standard cake higher than a C plus?
Yes or no?
Because I am somebody that says no.
I'm very curious where everybody stands on this, honestly.
It's a very standard C.
That's what I mean.
I do wonder how many people see cake as higher than C plus.
I feel like it's probably a lot of people.
I thought that was a burger.
Okay.
So I'm gonna guess that I have to take a picture
of this with the poster.
Oh.
I can't wait to see how you use this.
I use it myself.
Wow.
58% higher than a C plus.
That's actually really surprising.
Okay.
I would say it's a C plus.
Maybe a C.
Some, but some cake is terrible.
I have never, okay.
Ice cream is always gonna be an A.
Because even like bad ice cream, it's ice cream.
It's just, it doesn't matter what ice cream it is.
It's gonna be fine.
Okay.
What are my options at the dessert?
It's cake is, okay.
There's vanilla ice cream on the table over there.
There's cookies.
That ice cream is always gonna be perfect.
I'm always gonna be okay with that.
But I've had a lot of cakes before that were bad.
That were way less than a C.
Grayscale, cold, warm.
Whoa.
This is really weird.
I'm gonna do this for one second.
Game boy.
Did I even activate it?
What are these bad cakes?
Dry as heck.
I have eaten cakes before that were super moist.
And okay, this is higher than a C plus.
This is all right.
This might be close.
But I've had cake before that.
I feel like I'm eating sawdust.
Oh, all right.
I kind of don't want to do this anymore.
Do you know what I mean?
I don't know if I like this filter.
Now I understand what it was for.
I can't even read the instructions.
Yeah, we are going to change this.
What is better on average?
What were the other options?
Cake over pie?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
No, no way.
Over like a banana cream pie or a chocolate cream pie.
I thought that apple pie,
I thought you guys were apple pie Andes.
All right, I can't even look at that.
Apple pie.
I don't even like apple pie.
Oh, a lot of people just heard that
for the first time, I think.
A lot of people may have just heard that
for the first time.
I want them to be closer.
Okay, well, did I just do it?
I just beat it.
Oh, okay, let me explain.
Let me explain.
Everybody that's saying, what the fuck?
If apple pie just had the sludge in it
and not the apple pieces, the apple slices,
if it was just the pie crust,
the sludge filling and no apple slices,
I would love it.
You take the apple slices out
and that would be one of my favorite pies.
That's fucked up.
That's fine.
But that sweet apple flavor is great.
I just don't like the warm, hot, slimy, slippery,
like apple, no, no, no, no, no.
It's just, I don't like it.
I'm getting achievements for doing this.
No bully.
NA has the worst cuisine.
What does that have?
That has nothing to do with,
I'm sorry, but banana cream, where is banana?
Where did banana cream pie originate from?
Because American desserts, hold on.
Hold the phone for a second.
American desserts are ridiculous.
Where did banana cream,
who made the first banana cream pie?
Coconut cream pie?
Are you serious?
What about donuts?
Who made the first donut?
Eh, it's probably like German or something.
Banana cream pie though, where did it come from?
Look it up.
Pecan pie, look it up.
Excuse me, cotton candy ice cream, look it up.
I'm just kidding.
American desserts suck.
No, they don't.
It's like one of the things that Americans make
that are very good.
Americans make fantastic desserts.
Barbecue?
Yeah, excuse me.
I don't want to hear that.
Look, I know like Americans, hey, LLM.
I got a nice smoked brisket.
Come on, Gwen.
I do not want to hear that.
Do Oreos count?
I want to say yes, but I can't
because weren't they something else like a long time?
Wasn't there like a whole thing about Oreos
and what are they called?
Hydrox, is there something?
Was Hydrox American?
I think it was.
But do other countries have cereals with mascots?
Checkmate.
That's right.
Yeah, sorry.
Tony the Tiger.
Tony the Tiger, it's American, okay?
Yeah, they do.
Oh, all right.
You want to have a cage match
between Tony the Tiger, Count Chocula
and that fucking wacky Cocoa Puffs bird
against whatever the fuck you're going to bring to the table?
What's going to get in there in the cage match?
Wait, were they fighting?
I forget.
I think they were fighting, weren't they?
I don't know.
I've never really thought that much about cereal mascots.
He's patriotic for cereal.
Of course I am because they are great.
I'm available.
All right, what am I doing?
Yeah, Captain Crunch.
You go, yeah, my cereal mascot from, I don't know,
wherever, from England,
my cereal mascot will beat your cereal mascot's ass.
Oh yeah?
Captain Crunch will launch a fucking Crunchberry Cannonball
out of his ship at you, all right?
You want to sail the seas against Captain Crunch?
Bring it.
Why do I care about this?
All right, I need to play the game.
Play the game, nobody cares.
Oh, I think a lot of people care,
judging by the amount of scathing reviews I'm getting.
All right, so I got to get that.
Let's get a picture of that first.
Well, that was way easier than I was making it.
You still eat Oreos?
I'd say maybe sometimes.
Whoa, what's this?
That's kind of cool.
What about the Honey Nut Cheerios Bee?
What's your number one snack right now?
I don't know if I could say,
it really does vary depending on the mood.
Celia always fond of games.
Can I play this?
Honestly, if you want the real answer,
it's probably hummus.
I could eat hummus all day, every single day.
And I probably have always one of the first things
that I get at the grocery store.
Did you nick my biscuit?
Love it so much, it's like the best thing in the world.
What sort of accusation is that?
Did, didn't you?
I can always ask Kate, you know.
Oh, right, so what if I did?
I was just sitting there going uneaten.
It's not as if it could have gone cold.
Hummus with a little bit of bread.
Kate, can you please run shortbread for PXE
for our esteemed colleague.
Non-bread.
Chickpeas are so good.
What am I supposed to, am I supposed to go in?
Wait, I'm not actually supposed to walk.
I am.
Okay, hold on.
Wait a minute.
Wait, this is really cool, hold on.
I gotta jump down on it.
That makes sense, doesn't it?
Oh, that makes so much sense.
Come on, get in there.
Yes, it's something like that, right?
Oh, wait, what's this?
Am I overthinking this like crazy or what?
I'm overthinking this one?
Okay.
Hang on.
Oh.
Did that sink?
You make my biscuit.
Me?
What goes on?
I steal your biscuit.
Must they flip?
What sort of accusation is that?
You did, didn't you?
I can always ask Kate, you know.
I don't get it.
Oh, right, so what if I did?
I was just sitting there going uneaten.
It's not as if it could have gone cold.
Well, if you're gonna kick up a fuss.
Oh, I get it.
I fall into it.
Maybe please run short my Doki XC
for our esteemed colleague here.
I get it.
Biscuit thief.
I don't get it.
What am I trying to do here?
What was the, why was this cool thing here?
What?
Is this just a cool thing?
Well, okay.
All right, where's the batteries?
I did this one in the demo,
so I should get it pretty quickly.
It's two, right?
Yep.
Okay, and then I need to take a picture of this,
put it this way,
because then, aha.
I pre-played this level.
I did it in the demo.
What about on this table?
Something to pick up?
Everything keeps breaking.
You think in a simulation,
everything will find a way to maintain itself,
but no.
Change the filter?
Yeah, I have to wait till the next level.
Keeps me busy.
Some piece.
I could have done it, like dropped out,
but I would have probably had to do all these levels.
What is that?
This is Tetris.
Does it actually play?
Ooh, yeah, it definitely does.
All right, so hold on.
How do I do this?
Dude, all right, I can get this.
Wait a second.
Can I?
Maybe not.
Shit, all of it was gone.
Whatever.
This is cool, but somebody else can figure this out.
It's a fun little thing.
What's this one?
I'm right here.
Give it to me.
Holy shit.
Can I go all the way up?
All right, I did it.
That's fun.
Those will stack infinitely.
They will?
Oh, shit.
I found something else fun to do.
Hold on.
I don't care about the level right now.
Like, I just want to do five of those.
Where was that thing?
Yeah, I'm gonna get a picture
of like three or four at the same time.
So technically if I go like this
and then like that,
it's gotta get one and I'm good.
Oh, shit.
All right, I gotta take my time.
I don't even care about the teleporter.
And I'll go back because I can,
let's go like this.
That's better.
Goodness.
This guy sucks.
No, it's kind of hard to get these.
Oh my God.
Uh-oh.
No!
Go, ah, wait.
Oh, fuck off.
Shit.
I want to restart
because I have a better idea.
I'm gonna put them closer together.
I want to get them all.
This is gonna be so stupid,
but I don't care.
It's fun.
All right, so here's the plan.
Plan is put this in a spot
where I can get to it easily,
like down.
Okay, here we go.
Now, I'm not stuck.
I'm doing something weird.
No, no, no, no, no.
God damn it.
Oh, yep.
Here it is.
Absolutely perfect.
Now, I can fall down and get these stones.
Do it like an idiot.
I lucked out so bad right there.
Okay, it's time.
I got them all.
Stop doing that.
I have to go straight up.
I need to break the fucking video game.
This is it right here.
Here we go.
Shit, hold on.
I have to air strafe way sooner.
Let's go.
Luigi, Luigi!
That was kind of fun.
You just scared my cat
and my dad.
Well, keep me on lower volume.
This is a comedy stream.
You woke up my husband.
Well, I,
why are you listening to me?
Full blast.
What are you doing?
That was fun.
That was worth wasting 15 minutes, 20 minutes on.
Is it only two or is it three?
Oh, it's only two.
Did you know that scientists have to spend years
developing new technologies?
All right, let me turn this off.
Negative is kind of cool.
How do I just turn it off?
Do I have to pick one?
Is warm the default?
Grayscale is the default.
I'll try warm.
Actually, I kind of like the color.
I like the color.
Wait, there's an optional level here, isn't there?
Beauty of the simulation.
What you can achieve in a year's time can be.
I have one shot.
That's not bad.
I actually prefer the warm.
I mean, they had the cold tones,
but that's still fine.
Stop right there and shout your guess.
Three.
The answer is three.
These might be useful.
I want my, I want my camera back.
What should I, happy birthday?
Happy birthday, whoever's birthday it is.
No photos allowed.
I only have one shot here.
That was really not what I thought I was gonna, whatever.
It kind of worked.
You idiot.
Now this is content.
This game is pretty fun.
I like it.
Okay, one shot in the camera.
Now what?
This one's complicated.
Quite.
I feel like it's gonna be pretty simple.
Watch this.
Where is the teleporter?
Over there.
I need two.
Okay.
Where's the other battery?
Is there more film up there?
It's all right.
I just want to see what's,
I only have one thing of film though.
I need like a wide shot of this.
Oh.
Shit.
Oh, stop.
There's one angle I can probably get them both in a picture.
Through the wall?
Hold on.
I go like this.
Will this count?
And then say if I do that, does that work?
Kind of.
I need to.
Yeah, I know.
But like, ah, it takes a second.
The easy ones sometimes are,
they, you know what I mean.
Sometimes it's not that simple.
Takes an extra two seconds.
Hey.
Now this is the mahjong table.
All right, this turns this on.
Cool.
But interesting.
You're all so creative.
What do you call a melon that commits a crime?
A water felon.
I didn't even need, I didn't even need to look it up.
See?
This is weirdly placed.
Why is it like this?
Probably a duck down here.
Well, okay.
You're tracking dirt in.
Sit, sit, sit, sit.
Should I sit?
Ah, nice.
Yes, we are quite quirky like that.
What did we do?
All right, I need, all right, let's just spin it.
And just put it over here.
And then this, oh, it's not correct.
Now I know why that hole exists.
I get the whole thing.
Okay.
Then, is there a good place to get this whole thing
on camera?
I hope the camera doesn't break.
Bond over a cat pet session or something.
I have heard petting is quite soothing.
It's probably right here.
Yeah.
Cool.
Simple.
You gonna play Armored Core?
I might.
I'm gonna try it, but I'm gonna be very, very honest.
I don't know if I'm gonna play it for a while.
I gave my take on it.
I'm definitely interested.
Okay, so, looking into this setup,
there's clearly something wrong with the system.
The deeper you go, the more the data are corrupt
due to lack of upkeep.
Definitely gonna do Sorcery later this week,
but there's a few things to do.
We'll see.
I'm interested in it.
You can tell my chin is currently pointing
straight down into my neck.
I'm leaning back because of, you know,
burp is a hiccup is here.
But besides that, yeah, I might play it.
Despite that, it's still wondrous.
Let's go, look at that.
Yeah, it definitely worked.
Ah, I can't be clever like that.
Oh, Jerma, hey, you're stupid.
Have you been moisturizing your neck?
Question is, have you?
Well, very clearly, I'm probably gonna shoot
from the bottom up.
How's this?
Just don't wanna cut it off.
This should do it, right?
Yep.
I like these ones, these are fun.
Wait a minute.
Wait, what the?
What?
What happened?
Where am I?
And what is down right now?
What?
I just tapped it so many times and it...
Okay, we're good.
Pray that you've been enjoying your explorations thus far.
I have been.
Thank you, cat.
Hamster powering his brain is getting tired.
That's such a rude comment, but it's funny.
So you get to stay.
You know what I mean?
That's a rude comment, but it was funny.
So you get to stay.
Oh, there's more.
There's many memories stored here.
Many impossible things.
Hmm.
Filter?
I like this filter.
Okay.
So I need to stand here to activate this.
Is that correct?
That is correct.
So I need to take a picture of this while this is activated.
That was the dumbest idea I've ever had.
Okay.
It's on a timer.
Okay, I had the right idea.
Get me in there.
Shit.
I'm just trying to go.
So I'm just trying to skip it.
I'm just trying to skip it.
You know what I mean?
Is this on a timer?
Okay, this is on a timer too.
No, it's not.
So it's just as simple as,
is it just this simple?
You're doing great, as Tony would say.
Thanks, Tony.
Blueprint.
I know what to do.
Sort of.
Uh-oh.
That's not good.
Wait a minute.
I feel like I had it right,
but it's the wrong angle.
Did I actually have it right?
You are one brain blip away.
Like this?
Why won't that get powered?
I need more.
Oh, come on.
I'm touching it.
I only have one photo.
Shit.
I'm so close.
Somebody said I was one brain blip away.
It's not.
Just take a picture of this, right?
While it's, no, right?
This didn't work last time, did it?
No.
Stand on top of it and then grab.
What angle?
There's a certain angle I gotta get this from.
I don't know.
I'm trapped here.
Do I have to go up top?
No.
Walk through the problem slowly.
Okay.
There is a teleporter over there.
I have to stand on that.
I have one photo.
To do this, I have to depress this plate
while at the same time, this needs to be upright.
I feel like I did the last three very easily.
Everybody relax.
It's all right.
It's a puzzle game.
You're supposed to take time on some of these.
Why am I having trouble?
Wait, hold on.
There's a ladder.
Maybe.
No.
I need to get it all.
I need to get it in view.
The whole thing.
Shit.
I don't know.
This is gonna be so simple and I'm just not seeing it.
I did the hard ones without a problem,
but this one is just a head scratcher for me.
I don't know why.
I figured I got it.
I got it.
The sneeze actually made me know what to do.
I just had to jumble the brain around a little bit.
Okay.
It's over here.
You gotta take a picture of this.
Hold on.
I got it.
It's I have to do it like this.
Watch this.
Ready?
Hey, here it is.
All right.
Now I go over here up on top.
If I could get on the ladder, that'd be great.
And then that allows me to, if you check this out,
now I'm able to
fucking hit this.
I need to know the sneeze quick.
Is there another camera film that I'm not seeing somewhere?
Am I just overdoing this?
Shit.
This is the only one I've been stuck on for this long.
I've been playing this game for two and a half hours
and it's the only one.
I know it's simple, but I can't, what is it?
Don't tell me.
Oh, it didn't work.
Why did it not work?
Speed is impressive.
All right.
You can take him out of emote only.
Glad I sneezed.
I, okay.
Let me tell you what my problem with that solution was.
Stop.
Everybody hold on.
I took a picture of the thing when it was depressed
and when I went, it didn't go forward.
But when I took a picture of it, when it was timed,
the timer and you know what I mean?
That was not all right.
I took a picture of it when it was like this,
but it doesn't last.
See, I didn't know that's what it was.
You know what it is?
I did that one instantly.
You just almost killed me of laughter.
You just sitting there laughing your ass off at that.
You know that they're gonna study us
in a hundred years, right?
They're gonna study you.
Oh, stop.
Okay.
This is, I don't have the camera anymore.
Yeah.
What do you want to say to people in a hundred years?
So when some scientist is going through
like the thousands of hours,
the hundreds of millions of hours of streams
and videos and stuff,
they're gonna have, they might see this chat.
What would you like to say to the scientist
a hundred years from now?
Seeing a lot of fuck yous.
Now this scientist is gonna look at this and be like,
what?
How primitive were they?
They must've been very primitive.
They immediately on talking to a potential scientist
in the future, went right to vulgarities.
Primitive species.
Okay.
I can't look at that.
That actually was weird.
That was, that was too much for my head.
I really don't like this level at all.
If there was a button,
if I could press F5 and skip this level,
I would do it right now.
Not because I don't think it's interesting,
but because I don't think I can do it.
I don't think I can handle it.
Oh, what the fuck?
God.
Take your time.
You got it.
You beat Sekiro, remember?
Yeah, I did.
Thanks.
That was a nice chat message.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Oh.
Was I supposed to get fooled somehow?
Oh, I was.
Wait.
I think that was supposed to fool me.
Just making sure it's not going to do that again.
Oh, get over there.
Whoa.
Oh, that.
All right.
Somebody on the dev team is a magician.
Can I make that?
Can I say that?
I'm going to say that.
Somebody on the dev team, I think, is a magician.
Like, they know how to do magic and stuff.
You know what I mean?
I think someone's a magician.
Like card trick.
Hey, look.
The salt shaker on the table disappeared.
That type of magician.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
Somebody's a magician.
And I'm curious.
These are little sleight of hand tricks.
Okay.
That's, okay.
That's cool.
Don't even try to tell me that that's not interesting,
what we're looking at.
Because that's really cool.
All right.
It is not what it seems.
Yep.
Uh-huh.
Cool.
That's just, has that just been here?
Weird.
All right.
Now what?
Is it saying to go down?
What, what are we going to, what's the reveal?
Ah, it's stimulating his monkey brain.
Should I just fall?
Ah, that wasn't part of the trick.
That wasn't part of the trick.
He went the wrong way.
He's gone.
He was supposed to go in the door over here.
He just walked up the cliff.
Um, watch your step.
What is it trying to tell me?
Wrap around and jump this way?
Intriguing.
Okay.
Then from here,
I'm imagining there's probably a false floor here
that I fall.
Don't jump, don't jump, don't jump.
It's telling me to kind of wrap around and fall?
What is it saying?
Like go right around a circle
and then left around the top left circle
and then straight down.
Are these directions or is this something else?
I feel like this is correct.
No.
No, I was down here already, wasn't I?
Yeah, I was already down here.
Watch your step.
Is there just a hole in the ground over here
that I'm not seeing?
Filtration system proofs for how long?
Let me sit down for a second.
What is this trying to tell me?
I came in this way.
The only logical way is over here, right?
Like this, out this way?
No.
I was imagining like right here.
And then you watch your step.
No.
I'm kind of stumped.
I wonder if it's very simple.
What does this mean?
Come on, teleport me down.
Fuck, I thought that was gonna be it.
Trace it and then by the,
your movements of the mouse will bring you down.
Hold on, let me drink some of my drink.
You're a clown, you're a clown.
You're not saying that,
but that's what I'm getting from the emote.
Shit.
Why is there no edge here?
Ooh, look.
Look at these.
Okay, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Here we go.
All right, so it was,
I don't remember what was,
oh, don't go that far back.
All right, so it's around the bottom right,
loop around the top left, straight out.
Cool.
All right, sneaky, sneaky.
He's got yellow brain.
I don't know what he's talking about the pillars.
Don't let them bully you.
You did good.
I think I did fine.
How many batteries?
Two or three?
One, really?
It was never gonna be that easy, was it?
How do I get in there?
Oh, God damn it.
It's a fake wall.
Okay, that doesn't look right.
Wait, this does not look right.
I have to take a picture of it before I go reveal it.
I have to take a picture of it.
I think I know what to do.
I like, I know what to do.
I know what to do.
Watch this.
Ready?
Wait a minute.
I wanna like spin this.
How do I spin it?
This?
Tricky.
But even if I rotate it, will that matter?
It's not real.
Hey, what happened to it?
Where did it go?
What?
Oh my goodness.
I don't know what's going on.
So I have to make it active, get a picture of it
and then rotate it and take a picture of it again.
Wait.
Okay, okay, okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I have to touch it from the front.
That might be all right.
I get it, but I don't.
Does that work?
Shit.
Fuck it.
I don't know.
I get it, but I don't.
I have to take a picture of it
when it's right facing right at the camera.
How do I get it to move without it being the wrong direction?
I have a different idea.
Let me try this.
I do what I just did and then I take a picture of it
and then I put it the other direction.
Let me try that.
So now what happens if I do this?
Will it be facing the right way?
Do you know what I mean by this?
You see what I'm doing?
I mean, that's correct, but it's not right.
It's kind of correct.
What if I just, can I drop it?
Will it fall out?
No.
Ah, this is a, this is a stumper.
Like, well, can I, will it just, it's not falling.
Wait a minute.
That's not what I have to do, is it?
There's nothing there.
It's, the shit's empty.
There's nothing.
Ah, huh?
There's nothing there.
I would have tried that.
I would have just, I would have tried to do that.
What the hell?
I would have probably tried that.
Oh, what?
Well, okay.
Oh, I beat it.
Was it bugged?
It was bugged.
Wow, okay, that makes sense.
I was wondering, I was like, why is it not there?
I thought I had to touch it for then it to be active
that it would be there.
All right, I want to do the super secret level.
Where is it?
All the way up?
It was there one time where it didn't show up.
Yeah, I thought that was a bug
that it wasn't supposed to be there when it flashed.
So I was like, oh, that was a bug that it was not,
that it's not supposed to be there.
There's no optional level here?
Oh, okay.
Let's go.
I'm going to take a quick break.
Looks like we have,
we have a pretty decent amount left.
Two more chapters.
I will be right back.
I'm going to pee, refill my drink.
See you guys in a minute.
Looks like we got two more, oh, wow, what a blunder.
Give me one more second.
My drink, the other room.
Give me one second.
Cookies.
I want cookies.
Keep going.
So this is chapter four.
Let's go.
Mirren's workspace awaits.
She's rather special who started all of this
with good intentions, no less.
She even made me, and for that, I will always be thankful.
Even though she, she really loved this place.
How many blinkers did you just hit?
Oh, this one's cool.
Observatory.
It's different, isn't it?
Mirren was passionate about her studies.
I love the music in here.
Pretty relaxing.
Okay, let's go.
What mechanic are they going to introduce now?
Two batteries?
Why are the batteries different?
It's spreading, I'm concerned.
Is this a regular battery?
Why is it so, oh, that's what makes it so weird.
You can't take a picture of these phantom batteries.
Oh, whatever, just put it right here.
That was just a cough.
That was just a regular cough.
It was a regular cough.
It had nothing, it had nothing to do
with any of the things that you're talking about.
It was just a little, okay.
You know what the cough is from?
I just drank a bunch of kefir and it's just settling
and it was like, okay, it's settled
and I had to clear my throat a little.
That's it.
Can I pick up everything or just the kefir?
If kefir is, oh, hold on.
People are talking about snacks.
Saying, hey, hey, what's your snack of choice right now?
Kefir is another one?
Wait, okay, so that can remove that gray stuff.
There it is, cool.
Um, what do I take a picture of?
This is incredible.
The system is self-learning and ever-growing.
It can be used to build structures,
new buildings, support it on its own energy.
This could truly help push the principles
of my research to new heights.
I need to show this to Haria immediately.
Excited.
Um, what am I missing here?
What?
That's not what I took a picture of.
I wanted to roll this down the stairs.
Okay, what?
So I'm supposed to clear something with this.
The teleporter, what the hell is going on?
I take a picture of the, this right here?
I'm like, what is, okay.
So can I, I don't know, can I walk up this or something?
Where's the game progress?
Um, I don't know.
Oh, Matt, I probably have to climb up this, right?
Somewhere?
Hi, okay.
I, again, I'm playing chess
when I should be playing checkers.
There is the end of the phone call.
He made it, I'm so happy.
Nice work.
Appreciate the view, you made this,
you can master anything.
The weather disruptor.
We're gonna make, um,
weather machine or something?
I need film for the camera.
Oh, hi, can we reach?
Not even the sky can limit us.
All right, there's a, something over there.
Looking for film for the camera.
Okay, is that film?
Nice milk voice.
Yeah, yeah.
Here we go.
I'm sure you noticed by now,
using film was always Mirren's idea,
one of her many passions.
All right, now make the bridge to the film.
That's the fucking worst bridge
I've ever made in a video game.
That has to be the worst bridge I've ever done.
I, okay, everything's fine
because you need to do it like that.
I know what to do.
You gotta go down here.
Enough solution.
What do you mean, dude?
I have it right.
I just didn't do it in the right spot.
Hey, I made it.
Look at that.
Five pictures, oh boy.
This is gonna take a lot of brain power.
This might be the one.
Okay, five photos.
What do we got?
We got a foil, two batteries, and a cage.
Okay, I need to take pictures of batteries
and drop them in here.
Go look for those first.
Use, useless junk for play with.
That's not a battery all the way over there, is it?
Nobody said they wanted to bet on that.
You would have lost.
Let's take a selfie and clone yourself.
Well, I'd have to set the camera up
and get my entire body though.
Otherwise it would just be awful.
One battery, that's it.
Dude, you're a lot smarter now that you have a job.
Oh no, he has to use his brain every day.
This is, I don't like this anymore.
Okay, so what do we do with this?
How about cupcakes?
How about, how about cupcakes?
Whoa, shit.
Um, well, interesting.
I need to go down and put it like there.
Oh, uh, what's going on here?
Jesus, I didn't want to do that.
I have to drop it from here and catch it.
Drop it from here and catch it.
No, I'm going to do something insane.
It's going to work.
Check this out.
Okay, watch this.
So far so good.
What the fuck?
This is not what I thought that was.
Oh, I thought this was flat.
I thought this was a flat painting.
Oh boy, that's makes everything different now.
Okay, well, my plan was not a good one then.
My plan was really bad.
Knowing that, I, I, I, I don't know.
Is something in here that I can get?
The, the, the, the beats.
Yeah, okay, more film and a ball.
I guess maybe this, does that make sense?
Sense, does that make sense what I just did?
How do I get out of here then?
Um, shit, I don't really know what to do here.
I guess I could, I have to like replace
this whole level with this thing, kind of.
I'm going to try my stupid idea.
My idea is really dumb.
It's my idea is actually completely moronic.
Like this is the worst idea I've ever had.
What do I do?
Um, not over here, right?
I wish I could move it forward and backwards.
I mean, catching this makes the most sense,
but then how do I get out of there?
I mean, how do I get out of there?
What a fucking mess, but I think it's going to work.
I actually think I just did it.
Yeah, I think I got it.
Did I?
It's right there.
It's the right idea.
Hold on.
How can we be silent?
I'm, I'm trying to concentrate.
It's, this is a lot of brain power.
What pictures did I take?
Why is there a whole fucking building over here?
What is all this?
What is all that?
I'm so confused.
I wanted just a picture of the tile.
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah, it sure is.
It sure is that, isn't it?
Okay.
I was wondering how you would call this.
That was so long.
Oh, that was so long.
That took so, I was going to build a whole structure
to pick that up and walk it all the way back.
Wow, I can't believe it.
Okay, we're good.
Chill stream tonight?
Yeah, I'm, I'm just hanging out.
I'm having a good time.
Okay, here's the problem.
How do I get them both?
Hmm, can I get around?
What is this here for?
This has got to be here for a reason, right?
I only have one picture.
I have one photo to take.
I just don't know what to take it of.
You want me to take a picture right up here, don't you?
All right, I get a picture of the sky.
That's not what they wanted.
Okay.
I'm going to get it right here.
I just did it.
Watch this.
Watch this shit.
You think, you guys think I'm fucking around right now?
You think I'm fucking around?
Watch this.
I got, I'm going to get it right here.
Oh, come on.
If I only had another shot to take.
I'm so, it's so far away.
It's right here, but it's just not right here.
Press it.
What's up?
What's up, cat?
Huh?
What do you mean?
What's wrong with it?
Fuck you.
God damn it.
I just learned that by doing, we're good.
Everything's fine.
You take the picture through the wall.
Is this your solution to heal the world?
Brute forcing the puzzle.
Well, hey, we all have different ways of learning.
My way of learning was jumping off the side of the building
and trying to take a picture of it while it came into view
to then slide down it while falling to my death.
And you can just take pictures through walls.
So, but I figured that out because I did that hypothesis.
So I figured it out still.
All right, this will be interesting.
What, where am I going?
This one, we're doing the same thing we did before.
I've already learned.
I already know what's happening.
I already got it.
Pretty much a done deal already.
There we go.
Stop with the pictures already.
It's the whole game.
I'm going to go cold.
I like the cold colors.
Optional challenge.
I want to take a look at it.
There's gotta be a way, right?
Hold on.
Come on, there's gotta be a way to take,
to keep this going infinitely.
I don't think there is.
Is there another one?
Oh, wait, is this just very simple?
Oh, I need, wait a minute.
There it is.
One, two, three.
Wait, I need one, yeah, one more.
Did I cheat?
No, I think that's what you're supposed to do though.
That was a fun one, I liked that one.
New camera filter, painting.
I'm kind of curious about that.
Does it look much different?
How do you even program this?
That's what I'm saying.
That's wild.
All right, somebody can take a screenshot of that.
Music, I must admit, magnificent with the guitar.
She's promised to come play for us here again.
I have more tests to perform
before sharing my theories with the others.
I haven't felt disinvigorated
since my first successful Violet build.
All right.
All right, coil.
A lot of coils.
Far too many coils in this one.
So I have to power all,
I gotta power up all these.
It's interesting, that's for sure.
All right, this one is powered.
The radio is what powers the coils.
Okay, so here's what we're gonna do.
Try it the simplest way possible.
Shit.
Ugh, no.
That's them all, yep, nice.
I got a flow, I'm in the zone right now.
Okay, coils.
This is lever.
All right, so I need a radio box to go right here.
The hamster is running, oh yeah.
A beat that just makes you wanna get up and dance.
And also power a teleporter over here.
All right, is that it?
Oh, that's it, but wait, there's one over here.
Oh, no, that's it, there's one.
5G audio.
Telephone, telephone, telephone, telephone, telephone.
Wait, I can't take a picture of that.
Good to hear from you, bud.
Okay, so this is a photo.
I get it.
All right, so I have a camera, right?
Yeah, okay.
I'm really rolling on this one.
Five pictures, I wonder if it's just timer, right?
Oh, this is gonna be easy, watch this.
Nevermind.
Light travel, sound travels, light pulse sound
equals kinematics of weather events using light and sound.
I think I have an idea, ready?
Watch this, and let me look around.
Can I play something on here?
I don't think so.
I think I have to stick it closer and closer.
How?
Oh, yep, watch this.
That's definitely how I'm gonna do it.
Oh, I have to be standing the right way.
I got it at the beginning when we take pictures.
Um, I don't get it.
I get it.
Let's get a picture of this.
No, nevermind.
So I have to bring it, I don't know.
I can't take a picture of that.
That doesn't do anything.
What can I do?
Interesting.
Oh, hold on, it's right there.
I already got it.
Here's the, whoa, oh boy.
This is gonna take a little bit of extra peanut butter.
So not much else to do, but that's kind of cool.
So I'm just gonna play with this.
Thank you.
I'll cherish this.
Okay.
Can you think of like the most childish image to draw?
Like, I'm just thinking, okay, what would you draw
to be like really just, oh, I know.
How about like somebody with like the finger?
No, he's gonna be waving.
Ready?
No, that's fun.
It's a cat.
All right, now this is where the fun begins.
All right, we need that.
We need this to be, jeez.
Actually, this has to be first, I think, right?
So if I go like that here,
and this needs to be right here.
Is that gonna work?
Oh, yes.
Where there is truly a fickle thing,
the claimant can impound non-living thing.
Impossible questions and impossible solutions.
Optional challenge, let's go.
Only one piece of film, that's fine.
I don't need it.
I have an idea.
Just stagger it.
See what I mean?
Oh, I get a better picture.
I need a lot less of the outside.
There we go.
That's definitely what I have to do.
I just not, I gotta get it right.
Kind of better, kind of.
I don't know if I can jump to here though.
Damn it.
Can you please play a soap cutting video?
No, get out of here.
I got the right idea, it's just not the right execution.
Jumping?
That looks pretty good.
That looks kind of good.
Oh, that is close.
It's gonna be really close.
So close, but so far.
Maybe, is that it?
Oh, it's so close.
I think that might be it.
I'm trying to catch the last pixel.
Damn it.
That's the right call though.
That sounded like Arnold.
Wow.
I'm so fucking close.
That could be the one.
Ooh, this could be it.
It could be.
Damn it.
Damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it.
There it is.
I got a new filter, rainbow filter.
Wow, that's kind of wacky.
Looks like the negative.
I'll try it.
I'll try it for once.
All optional content completed.
Let's try this one.
Spill.
There's no other photos here, right?
I think we're getting to the end of the game.
One more section.
I wonder if it's, how long it is.
It's one of these.
It's one of these where I have to go
like three different ways.
Okay, I see the teleporter.
All right, well, that's not gonna work, is it?
How many does it need?
One or I can't tell.
It might just be one.
Is it one?
I hope it's one and not two.
If it's two, then I'm in trouble.
If it's one, I got it right here.
It is one.
That was the first try.
Photocopy?
What does that look like?
Nope.
Stay on this one for now.
I feel like we didn't get a chance to see it.
This game is really good.
It's just really, the puzzles are hard,
but they're not too hard.
Did I do them all?
No, one more.
Optional.
Okay, there's one more optional.
And then there are two.
All right, there's one more regular level,
and then there's two optionals.
Let's try this one.
All right, they've introduced weight.
I don't have the camera.
All right, so I'm gonna take a picture of,
okay, I'm gonna take a picture of the watermelon.
Seems easy enough.
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
Why can't I look through this?
That's kind of weird, right?
Oh, just stand on it.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
I did not want to go all the way back.
Hmm.
Can I just throw it?
Does this take a picture?
Wait, what is this?
I don't think this takes a picture of anything.
Yeah, because it's all, yeah.
But wait, can I get over here?
Damn it.
What do I do?
Shit.
Oh, my melon!
I don't have the camera,
so I can't take a picture of the melon.
Wait, can I stuff it in here?
What's this hole here for?
This hole is weird.
Oh, my God.
This is a weird hole.
That's a weird hole, isn't it?
It's perfectly for a melon.
That is a perfect hole for a melon.
Hmm, I wonder.
I got an idea.
Here it is.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
This is gonna be wacky.
Can I stand on something?
I can't move anything over there.
I can't stand on something.
Can I activate the camera through the ball here?
Like if I jump off?
No, there's no way to hit that button.
Fuck you, game.
I cheated.
We know.
I saw somebody, okay, I was moving over
and I see somebody say, cut the watermelon.
I was like, what are they talking about?
And then I realized I took the picture
and I was like, that's how you cut the watermelon.
So I half cheated.
I didn't know how to do it until it was too late.
That's not even enough.
Yeah, I got it.
Okay, I get it, I get it.
Interesting.
That's funny.
Please repent.
You need to eat a watermelon on stream to repent.
Hey, new camera filter, watermelon filter?
What does that look like?
I have to know.
Yeah, all right, it's expensive,
but let me tell you something.
The best juice, the best fruit juice
you can possibly purchase, and I mean it.
Have you guys ever had evolution juice?
Evolution watermelon juice or evolution orange juice
is nothing compares.
Absolutely nothing compares.
Absolutely nothing can ever compare.
A whole lot of no's.
Really?
Never heard of it.
Has anybody heard of it?
You know where you sometimes will see it?
You'll see it in Starbucks.
Starbucks sometimes has them on the rack.
Does anybody know what I'm talking about?
Does nobody know this?
How does nobody know this?
I've seen this across the country.
It's not just in Vegas.
Nice hallucination.
No, I'm telling you, it's life changing.
Now, evolution, evolution juice brand.
It's expensive.
It's a cold pressed juice.
Their orange juice, it goes absolutely nuts.
It's the kind, okay, so when you see it on the shelf,
it's half of it, like all the orange
is settled to the bottom half.
And then all the top is like a clear liquid
and you have to really shake it up.
This shit is fucking unbelievable.
I don't buy it that often, but when I do,
and they have a watermelon, oh man.
It's no, it's not pulp.
It's not pulp.
But no, it is kind of pulpy because it's,
you know, it's the real shit.
No one's had this.
There's such an unbelievable orange aftertaste
that tastes like a real orange.
They sell this shit in Starbucks.
It's not shit, it's delicious.
How much, okay, how much is a large,
like 32 or like 20, like a big jug of orange juice?
Like how much is it now?
Six bucks, seven bucks?
So this one is like nine to $10 per jug.
Six or seven, yeah, that's usually what it is.
But let me tell you, if you have an opportunity to try it,
it's gonna ruin everything for you.
It's gonna ruin everything for you.
It's gonna ruin everything.
How big of a jug?
I think it's 32.
I think it's 32 ounces.
It might be more than that.
$11 for, actually, I think that is accurate.
Let me, hold on a second.
Give me one sec, I wanna look.
Actually, I own one right now.
I saw it and I was like, holy shit, I need this.
Give me one second.
I'll give you the exact ounce, the exact ounceage.
God, I just slammed a bunch of it too.
I just ripped it out of the fridge
and just started chugging it.
It's 59 ounces and I believe it was $11.
So it's about 60 ounces.
So that's about, you know, 60 ounces, yeah, 59 ounces.
No, I didn't drink 60 ounces.
So it's 59 ounces.
It was about 10, 11 bucks.
Maybe you can get it cheaper.
Maybe it's more expensive somewhere else.
The orange juice and the watermelon juice.
I think they make like, oh, there's vitamins in this one.
I don't get any of that.
I just get the straight up juice.
But I don't see it that often.
When I do see it, like my eyes just lasers
just shoot out at it.
Like, it's the one with the cursive logo, yes.
But this is the kind of juice that you sip this.
I cannot work with that.
You sip this like it's a fine wine.
I just, I just told you I slammed it.
Yeah, it's all right.
Okay, I need, where's the, where is it?
It's really good.
You know, if there's one thing that you can tell,
okay, if there's one thing that you know about me
and this stream and everything about this,
I don't mess around when it comes to food brands
that I like.
Have I steered you wrong before?
I do not mess around when it comes to foods and beverages.
I don't screw around.
I recommend only the finest products,
only the most delicious beverages, only the best.
Dr. Oetker's sucks.
That is one of the most,
that is one of the finest frozen pizzas.
I don't even know if they make it anymore.
But no, no, no, it does not.
I've never steered you wrong.
I believe everything I've said
about different beverages and foods.
Fuck the cheesy gordita crunch.
That actually might constitute a ban in this channel.
Do you think that that's, I mean,
that really might constitute a real, like, permanent ban.
How do I, what am I doing here?
What about McDonald's?
Yeah, I love my McDonald's order.
It's two double cheeseburgers, no pickle,
one McChicken, not spicy McChicken,
but sometimes you can't find that anymore,
and then a 10-piece nugget, meal, so you get the drink,
and then those nuggets are to be shared with the group.
Not, that's not the old, like, two or three years ago
when me and Ludwig were talking about it.
No, that, two double cheeseburgers, one McChicken,
and then nuggets for the table.
Sometimes I don't even eat those nuggets.
It's just like, hey, they're here.
No pickles, no, I don't like pickles on.
Three burgers, holy shit.
They're not, a McChicken is pretty small.
No fries?
No, you, the fries come with the McNuggets.
And I might, I don't really eat the nuggets.
It's just like, I get them because,
here's the thing about nuggets.
A lot of times, people don't want to order them.
Like, oh, yeah, I could get nuggets, but mm.
It's like, don't worry, I got you, I got you covered.
I'm gonna get them,
and we can all just share out of the box, fine.
I got you, I got you.
They always get eaten.
They're always eaten, all of them.
I don't eat all of it.
There's been a misconception
that I eat every single thing in that order.
And here's, listen to me.
If there is no group, if there is no group,
a McChicken is deleted, a Double Cheeseburger is deleted,
and it's a 10-piece nugget meal
and a Double Cheeseburger for the Powerade, that's it.
Why did I just take a picture of this?
All right, where am I, where am I going?
It's over there.
I need to, I need to look,
see what the hell's going on here.
Get me, okay.
I need to dispense this, like, pissing me off so bad.
There we go.
Okay, so what did we learn?
We learned a few things.
We learned Evolution Juice is probably the best.
It's three, damn, okay, hold on.
Three.
Your order comes out to be about 2,000 calories.
How much is a Double Cheeseburger
for McDonald's with no pickle?
Just one Double Cheeseburger, what is it?
Just a Double Cheeseburger, it's 400.
That's four, eight, and then how much is a McChicken?
Standard McChicken, nothing on it.
350?
It's 1,100 calories.
This level's too hard.
What size drink?
I usually don't do, I don't really get,
here's what I'll do.
I'll get a Powerade and I'll just put it in the fridge.
I'll maybe take, like, a few sips out of it,
but I usually save most of it.
Hey, another voicemail.
It's getting harder and harder to reach you.
I hope you're doing well.
I am kind of a weird person,
and I know a lot of people are like this too,
so raise your hand if you're like this as well.
When I'm hungry and I eat,
I don't really drink a full drink.
I just kind of, I think a drink kind of fills you up a lot.
Sometimes I won't even take a sip of something
for a little while.
I used to be like that, yeah.
I think a lot more people do that than I think.
But obviously, like, I'm not just gonna wolf down food
without a drink, that's not good.
I'll take a sip or two maybe every so often.
A lot of people do that, yeah.
I think that's why I'm able to eat a little bit more food,
is because I'm not filling up with a big 32-ounce drink.
The drink is the first thing I finish.
See, that's super foreign to me.
And let me make this very clear.
This is a once-in-a-while delicacy.
I am not eating 1,100 calories,
1,200 calories of McDonald's every day.
This is like once in a while.
And hey, guess what?
I have some really bad news for you.
That large milkshake that you got
from the fucking ice cream store
is probably 1,400 calories.
So, hey, don't come charging at me.
This is weird.
All right, so I need one.
Okay, let's try to get this done.
Weird, okay.
Oh, goodness.
All right, so this one is, this one has color.
It's time for the ultimate poll.
The ultimate food poll.
You guys ready?
Let's do it.
How many scoops of ice cream would you consider to be?
That's good.
From, not from the freezer
where you're doing it on your own.
I'm talking about you're at an ice cream store.
And it's like, okay, here you go.
Here are the sizes.
It's one, two, three.
One, two, or three.
Which one is it?
I'm gonna give you the correct answer
when we're done doing the poll.
The correct answer.
Somebody said one.
I'm ashamed to say more than three in public.
Look at this.
That was not as hard as I thought it was gonna be.
Decentrist Andy, we already know this.
Well, that might not be correct.
Let's see.
Okay, very interesting.
The correct answer is one.
Correct answer is one.
I'm gonna give you the reason why.
I've gone to get an ice cream before.
And you go, you know, usually it's usually
at the, in the evening times.
And one scoop of ice cream from a place,
from a store is usually massive.
Massive.
To a point where I'll eat half of it.
I'll eat two thirds of it and be like,
oh, geez, I just can't do it anymore.
It really depends.
Yeah, somebody, that's a good point.
It really depends on where.
But most places really, really pile it on.
And I've even been to places where I go, yeah, yeah.
Can I, can I get one?
Just like the little, just small one.
And the worker is super nice and really, really wonderful.
And they're like, I got you, I got you, yep.
And they really just, they kind of give a little extra.
And it's just like, okay, all right, all right.
We're good, we're good.
Okay, that's all right.
It's like super nice.
I would like to order the little kid's,
I want like the smallest possible one.
Because after a while,
please raise your hand if you like this.
After like bite number 10 of an ice cream,
it sort of starts to get a little,
the flavor kind of goes away
and it kind of just becomes like milk to me.
It gets a little kind of heavy and,
not, yeah, bite, like you're eating a,
there was a communication breakdown.
There was a communication breakdown tonight.
There was a, oh shit, this is so funny.
I should have, I should have started like this.
I'm talking about in a cup, not,
I shouldn't, I'm not talking about an ice cream cone.
I'm talking about in a like cup with a spoon.
I probably should have made that a little clearer.
I just keep imagining just,
just taking big bites out of an ice cream.
You'd be like, holy shit, dude.
That's like, that's what like a dog would do.
Like stop, slow down.
Okay, so now that we have that clear,
when you get more than two scoops of ice cream in a cup,
it's, it just gets so heavy after a while.
I'm glad we could clear that up though.
Thanks for joining.
Magnificent athletic feet.
And with that's grace at that.
I just keep seeing somebody just be like,
oh, thanks, I appreciate it.
Like bite, bite, bite, bite.
I feel like I was going to be,
I feel like I was on like a prank video.
Like, what is this guy doing?
Okay, now here.
Yeah, there was a little communication breakdown there,
but that, that was, oh, that was funny.
That was so funny.
Oh man.
Back here.
You've done whatever's in this maze of memories
and forgotten wonder.
Did I win?
I hope your experience has been pleasant so far.
To me, it's been.
This is going to be awful.
Okay, so it's blue, blue.
What about the McRiddle?
See, the McRiddle is kind of where I draw the line
because I don't, it's not that I don't like the McRiddle,
but it's kind of too much for me.
All right, I need a minute to pay attention to this.
What's the point of me doing this by the way?
Yeah, why wouldn't I just,
it tastes really good.
I need to, give me a second.
Ooh, this just hurts.
This hurts.
Okay, I think I'm just going to skip the blue.
I don't have a camera or anything.
I mean, it's open right now.
Can I just, wait, yeah.
Is it changing?
It looks like it's changing.
Damn it.
This one is confusing me.
Well, am I missing something to do here?
I keep thinking of somebody just biting an ice cream,
like hard.
I feel like that would be so bad on your teeth.
I feel like my teeth would just, ugh.
It is a mobile game ad.
So what?
I guess, okay.
I think I understand.
If I go through blue, walk through blue, step on that,
go through, I don't, I don't, I don't get it.
Let's go through red.
They line up.
Yeah, but I mean,
why would I walk all the way over here to turn it red
to walk all the way that way?
What is this one even doing?
This one's not even taking down something.
What is it?
What is this doing?
Is it doing something?
What's the point of this one?
I'm going to just try this way and see what happens here.
You're changing the portals.
Red has always been over here.
Now that's blue.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ah, okay, okay, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
All right, sorry, I was talking about ice cream and shit.
All right, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
All right, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I know exactly what, yeah, I got it, it's done.
I wasn't, yeah, I think,
I don't think anybody knew that was going on
except for one person.
What's this, what type of ice cream?
What's the, what's this for?
Soft serve, oh yeah, this is an easy one for me.
Isn't making it this far enough?
Haven't you gained all the knowledge
this place has to offer?
This was our life's work,
and it's meaningful the way you want these.
This is the big reveal.
That, wait, aren't I still in the simulation?
Scoop, I believe, is the correct answer.
Scoop is correct with one,
one thing that takes that completely out of the way.
Soft serve with a cherry dip is unbeatable no matter what.
Cherry dip, vanilla cherry dip is,
with a soft serve, nothing will ever compare, ever.
They do, like chocolate dip too is good as well.
I think cherry dip soft serve is just S plus,
and even the best S hard ice cream is below cherry dip.
You never had a cherry dip before?
Uh, Dairy Queen used to do it.
Is Dairy Queen still doing?
That's where you can get it.
It didn't work.
It's really good.
It never, it wasn't supposed to happen like this.
I feel like we need to pay attention right now.
They were all supposed to find the answer.
Hmm?
This, this isn't it, it can't be.
The solution, it all made sense.
The formula, the structure,
this should have solved all our problems.
This should have been the answer.
I need this to be the answer.
Why?
Why isn't this working?
I, I can't give up.
I'm sorry.
When I realized what you were looking for,
I didn't have the heart to tell you.
An impossible solution for an impossible question.
Mirren was, she was crushed.
They all were.
I didn't want you to have to, to feel as they felt.
It's a painful burden, knowing.
Twist is good too.
Soft serve twist.
Honestly, I'm not sure I could really pick,
you know, hard scoop ice cream is better than soft serve.
That's like a ketchup versus mustard fight.
I don't think I'm going to crown a winner there.
He does not care.
What, what, what happened?
Did something really like bad happen?
Oh, what did I, what did I happen?
What did I do?
Oh, I don't know what happened,
but I'm sorry.
I didn't, I didn't mean, I'm keeping it on watermelon.
No, I wanted to be, that's the last part of the game.
This is it, the final chapter.
Mustard is disgusting and you should feel disgusting
for liking it.
Oh, should we tell him about honey mustard
and how that, it's just sad that that opinion is,
that's, if honey mustard is existing,
just makes it hard for me to agree with that.
A good stone ground mustard with honey mustard.
Oh, ketchup is good too.
I don't love ketchup on a lot of things,
but the things I do like it on, I love it.
But it's home.
Honestly, mustard is way more versatile than ketchup.
Ketchup is just kind of ketchup and it's just ketchup.
You know what you're getting and it's very classic
and it's good.
But there are dozens of varieties of mustard.
You can turn it into completely different things.
Now you can put like, you know, a hot sauce in ketchup
and you can change ketchup a little,
but I think it's, mustard has changed almost completely
when you add things to it.
All right, let's go for it.
What do we got?
Final chapter.
Everything's kind of floating around.
I have a feeling I'm gonna have to touch some stuff,
but pastrami sandwich with mustard on it,
slice of cheese, the mustard makes the whole thing.
Camera over here.
All right, are you just hungry?
I think I'm just hungry every time I stream
because I don't eat on stream.
I think I've figured out the formula, guys.
I don't eat on stream and sometimes I'm live, you know,
for four or five, six straight hours
and I just, I'm not eating on stream.
So I just, I'm thinking about the delicious foods
that I would like to have.
Okay, so I don't have a camera.
Can I take, all right, I think I can take this.
All right, I got it.
This will delete the fence, right?
Wait, this is taking a delayed photo.
Should I do anything about this?
There's a lot of photos in this thing.
Are we gonna get to see what it looked like?
So I'm imagining I can then,
can I teleport myself in here?
Now that's cool.
Where's this phone?
Can you hear me?
Ham and cheese, mustard in the toaster oven.
Oh yeah.
I think it was the, oh yeah, that just fucked me up.
All right, I won't talk about food anymore.
Let's go.
Oh, oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
Barcode.
Reserve it?
I'm not there.
Holy shit, that's, okay, that's cool.
Barcode forest.
Anything here I can grab or no?
I think it's just a cool thing to do.
Hmm, I'll just take a picture of this.
Now I have to teleport in here, so how do I get,
maybe I do just have to stand in the forest.
Will it see me in there?
Oh shit, I deleted it accidentally.
Why would I go in the, why would I do that?
How do I get out of here?
Forest, I can do it twice.
It's a lot easier than I was making it.
Okay, picture, let's take a,
I'm just gonna take six selfies.
I think that's, I don't need more than that.
Wait a minute.
How do I, how do I get out of here with the battery?
Hmm, okay.
So now, can I get out of here like this?
Oh, wait a minute.
Okay, got it.
Now, how do I get?
I know, and I don't have enough photos.
What if I'm holding the battery in my hands
during the picture?
I'm doing that.
Let's go take a look.
All right, I need to get over there.
There is no battery.
I have to eventually teleport over there.
And down here, it looks like bullshit.
It's a text.
Elevate the pollutant degradation system.
Geniuses.
Is as though our success are the result of a team effort.
Future is looking bright and I'm having a lot of fun.
Metabolic flux analysis of bio-coded specimen
makes for fascinating research.
All right, pick any of this up.
Okay, the camera is right here.
I don't have to jump.
I think I've jumped to getting it.
No, I don't.
I have to jump.
Did I get it?
Aha, I did it.
Listen to the megaphone.
Still wear those beads on your arm?
Talking about my crystals.
All right, do I need to?
Yeah, I had a black tourmaline bracelet on one day
and everybody thought I was like a healer or something.
And it's like, I just liked it.
I wonder if I do this.
And this will be kind of far away,
which means I can teleport up there.
Aha, yes.
This is to get it in the right spot.
This place, it's old now.
Fallen apart.
Data left alone for too long.
Corrupt.
Please, be mindful.
Only got two more levels left or two more areas.
What's the mechanic in this one?
Camera's back.
Weird.
Hiraia left.
These.
If these have struck the light here,
something must be wrong with the camera.
Because I don't want to forget.
This is dangerous.
We came here to challenge wonders,
but now we are left.
Don't seem to fit together.
Perhaps our time will be better used out there
and in the world.
Hiraia must have felt.
How could you?
One battery, it destroys everything
it takes a picture of now, which.
When was the last time I heard somebody do that?
These.
So what if the weather disruptor didn't work?
This can't be the end of everything.
Search all the memories.
I gave up.
Okay.
I refuse to leave this place until I know the answer.
Until I save everything.
I need like a, sort of a bridge or something.
Hmm.
Is that far enough?
Whoa.
I forgot everything.
I got to take a picture in front and then behind.
There we go.
This is wild.
Wild.
I'll give you a baby scoop ice cream.
I just, it's a manageable scoop.
And sometimes I just want one, just a little bit.
Especially if it's something like, oh yeah, here.
Here's our, our special, you know,
blueberry cheesecake ice cream.
It's like, okay, I just, I don't want a whole,
I don't want a lot of that.
I just want enough.
But it sounds great.
It's pretty here.
And the sound of the wind is nice.
Is this what yours once was?
Is this what you're trying to get back to?
Maybe take a picture of the windmill?
Ow.
You're going to get a sample and get full from it.
Now I want one scoop of blueberry cheesecake ice cream
or strawberry cheesecake or fudge cheesecake.
Or, oh, it's nine o'clock.
It's over.
I'm about to say something that's going to really,
I, and you know what?
I might not even say it
because a lot of you are going to hear this
and it's going to be a sigh of God damn it.
Butter crunch ice cream.
I'm just going to wing it.
You're completely out of my range.
Yeah.
I can't find you.
Vitals are still fine.
Like you're in a deep sleep.
New game plan.
What is that?
You're going to need to break the system somehow.
It's butter pecan ice cream,
but there's no pecans in it.
There's just little crunchies in it.
It's that delicious, buttery, sweet flavor.
That's boomer ice cream?
It is not, please.
It is awesome.
It's really good.
Mirren is refusing to listen to reason.
You Americans disgust me.
I'm not the only one who put time to this project
and it's not wholly a failure.
That's a green eggs and ham moment.
I even built a simulation of the world outside
just to keep track of the climate.
Just wait till they take a bite.
But it's not enough.
It needs a solution.
Some things just aren't.
Oh, I think I was supposed to copy this.
Not like this.
The only thing I can copy.
Best Ben and Jerry's flavor that is half baked.
You have a, oh shit, I do have the camera.
Oops.
I don't need it.
Okay, I just beat it.
Watch this.
Half baked is my go-to.
Yeah, I think it's just the easiest one.
It's definitely the easiest one to get.
There's a lot of other good ones for Ben and Jerry's too,
but half baked is just the best one to get.
Fish food's pretty good.
I'm a sucker for marshmallow, so.
Okay, just one.
Good enough.
Hmm, interesting.
No more film on the camera.
Can I jump over there?
Hmm, did I do this wrong?
Not this way, right?
Oh, there it is.
Okay, it's right here.
Hmm, I think I just did it.
I did it.
There is one.
I feel secure.
This is the last one?
Just as your friend said.
What about up top?
I wanna see up top.
Last level, so let's take a look.
Ah, there's one more.
Selfie?
Selfie, but I have the camera.
Hmm, I'll take another one.
Yikes.
Battery, two batteries.
Ah, I, um, hold on.
Hmm, I need to get a picture of this.
What about that moldy ice cream?
Yeah, but that was my fault for having,
I didn't realize it was there for that long.
It wasn't even moldy.
It was freezer burn.
That was very funny though, I will admit.
Timer, that's just, that's the stacker sound.
Woo, woo, woo, woo.
And then it goes, oh.
Hmm, camera.
Very obviously, I need to, like this, this over here.
And then take a picture of me there
and then teleport across the game over there.
Yes, this is it.
We're at the end.
This is the final level.
I want ice cream so bad now.
I, I do apologize.
It's getting later here.
It is definitely very late where you are potentially.
Five minutes.
Choices made.
Go.
Oh, this is gonna be a huge fan of the S,
I can already tell.
It's still going.
Why, I'm rewinding time.
What's happening here?
What the hell?
Oh boy.
Hold on.
What do I, I don't know.
Where do I go?
I just, can I reach another level?
Where did it, where did it, where did it, where did it,
where is it?
There, why did it disappear before?
Come on, go.
Hesitation is the enemy of innovation.
Oh my God, dude, come on, this bullshit.
Oh my God, I'm not letting it go.
It's, what am I supposed to do with this?
Huh, where is it?
Dude, what am I, what?
What was the, why is the radio there?
What was the point of the radio?
I don't get it.
It's just a distraction?
Was it really?
That's annoying.
Oh, what about, what's his name?
I don't know, whatever.
It's a distraction, just go.
It's time for distraction news.
Oh my goodness gracious.
This fucking level.
Get up there, you stupid fucking thing.
Oops, I fell off.
What's this?
I'll take it, I'll take it.
Teapot?
Where are we going?
This way?
I need two batteries.
Two, oh my goodness.
Oh shit.
Why did, where are the batteries?
Oh, oh boy.
Okay, wait, don't do that yet.
Hurry up, come on.
What the fuck did I just do?
Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, come on.
Wait, where, wait, hold on.
What the heck just happened?
Oh shit, this is not real.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Ah, um, ah, ooh, ah.
All right, what do I need?
Do I need batteries?
What are you trying?
Okay, go around the pillar in a circle,
but what's the pillar?
Where is it?
Should I take another one?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Come on, dude, do it.
You're killing me with this bullshit.
You are killing me.
You're killing me with this.
You're killing me, you're killing me,
you're killing me, you're killing me.
You are killing me with this.
Um, you're killing me.
No, no, no, it's over, I lose.
I just got three Luigi notifications in a row.
Luigi is spam texting me right now.
Grr, I'm flexing that one.
Okay, now the battery is down here.
Fuck, I forget, I forget, I forget.
Hold on, go back, back, back, back, back.
What, um, um, yeah, yeah, yeah, yep, yep, yep, yep.
I take, um, I, why did I fucking forget this?
The photocopier, I forgot I had
this stupid fucking photocopier.
I don't even need to take two copies of this.
I have two, I already have two copies.
I forget.
Pace is fine, I got three minutes,
so it was two and a half minutes.
Okay, all right, I need two batteries there.
Okay, we're gonna teleport over there.
Am I, no, I'm not.
Okay, all right, all right, now I need to get batteries in.
I need the radio.
Do I actually need the radio?
Where's the radio?
Can't I power this some other way?
Take a picture of, um, oh my God.
Bleh!
Okay.
All right, now, where's the, wait, wait.
Oh no, oh no.
I need to take a picture of this whole thing.
Oh, it's over, I think it's, I think it's over.
Boys and girls, it might be over right now.
Oh, fuck off with this stupid horse shit.
Oh, God damn it, this is really hard.
Get these bushes out of my face.
Okay, I'm gonna take a picture of the radio.
We're good.
All right, I gotta stop fucking laughing,
like stop laughing.
I, get this shit away from me.
I'm good, okay, everything's better.
I just need two of these, that's it.
Oh, oh, I forgot, I forget.
It's gone already, why is it gone?
I remember, I don't even need two of these,
but I'm gonna take two
because maybe the last level needs it.
All right, let's go, plenty of time.
Just use the radio, boom.
That shit is so far away.
Oh, you're driving me fucking crazy with this.
What, just drop it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
What was the point of that?
Why did I just even do that?
What?
I did it.
You did well.
Thank God.
It's thanks to you.
I got, I got it, I got it, everything's fine.
She was desperate, but I see now,
there is no singular truth.
That was tough, that's not a perfect answer.
Anything meeting you in this place
was the closest I would ever get to knowing.
The red world that awaits you.
Is it loving?
Is it healing?
Ow, what?
You didn't tell me there's physical force in these, man.
I see.
Suppose our time has come to an end.
Thank you for stopping by.
I wish you well.
This is the real final level then.
I beat the level already.
You really get, I'm gonna get a Luigi text
before I even get to try it.
That's kind of,
that's like the last plant on earth or something.
Don't drop it.
You probably need some rest.
Too good to be true.
So awful.
Not yet.
We can keep brainstorming on that.
Hmm?
Wait, what's that?
I got the plant.
What kind of plant was that?
I did it.
I got the good ending.
Well, that was great.
That was a really fun game.
I enjoyed that the whole way through.
Should have taken, should have taken the kitty.
But you, what's wrong with you?
Most streamers beat this in 20 minutes.
The opening cut scene and tutorial is 20 minutes.
Nice try though.
Speedruns will be fun with this though.
People will break this.
They'll take a picture of something like three times
and crash it or something.
There's a lot of levels.
That third chapter had like 20 something levels.
22, 23.
The any% right now is 24 minutes.
Jeez, that seems hard.
You're gonna do bouncing duck sim?
Yeah, not tonight though.
I think we've been live for a decent amount of time.
I'll be live again on Monday
and Monday is an interesting day
because armored core is an option,
but so is bouncing duck simulator.
The U2's also launches on Monday.
Well, it's for sale on Monday.
I don't think it delivers for a month or two after that.
But bouncing duck looks, that was a poke recommendation.
I looked it up.
It looks pretty great.
So we'll figure it out tomorrow for a Monday.
And then later in the week after Monday,
probably on maybe Sunday, Friday, Sunday, I'll pick a day.
We'll get back into Sorcery part four.
Oh no, you guys are right.
I didn't, I didn't save Kate.
That's on me.
That's my bad.
Very cool.
I give it a very, very, very fun out of 10.
That was very good.
Very enjoyable.
Just the core gameplay mechanic alone is worth playing it.
That's, that's it.
Perfect timing, I guess.
People said this was a three hour game
and it was gonna take you six hours.
Yeah, but I feel like it,
even if I, even if you blow through every level,
I feel like it would take you more than three hours.
I did do the optional levels too.
Almost all of them,
which I'm sure that added at least 45 minutes to an hour.
Pretty average play time.
Yeah, and we also talk about ice cream
and ketchup and mustard combinations.
You always have to add the streamer one to two hour
of I'm walking in a circle and talking.
But yeah, I'll see you guys on Monday.
Gonna start with Bouncing Duck Simulator.
And after, I might just play that the whole day.
If I get over that or get bored of that,
it might be an attempt of Armored Core 6.
Either one of those two will be on Monday.
And then later in the weekend, we'll do Sorcery.
Thanks again.
See you soon.
Take care of yourselves.
Get some sleep.
Have a wonderful rest of your night.
Bye, even though mustard is dog shit.
Hey, we can have different opinions.
Yours is just wrong.
Thanks for coming though.
I'm a mustard Andy, okay?
That emote, how many emotes?
I just, why are these emotes even here?
Does anybody think German mustard is still funny
from like 2016?
That was, I don't know what to put for an emote slot.
And there are subscriptions on the channel.
I have to come up with something.
Guess this is what it is.
And then eight years went by
and I added one or two more emotes.
Honestly, I think the BTTV emotes just sort of took over.
It was just, if something was,
the mods was just added.
That way everybody can just use them.
Some of them I think deserve to be sub emotes,
but a lot of them just should be BTTV.
All right, see you Monday.
Take care.
Call your mother.
Drink some water.
Take care of yourself.
In what order?
Whatever order you are comfortable.
See you Monday.
Take care.