I am back. Let's change the game and the title of the stream to roller coaster. How about um
coast? I'm just kind of chill and play roller coaster. What's what's a good title?
Roller boffin? How about just rct2? Just roller coaster tycoon 2. Twitch integration? Unfortunately
twitch integration no longer exists. The server that was hosting it is no longer online. So the
only way you can do twitch integration unfortunately is I would have to open and run my own server on
my own computer with the uh it's no longer operational anymore. I have to make my own server
and that was going to take longer. I mean I was I wanted to start streaming so
so let me move over here yeah and there was other reasons why I didn't really want to do that
immediately. Like I'll just turn it on and run like a java server on my own computer.
I feel like there's some security holes there that I would need to make sure weren't there.
All right uh hold on I'm just gonna write roller coaster tycoon 2 on sale now. No
whatever it doesn't matter. Roller coaster tycoon 2 with germa.
That would be so bad. I can fix it later. We'll come up with a better
we'll we'll come up with a better one. All right let me get it open.
I mean we're talking like a true nostalgia factor right here. Don't ask me why it was
today was the day we were going to play this. But it is. Can you hear it? I bet you so badly
you guys want me to change the screen right now and listen to that. You remember that?
All right start a new park. Roller coaster tycoon 2. Nope never mind.
There it is. All right so what do I want to start with? My own park or should I gotta like
kind of remember how to play? How about crazy castle? Yeah this is open rct. Build your own
six flags adventure. Build your own six flags. Okay I okay you gotta I remember this stuff.
Build your own design a six flags park to build rides and other six flags parks are designed
and build your own. You have to have 1500 quests in your park at the end of October year four with
a park rating of at least 600. All right so there are some things that I remember that I played
this game a lot when I was younger. I played roller coaster tycoon 3. I think even on this stream or
on a video before. Admission price. What I typically do is I make the we I do it just like they do at
every six flags you've ever been to. The park admission is like 30 or 40 bucks. Like 20 bucks.
All the rides are free and then you just you just drain them at the concession stand. I'm not going
to charge for toilets. That would make me a monster. But we need stuff here first. Let's pause it.
How much money do I have? Okay remember I can remember the controls. You can you can spin it
around too can't you? So let's hold right click. Zoom in. Zoom out. I like the zoom in. It's fine.
Okay so we need this is I gotta name the park. What is it called? Where's my where's my name
the park thing here? I think I have to open it first. So I got a big open land. Let's do
let's just get everything laid out. Let's do like just dirt. Let's go dirt. Well it's already kind
of this the stone right? I mean I can't do it when the game is paused. Why not? Let's go up here. I'm
thinking a little little line this way. How much money do I have? Where's my total money? 9,700.
You got to start very slow. So I'm thinking hamburger stand hamburger stand ferris wheel
and then that's it and open it. Where are my rides? Where's my ride development? I know I have that
somewhere. His rides. I'm thinking the choo choo train. Slow. No no no no no no. Just hear me out.
I'm thinking the monorail around the entire park. Is it R to switch? No no no no stop.
You know what I mean? Have the monorail go all the way around the whole thing.
You'll get on this ride. It'll take like three hours. You can see everything. So let's go ahead
and get this made. I want to flip it this way. So to know actually it should be like this because
then I can have it be going all the way around. Let's go like this. Forward. Okay all right that
looks all right. Now let's go ahead and start building the track. Oh shit. I have to do the
doesn't this cost a lot of money? This is insanely expensive from what I remember.
How much is it gonna cost? 90 bucks? Oh for the love of god that's way too much money.
I'm just gonna cut it this way. I'm gonna use this as the edge here. All right can I cut it now?
Let's see. Let's go forward one right here. Okay let's see. Can I cut it? I think so.
Yep all right we're good. All right how much is this? 157 dollars per? No keep going up a
little more. No back it up. What's the point of a monorail? I don't think there is one.
No go back. Back up. I have to back this up. I turned it a little. No I didn't. That's all right.
All right it doesn't need to be exact. Just like it has to be close enough. This is a big park.
I don't think this is. I'm gonna run out of money before I do this. Okay uh let's go. Let's close it.
This is not a roller coaster. This is a road. This is just a you can ride around and view the park.
How many miles is this? Take out the loans? No no no all right. Well this will we'll keep this here.
I'm gonna build out this way first. This is a huge park. Big big big big park. It's okay.
This will work out. This is actually this is not bad because this will be my area to build.
I just need to go up. Oh yeah the monorail is sitting on the ground.
Yeah that's right. It is just on the ground. How are you gonna see everything?
This is the slow moving car on a track. It's all right. People will like it. The kids. This is for
the kids. The kids will love this shit. I was good. I was always so bad at trying to do this shit
because you got to match it up. Oh I can do better anyways.
All right so I'm gonna go like this. That's a good start. No monorail. I'm not doing the monorail.
It's like we're gonna start easy. We're gonna start with like the haunted the ferris wheel.
You start with the ferris wheel every time. Oh the maze. This one's fun. No no no. I need like an
information center first. Okay we've got funnel cakes, hot dog stall. Where's like the info center
and balloons? Yeah bathroom. Not yet. Let's put ATMs. These are important here. ATM here.
Go ahead and open it. Okay let's get another ATM. Let's go ahead and open it. Is it already open?
They both opened. Good. All right. It's off center. It's fine. I can. It doesn't matter. It's
un- why? Why is there no music? Yeah this is supposed to be music in this game.
What's going on? Guess can't get to the entrance of cash machine one. Yeah the park's not open.
I don't understand. What are they? What are they? How do you move shit around?
Can I not pick it up? Spin it this way. It's because the thing the lip wasn't there. All right.
All right so let's open them up. To uh now we're gonna have a small ride here.
I want and um should I do food? Yeah let's do burgers. Burger food right at the entrance.
No I'm not gonna rebuild the monorail. I turned that turned into a disaster.
Food right at the entrance. I bought anytime that I go to a place like a Six Flags. I always want
food right at the front door. We're going here. Right at the front door. Burger price. Make it
same throughout the park. Profit per item. It's gonna be a dollar sixty. Remember this is like
1994 prices. So you're probably like what the fuck dude? What are you talking about man? It's
like should be six. No dollar sixty. This is like back in like the fucking 30s. Let's get uh now
we let's get two burgers. No we got a variety. Put on the Animal Crossing OST. You got it.
How do I like pause this? Animal Crossing soundtrack collection. Complete edition.
All right get comfortable because this is going to be a real snooze. That's not a way you should
describe your live stream. There we are. Just sit in the background. Get under the covers you know.
Wait isn't it like four o'clock in the afternoon? All right go to bed if you're like 78. Okay here
we go. So we got the burger stand. Let's go with a french fries right next to it. What do you say?
The game's paused. How much are the french fries? Same price throughout the park. Let's make them
uh let's make them a dollar forty. Make them a little cheaper. So we got burgers fries. What
the hell else are we gonna do here? How about a pretzels stall? Yeah that's a good snack.
Pretzels would be a little cheaper. A lot of people. We got a lot of foot traffic here.
Make them 90 cents. Okay let's uh I think we need drinks too. How could we forget lemonade?
Uh lemonade price. Dollar 20. Make it the same throughout the park. Dollar 40. What I should do
is I should make I should have no drinks and to scream on a big intercom. Hold a cup outside.
It's free. We'll do a soda as well. Is this spongebob music or is this?
No no that's too clustered too clustered. I don't want to do that. We need a ride.
We're doing a nice relaxing easy ride. We're doing an intro ferris wheel right here.
The line doesn't have to be very long although these ones always have a ton of people that
care about them for some dumb reason. This is the entrance right and here's the exit. All right
so uh ferris wheel. Okay no forward rotation. Number of rotations. One. Reliability. Inspection
time. Every 30 minutes is fine. I want it to be uh we got to be a central theme here. Ice. No.
Space. No. Plane. What's wrong with one rotation? It goes around once. It takes like 25 minutes.
The theme should be pretzel. I don't think I can do a pretzel theme. Gravy? No that's castle. How
am I going to do pretzel themed? I mean the log cabin should all right let's we're doing this is
a pretzel park. Log cabin. That's all right that's fine. It's really it's very ugly but it's okay.
Okay admission price it's free or should it be like five cents? No. Okay that's fine. It is now
ready to test. I need to get a queue in there. Just go with the standard queue. That's fine.
And then I don't I'm one of those people that doesn't like to have the queue be I like having
a clean exit not the queue exit. Am I charging? Only am. Charge for admission. All right so far
so good. Two bathrooms. No those are ATMs. That'll be tested to be ready to go. I need staff too
right? Yeah. I need a handyman. No I don't. Not yet. One mechanic. One. Okay I need the entertainer.
Those are important to have like just sitting right here. Where do you go? All right you go here.
Is it knight? Roman costume. No no no no no no. Astronaut. 55 dollars a month. That's
all right that's really really really low. I want you to be in this area here. Do not go anywhere
else. Just stay at the front door. Thank you. That's his path. I'm walking around. All right
I need to now should I open the park with one ride? I have to start making money. We have an
astronaut, a ferris wheel, and food. Okay should I make the park like a dollar? This is not even
worth going to. Five dollars. No it's no no no not yet. No no no no it's not. I gotta make two more
rides. I'm not gonna get. No no no no not gonna happen. Here we go. This one. Oh I love this one.
Custom design. No no no no no no no. This is a lot of money. Uh no I can do. I'm gonna do custom
design here. We're going over here. One two three. That's fine. Let's get it started. I'm gonna go up
with a chain. Can it can it even do it? Special. Station platform spinning tunnel. Oh yeah that's
look at this. This is like some cartoon shit here. Okay station platform. No I don't need that. I
don't want to be that long. I'm gonna go spin up and then come back around. Why is this a puke ride?
No it's not. I'm making it very easy. Uh is that as high as it can go? Not just a circle. Pog
champ. What's going on? New ride attraction. Steel twister. You got it. What is this design?
This is interesting. What a way to describe it. It's very interesting isn't it? Let's get this
back to ground level. You fucking nailed it. Let's test it out. Test. How many cars? No this. No no
no no. I want to test this. All right. Test. Can't test car ride entrance. Not yet built. Oh get out
of here. Entrance is right here. Exit's gonna wrap. It's gonna be a very popular ride so the
exit's gonna be this way. Okay test it. That's a lot of cars. Nice. Then you get like all it gets
all spooky in here. Why is this so slow? This is too slow. There's no draw. That's supposed to be
a drop. Sports car. Vintage car. No make it cats. Continuous circuit. Wait for a full load. Don't
wait for a full load. All right main color scheme. Let's go. Let's see what do I want to do. All right
let's make this like... I don't like the red. That's not bad. Oh it's gonna be pretzel related
right? I'm gonna step in and say I'm not doing that. I'll be able to just say different colors
per car. Car one. No no no. Um car 20. No no no no no no no. Different color. Same. All the cars
the same color. Make it looks like blue. Nice. Okay. Play music. How much? Five miles per hour.
The admission price is free. All right so now we got that there. I gotta get I gotta add some
some some lush vegetation. How many how many how do we get rid of the cars? No no no no yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah okay this this ride is fine. Close the ride. I don't know five cars? Two? Three. Five.
One two three four. I'm gonna say seven. I'm gonna say eight. Let's test that one out. That's better.
Can I make it faster? I can't make it faster. All right so that's ready. Why is my park for babies?
Do you see how much space I have here? I need money before I I only have 5,400 bucks. You have
the cheap cheesy rides at the front and then like the real daredevils have to go around back here.
You don't want to have your kids walking all around if you got them in like strollers and stuff. No
you have all this stuff really close to the food to the the atm's and the bathrooms. Don't you
understand? All right so that one's good. Let's get a cue on it. Okay that's that. Get that fresh
cobblestone. All right I need some decorations because I hate this. What are those trees?
These are ugly. I need like a little garden over here. Hold on. No hold on. I need a garden. I need
a little garden. That's what I need. Close this. Get this over here. Make a little circle here so
people can walk into the garden. Right there's gonna be a couple of like a little thing here.
There's gonna be a little thing there. No that's fine. Maybe put like a shop right there. Let's
get some. Let's do that first. Get a thing here. How about a funnel cake shop right here. Right
around the corner. No right here. It's all 50. And then let's get some vegetation here.
Let's go with um people like fountains and statues and stuff right. A couple of walls.
That's nice. And then we'll do some you know just some of this shit. That looks that looks pretty.
It does. I got the dinosaur. Funnel cake shop. And we'll uh yeah benches.
That's under here. Uh benches. There's little benches here. Right there. Perfect. All right.
How are they gonna? What do you mean? How they sit? Oh the wall. That's for me. I'm just flying
around in my fucking helicopter. That's for me. Actually let me get some seating here. Seating
in front of the ATM. You gotta have seats and trash cans too. Next to all the food stalls. I
remember that was very important in this video game. Trash. Trash. Trash. Have a place to throw
you trash. All right. It's coming together pretty well. I think. This is a fun little ride. I got
my little secret like garden area. Let's get a tree over here. I don't like a couple of trees.
No I don't like those. I need some. I want bushes. Little ones. No don't like that either.
Don't need. I don't need anything over there. No I can put stores and stuff. Don't need it.
All right. So I got two rides. Here comes a good. Here comes a wild ride. All right. We're gonna do
something fun. I'm thinking the go-karts. Castle carts. I mean this one's cool. Yeah.
Automobile antics. Vehicle design unavailable. What do you mean unavailable? Do these go fast?
No. I already have a cart right there. I'm not doing another cart ride.
We'll do the pirate ship. Everybody hates this. Give us the monorail. I don't have enough money
to make that. What am I spending money on? Money's being deleted. This is. I'll put this right here.
Yeah. You want to talk about park design? Oh shit. It's the wrong way. How do I flip it? How do I
flip? I can't. I can get up there right? Usually can't you just put your cursor and it does it
right in front? It's an oil drill. Oh okay. There we go. Damn it. It's okay. It's all right. I remember
everyone was saying this is uneven. Now I can be fixed. Uneven German. Uneven German. Right. That's
what I'm saying. So now I can fix this. Okay. So that's done. Let's go up from here. It's this
little one here. Bang. Bang. Bingo. Now that's going to be cool. Now I'm into that. All right.
So that's that. Let's spin it back around. Let's take a look at pirate ships. Swinging inverted
ship. That's all I can do. Number of swings. Swing mode. All right. Number of swings.
Two. One. Eight. Let's increase our productivity by like 10,000 percent. Durability. All right. I want
to do. Let's do. It's kind of part of this ride in a way. Let me see what this looks like.
No. We got to do some like some actual color coordination here. This is cool. And then these
people drive down and they'll see it. And it'll be like whoa. It's like going over your head.
I need one more ride and then I'm going to open the park. Has this guy got any water? It's been
like four days. Okay. Let's go over here. Final ride that I'm going to make is going to be a
coaster. And it's got to be a little shitty one because I don't have enough money.
See like from 2500. Spiral. How much does this one cost? Seven thousand. Seventy two. Eleven
thousand. Why didn't I get one of these? Look at how awesome that is. I don't have enough money.
Now I need to make money first then. I'm ready to open the park. I need a. How's research doing?
Take out a loan? No. That's not how you win. I need a bathroom. Let's put bathrooms. I wish I
could do it here. In fact let's do this. Let's fix this. There we go. Is that one? One more. Nice.
All right. It is time to open the park. Welcome. Except wait. Give me a janitor and an engineer.
Okay. Come on in everybody. It's only eight dollars. Welcome to Six Flags. Six Flags. How
do I change the name? Why isn't it over here? Here we go. First customer. Carl S. Oh Carl S.
Welcome to the Big Top. I don't know. The Big Top Circus and Resort. Got it. What do you mean boo?
What's wrong with the Big Top? All right. Where are they going? People getting in line? What's
wrong? Recent thoughts. Where are you going? Somebody. Look at they're going. Already going
to the garden. They love it. Is this person leaving? I don't want to go on something more.
I want to go on something more thrilling than the ferris wheel. We'll get on the this one.
That's what this is for. Is everybody on these rides? No they're not. They're not testing.
They're all open. Oh the pressure is starting to mount here. I'm not hungry. The in-game music.
All right. I'll turn it off. There we go. I need to name this something. The the oopsie daisy. This
one is just ferris wheel. F wheel. This one's called. This one's called Bumperda Bumper. And
I think that's it. They're getting in line. Look. They're already riding the car. There they are.
They're so happy to be here. How much money do I have? 33,000. Nobody's in there. No thoughts on
the funnel cakes. Where are people going? I'm not thirsty. I'm not hungry. I'm tired. What would
mean I'm tired? Why are you here? I want to go something more thrilling than Bumperda Bumper.
I want to go on something more thrilling than F wheel. I'm not thirsty. I'm tired.
These are easy. Motion simulator. Film. Avenging aviators. Thrill riders.
Okay. That's fine. No music. All right. Let's go. Open it up. Open. I don't need to test it.
Open. Let's get it over there. That's thrilling. What are they saying? I'm not hungry. I'm not
hungry. We'll get in line. This is VR. Okay. They're just walking around and not finally.
There's people getting in line for this. New vehicle available for Steel Twister. Floorless
Twister train. I need more money. It's like 50 bucks. Oh, they line it up. They actually like
this one. Look at it. It's the first line that actually has a line. Uh-oh. Oh, shit. I have to
make this longer. I'm going to charge more money. 12 bucks to get them. Oh, there we go. People
starting to fill in here. 81 people here. I told you this was going to be a good idea.
This is not that cool though. Has anybody been buying these? Zero per hour. Burger sold zero.
Why? Is there a reason why? Too expensive? $1.40. $1.20. I mean, people have to start buying these.
90 cents. It's fine. $1.20. What are you doing? All right. What's popular right now? I've got
2,800 bucks. Don't they usually say, oh, this park is a big value? The park is really clean.
I want something more thrilling. On Oopsy-Daisy, queuing for VR sim, walking, queuing for Oopsy-Daisy.
People really love the Oopsy-Daisy. I should make two of these. Yeah, I'm just going to make two
of them back to back. Making sense portraits. Turn this way maybe. I think I can still do it. If I
go like this and then like that and then can I turn it this way? Damn it. I can't just go that
way with this. Wait, I can go that way. That's not going to do it. I don't think that's going to work
though. Pulse there. Okay, hold on. Done. All right. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. Now this is actually kind of damn cool. I will say for myself. Now just hold on a minute
here. Look at this. Look at what I've done. Look at what I'm capable of, mom. Now check this out.
Now we've got to connect this in a very, very convincing way. So I'm going to say we can go
we gotta go around here and this is going to take us to the next part of the park.
Yep, nothing goes upside down. Okay, now just open it. Test it and open it. Try to make a third one.
Should I make four of these just back to back to back right here? They can't hit each other,
right? This one's going to swing for less time. Okay, let's do the same color scheme.
Looking good. So open it. That's fine. There it is. What was this called? Oopsie daisy.
Oopsie daisy. They gotta have a similar name because they're right next to each other.
Um whoopsie daisy and whoops uh whoopsie did whoopsie oopsie daisy and whoopsie daisy.
Whatever. All right, that's done. Now that's kind of cool.
That's an attraction if I've ever seen one before and this one can hold way more people than this
one. See this is what they don't understand. This ride is faster than this one. This one's
longer with a shorter line. This one's faster with a longer line. Now I got 2,300 bucks.
What do I want to do now with this? I want to go out here. I got 191 people here. I need to
charge more money because I'm not making anything. 15. Turn down the crowd volume. Is it too loud?
This is really starting to fill up. Everyone's realizing what's going on here. All right.
Uh do I have enough to do anything? I need like a coaster or uh I don't have enough money. I need
like a little one. Mini roller coaster. Here we go. Crazy crabs. 5,000. What if I do I need to
save this because I'm going to try to just do one that goes up down really hard and then rips around
his ends. Uh let's save it as auto save. I guess it's just auto saving. That's all right.
All right it's auto saving. Look at how fucking huge this line is. All right here's the diabolical
plan. Are you ready? Number of swings. Oh I was gonna make it like five. Oh the the crowd's
getting is drowning out the actual music. I see what you're saying. I'm starting to get a profit now.
Is the burger stand closed? Yeah. It's one of the fry stalls. Whatever. It's okay. I want to make a
roller coaster. I can do it. Here we go. Mini coaster. I'm gonna do my own and it's gonna be
over here. Back here it's gonna start. It's gonna be a small one but it's gonna be crazy. That's
enough to go up and then down right? What if I just do one car? I can delete this. I can sell it later.
No I need one now. Three. All right. Okay here we go. Here we go. That's that's fine.
I'm gonna go up with the chain. I'm watching my money closely here. Does this have a chain on it?
No it doesn't. Back it up. Back it up. Wait back it up. Okay that's it. That's it. That's it. No more.
Let's turn. A big turn. How much money? 1,900. I gotta close it now. All right then straight down.
1,500. I got it. I got it. I got it. I'm just making Mario's circuit from Mario Kart Super Nintendo
Edition. Got it. Done. Okay I got that. Now this is gonna be good. What would I just get? Oh shit.
I need. Wait wait wait. Quick. How do I make umbrellas? Umbrellas umbrellas umbrellas. Umbrellas.
Where do I get them? Hat stall. Umbrellas. Buy one. It's not open. What is obscene? I'm not sure.
What's obscene? 10 bucks. I'm making it all back. Can you imagine going to a park and it starts to
rain and you're walking by a stall which there's a little ticker but by the second the price of the
of the umbrella is increasing. All right let's go back down. Back down. Back down. It's fine.
Hi. The person in front of you. Hi I'd like to buy an umbrella. That'll be 14 dollars please.
No it's my turn. I'd like to buy an umbrella. That'll be 18 dollars please. Get out of here.
All right I just made a shitload of money. Let's go back to like six. Seven. Six fifty. It is now.
This is a better park. Let's increase the price to about 25. Hell yeah. All right let's go up here
and test this coaster. Test it. What's it look like? What's it like? It's just a little one.
It's just a little guy with three. See how much how crazy this is.
Lift hill chain speed faster than that. Let's take a look. Why is it not showing? That's pretty cool.
10 miles per hour. Is it talking this one right now? I don't understand. How fast does it go?
I mean this thing goes 45 miles per hour. This thing almost goes 50. All right that's fine. Wait.
Excitement rating medium. Intensity medium. Medium. You don't want it to be too crazy.
Okay leave maximum wait time 10 seconds. I think it's free. What about the car? I want to change
the colors here. Can I? Yeah. That's ugly. Hold on. That's very ugly. There we go. Now I'm ready to
open it. Let's go. I feel like there's going to be a line for this one. So we're going to do a little
bit of an interesting squiggle here. Welcome to the ride. I'm going to call this one whatever the
name of that level is. Look at that. They're already flooding in. This is perfect. They're already
just getting in there piling in. I told you this had to be done like this. This is going to fill
up real quick. Look at them going to the ATM. 35 bucks to get in. Let's take a look. How are we
doing? I'm not hungry. This park is really clean. I want to go something more thrilling though. I
just got that. More thrilling. It's already here. I feel sick. Why? Where is this person?
I feel sick. Heading to bumper to bumper. This thing is so popular. Luigi's Circuit was great.
Yes it was. Wasn't it? Why is that me hungry? I have a general. Are these selling? Okay it's yeah
five burgers have been sold. Why? Let's go this way with the park. What's wrong with you?
This is going to be an impossible ride to fill up. All right what have I got?
4,000. I'm turning a profit. I'm going to say we should do something else like a little
what's the word for research? Vertical shuttle cars. No I don't want to do that. I want to focus on
no shops and sceneries. No water rides. No gentle rides. Thrill rides and roller coasters and shops.
Marketing campaign. We're going to do a marketing campaign for a ride. I need another one of these.
They're getting too full. Is this going to work? This is going to crash into each other.
Give the people what they want. You know I agree. Which way do you have to be facing?
All right this is look if they want to ride it. Look at how big of a line this is. It's ridiculous.
All right I need this. VR sim. What's wrong with it? No. There's like puke all over the place.
78 people are in this line and you guys didn't want me to do this?
All right let's go. I need to connect it. I'll put some benches in it. Maybe a store right here.
Fire chip. Seven. Let's get it the right color scheme. Who's trapped? All right I need another
janitor. 4,400 bucks. I'm doing great. Who's trapped? Who's trapped? Where? I want to go home.
Who? You can find your way out of here. Look at uh people. I can't keep these lines empty.
It's because I separated the roads. Yeah they're. Wait a minute. Is this fucked up? Hold on. Wait
wait. I didn't want it like this. There we go. Everyone's fine. Where is it? Where is it? All
right. I need a janitor. I need a new janitor. Another janitor. Somewhere. We're gonna. I'm
gonna have to have you patrol over here because it's dirty. It's fucking dirty over here. You need
to be like around here. This area. That's where you go. Still raining. I need more barrels too.
Just keep it at 20. What if somebody wants to buy one though? Like randomly just to buy one.
They're not going to confirm buy one unless there's a reason. 10,000 dollars an hour.
Wouldn't that be nice? Look at how popular this one is. What's wrong with this? Why is
nobody on the line for this one? What's going on here? What's wrong? Nobody want to ride this one?
I'm not going on pirate ship one while it's raining. Okay I get my pirate ship one. Excuse me.
Luigi's circuit has broken down. How? Wait. Are the people still on it? What? I need an engineer.
Why are the people still riding this? There he comes. All right good. I need one more uh one more
engineer and a security guard. Okay and barrels and more shops. Yeah I need more shops. I need
more benches. Let's get some more stores. I need I want a fountain. A giant ice cube. Uh yeah like
right here. Look cool. That's kind of cool. That's cool just to look at. Um wait a minute.
This is too this is too cramped. I don't like it. I don't like it. It's too cramped. I don't
can I get rid of it? I don't think I can get rid of it. Does it cost money to look at the ice cube?
You have to crap my pants at the amusement park. Okay there it goes. I now have enough money to
make another coaster and the next coaster is going to cross across this one. You know what I'm saying?
This one's going to be fucked. Reverse freefall coaster. Check this out. Yep. How much is this?
4,000? 3,900? Now this is going to be that's pretty. Poster inside of the coaster.
That doesn't crash right? Okay yeah it's fine. All right we gotta change the what's with the
red platform. Okay reverse freefall car. Full load. All right you can't do anything else.
That looks good. I wish I could change the color of that. Can I? Let's give it a test. Nice. All right.
Put more speed on it. I don't think I can. No it's already very intense. This thing goes up to 70
miles per hour. Make it taller. That's too high. That's way too high. Is that too much? That's like
a test of strength. It doesn't even go up halfway. How do I make it go faster? I need to increase the
power? How do I do that? Close it. Like this thing back here? It gains speed from the straight track
pieces. It's the gear tab of the ride. Yeah but I was just. No it's not. No I can't do that.
Do you want to refurbish horse mine? No. That's not there. The other gear? Yeah is it in here?
I think I have to make more of these sections. So I need to go like this then. I should have
just made this myself. What a waste of money. Better? Let's try it. No. It's gonna have to do.
Let me take it down one two three. Now that's a real scary ride. I want it to be like you're
just about to go over it and like fly off the ride. Just barely one more. Make it like
holy shit it's going over the thing. Yeah I think that's a good idea. Let's see if it works. The
name of this ride is going to be called just barely. Oh just barely. Just barely. Any more
force and you're off. Bumper to bumper broke down? What is it? What even is bumper to bumper? Oh the
thing underneath this mess. How does this break down? Now this thing's ready to go. Okay let's get
that car. Cool. The color scheme's gotta be different. This is gonna be orange. Orange
cars to make a match with this. This track is wrong. That's better. Actually I kind of like
the orange. I like the orange. Yeah it works with this. Cool. What's the intensity by the way? Good
for rating. Very high. Yeah good luck on that one. You want intense? I'll give you intense.
All right I think I need to. That's better. This is getting a little loud. I think it's ready to
open as we make the kiosks. Wait how the hell do you get up and down and out of here?
Make stairs go on to here? The path in the back. Oh okay I see. This one. Ah it's the face of the
bumper. Because you go in here and go that's the line. All right so then I fucked this up it's okay.
Okay now I'm going to connect this. The VR sim has broken down like three times.
This needs to be connected over here so we're going to build out. I think I want to go
from here. Yeah let's build out from there. I'm gonna make this a double sidewalk. Triple sidewalk
because this is ugly. This is very very very ugly. What have I just done? What'd I do? What'd I do?
What'd I do? What'd I do? Oh okay well please replace that. All right so that's ugly. Let's
go up this way with it. I know everyone's gonna freak out. I got it. One two three four five six
seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen. Therefore seven. One two three four
five six. Seven is the middle. One two three four five six seven. One two three four five six seven.
One two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen. One two
three four five six seven. One two three four five six seven. Got it. I'm gonna have like a big display
here. That's gonna be another section of the park over this way and over here. You can find it. Get back
over here. You know what are you doing? You can't be that stupid. Open it. There we go. I gotta put
some distraction. How much money do I have? Make this more expensive. Forty dollars to get in this
fucking park. We have to see what they think. Already getting loaded up. Is it too intense?
No people are getting on. I caught that sneeze. Just barely. It's too intense. Just looking at
just barely makes me feel sick. People are getting on. Here we go. Whoa that was intense.
I need the bark bags out here. Click on the main gates. What about it? Park rating. Look at this
park rating. People love this place. All right looking good. Now I need to get some money. I
have to make money. Let's increase some scenery over here because this looks terrible. Fences.
Let's get a fence. Let's do this fence. This is a big fence. Looks good to me.
And then I'm gonna put. Let's close off this area. Roto drop is now available. Let's go. Let's make
like a little nice garden for people to puke on. Put on the new leaf soundtrack in due time.
Okay that looks all right. Now let's get some bushes and trees and bushes.
Maybe let's just do flowers. I'm just gonna do purple. Yeah watch this. Groups of three. One two three.
And then I'm gonna do space space. Yes space space and then three spaces. Yellow I guess.
I'm gonna do the same thing. Space space and then space right there. We're gonna go. All right now
I'm gonna do. Um how do these look? These are like evil. I don't want those. Uh how about
how about these? No bushes. There we are. That's what I want. I want these fluffy ones.
No I want like a tree. There we go. These. That's what I'm that's what I was looking for.
Okay now I'm gonna do the same thing over here. I'm gonna add a couple things in here though.
I fucked it up. Wrong. What do you mean wrong? I fucked it up. Wrong wrong wrong. How is it wrong?
Space space. Oh right. Okay hold on. Let me. I'm gonna change it up though. Let's change it up.
Let's do red and let's do pink and um let's do pink and red. Let's do pink over here. I don't know.
Keep it symmetrical. Didn't people scream in my face when I did symmetrical?
Just barely broke down. Lined up to do this. What do you mean it broke down? Where? I had people
screaming in my face because I was doing a symmetrical garden and now all of a sudden
you want a symmetrical garden? One two three one two. What is this? Is that a corona trigger?
Space space space. Nice. That's. See now I did it. I don't like the way this looks though.
What's going on here? What happened? Why? This looks completely wrong.
Oh it's because they're in the middle. They're in the middle. Okay. Now we're gonna do a little
thing in the middle I think is what I want to do. Just a little thing. Small. A duck in one of them?
Yeah. The duck at the end. Two ducks. Double no. Double duck through the whole thing. That looks
great. I like it. All right. That makes it look a little better I think. Maybe we should have like
a statue or something. Double wall. Is this Abe Lincoln? Who's this? What is that? Oh it's Egyptian.
Bump it a bump. It broke down. All right. Do I have enough money? I only have $522. How did
that happen? Where did my money go? New benches. People can enjoy sitting around here and that's
we're gonna put some soda machine over here. I think that works. Ice cold drinks. Ice cold
pretzels. What are you doing? If they take a double water fountain I'll just sell these and
put them over here. Now I need like a I need ice cold first aid. There's my information center.
How much are these? All right. Where's this? This is the drinks. Hot dog. Chicken. There it is.
The park has received an award for being the safest park in the country.
Oh it's it's slider.
You know KK Slaughter to me is what I would think it would sound like if a bug sang.
Imagine you just heard this muffled through the wall and you went in there was like a
beetle just swaying back and forth. That's what I picture. Drinks and we'll do food over here.
Hot dogs. Yeah hot dogs and just a couple of drinks.
KK Slaughter's been the most modern pop music. Oh shit a bug. So uh chicken too. I'm gonna go
let me I need a first aid room. I really do. Should I put it though? I don't I don't like
this the symmetry over here. First aid should probably be on the in front of the rides of the
most dangerous. What do you guys think? Yeah let's put it over here. First is first aid free? I guess
yeah. It's just available in case somebody pukes. Imagine going to a roller coaster and right outside
the entrance is a medical tent. Yeah that's actually pretty scary. F wheels broken down.
Uh oh. Is it time to liquidate this thing? This is not even the right color scheme.
What am I thinking? All right I wanted the fountains over here. Can I get it? Can I pick it up?
No it's just it's in a weird spot. Why did I put these here? Got it all right. Can I get the other
one? I'm pretty slick. People really like the ice cube. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Put more benches here. What an attraction. Everybody was supposed to sit in front of the ice
cube. All right look it. You got at least two, four, five, six people here. Should I do a second cube?
Why not? That's 25 bucks. All right I wanted to put fountains here. Here and here maybe.
The tornado is a little distracting. Oh I like that. That's nice. What could this go?
That's actually I kind of I like it.
Didn't go all the way. Oops. No my garden. No that's fine. What's this bug?
Volcano? We're gonna have some cool. We have to have things that they go by, right? What are these?
Are these fireworks? Okay. I need to stop spending money. Put on some music. Okay.
Which I put on. I need some rain. I know. Come on. When's it gonna rain? Mario 3D world.
3D world. Don't I hate this game? Which is the one that I don't like? Mario. Super Mario 3D world LST.
Oh this is bopping. Okay so how are we doing? Let's take a look at the. Let's get a good view
of what's going on here. I've been queuing for Luigi's Circuit for ages. I need more cars.
I gotta. I need more cars. I gotta close this down because people look. Look at this. Everyone hates
this. I need to go to the bathroom. What do you mean? This bathroom? That's 10 cents right? I have
to go to the bathroom. I have to go to the bathroom. Uh I guess I'm gonna make some more bathrooms.
Are they just standing in line? That's their problem? I'm not hungry. I've already got a cuddly toy.
This park is really clean. I'm not thirsty. Whoops daisy. Whoops daisy was great.
Okay so Luigi's Circuit is taking too long. I'm gonna make the. I'm sorry. I have to do this.
It's gonna be bad but I have to do it. Ladies and gentlemen Luigi's Circuit is now closed
for maintenance. I'm gonna add a couple of cars here. Bingo. Six cars. How long is the ride?
Max leave if another train arrives at the station. Wait for. Okay I think we're good. We've got more
cars. I think that's good. I think it's good to go. Open it up. It's back open. We've got three
extra cars. What do you mean music? This is uh guys this is. What song is this? I don't know.
This isn't even closed. What? I don't know what this is. This is called Super Mario World OST Extended.
How about Beat Block Skyway? That's next in line. It's the same song. Hold on. Wait what's wrong?
Why people not going on the ride? Is this going faster? What's going on? People don't want to
get on this ride anymore. Why not? I don't. Why you guys think I know what like a porn song is?
It's Mario 3D World. What are you talking about? Okay um what's what is a what's a what's a
relaxing one? Stardew? How about Dune? That sounds pretty good. Okay uh I want to build another
coaster but I don't have any money. Should I make a fourth one of these? No. No one's even riding it.
There we go. Now let people in line. Take out a loan. I hate doing that. I really hate taking out
loans. Um I'm actually I'm in I'm not in the red loan. I can't. I gotta wait. This is freaking
me out. I don't want something. I'm putting on fucking Mario RPG. There we go. Guests are
complaining about the disgusting state of the park. What are you talking about? Where? I don't know
what you mean by that. Okay now I want to put the game sounds back up a little because I like to
hear like a little. That's a nice level. People are not shitting. All right there's plenty of
bathrooms. I need another janitor. Oh it's this. All right what did not there's a janitor that's
doing this isn't there? Where are you? Who's the one that has the path? It's you. What's your path?
Oh well add this to your path.
This game is so good. If the guy doesn't have a path. Yeah he can just wander. All right you take
care of that like the front end here. Are you still just what does that egg mean? Walking to egg?
Oh no no no he's an astronaut. Right okay. I think it's time to change to a panda.
It looks good. There we go. Clean it up. Make it look nicer. Would I ever stream it? I've
I've beat this game probably like 40 times. I don't know if I'd be able to add very much
but I have we've talked about before. Who cares? Just kind of do it. All right. All right well hold
on. I need to do it. I need some. I got 2400 bucks. Can I fast forward time? You can do this?
Try to just do this really fast and until I can build a new coaster? Because I want to build a
giant one. It's time for the monorail. I think it's time. Can you imagine? I was going to go
around this whole thing with the monorail. It's time. Monorail. Or how about a choo-choo train?
Elevator? It's got to be back. The path. There's going to be a path that leads down here
to somewhere over here. And we go around this whole thing. I don't have to finish the whole
thing right now. Yeah this is the best soundtrack for any Mario game. Well I will hold that up.
Track to track to any Mario game you've ever played. All right let's go back here. Now let's
go up. Up, up, up, up, up. Up, up, up, up. Good. Wait. Okay. So they get a good view.
No that's not necessary. Just go around the whole thing. Here's the intro. Go around. I'm
almost out of money. I don't have to finish it yet. I can wait. It's just this is like I'm
making like a prison. Fuck negative 44. What do I do? Delete? No I'm gonna wait. Just wait.
There we go. Okay positive again. This is gonna be cool. Ready? Watch this.
Don't pack it up. Really? Come on. I thought I could do this. I gotta go back. It's gotta go
across this way. Is that too low? That's not too low right? Is that too low? That's not too low?
Oh it's if you stand up.
Okay it's fine. It's not too low. We're good. Straight ahead. I might have to change that a
little. No. Ugly. Ugly. Is it where Toad explains you how to play the game? Tutorial Toad comes in.
Damn it. Do a Toad impression. Got it. Monorail is done. Retro style. Yeah. No that's ugly. Four
trains. Five cars per train. What does that mean? Continuous shuttle mode? What a shuttle mode.
Reliability. All right. This is we gotta change this. This is gonna be orange. We got too much
blue. Like orange. We're gonna make this like a little like a gray. No. That's better. Less
assuming. Station style wood. No. Something something new. Something something daring.
There we go. Pretzels. All vehicles of the same color. We're gonna make these orange and
oh what what who crashed why did it crash four people died how what happened wait hold on
don't get 20 never mind is it fine did somebody come over here what do you need clothes somebody
get away where is somebody to fix this i'm not going on wait wait wait wait wait what's happening
here i've been queued for luigi's it's too crowded here this really is i don't know what it is man
but i really i keep seeing the the orange crest toothpaste they don't make it anymore and i wish
they did you know the orange shower clean toothpaste i loved that stuff bumper to bumper
is broken down somebody fix it where are you off to answering radio call responding to bumper to
bumper no no no no no why are you not fixing this right i love that orange toothpaste it
it was a gimmick it was a marketing bunch of dog shit but seriously that they made this thing was
like a shower for your mouth and it was super sudsy super bubbly i i what's wrong with this one
oh this is all right i didn't let me just do this um i need these i gotta open the monorail
while there's still time just barely broke down too what's with are they all queued up to break
down at the same time i need not i need more engineers i need like two i need i need another
i have to have one all right this is nice and done let's get this out here i'm gonna actually
extend this from the secret garden this way never mind i can't uh i need how am i gonna over this
way right through here because you gotta be able to access the monorail at the beginning of the
park there there we go all right don't remove the supports it's fine so now let's monorail
i need to rename these all right look at that like will there be a line at the monorail
i don't think i should i look a big snake this could it always works out this way these stupid
things are the most popular rides in the whole park open it open for business there it is no
that's slow it's gonna be a long ride don't go too fast you're gonna bump into each other
the toothpaste express there we go nice see oh i can't wait to ride the monorail
are these both this is still closed are they both just
not operational though why is this one still closed luigi's circuit open it the person did
even fix it all right it works open for business come to the monorail all of you
um
who cares it's back to normal how come nobody can ride it down time why are they not getting on the
ride moving to end of station moving to end of station guests are complaining about the amount
of trash in your park what's going on moving to end of station what's going on here oh there
we go i need to have uh i need to i've gotta expand we can put something right here i've got
4,400 bucks i'm thinking of an expansion of a not a roller coaster but it's just a thrill ride
one of these eye poppers on the line to the no no this is too clustered a little boss fight
water ride what if i don't okay wait this is the one this would be fun yeah this would be fun all
right check this out uh right in here make a little just raft area station platform i'm
gonna say like this it's not water check this building a water ride on grass this ride sucks
no this is stupid this is dumb no this one this is not a fun ride it's stupid
river wraps rat river rapids splash boat there we are this has to be on uh i wonder if it has
to be here does it have to be on water let's do uh s bend no no let's pull it all the way across
yes bend i can't construct too high what do you mean what are you talking about it's too high
i'll watch this this is not porn music here it comes oh i need a i need a photo thing here
right here photo section bang drop it down ah seriously like why do they have to be so huge
number roller coaster tycoon 3 where it is auto completed for you i have to go up let's do it
twice do i got the money is that lined up i think that's lined up oh shit oh got it and yeah i have
to build all right the entrance and exit this could work though no this could work this can work
this will work i just have to do something really really really really weird
um i think it's still i think it's possible what hold on why are there so many cards
okay let's start building this out higher finally jesus i don't even want money
how are people gonna ride this they're gonna get on it and ride this ride look
this takes way too long i should have just gone up and then down damn it okay here it goes
boom nice and they get the picture taken and they get to go down one more
now here's the real issue trying to get this to work
i'm trying to do a staircase it's all right it still works done no that's it all right
that doesn't matter i can build this out here just wait you'll see what i'm talking about here
i gotta build all the homos section this is when they're introducing the character of gino
gino is a doll it is a little boy in one of the towns it's one of his favorite toy mario and this
little boy have a little stay like a little standoff where they pretend to fight each other with the
toys guests are complaining about the amount of trash okay there we are that's fine okay so now
this is connected also needs to connect to here all right it's ready how does it look it's all
right take that i need to take 15 boats down though maybe no i don't think i no i don't
okay i can change the color of the water that is actually i like it it's gold unassuming
that's the luigi circuit you suck all right uh it's pretty good ready to go open open for
business wait for the monorail i thought it was broken i guess it was what a mess should i just
scrap this thing and make something else how many more janitors do i need uh people like this right
yeah no not really you know when you're not when you're not filling the whole stadium there's a
problem where those janitors get over here you just stay over here this is where all the trash
is collecting you just stay right there all right research funding for roller coasters it's i want
to have that i'm gonna wait till i have like fifteen thousand dollars now we play the waiting
game this thing is not fixed i'm looking for a mechanic what are you doing oopsie daisy is
broken down well what are you doing you you right here fix it i fixed it it's it's uh i
do sometimes you turn the router on and turn the router off it's fine 4100 i need some more shops
get some cotton candy dollar something else over here how the prices hot dogs uh fruity icee's
i like it stick it right here dollar 10 something i guess i gotta put something here
i think i'm just gonna make trash i have trash cans everywhere i really do have so many trash
cans that's not the problem it can't be people just come over here to dump the trash this is
the trash corner okay 3600 where's my financials screen
where's my financials cash uh negative sixteen thousand dollars is done all right and i've been
dropping off a little bit here park value i'm doing i'm evening out but it's still fine
weekly profit 98 that's still positive marketing vouchers advertise campaign for a particular ride
i'm going to advertise this one is it summer what day what is it it's june advertise this ride
what's it called it's called splash boats one for three weeks weekly profit negative 3700
i'm gonna name it better i'm kidding jesus uh splashers the squasher the squasher
you don't want to name your ride the squasher
uh how about soaked uh gusher gusher slushy i like the president soaker
oh no not the ferris wheel where's my entertainer is he still running around
i'm doing this shit in the same spot you gotta i gotta have you get the night i need another one
because this other one needs to be in them what's the longest line in the park
probably this one probably oopsie daisy whoopsie doozy whoopsie daisy i don't well i don't whatever
the names of these are this is the longest one right he's not just like pushing people over in
line right what if he gets on he just pushes everybody out of the way and then gets on the
ride this would be so annoying there's enough room for one person to be standing and he's just
pushing people out of the way yeah that would be funny that would be funny
guess we're playing about the amount of trash i'm what do you think i'm trying to do
i have to put cans around i've hired more janitors i'm where are they now watering the grass
who's the dickhead watering the grass what are you thinking what's for your path you don't stay down
here all right how's gussy gussy uh gussy slushy doing i just advertised this and nobody's going to
see it i should have done it for this 5100 i'm making money oh these people want to get off
i need something for the middle something for the middle the 3d cinema that might be kind of fun
3d cinema stick it uh let's over here because it's very crowded okay it shows 3d films
3d film mouse tails mouse tails is fine okay let's make it that color scheme
uh no it's got it's kind of just a gigantic like cheeseball that's fine all right no more
spending money good maybe i could get one more thing here yeah let's get one more
this oh yeah the roto drop these things are awesome put it right somewhere cool
that's it's gonna work but it's really stupid and i i don't like it but it's
what am i gonna do take it off i hate it so much we'll see if it lasts i'll give it 10 minutes
i hate it so much already i fucking hate it i'm trying to make it work
i can't i should build another one on top of this one this is such a mess why is it even allowed in
the game i shouldn't be allowed to do this you can't even see the rides anymore i you i can't
i'm gonna have to turn the camera on i can't man this is this is the shit that looks like
my clothes of a dirty laundry in the corner that's what this looks like
this is a dirty laundry clothes pile of rides can i even make i don't think i could even make
this work i have to go this way and then okay i think i can here we go no it's gonna be up
back it up from here i could turn it right it's gonna be straight oh come on how the fuck am i
gonna do this how am i gonna do this exit on the right like over here look at how cramped this is
i can't this is shit in the way oh fuck i gotta hurry up got it oh hey do you guys like my
tree and its roots all over the place i really do like i'm gonna make this thing green
the only green thing in this whole park it's just a fucking tree there's the leaves
have you have you written the big tree yet
big tree all right how fast does it go free fall drop yeah that's really tall it's so fast
all right how does it look let's see we're gonna get one more test
not yet available 73 miles per hour 70 80 80 to zero uh oh i don't think very many people are
gonna ride the big tree come on one daredevil is gonna get on here i don't even know where the queue
is people are getting on this guy's gonna get on the only guy in the park the one guy riding the
big tree and he's dressed as the big tree that's the best part he's ready get on there crazy j
why are you guys going up here this is the exit he's just waiting patiently he's the only one
waiting come on crazy j get on it there it is let's see the thoughts all right here he goes
oh no wait he was shitfaced that's why he came over here there he goes see you later crazy j
that was nothing what do you think what do you think he's fine two more yeah this is fine
two more people got on i have to go to the bathroom where is he right here i need to go to the bathroom
heading for restroom four if i go up and down more than once i think it's fine what's the giant
meatball that's the cheetah that's the that's the cheez-it theater all right this is good
you're getting back on this path is disgusting or how many i got 917 people here 4100 i need a cool
coaster i forgot this ride was fun put another big tree on top i can't there's no room for it
i need a brown roller coaster that goes all around this as if it was and more tendrils
wooden rope i need a little one steel wild mouse with mouse with mice it's too high all right well
that's fine that's fine that's all right this is not going to hit anybody right and then
i need more money dead air i'm concentrating there's too many rides here i need another
loan i can't i don't even i can't get you'll see this is going to look really interesting you'll
see i'm gonna have to go further back a little yeah okay i'm gonna turn it here i'm gonna cut
it here and then bang right here oh got it look at that shit the color of mice is it gonna run
i have no idea i'm gonna make this green yeah that's better maybe a lighter green yep um
let's give it a try let's see what happens save it just in case fucking horrible happens
what there we go the tree and the weeds and the oak i'm excited oh turn it off turn it off turn
it off turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off
close the ride god okay so what happened it couldn't go up this why this has to be trimmed
okay trim it go forward all right good try it again oh we losing frames here hello what the
fuck is happening i mean i can see you guys typing to charge my internet card oh shit uh it says i'm
still this is freaking me out yeah you guys can just hear me uh uh yeah can you see my mouse
moving you can hear but not see yeah i'm looking over here it's like going all over the place
guys strange yeah i paused again mouse is moving what's the this is really weird hold on time for
a telephone stream uh no it's not the game it's the something going on with i don't it's not even
like my internet it's weird it looks like it's my internet but it's not my internet let me do
something here yeah the game is paused but that doesn't matter one sec this is fucked up because
over on my obs i'm like red like completely in the red so don't ask me why this is happening
well i'm definitely still dropping frames because here like if i'm positive it'll probably happen
yeah see let me it's very stuttery yeah it's all looks like it's all screwed up
give me one second let me i'm gonna try something give me one second the stream might die but it
might come right hello are we still are we still bad uh yeah this is weird this shouldn't be
happening they just fixed it they just fixed it and the same thing is happening again yeah this
this is legit the same problem from three days ago i'm dropping like 70 percent of all frame
this is this is just fucking bananas people the people on like the engineering team actually even
like fix it in the back end something really fucked up is going on somebody is killing this
node i have no idea what's going on but like like this is how fucked up this is right this is the
last three days shit's been almost perfect we that's i think i dropped like 100 frames last
night in like eight hours and it was perfect it was perfect we got perfect for five hours straight
so what the hell's going on you know i'm saying like somebody's fucking dumping us
i'm gonna i'm gonna wait i'm gonna sit here for like a minute or two i just want to build my mouse
roller coaster are we good are we here is this is it fine what the hell is going on what the fuck
it's back to normal now for now is somebody like pissing on like the electrical outlet next to the
node that's a bit what i like to make no sense what in the name of god it's it's fixed it's back
to normal that was just like four straight minutes of just dead internet what in the name of god
all right well whatever let's keep what i need to test this all right okay welcome back everybody
hopefully uh hopefully we're still good here for a while all right so what was it okay i was
testing this again my mouse my my new mouse coaster where is it close it and open it back up
test why can i not test it why can i not test the coaster is it because it crashed can i never open
this ever again no i don't want to open it i want to test it nobody's in the cube yeah i know
it's because it crashed you need to repair it let me go through and find out where it would
uh crash again let's see so it looks like here it goes i fixed that one so it's gonna go down
wrap around then go up i think it'll make it up that down catch up caught i think it'll be fine
though okay let's try it again here we go all right come on work work work work work work
there we go first drop passes by over here chain added all right we haven't seen this before
it goes around down and around come on keep going delete delete delete delete delete delete
delete delete delete delete delete it stop stop stop stop stop okay so right here i need a chain
here like right here so like right here needs to be a chain right i think that makes sense
that simulate the ride oh that's helpful i didn't even know that was possible delete delete delete
delete delete delete so it'll get caught there slowly fall over here and then that should be it
there it goes and around no it's got to be this one here damn it this is bad i'm gonna have to
change this whole thing here it's got to be straight like this on the chain on the chain
chain turn it turn it hard turn it hard and that's it right there oh what how was that
possible what did i do i screwed that up bad that's not it right there damn it look at that
looks perfect i think i have to do it from here straighten it out chain on straight bang a no
straight again turn turn straight and then here i need to get over here
i need to get rid of this how do i get on the other side i want to like get over this way but
i can't get over there i really have to go all the way around all right that should help
shit did it no i need to turn the camera what the hell okay no it needs to be down and over
i just want to see what it looked like oh you son of a gun look at the poles go back it up then
not quite a little bit over i can't even see it damn it i had it done where even is this
shit i'm gonna fucking puke on camera is that not it what oh my god
shit no it's too much going on here it's impossible to see this is in the way change this color okay
um i'm just going up and we're gonna meet in the middle it's got a half thing on it okay meet me in
the middle i can't even see it okay so i'm gonna meet you in the middle okay sounds like a plan
i'm i even lined up i don't i don't know sick it's 65 feet i need 65 feet over here
that's just never gonna happen it's never gonna happen i have to redo this whole fucking thing
here we go i need to get this 65 feet 65 feet that's 70 feet 65 feet 65 feet completed
turn it this way with this right there okay 65 feet now i think that's it that's not even 65
feet that's not where is it i don't i don't even know where the car is can you guys see where it is
oh it's up here this is a katamari ball all right it's good okay will it make it please make it
it's not gonna make it it's not gonna make it this is a chain right oh my god thank goodness
it's a chain hurry up you just have to go around and then there's a chain right there
the big tree hasn't been fixed what there we go wrap around catch it yes it did it okay it's
completed it worked done get this thing open let's do a live test 44 people in i can't even
click this line hold on important just make sure this live test board the big tree yeah it's fine
yeah it's good people stuck on the broken ramp oh whoa you're right good all right let's not open
it get it open um all right i don't i don't i don't i can't even look at this shit
this is so ugly this park this sucks it's so ugly can't can't get to the answers of steel wild
mouse one what are you talking about how what do you mean you can't get the steel wild mouse one
i don't even know what that means oh okay okay they can't get up here
it's what a stupid placement okay i can fix this i can fix it oh my god this is terrible
no no pull it back uh okay we're gonna go this way and then we're gonna take a one more that
way and we're gonna take a little go right down down straight no i'm gonna have to go down the
whole way and then turn it like right here i don't i don't even know what's going on
okay i need to slow down but why is this pre-recorded pre-recorded how it took him
that long what do you i need to see this with different set eyes because this shit is fucked up
guess they're complaining about the amount of trash i'm not sure which way to look at this place
he's pretending to be bad well no i actually this was going pretty smoothly until uh i built
the second one of these that's when it went off and then i just tried to see how many things i
could get in the same spot actually you know i'll be honest i think i did a pretty good job
let's put another one i mean nobody said that pathway exit to luigi's
uh wait did he just did he just pick up throw up this guy right here
and throwing up this ride's not even that intense this ride's stupid
there's so much throw up there which one of these is closed it's broken down where are my mechanics
get another one there are almost a thousand people in this park just looking at the big
tree makes me feel sick no one's getting in the big tree line anymore i know what to do cut the
tree down no now i just wait and make money and i'm yes i'm looking over here because it hurts my
eyes to see the other stuff you're right okay so now we're gonna go uh i steal wild mouse one needs
a new name the weeds so yeah into the weeds the big tree these need to be changed no there
shouldn't be blue anymore doesn't fit the theme gosh your slushy broke down it's all right i want
a cool water ride now i'm sick of looking at this i can't even click in here what's going on over
here what are you doing i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it 1200 i just have to hang out
for a little bit which one is this called all right looks good i want people to come in
because they see somebody playing roller coaster tycoon 2 and this is what they see and they just
shake their head a few times and then ask how did he even manage to do this well you're gonna
have more questions because there's another one coming in this way you'll have way more questions
just gotta wait till i get a few more dollars i'm making money though i could just relax i'm
gonna increase the price 45 bucks what do i need a thousand guests i want a water ride too though
all right i'm gonna do a uh do i have log flume dini slide log flume all right yeah i do that's
already what it's what i have over there splash boats that's what this is log flume that's really
cool how does this tree relate suspended swinging coaster a giga coaster they can go up to 300 feet
oh my 25 000 holy shit i want to like do this around the whole thing how much how much can you
take up for a loan advertising campaign is finished anybody ride it no how much can you have what can
i do for a i'm supposed to see i can do this 60 how much can you take i don't want to lose all my
like company equity though i have 36 000 dollars to make a giga coaster i'm gonna go overboard here
this is gonna be the end i can already tell you how do i turn off the emote only all right i have
36 000 giga coaster i can't can i actually put it right here no i can't this thing is gonna be
fucking insane slow down i'm fine hit the brakes hit the brakes oh my god that shouldn't even be
real i don't even money this is seriously like have i just given up completely on this
you're not gonna be able to tell what the fuck is going on what's up oh right hi i yeah i forgot
i forgot i was live it happens that was the best of us yeah i'm streaming you're right yeah yeah hey
i how many i forgot like four times now i just spaced the fuck out yeah i did i really did it was
like a hard space too i need uh entrance the entrance look at these i don't have to do anything
crazy for the entrance and exit here all right let's see will this do it what is this gonna do
where is it what is it doing what is it doing up here this is not this is not the brake part
the game was not paused yoshi yoshi commits tax fraud ost all right what happened what's going
on here are these not let me see here hold on it's the chain right so chain chain the chain is still
on we're gonna we're gonna turn and then close it so what happened there what's the problem
i don't understand what are you doing why is it stuck chain adds act as a block brake i thought
the chain pulls it up the isn't the chain supposed to pull it up you need block brake when you have
two trains there's a train stuck further along wait hold on the way this is what you're talking
about okay so i have to go over here and take these brakes out here the boosters aren't fat
they're 170 miles per hour what do you mean they're not fast enough okay here's boost
so right here is where it needs to go out so let's go like this i need to get rid of these
i think these are all brakes right boost boost boost boost boost boost done faster i can't go
faster that's not gonna happen all right turn it on we're good all right we're good let's try it
again multiple weeks this is like taking a trip to the moon it took weeks to get and it takes
weeks to get down oh my god that would be horrible holy shit i can't believe it didn't crash
these people yeah these people would be liquefied max speed 120 miles per hour
let's see the let's see the g's vertical g's like skull cracks let's see
your stomach goes into the fucking back of your throat
oh my god all right it works open for business i wonder if anyone will get on this i love how
this is parallel to the monorail this thing's gonna go by so fast this is gonna blow other
stuff over no one's gonna ride this i still i got 13 grams still all right it's still
3d cinema has done what it's all right so what about a scenario where i change this
and i make it go all the way down here slow drops slow drops and just make a gigantic snake
and you actually are on the ride for like two or three months what's my park rating
people are left people left sorry yeah i got too concentrated over here i this was starting to be
all right and then i just just this happened and i i lost control completely hold on let me do
something over here let me at least spread this out a little bit so it's not like concentrated
nonsense all right how about i want to do an actual cool roller coaster one that i actually
would be proud of bobsled coaster that's pretty cool that's really cool i want to i want to make
one a bobsled coaster all right let's make this for real let's say what can i do on ride photo
okay let's go up let's go let's get let's go up this way they're already 20 bucks
just gently go up like that okay not too anything nothing too ridiculous at first
let's just go up a little bit like this drop that bend it to the maybe maybe give it a nice turn
here i want a big cup all right interesting charge higher for umbrellas i can't there
and then i want it to go up again so that's it this is the first little bit of an oops
you know like up bend it this way check this out ready so make it a little bit of a of a
tilt scenario like this come on you can do it come on okay bend it again a little
now we're going to go on part two here part two is chain i think that's enough speed it might not
move i hope it is up up again higher that's all right right there's fine it looks good now let's
really bend that twist it down i ran out of money that's good enough and then bring it down
let's bend it over this way i think i can go up can i go up and over yeah i should be able to turn
it one more time i got five grand still those things are so expensive bank it again straighten
it out down we're going to wrap it back this way one more time slow it up come in for the close
go down with it this way harder right there drop it at the very end connected all right
and i'm putting i'm putting like a statue up here
test it how does it work i like the little pretzel here
how are you guys getting a dick out of this this if this is a dick then i don't that would be
uh an issue i think i would that were never mind all right it made it around the first pretzel
come on what kind of dick this listen that is not a dick it's if anything oh
all right so i had trouble i need to make this a little smaller let's go this way with it
i'm gonna say um i'm gonna say um so over here this needs to be straightened out
so we're gonna go forward with it wait i think i can go like this
it should do it all right get over that first hump just then i can go up this chain here there's
no way it's gonna go up this this has to be a chain as well no way not gonna happen you know
i mean you know what i'm saying you know what i mean this has to be a chain this whole thing
is just gonna go away and then down what's the size on this guy 40 feet 40 feet i got it right
there tighter 40 feet 40 feet straight ahead how's that 40 feet that's not even 40 feet what are you
talking about it's not 40 feet that's not 40 feet how's that 40 feet that's not 40 feet what's
going on there that's not 40 feet that's bullshit double click what does that do
damn money is that it is it going in there all right does that does that work does that help me
out there i think it does ladies and gentlemen tested i'm sorry i forgot i was streaming is that
but from this angle it's also incorrect did i just get it what is happening 50 50 feet just go
forward 50 50 straight ahead you've done it you've done it now you can play the game now son
thanks dad please cost end this unholy stream why would you ever want that to happen what happened
you you've failed your objective oh whatever i don't care look at how slow this is it's not
going to be enough this has to be a chain or something this is so slow it's not going to
happen i gotta just delete these makings chain is this little oomph gonna be enough
open it i don't care come on now people are gonna be fine there's no there's nothing there's no
enclosed thing that's good can i define momentum when you go uh when you're going forward at a
certain speed and when you're the way to slow yourself down you're going your weight is pushing
forward so there's you have that extra you know um i can't talk right now it's forward motion
and the momentum is like your weight combined with how fast you're moving forward and then if
there's no more engine running you turn the engine off and you're still going forward you're still
going to move forward because you have momentum oh he's leaving us in the realm i just wanted to
work uh this is my fifth year running this place this has been a nostalgia trip though it really
has i'm doing this same exact shit is anybody even riding this see this is fun you go around
one two then you go to the drop yeah this is a fun coaster this is not like broken or bad i
screwed up or anything i mean people people have you all you know you killed somebody no i didn't
this person's still in line do you really want to go on this
you sure that you want to go on this ride you really i just want to make sure you're aware
of what happens when you're on this i can't even whatever at the very very very end
why would it explode here of all the places here look how slow this goes too much wiggle at the end
no i got it wrong make more of the dinosaur statues you know that's not a bad idea
okay i have so much trouble with this i've roller coaster tycoon 3 you just hit the auto
button and it does it i didn't i didn't play this one as much as i played three
i'm gonna fucking lose my mind this is like doing a three-point turn in like a parking lot
it's like parallel parking a car end of sanity no i'm fine although i'm probably gonna stop
streaming soon though it's getting late all right somebody get on it it's safe i promise
what's the problem why does nobody want to ride it what's the issue you made it around good up
around goes all the way around comes over here and that's it is the engineer gonna ride it
it goes slower than the people are walking temporarily ride sucks lol true did you just
do two comments answering your own thing
here we go cool bends on the bobsled somebody waiting in line it is safe plenty of time for
this to slow down around a little bend done it's safe to ride get on welcome oh ride sucks yeah
true true oh my god this thing this is off this is right off
all right it's been fun i think i'm done streaming for today why does your theme park
why does your theme park look like the cables behind my tv well that's a great question viewer
the answer is not so simple nobody riding the tree either why is it closed no
there's a ride back here that's been closed the whole time where are my rides where's my ride
overlay now the duality of chat i'm hungry i'm not hungry it's not closed it's just unpopular no
it's closed where is my list where's my list broken down the big tree i just saw it move up
and down what are you talking about how is it broken down all right it's open people like this
one and you guys said this is a shitty coaster look at how wrong that was we already got a line
out the door this is like one of the biggest coasters in the park that's fun i need to do go
carts all right that's the last thing i'm gonna do i'm at my maximum there's go carts there it is
go carts let's go and let's seal it up is this the where is it it's like where's waldo i have no idea
where it is uh never have any idea next to the ferris wheel no no i'm saying where's the thing
to end it it's like over here right i can't even see it that far so it's over here right in there
right there i'm gonna run out of money yeah this this is my official who gives a shit
i had a lot of fun though this game's a blast it always is all right almost out of money and then
i have to i can't take out any more loans all right so it's over here i can fix it a little
bit i think out of money what are the cheats what are the cheats anybody got a cheat code
no i need this thing no where it's right here the go carts there it is okay is everything
screenshot is just this one screenshot that's all i want okay uh i'm out of money so that's the end
screen so how do you sell the park look at this place i have all this room and i concentrated on
the tree select everything sell everything no i spent a lot of time making this mess
yeah i got bad cable management in my pc so what save it save all right i'll save it i'll save it
i'll save it save save game and then sell everything but how do you how would i do that
i'm in the negative right now just go by one by one and then i'm gonna pay back my loan and
then leap okay what's left what who's drowning stephen k has drowned who where who's drowning
where are they there's a duck these are ducks let's pay the loan back don't even have enough
hundred thousand dollars only the tree and the monorail and this mess well that was actually a
lot of fun i had i actually had a really good time this was a fun game up until uh the last
probably 45 minutes to an hour when i just uh i just lost my mind why is my rating so bad
because i started to do this and i also just like 10 people just drowned
oh this is so funny what a fun game but that's gonna be it for me we're gonna do the bits
which would cost tickets well before i go let me see one more thing that this
close this you can go even higher 345 feet oh my god there's buildings aren't even this tall
can they can you add anything to this refurbish vertical tower entry no there's nothing you just
do the vertical tower i did enjoy making the tree so if there's um i i did want to try to get the
twitch integration to work but sadly they shut it down like last year so i'm gonna look into
having a server because what happens is people in chat are people in the game every single person
in here is somebody from chat is how that integration works that would be really fun
and i would play this again if i could get that to work but i do need to set up my own server
which i kind of have to figure that out but uh in the meantime i'm gonna call it here we're
gonna do the bits and i will see you guys in a couple days today is wednesday i will see you guys
on saturday so i'll see you guys saturday and sunday this weekend we've got some interesting
things to do saturday and sunday is going to be hopefully the internet works because every saturday
and sunday stream everyone always gets shut down by cox for some weird reason but we're gonna try
it anyways we're gonna do connect i have just under 30 40 connect games ranging from ones that
are probably fun to ones that are probably be played for about eight minutes and then
immediately taken up that's gonna be on saturday i am preparing myself for that if you have an
idea of a game i i have it i went through meticulously and purchased every single connect
game that i thought would be even remotely interesting on stream there's 40 of them
almost every single one we are going to do that for saturday and sunday i don't know how long
that's going to take us i don't know exactly how far we'll get through them we may need to add
another day i don't know but thanks for joining me i'll see you guys on saturday take care see you
soon and we will do the bits if you take it off have a good one i have already saved this park i
saved the park a few times too so i saved it before all the nonsense i can go back in there
if i really want to but let's do the bits let's go back uh six and a half hours ago yeah that was
that was also that was open rct2 uh debauchery man thanks for the 250 remember that part of
the matrix where neo couldn't drive off that building so he kicked walls until he was launched
upwards that was my favorite part that was a pretty good part referencing the first game we played
tonight that game was also very fun and yes i was kind of just mouth open being a weirdo the last
hour or two here forgetting i was on a live stream but it was fun it was it was relaxing to me
making you know shoots and ladders what is fun coaster let's see then you go to the drop
yeah this is a fun coaster this is not like broken or bad i screwed up or anything
i mean people people have you oh you know you killed somebody no i didn't
fun coaster thank you debauchery man again for 250 remember the part in golden eye 007 when
pierce brosman panics and starts kicking random doors until one opens that's one of my favorite
parts me too hey shelby kuhn thanks for the ten dollars hey germbo i thought i'd give you a little
bit of money also here's a drawing i drew of you and me hope you like it i love it yeah i love it
this is this is amazing it's fantastic thank you this is the cutest like picture ever thank you
shelby kuhn auto in the window yeah that's true and thanks for the ten dollars as well put that
one up on the bridge yeah hey og lossy thanks for the five dollars ho ho you missed that one
try another six dollars actually thank you og lossy seven layer wario thanks for the three bucks
i took off work for the carnival stream to make a bunch of food for my partner and i can't wait to
see it you're awesome should be between four to six hours long that is the time we have blocked
off so should be a whole day event hope you enjoy it thanks for three dollars quarter dime
thanks for the three dollars i want to get off mr bone's wild ride nobody ever said that though
people got in line they rode them oh they just didn't hey me mevious thanks for the five dollars
help i fell asleep on the car ride and when i woke up the park was closed it's been three days please
stop the ride flug boy thanks for the five dollars hope you've been doing well jeremy want to say i've
been being haunted lately by an automobile in my town lately because of the sole reason its first
three digits on its plates are jacks death of rumor maybe thank you the five dollars plug boy
teepo thanks for the five bucks uh bro you're violating the americans with disabilities act
wow because of rumor rumor about jacks yeah thank you teepo for the five dollars
is is because i didn't well i couldn't how did i make i couldn't i made i tried to make stuff
it's talking about my park why did i just fade out did i i should be here there's there's way
more going on at that park i think a lot of things to be concerned about there he's gone
wolfgang thanks for the 10 bucks germa i don't get to watch your streams live too often but i'm
always happy to catch one you're one of the best i'm honored to be put in that category for you
thank you for the 10 dollars thousand bits thank you both game thank you amazing sponge for the
250 hey germa i worked a teenage job this past summer in an ice cream shop which means i've
earned enough to tell you how much i appreciate your streams vodz highlights in you i know it's
hard to appreciate your viewers due to their incomprehensible scale but i want you to know
you make one 16-year-old rhode islanders life a lot better with your work good luck to you for
your first full year in vegas and good luck to me for junior year in high school good luck to you
new england i miss it all the time but good luck thank you amazing sponge for the 250
and as the channel grows i do i never want to lose that aspect of
people just becoming numbers it can be hard sometimes to essentially let's say you do this
in this you know two three four five thousand people here it's hard to individualize everybody
but i don't really i don't want to have that scenario where people adjust numbers it just i
don't know it freaks me out a little but then on the other hand right it's it's sometimes it can
kind of be overwhelming sometimes if you think about it not this kind of thing but just trying
to go over in my head the just how many people might may or may not be here but over the years
i've it if there's five thousand ten thousand five hundred thousand people here i would be
i would act the same i wouldn't really change anything i feel like i haven't really done i
haven't really changed who i am as a person i don't think since starting this i think i've
been pretty much the same as i was from 100 views on a youtube video to people watching this maybe
i have maybe a little not that i've been able to see and look in the mirror and go you've changed
i don't know maybe that's the talk of the villain that is changing i don't
but thank you gnarly for the 250 you playing super mario rpg ost makes me want to see you
play another mario rpg like paper mario or the mario and luigi series those are some of my
favorite games ever the mario and luigi series believe it or not is made by some of the same
people that made super mario rpg same director right there's a alpha dream maybe the developers
that released back when they were doing that i think that's accurate i have played superstar
and i've not played the other ones though i would probably like them
but yeah i wasn't that big of a fan of paper mario not really i respect paper mario but i
don't really enjoy playing paper mario i respect it but i don't really it didn't grab me like the
other ones did that may have changed since i've grown older maybe i will appreciate it now than
i did maybe 10 15 years ago i don't know but that was uh gnarly smelly boy thanks for the 250
smelly boy germa you're insane if you don't think we'd all watch you do a playthrough of super mario
rpg seriously what you did for sorcery and played uh seriously do what you did for sorcery and play
it over the course of a couple weeks like every other stream it would be great uh mario rpg is
not that long of a game it's you could probably get through the whole thing especially if you know
what you're doing and where you're going in seven to ten hours i don't think it would take that
long maybe maybe a little bit longer 12 hours maybe should i should i just do it should i
what do you think should i do it should i stream super mario rpg yeah i mean yeah of course i'll
love it i haven't i'd be you know when you find that game that you love and it's like one of your
favorite games ever made and somehow you stumble into it and end up playing it again every few
years i have played super mario rpg and beaten it probably yeah like more than 20 30 times
i play through it probably once every couple years yeah let's do it that would be a chill just
stream or two yeah let's do it why not we'll do that after connect yeah fuck yeah let's do it
let's do it i'm ready that music too just made me want to play i want to go down the the river
again and collect the coins yeah after the connect weekend we'll settle down and i'll play through
mario rpg still gonna do the gta online casino i still am looking for people to play it there's
like three or four other streamers that i'm through a line out to and i'm trying to see if we can set
something up i think that's more fun with other people like streamers or youtubers whatever not
youtubers we don't i mean she got ghosted it's real money don't they give you like a fake currency
to use for a little while don't forget sam and max the thing about sam and max is the last couple
times i was thinking of doing it i was on a poll and people nobody voted for it that's why i'm kind
i'm kind of waiting i think we hit sam and max exhaustion because i played through both the first
two seasons pretty close to each other i think we may have seen some sam and max exhaustion
so i'm just gonna keep it in the pocket for a little while we'll go back to it we will i'm
not just gonna start it and not finish it especially the fact that it's the third season
and i did the first two full seasons thank you lemon pudding for the 250 germa apologize publicly
to fortnight jimmy 2010 for what you did yesterday or i'm gonna tell grill master barbecue about it
and this time he will ruin your career grill master bbq i don't think it's streamed in like
seven or eight months so i mean okay he turned it on once he winked at the camera like 15 times
over the course of about 14 minutes he sat there for about 15 minutes he winked like three four five
six times few minutes went by he winked and then he turned the stream off i didn't know what he
was but i think he was part of his he did this thing whereas he did a big arg on his channel
and he really got way over his head with it he had the hours and hours of arg footage on his
channel and he was he was doing something with the twitch thing i think it got too much for him
and he didn't want to do it anymore so he decided not to do it anymore i guess i was keeping up a
little bit hey thank you raddest raccoon for the 250 hey germa germa chomp just want to tell you
that i look forward to your streams every week and your streams have helped me through a lot
of days where i was feeling extremely anxious and depressed you're the best thank you raddest raccoon
this community has a way of making us all feel a little better and making us all have fun
the last three streams in a row here it's just been a lot of just fun back and forth i think
like it really has one of my favorite things about this channel is just being able to go back and
forth with you guys i love that the live just bullshit it's so much fun for me hope it is for
you the back and forth bullshit is it's great but thank you i'm glad you uh i'm glad you're here
glad you're hanging out glad you enjoy the stream also thank you to uh a al the chemist al the
chemist for five dollars they just say germa defoe thank you al thank you s10w update for the 250
hey germa hey i'm back to watching your streams again happy i get to see a stream again
even for a little bit you and your humor have inspired my movie directing style and now that
i'm able to make my first movie soon i just want to say thank you for inspiring me from the bottom
of my heart even if you don't know me that well thank you peace and love stay great thanks good
luck with your productions whatever they may be maybe give us some more info soon we've got
doctors yeah we got directors we got scientists we have dentists i told you guys this before i
i got like an email newsletter from twitch and it said it was that who has the most dentists
watching their streams and i was number six i was two slots above dentistry xbbq so i mean
i'm i got that's kind of interesting thank you though good luck uh feono thanks for the five
dollars feono hey germa read this in your best text to speech voice hey play doom ost okay
uh hey germa read this in your best text to speech voice hey germa play don't know st
there you go hey egg scramble thanks for the 250 great stream as always enjoy the rest of your
night buddy also can you remind me of the date of the carnival so i can get work off the 21st
of september september 21st of this year 2019 thank you egg scramble for the 250 demons v thanks
to three dollars and 33 cents there's uh no message but thanks for the three bucks and 33
cents i'm gonna run the credits they may have been destroyed when the internet just that was
really weird the stream kind of cut in half for two minutes or something and then went back
completely to normal it was strange that was very strange hopefully we got most of you
thanks everybody thank you demons v for the 250 on top of the 333 they say big sim think hard
big sim and then the meatloaf i'm not sure what that is but thank you for the 250
i appreciate it demons v you ever played animal crossing yeah i played the last one that was on
the ds what was the last animal crossing on the 3ds i put it i did put some time into that i put
probably maybe 30 hours 40 hours into that one that is newly okay i never streamed it it was
it was just something i just sat around in bed playing 30 hours is yeah that's not a lot yeah
but it was that's a lot for lying in bed for an hour and playing it for 30 days in a row
when the new one comes out i'm not sure i would stream it maybe i would yeah i played that game
for a month straight a full month oh i'm just realizing something this stream title i was
going to change it event where i didn't say i was going to change that it was just roller coaster
tycoon 2 that's the most unclickable title you could ever have whatever this is the name of the
game when the name of the game is underneath the stream so my stream in the browse page was
roller coaster tycoon 2 roller coaster tycoon 2 good that's great that's a very safe normal title
hey i still clicked it all right good yeah that's the kind of title where somebody comes in and if
they ask the name of the game there is a 100 chance that they're just fucking with you
but uh i will see you guys in a couple days for the start of the connect weekend i will see you
on saturday and sunday saturday the 24th a couple days from now same time somewhere around like two
three it might be pulled back a little earlier maybe we'll see keep an eye on the sus good night
goodbye thanks for watching