Yeah, I know I said I'd be here at around noon, but I'm here now. I'm here. It's possible that Jeremy's gonna quit streaming one day.
What do you mean possible? It's absolute. You know, it's very possible that one day Jeremy's not gonna stream anymore.
What do you mean by- that's absolutely going to happen one day. I can't- I don't- I can't live forever.
Or possible that one day he won't stream again.
Possible. We found all the Horcruxes. Yeah, okay. You think so.
You see, that- that- that- Voldemort, what a dummy.
Why would you make it all those fucking objects? Why would you make it stuff like that?
You- you made it the most, like, popular things, you know? Why would you do that?
No. If I had ten Horcruxes, five of them are gonna be surgically attached to my body.
Oh, no, one of them. Not five of them, because then if you, like, fucking shoot at it and stuff, then it's gone.
I'm sewing one of my Horcruxes into my bed. Why would you just put it in a vault? No, it's gotta be with you, around you at all times.
Why would you keep them on you? That defeats the purpose. No, because then you gotta come through me.
I want one on me. I want one to be my baseball hat.
You know what a great Horcrux would be, guys? Shit that you wouldn't even give a shit about.
Why wouldn't he have made one of his Horcruxes his showerhead? Who the fuck is going to do that?
Who would ever go into Voldemort's shower and say, this is definitely one of them? No.
The handle, the little flapper of your toilet. I'm not gonna make it some elaborate, mystical device or being, no.
It's gonna be an old book that I didn't care about reading. Or a toilet seat. Or one mug.
Anyways, hi. What was the joke? Oh yeah, people are just kinda coming in and just catching it halfway.
Just go watch the beginning of the stream. It's only been like three minutes, so you can catch up.
What if it accidentally gets destroyed?
Um, I don't think I'm gonna be taking a shower and cast the Iviticus spell into the wall near the showerhead.
Magical spells would be banned in my bathroom. It just wouldn't be allowed.
Like, now fuck that. You wouldn't be allowed to cast spells in my house.
You know how people have the rule of take your shoes off before you enter the house?
Put your wand of no spells in this house. None.
We're gonna do the Olympics today. 2012 London Olympics.
Not Mario and Sonic at the London Olympic Games. No, we're just doing...
This apparently is the one that has the most of games to play.
I think it has 35 events.
I also have the Beijing one. 2008. For some reason. I don't know why. I own it.
It was not that expensive. Don't worry. This sucks. Just go play God Hand.
I mean, that's an option if I don't like it. I don't think that's gonna be possible, though.
I saw a little bit of the preview of what this... I'm gonna try to get gold medals. Silver medals, at least.
You ready? I am. Here it is.
I've had to hear this in my ears since the stream started, by the way.
Six straight, seven straight minutes. This doesn't change.
All right. Olympic Games. Take on the world at the London 2012 Olympic Games.
This is almost ten years ago, yes. I'm gonna... I'm doing it. I'm gonna try to win as many as I can.
How do streamers even read chat? We have s... s... We don't. We don't.
We don't. We just pick out one thing that somebody said every ten minutes.
And hope that it's fucking relevant to the conversation.
I'm just kidding. Face Camo Riot. See? No, I can read that one.
Select how challenging the CPU will be. Well, we can't even do hard, so don't even tell me to select it. I can't do it.
Play tw... Well, hold on. Play 12 events. Play 20 events.
Is this like Mario Party? Am I only selecting just the amount of turns we're gonna have?
How funny would that be if this just opened up on a game board with the dice and shit?
What? No no no no no no no no no! Don't... Oh, a six.
That'd actually be awesome. I kind of wish it was like that.
That was kind of funny I guess. I was... that was just what it sounds like when you play Mario Party with the dice.
Like, that's just... I mean that was a fact. Not a joke.
All right. Who am I playing as?
Okay, we have
Australia
Hmm. I have to be the United States right like I'm from the United States. Is this locked?
What?
Why is the United States locked? What's no, it's definitely not locked. Oh shit. Okay. I am
American
Somebody made this joke, but I'm gonna make it too. I
Had a plan to make this as well. I hope it's like an hour and 40 minute long cut
Splendid glowing like a beacon here in London's East End
So many nations represented here already to compete alright, so do I have to be part of the opening ceremony
Somebody tell George not to spin the camera so much. I'm gonna fucking puke mate. You're going too fast
Biowork
Day one select Oh customized team. Okay, edit the names and appearances of each athlete. This is what we came here for
Oh, I get to make me. Oh my god. I get to make me
Wait, I get how many me's am I gonna have?
Wait, these are all different me's
Well, what should what do I want to do? Oh
No, this is gonna take like three hours
I
Hacking archery cycling
Did I just be all of them? Okay. I want to buy one to dive
It's like an athlete type. I don't think that's okay. Yeah, I don't even have that hair anymore
No, I'm gonna do a bunch of events. I want to be part of all the events at least as many as I can
What was it?
seven
Okay, what about variant?
Edit name
John
Peterson, oh
Angry were you when you wrote this part? Let's go back Jerma. Wait, my name is Jerma Matthew Kennedy
I'm Jerma Kennedy
Jerma Matthew Kennedy
Why am I Jerma Matthew Kennedy? That's not me. Oh, did I do it?
Okay, there's Jerma Matthew
He's a real people
Alright, let me do this quick. It's just it's gonna be me. Alright, I'm I want to be I want to win all the gold medals
Shit shit. It's different person. There is it just two athletes for each category. Oh
Wait, can they both can they both be me whatever in the pool at the same time? I have to be somebody else as we as we
About bugleberry no Jax. Yeah, we'll do Jax Jerma and Jax, but I wanted to be me
Okay, I can't do view. It's just gonna be me. I don't care. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'll make it Jax fine. I but I'm gonna try to win as many with both characters. It doesn't matter what character it is
It's still me. I
Mean not really that's not that close
I'll make a game to grossy too. Don't worry
He's the same person
Diving is done trampoline
Okay, trampoline
second athlete
We'll do bugleberry. How the hell am I gonna find a bugleberry here? I'm not gonna be able to it's not even close
All right. Yeah, this is gonna get really fucking boring if I sit here and just edit everybody's name
It's all I'm just going I'm just name. I'm just gonna go go go. Here we go
Done done. No, I need
Six right? No, I thought it's supposed to be six seven who cares
It doesn't matter if it looks like a different fucking person. I don't care
All right. I don't care. I'm gone. All right one. I need to do one more. We need to do I want
Okay, I'm on track. They're all me
He's cheating
Okay. Yeah. All right. So good. We got doping Dan and then Bob fast. That's pretty good for the the track team
How about some strong strong man?
This is the this is this is javelin what are they did why is it just the names are just describing what they can do
Strong Dan. Okay, fine
Wait, don't we already have a Dan?
There's already a Dan who cares Dave Colgate. All right. Well, hold on
All right. That's fine. How about jumping?
Weightlifting Dave Colgate
I'm better. It'll be a surprise when we see a stupid like a stupid fucked-up name
okay, this is our how about Dave Colgate and like
Mike Crest
They're the both athletes on the weightlifting team. It's just turning into just an ad. All right. Where's Mike Crest?
Sure, do Anthony Bantony. I gotta play the game
Jumping or Anthony Bantony? No. No, this is the game. No, I'm gonna win a bunch of gold medals
Make a guy named. Mr. Bald
That's not even funny, but I think why is it funny?
Well, why not a first name?
Okay, this is mr. Bald
Mr. Mr. Tall
Mr. Bald and mr. Tall
Mr. Bald to
No, no, no more. Mr. Bald
Just make mr. Clean
Make weak Dan
Well weak Dan has to be in the same
Okay, mr. Bald and mr. Dan
Okay, Mike Crest and Dave Colgate throwing
Okay, Dan bald bald Dan. There's too many Dan's too many bald
And this is how we like named our kids
Make a kid Pisto
Make it make it somebody
Just name somebody the baby
Name somebody's name actual baby the baby
Okay, this person's name is gonna be actual baby or like just gonna be like one actual one-year-old or something
With the baby and then in brackets two years old
This is their name. All right, I'm done after this. We're going after this one. How do I do it?
Okay
What I was gonna say like I'm doing and he's holding up two fingers
All right, I'm done wait this the whole does the entire women's team
Yes
Okay, I'm done
Alright, I gotta go. I gotta go. Can we play old metal? Where did I not go through?
Yep, come on men's long jump women's archery choose two events today. Alright, which one men's long jump and
then women's archery or
men's 200 meter
Do the 200 meter, okay, I'm ready. I don't know how to play
We're about to start the Olympics
Songs songs playing over the other song. There are three songs
I
Don't know how to do this
The eight go through to the final all right, mr
Dan yeah the first of the four of the eight goes for the final by the way
This is the first time that mr. Dan has ever stepped foot on track and field the first time he's ever done a long jump
Welcome to the Olympics mate. Don't slow
Press X to begin running
Tap X to fill the bar fill the bar above the white line without overflowing it
That that's me touching it once
Speed lock what the fuck
Lick of L as the athlete approaches the white line
Get one practice run
I'm ready
All right, mr. Dan, let's go
Team USA for the next round. Well, this is his first attempt ever. Okay speed has been locked in
Well, he looked distracted on his approach towards the board
Looks like he snapped his ankle. He really twisted his ankle
That's embarrassing that's in front of 200 million people or
I could probably beat that right now. Yeah, I could probably do that right now
By a huge amount by the way, not a little
Alright, come on redemption. Mr. Dan
Groove it. I could in the second round. That was super fast. Alright, here we go. I mean too low
Sensitive I think it is I'm trying not to do it so hard
That was five point four. That was okay. Well, this is a bit of a shock team USA are in last place
Come on, I think it's pressure sensitive
Smooth athletes on the runway. I got no idea. Okay, so hold on. That was pretty good. Let's step over the line
What?
Here's the scoreboard and it shows team USA in eighth place
God damn it. All right
That was good
What's that one right on the line? You better not disqualify. Yeah, you're gonna disqualify that bullshit
What
Here's the scoreboard. We're gonna adjust that dude's glasses. Okay, that was right on the line. I got disqualified
The world records eight. I still don't understand
So, okay. I'm good. I'm I pressed it one one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven two one two three four two
Fire one two. It's two. It's hard. Okay, here we go
That better not be a foul that was before the to say it's a foul
How many times do I have to do this?
I'm just embarrassing myself
chance saloon sixth and final attempt
That was so bad. I just hard
Well, that's awful a new personal best is not even as good as
Like a 15 year old in high school to the middle to the end all wrong
Eighth place well totally frustrated and ejected and quite rightly so
That wasn't the best performance
8.1
Well, this is a massive shock one of the favorites has gone out team usa miss out on qualification
That was qualification. All right, I got men's 200. Are you kidding me? I'm gonna fucking destroy this
Sorry, mr. Dan
Comes to redemption. Yeah
Because this one absolutely is going to be tap x as fast as you can and i'm going to destroy all those
This is a terrific venue
From some recycled and okay, what's the shove button materials? This really is a green stadium
Of the new millennium. Oh i'm looking for the r ready to go on the first step
Of their olympic dream. I was looking for who us. Okay, there's bilping dan
tutorial
Press x to launch
Tap repeatedly to fill the bar fill the bar above the white line without overflowing the speed
It's actually very hard to keep it here. I'll tell you
I see running like that
lunge
Okay, keep bar in the green. It's so hard to do that. You have no idea
It's so pressure sensitive and so fucked up
All right, let's do it. I'm ready
Pop four doping dan get in there
When do I go just comes down to perform?
Hold on
Come on drugs you motherfuckers
You'll never beat me. I'm gonna catch up to this little brick
Second place third place
When it came down to the finish on the line good strength to go through the tape another good performance
Oh
Okay, this is it this is the real one this is for the olympic gold medal
I gotta get a gold with doping dan. Come on. He's psyched up for this. Here we go
Okay, i'm ready. I'll be ready
Certainly middle of the pack in terms of best times this year
However, there's no doubting the ability deep inside that body. The question mark though has been over the desire
Has to work harder at this stage 50 meters gone and already in stride
Well, this race really starting to take shape as they approach halfway
Leading the way it's island
Into what's the line here?
That's the gold medal
I want to see that. I want to see that
See how small that bar got at the very end. That's the gold medal. That's one
Don't worry. I'll get a shitload more
Wait, do I have a medal ceremony?
Is this a league game? No, so smooth from start to finish
Straight into the stride and then once in rhythm
What a performance amazing
I think I lost final check on the standings. Then what's an event? This has been
Confirmed now a gold medal for the usa. Holy shit 21.71
21.72
Zero point one. This is the moment where finally the athlete is crowned the new
Olympic champion
Emotions running high no doubt as they step onto the podium. I did it big smiles as the chris's one for the national anthem
There'll be tears flowing
Wait, that's not that's not the whole thing
condensed national
Take a commercial break
These are memories that will live long for these oh say can you see a medal from an olympic games
is
What so we'll be back let's have a look I actually forgot the national anthem had to stop I had to just get out of that
Well, that's it from the olympic stadium for now from seth bennett. We'll see you next time
I had to get out
All right. I got a gold medal. Yeah
You've had a mr. Dan couldn't jump
I got a retry token. Well, you get currency if you do well
I got three medal points. Ooh. All right day one
Campaign summary either results in the events
But did not qualify. Okay
Medal tally, let's take a look
United states one gold medal
Poland's right underneath
Important link is it find out? Yeah, that's pretty important
That mouth
Why does it have such a scary mouth?
Okay, we got women's archery under breaststroke trampoline
Rapid fire pistol. Oh, how many can I do too? That's it
I need to do all right. I want to I want to rapid fire pistol
And then I want to archery too, though
Trampoline I wish you could do more than two
Okay, men's trampoline. Here we go
Rampel how do you do?
What are you doing a trampoline lips and shit?
All right, let's do some backflip. This is me. This is me. I gotta do well these athletes equally matched
All right, select the routine
Select the tutorial routine and proceed to the next phase when selecting routine look at the difficulty and tariff before making a decision
What's the meaning tariff?
Pay taxes on my routine
The athlete will automatically build momentum. The routine moves are shown in the upper left area of the screen
Okay
So it's like circle
Square
press circle to start a tucked somersault
Press square to perform a pike shape at the start of the second somersault
New button prompts appear when you must perform each element
First down as the somersault completes to exit
You only have 70 seconds to complete all eight skills any missed skills will award zero difficulty points and occur a heavy execution penalty
And try to time your inputs
Okay, here we go
I'm gonna do like fucking five backflips
Do people like shut up in the stands like golf you would need that right they do right in 2000 in sydney
Trampolining is now very much part of the fixtures and fittings
Three times men have competed in this event and there's been three different winners
beginner
Oh, but what are they no room for error?
They only get one chance in this event so selection of the routine is germa germa germa. What what?
expert two no
Well, they only get one chance on the trampoline and they've gone for a big routine now
This will be their chance to shine
Fencing up and down just not good enough. It's the tricks that'll get in the points
I'm doing them. How do I do other skills? I know one move. How do I do other moves?
Just jumping up and down isn't going to score him any points here. Oh shit. There it is really executes that beautifully
Oh fantastic
And he really needs to get the tricks in now great work with the routine there shit
That was a triple. I just did a triple skill level out there ideally
He needs to finish that routine on his feet not his front
Come on. We really need to see the routine now. Come on
Oh showing great technique there
He's not gonna get far in this competition. Just jumping up and down i'm doing it
I'm gonna recap on that one now. Here's the replay
Oh, that was sick. These are incredible moves. Oh
Oh, I can't I get it. I was doing the same move over and over again
Finally there's the other move it's that same spin. Okay. All right. All right what I get six
Intrigued to know what the judges think
Oh showing frustration more than anything. They know that performance just wasn't up to scratch today
Well, that's all the action we have for you now from this event time now to hand back over to Seth bennett
That's your commentator alison kerbishly
I looked over the chat somebody just said fucking loser. How does this work?
To the world artillery barracks here in the artillery barracks
This should be a great venue for the shooting events. I feel like throw grenades
rapid fire pistol
Until 1984 men and women regularly competed against one another in the shooting event
What is this?
Is that that is a grenade i'm holding a grenade. What's a grenade in my hand? Oh, no, it's not. Oh, dear
R2 r2 to shoot
Kind of good
Time limit per round reduces across the event the final two rounds last for only four seconds
For the best results aim the pistol in one continuous motion to shoot all the targets as quickly as possible
To say these athletes can afford to make a mistake today any slip ups and then they won't I came right from the trampoline
Okay, here we go. You gotta be quick
Can I just shoot the same target in five different places eight seconds to hit five targets
We go three two one
Oh, I got it. Okay. All right. All right. All right. We got I got six out of there. I got a six. It's okay
Always good to get on the leaderboard in the first round
Round two
Let's get I only have four seconds to do this at the end. Okay six seconds
The results on the scoreboard aren't good
And some way behind the leaders
It's nerve-racking, okay
I'll get it this time
Thanks up round three. Let's go six seconds
Okay
All right, I brought it back
Let's go i'll pull this back
Okay, do I have a red dot four seconds
Oh
That's hard as hell
I gotta get into fourth place fourth place is placing right place
No, wait, this isn't mario kart. It's not like bronze two
I need to get third
Number five this gets really tough as the scoring rings tighten
shit
That's it. I gotta pull the other four. All right, let's go team usa in one more round. I gotta nail this one
Number six then final round to make this one count
The fuck out of here. I'll take second place right now. Let's pull it back up through a silver medal
fourth place
At least i'm mario kart placed
I'm using a retry token
Wait that was wait that wasn't wait what hold on a second that was wait, hold on
That was just for the qualifying that was not for the medal
I just retried a qualifier with a retry token
Oh, well, he looked so upset. Did you see him? He was holding his head. He's like i lost I didn't know
You'd be qualified what?
If you qualified you'd be happy. Why would he be so upset on the screen? It's all right. It gives me practice
Six seconds to hit five targets
Pressures on i'm gonna take the second place to qualifying four seconds then to hit the five targets. This is a good practice
Yeah, i'm gonna nail it now. I've got the rhythm
Second place
Here's round five then five targets four seconds to hit them. I'll take first place at the real actual medal event
Team usa so far and the scoreboard confirms it there in first place
Here we go round six then the final round has to shoot well here and he did
First place then now he's happy. I needed to be happy
To produce your best at the olympic games is all anyone why do they need a replay for this?
Well, let's take a check on the final standings in the top three. All right
In this one men's 20, it's rapid fire pistol. This is the one that counts I have one
return token
All right, come on me go i gotta be clean
Round one, let's do it. Eight seconds to hit the five targets
plenty of time
All right, it's okay. All right. That's all right. That's the second
It's really tight at the top of that scoreboard at the end of that round
And with this show just how good competition this is at this stage first shot was fucked up. Yeah it was
Here we go round two then two seconds off the clock
Same number of targets
That's all right. That's good. Good. Keep it locked in first place
94 94 tied what happens if it is tight round three
Here we go
Oh, there was like a loud sound outside. It didn't fuck me up
First place
All right, I can lose it really quickly here don't get overconfident
This is the four seconds
What happened why did it fire twice oh my fucking god, why did it go pop pop
Decent performance the pressure sensitive bullshit of the biggie
Needs to remain accurate here. Come the fuck on
You gotta be kidding me, dude. Are you serious?
I don't think I can even do that double tap again if I wanted to
On the sixth round five targets four seconds can't make a mistake here in the final round
I'm thinking if somebody did that they missed twice and they went like oh my god
What happened did I win here's the replay of that I got a bronze medal
And can you take gold in this event a real performance from this athlete?
Plenty of smiles in the hungarian campus this athlete takes home a silver medal
This is a proud moment for this athlete retry. No, I can't I need to save it. Have fun with your bronze medal
A bronze is fine
No, i'm not gonna retry it
Traditionally at the olympic games it runs one gold another fantastic achievement
Why is it so sad to look at that screen?
Okay, I want to do the archery. I'm gonna do archery. What's
K-ring
Oh, this is discus throw. I'm gonna do k-ring. I don't know what that means
I'm gonna do it
Wait, do we is this gonna we get gold medal glenn here?
Okay, here we go. This is
archery
Come on glenn where's the bow?
The boy this is gonna run around like stab stuff. It was so important in the 14th century. It was compulsory. Oh, okay
hold
Hard to draw the bow
Use l to aim release r quickly to fire the arrow
All right
Flight's affected by the wind be sure to compensate for wind strength
Is drop?
Okay, 20 seconds before the shots forward you got it
All right, come on christin reed
Kristen reed's going for the gold number one two megabits per second up to the top left
That's not a bullseye
Two miles per hour that way that's
It doesn't think two miles per hour was gonna be that big of a deal
That's a qualify that's pretty sick let's have a look at the leaderboard then yeah that I did great after the first end
meters per second
So that's actually like six
Seven miles per hour
Why are we doing um dumb dumb from the united states boy?
Why come they don't do how come they don't convert every single thing for the one country on earth?
That doesn't care to do the metric system. Why couldn't do why don't you do that for me?
I expect you to do everything twice. So I understand it. This is it
This is heavy wind up. Thank you
Thank you
This is actually fun
I like this
There's a flat earth competition at the olympics. I don't know what that means. Let's have a look at the scoreboard
Is that like just bring a bunch of beer and yell at each other?
And they've done an argue about it. What do you what do you do? I don't know what that means
This certainly isn't theirs to be taking for granted at this stage
What do you have a competition?
Uh, I think I think you're looking for debate and the competitors will shoot towards the magnificent media center
You compare the planets to see what one is the flattest
This is arrow number two for this athlete I need a bullseye right here. You gotta do it quick
Almost hit the other one
That's a qualification right there
Yeah, if I just play like that i'll be fine
This is the final end let's try to hit the other target
This is the final end only two hours to go. I mean two hours to go
It seems like a long time
Damn, I can't get in that middle. It's magnetized
two arrows, oh
two hours
I thought I thought he said hours
All right, here comes. Okay, quality finally. Will this be can I finally qualify for two events?
Men's hiring finish cycling. Oh boy, this is gonna be interesting
This has been described as a
Is doug dopamine here? What his name is?
And dope six of the world's best trying to make it through to this olympic final. There's what is the name dope?
Doping doping. Yeah hasn't been a good event for team usa never once finishing on the podium in the three occasions. How does this work?
Oh, I can't go that way
repeatedly tap
Oh, yeah, you're gonna see
Hold down x to cruise
Oh, I see you use the stamina push
And hold to move
How many people are on the track when we do this?
Okay, I know how to steer
Sprinting uses stamina cruising regain stamina slipstream behind opponents to quickly regain stamina. All right
Am I all the way at the end just like bullying everybody
You ain't fucking passing me
This is what it sucks. That's why it sucks to be cold versus koopa
You ain't getting by me. You're getting by me. Good luck. I thought it was putting his hand throw punch
Performance is no denying that as we take another look at the isn't what i'm doing illegal
You can't do that
Let's take a check on the official results then following that race like I can get this
All right. This is this is where it counts
It's called blocking. It's illegal
Can I get two goals back to back?
They don't care
All right christen, let's go
I'm ready
Wait, what I can pump the crowd up. All right now I can't just whip it
Having seen the first arrow what adjustments will this athlete make here we go. All right
Good shot required to finish end one on the high
That's not wait. That's the exact same spot
That was the same arrow
It replaced the other one. Holy shit
Expected the united states make a strong start to this. Okay, I gotta be better
25 26. I gotta get that gold medal
I'm gonna pump the crowd up again. How do I do that square?
Still on a breathless day at lords
There it is
No wind
Yep
Hold back the points from the seven not bad. Let's see if we're good first place
Two more chances I can overtake it. I know I can
That's a ten that cream that top number
Oh, yeah
Let's get 30. I'll fall into first place. I'll get that gold medal. I can smell it. Oh, that's all right
More to the total for that
29 it's good. That's a good score
Three points ahead on the scoreboard do it again every wind here
That could have been that wind changed on me right when I was about to let go did you see that
Oh
It was seven did it change to seven? Oh man. That was a huge amount of fucking wind
Britain's gonna fuck it up
No, they're gonna have just as much trouble. I'm gonna be in first place still where we go first place. I told you gold medal
Those double tens back to back last round really saved it
Told you close
Close
Here we go here comes
Nice work kristen second gold medal
And
I completely forgot about the happy birthday shit
from the green screen day
Can you get a minus two permanently?
No
That's not you can't do that. It's the final of the men's care. All right. Remember the tactic here is fully
The goal here is
Square in the circle peg hole thing just get it in there futuristic approach to this like a baby toy
Specifically designed get the square just it's not supposed to fit but you're gonna get the square into the circle
It's in the shape of their lives and there's no reason why they can't go
To win a medal here
Am I getting booed just don't let him go by you wait, why is he taller? Why is he flying?
Do you see he's flying?
Did you see that? He like grew two times in size and was floating
It's another gold medal
Plenty of heart plenty of energy plenty of passion and most of all plenty of power. He almost came inside world
There we go, here it comes
Well, this is the moment where we can enjoy success and certainly they'll be doing that on the podium
Time for the national anthems to celebrate
Let's take a quick check on the overall medal tally three golds one bronze
That concludes things for the day no more events remaining in this session so from seth bennett and all the team
Will bid you a fond farewell skip skip skip you skipped
No, that's just
That's abbreviated
They look they abbreviated it already. So i'm just like I didn't I pressed x. I didn't know I was gonna skip it completely
I unlocked spain's outfit
cool, I guess
All right, what's next two events
Press stroke disc throw and weightlifting. Yeah
We need to do disc throw
Is there wrestling? I don't know. There's a lot
there is
45 different events and I think some of those are
25 meter 50 meter 100 meter, right? It's supposed to be 40 events
This throw i'm ready
Put it in 3d is one of the oldest events to feature in the olympic games. How does this work?
Push and hold r don't release the stick
When the ring appears push and hold r this way don't release r until all three
what
When the ring appears push don't really what the fuck are you trying to get me to do?
Okay, let's try that again
push this way
Okay, when the ring appears push the other way
Don't release it now. Okay, push this way
push this way
Push that way again push when the ring appears release r
Best throw flick when the yellow line is in the middle of the blue zone
Okay
Here we go certainly put the pressure on with germany lithuania and estonia all taking medals
That's all right. That's pretty good power and then
So it's a foul but here's the scoreboard and that tells its own story
This is qualifying i'll get it
round two
power lock flick it
I'm not gonna qualify i'm not gonna qualify
It's good
I have to really clean this up right now
Eighth place
I'm gonna do a high angle
That's what we call it's going out of the stadium
I just broke a record
That'll bring me back to like fourth place
That put me in first place
That apparently was so good that I went from eighth to first
I can't laugh
Don't laugh
All right, I qualify I qualify
The u.s.a
Power new
When I broke the olympic record in the qualifying round
Why can't I do that during the actual competition? Does it?
Shit
Hey, but I gotta make it count
You can hit 500 home runs
In the exhibition games, but in the playoffs if you go 0 for 10
That's what people remember
It's true. All right, here comes weightlifting
Over 155 kilograms
Here we go original one and two handlers at the first two olympic games
How does weightlifting work
Tap x you must build power above the indicator
Pull l and r down simultaneously
Push l and r up simultaneously not pushing straight loses power
All right
Tap x until the judges turn wild turn white what?
Oh the light, right?
Okay, you can only attempt three lifts. So make each one count
Try to lift as straight as possible for maximum power
The athlete will start to tremble when he's about to drop the bar
Okay, let's do it
Competing in qualifying in the weightlifting. It's the first round and this athlete has to choose what weight they want to come in on
Rack the whole thing
If he doesn't get this right, he'll be very disappointed
Couldn't get them to budge what strange effort that I was tapping x
What happened? You're gonna get a good idea as to exactly how this lifter feels tap x right successful with the first attempt
But will he throw more weight on the bar for round two?
What well doesn't manage to lift anything here do I have a timer of like two seconds
I want to lower the weight down
I don't okay. I'm trying to adjust the weight. It won't let me
Well, this is the final attempt for this athlete
Obviously the nerves are at an absolute premium here
Well, you can see the athlete very frustrated with that. You make it all the way to the olympics
And you say hey put put on like 500 pounds dude
Take it off an inch off the ground
Holy shit, that's so embarrassing. I want to should I redo it?
I couldn't even take any off
Retry token. No, no, no
It's all right. I got the disc throw
I was just tapping x why couldn't I
I wasn't doing anything else
It was like tap x to you till you get to the power and then you press down with both and up with both
I didn't get a chance to press down
Welcome to this beautiful
All right, here comes the guy with the world records what a value this is are you ready for this world record
Pump them up
The athlete will spin around as fast as possible before releasing the discus all two kilograms of it
Get that out of here. That's a perfect throw
Full power. I just broke I broke the world. That's a world record. I went I don't have to do anything else game over
Can I just leave
Can they okay?
Can we just stop the event just give me the gold medal I could watch the rest of the event
All right. Now I have to beat the world record that I just made nerves should be gone by now. This guy's a fucking maniac
Oh damn it
That world record
Nobody can do anything to catch this athlete now, I need 75
Can you imagine being in the olympics?
You train for 10 years to get here and the first guy that gets up for the first heat
Breaks the world record
You want to talk about just completely demoralizing?
I don't think i'll ever get past 70 for six
Justice is back full power break the record
oops
Sorry, it's still in play
Doesn't matter
I just i'm not gonna be able to do it. I'm just throwing it into the ground
Should I bm this is round number five then i'm trying to let it go. I'm just trying to drop it
All right, i'm going for it again
They're in first place
Y'all fuck off. Whatever. I got the record who cares
We just did olympic records
Let's have a look at the replay he's not even human
The approach really the release point great
And it just came down to the distance fantastic. Holy shit. That cameraman really is messing up
Like I took pictures two or three seconds after it landed. It's horrible
That's like two or three thousand milliseconds lag
Training
Next song celebrations will begin. Um, well, that's the end of the day plays if you win plenty more action to come
Okay, we got four gold medals
I want to take a look at the standard metal tally. Let's see
Oh, i'm just i'm killing
four
four golds
Javelin throw you got it. Absolutely
freestyle of swimming
kayaking
Okay
kayaking iking and javelin throw
Wait, do we get to use?
uh the record holder
I feel like if he if he could throw a disc that will
Just give him a javelin teach him that too
Yeah, any object that you just have to throw hard. It's really fun. Just teach him everything
Olympic games always has a strong dan. Okay
Oh boy
Have to begin running
Have to fill the bar
pull
push
The perfect angle is 35 degrees
Okay, I didn't have very much time to process that. Okay
Don't get that much time to do this
Starts the run now. What where's the foul line? What because I stepped over it after throwing this one
There's no point measuring it that throw won't because it's a foul if he goes in round number two
Get out of here. Come on
68 confirmation on the standings. I want to beat another world record
I can never reach that high again and it sucks. I want to do it
Beat the olympic record. Oh just personal best
Should be no nerves now in round number four
I fucked it up
Sorry, I'm still on the first place
Here we go again then in round five of the javelin I get it. All right, it's gonna get more speed
Okay
If you had to stand out there and just stand with your arms to your sides and stand straight up and not move at all
And this dude got three attempts to throw the javelin at you
Would you do that for a hundred grand?
Do you think he would be that accurate to get you? I don't know. I feel like it'd be hard to be that accurate
It's a lot of money. Yeah, yeah, because yo you have to stand still. Yeah
And there's there's like an operation style device that's on your body that if you move it goes
And then just did the 100 grand is removed disqualified. So we're gonna come down to this the delivery
36 degrees
Washed up don't throw so early. It's freaking me out because I stepped over the line once good technique
absolutely rock solid technique
I just gotta get one or two good ones. That'll be good
All right, here comes kayaking this one's gonna be interesting
If he gets too close, i'll just move. Yeah, you can just be like, all right, whatever i'm gonna take
This looks pretty cool
Wait, did more than one person do this event at the same time?
Isn't that kind of dangerous? Why is this like a mario kart level?
Is it like this?
Until the final big drop big man. Let's have a look at everybody. I didn't even do the tutorial. Oh, yeah, I did
Okay l is used to propel and turn
hold while turning
Hold x and boost forward
Paddle downstream through the green and white holes to successfully complete
Hold well to paddle past the red and white holes uptrend gates must be completed while moving back to the course
Hold r2 to plant the paddle
quickly turn
Right towards the gate
Turn and paddle upstream between the red and white bulls
struggling a little later
Leave the athlete
Uh, there's eight people here. It's gonna be a mess
Wait, am I cheating what happened? Why do I have a 10 second head start?
What hold on am I gonna get a penalty for that?
It's a tricky approach into ben nevis here
Have to slow down to get through that gate
What is just me
Is to stay dry through this upstream gate
While this gate proved to be a little problematic, but now what are you talking about?
Completely missed altogether great great comes this athlete
Did I duck under it I'm sorry, it doesn't matter what game it is
Is
It's just all I think of is connect whenever I see a kayak or any water sport for that matter
Just just connect this is microsoft connect presents minigame. That's all I think of is just minigame microsoft connect. That's it
And it sucks because this is a really difficult thing to do. This is really hard
This is like a really just grueling sport
And it has been dropped in my brain too
Funny connect game
That's all right, I did all right
Brilliant
Does not look brilliant does not look like a guy that knows that he's doing this looks like you just took a guy
From the audience and put him in here
Oh pretty good time for somebody that we just pulled from the subway
We gave him 50 dollars
He said go for it
Well, this is the final scoreboard holy shit, I did really really well
Well team USA with this is the important one here
Am I is this olympic little league?
Am I in competition with like 13 year olds?
Everybody literally sucks at kayaking. It doesn't matter how good you actually are does it athletes all come through the qualifying rounds
All right, I gotta get a good one
This is for the medal attempt number one that good speed
Good angle and that's a snapshot moment
Right underneath the olympic record damn
Comes to a close a little too early
A huge lead in this one
This is the second round. Why is that so slow? This looks very good
Well, that's going to be a foul needs to stop before the line
Why did I fall down?
A wonderful performance so far and the results on the scoreboard are just as electrifying
They know it's a terrific terrific lead that this athlete takes from here
Third round of the javelin now
I fell down. Is it a foul if you fall?
But he just looks stupid
Midway through this event and the USA are in first place
Throw it straight i'm trying
Fourth attempt this two more remain
Oh, this is bad
Who cares just throw it on whatever that was a horrible one, but
You won't get close to his personal best with 50 community subs from who suck mick jones
Thanks for the 50 subs
That's insane on the scoreboard 50 community sub
One's for you. You ready?
This one's for the 50 subs. I'm going to break the fucking world record right here
Next one goes up. It's high and it's long
Not quite the right trajectory though
Not a great throw. We only need one to win
Okay, this is it. I'm gonna break it at least their olympic record later
Six and final round then for this athlete
Nope, it wasn't going fast enough shit. Sorry
He's in 50 subs
That's still gold medal I still win
Here is the replay
Let's take a look at that big one again. Yeah right below the olympic record
That line right there. Damn it
This works strong damn
Nice work
Well
I just I didn't mean to skip it. I pressed x way too early and I skipped it accidentally
Time for the gold medal and kayaking
Don't worry, we're gonna hear it right here because i'm gonna get the goddamn gold medal
All right, come on kevin
Come on kevin, let's go
Well, that shows the control of the kayak the way this athlete's leaning leaning very hard to one side here
Moving nicely through the first time check
Well, the next gate is against the current it's upstream
Made hard work of that gate
Completely and utterly missed that gate. All right, we're good through two sections
Clean through that last gate
Well, this is all about timing through the oval
Come on needs to keep on top of the white water through this upstream gate
Did well to get through that gate
There will be some disappointment because this athlete has picked up a few penalties here
Maybe this athlete can take some consolation out of a good final section
Needs to improve on the performance so far
This is the last big drop of the course. It's a big bet
Well, it took an awful lot of hard working effort, but eventually got through that. Yeah, that's a finish
That's gotta be decent
Well, it's a good start to this one very very smooth going down the road
Negotiating some of the hazards very well here
Looks good looks very good at this stage
Not at all time to paddle powerfully not even close
This is good. What's bad?
Oh the smoothness is just absolutely smooth
Any medal is a good medal when you come to the olympic games and the celebrations of this athlete will tell you exactly that
Oh bronze medal
What was it? What was your score?
What was the score? Why didn't see what was the score?
What was the score I want to I want to see the score I want to see the actual score
What brings to a close another fantastic day of competition here at the lee valley whitewater center
I hope you've enjoyed it as much as me from seth bennett
God damn it
I wanted to see how much time they had against me
Let's take a look here. We got
The united states china's got two gold medals now
two bronze medals
Bronze are gonna mad up in the end
100 women's skeet
And i'm gonna do the breaststroke
This is definitely just tap as fast as possible
But no way it's not
That's all you need to know
I don't know why I was like looking at the other monitor over here for a second
I thought they were all naked like actual just completely butt naked. I was like what the hell
And then all right. Yeah, they're with a little underwear
How does this work?
go
die
Tap x repeatedly while underwater
Hold down to swim
Square press the correct button the final boost press x at the end of the race to lunge for the wall
Time each stroke to when both arms are fully extended to build the most speed
All right
Go lance
Press x a knowledgeable push descends. No, what if you lunge hard and slam into the wall?
What oh
Focus there's the l and r up here
This just reminds me of those old shows where you know talk about the
You got the hot dog eating contest the guy with the bear
This is like this is like the man versus the otter
And we make sure we give the otter. Well, let's take a final look five seconds before
I got five second head start on the otter. I was the otter out of the olympic games in this event
Not good. I'm afraid for team usa
Bears shouldn't eat hot dogs. No, they really shouldn't tell that to like late 90s television
They thought they sure thought it was real funny
All right, i'm gonna do this well
Oh shit
I'm gonna do so well here
The reticule will shrink when the targeting to hit track the targets move before shooting for the best result
I'll always shoot the yellow target first
Okay petition these athletes equally match not much between them
Well, here we are on station one first up the single
Almost blew that one
Here comes a double let's have a look on the double whatever
Locked in the shooting. Come on. I gotta do this. Well only one
Fuck I missed out with that last shot
Looking for the double hit
That's tricky
Just a single right what happened it
Just didn't react fast enough to that first target I think it's the r2 is messed up. I really mean that
It's a good round and there's no doubt now
That this competitor can have the confidence that they can keep up with the leaders here
I feel like that's a weird way to hold a gun. It's like let it rest on your shoulder
Ah, it's a bit disappointing that's open like that from the high house
Well station number four asks a lot of the shooters first a high single then a low single followed by
That's how you hold a rifle you have it like open like that over your shoulder
Yeah, I can't say i've ever held a rifle before in my life, but what the hell did I know this is the double
I think I got the hang of it
Just got to wait stay in the middle and see where it goes two more targets still to hit
It came out fast very fast
You're saying hog
There's another one
First close i'll give it to you
If you close your eyes block your ears and yell really loud I guess it's pretty close
The person in last place only hit one target did they
Yeah, they did
What's the excuse there? Do you think?
I think the next day you fake an illness right the next day after the olympics you go like god turns out
Yeah, I got I had like fucking wicked bad diarrhea
Yeah, I was like I had like I was like wicked fucking sick with diarrhea and shit
Like this that's that's what I would do like I tried my best right?
But I mean I was feeling terrible
If you say wicked again, I will sub for real that'd be wicked cool if you did
And i'll stop station number eight
Nope
All right now let's make it really happen give a solution to any social issue just saying he has diarrhea
That's an incredibly easy to understand thing
There's no nuance there. It's just
I have diarrhea
You don't have to explain that you don't have to tell anybody anything. It is no beginning. There's no middle. There's no end. There's only
Diarrhea everybody understands it
And it's a thing that nobody wants to question either
First up station number one, although be careful using it that often next up. It's the double high house first
Oh, I thought I missed it
That's good, I like it
Or if you hit one, you know
I mean if back in the day when there wasn't really any cameras here
I would just say I tried to do with my eyes closed. Oh, all right. Damn. Holy shit. Yeah, I tried
I got one that's impressive
Put him on the screen
Putting the pressure on at the top of the scoreboard, but there are two or three others that are very close by
Yeah, this uh
Anna and it's really close
Oh, I dropped it. Well, that was close
Station three at the double. All right, we're good. You can miss one. It's okay
Good execution on that round
Re three three
She's been perfect. All right, I gotta be perfect here
I want that gold medal
Well, this is a biggie station number four
six targets in total to aim for
Take the board down omega lul losing omega lul losing you're losing to norway
Oh looking for the double on station four
I'm gonna don't i'm gonna delete those channel points if you keep using them
This is the double don't do it. Have you guys even seen the new emotes yet?
This place at the midway point for team usa and things definitely going to plan
Can we see the new emotes please? I want to do the diving competition
I feel like I would be really good at that one. What can she do on this double?
That was good. That was clean
I I really I ran away with it here 17 to 13
I can relax
Yeah, it's all right. I can miss
German punching or why are you doing the punching shit? This is the double low house first
This looks like a lot of fun
It's the end of the round now on the scoreboard has a really but is it weird that I don't want a rifle
I want a plate shooter
I want to shoot the clay plates with clay plates
Like tribes. Yeah
I just I want to try to play this shooter gun
Try to hit the other that'd be awesome. Well, it's been a good performance for the usa. That'd be so hard
And this is a shotgun. Yeah, but I I don't I want a plate gun
Somebody that knows explain it to me. I thought shotguns were
really low range
There are two targets here on offer that can be hit. Will it be enough though to win a medal? This is station number eight
It's just a big spread don't they just the pellets all spread out like all over the place
I guess that's kind of the point
That's just video game logic
Really?
I thought that you shot like this like
Bird shot
It blows up out of the gun and it just goes
Oh, that's cool. It's called bird shop because they shoot birds in the air
How can I live in america and not know anything about guns?
I don't know. I don't I don't like use them
Just because just because you're in america doesn't mean that
I have like four shotguns
And these moments will be captured and will be on the front pages of the papers in the morning I got six gold
terrific performance
I've kicked a gun before
That seems like a bad idea
I'm, not sure that's smart. We got high jump
Table tennis. Oh, yeah, this is gonna be great. I can't wait
And it's really high jump. How does high jump work? You just jump as high as you can somebody measures it
I don't think i've ever seen this
Wait, is this thing where they jump they arch their back and they like slime their legs around the bar
This thing's insane if this is what I think it is
Yep, this is yep. This is it
Fill the bar
Those these ones are so hard to do flick when the athlete reaches the white marker
Press x to kick your legs and avoid the bar
60 degrees is perfect jump
Right
Nobody can jump over that nobody can jump over this. This is like 15 feet high. How big is this?
Who the fuck was able to do that
Having under the bar only gets you onto the outtakes of this olympic games
Here's the replay
Well, here we go attempt number three looking for better things. I can't lower it
What the fuck?
Welcome huge disappointment for team usa
This is the olympic stadium welcome one of the most sustainable ever built the low ball is set into the existing landscape
Well, wait, the world record is 209
Why did I think I could jump over 2.6 if the world record?
Is 209
Why are you even allowed to put it this high?
You got to be kidding me. All right, i'm coming down
to
171 80
There it is
That was close I could have gone a little higher which country you want to win the gold medal in this event
You've got to respect the stuff that athletes made to this competition 190. Let's go
Is this the poker event in the olympics? Let's go
Oh, I got it
I'm going i'm going for 210
First place a stunning start to this competition really laying down the benchmark for everyone else to follow
Oh shit, what happened? I didn't even see a replay
Nice approach why can I not lower it?
After three rounds not they're not gonna give me any fanfare for that. I just beat the I just did the world record
I can't lower it. Wait, once I beat the world record everyone's like no, no, no, no, you gotta go higher
No one's gonna be able to do this
Anybody else has street of this sport until five minutes ago record attempt
Is a good take we gotta go higher than that. Come on man
A stutter in the run-up will have cost this athlete
No chance of going clear when you hit the bar that hard
This is a limbo, you know, you have to go over rather than under the bar
Here's the replay. I just imagine like
You head off the side of the bar
Again, this is world record in the qualifiers, right?
I didn't win anything
All right, as long as I continuously clear two
I'm gonna start at one
They've moved on nicely through to the olympic tennis event i'm intrigued by this one
This is the excel london and next up the semi-finals of the men's table tennis
I love ping pong. It's I love it. I'm terrible at it
I consider going back and forth three times a victory before somebody goes. Oh too hard goes into the ceiling
Whoops, just get it again, man. We'll do it again
Going one two three. Oh, that was fun. I don't know how people do it that hard
I don't know if the star does this shit
Just like the didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't I can't even I can't see that fast
I can't even see that fast. It's impossible
Push it for a straight top spin
Aim to the left. So it's just timing
Aim to the right
It's for backspin
Oh, you can move press r quickly rotate towards r to add right spin
Okay, I need to read seven points with a two-point lead
Usa versus france peter ko. Oh peter ko. Okay, I made this name for a second
It's a great reception here for our two competitors slows the rally down with a side spin
Oh what happened
Come on this is so awkward. Okay
Starting to build
Fantastic backhand I get it
Hit the corner of the table. They hit the corner of the table. I got the corner
Let's be taking a battering. It's another point lost. This is the resident evil tank controls
They're like killing me
It's right across the table with a forehand. Just don't get yourself into trouble got a one by two. Remember that's important to remember
So the rally's starting to take shape
Fantastic rally kept alive. Why are we both treating this like it's a bug flying around the room you're getting away from me
Shit by my face
Yeah, we're paying 10. Got him
Does anybody else feel like the table should be raised like a full foot we're really hunching down here
beautifully on the backhand side
Places the ball with the backhand. Oh, did you see that curve to win the point at this?
Wait, how did I get that correct?
Oh, yes, oh did he get it on the edge you mother fucker. No, we did not
Help he cannot you gotta win by two points
Oh shit the camera thing
Fuck i'm sorry
So the rally really starting to take shape
But he really needs to focus now. Here we go with the first serve of the second game
All right, let's say all right this i'm talking about look at how high the guy on the right's chair is
Why don't they just put a couple of books underneath the table to make it be like four or five inches higher
We're all like leaning down here. Is it why does it have to be this low?
That's not good
Yeah, I yeah, I know I said it first that means I I can say it's fine I can say it first
Why am I acting like this
Look at the way that i'm volleying this back and forth
I don't get it. So i'm trying
It's too weird. It's too weird. It's fucking weird. It's weird. All right, it's weird
Yeah, let me explain this
Okay, imagine this is a gta 5 mini game that you can pull up to right?
That's how this feels like to play it feels like this is a gta 5 game. You know, let's put golf in
Let's put like this in yeah, this was this was like, yep. Yep. Yep
Take all blame away from me
And this is where we come back
What a shame he's trailing here and the difference between the two players is getting bigger
How do you miss that why are you just like swatting at it for some answers?
Why that was so just violent and just incorrect the serve is crucial
Pressure on they take the point. Where can they go from here point now? Can they get that place moved back?
The olympic action from here for the moment seth benet will now wrap up the results
You only get so many world records for the day, okay
Okay
We need I have the I currently have the world record
My world it's 210. Why does nobody care that the record's 210?
We're starting at one nine. We're starting at two
Looking for a solid effort here and go no one's ever gonna do that. I'm the only one on earth that can do that
Now I have
at least
Four or five attempts to break my world record
This is the current record while this bar is getting ever so high now
This would require a great lead you stupid asshole to get this world record
I have the world record. What do you mean get the world record? I currently have it
Yeah
The heel
Who cares kicking any point at the world record I got the world record last time why nobody care about this
All right, I got seven medals i'm doing very good men's table tennis
I
Am I in the finals for the men's table tennis? I just got beat
absolutely horrible
Why am I in the final?
I still qualified
I'm done
Why did I qualify well take advantage of it take advantage just like the fucked up rules just let's try to win
Take that it shouldn't be it should be legal
Shouldn't like the white should not it shouldn't be painted white. I don't know to keep the rally going
Wow, that backhand what a joy to watch
It's a real mess of that back. All right, that was like a wiffle ball
Forehand back across the net
Backhand will test his opponent
Oh, he's gonna be disappointed with that forehand
He seemed a long way out of position there. There was just no way he was gonna return it
It
A little shimmy. Oh, okay rally starting to build
It's the forehand back over the net
Forehand keeps the rally. Yeah
Damn it. Well, his opponent was just simply too good for him there and he'll lose the point
There we go. All right, I got I can I can beat this enjoying it as much as the crowd are
But he will take the confidence from that point
Nope, nope, nope, it's tagging
First x for a special. I don't think I have spent one. It's not real
Starting to get into the game as the rally starts building there is definitely no argument there at all
He wins the point with that fantastic play
I don't know why I keep going for but you have to
This rally really starting to take shape now
Using his backhand spike it a fantastic forehand there
Loses the point there with that play
Oh the stupid plastic ball in on the other idiot's side
Good job. What are you saying?
Wait, is this just like a complete just you just tearing ping pong apart. Yeah spike it plays the forehand there
Forehand keeps the game in play
I'll be disappointed with that forehand
All right spike it
I need one more point and I win and he start to really build a significant lead now got it. Yes
Wait, is this just going to be a straight how many games do I have to play?
How many games of table tennis do I have to play?
That's the three but it but who is this are we the two best in the world or is this just for like seventh place?
How does this work looking to force the errors? Is this for bronze?
I'll get it
This rally really starting to take shape now. There it is. Good. He's got to be pleased with that the point is
Does this look like the work of the best in the world? No, it does not
I did really well there to force his opponent sara. He'll take the point with that
Can I take the bronze medal and then just say i'm done?
I don't even want the gold one. You just gives this. I don't even want to attempt. It's gonna go in the stands into play
Asking the questions with a backhand
What an incredible rally the crowd are really loving this to see he wins the point there with some fantastic approach play
That was awesome
How did I do that with my backhand? I did it with the other side of the panel
I really is starting to play to the crowd now and they are responding. What a fantastic point one
Ah
Thought it was going out of bounds. He just couldn't return it successfully
No speed lost on the ball there with the backhand
What a fantastic point here we go then serving for that. This is it. Can he take it? I will take it
I didn't get to the head
And he'll lose that point
This is waving to somebody in the crowd. What was that?
So the rally really starting to take shape
Really can't afford to lose any focus now with this rally
This is the point going to come from in this rally
What about this is the point of all of this?
Shit come on i'm starting to get into the game as the rally starts building
Both players really matching each other now with this rally
Give me that bronze
Give me the bronze
Is it
I came in first I came in third place
Bronze medal
Appreciate how hard they've worked. I'm just realizing the name of the stream is called silver medals and I don't have any
I have three bronze medals like six gold medals
Well, this place is rocking
And quite rightly so
The sheer joy and ecstasy on his face
Tells you everything you need to know about how much winning
All right, let's go
Let's take a look at the tallies here
China
18 the dude getting a lot of silvers
I gotta start to be ready here
women's
springboard
men's 100 men's 400
no, uh
butterfly
100 100 sprint. Yeah, we'll do the 100 sprint and this is the diving. I can't wait
You own two of the 23 possible world records
I'm ready
I want to do the high this is not the high dive though, is it? No
I'm in three meters springboard. Here comes gold medal gwen. We gotta get the gold medal
That's x to begin the dive
Let's circle to enter a tough somersault
And then hit it again
Then hit down
I wish eleanor to rotate the athlete
To get the perfect splash
Okay
Yeah, it's all about the splash
We're square down
Well, this is quite hard not the most difficult
I help but wonder whether this diver has been affected by nerves. It is always a big thing to compete in olympic games
Almost a full-on belly flop. Take a look at the replay, but i'm sure the diver won't want to
They know just how badly wrong they got it low marks difficulty taken out of the equation because of the incorrect dive
All right, we're gonna do
Oh shit, okay square is it square immediately needs to compose herself. What the fuck is going on?
That one quickly get it straight out of her mind and move on
It hurts so bad
Here's the replay
The twist was good. But after that
Everything else just went wrong a massive splash of water and that's one of the telltale signs that the dive didn't quite go to
Japan
You would be feeling that for months
Okay, let me try this one more time
We're just gonna do the easy one
I have to qualify
circle down
I don't i'm not
Look
There's no way i'm gonna have enough to qualify. This has got to be fucking incredible. Here we go
Square square. Well, this is quite risky one of the tougher dives in the competition
Oh, yeah, i'm screaming
No splash that's gonna be tens
All right, do another really difficult one
Here we go
This thing is impossible
A few errors in there and there will be points that are lost here
It's so funny. It's not even that funny, but it just is for some reason i'm trying
Okay, wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute that was fucking awesome
That was incredible
I don't get extra points for doing something a human can't do
Okay
These are the final standings
It's an unlikely defeat for team usa. I'm sure the athlete will be extremely disappointed with the performance
Well
No, I can't retry. I can't I gotta tag swallow the loss
Those retries are for Olympic level competition
The old metal gwen doesn't qualify. Oh, you're gonna have to go get that name changed
So this is just run as fast as you can yeah, I think yeah, I did this already
Yep, I'll I got this
What do you think should I do a two three second head start five second head start be a total asshole?
These athletes are so close in their ability
run backwards
Try and get an early win in this I see later you fucking toads
Wait, doesn't doping dan already have the gold medal in the 100
Are we doing this again?
Does everything so well here look so smooth quickly into stride and then it's a case of 200. Oh
Nobody can even
I'm gonna go what's the world record i'm going for it
nine point two six
nine point five
Nine point five eight
Let's get it right now
Nine point five eight whole of these games are we gonna see a world record?
Yep, you are
Who still wants it with 50 meters to go
And this really has been bought to life the jewel of the olympic crown
These are out of their blocks in the 100 meters final
No lunging just run just forest gump style running forward
Just don't even stop just keep going
Let's have another look at this then a brilliant performance from start to finish just look great
Through every phase of this race
So strong with every stride and then when it came down to winning it made sure that he was high schoolers have better personal best
And 9.94 the world record is 9.58. You say me tell me high school track and field goes to france with a hard
Competers are the world records all the way. I just based this on myself
I did the mile in 16 minutes
And I just kind of walked back in high school when they timed it
I think I actually one year. I really did try
I really got ready for it
Oh, I got put like in a wheelchair and like threw up behind a tree. I remember this have I told the story
I did the
You remember when you high school used to kind of track?
They did like the
Everybody's school had the different track and field
It was like a presidential and there were two different tiers of your health
And it was how far can you reach how many times can you do a pull-up?
How many push-ups can you do you guys know this?
Right, so it was during that it was anything under I believe eight minutes the mile
Anything under eight or nine minutes, I believe was eight was considered really good
One year, I really truly wanted to do it. Well
And I got ready every day. I was
Just trying to eat better and I wanted to try to stay loose
And if finally the day came that we were going to do it
And I really gave it my all
I was running the whole time. I tried to get it under seven minutes
I believe I got of somewhere around seven minutes the mile
And then after I was so winded and so fucked up that I I everyone was going back was gym class. Everyone was leaving
And I was the world started closing in
I just kind of sat down for a second. There was the bleachers there at the time where my high school was
just kind of sat and hung out there and the
Physical education teacher came over
And she said are you all right? You're doing okay. You're doing all right. I'm just like yeah fine
I'm fine. I'm fine
And I ended up getting up a little bit and I ended up puking behind a tree
I was like, hold on a second
I put my hand on a tree and I just went behind it and I puked behind it
And she saw it and she was like, oh shit
I didn't say shit, but you know, i'm just paraphrasing
and
She said where you can you move or can you walk and I had to sit down
Maybe four or five feet away from where I just threw up with my back against another tree
And it's just like I I got it I can't I gotta sit here for a few minutes
So they went and got a wheelchair and put me in the wheelchair
And she wheeled me through the high school
And i'm just like i'm fine. I'm fine everybody. I'm all right. I'm okay. I'm okay
And then finally like I got some water but just going down the hallway like with her pushing me in a wheelchair
It must have been just so strange to see me doing that
and then
I got some water and I went to
Math class with a little note that just said hey this dude
I don't know what it said probably two teachers talking to each other probably just like dude this dude just fucking puked behind a tree
It's okay that he's like eight minutes late
Like dash like holy shit talk to you at lunch and they probably talked a lot of they probably talked shit about me and stuff
I bet they did
He's got a golden what?
china
I got um, it's getting close
All right, we're gonna do the 400 meter. We're gonna do the 100 meter butterfly
Wait, we said last time
You said you did it because that last time you had to run a mile you couldn't because your nutsack was all fucked up
Yeah, that's true
That's actually true
I had I had
It's true. I did I told you that what did I tell you that?
I told you guys about like my like
What did I told you about that?
I went to the doctor and like I was I was I thought I had they thought they had so I had some called like a
testic appendix
And like my balls hurt all the time
I when did I tell you that did I actually tell i've been around for way too long
All right. I got this
It's your doctor. He screams now. He told us well, that'd be really weird if my doctor when I was like 15 was screaming right now
All right, I gotta really do well
Do well
He tried finding other words right onto the line really as now the athletes take to their blocks
As they emerge from the water, we see the early leaders
All eight athletes very very close through 25 meters
And now can they lead from gun to the final touch
Tumble turn and a strong kick off the wall. I gotta be doing really well here
The record record olympic record
I can do better than that
Who cares guys I have to have something to brag about for the next three months
I'm going to play the game. They go like 10 gold medals and they did like three four world records
I need this
Here we go ready state of the arts 80,000 in capacity and beautiful on the eye
Is a good performance running strongly approaching the end of the first hundred meters
This is not even i'm not even winded I just had a bad day i'm thinking about something really sad
Do I have to finish?
Am I gonna get past do they have to wait for me to finish?
I hope so
I have to go few behind a tree
Is the ground really hot?
Am I walking around in bare feet?
Hey quick somebody get the wheelchair for him. He went way too hard in the first 10 seconds
It's silent
Yes
Watch the replay. I don't know if I want to watch the whole replay
Why are they playing? What's this music?
Does that break the game?
They won't even show me
It was loading the replay, oh jeez
I almost want to do that whole thing and not even come off the
Just don't even start
And just see how long the timer will count
Do you think it'll count do you think the game was ever programmed to be like, oh is somebody going to sit here for 10 minutes?
Has seen periods of dominance for the usa in germany australia. Let's go for the world record double defending champions
Two lengths and about 50 seconds separates this athlete from olympic glory
From the water and the early leaders show their heads
Still some distance to go but at 25 meters the early leaders in control
Stroke for stroke she's striving for glory
Strong king in the top usa in second is china in third place canada
Three quarters of the race come as we enter the closing stages
World record 56 56
What is it? Oh
In this one who was gonna win utter domination from start to finish
It's one second ahead of that, uh, I got the olympic record already in the qualifier
Enjoy that nine gold medals
I think this is the last day
Did we even see all the events? I don't think we even saw the events
This is not good
I've got to this last day. I've got to get two medals or i'm gonna lose first place
Women's freestyle and women's 100 freestyle. Oh shit. Yeah, I gotta make these good
China's in second place. I've got to keep it that way
Well, there's so much at stake here and only a tiny amount of time for these athletes to show exactly what they can do
Wait, this is just is on. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. All right. Let's go. Let's get a qualify
Look to the middle lanes for the fastest swimmers
Great start
I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it
All right
I was just doing the thing where you play any game with anybody under the age of five
You let them win and then you kind of catch up and then you wait I lost
Braces, this is bad. No china didn't win. Not yet
Here it comes
Old medals right now
Here we go. Then the athletes are ready
Starting to take shape as we reach the quarter point now starting to stroke well at the quarter point
Not strong enough here
What are you doing at the timing on the kick that was required but still just about hanging off in second place
Start to hurt as we enter the final 25 meters
The moment for the united states seems to be drowning pretty much did go wrong technique just falling apart
Breathing patterns nowhere near didn't quite come up to the performance level we expected
These the final standings though
Well disappointment for the usa a surprising result as they don't qualify for the final with that
Yes, we still in first place
Yes
We still get why do we get first if we're tied with the same amount of points?
Continues to burn here at the olympic stadium in london, but it has been a quite terrific games
The performances have been every bit what you'd expect from the biggest show in the world of sport
So many iconic landmarks that have just become part and parcel. I want to do the other events. There's a bunch of other events
Really brought to the table the flags wave in celebration after so many good performances
Old takes priority
The nations coming together as one for the last time at the 2012 games
The city has hosted this magnificently and this closing ceremony really does signify how the whole of the world has come together here
This is on medium hard has been unlocked
What is that structure i've seen in the background a bunch of times that what's that what's that structure the heart and soul of these games
the red one
That thing right there
We kept it kept on like showing that from different angles
And go deep into the london night, I thought that was a roller coaster
Thank you for joining us
I was in the distance. I was like, wait, what is that? I thought it was a roller coaster
Oh, it was like, oh, there's like a park over here. There's like wherever the stadium in london is
It's not big ben
All right. Hold on. Let's say events play
Here we go
diving
men's three meter men's 10 meter
men's synchronized
What is that? What do you mean synchronized?
field
Long jump. We didn't do shot put
Crack we didn't do hurdles either
All right. I want to do hurdles
hurdles
uh
Triple jump and shot put yeah
Let's see. What else do back backstroke?
I think i'm pretty good at that. Uh, what else is there in here?
Okay, I want three meter
10 meter
three meter
And then we'll okay. That's what that's okay. Let's go
on hard
Pair as individuals or pair up into national teams
What either two or four players must join?
Why can I do individual?
Oh, because it's okay. Okay, right because it's a synchronized
This is the synchronized shit can't be in here
Take them off
Okay, no synchronized
I'm now what diving that's diving shooting rapid fire ski
I already did those archery
All right, you know already did gymnastics men's trampoline men's vault
other sports
skulls
I have no idea what skulls is
Do weightlifting again? I will
Let's do these ones first. I already beat the game. I don't have to do it again. We're doing just the extra stuff
Hurdles, I actually want to do some of my theories
Okay, so how a doping dan obviously he's got two or three gold medals, so how does this work?
Okay, press x
You tap same way you do all the other ones
Press as you approach the hurdle
Body bounce off of it. I get it. See if I can beat them all let me say you're gonna play fall guys. Yes
Just not today
We'll do that probably next we'll do that probably on monday
Plan on monday afternoon fall guys
Well, here we go then a great ovation for all eight athletes, but now so
Good start to this and that's vital in the field of this standard
50 meters to go
This is much harder than it looks
So much to analyze
The stride was choppy. It wasn't smooth
They didn't really get into rhythm and come the final few meters were nowhere really to be seen
How far he's his legs are just spreading there. What the hell has a cool car. All right, whatever
Next event
Usually three steps then jump the timing is half the battle. Yeah, I probably feel like it'd be very difficult
What's his next one? I don't remember
Well, the conditions triple jump right for some long distance jumping here. It's the triple. What the hell does this work?
Mm-hmm. So then you go
run
Wait, oh this is oh, this is uh, this is a mario thing you get to go like what?
Right, I get it
That wasn't bad gonna call me on fault
Not terrible not awful
Yeah, thanks for saying everything I said
He's too hard
This meter makes no sense
Thirdly through this competition
Needs to do well here, it's all right. I did that was like something
This is not even it's impossible
Probably gave away too much distance early on
The seventh after that round and the scoreboard confirms there's still plenty of work to do early
Well, this is the final attempt for this athlete
That's got to be at least worthy of anything
That's worthy of something
Thanks a stunning jump
Not doing so well to start
That was dumb. I don't want to do that one anymore shot. Now. This is what i'm talking about. I'm ready for this
This is where I make my money
rapidly tap x
Push not throwing straight loses power push up perfect throwing it was 35 degrees
All right
Can you fall over
What happened there
The leaderboard says it all seven trying to get it just great
I got four more chances. Come on
Don't make me laugh don't make me fucking laugh
All right, I gotta I can't look at chat
Performance is reflected on the scoreboard with a low showing accordion
Wait for the angle i'm i'm trying to i'm I know i'm waiting
When it comes down
35 right i'll get it
35 is a perfect angle
Oh
It looks like he's on the phone
Last chance to get world record. I already got the olympic record. I gotta get the world
To go new olympic record
See it quick across the circle and then explosive as the shot went flying high into the air
Great how much of those little shot putt balls away?
On final check on the standings then what an event this has been have to be really heavy
They're 16 pounds
Wow
That's dense
That's insane. There's plenty of tension in our 100 meter backstroke
Well, here we go this athlete's one of the favorites in this competition
You start in the water
Into the stroke now as they emerge from the water pulling hard through the water at 25 meters
So nearly halfway and it could be better for this athlete
That's a strong push as the athletes come towards the surface. It's very close at the front
in first place
come on
I didn't choke. It was I got to the end. I realized I was in third fourth place and I just gave up here
We go finally we get to see me the real me
I was wrong will the big splash on entry have cost him dearly
The entry was poor. Let's take a look at the replay. He's dead
Good elevation nice tuck
But when it came to stretching out
Big splash is the body doesn't go in quite on the straight and again that will be reflected in the scores
Ambitious is he gonna be with this attempt? I got it. This is backwards. Well, this is the toughest guy that he could possibly have chosen
Certainly can improve on that second round performance
I keep thinking of the accordion. It's fucking messing me up. I could just see the tiny little errors
No doubt there are a few nerves as the scores start to come in god damn it. All right, come on
Team usa needs to pick this one up. They've not been very good so far. They're back in seventh
Well, it's pulled out of that dive
Excuse me
There will be another opportunity needs to compose himself here
Well, not bad
I don't
Let's take a look at the replay a degree of difficulty and well executed
That was not bad. What about the judges? What's their view on seven seven seven eight eight? Yeah, that was good
So after that round six places what this athlete's looking at is not ideal
But at least it's two places above the bottom
This is a big moment a really really tough arcadum five community subs. What's going on arcadum? Thanks to the five subs
You guys don't know arcadum. I could do not know arcadum. It would be nice. That was a really fucking goddamn
Dungeon master i've ever seen in my life
Go check them out. That's the kind of performance. Thanks for the five subs dude if you're doing well
Is over to the judges to get their view on this
The dnd god himself. That's true. Let's have a look at the leaderboard and team usa are in fourth place
Does it get 10?
Wait, I got a 10. No way. Wait, can I can I get somebody clip that? I want to watch it
I didn't even see it. What happened?
I got tens across the board
Holy shit taking those more difficult dives as this competition goes on
Well, this is an ambitious bold and brave choice can this athlete do it? Oh seriously, thanks arcadum
we're playing uh
We're playing olympic games
And I beat everything
I don't know what just happened, but that was fucking 10
That was 10 had to be this that was unbelievable. That was the best thing i've ever done
Of a belly flop i'm afraid to say check this shit up took the big risk and it didn't come off on this occasion
Not a good gamble as we look at the replay
Well, the judges will have their say now
Here's the scoreboard team usa have to adjust
I'm trying it's left and right on the d-pad, right?
But just a shame the end didn't quite match the start with that dive
Whatever. Let's have a look how the judges rated it
That's fine. We didn't I who gives a shit about the three meter i'm with a 10 meter
He's a pc gamer. He doesn't know what his stick is. I it's I know this is the one I wanted to do
Here's the huge one, this is the high dive
Wait, how do you do this?
What's a frustration I think in the end a shake of the head
I
Just had like a party in college
Check this shit out
No, no, no bob. Don't do it. I'm gonna do a big one
I'm going off the roof
Get him off the fucking roof. Don't I don't want him on my fucking my roof
They're currently sitting last place. That was a 10 difficulty
Only this athlete knows i'm gonna give you a few minutes
It's gonna take you a long time to get over this image. I think
Didn't like that at all and pulled out just in time
I'm afraid to say that was nowhere near the best from the diver from the usa
God damn it
Not enough asian not enough strength also seem a little bit out of sync the entry into the water will cost some valuable points
I'm trying to down the timing of that dive a shake of the head in frustration and understandably so
Just do i'm hurting him
Didn't achieve what he set out to there
I'm just doing the easy one
Fourth dive must select a good one here
To cram all of that into the routine but not quite why is this guy in the olympics as he would have wanted
I don't know. It's like it's like the commission his son is the replay
This one of the more simple dives
And this athlete really had to execute on this
Let's take another look at the scoreboard. I want to try something
Massively difficult this dive forgettable. That was a forgettable performance
What was wrong with that
Here's the replay and this diver may want to look away now
That was just like dropping an action figure that will cost dearly off your tree house
It is the pool
Team usa are in last place
Went to the final round then to get what the hell
This diver is gonna have to take the biggest risk possible
I
Dive that
Here's the replay
It was an ambitious dive but just not executed at all
All right, that was fun
I'm doing the next one
I'm not done until we do the actual scientific hypothetical theory thing
Oh, this is the vault. Okay. I'm looking forward to this
Tuck with it. Wait
Oh, this is not a pole vault
I thought this was the pole vault
Press into your somersault
0.5 twist
And then hit down
It looks like it hurt
All right, we're just gonna do tuck
Concentration there just didn't perform the selected vault
Oh, that's just simply disappointing. They're not gonna be happy with that
Oh, so let's indulge and have another look at this. Here's the replay
Why did gravity turn up times five when I got halfway there
So here come the judges scores
Quick look at the scores at the end of that round and as you'll see
Do I have a backpack with magnets on me and there's a negatively charged ion plate underneath me
Straight i'll get this one be hard
Well, this is really interesting stuff now a medium difficulty selection could really turn out to be a good choice for this gymnast
Yep, i'm okay
You don't die that just made it a taffy i'm gonna be fine
Well, let's have a quick look at the highlights of that performance then
Well in come the scores now, but I honestly can't see this gymnast getting high points for that vault
All right. What am I doing wrong here? I'm trying to stick it with with the uh left on the analog
That's too late
I want to do that one again. This is eason dawney. Welcome to the final of the men's single scores
What is skulls?
Wait, wait, it's a it's a rowboat competition
Let's take a look at the line up
tutorial
Press and hold the triggers to begin rowing
Release l2 to return the oars and do it again
double tap to boost
Hey, i'm going to show you everybody at the gym that uses this fucking thing. It's the only specters cross the finish line backwards
And like you want to correct them
But like when you see somebody at the gym going like this
It's like, oh no, he's just kind of gonna keep he's gonna do his thing
Okay
I'm gonna go all the way
Saves gum
Why am I getting destroyed
Why is there so many people on bikes over there
Are there two events going on at the same time?
Just losing to the bikes i'm i'm not racing the bikes
Sites and situated not far away from winza castle. This is one of the more pit to rest venues
Go
All six rowers pull away from the blocks then here
Well, this has been a decent performance so far but needs to up the stroke rate here
breathless day
Terrific conditions to rowing
Britain the front runner. This is an impressive performance
Good pace this from china have a real chance of winning belgium are doing well here in third place
Just to piss off the pace team usa they're back in sixth
Through 500 meters. That's the halfway point
Go faster. I can't
What's wrong with me what's wrong with my guy what's why is he quitting what's wrong with my guys
All right, if there were 10 people on this i'm the one guy pretending to row and not doing any work
Hurts my arms and i'm not even doing it just pulling in leaning back to chill him
See again not a particularly good performance
Right early on was down and then when he needed to pull through it didn't quite happen
The middle section just letting him down and then coming down the home straight
We're really expecting more from this athlete
But on this occasion, he just couldn't quite put in the performance we were hoping for
All right, I want to do some stuff
I want to do some things
All right, each folly ball weight lifting
Karen what did I did that right kayak single of karen? Wasn't that the
Isn't karen the same thing?
Did I do both?
All right. I want to do
What's the last thing? I don't think I really yeah, let's just do these I want to do I want my theory to play out
Oh karen's the bike, right? Okay
I want to say something
You wanted to do the vault again?
All right, i'll do that before I go
my too late flop
No
Oh, I would do 3d mode, too. Yeah, there's still more to do. Hold on. All right, here we go men's 100 meter
Here we go
They must get off the blocks quickly ready. Oh, it doesn't automatically it doesn't I can't do it. I wish I could
Injury
Seemed to struggle with this one from the start. I don't know what was wrong
But maybe there was an injury or something else just didn't look as smooth and the result very much reflects that
And it's gold for jamaica
Okay
Let's check out the other one
Because I didn't do this one coming up. Yeah, I didn't do volleyball
I feel like I want to put in the beijing one and play the other events that aren't in this game
We're gonna do that i'm putting in beijing one
With the sam that's arrived for the 2012 games. There's other events. I think on this game that aren't out here
I'm gonna i'm gonna just play them
All right, serve bar, but this is an actual game of volleyball
Okay, then press x press x before the target begins flashing
Use l hold l
I get it. I know how to play volleyball
All right, let's go i'm putting in beijing wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no I want to do
Stop putting in beijing
I'm gonna take a piss and go i'm putting beijing. Oh, yeah, 3d mode. Yeah, right, right, right, right
It's probably gonna fuck up the tv. Is this gonna fuck up the tv? How is this 3d?
You just see it twice
You have to cross your eyes
Oh, you need the glasses. Okay, but hold on a minute
What the hell would 3d glasses do for this?
But what would it do?
Do I need my individual eyes?
You need to type be a 3d monitor
Oh, okay. All right beer back. I'm gonna put in beijing and i'm gonna go uh, take a quick break up beer back
Okay. Hi, um, why is this taking so long to make a save profile?
Saving please do not switch the power off
Didn't just take one second
Why is it saving 10 gigs of space I don't understand
Why is it taking so long
What do you want us to tell you make me I don't know make me feel better say I don't know
Do your ps3 is just working hard
I can hear it. Can you guys hear the weird little like switch it off switch it off switch it off. What do you mean?
It's fine
It's just a old ps3
Yeah, so this is 2008. So if we're probably gonna
Lose some physics and some graphics on the way back
The worrying of the hard drive. Yeah, okay. I think we're good. I'll be
Sega I think we're good
I probably need to change the title, huh powered by games by that's very old
The official olympic games
2008 already looks a little crusty
Can you already do this?
Some games no, I don't care
All right competition
Some features of competition only available sign. I don't care
Play on this system
track, okay
Field. Yeah. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on a minute. There's
hammer throw
Let's do 100 100 meter
Hammer throw
This does look like a racing game. You're right. It does
diving
Let's do diving
uh
Parallel bars rings floor exercise beam uneven bars. Yeah
shotgun air pistol
We did these let's do air pistol
archery weight lifting
judo
Combined events to cap one
Okay
I'm ready. Let's do it
I'm looking forward to judo
Hey, i'm back from the playstation stream. It sucked
Wait, like an official ps playstation stream is well, what are they doing? What are they talking about?
Anything interesting?
This feels like an old sega game
I hold l2 and r2 to build power
Once the power bar hits the red zone, you'll launch from the blocks
Press x and o alternately or toggle l and r to build up speed
This is way more complicated than 2012
Press r2 to showboat
All right, let's go
Where am I?
Just showboat the whole time
Well, that's me
All right, hold l2 and r2
Okay, here we go
What who the fuck is that guy? What's that guy doing? Is there a waiter here? Oh, no, that's official. Okay
All right, I lost that one's way more complicated than the first than the I said first game
But it's the second game first game of the night. I can't wait to do hammer throw
If I knew that hammer throw was an olympic sport, I probably would have tried to do it
That sounds like fun. Just whipping a hammer as hard as you can
I get why people do this shit. That's fun
Throw a hammer as hard as you can you got it. Oh, it's this
It's the back the fuck away from me or I cannot control if you die or not event
Holy shit, this is gonna be impossible
I don't hold on. I can we do that again?
Okay, so you start spinning
rotate l
To match the marker
Press l2 or r2 to release the hammer
What direction should I throw the damn thing? He's gonna wreck somebody in the crowd
Now that's what the fence is for
The long shot is a very long close-up of this guy's face
I mean, is it skip or is it continue?
What'd you say?
I skip it
No, do not skip you're skipping don't skip. No skip. Don't skip. Yes
All right, let's go
Okay, just gonna match the
Match it with the meter surrounding him. Wait, i'm not the ball. I thought I was the ball
I thought I was the ball. I didn't I thought the ball was my movement and not
Okay, I get it
Why wouldn't I be him turning and not what i'm i'm the meter turning? Come on. Okay, i'll get it this time
Pick up not bad. That's all right
He's just not producing his best today
Yeah, you can see as he walks off. He knows he needs to do better than that
Bit of a lackluster effort there needs to improve on that
Yeah, but in this event all it takes is that one big throw two ai's talking to each other. That's what it sounds like
Yeah, it is. Yeah, it is. Well, i'm you know what I mean though
Oh foul you didn't take that long to tell me it was a foul
You could have done it immediately. That's pretty good
Damn it. I can do it again. I can be better with the ball. That's hard to do. I'll get it
That's gonna be a fucking world record right there
Right measure that shit. That's above the world record
Yep
Did it that's he's doing the hulk hogan. That's what I would do. That's a great celebration
three fouls and world record
All it takes is one man
Nice all right. Let's hear it. It's time for the music
Please stand for the national anthem of the united states of america. I'll be right
I don't think you can get dmca'd
With the national anthem
You're gonna get sued
What was next there was a lot of shit on this list i'm looking forward some of them were crazy
Disney owns it. I think the day that happens
That's the turning point
But for society just to collapse like absolutely collapse
Like if disney copyrights the national anthem you're gonna be eating your food out of an old can that's in your basement like there's no way
Oh, here we go. This is a big one
Anybody understand this rotate l to match the green marker and r to match the red marker
Oh, I don't think you're gonna pick my dive
Oh, here we go
Wait, where are the balls? Oh, I get it. Okay. I get it. You have to
I thought I was the balls again
This is fucking horrible
I get it
Yeah, that's hard to do. It's like scratching your belly and patting your head at the same time. Why is it off to be in slow motion?
That was pretty damn good
That would have been at least eight or nine
This was when I was flashy as the other one. Let's see what happens if you just completely fuck the whole thing up
I'm gonna try to not get any points
What's with the harry potter whispering thing?
Actively pretending. Yeah, I I guess you just do the move but
depending on how long they were in the
I better get a zero, right?
Okay
Uh, I don't want I don't do that again. How do I speed time up?
This game is way worse. Yeah, it is way worse. Well, we haven't gotten to judo yet. So hold on hold that thought
All right, that's it, right?
That's it. You have to dive 10 times
What?
No, I don't
I don't know how you make the high dive not fun in a video game
Is that even possible?
All right. Cool. Good saw waiting room. I don't even know what that disc is. It might even be gone
I have no idea where the saw disc is
You
This is giving me so much anxiety, holy shit boy why
To skip to saw 2 I have to buy saw 2 I don't own it i'm gonna play it though
Here we go. Now it's time to fucking plug
Parallel bars i'm gonna do all kinds of crazy shit up here
There's l2 and r2 to until vertical to achieve a good lift
So you go bang bang bang bang bang bang bang, okay, then how do you trick
The l and r left or right to position the arrows beneath the hands
Okay
Press the displayed buttons in order for the perfect dismount
Okay, let's go
Sounds like wario. We're gonna jump up or no. How do you approach this?
Oh like that good. Here we go
I'm doing that. I guess
Pretty good. Wait, what's this?
This is just like lining up mini game line thing just not even doing anything
It's just placed weird circle underneath where he is. I'll tell you if you ever have it wait
Games quiet. Oh shit lost
Game sucks. The london one's better. I know I know but I we gotta see the events that I didn't play in london
Turn it back down. That was one guy. Okay, play the 2016 one
What is it for is it a ps4 and xbox one?
I was under the impression that after 2012 the games would really just awful
Keep the fucking arrows. I'm not I want to keep the arrows. How do I skip this?
These little mini games. I'm not even controlling anybody just fall off just fall off
Don't hold it. Just fall down
fall down
Fall it's just gonna play the animation. No matter what it's just based on how many that's sad
Dad
Yeah, this 2012 was way better
Thank god we're out of that. I need to get to judo first and there's a shooting one
Huge disc is throw but throw the disc in real life
I wonder how far I could throw a disc frisbee style. What do you think? I could probably get it
It doesn't weigh that much. I'm gonna say
25 feet 30 feet. Is that really under shooting it there 40 feet? I could do more than 40 feet
I could probably get please don't have please let me walk around. Please please let me walk around
Please not have it be a mini game. Let me walk around and do moves, please
That's it. That's it. I can't walk around with the analog and jump and stuff. Come on
None of this matters i'm gonna hit i'm just gonna hit every button randomly
David cage game
The only difference is there's a story there
No story here. Look at me
What do you think my floor exercise would be
Dude, what if I did like a germa olympics?
Has this got a bunch of like my drunk friends to come and do like random things
The floor exercises and stuff
And then you guys would have to vote on who wins. I kind of like this idea
I need that
I wonder how the other one would actually take
Last time you did a floor exercise you left for two months. Well, I wouldn't participate in that
Six
I could do a floor exercise. I don't have to move around that much. I can just fucking pantomime and move my hands and
Like magic tricks and stuff
That's awful. This game is awful
It's truly awful
One of these has to pop out and make us
Happy, right? One of something's got to pop out here to do mario and sonic. There is a new one, isn't there?
No, I don't even want to do I know what it's gonna be. I already know what it's gonna be
I don't want to even see it
I already know what's gonna happen. It's gonna be just stand still. Why just press x once
That doesn't matter. It's tony hawke grinding
You can actually fall
By the way, I always saw this
As the most difficult thing that a human being could do
In any doesn't matter what no matter what it is
This he doing a backflip and landing on this
And not shattering every bone in your body is insane that you can do a backflip and land on here
Do like a backflip and spin four times in the air
It's a cartoon. It's not even possible
I named something harder than this. What what is harder than this doing surgery on somebody?
uh
I mean that's that's hard
But is it hard is it as hard as doing a backflip on a one inch beam and staying up and like doing all kinds of like
Look at me using all that
Shattering your bones. Do you know what they're made out of?
wood
This is like a block of hard like foam wood shit. I don't even know what that I don't know what it is
No, that wooden bones the actual banister thing what is it made out of?
Guys if your hand if your body was made out of wood
Opening and closing your car door would just hurt you every day
Walking up the stairs would be hell
Oh my god, I thought this is gonna be so much fun
I thought it was gonna be so fun with all these different gymnastics events and they got rid of them in 2012 because they realized that
They couldn't figure out a way to make it fun
That's why none of them are here
They could they just didn't that's true
Thank god. It was quick judo better not be like this
I better be able to hit circle to punch and x to kick or i'm gonna be really mad
If judo is a rhythm game, i'm gonna pull the disc out
You heard it if judo is a rhythm game. I'm i'm pressing the release disc button
I'm gonna snap the disc. It's dangerous. I don't do dangerous things on stream anymore. You don't kick in judo
Here we are finally now we can actually get some goddamn action
I didn't do the tutorial
You just shoot why am I setting up a math problem?
What's the point of the first one?
What's the point of of using graph paper?
It's pulling me down
It's the hand getting tired
Why can I not set that every time?
They by the way, do they shoot bullets?
Or is this like pellets or something? By the way, what's going on here?
It's just hold on six. Okay. I was I thought I was gonna keep shooting the same spot where eight was
Yeah, what is going on with these glasses?
What are those? Is one of them a magnifier and the other one?
Is this a jeweler? Is he working on diamonds? I don't know. What is this for?
Looks like a warcraft gnome
This is crazy. Well, i'm i'm what is it for?
I kind of want to try these on
Just close one eye and just look through kind of the magnified one
I think I would like these in real life
If I was able to switch those down
Plus two perception. Yeah, that'd be awesome. I'm not even trying i'm just kind of hitting things
Grandma, look at me. Hey, look at you
I'm not trying but at least I get to play
10.7 is not just 10.0. There's higher than 10
Get extra in the middle
You can get in the middle of the middle
Yeah, I guess I lost
didn't even place
archery, okay
This one should be fun
I thought the controller was on her head. I thought it was like what's with all these weird apparatus?
I thought that was something on her head
Okay, wait
Whatever let's go seven. Oh
You think they're ever gonna make a game that uses the huntsman style bow and arrow mechanics in an actual video game
I want it so bad
TF2 has that yeah, it's been like 12 years
I'm not talking. Hey, i'm i'm not saying
Hey, give me a game. That was give me a game eight years ago. That came up with this. I want one now
And I want it to be like a single player game
I don't want to be online because people are way better than me online and they'll just shoot me the barn
I run the head first before I can shoot them. So I want to do it at my own pace with my own single player time
No, not in minecraft. I'm talking where the whole game is based around like awesome
perfect incredible
archery mechanics six
Just bow and arrow just perfect like they spend three years perfect making it perfect
seven horizon
No, it's not no, it's gotta be first person. It's gotta be first person
I thought it was actually gonna hit still just make it yourself
I don't I don't know shit about making video games
forehead
Crisis three, is it good?
Crisis is a weird game. I feel like i've never played crisis before but I know i've played it but it sits in this weird place
In my memory where I may as well have never even opened it once
I don't remember anything to me crisis and far cry
Just blend together into the same video game in my head
Ten and they're very different. Yeah, I I don't know why it's just that's the case
You know what? I think it probably is nine
There's like seven bar cries and like four crises. It's like they they just feel like they're all
There's a lot of them
How many crises are there?
Nine three four, right?
It's 2020 bro. Every day. There's a new one. Is that guy wearing flowers as a watch?
I skipped it way too quickly. It looked like it it come our judo. Here comes the judo dream
No, it's weightlifting
rotate
Eleanor opposite directions to increase power
Slowly rotate eleanor outwards from the bottom. This sucks
472 pounds
I can't even all right. It's you rotate different directions. That's so hard to do with i'm gonna do it. I'm gonna try two hands
My fingers bump into each other because it's a fucking playstation
Why would you make why would you do that?
If you put both your thumbs on the analogs and you rotate opposite directions your thumbs hit each other in the middle
That's the most bogus fucking thing in the world
Pick up a playstation 3 controller right now
Rotate it in opposite directions and come in and meet in the middle and you tell me that your thumbs don't touch
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope
Your fat thumbs I don't
I'm having a look
Does it feel like you have like a company meeting like
Everybody, okay. Let's talk about this. All right. Yes, uh, let's go over the day here
Uh, so we've uh, that's done. It's all right. The game's done. It's ready to ship
It's not fun at all. It's like the opposite of fun
Uh, I don't know what may have I don't know. Wait, wait, hold on. I'm lifting
Turn your arms out
What?
Do it turn it up, man
You're right
Do it
He did I did I lifted it. What do you mean? No lift he put it over his head
He put it over his head
Let's see if he let's see if he lifts it. I don't think he lifted it. I don't think he did
What was I saying?
It doesn't matter. Come on. You can do it
Come on, you can do it
balance
That's the world. That's personal best. That's the world record
230 kilograms
Wait, what's 474?
I couldn't make it that high
Wait, that's the lowest the minimum weight. That's so funny. That's the minimum
Is it this is the only reason why I stuck around for this long in this game is for judo only
You understand i'm gonna get punch kick throw
Jump
It's not good. Yep. Okay
Match the arrows to gain an advantage
once you have the advantage press a combination of
This just punch punch punch punch kick punch fight
The throne reduced okay
When in or performing a hold or a pin press r2 l2
I don't I kind of don't I didn't I don't get any of that, but it's all right. Let's go
Here we go 81 to 90 kilograms
Destroy this isn't a rhythm game
Nah, you didn't get me
Oh shit, what happened? Is this judo? Are we trying to take the tags off of each other's shirts?
escape
Wait, who won?
Wait, wait, wait, wait
I didn't read the rule. I I I didn't read the rules. It said move move move
L2 r2 r2 r2 r2 r2 and then mash the face buttons
Okay, i'm ready
Let's go throne
Nope, what is this?
What's wrong with me?
What is it? Was he doing the mandible claw? What just happened?
Why did I just fall down?
All right. Okay. Okay. All right. I'm done
I'm done
Why would you play the judo one if you don't know what judo is? I know judo is an event. It's a martial art
We throw people in
If you get pinned you'll lose
That end of the stream voice
Yeah
Yeah, it probably is
It probably is
That is accurate
Actually, I didn't do disc throw
Which is I want to do that
Not like it's gonna be any fun
But I plan on playing fall guys is what we're doing next to play that throw the disc out the window
no
Guys, i'm gonna put this back on ebay for a dollar five
I think that's what it was. It was like a dollar. It was a dollar and 10 cents
It was not more than a dollar. I know it wasn't it wasn't more than two
If it was then that's sad
When is movie night for real? I'll give you that I would give that to you right now
So the dlc, yeah
That came up on me out of nowhere
Uh dlc movie night
Uh at least like part one
is going to be
on
saturday
saturday the 29th
I think that gives me and some of the mods a lot of time to really get
a good playlist
They don't want to do it just like in the next week because I feel like there's a lot there's hundreds of them
So I really want to be able to go through those
So saturday the 29th
I'll get on your calendar. That's dlc movie night
So long from now, it's gonna go by real quick. I promise
I don't get it. I don't know how it works
But I will see you guys again. This is the
First time i've done two streams in a row since coming back
I have some stuff to do
Over this weekend
I'm gonna go do it. I'm gonna take care of it
And i'll see you guys on monday
Still continuing to ease back into live streaming
And I feel okay. I actually feel okay. I feel pretty good
but I don't want to
Push it
So I don't really want to do three days in a row
I really want to get up and move around
But I will see you guys on monday. I think that's a good place to start. We'll probably do
monday tuesday
Probably monday tuesday thursday if I would say next week
I think that makes a lot of sense
Because those of you that might be out of the loop. I just I know I say this at the end of every stream the last
Three or four streams since I come back
But i'm going backwards
to
Streaming less sort of how long I streamed and times I streamed before moving to vegas
I streamed probably three days a week
Back when I was in massachusetts for about four to six hours
So we're going back to that
This medical stuff is still ongoing. So i'm gonna keep it that way. I'm gonna keep it like it was a few years ago
so
I've had a lot of fun though sponge bob was a lot of fun these games
Well, then this one not so much, but 2012 was actually great. I had a lot of fun
Hope you enjoyed it. We'll see you maybe again on monday. Have a great weekend everybody. Let's see if I fixed the credits
I tried again today
I really did. Let's see if it worked
Here come all the subs maybe
Hey, I finally got it to work
This is not in the right spot
And the font is weird. Why is the font so weird? I'll fix that
But thanks everybody for subbing
We had some community subs. We had a lot 50 community subs today from suck mcjones
Thank you. That's a huge amount of money
Do a different font to every stream
Do I need to teach you how to use obs? No, i'm telling you i've done this correct
Every time I didn't change anything. Why did it change two months after me streaming? It doesn't make any sense
I didn't change anything. I don't like when things change around me
There's no music. What the hell am I doing? There's still no music sneak up on this sniper
Wait, why what was that?
Why was that so loud? What was that?
um
This is bizarre
Why is this right now?
on my browser source
Wait a minute this this needs to be explored
vlog
overwatch
Is this a muselk video?
Why is this here?
I didn't do this
Out of the water. I mean, I didn't do this. I didn't put this here
You know like will the game I swear to god, I don't know why this is here
You go in and it's just like can you click on people and that decides whether or not you're gonna win the game or not
Is this like part of a playlist of a video that we watched yesterday? So addictive so fun. It has to be right
I mean like i'm like trembling right now. It was just it was insane
It was just awesome and I can't wait to get a chance to play it again
Uh, there was this one thing I have no way. Well, there's muselk. I don't know why this is here
I have no explanation for that. I can't even tell you why that may have happened
Is this a setup for a joke? No, I have no idea why that happened
It was just my I went over to the my ending scene. I turned my audio on
And it was in the middle of a video
Probably a second or third or fourth video
Or maybe even like a 100th video that just was playing recommended over and over again all stream
I had my I don't know that could have been happening
It's very possible that this browser source was just playing videos in the background. Whatever
All right. I will see you guys on monday. You want who should we raid? Let's raid somebody who's available right now
Who's available and what are they doing? It's very important
Star's playing heart stone
Yeah, let's go say hi to star we actually were just talking the other day
Great star
It's very rare that I actually catch him streaming. He's probably gonna be he's probably gonna be like mad
And they just can't
All right, be nice
We're done. We'll do
I'll see you guys on monday. Have a great weekend
The bio you were talking about streaming together. Yeah, we we were talking about these games to play
I'll see you guys on monday
Please criticize every move he does in hearthstone tonight end