Hey. Hey. Hey everybody. What? Oh, this is crazy. Homelands. I just saw you like earlier today.
Did I see you earlier? We ran into each other earlier today? That's weird. The same day. I
didn't know you shopped at this this grocery store. I just saw you at the gas station
earlier today. God, I would say, how are you? But we already talked about that.
Uh, welcome back everybody. It's true. I saw Jerma at the gas station and he went like this,
this, this. Uh, hi guys. Today, uh, we're going to continue the trend that we've had the last
three days. Uh, somebody just wrote, please tell me you're going to play Muppets Party Cruise.
I don't have that. I'm really sorry to tell you I do not have Muppets
Party Cruise. It's not like I put it in the title. Sometimes we forget about this.
There were four thousand PS2 games. I'm never going to play them all. All I can do
is just get through ones that I remember and ones that look interesting. Why not? He's lying.
Not with that attitude. Not with that attitude. No. And I don't just want to look,
okay, the same thing happened with the, uh, the VR stuff, right? Like I really want
to play a bunch of these and give them the time that they deserve. That's why we're
going back and forth because there's a shitload more VR stuff I want to do. We got to take a
break. We're getting ping ponged between VR and old console stuff. He's back. He knew my stream
was turning on, so he just drove his car by again. Hey, didn't I see you earlier today?
I thought I saw you earlier today at the gas station. He's back. I swear to God,
I live in a fucking video game simulation. Are you guys real? Anybody here real? No,
no, no, no. I think a lot of us know. Has ever anybody even asked the question to a bot like
that? Are you real? Like on Twitch? They have to answer correctly, right? AI has to give the
correct answer. That's actually kind of scary. Anyways, just letting people trickle in while
we hang out for a minute. Oops, that's a bunch of disks. Yeah, we're going to go back to VR
after obviously this weekend was PlayStation 2, and I did see quite a few people a little
bit angry with me for a good reason, because I did say yesterday that I was going to play,
hey guys, start with Clock Tower 3, and we're going to play a bunch of other shit.
And then I played Clock Tower 3 for nine hours and beat the whole game in one sitting.
I had a great time. I thought it was a fun stream. Hey, that just means we get to do
it again. You know what I'm saying? I thought that was a lot of fun. So speaking of fun,
I'm not sure what to start with today, because there's a chance that I might just get locked
into one of these. I'm thinking we start with... It's tough. I don't know. I don't
want the same thing to happen. The same thing can happen. Should we start off with Stuntman?
I can't get stuck in Stuntman. That's not possible. I also have Stuntman Ignition,
but I can't play that one first. Which one of them is better? Stuntman Ignition is so good.
No, but don't get me stuck here. Ignition is better. All right, well, let's get a taste of
the good one. Don't let me get stuck here. I will. Where's Metal Gear Solid 3? Actually,
I was talking to Italics about that the other day, about how that was my favorite Metal
Gear game. Okay, here we go. We're going to play Stuntman Ignition. I would laugh my ass
off if this turns into a Stuntman Ignition, like, six and a half hour stream.
It's not going to happen. No, I have to play... I got 25 to life here that has to come up next,
but I might get lost in that. Look, it's all right. Even if I get lost in them. I got
PsyOps, Freedom Fighters. These are all classics. This is made by THQ, one of the
old glorious companies. Paradigm Entertainment. Black Screen. Shouldn't be Black Screen.
Every mangled mass of steel has a story to tell. Pretty good Spike TV intro we got going here.
So you're a movie actor in this, right? A tale of speed, guts, talent, style.
You're a Stuntman. Stuntmans are actors. They have to not only drive the car,
but they have to pretend to drive the car. They're gonna be in those camera shots.
They have to look like they're fucking really driving as hard as they can.
I thought I was watching an ad. Well, you kind of were. You kind of were watching an ad
for this game. Stuntman Ignition uses an auto-save feature. I'm actually probably
gonna run out of room on this memory card here. There's been a lot of eight megabyte
save datas over the last six months on this thing. Well, I guess not. That's gonna be a
problem though. All right. Stuntman Ignition. Career. Quick fix. Options. Audio controls.
Gameplay. Thrill cams. Oh, this game kind of looks terrible. It's really blurry.
This was the game that I properly raged at. Vibration off, always. 75, 75.
Arrows on. Okay, we're just gonna keep this shit here. I gotta read the manual, right?
This is like every PlayStation game. Okay, handbrake. Brake. Gas. Camera control.
Action. And then look right and look left. Isn't it nitro? Okay. Career. What are you
doing? Why are you saving every five seconds? Should have got the PlayStation 3 version.
Uh-oh. Ricky Langston. Do I have to drive? Dude, I did it. That's an S. That was the audition.
That's a very expensive audition.
This guy's a real asshole.
I'm told this is your first time on a big set so I'll walk you through how it works.
We'll have you wired up in your vehicle and your coordinator will call out all the major
director stunts we need you to hit, okay? He'll also mark them on your heads-up display
with yellow stunt icons. These include drifts, gaps, jumps, closes, and other maneuvers. We'll
be using a point system to judge your runs. All the directors do it. It's how we keep track
of the drivers in the biz. More precisely you perform, more points you'll earn. Fail
We all use it.
Oh, do I get to have a strike here with the other stuntmen that are getting fucking abused on set?
Yeah, nice to meet you too.
There's another one.
This is Vegeta.
This is Christopher Seabot.
A huge finale where the town gets ripped apart.
Before each scene I'll give you shots of your key stunts with tips on how to pull them off.
Right now this stuntman is probably just sitting there with a dump in his pants like,
holy shit, this is my first day. I thought I was gonna have to put on a wig
and pretend to be an old lady and fall down in a crosswalk.
For your first scene you'll double for the town's trouble-making drifter in his R3000
as he flees the volcanic eruption. The highlight will be this huge jump over a burning semi.
The key is to hit the ramp straight. That'll set you up for the stunt that follows.
As soon as you land you'll have a pair of precision drivers coming at you fast and you'll
need to gap between them. It's dangerous so be careful and don't be afraid of retakes.
Mr Langston's a picky director and it can take a while to make him happy.
Okay um get up excuse me can I go to the bathroom first I kind of have to go to the bathroom
all right let's go three two one action gap the cars what what do you mean gap the cars
that was my first day this is a tricky set you need to watch out for those hazards
oh I thought I was supposed to jump hold on wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute
I thought I was supposed to jump okay then we turn um what if you destroy the whole town
what what oh yeah well we were not authentic we uh we we put a bunch of like hydrochloric
acid in a local volcano it wiped out fucking like an entire village but let's at least
we got it for the shot right god damn right that was good all right um so
I feel like this game's playing in slow motion
this is like 640 by 480 it's so blurry in my screen and it's playing at like
18 frames a second oh I got it got it they're killing people seriously what the
fuck is going on here what how many stunts do I have to do these aren't stunts okay I'm
sorry but you are just dropping molten bombs on these people that was too boring too boring
you're gonna have like a dead sea scrolls obituary for this 10 minute string here give me
a break I got a new car oh with this one we're gonna have you uh fucking jump over the uh
ocean your car's gonna get wings you're gonna fly past a plane be careful they go under the
plane what the hell are they doing stuntman ignition is all about stunt points and stunt
stringing is how you rack up the big numbers every stunt earns you points and goes into your
stunt string if you perform a stunt within two seconds of another stunt that will continue
your stunt string and add another number to your multiplier now your stunt stringing be
sure to watch your stunt indicator on the upper left it tells you what stunt you just
performed and how long you have until your string breaks you have to stunt before the string
fades out if it breaks your string will be cashed out and added to your total score on the right
what stunts continuous string all of them yeah throw a drift get close to anything in the
scene pass through a time gate hit a director stunt jump a ramp you get the idea look for
different ways or objects throughout the course to keep your string alive now if you
want that fifth star you're gonna have to string it that means keep a continuous string from your
first stunt to your last your total score should read zero if you string the entire level together
try the stringing rehearsal and see if you can do it and by the way after you do all this
the actor's gonna come out of their trailer go where you were at the time of the cut
say three sentences and then go back in their trailer what a fucking hard job string the
scene action all right let's string it how do i handbrake oops on the car something's wrong
with the car the drift is what jump god damn it do it again do it again do it again all right
it's not as much as a drift as it is a hard stop yeah that's not really a drift
this would be good done there's more no there's not okay passed next scene all right
today's run will be the drifters last scene when he tries to escape the town and gets torched by a
lava boulder at the end the feature stunt is the pyro charge as you cross over a certain
lava fissure in the ground which will mark on your HUD trigger the charge and set your car on
fire get hot but you'll be wearing a cool suit once you're lit drift hard to the right
and gap through the car wash that'll extinguish the car wash onto the big finale remember kid
watch out for that lava yeah by the way our director is a real fucking psycho
he's decided to make a mouse trap in real life there aren't any actors here so what was
it getting lit on fire action i'm dead there you go three two one action hit the object got
it there's a real volcano here all right hit the right here okay i see why are there other
people driving that was just the time crisis guy get in the get beautiful come jump they just
threw a car at us oh shit yeah the really hard part was donkey kong was really expensive to
hire for this no come on just edit it why do we have to do this in one take they're all
one-upping each other now now didn't you see birdman yeah we have to do that with these
fucking horrible stunts they've raised the bar for us yeah watch it seamless it was it was
that was better than last time watch you watch we're gonna watch the guy throw the car
did i not hit him oh what was wrong with that i killed that guy i killed that guy
is that it i didn't ignite so wait a minute you're telling me that christopher sabat the voice of
vegeta is the guy that says action in time crisis really wow this is the movie this is
the scene from the movie pretty good i wish there was dialogue over this that was pretty
good my window smashed even look at how good look at how talented i am as a driver
i hope nobody was in there it's the windshield you blame it on the windshield that could be like a
comedy part of the movie well like there's got to be like a sassy british guy in here
i can't see out of the fucking window might end up like arguing back and forth and that
happens and there's no more dialogue all right two two motorcycle we're gonna get stuck here
let's talk motorcycles kid directors love them because they're fast and loud and punch to any
scene but they're also harder to control more dangerous so watch out or they'll be mopping
your skull off the pavement there are two major stunts unique to the bike first is the wheelie
it's a great way to start any motor run and keep your strings alive pull back on the left
analog stick as you hit the gas pull back that front wheel and while you hit the gas push
forward to drop back down then there's the slide to pull it off perform the action as
you pass through the designated stunt box okay that'll make you lay the bike down on
one side while you're still barreling forward so in the box how do you do the slide is simple
as that what combination buttons is it he just said do it you got to be in the stunt box
is it just it's just simple it's just simple the action button which is what's the action
button triangle okay here we go one action pop a wheelie press triangle drift left close to the
crates oops drift left good slide i press triangle u-turn nice what u-turn all right
so what do i do wrong there not path let me do again hit the dab action all right
slide slide under i'm pressing triangle right under uh so three square is the slide button
action so it's not trying it's square no that's not it either r1 trip left i'm not on the
bike anymore it's r1 three one action r1 there we go it is r1 triangle
this is fun i just wish we were in a higher resolution
all right good good get the jump with a wheelie all right pass god damn it
okay i passed we're fine in this scene you'll be doubling for a desperate team racing through
the carnage to rescue his grandmother in her mountain cabin the key stunt begins
you'll be the grandmother i can't i'm sorry keep it high speed when you land then a blast will
hurl a couple of cars finally get to be the grandma serious force dodge under the flying
cars by sliding the bike like we rehearsed after the slide you'll move real quick into
a hard drift left so be ready for it continue up the mountain and end at the grandmother's
house
dodge under the flying cars why are there flying cars drift i was doing a wheelie for no reason
one action this game is on the 360 and ps3 well fuck me really that's live
close left there are better versions it's way better on those i didn't know why is it on ps2
why would it be on ps2 left the original was on ps2 fuck turn left more time added left
come on get on the bike get on get
okay we're good oh that was pretty sick got it what
oh he did it right when i landed the tire nice tourist world stunt award dominations
to grandma's house we go i got the award let's take a look at how that movie played out
nice i gotta get to grandma's okay one of the cars they left that in yeah you didn't
predict that was gonna happen should have got extra points for that one
these days all these fucking little shits all they use is cgi back in the day he used to get
actually hit by fucking cars that's the end of the movie those camera angles suck scene earth
shake all right we get the earth shake scene movies aren't shot in order as i hope you
know what scene comes just before volcano climb while the teen's still trying to get out of
town and up to his grandmother the big moment here comes early in the run
when you take the ramp over a major drop and smash through a burning billboard
keep in control when you land so you can navigate across the fiery rooftops
and take the smaller jump that follows you'll really be putting your body on the line here
kid i kind of want to play team standing should i just get this for ps3 and just like
play up to where i am now i feel like i feel like this is a whole stream
let me do like another one or two what happened to that car today i'm not going to make the
sign that's too uh this is just a guy that bought a motorcycle and has no training doesn't
even know how to ride it i kind of like how crusty it is on ps2 though
easy close through the sign bingo got it
what oh my stomach oh i couldn't even laugh land on the box
am i going fast enough
i tried to press r1 didn't work quick oh i swear to god i pressed it i didn't get it i'm
not gonna pass this shit it worked what stunt are we filming here exactly good question
all right didn't fall off that time good this was perfect he did i didn't stick the landing
very well it's okay he's all right i love these camera angles they make this so much better
i don't even care about the video game i just want to watch like the full movie
i only fall down twice right do i fall down three times
from so far away
what a terrible movie you can't even see anything what a waste of footage
they gotta get the get a new b team here man yeah i oh man this is fun this is fun i'm doing
terribly but it's okay stunt city fire whooping and hollering too okay we got a new area
this one's locked director intro all right so now we're gonna move on to this is whooping
and hollering too we got a new movie can i what i wish i could watch the whole movie or
something
what did he just say
that's our version of stunt driving man anyway dude this flick's called whooping and hollering
brothers getting in car chases with the cops and all that kind of stuff
hey that's mr sate i can tell that one from a mile away
we planned out some huge crazy ass stunts for you so any chance you get to flare it up just
do it okay you just take it
just hit your marks it would be cool it's good to meet you man have fun out there
and i'll see you on the set yeah i don't even know where the set is oh god this is gonna be
look kid this director's a clown so we may have to work double time to give the producers what
they want because of course they sign our checks you'll mostly double for the creek
boys and their signature muscle car the general creek boys try to stop the corrupt
sheriff from foreclosing on their family's land you'll also have a scene on a dirt
bike as the crazy brother otis a fun scene is uncle cletus in his monster truck full of moonshine
and a great run as a bank robber in a hijacked armored truck this will be your first time to
shoot chase scenes so be sure not to fall too far behind the lead car or we'll have to stop
and reset most of the action happens in the town square but we've also got some exciting
stunts planned in the junkyard and in the lumber yard faxter and his crew are all about
backwoods mayhem so i hope you're ready to tear things up literally he thought i was playing
metro in this first scene the creek boys uncle cletus has loaded a ton of moonshine into his
monster truck and he's trying to escape the cops big thing here are the crushing stunts
when you see a crush icon drive your crush over the marked car to smash it
this is a tightly choreographed run and if the icon turns red that means the cars left
the shot and you've blown your chance what it's about it let's start this movie right
why would i do why would i crush the car all right let's go three two one action hit the
police car hit the police cars all right that was the wrong one somebody might have been in
that one
reshoot and it's too many messes three one action hit the police car not that one police
cars one two three hit the police car wait how am i supposed to get over that hit the
police cars what the fuck i'm not gonna make it it's too much there's too much
i'm playing this on an iphone screen that has been blown up 15 times stop the tape don't hit
the gap i'm too slow i'm gonna have to get the ps3 one this game is really fun but it might be
too much that i might have left this one in the up too long at the police car at the police
police cars police cars jump the logs jump into the tower oh come on did you see that
cooler than you shut up dude that's gonna be at least three times all right i'm okay with a
three star ignite your vehicle for the first time monster mesh bonus color customizer
monster truck unlocked all right let's go get it on ps3 before you get too far
is there another one like is there another game like is there another stuntman i i like the crust
but it might be too much crust put in the original one for ps2 what's right what's it how
about the original one i have that one yeah there's a little too much there's too much
crust on this one hold on i'm gonna put the first one i'm gonna get this with ps3 i'm gonna
play this i'm gonna get up to where i am right now this game is really fun let's try
the first one what is stuntman 2 to stuntman 1 there was a modern stuntman
which is going backwards in time downgrade to another downgrade i didn't know you could
actually watch the movie after that's really fun well and you we knew it was gonna happen
you know it was gonna happen eventually hold on delete a bunch of shit was it system browser
what is it why is there so many alias what the hell is even on here stuntman career clock tower
three alias casino five one two three celebrity death match remember that one true crime fifth
grader are you smarter than a fifth grader madden nfl set one madden nfl these are old
you got a lot of uh look at this all these old oh the x team the imperfects monster rancher three
yeah we can go ahead and fucking delete this my game sucked uh i'm gonna delete this person's
rosters 2012 that was monster rancher three not monster rancher two you think i would
delete monster rancher two i can't delete that sentimental uh i like that video i like
that stream this yeah this was stupid two was the one three was the one that was bad
what are you guys talking about pretty much all the madden nfl 08 can be deleted what about
this what's this one eee the miss oh that had netty is the godfather no don't copy the
godfather that's what i thought
i don't have a question among my decisions
all right we got 1700 for you we're good professor professor goodbye what else is here
can i get rid of all these just look at how much space this takes up for alias
this is half the memory card our alias save files get the hell out of here uh all right
that should be good don't get rid of these stop deleting my memories okay i got 5000 for you
that's enough this is the incredible hulk why is he all right i got a question why is the
incredible hulk hulk icon so small shouldn't it be huge shouldn't it why does it have to
be so little all right that should be fine i would smash your ps2 if i was there all right
you would smash my playstation 2 what a dick yeah i would just get another one what you don't
know is i got like six of them back here did this just say bullshit what was what did it just
say in the days of its infancy the stunt performer's profession was pioneered by the
daring and ingenuity of acrobats and circus acts as the public's demand for on-screen chases
crashes jumps smashes and explosions is never satisfied so the stunt performer has evolved into
a highly trained professional this is real footage for the timid this is where men and women
we really did default we went down to like to make it happen back to like the 20s
holy shit somebody's in that car
motion insane hundred pounds of pressure all right here we go stuntman the original
the first one stuntman career stunt constructor uh setup dvd extras this is a movie wait is this
for the terrible one that's for 64 and everybody hated this is one of the worst
games ever made isn't it over 40 minutes of cinematics it's making it crusty well don't
say that and not give us any you gotta give us a clip you didn't voice acted by the original
cast what you're not going to hear a sample of in the trailer shadow of apocalypse that's not
how you spell that what else we got hello what are you doing why am i fading to black
splashdown what is their next project coming up here miami all right somebody look it up
what's their last project here was the last thing they made driver what i don't know what
is this supposed to be driver three this is not driver three how could it be driver three when
he's not driving a car it was a door for the car okay this is driver three you don't think
you should have a car in the trailer the closest thing that an elevator was the closest
thing to a moving automobile in that whole trailer for driver three he'd think he'd say no
but we push it right to the edge the whole commercial play it's on the playstation 3 e
shop for 10 bucks i can download it while i'm playing this well i have that that's not
possible the playstation 3 is not hooked up right now playstation 2 is i would have to like
i don't have like another i can't that's not it's impossible
it's not my career that's for another day enter your name uh i can't just make it
no i don't want to do uh how about like this alien name oh that's me this is where the
truck's heading straight at me should be about 30 i'll be hitting about 60 if the truck
clips me it's anybody's guess where it spins me what is that part of the movie or is that guy
talking about how he was going to get hit my car and possibly die what toothless in whapping
that was going to happen i might get clipped and then get shown on the internet somewhere on my
community of people they've taken me out of context and clipping me saying something stupid
and like posting it in places and now i look like an asshole gangster comedy two hopeless
small timers up against the police and gangland kingpin the dentist one of the leads vince is
trying to get across town for a pickup but he's already late i'll have constant radio
communication with the director for every stunt i do time to get on set well without christopher
sabat this is something i don't like even care anymore it's magic what like a good voice
actor could bring to the game what accelerate 180 apparently that didn't work all right the
e-brake is way more sensitive in the original version it's even crustier i mean you're talking
about you on your special instructions on your online order at pizza hut you said leave it in
the oven for an extra 10 minutes how is that not a 180 yeah not only that you said views twice
as much dope i want like four more inches of frost what is happening here one that i'm doing
an e-brake that's the e-brake right 180 e-brake how are you supposed to do this
it's square in this one no it's not is it really it's triangle in this one where they
changed it on me square 180 e-brake now that's regular break that's regular break guys
hold on no the e-brake is definitely circle still
spongebob driving the car if you need instructions check out the instructional booklet
triangle accelerate 180 e-brake i don't think that's a possible move to do with the car
here do i have to do that left into the tunnel i don't think it's an indicator i think you just
have to do it i don't think it's like you did it yeah it's okay you just have to do it
yeah all right you don't you actually don't have to it i get it and the other one when
you do it it's like the thing lights up green got a new car you've earned a new ramp a new
arena toy because we're in britain the cars are right-hand drive so we get left-hand drives over
from europe and drive those we'll actually control the cars with mini steering wheels
we keep out a shot what they do that but what if they what if the car what if there's a
shot of the person driving this two steering wheels you have like a wee sports steering
wheel in your lap that's not how they do it yeah why can't you hire vince and ray escape to the
docks with the safe in the back of the car i need to do a 180 turn here then stop close
to the jetty edge to make it look good all right internal exposition here wow we really
did add extra crust and devolved what about that guy hit the guy i missed them all go back
to the other game well i'm gonna get the other one for playstation 3 so it doesn't look like
it's a blown up ipad screen i got his reaction just fucked me up so bad what what are you
going to do swing round break in the boxes and swing round reverse 44 degrees
and then swing around that's too much crust on that one that's too much crust
i'm trying to back up they just the i'm covered in fucking pizza dough
we're gonna put in 25 to life stuntman ignition i'm gonna get the players three
we're actually gonna play play muppets party cruise oh you can't so bad he can't even
swing around we went backwards we the sequel was better than the original and we watched the
original movie we did it in reverse that's not how you're supposed to watch lord of the rings
that's not how you watch star wars now this is an idos game i don't know why every one of
these gets captured strangely see what i'm saying like this makes it like a weird box for all
of them 25 to life by idos interact what's happening you missed how did nobody get hit by
any of that was it playing laser tag yeah even in the slow motion here comes like a slow motion
shot you missed that was a very weird intro yeah let's go memory card does not have a valid
save profile retry what do you mean that doesn't have a valid profile you must create
a new profile okay oh we got a copyright songs here profile one doesn't matter
i guess i gotta get rid of the copyrighted music
no no no back i gotta get rid of i don't want the vod muted go back quick
all right are we good i think we're good aiming is normal no normal blood and guts
enabled multiplayer online god single player normal available levels is
on this easy normal heart and oh my fucking god i'm not going to do that one what's that guy
doing no subtitles you're just a little rump baby boy you taking up all the good loving
your daddy where you been you smell like sticky icky ooey you've been hanging out with
that asshole shawn again i know he acts like a sucker but he's still my best people
so get off his case only god could judge him darnell go to your room damn mom he's
mr good fights boy if you don't get in that room you promised me you would get out the
game what the fuck i'm ready to be out to miami we talked about it but shawn ain't trying
to hear me yo it ain't that easy to walk away from this game monica this shit is all
i know you're gonna be knowing this game all by yourself in a minute i'm not raising a child
who screams thug life all day tomorrow i want to book the plane ticket you expect us to eat
i gotta get this paper by any means necessary i don't really know what's going on what am i
gonna do oh perfect timing for a phone call oh back when the phones were on the wall and
you had to actually go answer this is the france's family no one's home right now
leave a positive little guy what you said maybe there's a way for you to get out the
game and make right grab it hey hey what's up man yeah i'm sorry i'm here
did he just check his phone for a missed call no no no i deleted the copyrighted music don't
put it in here i'm out player i ain't built for this anymore i ain't gonna let you leave
motherfucker i made you i can't be the dope man forever my seed can't grow up in this
street drama i can't believe you letting the bitch break up our family this is supposed to
be m.o.b over bitches come on don't disrespect my lady and you don't have to justify my
thug i know i made a deal with the devil by being in the game i don't like it but
who is this you can be out after one more big job this time it ain't no 50 000 ecstasy deal
with no bull in arizona it's time to get some major baby you know what i'm talking about i'm
talking straight eskimo style all right whatever so after this last job then everything's straight
for sure home all right then i knew we could work it out one day soon my brother don't
what are you don't point that
for chapter one one last deal just need one more
what is that supposed to mean you can
jail what this was written by ai this is just okay you know when you open your iphone
and you just auto end sentences you just fill in the words with the auto word that it has
you know that like that joke on twitter people do this whole script was written
by the autocorrect iphone fill in the blanks thing the predictive text that's the
whole script is written by predictive text fight your way to the warehouse take secondary
objectives take two human shields defeat 20 enemies achieve 15 accuracy freeze arrived at
the west harbor warehouse is ready to do the deal but the money drop has gone bad detective maria
mendoza was waiting for you and the columbians were dead before you got there the police are
about to swarm the area and mendoza is going to pin a double murder on you escape by any
means r1 okay look at them i love the playlist down there that's not playing
can i drive a car put down your weapons now
okay not good well you were gonna pin a double murder on me but now i actually have like a
quadruple murder isn't i thought the whole purpose of this was to get out of here
and not shit i gotta get out of here she's gonna i've been framed for a double murder
might as well go for a septuple kill actually climb i thought i was going for a stealth kill
this game just sucks
this is just the beginning of every pub g match
vr streamer what's up my kneesy press to lean around corners
what no wait hold on up is who's driving over me what's up man oh you can just talk
why is he talking about crust i'm not even sure this just classifies as a pizza somebody
just i opened my mouth and somebody just took the big vat of restaurant industry tomato sauce
and just threw it into my face
how do i not get exploded there's a what where are you
there's a health pack can i fall into the health pack and be alive oh i just touched it
i gotta jesus turn off the fence power grid wait it's electrified
you ain't getting out of here shit i just have to come on
where's this guy what how do i get off of fire i'm still on fire
okay it doesn't really bother him that much turn off the power grid
where's the power grid turn off the power
please god have mercy on me shoot it through up there how the hell do i go ladder is there
just follow the green gas uh the green gas is up there uh shoot the lock open the door the door
is electrified fence go around i mean go around where to go in this building there's
a door near the red car right how the fuck do you did you know that wait what you're talking
about this one what okay i'm almost dead blind do you see how much fucking pizza crust is on this
do you see this make it full screen can i touch this
yeah it's it's definitely even crustier for you guys it has to go through a compression
a play it's like a planner i was gonna say virtual boy is there health i need health
give that to me i'm not doing why is he on fire
this is one guy left i think give up fuck face press the i can't even see what that says
it's either it's a button press the button to zoom your weapon right bumper okay i just i
guessed what i shot like his head off what the fuck go to your car down the alley up
no don't kill me i gotta get i'm just gonna walk out of here i've got him now
hey
that guy did it not me i need help i have to complete the okay i got two objectives complete
all right now let him go get out of the way get out of here i'm not having 23 24 murders
stop vr quality aiming right there come on oh use the key to open the garage door
they had fire extinguishes back then i have to get to my ride can i drive that car all right
whoa easy there pal give me the health fuck that here take my wallet how do i open the door
all right watch out i need to open this no don't kill me i'm not gonna kill stay calm and don't move
these pigs don't fuck around just don't hurt the hostage
all right get out go whoa hold on i need you again come here for a second
so
oh my god okay just don't shoot the hostage leave don't shoot that hostage leave that hostage
alone i love the there he is can't aim from here
surrender immediately we need health though
if we play a hidden object game it's called can you even see the people down there i can't
one guy left health health anywhere around here i just don't want to do this all over again
it's my car thank god i'm in deep shit now i gotta call sean
oh
this shit is crazy popo was up in there i was bucking them fools and barely got away
hold up hold up it's like they knew what the fuck are you talking about
it's gone the columbians were dead when i fucking got there i don't panic
meet me at your crib in two hours is he here oh this is a double cross it's all good
i better get my cut chill call you later okay cool get to your car i got a new outfit
some decals a beanie they didn't spend any time at all doing a double cross scenario took
them five minutes please don't play this for eight hours i'll be lucky if i play this for
eight more minutes i just need to see i'm trying to get out of the crew and they're
coming after you because it's gonna make meeting sean at your apartment more difficult
head to your apartment but try to avoid the police you don't need to see any more of this
can i get in a car there's got to be a car sequence here get to your apartment quietly
this is mine did you not read i just don't got i don't i know it said quietly but i i
don't do it i don't care no get in there be quiet i can't climb over that it's pretty
quiet i can give one more time one more time one more one more one more one more one more one more
that's it which one of these is mine that is this one my apartment didn't really tell us which
one it was stay off this chat what are they doing what did i join the wrong discord what
are you talking about can i go in this door what's that stain on he's controlling someone
did you hear that he's jedi mind tricking somebody i can't go in there no i want no give
me the other weapon how do i cycle weapons stop screaming how do i cycle weapons i can't there
it is okay wow oh my god oh my god
oh this head was made in a paper mache that's not my fault where is this guy
here's what's stuck anymore which one is mine 27 28 29 how do you do this silently
silently that's weird 30 it's pretty good orson well's voice it's probably at the end of this
yeah i would assume it is is a 900 TV and i'm selling it for 100 bucks
did i say that or did somebody else say that 900 TV was one of the offices
can't stop this hit the button
die here give me help all right get in my apartment it's probably this one with the
light on it 15 could have just opened it there's my house there's my bed what do i just do with this
there's the 900 TV uh i guess we're just gonna keep going this way
but building for apartment 25 so this is it wasn't 30 it's up here
a girl now then you take my fucking money till i get my cheddar you haven't i need to make a withdrawal
apartment 25 to life there he is who's shooting what the hell is this
what is going on out here okay no he got up he got up he actually got up no he didn't
how do i have a sniper rifle and i can't kill you from this far away
there's another one he keeps coming back this guy does not quit well now you don't have a
head anymore there's got to be health in my house anything else in here what about okay
hold on i need to make sure what about my tv what happened to my door oh my tv sucks
damn it take it can i swap it out first person mode
can i swap it with the okay now let's do this night let's go with this
i'm gonna go the back door okay
he's gonna play this for eight hours no i'm not gonna play i'm just gonna get to the car
sequence where i can drive it's gonna be next what's that that looks like something i can
interact with why can i what's the point of coming back here return to your car what was
the point of being able to come behind here immersion it's called world immersion there's
a hole in the fence you liar why no there's no hole in these god i couldn't even see it
how do you even see that go back to the car and then let me drive it keep saying that
faction i'm dead what's up my knees i'm the fucking man easy why is it just a yellow button
let's go i would have to do that whole thing again all right coming up next i kind of need to
buy no i can't play this one yet i can't this one is the 12 hour game
i'll just let's do it fuck it put it in this is without warning this game is a two has a 12
hour time limit on it i can't do this one i'm gonna put it in hold on hold on hold on like
let me let me just take a piss i'll be right back first piss of the night this is another
capcom game we put a lot of capcom games i've noticed i have 12 hours to beat this game
i read the back of the box you have 12 hours the clock is ticking play as six
different characters and experience the game from each of their perspectives unique timeline
element i gotta plug 12 hours without warning well let me mute so you don't blow your eardrums
out opening this fresh beer it's a coke just kidding all right ah english without warning
welcome to the rest of the stream everybody subtitles make sure they're on
one let me just look at them no vibration please display screen brightness it's probably
the screen brightness here we go i better hurry the fuck up circle studio presents
you have 12 hours i have 1900 hours to beat this what a lie all right i can relax
daniel's chemical plant that's like three or four years
you don't see the knife he was very clearly brandishing a knife see the counter is counting
down to secure the plant to find and rescue all hostages and to eliminate any terrorists you
encounter secure eliminate protect it kyle rivers you're counting down let's go
but get me that story you remember he's used for hey wow do not do that to your boss let me
just make sure i make that really really clear here don't touch your boss's face don't slap
your boss in the fucking mouth that's a quick way for you to get insta fired and potentially
like charges pressed on you uh yeah whatever you say as we have suggests they're led by
he's prom the anti-capitalist movement and although he's a french canadian
he's been operating out of the middle of the last 20 years
i thought that lady was just being the same so far durbeck has made no demand
we're getting a lot of different characters and names simply be to blow the plant if he does
the explosion will kill everything and everyone in a two-mile radius oh no not the anti-capitalist
we could be looking at over 300 000 civilian dead he must be stopped an executive order
has been issued and verified is not to leave the plant here we go 20 hours wait did this i had
how many hours did i get 12 hours you have 12 hours why do they why do i have 20 this is
command clear out the local area to establish sorry uh clear establish entry point and wait
further instruction eliminate durbar we have uploaded blueprints of the area to your pda command
out by the numbers people stay sharp why is it counting up should it be coming down
it's counting up and find cover it's a clock yeah but i thought i thought it's supposed to be
counting down 12 hours follow your original oh it's inverted uh i need to change that
immediately to move around use the left analog stick move the camera use the right analog
stick to raise your gun hold the r1 button down lightly to fire hold the r1 r1 button down
firmly now just no inversion okay let's go don't change this is bad to lock onto an enemy move
the crosshair over them and then hold down l1 when it turns yellow no this is only available
in standard only in here oh my eyes for real it's too zoomed in this is the shark game again i'm
gonna throw up it's gonna happen again jones is the area secure looks clear fire in the whole
america we're compromised they were waiting for us this is no terrorist sale it's a goddamn
army what's your position i'm in the water treatment plant i just lost jones only reagan
and hooper are still alive the rest of the team are kia request mission status over
mission parameters remain intact this whole america all of america parameters remain intact
copy that command we have no contingency rivers it's down to you over i need intel are
we linked to the security cameras we have a visual on the hostages they're being held in
the cracking towers the doors may be locked down but intel shows the lock controls are in the
tunnel reagan should be able to open them proceed with extreme pre rivers out okay now
where do i go the crouch press where you have to crouch behind a crate press r1 to break
cover and fire how much health do i have this already said 30 fps like 12 fps with 30 fov
how do i open that why does it zoom in can i just take it how do i open this what do i
just okay that's grenade open med kit i'm good all right all right i admit this is bad all
right this is really bad i don't have 11 hours in 49 moments to beat this i only have 11 and a
half more hours oh capcom made this though you know i mean like come on capcom it's like a
time shooter give me some slack i was it was worth a shot total missing hostage statistics
41 total people missing was i supposed to save anybody capcom made a bunch of shitty games
during this era you know what you're right they did you know we're going to jack hooper this
twin might be time to get a good one in here it might be time to put freedom fighters in
that's a good one command to hooper what's your status over we got ambushed small arms both
sides rpgs we're at least two men down take a breath hot swap the disc focused hooper we
need you to make your way through the storage fields to the docks and secure the area what do
you think will happen if i hot swap the disc copy that copy that copy that you map screen
shows the route to any objectives you have complete press select button to access it is
there a timer no there's no time to roll hold down l1 and press x did i i got baited to play
this receiving me i'm here laughing there is speed it up come on i think i'm dead i just
don't hot swap the disc there are just no there's no countdown mechanic
putting in freedom fighters i gave up on that real quick i thought it was gonna make me sick
okay that's that that happened is is it actually possible to blue screen at playstation
i'm surprised i didn't even know that was possible
trigger console is a nicely ungrateful streamer it's fine challenge everything
freedom fighters now this is a real game i think we're essentially playing the last game that
was just on the screen but much better you still love the multiplayer yeah i don't think
ever i don't ever play it britain reluctantly joins the communist block despite us protests
mid-range nuclear missiles are placed in cuba world war three uh the mexican communist
party celebrates disputed victory in presidential election what happens in 2004 uh oh in 2004
world war three erupts yesterday reports of low-flying drones from all over the
u.s.a government dismisses the sightings as weather balloons hey we know i gotta give them
a little bit of credit here they could have easily had been like 2006 no no yesterday could
be at any point that was in 2000 1999 it could take this could take place in 2019 right like
in regard to the game it's a timeless game now submarines are so cool holy shit
thank you they kind of are submarines are so cool all right i'm ready germo you're a nerd
that's all right that's fine with me checking memory card uh yes just make sure we got some
stuff selected uh video get this shit in widescreen uh-oh my screen's too big 16 by 9
sound what are you doing don't turn the music down choose difficulty this is important
demonstrator a walk in the park rebel have a blast freedom fighter you got what it takes
revolutionary against all odds so this is easy normal hard and impossible
i'm gonna go with normal i'm a rebel have a blast uh what's my name man delete he's playing
on easy mode this is not easy mode this is the normal difficulty who cares tom i'm not
playing on easy i'm playing on normal name it that face when propaganda i shh anyway when
i couldn't pinpoint the exact location of my humble summer cottage in the hamptons
she dropped me right there 60 fps damn i look like an idiot still holding the drinks i've been
paying for all night well who cares you know her loss he popped the clutch let's get on
with it let's start for the work seat today bro let's see isabella angelina a condo in
midtown manhattan drain plug and leaky garbage disposal god do we have to get the crappiest
route every monday morning play is this guy i wish for once we get a fancy condo on the east
side with a view whoa isabella angel whatever she's that hot spokes babe for the warning
against red's movement i saw her on tv yesterday no idea besides i don't follow all that
conspiracy crap like you do what do you mean conspiracy crap well doesn't the soviet invasion
of south america bother you you need a reality check bro know what next thing you know you'll
be waking up under a russian flag and you won't think it's conspiracy crap then right
you're so in denial but try listening to those warning against red's guys what
speaking of which how about this oh are we painters they like to check out the plumbing
oh plumbers hello plumber's on patrol anybody home
no wonder sister sludge sure needs a drain surgeon here uh there is one here freeze
don't move remain calm whoa hey stay i was right i was right i was right where is your
girlfriend citizen girlfriend hey she's not that was a meaty punch i will ask again where
is isabella angelina what her look i think back end look she's not like i had a really
wet face that was a wet slap i want to see a lawyer buddy my place this guy manhattan
invasion okay let's go so this is this is a retelling of if world war three happened
right let me read the back of the box i don't have a back of the box it just came as a single
disc i have a wrench so i'm actually playing as the plumber what it is fortunate that you
found me quickly this way who's talking oh this guy all right nice reaction time
he won't trouble us anymore that was unbelievable hurry we mustn't linger here
you're the one leading more soldiers shoot them get the guy up there oh no i'm out of bullets
we must leave now can i pick up okay bullets in the ground how you reload the gun see those
soldiers down there we are not as well supplied as the enemy so we'll have to improvise l3 is
aimed at the fuel barrels rather than the soldiers that well bye-bye that was kind
of a half second delay there i think i did like a full flip um was i supposed to get
hit by that much i just got a bomb dropped on me you're wounded take that medical kit
behind the ambulance got it how do i use it r3 bring up the inventory and select the med kit
with the left analog stick and just let it go i'm assuming yep and then r1 good you are
ready for battle again we're not out of the woods yet it's us or them where are we going
so does it don't go down to take a swing at me oh he's wounded you have a help man
save this man's life do i get to have like i guess i owe you one pal watch our status okay
come with me guys i've got supplies 25 charisma do you have stat points in this game
where'd they go i don't know they went they went too fast okay grab a molotov let's show the reds
okay press and hold r3 is it so it's just like red dead redemption throw those babies where would
you like me to throw it like over here oh yeah that was a big throw you actually have to do
a jump shot is there anymore i think i did that so well the game doesn't understand that
i got them all in one throw just get the pistol back out who are you shooting at stand up no time
to waste they'll be back if we don't hurry you get to control in whole army somebody said really
open this manhole with your wrench we can escape to safety below in the soup
it's kind of chunky it's all right it's a little crusty but not you can have a little
bit of crust how does opening a manhole give me more charisma because it's scary down there
can i get out of my plumber outfit it's a warp pipe citizens of new york and comrades from the
soviet armed forces welcome to our first news broadcast after today's events my name is
tatiana kempinski and i will be your regular news anchor from now on we hope in time to
take a cooperation of most of your familiar tv personalities once they return from a re
education program at that training facilities in a small yellow sponge man i will make sure you get
all necessary information about our efforts to restore peace and stability the kids that live
on street next door to you our soviet leaders have been concerned for years by the plight of
the poor american people suffering under a corrupt regime today we have finally succeeded
in liberating the suppressed masses of americans from further hardship and we will
soon restore law and order in a new rule of government and they expect and believe that
every citizen will spare allegiance to this new order cooperate and you will reap all the
benefits of the soviet system all measure of resistance will be futile and dealt with
swiftly a great leader comrade general tatarin will be addressing the nation later so on behalf
of the dedicated staff here at the studio and the glorious soviet armed forces welcome new
york to a better future that was an easy invasion so we live down in the sewers
we make an army in the sewer and then we come back up and we fight well gaming this is called
freedom fighters this is the hq the brooklyn rebel base to enter a location go to the
map and press x this is our base it's a safe zone we store equipment here with complete
control of the sewer system the tunnels enable us to bypass many of the soviet roadblocks
interesting all of our maps will indicate the location of the sewer access points
let us go over to the table take a look at the map this police station and post office
okay what about like the post office the post office is a soviet stronghold
your brother is being held somewhere inside raise your flag on the roof to signal our
victory to get me the police station you'll have to destroy a sniper's nest on the gas station
okay destroy sniper's nest on gas station raise your flag on the roof to signal victory
to get to the police station you'll have to destroy the sniper's nest on the gas station
destroy gas station and raise flag on post office all right the post office is a soviet
stronghold they're gonna send a plumber to go assault a soviet stronghold yeah
from plumber to sniper elite in two steps all right here we go is that a is this a bad guy
no no i see the red white and blue man i gotta talk to you what's up want to blow that guy's
station you're gonna need some explosives you can find some in the other neighborhood
find a manhole press x and select another location so i have to go blow that guy's station
you're gonna need i need to get explosives you can find some in the other neighborhood
so i gotta go to the other i gotta go to the other neighborhood so i gotta go to the
find a manhole and we're gonna go to the other another location the post office is a soviet
stronghold it is used as a supply depot to support uh maybe not to the same one he didn't
have one right next to him or anything all right well let's just go do i actually have to go
back to the warp pipe and go to the other location so i have to go to the police station
well i didn't know if i wanted me to do that now i can't just go explore
so how do i select the another one secure the police station and liberate our leader isabella
raise your flag to signal her release the police officers will assist you but they need your
help taking blind chains on the nearby gas station i can't select any of these other
i'm in that one the ones in the middle i can't select troops advancing into the city
your brother is being held somewhere inside raise secure the i can go to the police station
if the police station is the other location that's the only one i have i thought you guys
talking about like i need to pick a different sewer in the post office one i knew i could
go to the police station just didn't know i could if i could select the other sewers
manholes all right let's go so look for explosives in the other neighborhood here
is there any stuff in this game should i be worried about stealth i'm just kind of go
no these are okay these are just cops please help we're pinned down here all right c4
uh why who just shot me in the head what hey
i can't believe it we're just a fucking plumber
approach i didn't know that i was gonna insta die
they're like standing in the same spot okay so the tiny little window right there do not move
but i'm i have to pick up the c4 help we're pinned down here all right i'm fucking ducking
grab the c4 find a manhole and select another location so i have to go to the other so
that's an explosive got it so i'm just abandoning them i just took their ammunition
and leaving see you later post office what an asshole yeah really the post office i blow up
the sniper's nest oh would you look at that so that's the guy somebody said the gimmick is
you just gotta bounce back and forth between levels and it's a rpg shooter puzzle yo man
i gotta talk to you you do i have the explosives now check that you found some c4 all you gotta
do now is blow everything's interlinked all right blow the gas station you got it let's go
holding in the left thumb stick and moving right stick is kind of who's the other guy
okay saw it rifle wait where was he did he come out of the trash what the fuck okay
uh that might be a good guy no way pal no one gets by until isabella is free
okay so i gotta remember this spot at least there's no oh look a new sewer so i now i've
unlocked the sewer now let me just look at something here post office can i no bonfire
lit what the nuts i can do over here over the guy behind the fence can i talk to him i guess
not you can save it i'll save it right now are you sure you want a quick save yep what is the
name of this shitty game hey whoa hey this freedom fighters can i go through here let me
take a look is there another is it like a i don't know there's a crouch a gas station
gonna blow that up another sewer they seem kind of in the what's the purpose of having three
of these sewers right here as save points does he even have ape escape i do not have it here
but eventually probably gonna get it all right what we got place c4 explosive walk to the base
of the large fuel tanks and press x i thought it was the gas i thought it was the tanks the
gas you know what i'm saying these are on a timer oh god snipers have been eliminated
from the gas tank now we can go back and help the officers right that doesn't explode
all right now let's go back no wait wait raise the flag raise the flag on top how does one get on
top how do we get up there no i don't have to do that that's in the other place right
uh which one was it secure the police station and liberate our leader here we go just play
wolfenstein who said that was a bernie sanders voice all right let's see what now what
you're gonna join me join my team i helped you're the only one left that's not good thanks friend
nice to get rid of the snipers listen if you're going to infiltrate the police station i recommend
you use the subway tunnel you can maybe go around more bullshit subway tunnel okay well
there we go you mean this thing right here wait hold on okay i just want to do it i'm
gonna come out here he's gonna go captivated well that did not expect them to be right here
all right i only have i have no bullets actually still i've known that what what can i i don't
have i guess i have to wrench these guys i can molotov i have 10 molotovs what that is
perfectly in a place where i can't hit them come on just lean into it give me a bolt
yeah give me that give me give me whoa whoa whoa hide hide nice any more people in the
hallway i got a med kit there's a couple of me like you can't even talk no bullets in anything
all right let's go in the game auto aims just snaps to people
everyone's kind of scarce in this game i don't why are you standing here
the parking garage but stay low or the soldiers will spot you
why didn't you do what have you been doing okay the police station through the parking
parking garage stay low or the soldiers will spot you stay low i'm gonna go through here
can i just headshot this guy
okay there oh yeah there's so there's a million people here how am i gonna do this
i have to get in through the parking garage but the parking garage is closed
what the hell are you doing they're looking for me oh shit no this no this
that's not fair you went through the fucking wall not fair you went through the goddamn wall
defend here defend stand your ground defend this area what are you talking to
that's not fair you hacker
okay so i'm gonna go down there regroup
stay low stay low i went the right way the first time what about any of the weapons or
guns down here swap weapons this is a shotgun i feel like i don't want to use maybe we'll try it
can i do that with the pistol though um no i can't only one slot that's unfortunate
are we talking politics in the chat that's a banned topic we don't talk politics here
i better not be seeing any politics in this chat well there's some stuff in here
this game is politics this is not even this is fake politics
that's like saying when you watch 24 it's a nice politics this is fiction
holy fuck oh fuck i'll tell you for a playstation 2 game the shooting is actually kind of fun
the guy up here where are they outside what come on come on got it i'm getting killed though
you want to play this on a harder difficulty all of you everybody regroup all of you strange
all right um i need to heal so i gotta get up to the roof all right dead everybody else
health pack i'm getting the hang of this i'm gonna go up some more
i gotta plant the flag on the ceiling just go up i just don't even stop why would i stop
oh that's why because i can't go up any further than this nope nope computer
solitaire was solitaire in another video game or is it this one are we still in the same game
we are right you had 60 ammo for the shotgun and you're already out
yeah because these guys take three hits
oh one i lied
holy fucking jeez what the where is he to the right help me who said that somebody in here
oh that's isabella go to the flag and press x to hoist the stars and stripes
here we go that's all i have to do you have to just put up your flag and then they'll have
to leave oh he put up flag let's go home there are 200 of us down here nah this is the equipment
of playing like call of duty online this is our building it has our name on it don't you see
no you destabilize their economy first then raise your flag all right now i got three
people here work demolishing the fuel station we're able to move around at our leisure now
that the snipers are gone okay got any of that okay so we got police station post office now
the post office is a soviet stronghold it is used as a supply depot to support so we need
to raise the flag on the post office your brother is being held somewhere inside raise your
flag on the roof to signal our victory to get near the police station you'll have to
destroy a sniper's nest on the gas station so to get near the police station your brother's
being held instead of just gotta go to the post office that doesn't sound anything like
burning i mean it kind of does it's not perfect but it sounds similar all right so follow me
chris i'll take you to the safe house get my shotty yeah so you know this guy's like yeah
i'll let you know isabella you're back yes and i owe it all to this man and you must be chris
come on in lol all right you lead the way this is only a temporary base we're using it as a
staging place for this mission staging let's plan for this our next move what and or not
you have a new bike session now you all right you okay you probably take you first sit down
you need a glass of water here we have an overview of the enemy compound you can see
them unloading equipment they're using this post office as a temporary command center
i'm planning further advances into the city get flag on top of their flag really set them
back if we recapture this area you won't ever since you proved yourself by rescuing me
people are starting to believe in you i'm playing operation and i'm hitting the sides
i'll let you lead two of my best men in action god damn it the funny bone doesn't go
there walk up to each of the freedom fighters and press x to recruit them let's go
Roger that let's roll oh i can't touch anything fall in you got it they'll never know what hit
them as long as they're recruited these guys will follow you wherever you go just like
get that guy no wait wait wait how do i wait
pull out here yes sir fall back wilco hold on wait we're taking fire hit the dock
wait stop moving regroup moving out where's the other guy regroup where did the other guy go
all right what the fuck are we supposed to do defend this area that's defend position
defend i'll be right here scout that area there's also scout check over there around here
report activity find the reds observe enemy abort get back here you guys good job they're
very fast all right because i don't know how the hell to get out of this building
detect and report remember jesus you are a leader you can issue a leader command
or shoot them to attack that small patrol
stop please go fight good you're meant every enemy in the
is he dead one of these die i have to relax where's he at the spot number great you're a
true leader no sometimes it's important to know when to attack i'm gonna target get on top of
the container okay was that a bad guy can we i think we can finally be out of this nonsense
of the buzzing so we have to go up here can i get through this way remember to check the
map once in a while what button is that okay that's what we're standing we're gonna get to
the post office on the map you can see the mission objectives it's easy to get lost so
use the map to find your targets they might make life easier for you
got it wipe them out i didn't like i just walked into the barrel and it didn't die
there's too many fucking land mines here i don't have any health take them out take them out
take them down get them eliminate them bring it on hit their position
oh
oops touchdown
didn't save i'm i'm right here he's standing behind the explosive barrels
there well they you can't really not stand behind them they're everywhere
follow me chris i'll take shit take you to the safe house
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i know hi hi hi hi let us in you're back yes and i owe it all
to this man and you must be chris come on in open open yes i know what happens these are the
friends we gotta go back up okay i gotta save this time god damn it this is only a temporary
base we're using it as a staging place for this mission let's plan our next move nice holster
like it or not you have a new profession velcro on my back freedom fighter this game got fun
i don't know if this is 12 hour stream kind of fun but it's still fun to play
freedom fighter here we have an overview of the enemy compound you can see them unloading
equipment they're using this post office as a temporary command center and planning further
advances into the city from here let me do that i gotta get them back if we recapture this area
you won't be alone ever since you proved yourself by rescuing me and the story starting
to believe in you there's a pc version that's pretty sweet i'll let you lead two of my best
follow me into action let's go you know where to go that way get them these guys will follow
you wherever you go just like bodyguards right hold back hold back hold back is there i need to
remember you are the leader you can issue your men commands recruit to attack that small patrol
watch for soviets good your men will fight every enemy in the direction you're pointing them
why do i like help this guy run to that get back here i need a save point god damn it
destroy that observe and all right hold back fall back great regroup you're a true leader
now sometimes it's important to know when to fall back
on top of the container i'm just gonna shoot the red i didn't do anything take the skin
hit them
draw oh fuck i need bullets bring it on stop doing that noise who's on my team
check our print check over there oh i can't handle the noise i don't have any med kits either
oh it's a hearing test it really does sound like a hearing test and you guys have a med
kit i have to go this way search over there scout ahead detect and report remember to check the
map once in a while i know on the map you can see the mission objectives it's easy to get
lost get in there check them out i'm gonna die sound is killing me i can't i'm sorry
i'm gonna change there's a pc version i gotta change i'm sorry that that noise is gonna haunt
all right i hope you guys are ready for me to put in a game that i think we're gonna be on for a
while we're gonna play psyops the mind gate conspiracy damn i want to like keep playing
that too just like i couldn't i was feeling that buzz in my teeth is it because i blue
screened no i wasn't doing it for the first like 30 40 minutes we were in that game
uh this is one of the most requested games for the playstation 2
five waiting room like you don't get to eat fucking cake every day okay you gotta eat
vegetables and like meat you don't just eat strawberry ice cream every day okay let's see
the special features we're gonna check that out first it's a music video is this gonna be
like the license like batman forever they just put in oh my god that yeah it is seal kiss from
a rose they just put in batman forever movie clips is that supposed to be the main character
of psyops um i had enough of that psyops the mind gate conspiracy what's the extra content
cooperative play all right i'm ready i was watching that yeah well now no nobody after
the stream is over is going to be watching it elite elite elite no no these are playstation
2 games man they're hard as shit here's your man nick scryer facial reconstruction and
a memory wipe intelligence has the movement attack in the refinery in about 90 hours
this memory wipe will give us plenty of time to drop in all spooky scary movement
cy probes i've done some homework on mine gate your boys got quite a reputation and it's not
all good okay he's no boy scout but nick scryer is mind gate's best they dismissed general
kriger but scryer stayed with mine gate and took his psychic hands he's got like lizard hands
like ripping people's heads off well getting coxed yeah we are unfortunately
so that was like 30 years ago fast forward into 20 years ago no no no no no that
okay i thought there was a didn't i see a flashback of this
i did glittering that's what you get for throwing a cigarette into the ocean
don't do that shit i think the fish down there they're gonna have to smell that tobacco dispose
of your cigarettes in a timely manner in an ashtray and throw the ashtray into a trash
bag and then tie the trash bag up and throw the trash back in the trash first contact
wow he's throwing the bazooka i only had one bullet in there we don't have any more
just throw it
no what do you mean no i'm gonna get a nuke what
i didn't even see it i'm not a nuke
all right what the hell are you guys doing
oh five waiting room huh what about this one
the movement the movement the movement the movement it's a lot of medals
did i get it i got the gun who's doing this i have no idea what's going on
sir no that was my friend take this one to solitary forgot that the oscars are tonight
nick you're finally here are they who's even nominated nick i don't know william defoe is
bird fox is going to win best meme movie how the hell do you know my name i can help you
get out of here but you have to trust me trust you trust this for now at least just get out
of the cell block and meet me okay so meet up at the supply room where the supply room damn she
seems familiar whether i should trust her killer ah whatever at least he gave me a gun it's
better than kicking the nuts uh why would she kick you in the nuts escape from solitary
confinement and meet the female agent in the supply room the pistol is silenced to aid in
stealth press r1 to fire your selected weapon stealth can i do anything else
press the l3 button towards a wall or object for wall move and the okay wall move just need
to check it out see how it works crouch i think i did is there a sensitivity option
no auto locks okay kick that i need to stand up give me that gun uh soldiers drop their
weapons when killed weapons can be picked up okay anybody in here do i get to store the med kit
inventory supply select to access inventory power-ups can restore health and psi energy
okay search the compound for more power-ups so i select this i can use that no reason
me to use it right now pistol ammo and just okay you can just boot shit anything in these
enemies nothing no oh it hurts so bad this is when i get my psychic brain powers
okay so stealth i have to be quiet in real life too enemies can see what did that say press to
lock onto an enemy or object wait wait wait so i can hold the button down to strafe
so the triangle is to lock on somebody did i i locked on in it and he no what i'm trying
just to fucking figure out how to control the game how are you still living after that
i have one bullet left how do i switch guns didn't i get pistol ammo yeah okay so i can
strafe my whole triangle it's time to kick something maybe well nobody else even down here
so we've been playing shoot man games uh well this is this game is not a shoot man game
this is the first little area and then you turn into a psychic the force unleashed maniac
it's too bad that stump man too was so fun but it was too crusty and i can get the better version
of it uh anything else i can do any more stuff to look at i don't think so all right give me
the silence gun stepping over metal or puddles will alert your enemies short rapid shoot short
rapid shots or burst fire is can i at least read the tutorial i gotta heal uh this is a
25% health 50% health watch the greats don't worry i promise i'll do that to somebody
need a key card anybody coming don't step on the grate critical body parts can be maybe like
this key card let's move that guy sucked okay where is she laughing my ass off what took you
so long where'd they take my squad that didn't take very long at all but you're not
ready nick you have to recover your abilities i'm ready to go now you need to find something
he just fucking sucks laughing my ass off oh don't do that to me again don't you
it's for your own good the hell it is it was just air it was just air calm down
i'm inside the movement as a double agent i can keep helping you as long as i don't get caught
what did you give me first things first you don't have security clearance but if you
trip the switch all security beams will go down then you can make your way to the elevator
to get to the second floor here's the keys the generator here's my american express before they
discover you've escaped be careful where you use it though because nobody takes it anymore
let me get my institute for that come on what's in your wallet not like this my gate
training facility 12 years ago telekinesis training here we go all right nick let's start
your telekinesis training to keep it simple i'm going to start referring to telekinesis as tk from
now on tk also we've juiced you up with unlimited psi powers during this test hey thanks in the
real world all psi powers drained with you we'll skip the spoon binding and start by
controlling tk5 first select a target to tk by moving the aim retapool over the object first
always refer to the hut for control instructions stand at the edge of the map
and do tk pulse to the three friends you're playing with it's guaranteed that you'll
fucking annoy the hell out of them and they won't want to play with you anymore
okay target object with aim okay pressing hold l1 select and lift ob so l1 is selecting
the lift object and right analog stick if you haven't figured it out nick the telekinesis
button is pressure sensitive so the pressure applied determines the height of lift i got
that's not going to work with my shitty mad cats controller to continue your training
do i even have that my pressure sensitive button is not that's not going to work
all right nick next i want you to get over this wall it's too high for you to jump a
climb over so use tk to arrange and stack so you admit press and hold l1 to select
and lift object move object with the right analog stick and release it uh yeah so i'm just
gonna jump over them okay that's easy enough why do i have two two minutes and 43 seconds
today i just tried to jump come on why are you turning to the left climb it nice climbing
nick i want you to use telekinesis to move a crate through each hole in the wall this
is just destroy all humans but with less hey laughing my ass off don't throw the
crate easily first get a crate through the hole on the lower left
move crate through the hole press the yeah until it's at the desired height move the object with
the right analog stick mm-hmm god damn god damn it guys i don't think i can play this with
dumb bootleg controller okay let's try it again what i want you to use telekinesis to move
oh the left hole okay i'm pressing it as lightly as possible i think it can i oh man this is
gonna be hard to do all right i can get it now move a crate through the hole in the center
i can get the ones that are tall now pick up a crate for the last hole
okay the multi lift high for a normal tk lift you will need to use a technique called tk
multi lift refer to the herd to walk you through the technique release lift an object
to its maximum height release l1 then quickly press and hold l1 again to lift an object
higher okay so you go like this and then you it's all the way at the top okay come back this
way good job the next section is through the door behind you now to the good stuff let's use
telekinesis to throw objects at live targets but don't worry these guys can't wait this is
gonna be great first use tk to throw a crate at the stationary test subject these guys just
stump man with the right analog stick in the direction of test subject and then release l1 to
throw object
now try and hit a moving target okay well i doubt i got it that guy was moving
this guy's just trying to run away now isn't it finally try to hit a moving on an irregular
oh please god don't hit me got him now that you you can also tk most enemies
take up that guy and throw him against the wall a few times his weapon will drop after he
dies okay let's try it again that was cool oh god damn it now to the good
now killing people in training that's good fun isn't it it is good fun you're right
trying to hit a target moving on an irregular path oops no no shake the gun out of this guy
that didn't count no no no no no no let you practice throwing objects you can all
right from against the wall pick up that guy and throw him against the wall a few times
his weapon will prop damn keep throwing them into walls this is not even a training exercise
that guy just shot actual bullets at me now tk the next time and while he's in the air
use your weapon to shoot it so i did the first guy you've got it nice okay fun there's
another gun right in front of you nick target it and tk throw it to yourself to collect the ammo
oh that's cool all right let's see how you handle a live combat situation soldiers will charge
into the room and attack you from all sides try and use cover while eliminating the threats
use the explosive barrels to your advantage you can also use the assault rifle but don't rely on
your gun kill the designated number of enemies using tk in some way you have limited health and
tk firearm kill five enemies using tk within the time limit use assault rifle if needed
and you can shield yourself behind objects all right oh shit you can throw them into the
barrels dead who's left oh fuck i died i got too i kicked right in the chest there's
another gun right in front i was having too much fun all right killed five enemies didn't i
didn't kill five people how is that possible got him into his friend there's another guy
sometimes i feel like it doesn't work when i let go nice work squad maybe someday you'll
be as good as me right into the box that dude's gonna be a boss probably when you get killed
you may choose to continue from the most recent checkpoint that was reached if you wish to save
your progress like the save checkpoint option from the pause menu okay uh you create a new
save that resumes play at the safe checkpoint so just gotta pause and hit save game don't
let me forget that so now i got my pk powers let's put them to good use so i have a key
card now that was gonna where was that gonna take me do i have a map or anything yeah
so i need to go uh where am i approximate location so i need to go
down to the generator room or actually straight ahead maybe yeah already law i just i'd spent a
i just did like an entire tutorial i don't remember what the hell the last thing i was
supposed to do was checkpoint is straight ahead so the objectives of the green things
okay oh there's even more i can only afford one color you picked green this is like every
room uh all right i actually don't know what the fuck i'm supposed to do that cut scene felt like
ages ago ow i just jumped into the laser grid whoops so i gotta turn that off just look at
the map again do i have to turn that shit off i mean that's the this this was on the objective
is there anything else i need to do in here no no no it's the room before this
i can't believe i just have to heal now tk the laser i don't think that'll do anything
okay wait is there was a room here wasn't there what was this this is that room with
the guy's head okay so we have to go this way so then from here i could go down
fucking mad cats it's not even a mad cat's controller anyways it's not a mad cat's
controller i don't even know what it is fucking of course i can't i can't do a light
touch mad because bad controller well let me at least heal all right this might this is the the
this is the look you can throw that at somebody can i throw this up
got him oh my god mad because cats now lift him up i want to throw him up in the air
is he still falling no he's right here i'm so confused where the fuck did you guys come from
oh that waterfall is so loud i can't even hear anything oh i went down there too it was very
unnecessary but i had to do it shut them off they're too loud good job nick what the hell is
this where are you i'm speaking to you inside your mind through telepathy telepathy those
that work for the general is it is so spooky nick hurry get a key card in the
guard room to use the elevator key card from the guard room new objective
so i can go through the i'll just open the laser door
let's go this way just using her chakra well didn't know you were gonna be here wait barrel
i'll be right back okay i'm back let's do it why turn the camera you don't just come here
fucking god damn it how am i able here we go this brings us back here we need to go
oh look at the map so i need to go to the guard room where's the guard room generator room
guard room is right through here at least it should be guard room upstairs where's the guard
room no i'm not in the right place destroy all humans this is not correct this is back in the
playroom how do i get i gotta go to the elevator how do i get to the this section
here security lower silo i think i was supposed to stay down there shit was i supposed to stay down
there what the hell am i now shotgun that's my secret item i think i did that's pretty cool
best weapon of the game really that's pretty cool all right so if i go up this way
just out of curiosity i wonder if i let's start here
uh that's like the beginning of the game does take me anywhere well i thought that was a person
he threw a gun away with full ammo yeah but i got the new secret loot one what's that
i think i came back there what was your favorite weapon in halo 3 um i don't know
this is yeah this is just back at the beginning
the default assault rifle that you get at the beginning of the game that's the only
weapon i think i've ever seen in that game all right this is the cell okay which i just keep
i don't know where the fuck i'm supposed to go this is the guard room
huh there's so many halo boomers in the chat
it was a celebrated franchise yeah where's that go a guard room is can i go down for
an elevator or something it's a total college game bro it was go down from here and now i
have no idea i i haven't been there i've been okay found it found it got it got it got it got
it got it good good good okay i want to shoot that guy big okay i really am gonna run out
of ammo aren't i it's that supply room again okay down no no no no no this is incorrect
what remote viewing enabled manga anime netflix adaptation in the the big brain exploding
now it's time to learn remote viewing or rb for short remote viewing is an out-of-body stealth
skill that allows you to go through doors and around obstructions when using rb you won't be
able to attack press the remote viewing button then move around like you normally would press
nice mean remember nick you can go right through doors take a walk through walls now use rb to
help find the computer terminal that unlocks the door so left to activate rv use the left
analog stick to move find computer terminal psi energy drains faster while moving in an rv
i thought i thought i could go through walls oh i hate this oh can i never use this i'm
never going to use this ability in the whole game this is what it feels like you guys want
to know what it feels like to be blackout drunk it's like that this is what it's like
you don't want to be like this now move ahead and exit the door by the terminal to get to
the next test my eyes kind of hurt actually after that next test why would you put a red
barrel there use remote viewing to observe the path of a god find cover and keep your
body hidden while you're in rv pk mine migraine find cover in high press left activate rb
use rb to observe enemy behavior so let's get the cover i don't have to okay i can
activate it like here all right rv observe enemy behavior press x to continue he's putting salt
all over the is he gonna see me i was spotted who oh that guy i tried to get away from i
thought i could go up really close next use remote i didn't want to do this part there you go
he walks around the corner and then surrenders and i got caught no you did he got caught all
right cool shit can i pull out now now sneak attack and eliminate his enemy from behind the
close range without being discovered so now i know what his route is he comes around here
and he looks this way let's see wait for him gotta wait for his route hello turn around got
yeah give this guy a medal nice work what's next this one's easy nick rb into the next room
and watch the enemy's patrol movement then sneak past the enemy without being detected
what how am i supposed to sneak past you're good at that sneaking around stuff now let's
thank you this is a good one but be careful nick if they discover you there you fail the test
take out both guys undetected to get to the final test
all right let's observe what they're doing that's enough of that okay what are you up to
where is he where is he okay damn it that's so bright if it wasn't so bright it was
it's killing me whatever just go i know this guy's right here
and this guy's right here shit okay i get i can do them both i can do them both real quick
i just don't want to do the mind brightness thing right here ready watch your stealth skills
but are you ready for combat no where's the door where's the next door how's the
hell's going on listen up nick use remote viewing to navigate rat in a maze you need to reach the
terminal and press the button to unlock the exit door the timer starts when you walk into the
maze terminate anything that gets in your way just a bunch of fucking mice use rb to
navigate the mage reach the terminal press x to unlock the door come on what that's unbelievable
i can't believe it that was so embarrassing not for me listen all right it don't matter i just
have to get over there i don't care give me this better gun i'm not gonna blind myself
where is it good get up you did an excellent job nick now let's go get some lunch i'm
starving me too what are we eating i wasn't i don't want to do that uh no look there's a
guy there thanks for the tip he's dead wait this guy's coming over here uh oh get his ammo
good call it's like being out of bounds in new vegas that was i i should have just shot them
what okay guy coming down from the ceiling guy right there who's left not that bad pretty
good quick tip you're out of psi power you can increase your cyber by using psi power ups
in your inventory he's doing a y pose that's not you can't shout that out i don't want to
see any more y pose shout outs this guy not noticed this yet what does he have in his hand
thanks to the key card hypospray some lab coats carry hyposprays pick them up to
instantly restore health and psi energy they can't be carried in your inventory okay
okay how do i get that that's how no kick kick kick kick these get new electrical electrical
grid gone now that i need to take myself can i shoot through here i could do psi power through
there let me oh wait wait wait let me look through this never mind i can't there was
another never mind where am i shooting this guy for him to be moving like that this one
open now oh my fucking jesus there's a minigun in here what can i rip it off or something
i don't i i think i have to put that down and then sprint across
wait a minute let's take a look at that area okay this minigun is there a way to get out
of here there's anything even in here can i open that door no lift it up i mean i can i
can hold it but remember mad cats dog shit controller all right look at so far whoa okay
got a med kit it's still all right we're good this looks like a long way do i get a force jump
completion time 23 hours and 37 minutes items broken with tk 37 preferred weapon machine
gun shots fired 300 accuracy 77 is not bad even though it's an auto target movement
property damage 69 120 bucks holy shit he made it inside the clock tower are you kidding me
how come there's no resident pog channel you know like a sleeping face with like a wow i'm
excited does it exist nick you're starting to remember who you really are are you saying
i've been brainwashed it's an awful idea memory to hide your psi abilities from
the movement probes when you were captured the shot i gave you should help reawaken your
powers no this is crazy deny it all you want but how else can you explain well i'm still going
after my men it's too late they're being processed into soldiers for the movement
they're probably being converted as we speak my men would never what press select move j what
did that cut off explore the movement's compound and locate the rest of your squad
oh god please let's go okay nick let's learn about mind drain also referred to as md
mind drain absorb psionic energy from another person's brain next game resident champ
we'll start off with the basics eliminate this guard however you'd like then i'll tell you
how to drain okay kill the guard i'm not gonna lie i wasn't even looking at the screen i'm
looking at one of the game i had here i can't pick him up i couldn't pick him up
close to the body then press and hold the mind drain button so r2 is mind drain the drain will
end automatic draining a dead body only replenishes part of your energy okay to replenish
all of your energy you need to drain a live target we'll try that in the next group so
electrocute somebody's brain till you suck out other energy got a live target now you can
only drain a person who is unaware of your presence sneak up on the enemy from behind
until you get close then perform the mind drain sneak up press and hold r2 to execute
mind drain until he dies you gotta be real close those guys will never get ahead with
that job sorry let's move on that was pretty brutal who are these people that we're doing
this to now for something a little tough i want you to sneak up behind each of these guards
and mind drain them until they pop without being detected by either one go for it so blow up their
brains all right i'll give it a try what a horrible way to go just microwaving that guy's
brain nice job nice yeah nice nice work excellent next you replenish your power or die
oh pretty matter of fact there boss for this last test i'm going to deplete all of your
side energy to stop then use mind drain to replenish all of your energy within the time
limit anything goes nick do whatever it takes to get all of your side energy back
okay refill to maximum do not die all right let me see if i can scalp this out here what
is anybody left side just this one guy right another guy to computer over here
maybe well he's right there is there a distraction button or something
hello uh where did you come from i don't know if i can get it to max now
now there's one more guy out of bullets not good i can't use any of my mind powers
one thing to remember hair now no brain no drain headless bodies have no side energy
so keep it in mind i remember him having hair out of here it's time for cold
oh did he have hair no okay he was bald wouldn't he all right door is locked
i'm supposed to do both this they're gonna make a walkway guaranteed what oh god i gotta
drop these guys in the electricity right i missed it so obviously turn this power off somehow
nope uh up here no button access denied why the hell not there's a ladder here
i'm gonna get fried if i do that don't press the warning button that's not an alarm this is
no okay i just want that's all i wanted to do oh my god monkaS anything else a teleportation
pad no not like a star trek thing is it everybody just get electrified one two three
let's go hey oh gas just fell in the room what do i do about this open the door
open the door oh no no no no no no no no wait no another gas room there was just a guy in here
oh fuck what are you doing he's got a key card break it oh for the love of god
there's a health pack in here wait you're not heavy enough got a key card right bingo
what are you doing any more health no i only have this one little sliver of health i'm gonna
start sneaking i'm gonna be in big trouble not refilling oh that was a crazy room
too many people there sanders you're not dead let's go i'm getting you out of here
i am sanders apparently that's all i got apparently is i am sanders that is truly
wait why was that
he came after me and his head exploded i didn't do anything
i didn't mean to really do that but okay what does this one do
i thought you were kidding me so that was what was gonna happen i thought you were joking it
didn't happen the first time so why did it happen this time dead not dead still alive no
all right we're gonna suck some brains out i think the exact uh wording was what does this
one do i knew what it was supposed to do but i didn't know what this one was supposed to do
i'm gonna take the machine gun i'm almost dead uh why wouldn't i just use the door
who's that for oh shit when was the last time i saved okay we're good next no not yet not yet
plus i think i only have one more for tonight where is it what do you mean what what is it let
me see i've got where did this one even come from i don't remember even buying this can you
cheat and get all the powers can you do that it seems like cheating like you just said i don't
want to cheat no no i'm not next thing yet i just want to see what else i have here
curious of what else is over here got uh urban chaos i've got the jackass game
jackass the video game i don't know what that entails there's also um i have the 50
cent game please don't play jackass i'm not nexting this yet no no no not yet not yet
i'm still going the 50 cent game should be its own stream that's what i was thinking too
but i can't play the 50 cent music yeah that's gonna be awkward hello come here no i want to
i'm trying to do something i can't do it no i'm in the wrong way i have to delete the vaude
if i played the 50 cent game i have to delete the vaude no i just turn all the music off
turn all the voice clips off and just walk around just shattered that guy's spine no go press that
button again press the button press that button that you just pressed god damn it i don't have
enough power how so come here fucking idiot just cut this shit already we'll just restart the
stream so we get a separate vaude i have to go turn the alarm off uh new vaude to get deleted
no stop pressing this button turn it off
every alarm is on right now all of them they're all turned on why am i trying to
jump in the fire i'm not gonna use that let's drain psycho wow i'm good can i drain the
guys that are in there no but what the hell is this implant device acquired why didn't they
come in the door they're just waiting for me oh god ah okay come on i can do this shit
i need to sneak better
all right that's it that's it i've had enough of you you you're the guy you right here turn it
off turn this shit off get what did you deserve okay where did you even come from okay relax
stealth what do you hear any med kits in here no not even not even any med kits unbelievable
okay here we go go do that implant device stealth how many people wait let me just do this right
how many people are in the room one two does that guy turn around i don't think that guy
turns around ever he's turning okay just wait for this guy to turn we're gonna stealth kill
turn done implant device what am i supposed to do about this i hate you
why did it show that on the screen was there a reason it zoomed in on this it got close of that
that thing okay but what was the reason for this it zoomed in on that yes it did it zoomed
in on that it went it zoomed in on that and zoomed in on this i'll die right now i'll go i'll
go get myself shot in the face right now to show you that again sure it did it did don't
make me die right now do it again i don't believe you you have to you have to trust me on this
allows access to the cario storage facility i think i doesn't have a head i can't steal his
soul so where the heck is that down there streamers lying to four thousand people what
lie when did i lie what are we talking about what did i lie about i didn't lie can i break
this ice just ice that would have melted unrealistic stupid unrealistic game
sarah i'm at the main training room the door is locked i should have known this is a high
security area probably the only one with the password is joe leonard leonard he runs the
puppet program meat puppet
the password is in his office find a way to get it but be careful powers are dangerous
can't you do it obtain the passcode for the door to the mainframe room some guy's office
i thought i did it for a second i was about to shit my pants and go get a lottery ticket
another cutscene your production quotas leave a lot to be desired first boss first boss first
boss programming process has taken time to perfect the general the general is quite aware
of our setbacks barrett but the operation is now ready to go forward we're leaving for the
flight z today he expects his quotas to be met i understand do i just walk in present myself
i heard everything and then a bullet just goes right through the top of my skull hey what's your
password 1733 mainframe password you just leave that out on your desk apparently you
were waiting for me somehow grabbed onto the wall what's in here i just fucking
pinney pressed myself i'm aware i need better guns this thing sucks one seven three three
four digits don't work anymore need to six didn't you hear the news
oh this is bad this is very bad actually six digit password can be broken with a brute force
in 12 hours now not good it's got to be at least eight health pack give me that
somebody says i'm actually yawning in real life you are come on this is the mind get conspiracy wake
up they 20 years ago if you had this game in your library of four playstation 2 games
because they were like 80 bucks each you would have been so excited for this one
resident champ i'll give you a resident champ okay did you find anything yeah the
blueprints of this place great send me the data meet me in the warhead storage room off of the
main silo where according to these plans i would just cry to my mom to buy me another
game from the mainframe room right there you'd cry look around i would cry until i got what i
wanted that's bad that's really bad go through the vent system and meet sarah in the warhead
storage room it's a pretty nice brave little toaster computer you have here somebody's
gonna get that reference i don't care if one person does i'm glad you did all right go through
the vent not pressing that it's the ventilation system how the heck am i supposed to get there
oh i need that because of the vent system what the hell is she talking about vent there's no
vents here where's this ventilation system in this room how do i get up there no i have to
do is my brain blind he's blind he's blind he's blind he can't see he can't even see
he's just fine most last time you guys had a piece of a big bowl of candy those last
like rices you guys had turn up r9k or i'm gonna tell my mother on you what's your mother gonna
do she's gonna say no that's a good thing that you're not on the computer all day
she's gonna applaud the fact that you can't use the twitch chat to write i'm jeff from
psychology 101 30 times and where the fuck did they come from i mean mom it's not fair
i was in the streamer's chat and i tried to write 400 pogchamps in five minutes
and i couldn't do it i'm so sorry about that sweetie and i and i also want another video game
because psyopsis is fun absolutely sweetheart yeah and i want a new tv too they do 4k now
don't you know ma yep what is that it's fog champ oh fire extinguisher what do i do with this
oh that was so cool so what i think i didn't i don't think i was oh wait wait wait wait
what about me i'm fine i think i was supposed to uh i don't know i think i made it did i
make it made it yeah okay i was supposed to do that i need a health pack what about you what
about me is there invisible walls here are there bumpers on this bowling alley or can i fall down
oh boy there's a bridge i'm not gonna fuck that up somebody said save that would have been awful
if i didn't mods are garbage i don't think you guys know nightbot is just blame nightbot for
everything nightbot like will time you out if you write like look at me a fucking thousand
times level d level a level d okay i've squished my head that guy better not be pressing an alarm
wait why but i can't my eye of krillog cannot go above a gap like that don't do it
where who's doing this i have a nice ride i didn't even do it i said like a dumb shitty
one-liner and i didn't even get it didn't have to he walked off himself yeah that's
what happens when you play in the real bowling alley dickhead i'm just trying to catch him
it's like a shitting why can i not drain him i don't know why i couldn't drain him
i desperately need health like right now what's this oh no i want that
it's literally to your left literally look at me that sounded painful come on
oh hey literally look at me okay that was almost really bad but i'm fine
oh that was painful wait wait where is he wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait where
he's dead where the fuck do i go uh we have triumph how about how'd you try it what are you
talking you guys just copy pasting didn't you guys know that i don't like that these alarms
access denied i have to go back down i don't like those pastas so i don't do them there's only like
two good ones anyways this is where i came in should i just go down what are the good ones
well i'd have to tell you i can't say it because then everyone's gonna start doing it
let it be a mystery forever i think that almost killed me i don't like the movement on that
close real close what is it what is it yeah i'm not gonna tell you why do you want to know so bad
is it rude germa at the grocery store no the door is locked no access what does this lady want
me to do go through the vent system and meet sarah in the warhead storage room i i'm in the
warhead storage room aren't i landing pad warhead storage i'm like right here
if i go through here i could have known that was probably gonna happen what did it put me
this is really bad i had to like jump off of that too and like break all of my bones of my body
no i don't want to next that uh am i really good i'm so slightly annoyed by that
through the vent into the warhead room like i should have known that was gonna happen
i already made the reference to like oh i have no help i almost died there
gotta get closer so getting lost for six hours i've not lost i haven't been lost
oh i'm going fine this game's fun it is i have to do this whole thing all over again
uh that was horrible i sucked that guy up now is it gonna go the other way
no do it again do it suck him up suck this guy up suck him up suck him up
he's doing it on purpose now no i didn't think i could i thought i could get a little bit
further away than that i don't think he's on purpose on purpose he's doing it on purpose to
get extra subs dude did you i can't did you i can't believe it man i got access to germa's
discord account and if you see the dm he had with his mods talking about hey i'm about
to do this on purpose there's hundreds of thousands of cases where like he had shocked
he had stuff calculated that's off right i thought i turned it off now it's off okay
turn it back on okay wasn't a good place for you to stay i got out of being in the meek rinder can
you believe it i don't believe it you better my god where you guys even fucking come from
it doesn't make any sense is still on fire all right i'm good
oh
video games warhead storage i'm here i've made it where is she why are you not just here why are
you not waiting for me don't fall everybody right now is just sitting there with their hands
in their mouth oh you're gonna fall up you've bit through all your nails they only have like
your pinky nail left what's gonna happen which did i bet you he's gonna turn the corner it's gonna
get blasted where the hell am i wait there's a little electricity room i was already here you
mean to tell me that this was this close okay this is the warhead room where am i supposed to
meet her down maybe i just have to trigger a cutscene all right we're gonna try to trigger a
cutscene here streamer hates his fans why what are you talking about i smoked three
packs a day i've never smoked a cigarette in my life a full one i have tried it though
yucky disgusting don't do it cutscene trigger the cutscene cutscene he tried but now he's
gonna die early that's not the case give cutscene please i know right this is bullshit
i'm gonna smoke a whole pack of cigarettes just for you why would you do that where's it going
no no i don't want to go off this what did i put button did i press go north left
what does north left mean which way is north i don't know which way north is north left
hey watch this hey hey hey hey i did it oh i would be so mad if i heard that and i was
a viewer i'd be like fuck this guy place not quite these warheads don't have any nuclear
material left but they still have plenty of the conventional explosives i've salvaged them for
the materials we need for you to blow this base me i'm trained for this kind of op at mindgate
mindgate the secret psi ops that's a joke i need to be sure that's why i didn't make it
they sign our paychecks don't you remember anything the memory wipe allowed you to be
captured your true memories were supposed to return once you were past the movement's
mind probes i'm sorry nick something's gone wrong but we have to move on according to
the blueprints this base has a major structural fault i've marked three key locations placing
the explosives there will take the whole place down it's like tiktok level acting
plant three bombs to destroy the entire compound plant the first bomb in the
implant ups okay you really loaded me up here medical kit i need a bigger kit than that
a lot of all right they're gonna be in the inventory i can't reach that who's coming in
who's coming in the door none of this stuff was even in here nothing else i just don't want
to miss anything because everyone will be saying oh he's blind compact streamer is too small
to reach the big boy ammo get that guy out of him dead all right i need to suck his head out
oh god damn it was just keep them all over here eventually they'll pile up in the corner
howl up i'm getting messiah of might and magic flashbacks who the fuck has that gun you do
did he still shoot me even though he's on the ground on his back this guy all the way across
let's do both this guy i can't hit this guy i'm gonna do this guy that does shoot myself
fuck where did i even just go oh what was the last save point it's right here we're fine i
just gotta get out there and i'm so aggravated what do i place the bomb in the implant facility
but first i wish it was more than one resident sleeper gameplay it's all right does this game
have music probably not the question is can i goodbye sniper rifle guy up there
still up there yep he came a long way nice dodge almost got me it was close that guy's dead
now the question is where do i oh no who i don't see anybody this was read before
and what do i plant these bombs in the implant room implant ups so i gotta go back
to the cryo storage and from the cryo storage i should be able to get to
is there a fast way to get to the crowd store who pressed that button
oh you've got this this room was empty turn it off turn it off turn it up everything's fine
i'm gonna have full health let's head this way all right cryogenically frozen place
which is i gotta go back through the vents so i have to go down right no up i don't know
which room is it in some 6k viewers all of a sudden yeah that kind of came out of nowhere huh
well hi guys welcome kind of jumped in view maybe a host or a raid did i miss a host or
something maybe possible well wherever you came from good to see you my name's uh my name's
jeremy it was vinny uh well hello thanks vinny i was gonna raid vinny uh last night but he was
turning his scream off we were ending at the same time i was gonna send some love
uh just go through here i was already in this room i have just deja vu again i at least have
to get to the first boss just walked right off the edge they're not that bright but then
again neither am i it was on your back all right i gotta get back i swear you guys are
just spawning in random places that has to be right what are you doing what are you doing there
all right where are those vents all right help me out here chat how did i get how do i get to
the cryogenically frozen laboratory i went to the vent and then i have to go back through
the vents right do i have to go up again is access denied let's go go north left
jump down all right why did i think you guys are gonna actually help me
run the elevator in administrator mode go that way wait wait wait i've been in this room like
five times i have to stop this no this is nonsense there's a vent up there no
everybody's so i guess i'm just gonna go down and then go through that door he's got
six k viewers and he's stuck in the game oh what are they gonna think about what are they
gonna say about me they're gonna say so many fucking things about this guy doesn't know
what's going on i don't i'm not going back and watching him again i only want to watch
this for the fuck he's going i was just trolling you guys just having a little bit of fun with
you this is we gotta go this way how did i end up in this room again it's not possible
this is a different room no we're good all right now back up here
i don't can i even make it up there oh shit i don't think i can make it up there
wait i need one more crate get in there i'm out of power oh shit can i push it 2000 people vanished
twitch bug it was a twitch bug there's nothing to do with what's happening on
screen it was a bug on twitch's end i love what somebody actually wrote wow that's actually
kind of embarrassing
wait what is this little one it was never meant to be all right i got a little one okay perfect
here we go really this is obviously not the right way i don't know which i don't know how to
get back just go back across the bridge pull the crate down why did i have to get stuck here
at this part and 50 000 viewers show up god damn it oh please it was so easy i was 5000 iq
negative iq trying to do this get up there quick no
dropping viewers by the second where did that come from just get me out of here come here
okay one two three oh it's it's plummeting it's plummeting no it was a twitch glitch
it was a twitch bug oh fuck you mad cats and your non-pressure sensitive controller what are
you doing
just please please let me salvage what's still here somehow made it worse
6000 down to 3600 oh no i have to do this again no i don't actually
oh i had to i wasn't supposed to go that way i was supposed to wrap around some other way
he's he's devolving that's so funny to me i can't i can't even play
okay so it's obvious that i can't go this way so i have to like i don't know where the hell i'm
supposed to go through here again yeah i don't mean it doesn't make sense to me quick
advertise your shirts hey you know i have shirts stock is plummeting no it's just fine
dude play half life did i not pick up the med kit did i use it already guys guys what happened
where is it i don't even know what it is i'm just gonna put it in quick before my value as a
streamer drops like another 30% quickly uh psyops is a fucking fun game interesting game it was
a fun experience maybe you'd play the whole thing quick i'm just gonna put jackass in i don't
even know what this game is but i'm just gonna put in views dropped by like another 40% after
jackass that is so funny yeah i know it's because of the the host turned off but it's
still absolutely hilarious how that played out all right let's just uh
i'm probably gonna ride down a hill in a shopping cart or something
game features stunts before me by professionals don't do any of this shit at home
don't do it here we go do i do i get to be do oops do i get to play as still losing viewers
still losing i didn't mean to he's playing he's playing jackass he's doing it funny slowly
going down the hill quick i'll do another game no try this one what about urban chaos you
guys like that one right that's a good one isn't it urban chaos is a funny one it's a cool it's a
classic isn't that people told me that was like a good game hurry up and stream cube world
what the fuck are you talking about cube world is gonna save this why would you play that
quick get out now get out now before it's too late
oh all right this is by rocksteady if you didn't know idos and rocksteady made this game
defcon one cube world is needed
i can't even uh that's one of my favorite 2019 scream moments already is that the last 15 to 20
minutes play jackass you dickhole hey all right i'm just gonna skip it's the same clip over
and over again rocksteady and idos we're gonna turn that off sure it will be will be nick mason
my god my head hurts that was too much stimulation hello um uh what is something wrong here
it doesn't do anything dopy pro logic 2 oh no enemy death cutscene what does that even mean
where are we going vod's going down cell take a player veteran channel seven news
channel seven news loading this is lani york for channel seven news it appears our city is under
attack at five this morning an explosion ripped through grand plaza station hundreds of early
morning commuters and station staff are reportedly dead jesus christ are wounded reports that the
explosion was a terror attack have been confirmed two separate middle eastern extremist fundamentalist
groups are claiming responsibility in an emergency meeting this morning government officials have
decided to increase the city's lockdown with a strict curfew and immediate no-go areas it appears
gang warfare is escalating with groups such as the burners which reportedly has 200 members and
is growing we have not seen t zero the new multi-million dollar riot response unit
no this is not jackass channel seven news that's ready to hit the streets later today
okay somebody came to the stream
upgraded weapons that includes somebody came to the stream
when i was doing the jackass and then they left most residents think the unit is an
expensive pr campaign to boost the mayor i'm gonna mute we're getting reports that hope street
police station is under attack by armed terrorists that station is where t zero is
temporarily based this is t zero's first real test we'll have more on this and other late
breaking details later channel seven first for news in your city i thought this was jackass
and it's like a horrible fucking what the fuck no it's not jackass
this is me this is a first person shooter how do i play
reload it's so crusty who am i shooting at
mason let's move i can't i can't i've lost it i've lost all function in fact that somebody
thinks that i'm uh fresh triangle what does triangle do
why do i have a cleaver did i get them it's the scout this looks badass this is
rock steady made this game this is not just a couple of prusties you know what i mean
you did great mason i knew you'd be a fine addition to t zero go in that room and grab a riot
shield pick up a riot shield all right i got a mask go in that room and grab a riot okay got
one l1 is shield r1 is bash t zero is here to clean up this city that shield is going to
help keep you alive so remember to damn well use it you've also got a standard issue stun gun
which you can use to bring some of these bastards in alive and keep some heat off our backs
where did that guy come from stun gun they're all dressed in like outfits i didn't know i
thought there was a bad guy he's running at us with an axe that guy didn't die last time
the jackass thing has got me all twisted important gang member in the cell
all right i'm gonna relax i'm gonna relax mason let's move don't shoot anybody
r3 zoom in on site
that's just fucking comedy is what it is this is actually a pretty good first person
shooter for being how do i get health back
you did great mason i knew you'd be a fine i know how to get that's in here
oh all right i'm collected again i'm back to normal i think t zero is here to clean up this
city that shield is gonna help keep you alive so remember to damn well use it you've also
got a standard issue stun gun which you can use to bring some of these bastards in alive
and keep some heat off our backs
okay i'm almost dead how do is there a heal i gotta go what have you seen anything like
this before all right fireman back up here there's a fireman up here all right there's a fireman
hey i was told to report to an officer mason that you great come on there's a door over
there i'll go break it down for you you watch my back i saved him anybody else i'm almost
dead we supposed to go in here i don't think we're supposed to go in there do we go in
there's another one of those gang bastards in there go take them out oh thank god all right
johnson let's go need johnson in here t zero then huh cool guess that means you could order
me around that door over there is locked i think i can break it down well the whole building's
on fire so i would get to it what did the fireman to break open the door okay flash that
can be used with a single-handed weapons okay check point all right use your shield to get
past the jet it worked and then okay now does this open who that guy just threw an axe
okay here i need you to open this door fireproof shields
work did more surprising to condemn you for a job on my crew come on moving to cover no no
i thought that was a high five let's try to high five the guy you did a great job
take care of that okay cool nice working with you mason i'm heading back to the front you
go on ahead quiet in the locker room locker room locate the locker rooms somebody's going
to be on fire right here there got him i need health bad hostage i just got oh i know at least
i have health now game that was brutal game doesn't suck game's actually pretty fun it's
great i would have this is a really pretty good fps for you know a long time ago think
about how long ago this was okay can we stop playing this now no this is gonna be the last
one this could be the last game of the night for now i i gotta i gotta get out here cool
i burnt like my funny bone it's gone there was there was too funny sometimes you just you
see you experience something that's just out of control and you kind of have to go to bed
watch out for that guy i got headshot from that far away nice watch out for this guy
is it which one is the hostage looks like backups arrived medic med kit is that med kit can i have
that who are you for t zero to see you i'm jane jane delaney if you need any medical
assistance come and see me or any other paramedic do you need medical assistance yes okay come back
when you need wait wait come here hey i think you're needed an admin give me your give it
i need to be treated all right let's go that guy uh whoa okay that was insane even though
it's a console dogshit controls it's really not that bad it's actually kind of fun to shoot
okay gang leader use your shield as protection we need the leader brought in a lot stun him so
use your shield and get close before stunning him this is infinite do i just get to like modern
warfare cheat right now got him non-legal got it good guy okay so now what's next
everybody out this door come here what do you need
okay it doesn't look good so i gotta take out the guy holding the hostage we're fine
fine
hostage situation he shot him in the head frank is down sidearm sidearm so okay let's try to get
the perfect weapon for the streamer joke
okay hey what's up watch out frank no hey it's me i'm here what i shot him in the
fucking head can you reload why do you keep whacking him in the head after getting shot
in the face come on wait was i supposed to do that oh he's okay good thanks man
forget that in a hurry hey good what does he got in here anything all right nice good work mason
the fov is not even killing me either interrogate that gang leader capture believe he'll let
something slip that'll help us get the jump off these bastards okay i want a forensic
team down here asap and i want you to join me in ops for a debrief come on this would be so
cool in 2006 oh yeah absolutely it's cool now okay this is sally taylor reporting live outside
the hope street police building earlier this morning this building was attacked by what local
eyewitnesses describe as literally hundreds of homicidal maniacs as you know today was also
the first day of active service one of my favorite ps2 games i could see that anti-gang
division are these two events linked who knows for certain one thing is known however the siege
ended when an officer in t0 saved the life of a fellow police officer viciously held hostage
by a mr carl estavez police have up to now refused to release any information what if we
all leave at once to force a germ market crash then buy back in five minutes and get
rich more news as it happens now back to lani in the studio
73 that's not bad you have unlocked emergency downtown let's give it a try
rescue the vip trapped in the city streets to permanently unlock prototype t0 weaponry
all right let's go we have an emergency discovered on the gang members
firm reason to i.p vital to the city's survival is being held hostage
during the mission you will have access to non-approved g0 prototype weaponry
if you succeed it will cut a lot of red tape so you get to keep them permanently
stay sharp i thought he just accidentally slit his own throat jerry you gotta hold the
blade the other way blade out oh we're done three minutes okay got time time limit oh i can't see
i think i'm good where are they downtown somewhere where are they a little shortcut
right there two minutes and 30 seconds to the end oh shit that's a lot of people up there
god damn it i'm out of bullets oh he's still alive how all right minute 53 i can make it
nope oh losing time i rescued you get to the helicopter in the town square oh shit oh no
let's go we gotta go we gotta go follow me come on down here wait wait wait don't go in the
fire 45 seconds remaining come on got it bingo this is like one of those unreal arcade shooters
but you can move how would you get arrests there they're like their own little packages
they're good so it's an fps yeah i'm just that's true so you get more points but non-lethal
you have unlocked the shotgun mark one the riot shield mechanic is really interesting even
now in 2019 no it's cool west side canals see what this one is this is channel 7 news
this is lani york for channel 7 news it was one of the worst attacks to date by gangs
hoax street police station and the emergency workers station what about difficulty on the
wrong one all-out assault last month t zero assisted officers in defending the station
and made many of the 56 arrests that day change the channel the gang's most notorious leaders
estaviz was killed the civil defense committee has seen this lady on fiber no you haven't
this is 25 years ago organized and coordinated when did this come out investigation into the
2006 has been kept highly confidential investigators have not released any of
the gangs 14 years ago objectives but these gangs have shown they are an army on a mission
several large corporations are aiding police by notifying them of any suspicious employees or
employee actions these companies include the accounts giant private was not around in 2006
and the energy conglomerate shiny energy 34 arrests have been made so far based on tips
from these employers many employees are being questioned after homemade weapons and explosives
were found on company premises if you suspect someone you know to be a gang member please
contact your local police department meanwhile the new riot response unit t zero almost a
level one seller on fiber in just one month t zero has made more than 90 gang related
arrests and last month more than 200 people with ties to gangs were sent to prison that's
the highest figure since 2002 nick mason who's a t zero enforcer has been dubbed the angel of
hope street by local police for his work in defending the station even so public opinion is
still mixed about t zero many feel it hasn't earned yes no unsure tag i'm getting word of
a terror attack at the south side canals police have quarantined like right now evacuated the area
but some police and medical teams are trapped it appears they were lured to the docks with false
911 calls t zero and police backup are en route channel seven's news chopper is at the scene
and can confirm that hostages have been taken we'll have more on this story as it unfolds
channel seven first for news in your city there's a lot going on there okay west side canals we got
an extra pistol clip this city sucks there's literally a breaking news alert about a terrorist
attack during the report about the terrorist attack yesterday jesus fucking horrible let's
get it this is like 12 fps locate the medical team got a cleaver can i break out of here
shoot this locate the medical team medical team how was that unauthorized force wait arrest
good idea all right did i do that or did he get the fire thrown at him all right you're
under arrest thanks for saving me we were responding to the call when these animals turned
on us they chased james my partner down there you gotta find her and then find the people
okay
can you heal me give me a health back thank you i've got another tooth okay let's get down here
find the medical team you could have dropped behind me instead of in front of me you could
have gone the other way and you would have had a you would have the jump on me so well
it would have been really really good that was a bad plan i want to start the cleaver
for a minute okay locate and rescue the captured medic
it says r2 to throw cleaver oh wow i have the shield though no that makes sense
swarming dark souls enemy yep this is a lot going on right now am i uh-oh bad this is bad
i'm dead he didn't bring nine cleavers yeah i by standard issue you get your uh mk1 shotgun
your nine millimeter with two clips and nine kitchen cleavers standard issue i think i fell
downstairs oh fuck okay how we doing the gang leader i have to take out bring him alive
these are the real hours these are the chat hours yeah everybody sold off their germa nine eight five
stock you guys held you held on to it dying who's dying whoops is that the gang leader
i didn't know i couldn't tell from back here is tara okay thank god am i glad to see you here
nick they said something about a warehouse kill him and let god sort of mode i'm sure the guy
you called is still in danger nick remember i'm unarmed if anyone attacks me i am really going
to need your help god sort of if you see any trouble tell me to take cover i'll try and hide
for as long as possible what are we supposed to do about this uh-oh this is gary's mod items in
here be careful remember i can heal you if you need it yes watch out for the gary's mod funny
thing what's now what do we do clear the canal of all gang activity oh those are some hee-hee
funny items they were um can you talk in a better place you have to give me that
stupid cutscene all right come here heal me okay you're gonna be fine here thank you no
i only got one more that's fine i'm not even gonna need it there he is safe this guy looks
pretty beat up mason not yet don't go there yet don't go there yet watch out he just ran
right into that move out of the way wow unbelievable you got a fucking dart in your neck man
you're crazy you're crazy almost there i just might i would explode that accidentally so i'm glad i
just made that happen was the extraction point oh the the wounded guy right is he
getting is that using one of my health packs you're good thanks he's gonna be okay maybe a
little delirious for them okay he managed to say something about his boss being taken by
i'm right here tell me let's be somewhere down there locate the owner of the warehouse sure
here you go owner of the warehouse i gotta arrest some people seriously that guy was just
immolating somebody has to i gotta arrest like a few people to make more money he actually
does breathe fire under arrest uh he fell into that i didn't do it so i still get non-lethal
oops uh forget about just kill them oh i know cheering
you're talking to the guy that's trying to save your life
oh i want to you are really being annoying nowhere to go no
oh
i need help okay he needs to tase him a little for being mean okay that i'm okay with that
okay we we gave him a little little shock i'm gonna die there was a checkpoint so we need to
go down to uh he needs to reconnect the power well that's all fine and dandy here
i'm trying to turn on the flashlight you can clearly see that i'm trying to figure out how
the flashlight gets turned back on it's not i thought it was like r3 or l3
it's r2 it's not r2 that's shoot gun it's not r1 either what is it up on the d-pad
okay you're the pitch black guy i need a one-handed weapon
oh okay in the basement let's go follow me sure so did we go the wrong way or is there a
basement to go down turn it on what happened what are you talking about what did you just do
what did you do was it up there uh it was weird do something the power is cut how do i get down to
the basement what about can you do this one try that one how do i get to the basement
i think i just to go back the other where we just were
like down here this is definitely it yeah there's all right repair that please
i would appreciate it sir come on
will do good
all right we'll go back to the warehouse juice it you can back down
can i just jump over this thank god no i have to go back and do that again
no i don't where's this coming from how do i have that many hands
i have to go rescue this guy again no what yeah i do all right that's it i'm done
that's the end of the stream so there are there are three there are three days in a row
playstation 2 madness oh that was so fucking funny thank you all for joining me we're
going to go back to vive uh next week so technically it is next week for a lot of you
guys i still have a couple i have like shadow of roam there's another one that i'm going to play
but that's like a whole stream i've also got the 50 cent game is going to be a long time so
we're gonna i've got a few other good ones thank you for hanging out for the last three
days my funny bone is a little drained especially the last two nights god thank you everybody
uh i'm gonna pick back up not for i'm gonna take a day or two off here i've got some stuff
around the house i need to take care of so you will see me again uh boing boing on wednesday
we're gonna go back to the vibe on wednesday probably gonna do mine show
because that's something i want to spend a lot of time on cube world
oh you guys killed me like 45 minutes ago that was just so funny all right you play cute world
uh i'm gonna be laughing about that in like another hour i'm gonna be downstairs sitting on
the couch i'm just gonna laugh about the fucking stream viewer kind of just plummeting
uh anywho let's uh get to the bits i'll see you guys in a couple days see you guys on
wednesday and we're gonna move to the bits see even more vibe changing this a little
do vr chat that's another one that's gonna happen probably not on wednesday though
because i really want to i want to get like a good avatar for that and i want to uh i
was gonna play it with key well probably she was gonna show me the ropes potentially
custom germa avatar be careful with vr chat i'll be very careful i'll be very very careful
or who knows we'll see if i even play it but let's go back to six hours ago see you soon
thanks for sticking around we're gonna put the the playstation 2 back on the shelf for a little
while come back to it maybe in a couple weeks for shadow roam now i want to play that i
actually want to play the new stuntman the one that was updated for ps3 too much stuff to
do but thank you divas for the 250 thank you for the 250 uh thank you nate for the 250
uh nate nice real name no gimmick two compact men go around me outside around the outside
around the outside oh it's m&m thank you nate more slim shady lyrics uh thank you the other
us for the three bucks hey germa i'm the same guy that spammed you to play dark messiah of
might and magic a couple years ago and now i'm back to tell you that you have to play
thimbleweed park i can't rest until you have germa pluto franker z thimbleweed problem
let me just look this up some other people were talking about this too we park thimbleweed
park it's a point and click adventure game developed by ron gilbert oh it's a point and
click game i really i was into those for a while we played a handful of those in a row
is that a good stream game it's free right now it's it's gonna be free on the epic game store
oh that's interesting if you're streaming it it'll always be a good stream oh well that
is a very nice thing to say thank you but i'm gonna see i should probably get like a couple
of point and click games to have back to back for a little while that chatter was lying but
thank you are the rest of the suggestion appreciate it thank you to nate again for
the two dollars and fifty cents when am i gonna play call of duty world at war for ps2
and it's right it's the fourth worst cod game of all time call of duty world at war final
fronts i love how that's the fourth worst rated cod game i probably won't play it but
thank you for the 250 thank you nate again for three dollars after deleting the ed ed netty
save file uh i'm gonna go office space on your ps2 uh no one's touching this thing this thing
is staying right where it is and ain't gonna move i had to flush ed ed netty to make room
for psyops this is my ps2 and it's staying here and no one's gonna break it but thank
thank you red thank you red lip coder for the 10 dollars thanks to the 10 bucks
hey jerma would you be interested in playing the jack and daxter collection on stream
i don't i don't probably not jack and daxter they are really good games i just don't know if
i have the sort of the patience to stream the whole things they are very good but with all the
same thing people are asking for spyro too i don't know if i have the the patience really
to sit there and play like spyro one two and three remastered i don't know i feel like you
do one you kind of have to do them all don't you they're very good games i just don't know
if it would be streams that i would want to do jerma refuses to play good games in favor of
random old games jack and extra is also old so spyro they just happen to remake them
spyro fucking sucks look at how polarized this is i didn't say that but thank you
for the 10 bucks i think you nate for the two three four five six seven eight holy shit dude
you don't hit it like 15 times in a row thank you for the 250 like two five six seven eight nine
ten eleven twelve nate coming in with a shitload you know could you guess what the what they're
asking me to do it has something to do with a half life they just wrote half life like
15 times uh thank you for the half life every half life that's ever been invented
and then have i ever heard of the daddy in toothless that one racing game i have no idea
what you mean absolutely no idea notice how the sexy lady and the police helicopter in the first
cutscene missed every shot uh and then this reminds me of a game i played it's called
black ops 2 they copied black ops 2 uh sorry to say unfortunately that this game came out
probably 15 years before black ops 2 whatever game had happened to be on screen thank you miss
melanchy for the 250 hope you had a good stream today had a good time watching as usual much
love thank you miss melanchy appreciate it glad you had a good time i had a good time
also mostly lost thanks for the 250 remember when you were going to set aside 12 hours to
stream without warning yeah but i think to my defense the back of the box it makes it seem like
it's one of those interesting experiences where it actually says you have 12 hours the clock is
ticking i'm so glad i did not do that that would have been terrible sticks renegade thanks for
the 250 two years sub holy shit uh you're worth every month i've subbed to you everyone
give germa all the germa hearts you have right fucking now uh you already all do all the time so
thank you for the 250 thanks for having fun really appreciate it forodian weapon thanks
for the five dollars forodian weapon and by the way sticks two years of subs that's
two years in a row i'm shocked that people subscribe for that long i have to start making
new emote badge slot things i never thought that that was going to happen i thought that you know
oh yeah they'll make like the two year one no one's going to get that one i have to make
more there are people that are still continuously subbing to this channel for years years in a
row thank you i'm gonna have to get a three year a six year that's ah i can't believe it
that's even remotely possible but thank you thank you forodian for the five dollars again here
forodian uh no drawing tonight but if you're going to revisit ps2 games again i highly suggest
war of the monsters it's a fighting game styled after old timey monster movies anyway have a
good night and keep kicking ass thank you forodian yeah i would definitely suggest anybody
that has a recommendation throw it get get it in that discord channel i check that recommended
channel all the time so if there's something you like oh fuck i got a couple of games that
he would really like to play now it's not guarantee i'm gonna play them but that is the
appropriate place for you know suggestions because it's cleaner it's easier for me to see
i can just kind of scroll down and see it but i've used that and a lot of streams have
come from that recommended channel a lot of them war of the monsters is on ps4 that's cool
as like a digital download or something but thank you forodian appreciate it
the thing with the play this ps2 has so many games i could sit here for a month straight
and do this i'm not gonna do that because obviously i want to break it up you know a
couple of streams in a row dreamcast two or three streams come back to it maybe another
time later in the year or something ps2 come back to it another time because i don't want
to get burnt out on like old weird interesting games i'd rather do them a few times in a row
put it back in the box for a while come back but i will definitely be making another list
hey it's time for slime thanks for the five dollars just want to say i'm so proud of
you for sticking through clock tower and beating it i had a lot of fun last night
and this is awesome i loved that game it was bad the game was like a little sloppy and
shitty but that was that was a full straight nine hours of fun thank you it's time for slime
for that awesome gift nice trick right now 100 bucks just came in toshiro.tv thanks for the
hundred bucks one hundred dollars and they say hey german just got back from my birthday vegas
trip yeah i'm looking forward to see how this went we ended up in the green after all the
gambling so this is how i'm celebrating oh hell yeah nice you made it out alive you made it out
you made it in the green good you beat the house no that's always a great feeling if you ever
play any casino games being up is a lot better than being done as all of us can probably
say this i can agree with that but thanks for the hundred bucks and they say after that also
ended up going to hash house agogo in the link per your recommendation
uh-huh yeah oh look at that thing yeah yes oh yes there it is i got the burger it was
the absolutely the most delicious burger i've ever had thanks for the info look at that
fucking bad boy right there that is the burger from hash house agogo at the link best burger
i've ever had so glad that you got to enjoy it that place is awesome and happy birthday i'm glad
your trip went amazing that's awesome thank you god i want i want that burger right now
how do i get that right now but moving on we got uh what do we got here uh thank you nate
nate again for uh three four five six or seven donations in a row about two
five ten twelve fifteen dollars from nate here thank you nate and they say what about chocolate
milk every day don't drink chocolate you just you don't don't ever drink milk every day
it's not good for you you know too much of anything is bad for you if all you ate was
apples it wouldn't be good for you i love milk yeah you can love milk that's fine but
you drink it three four five times a day every day you're gonna get milk poisoning and then
they also say legend has it the soldier is still free falling from psi ops it's a sentry gun it's
not a minigun once it sees you you're as good as dead well it's a minigun attached to a sensor
that shoots the minigun bullets at you when you walk by it it's a minigun with a robot
built inside of its head think about that hey platadonius thanks for the 10 bucks thank you
derma defoe william defoe didn't get the oscar oh that's too bad william defoe did not win
the best actor spoiler alert he's been doing it for a long time he's been acting for a long
time very long time he's been very good he's still our top banana he sure can you start a
new stream after this one i missed this one yeah i'll start in two days after this one ends
in two days i'll start a new one for you i'll come back with vr he was yeah he was in
platoon too wasn't he no he means right after this stream hey garfield the monday killer thanks to
the 250 garfield's back in action take a look at this garfin guy over here take a look at
the most expensive garfograph you've ever seen mr germa that is true unfortunately because
of the monumental bit reading price increase garf won't be around for every stream odi and
i will still try to cook up some garfographs when the stars align being the resident cartoon
in chat spider-man into the spider-verse won best animation oscar don't know if you saw it i did i
actually did see it but it's got action in heart and a pig spider-man garfield's favorite
i did see into the spider-verse garfield yeah i thought it was very good it's got some of the
most intense awesome animation characters great it's got good pacing it's a great yeah it's a
good movie what did i do to garfield what happened uh also nate here nate two three four
five five ten bucks from nate uh internet's going out direct tv told me back online
wait what's going on the internet's going out i don't know i maybe you should not
nate what is going on there's one okay one two three bit messages 250 250
telling me that direct tv told me my internet's gonna turn off my internet's
turning off now now i'm back hopefully you got it sorted out but thank you nonetheless
i'm back i'm off i'm back again thank you oh oh oh uh well i guess we can take this opportunity
to clearly state a few things uh one if you have been banned from this channel
uh all the mods are able to be spoken to about it two uh if you have been banned and you come
back with two three or four different accounts over and over again that is actually against
terms of service so i just want to make sure everyone's aware of that that's just scary
you can get banned off of all of twitch for that for your information can you really
um if you think that maybe you shouldn't have been banned maybe bring it up with the mods but
the mods have uh authority right there's the motorbike going by again
but if like i said before there are rules they're not we like to have a laid-back
environment here but if you have been banned or removed then you come back and you tell
everybody you were you come back again you come back again and somebody finds out
i'm sorry but you know we have to keep things going here if you ever fail a jupiter you get
perma banned that's not true but to close it out uh nate thank you for the money thank you
for the 250 a bunch of times hopefully you can get you should sort it out that's you have
a lot of money and i don't want to just say hey bye but i got rules man got to follow them
but thank you thank you also to mostly lost for the 250 i just want to say that my name is also
nate and these donations are all throwing me off thank you mostly lost something or other
thanks to the 250 yo germ stay safe out there and take care of yourself thank you something
or other really appreciate it guys thank you let's bring up the credits and take a look hey
thanks everybody for subbing all the new subs all the old subs you guys are fucking awesome
i missed most of the stream did you finally finish the germacraft adventures
yes i beat minecraft i beat the ender dragon got to see the whole thing it was cool am i
going to go to pax west i am not going to be going to pax west in fact my convention
uh trips will be pretty limited i'm not sure exactly where i'm gonna be going this year
we'll find out i was lying i watched the whole stream you told me a lie well then call me out
on it lying stream there you go see call me out how to delete a liar's twitch what do you
mean delete a liar's twitch you can't we've been going to the furry convention in alaska
uh probably not he read it i'm already there just look down the hall see he's in this rat
costume he's chasing me what would you guys do if seriously if i got in a full rat costume
at a furry convention it was just like running around on all fours how would you ever know
that none of you guys would ever know that was me somebody thinks oh there's like a rat
running around oh you're terminate five right guys and it actually is me i kind of want to do
that and just see if i get recorded like being a rat and then go into like the bathroom and like
change clothes and like leave no one would ever know and i could deny it every day now i assume
everyone in a furry costume is just you you'd get found out in two minutes no i would not
if i was in a full fursuit nobody would be able to know it was me if i didn't take off
the helmet i just i got okay i got i get i hire like a limousine company with like the
tinted windows i pull up in the limo i get out in full costume i wouldn't talk just walk around
wave crawl around like wave an hour or two goes by get back in the limo roll up the windows
once they're at least a mile away from the convention hall then i take off the suit how
would anybody know that was me because of the limo driver fuck all right what if i uh okay what
if the limo driver drops me off at a hotel no the limo driver drops me off at an undisclosed
location like a mile away from my hotel then the limo driver leaves i wait 30 seconds to
make sure he goes past the first intersection with the light at it he goes through it then
i take then i go into the hotel i walk to the hotel right the hotel's like a mile away
go into the hotel go to the front desk in the costume i don't take it off yet i get my room key
i wave i nod go up to my room take off the outfit go to sleep satellite imagery check in
in a fursuit and then okay call up like a lift be in the fursuit get dropped off like five
miles away from my house and then walk the rest of the way to my house and i'll just like
take the whole suit off and put it in like a trash can a limo is not stealthy you'll attract
more attention it's just a giant stretch that people would probably be like who's in that
stretch limo why do you have to be in a limo because i need tinted windows
oh all right i'll see you guys in a couple days uh hey zeus thanks for the 250 hey zeus
hey germ good stream tonight sharing about your viewbot software crashing
but what can you do oh my god i'll see you guys in a couple days for vr take care everybody
see you very soon have a great rest of your night have a great next couple days take care