Hi, do you want to play my video game that I made? It's called Bus Simulator 2012.
It's real fun because you can get like stuck through the world and there's nothing you can do
about it like oh yeah good need a fun good fun it's fun. Important! Note the driver number and
password. Keep them safe. Wait, is somebody gonna like hack this computer now? All right guys like
what do you mean keep them safe? What am I supposed to do? Am I supposed to write this down?
Am I seriously supposed to write this down? I'm writing it down, okay. Done. Security code. Do I
have to do this every time? I have no what? That was just so complicated. I have to enter a service
number. Let's just go like 916. I think that was one. I'm pretty sure that was a service number.
I don't I don't know. No clear. Service number. Eight digit service number? What is with this?
Am I opening up a fucking bank account? Like I just want to drive a bus. This is unbelievable guys.
Like seriously that just took way too long to do that. All right what am I doing? Select no
cancel cancel cancel cancel cancel. Whoops sorry. Can I actually make it out of this door? God. Okay
okay here's the bus man. The fee is five dollars. There's a lot of people over here. All right let
me just let me like try to pick up these people. All right the bus is here ladies and gentlemen.
Please watch your step and how do I open the door? All right door they open. Okay come on in.
Get in get in the get in. Look I'll show you it's easy. Get in the bus. Get on the fucking bus.
You know I'm just too frustrated from this. Can I just fucking run these people over?
Oh cool. Oh good good good physics. Yeah we can. Oh my god this. Nobody pay attention to the bus
that's just sitting here like crashed. So just how ridiculous this game truly is. I have in
Photoshop right now I have an erase tool and I'm just gonna drive by these people and they're
going to be erased. See watch. Oh I let go. I messed up. I made a mistake on that part of my
Photoshop thing. Oh these people too. You know I messed up that as well. Might as well just use
the paint tool and erase everyone. Look at these people are just gone. They're just gone.
Look see this lady in the green. Watch this. Ta-da. She's gone. And so is like the other six people
that was standing there. I'm just driving this thing into a fucking house. Unbelievable. Stuck
I'm stuck inside of a pole. I'm inside of a pole. All right here comes like another bus. What the
hell are you doing? Oh did you just like save me? Oh thanks. Thanks other identical bus with another
identical guy driving the bus. Hey hey other me. Let me ask you a question. Remember the
space-time continuum training we had and. What? What? So what happens if I get in a head-on
collision? Oh that was so awful. That was the glitchiest piece of crap thing I've ever seen.
That was like tactical intervention right there. Bringing back horrible memories. Oh hey look let's
get in a crash. Oh yeah. Hey I like to drive buses. Have you played my video game where you drive
buses around? It's fun. It's called Bus Simulator 2013. Where are his hands? This guy's hands aren't
even on the dash. He's not even. Look at his hands. What?