Hey what's going on everybody? Jerma here with a live spy gameplay commentary currently on Barnblitz.
So welcome. Just gonna jump in play some TF2 and I'll show you how to deal with a bunch of blue
metanaries. Oh all right let's play let's play let's play let's play come on come on just don't even
realize that there's a spy waiting for this heavy to turn the corner and get him oh oh oh oh oh oh
change change god i feel like it's been like a million years since i played spy especially
like live and being recorded so let's see how this goes pattern opportunity it's okay i still got it
and i had another opportunity it's okay i got that one too it's okay just chill out everyone
chill just chill out back here so that sniper is going for you he knows the changed disguise go
to a scout hide in the in the bush uh i should probably move here damn it this is bad this is
real bad actually not really i'm in a not terrible position because there's a i say that as a spy
okay i haven't really had an opportunity to say any words but yes the word i will say is yes at
the moment apparently you again where are you please don't tell me i'm not going to get that
where is he here i feel like he's dead ringering is that another one all i'm doing is reacting
i might be able to get this pyro and in fact we'll hopefully get couple here
there's spy checking which is a good opportunity for some kills
ah no no no no no no no get me out of there the shield spy never dies he always finds
your way does something spawn here i forget well it doesn't really matter because i'm in full
health anyways but something to talk about something to talk about i'll talk about something
in this video what the fuck is that is that what is that could i just see that shadow of the of a
spy i did yeah i could he had the same hat on that was really weird uh anyways halloween's coming up
and i have a halloween video that hopefully is going to get done and hopefully people think is
interesting and i'm not going to give you i'll give you one hint it has to do with iconic video
game characters as there's your hint what the fuck am i doing why did i just do that i just
jumped right down to everybody's face that was stupid i should get off of this why am i still
sniper that's very obvious oh shit hopefully he doesn't know he didn't good very very good
still alive too which is somewhat remarkable don't that yeah yeah yeah yeah you all know
yeah or do you okay well now you obviously know because i picked up the health
on the ammo i got like all this stuff hi hello he's gonna get killed by this
no what is i'm i'm bumping into sentries what am i bumping into what's even happening
i need a plan of action here that plan of action is going to be just run straight at them
that's a pretty good idea right yeah apparently it was a really good idea
because i made it out of that no i didn't no i didn't actually thanks for the help you just
like helped me get back up here i need to like do i haven't got to kill in like two straight
minutes i'm probably i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead son of a bitch son of a bitch come here
i did it do not kill me i'm not your enemy i am not your enemy now let's change to pyro
please don't hear that thank you for not hearing that what do you got that's a crit that's great
don't want to die from a crit still alive dude this is that i remember when i mentioned in the
beginning that i haven't played spy in a while like live don't ask me why i'm doing fairly
decently i haven't died this is just must be some type of fluke no where is he no don't shoot me
i will get you with this headshot when you turn when you come around this corner there to see
that do you see that i got him i got him on my head damn it somebody will finish him off no they
won't i will i will i don't even care i do care what am i talking about this is where we die
because i'm standing and totally still like a fucking idiot with the man melted the guy
man melted me and i died don't let him get it don't let him get it do not let them get this
under any circumstances get out of my way get out of my i don't want you to see me can i still get
it okay hold back hold back here hold back hold back i'm just a pyro just a pyro all right we're
okay that guy's gonna get backstabbed no he's he's gonna freak out and he's gonna turn to kill that
spy thinking that i'm not a spy i will end up getting the kill oh that's really really annoying
he thought he got the kill on the spy but the spy there's two of us and you know he just don't get
spotted that's bad because now i just did like the i'm definitely a guaranteed spy move where i
looked at him and i went no i don't i spun around real fast but it's not gonna get me killed i don't
think not yet at least let's change speaking of spy let's disguise as a spy i'm okay with this and
drop down get you and this guy too oh can we do this for another seven minutes i don't know but
i'm gonna go this way i want to wrap around to potentially don't don't don't holy shit why did
that not work i was like cut off by the door you are a spy who would win you cannot defeat me he's
where you're running where you're running man that was a spy v spy fight i liked i don't know why i
like to do that i like to activate the dead ringer jumping down but is the most obvious thing you
could like ever do just feels fun i'll get around him oh what am i god i'm breaking the rule here
what just what what what what that hit him i refuse to believe that i should have just walked up and
stabbed him but i wanted to get the double ambassador headshot that was a stupid move
i was trying to get on like the highlight reel and i should have just like killed the damn guy
koda walked up and just stabbed him right in his like fucking butt cheeks but no i gotta get like
boom like no just get the sure thing germa there i go again come on
come on gibs what do you say drop down on somebody we held him for a long time but it's coming down
to like the last second here it's going to be the last minute they're going to get it to like right
there and it's going to be either team's game i really don't know who at this point hey hey hey
well he pushed it pretty far for being one person on it for the remaining 60 seconds i really just
kind of want to protect this area i don't want anyone to jump down from here or something i think
we're going to be golden though i really do there is a scout look i'm pretending to push it with you
i for some reason thought that was over i don't know why holy shit you are a heavy they focused
on him 30 seconds now damn it it's all right though i think we got it as long as this guy
sticks around as long as these two guys stick around here i don't think they're going to get
it and we win the game nice nice use of the charge shot 10 seconds i thought that was by
final push let's see if they can do anything with it otherwise we win the game hey overtime
three two one 62 points when the fuck did that happen