Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with scrolls. This is a brand new game. It came out today
Well, actually it's not really released yet
It came into open beta today and it's the new game by Mojang. You guys might know that name
It's the guys that made minecraft
This is their second real release of a game that took a lot of studio time that they're currently in active development with
And I've been having a ton of fun with it today
It's it's 20 bucks and it's not on steam or anything like that as of right now
It's it's it's only on the Mojang store
If you just go to scrolls.com you'll be able to find it. But essentially what this game is
it's a combination of a bunch of different things and
And it's the reason why these few things are combined is the why the game is so much fun
So let's start with very basically the game is a strategy game
It's like a tile strategy game along the lines of magic the gathering where you have cards
You have to tap resources with the ultimate goal of destroying the five
Totems or idols on the side of the map that you do not own
So the gameplay is very difficult to break down in a very short like four or five minute commentary
But it reminds me of if you guys have ever played
heroes of might and magic the same type of
strategy tile movement in that game and the different attack damages that people have the different life pools that people have if
you were a fan of heroes of might and magic you will probably like this game because
Unlike heroes of might and magic there is no
Open world system you just attack people with the monsters that you have in your deck
Kind of like Pokemon you go against people you train against people and there's a ranked system as well
You'll be fighting people and trying to get higher on the rank system
You can trade cards with people and before I completely blow your mind here
I want you to sit down relax for a second. Take a deep breath and listen to the words. I'm about to say
There is an uncrating system in this game. Oh my god, calm down calm down. It's okay. Just calm down
I'm gonna tell you just just just chill out for a second. How you get cards in this game is
Through the uncrating system you make money by completing challenges by
Beating other players and by just playing the game you earn gold as a currency and what that allows you to do
Is it allows you to essentially unbox a crate for a hundred gold to get a random card now?
The random card could be a common card just a crappy kind of regular card that you already have
It could be a rare card or an uncommon card
so just the collection aspect of this game and the
Opening up the scrolls and seeing what you got because remember every card in this game has either a spell property and
Enhancement property like an enchantment property a it's a creature. It's an actual monster
So there's a ton of different things you could possibly
Quote unbox in the game and it makes building your decks that much more fun
And I really don't know what it is about these games. We play like TF2 this game
There's a couple others that have the same mechanic
Unboxing something and not knowing what's inside of it. It could be something terrible. It could be something really good
It could be something incredibly good. That's such a drive
I felt the same thing when I was playing Diablo 2 and you'd kill bail or Mephisto and be like, what's it gonna drop?
What's it gonna drop? Oh, he dropped nothing or oh my god
He dropped a grandfather sword that all that stuff is the reason why you it drives you to play these games
And I feel like Mojang Mojang everyone pronounce it however, it's actually pronounced
I think they're doing a really cool thing here where they're molding these genres together and they're making a skill ceiling
That's very high because I was playing earlier in just a quick match
Remember the member the game came into open beta today, and I just got absolutely smoked by the first guy
I played he like knew exactly what he was doing. He had a good deck
He'd probably unboxed a bunch of cards and it had a cool like synergy going between his cards and I got me going
I wanted I want to do that. I want to be as good as this guy
I want to build a good deck
I want to get good cards and it takes hold of you
It really does and I highly recommend you give this game a try if you're into this kind of thing if you are not
Into this type of game where it's very slow paced
Turn based strategy type card collection game
I would say you probably should avoid this title because there's not a huge amount of action
It's not like bombs are dropping down and like arrows are flying across the screen and stuff it
I mean the animations are very fluid. They're very interesting. They're cute to look at but I would say action wise
You should probably avoid this game if you're not into like the turn based strategy type game
But if you are and you love collecting things and you love opening crates in TF2
Then you probably would have really enjoyed this game and I got to give two thumbs up to this title so far
I haven't really run into any major issues with the game
I mean the only issue I have so far and it might be because I'm just pretty
inexperienced at this point right now
But the game can be very difficult especially even on the easy setting
I've been getting destroyed by some things and I'm getting better very slowly
So I'm not going to say that the difficulty is too high at this point
But it's very difficult you have to invest some time to study the decks
Know what cards do what they actually mean when you put them down and so on and so forth
But I'm gonna end the video there guys just want to give you a heads up that this game is now in open beta
You can go get it the only way you can get into the open beta is you have to buy it
So there is no free open beta you actually have to purchase the game, but I'm gonna wrap it up here guys
Thank you all so much for watching and really do appreciate it and go check out scrows, baby
I'll see you all next time. Take care everybody