Look who's back. Back again. Jerma's back. Tell all your friends and tell them to subscribe to me too.
Hey guys. Dad is home. It's been a while. This coffee is old. That's what you get. I'm gonna make
a tweet. I'll be right back. See ya. Somebody just said you can go offline at any time.
It's true. I don't think I would hold an audience for very long if I just turned my stream off
in 20 minutes. Hey, thanks for watching everybody. Yeah, I'm gone. Bye. I'll just turn it off. We've
been here for like 15-20 minutes or so. I do that every day. Nobody would watch this channel.
We wouldn't even get anything started. Okay, what are we doing? We're doing Dreams tonight.
This is Dreams Early Access. And those of you that know the Dreams is one of my most
anticipated video games of 2019. I want to play it. Please turn off the stream.
No, I know. Look, I know a lot. Here's the thing. I know a bunch of people say,
nah man, you could like paint a fence and I'd watch it. That's like the meme. That's the
joke, right? But imagine if I painted a fence every day. Eventually, after three or four full
houses in the neighborhood done, you'd start asking about something else. Ah, cool. You got
another painted fence in the neighborhood. That's cool. You're gonna play Devil May
Cry at any point? No, we're gonna do this like the next six months. Oh, um, all right, man,
like looking forward to it. Yeah, what if I built a birdhouse every stream? I mean, maybe
I would say at least 50% of people would be gone after the fifth birdhouse stream in a
row. All right, I haven't streamed in a while, so how do I do a tweet? Oh, like this.
Dreams and a couple of Zs. That sounds good to me. Zzz. That looks good. But yeah,
um, my time off was great. It was well spent with family. It was a great, relaxing time. It was
great to see everybody too. So I'm completely satisfied and I am ready to go back into the
virtual internet world of broadcasting. So what do you say we do that now? I'm gonna change
it over and here comes dreams. Let's load it. Why don't you stream with your mom? My mom
doesn't want to be on the screen. So again, this is dreams. This is a mix of I haven't played
it yet, so I can tell you maybe a little bit of a preface to this whole thing. I believe
that this is sort of a combination of 3D movie maker and tilt brush. That's kind of what I
gathered. All right, welcome intrepid creators. Before you get your hands on the creator
early access, we'd like to remind you of the following. Oh, we have a warning sign.
This is early access software. That means it's not the finished product. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
During early access, we may modify the software without I didn't get a chance to read it.
What? I want to read that. I want to go back and read that. Hey, do you want to allow your
pro? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on. Do you want to allow your user profile
and creations to be public on the web at in dreams.me? You can change this anytime in the
I mean, I guess. Yeah, we believe in giving credit where it's due, but we need your
explicit permission to do this. Would you like us to display your online ID alongside your
creations in any promotional videos or live streams? Well, my online ID isn't is not
me. It's like a made up name. So okay, let's just say that I create something here and it's
like the best thing that anyone's ever seen. It's gonna be my like fucked up shitty
PlayStation four name. It's not gonna be me. I'm giving credit to my stage name.
Um, but okay, who cares though, right? Because I know I did it and you all know that I did it.
So if it pops up anywhere that everyone will just know that doesn't matter. No,
I don't want to use my goddamn name. We're gonna get the intro video. Hello. Bonjour. Hola.
Ciao. Hello. This took the fill in too many people. Stop spawning people. You're gonna
crash the fucking server. Hello. I just got a hundred dollars. I haven't even been back
for five minutes. Uh, thank you to German wide about ace attorney. No, I didn't. All right.
Let me, I need to address that. I think this is like a big tutorial coming up here. Hold on.
No movement, no sound, pleat emptiness. Then big band, a speck, an idea. The idea could be
anything. It could be, it could even be everything. No, not loud and coming. We're good.
Fight. Monochrome.
Any matter.
Silence. And most exciting of all.
Death. That's not, that's actually not exciting. Everyone can conduct this power.
Everyone has an imp. Imps are the tall guy. Wait, I can't, I'm not doing this anymore.
Teams with their energy, waiting for you to choose your very own. I have to make my own imp.
Choose your imp. Wait, hold on. Is this just a color? All right. Well, first of all, hold on.
I need to address something really important because I don't want to get flack for this
because people are going to be very upset with me and they're going to talk shit about
me on the internet forums. And I have no way to defend myself. I can only defend myself
when this stream is turned on. Think about that. Anyone says anything about me,
I have to, you have to wait till like my next live stream for me to repeat it and say,
and try to fight for my case. Germa lied about Ace Attorney gave a hundred dollars.
Thank you with a hundred bucks. That's an insane amount of money, but more importantly,
didn't lie about that. Told you I was going to play it off stream and decide if I wanted
to play it or not because I thought it was a different video game than what was initially
told to me by friends and family. But glad you had a great time with the family,
Germa. Even if you did lie, I'm happy to see you back and barely on time. Still on time.
That's why I have the window. Thank you. What do you think? Which TV? No,
what's my favorite color? Green. My favorite color is like in between here and here.
Probably green. I've been waiting for this for a long time. Some of you guys might not know
this. Maybe you do. I've been waiting for this game to come up for a fucking century.
Actually, that's almost hold the options button and your impulse snapped the center
of the screen. Okay. Yes. Great. Your imp responds to the smallest movements of your
wireless control. The sound of your voice. That's because it's attached to the
controller's motion sensor. Oh God, no. You only need to move the controller
a teeny tiny amount to get your imp to respond. Okay. Go on. Move your imp around
a bit. Think of the light bulb on the front of the controller as a flashlight beam
conducting your imp. I hope hopefully I can turn this off. You see that little cluster
of creativity. The creativity clusters. To touch it. I gotta like rest my hands down
on my brachial area. That's it. I don't want to drive a car. I don't know why
people like this. Those two clusters at the top and bottom. I don't like holding my hands
out like I'm driving a car. But when you drive a car, the wheel is big so you can rest
your forearms on it. This is like driving. Look, look, look. Motion controls are
cool. Motion controls are interesting. But I don't like driving a car for more
than four hours. I got it in one second. Watch this. Ready? I'm pretty good at it
though. I'm pretty good at it. Let's see if I can get like all the donuts in one swoop.
Ready? It's a symphony. What if this was the whole early access? See how your imp can affect
everything it touches. Welcome to dreams. Playing through the wilds of your imagination.
Easy. You're wonderful. You're a dream, sir. Play this game on iPad. Sweet. Excellent.
Groovy. You found the wall of doubt. Don't worry. Everyone doubts themselves in the beginning.
I wasn't doubting myself. I was completely confident. Try using the pointy tip of your
imp to grab hold of it. How do you grab? R2. That was pretty, that was pretty ingenuitive.
That doesn't feel bad. Look at that brick. Who does it think it is? Get rid of it.
Did we do it? Your idea's getting away. Chase it down. Your idea. No, not my idea.
Ah, shit. My idea was it was a jack in the box apparently. Is it gonna, is it a loot box?
No, it's not. Do I have to pay for ideas? It should be in here somewhere. The second we
start paying for our imaginations, that's when, that's when like the Illuminati government
control this one. I'm just gonna be clear about that. This is cute though. This is cute. Don't,
don't talk shit about this. Why did I pick green? I'm an idiot. Green is the symbol of
intelligence. It's the color of intelligence. The only source of energy is you. What can you
do? It's not the color of idiots. Go take color theory and you tell me. You can possess.
Yellow is like anger. Red and like passion. Red is rage. Green is intelligence. Blue is
calmness. Look it up. I just like smash the light bulb. Three. Dream.
We have light. A good start. If only we had a way of exploring this place.
Let's see. Oh, I get to be a new character. Now we're really getting somewhere.
It's the X jumps. I don't, I'm confused. Oh, I get it. I get it guys. I get it.
Listen to me. Listen. Quiet. Stop talking. Stop talking. Listen. So this whole thing
was made in dreams. Yeah. Everything you're seeing here was made in this game.
Okay. Yeah. Brad. Brad. You and Mike have detention later. Okay. After school. My office.
And assholes. There must be some way to get out there. This whole thing was made
in dreams. I know it says that in the lower right headquarter. I know it does.
So it was a springboard. You got it. Great work. We're so close. I can't wait to make
my own video game. Oh, look at that seedling. The dream of us loves to help things grow.
Cool. Okay. So circle is to interact. Well, the circle is to get out. So how do I get in
there? All right. I have to use my hands. And then look at how shaky I am. Those of you
think I'm like making this shit up. Like how fucking weird I am and how fucked up I am.
Like look at my hands.
All right. That's a rumble feature. Pretty good song though. How is he moving?
Oh, I need to pretend to jump too. Do I make more music?
Here at last. Dreams. Your vast, vibrant, sublime universe of possibilities. Let's start.
You know, 2020 hindsight, I should have brought a bed in here. And right when this turned on
here, it said dreams. Let's start. I should just got into bed on camera. How long? Ah,
this is your very own home space. Home space. Okay. You'll always start dreaming from here.
Interesting. All right. So where do we go? What's this? A prize bubble.
I have to collect the prize bubble. I could find more. Okay. You've got the difficulty of a
four-year-old Easter egg hunt here. I think I'll get them all. That was a staircase.
Loot bubbles. What is that? Tic-tac-toe? How do I get that one? Of course it's got a name
like the Dreamiverse. Okay. Where is it? Well, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Give me one second.
Maybe I unlock a bigger jump. Like a super jump or something. Or a double jump. I don't
think I get anymore. I think those are the predetermined ones that I'm allowed to get.
All right. Main menu. Dream surfing? Okay. Dream shaping or dream surfing? Should we check
out what people have made first? Let's see what's possible. Let's do some dream surfing. I
didn't get a chance to read that. Was that a disclaimer about it being like nudity or something
or like R rated material? I didn't get to see it. Dream surfing. Here we can explore the wilds
of the Dreamiverse. Slipping and sliding through the strangest and most wonderful ideas and
creations. I can't wait. This is going to be so cool. Lose yourself in the kaleidoscope of
games, animations, music videos. You can do anything. And all sorts of worlds and experiences
made by dreamers just like you. Dream surfing is a never ending, ever changing stream of
dreamers imaginations. Let's try it out. I can't wait. I think some of you are underestimating
how cool this game possibly could be. Final version art and voiceover added to the fun.
Okay. Oh, I thought that. All right. So this is just the version 1.01. All right. Let's go.
Okay. Dreams. Auto-surf. Play through a randomly selected taster of the Dreamiverse.
Um, what are you looking for? Game? Story? Showcase? Let's just do auto-surf. Get the
fastest time possible. It's a race? What the fuck? What? I don't understand what I'm supposed
to do. This is really fast. Oh, no! It's like Super Mario Odyssey. Somebody's going to
make the entire Super Mario Odyssey in this game. Watch out. All right. I got crushed.
This is so cool. I won't make anything this cool. Shortcut. Mario Kart taught me this.
Oh, wait. Can you imagine when talented people actually play this game? What? What
I was wondering? Oh, I went right to the middle. I thought I could go in there. See,
I should be doing this like a speed run. How is that possible? That's not even possible
to do what I just did. That's not even possible. Oh, my God. I'm still trying to do it like a
speed runner. Turn on the edge. I did it. All right. That was cool. This is called Dreamiverse
Dad. I don't think that there are any created actual created things here. Thumbs up or
thumbs down? Rewind or skip? Uh, that was cute. I'll give it a thumbs up and then let's
go. Skip, right? What? Follow for update. OK, so this is a first person shooter. Aim. Shoot.
Swap weapon. Reload. Crouch. Jump. Free aim. Uh, OK. Is he dead? Why does he look alive?
I don't know. But I'm going to keep going. What's the goal?
Is somebody hurting me? What is hurting me? Oh, Jesus. It's this guy. OK, he is
homing bullets. Same game made both of these. I can't wait to make my own. I'm going to spend
six months making my own thing. Remember I made the joke about painting the fences in
the beginning of the stream? Uh, hope you're ready for a fresh coat tomorrow. He's dead?
All right, I was going to run by. This is so weird. This is so weird. I think I died.
All right, I want to see more. Watch out the gap in the door. It's a separate reality. The only
me is you. Are you sure the only you is you? What's that from? That's from something in
particular. This is P.T. Somebody remade P.T.? No, they did not. No, that was it? Hold on,
that was the end? I didn't get to do it? I didn't get to play P.T. It was just the first
door. Please hug me, this is called. This is called curiosity. Curiosity?
Uh, when everything is over, curiosity continues. Reach destination. Stay creative
and explore the unknown. Thank you Media Molecule for this game. This is fucking unbelievable.
I wonder how hard it is to use. It's a never-ending compilation of whatever anyone
wants it to be. Holy shit. I can run? Can I? I don't think I can run. I think I just have to get
there. Oops. So it's like a game engine that anyone can use. Yeah, but you don't have to make
a game. You can do anything. You can paint a picture. You can make an animation. You can make
a little cartoon. You can make a 2D cartoon. I'm pretty sure there's no limit to it
have to be a video game. I think I ran into an invisible wall. Uh, this one doesn't seem to be
done. Uh, I have to go. Wait, did I do the wrong thing? Should I have gone around another way?
Supposed to go up the mountain? Maybe. Jerma lied about Minecraft VR thanks to the five
community subs. Thank you. Appreciate it. Five more from Jerma lied about Minecraft VR. Am I
gonna run into another wall here? Keep lying. It's how most of us stay subscribed.
But what happens when I get here? I gotta see the whole thing through, right?
I can't just go this far without touching the beam. I'll never be able to stay.
All right, you ready for my dramatic cry moment? I'm gonna get there and I'm gonna
power off before I touch it. I ran out of battery or something. That's what I would have
done. Made it. The journey is never completed. Ah, shit. Well, I didn't have to do that whole
thing. Well, that's the end of that one. All right, let's go loop one. Wait, why is it? Why?
Is this a different screen? We got the rope. Was that part of the same game?
This is a PT playlist and it just happens to be looping them in here.
This is fucking crazy. No way is this possible.
Kids game. I don't know if it's a kids game. It's an anything game.
The off-road lands. Chapter one. We're getting a bunch of random things. We should be getting them.
This is overwhelming how cool this is.
Oh, it's me. Well, let me get some of the letter grid because this car is... Oh my god,
I'm gonna make a car game. I can't wait to make a car game. It's coming through.
All right, somebody just flushed a toilet. I can't wait to make something.
But I don't want to jump into it yet. I'm gonna see more creation.
Uh, I went. Factor Majora's Menu. Galactic Adventures. Press X to start.
No, what's happening is it's giving me random...
There can't be that many to pull from right now because it's only gonna be a week.
His six-year-old daughter had the good sense to hide in the bathroom,
but reports suggest he lured her out by telling her it was just a game.
Touch that dial now. We're just getting started because here comes the off-road lands.
Chapter two. So this is chapter two. So each level has to be its own loading area.
I can't wait to see how this connects to the PT universe.
The game is way too loud. I'll fix that. Am I just rolling down the hill? What the fuck?
I don't think that was supposed to happen. How do I just get out of here? Oh, I beat it.
Space pilot dogfight is this one. Oh shit. Cockpit you take off.
What? Wow, this is unbelievable. All right, quick. Somebody make Star Fox 2.
How do I lock on? What does it lock on? What does it circle?
What does enemy lock on? Who the hell has it locked on to? I want this one.
How do I do like a flip roll? Too late. Doesn't she show up?
Don't you have to zoom in and look at stuff? I hear them calling to me from...
When his ten-year-old son came to investigate the commotion, the father shot him too.
The window is cut off. His six-year-old daughter had the good sense to hide in the bathroom.
Reports suggest he lured her out by telling her it was just a game.
The girl was found shot once in the chest from point-blank range.
The mother, who he shot in the stomach, was pregnant at the time.
Police arriving on scene after neighbors called 911 found the father in his car
listening to the radio. Several days before the murders...
Yeah, didn't she hang out in the corner or something?
...repeating a sequence of numbers in a loud voice.
They said it was like he was chanting some strange spell.
I think somebody made the whole game here.
Hey, here we go. Let's go to the new chapter three of The Off-Road Lens.
Mine's gonna be up here. I'm gonna make like the Teflon of the Lost Ark or something.
What? Oh, okay. Giant sword. Look at this shit.
This can't be that difficult to do, though, because that was the whole purpose of this
game. They spent a decade trying to make this game completely accessible and incredibly deep
at the same time. Watch us go there. It is insanely hard to use. No, no way.
So easy. A streamer could do it. That's true.
Hammer Panic. Two-player minigame.
Hammer Panic? What is this? Okay, so you're a little hammer guy.
Didn't this look like a TV show or a cartoon?
Hit objects and your opponent's colored light bulbs to score points.
And you can jump in this, too. Hit the objects into your opponent's backboard.
Okay, so it's like a game of soccer. I can't even win with nobody fighting me.
Ah, I see. They have weight, too. The graphics are beautiful, too. The graphics are really nice.
Make your opponent fall off. Oh, I haven't played this in Minecraft.
What's this called in Minecraft? It's called, like, Quip Blower or something. What's it called?
That's Quiplash. Final results. Winner! End game. So you can make a little Mario party.
Here comes the bathroom loop. God damn it. I didn't want to play a horror game right now.
Wait, what? I'm not doing this one. No.
And final chapter of the off-road lands. Yeah, it's truly off-road. It's off the cliff.
Well, this is not a boat. This is a car. Car is still running. I'm gonna make a city.
I'm gonna make GTA 6. What is... That's pretty scary.
What is that implying? What? No fucking way! They're gonna get sued.
So many people are gonna get sued. Don't sue me, though. I didn't do it.
I'm just showcasing it. You can't get sued for, like, reporting the news, right? Like,
I'm just reporting the news. What do you mean wrong? Get the one up.
That guy hasn't played Mario 1.1 since that was, like, seven. Which one is it?
It's under here, right? Where is it? It's right here? I know it's right here somewhere.
Where is it? No, they didn't put that in here. They didn't program that in.
I can't run fast? No, it's going down. Oh, fuck. Oh, well. I'll get the...
There's gonna be... There's gonna be a one. I don't think it knows what to do.
Oh, Super Mario 1.1 was really fun. This is, like, look behind glitch.
I did. Dark Souls inspired Dark Dungeon. Inspired by Dark Souls. So this is not a game.
This is gonna be just a piece of video. I can't wait for Jeremy to die to Pinwheel later in
this game. This is called Main Menu. Press X to rock. So each screen is its own piece of
video. I want to rock so bad. Colored Notes will approach. This is Guitar Hero.
All right, let's play it. Don't touch that dial now. We're just getting started. Let's play Rock
On! What? Release the game for free and find someone who matches this... What the fuck was
that? That was a messed up loading screen. That was actually kind of scary. Is this a skateboard?
Holy shit. How do I steer it? I don't think I can steer this.
Oh god. It's too hard to stay on. I can't stay on this. Where's the camera? I don't know if I'm
still on it. Am I still on it? Yes, I still am. That was pretty cool. I need to make a
roller coaster or something. There are too many ideas flying around in my head at the same time.
Oh no. Holy shit, I actually got back on. I did it. Is there more? Is the whole level
coming down? I can't go off. I'm going off sideways. This is not how a skateboard works.
Just drifting off. Song list. I need to get out of here and do an actual play.
Newsletter blues. Taking sizable sips from the creek of anguish. Yes. A Life Took Lemons game.
Slayer scrolls. Scene 0.5. Title card. You are a slayer. You take on contracts called scrolls
to slay men or beasts in exchange for gold. You have journeyed to the quaint stonewall town.
You enter the dwarf inn. The innkeeper here is specially adept at finding the best scrolls
offering the most gold. Slayer scrolls. I want to go do that. Am I getting booed?
I forget what it is. It's not even the real game and it's still scary.
This is not even the right one. This is a pretend version and it's still just as bad.
Here we go. Slide. Is L1? Am I fucking Grover? Oh yes. I think I will take two scrolls.
Welcome to the dwarf inn, slayer. Do you have a scroll for me?
Always do, but before we get started, you should know there is an assassin here for you.
An assassin? Why did you let him in? He's got gold for ale, just like anyone else.
But a dead slayer in my inn is not good for business. I'll take care of it. Which one is
he? He's the fat one, hard to miss the lad. Remember slayer, no weapons in my inn. And keep
it quiet. A bar fighter's not good for business. I know I did mention the word Grover. That's the
guy that Grover always pisses off. That's the guy that goes to all of Grover's restaurants
and he fucks up his order every time. No, I wanted to have a slice of pizza. It's that guy.
No, I wanted, I didn't want spaghetti and meatballs. I wanted a pizza. Oh, I'm so sorry.
Where's the fat one? Oh, that guy, that's the fat one I think.
Is the guy fat or is he just a pear? Fill the assassin's drink with something deadly.
Another prompt. Dead? What is it saying? I can't read that.
Fill the, does it say dead? Why would they have a bucket of poison in here? Dip in sludge.
Here you go. Wait, there's two fat guys. No, it's not. Okay, here he is. Here you go.
He's asleep. Okay, I did it, right? Do I win? Quick work, slayer. That was no assassin.
What scroll do you have for me? This scroll comes from the Lord of Frostburg. A dragon
plagues the northern mountains. The Lord's knights have burned, have burned alive by
its fiery breath. Slay the dragon, bring the dragon's tooth. I can't wait to do that
after we get jumpscared again by PT. I think I just leave. Leave Dwarf Inn. Oh, god damn it.
Thank god we got the slayer scrolls seen too. This is actually really, really cool looking.
I think they had to sculpt these people too. So I have to go fight the dragon?
Is there a sprint? Yeah, right here. Giant snowman. I don't have a sword, though. Swing
sword. I don't have one. I can't wait for the 3D undertale to be made in this, you know what
I'm saying? Let's go out the door. It already exists? You gotta be kidding me. I think there
already is one. Well, great. Will they let me out? Where do I get one of those?
Oh, no. I should get this one. This one should be pretty easy. Fuck! How does one even make this
in this game, though? What do I want to make? We're gonna go with like three or four dog shit
things, and then I'm gonna get the real idea that I'm gonna spend the next six months on.
Make the Grover pizza thing. You want to make the scene from Sesame Street
where Grover fucks up the Muppet's food. That's what you want me to do.
You want me to spend at least three to four streams on this. Do it. But without the voices,
it doesn't make- I have to do text. I'm gonna have to get a transcript of that scene from
Sesame Street. This is a long song. How long does this last? 100,000 points. One, two,
three, four, five stars. Oh, that's all right. That's a restaurant worth going to on Yelp.
Yelp is fucking tough. It's really hard. How many times do I have to keep doing this one?
Did I not do the completion thing to do- to not have to do this one?
I think this is where the- whoever's making this, I think this is where they left off.
Slayer Scrolls scene 2.5. After days of journey, you arrive at the northern mountains.
As you climb the mountain, you reach a clearing. A dwarf waits here,
a axe in his hand, and a slain man below him. I don't want to do any more of these songs.
Okay, listen up, and don't you move. Need to take a piss? Hold it. I've got just 60 seconds
to go. I gotta mess all you folks out there in radio land. So sit tight and bend an ear.
Now's the time for action. Our society is rotten to the core. I'm talking to all the fine
upstanding folks got their wet hair cut. Southern jobs pulled out from under us.
Yeah, you. You know what to do. Now's the time. Do it.
Imagine what we actually got for this game.
There we go. Wait, is that- that's my sword? My sword is very clearly a leg.
I just do a sidewards kick.
Here it all started when I was nine. Lost my parents in a mining accident. Growing up on
the streets of Dwarf Hold made me an angry man and a deadly one. Well, thanks for listening
to this dwarf's tale. Go on your way now and let me ponder my ways. What did I get? Why
am I red now? You're dead? Let's go. Fight the dragon. No. I gotta make something fucking
wild. Skip it? No, I can't skip it yet. Oh god. Wait. What? Wait, it didn't even give me a chance.
Oh god damn it. Do I have to actually do something here? Is it with the clock?
Hello. Yeah, R3 doesn't zoom in anymore.
Don't. Don't press X. I think I did it. No, I didn't. What other shit do I have to press?
Don't you have to find like photos? Yeah, I'm-
Shot once in the chest from point blank range. The mother who he shot in the stomach was pregnant
at the time. Police arriving on scene after neighbors called 911 found the father in his car
listening to the radio. Several days before the murders, neighbors say they heard the
father repeating a sequence of numbers in a loud voice. They said it was like he was chanting
some strange spell. You reach a valley on the mountainside, the smell of smoke and ash fills
your lungs. The presence of fire would be comfort for your cold hands if it did not signal that
a dragon is stirring. Piercing screech of a dragon causes you to slip off a cliff and
drop your sword. What the fuck? Boy, what you looking at is the name of this. Oh,
it's the gyro to lean. This is stupid.
The following is an early visual concept created on Dreams.
Metro. Cinematic camera. Real-time footage running on the bubble bath engine.
That's what this is called. Bubble bath engine. I don't think there's anything else here.
I think it's just a little concept. Follow more. Follow for more content. I'm not following
anybody. I cannot move. This is just a static representation of what they're developing at
the moment. Boy, you. What you looking at? What you looking at? All right. Well, that's cool.
Here we go. Dragon boss fight. This is the holy shit. Oh my God. I can't wait.
This is the ending of Slayer Scrolls. You know when you're watching TV on the couch
and there's three or four shows on at the same time that you want to watch?
This is just channel surfing back and forth between those channels.
It's like, oh, I really want to see who gets chopped next, but I also want to see what happens
to Garfield. This goes to commercial and you change to the other show. What down to the
Patriots right now? Let's go find out. What was that? Take apple. Oh, he's going to burn
the forest down. What do I do? How do I kill him? I only have a sword. He's got a thousand health.
I got him. Where are you going? What am I going? What is he doing?
I got it. Take the dragon tooth. I completed the game.
Ah, this is the... Are you kidding me? Look at this sculpting job. This is so cool.
This really is a dream version of this level. Anything else I can do? Can I open any doors? I
think these are all different ways to go and we'll do a new screen. Book of the dragon.
Dude, this is so cool. What needs to be connected here? Alba blue.
That's it, right? No, something's wrong there. I can't read this. What does it say?
You've carried the dragon's tooth and made... Was that part of the book of dragons?
When you arrive the gates don't open for you like usual. Guards come outside to confront you.
They don't look too pleased to see you. The portal demo? Face direction of portal.
Maintain current direction. Uncap velocity. Cap velocity.
Is it supposed to be a portal gun? Oh, okay. R1. So it works. It technically works.
It's these little pancakes. Okay, so let's go like this. I'm not sure there is a win
condition here. It looks like a test. Do a loop. All right, I'll do a loop. No, no,
get in there. Oh wait, I can do it. Right, it's portal. You can just do a loop like this.
Wait, what? Can I now do a loop? Yeah, I can't do it on the ceiling. I'm trying just to fall
through. No, I... Oh, oh. I'm not sure this is gonna work. That's enough of that.
PlayStation Home Studio. Side table? Sit. Didn't they turn PlayStation Home off
completely forever? This is cool. You can just make this. Oh, you can actually move
things around. Interesting. I feel like you can make your own little apartment. Cool.
All right, we'll do a few... finish Slayer Scrolls.
You're no longer allowed inside Stonewall Town. What foolishness is this? I've been
traveling to Stonewall for ages. A fortnight ago, a slayer burned Icevale Village to the
ground. Every man, woman, and child was slain. Slayers are no longer allowed in Stonewall.
Stonewall is a beautiful village. I would never bring harm to it. I'm not a slayer.
You can't judge me on the actions of others. You are right. You have done good by this town
in the past. I will let you in, but make it quick. I think every option worked. Cuphead.
Dreams Edition. What? Are you serious? How do I shoot? Get... press while moving to get going.
Hold L2 to focus in and use R2 to give him hell. Press L3 to pop a squat for
the blueberries. What does that mean? Kill it! Kill them! It takes a lot of hits. Die!
All right, I need to get the coins. You can dash. You can jump and dash, right? Anybody else?
Oh, it's the tutorial level. Die! There's too many hits! I'm shooting them a million
times! All right, where's the end? I see a heart over there. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Oh, there it is. He's too short. I can't hit him. Oh, this is bad.
Oh, shit. Too many. Pop the squat. Yeah, that's right.
Do I have to collect all the coins? Oh, did you actually just hit me?
All right, I don't know if there's an end. This is really, really cool though.
I think I might have to just collect everything. That's awesome. You know,
get that one a thumbs up. They didn't make Cuphead. This is called the encounter.
Disclaim it. The following level is a demo for an upcoming project planned for
production after the release of Dreams. Currently being worked on so you might
experience minor bugs or glitches. Enjoy. Okay. Bigsurf77 presents chapter one, The
Encounter. That looks like a space station base of some sort, right? Guns or anything?
I don't think so. Oh, there you are. Yeah, I think it's time to finally leave this space station.
Oh, that's nice. Oh, fuck, I forgot it's a robot in a video game after the 2012.
There's something weird is going on and we better hurry. Hold on, I'll open the door for
you. The password was Olympic Banana. What a weird password. So it's just me and you, huh?
He was doing hunt and peck. What's wrong with that? There's nothing wrong with that.
Open it manually in the control room. Control room's on the left. Okay, what about over here?
Anything? This is pretty well made. Can I do this? There we are, the control room.
I don't remember that there were that many buttons. So press the button that activates
what? This? Let's see. It can't be that difficult, right? Oh, well, is this a job
for you or a job for me? Who does this? This is your sub sound. It kind of is. All right,
we'll press it. Well, it's my fault. There's going to be a monster right here when he turns
the lights on. It's going to be scary. Watch this. I told you. Lights go on.
No, unfortunately. At least the door is open now, I guess. Anyway, let's hurry.
Okay, let me ask you guys a question. How much money do you think I could make
if I just did that? Like this. If I was cute robot in horror game, do you think I'd make
some money? Do you think I would get if anyone would want that? I mean, it would
clearly just be a guy going like, but would it be cute? It might be. This is open. Can I
look through there? Between four and fifteen dollars. That's not very much. Here we go. That's
the ship. Let us get out of here. Well, it's not called the encounter because nothing.
The playable demo ends here, but I would be updated soon. Oh, it is. So that is the end.
Carrot7, thanks for the five community subs. Thank you, Carrot7. So this is just a demo of
what's coming. I mean, this is a pretty well made space station. It really was. You know,
come on. I gotta rate these. Hello? Why can I not move? That was good. Here we go. Slayer
scenes. There's so many of these. Eat apple swing sword.
Dwarf orders no slayers allowed in the inn. Everyone is afraid of slayers ever since that
lunatic burned an entire village. The dwarf says having you inside his inn is not good for
business. Well, what do I do now? I have a scroll to complete. If you ask me, you should
win back the favor of this town. There's plenty of people here who could use your help.
If the people like you, the dwarf would have no reason to keep you out. I have a feeling that
this is very long. This one is a real passionate person that has 40 or 50 different screens here.
Town favor zero out of five. Can I talk to townspeople? Oh, they have quest markers.
That's the how to train the dragon guy. All right, I've never seen how to train the dragon
before. Any of the movies. But every trailer I ever watched, I was always curious. And
somebody explain to me maybe if it makes sense or not. I don't know. I just, I didn't get it.
Why is the main, why does the main character talk like this? Is there a reason for that? I
don't know. The rest of the cast is like this. And they're talking. Oh, my friend,
you can't be you can't be serious. Well, you know, it's just me, the main character.
Is there a reason why that is? I just I didn't know. I thought it was there some reason for
it is to make him out of place. Oh, yeah, I just didn't know if he was like from a different
land or something. Because he's a pathetic weak dweeb like you. What? I don't talk like I
don't talk like that. Do I talk like this? No, I talk like this. I have a strong voice,
a powerful voice, a voice that commands a voice that demands. You know what I'm saying?
My voice is strong. Hey there, Mr. Slayer Slayers are brave, aren't they? Yes, we are.
I wish I was brave. But since you are, can you help me do something brave? Get on with
it. I don't have all day. I'm ready to help. Sure. What do you need? I want you to tell
this girl that I like her. She's easy to find. She's the prettiest of them all. How is this?
I'll tell her but you have to be more specific. Fine. But all you peasants dress the same
and look the same to me. You have to be more specific. She's playing by the other snowman.
All right. Okay, Toothless. Let's go find ourselves an adventure to go on, Toothless.
Where's the other snowman? That's not her, right? Where's the other snowman? No,
do you have a quest marker? There's too many quest markers. I need to focus.
Other snowman. The lady with the pretzel? The lady with the yogurt dip pretzel? No, I don't
think so. Where's the other snowman? Skip this one. No, it was a gunshot. Someone just shot a rifle.
This is going to take forever. Just hold on. Just wait, wait, wait. There it is. There,
there, there, there, there. You haven't even completed one out of five. They're all going to
be very quick. Oh, I like him too. Thank you for telling me. You have another mission to do?
Was she going over there? This feels really weird being a fucking adult here.
You know what? I don't want to be over here. All right, I'm going to go this way.
Oh, you two like each other? That's cool. I'm just going to sit here and just watch.
Get out of here, dude. Fuck off. What's this guy? Hey there, buddy. You look like someone
who can help me. I left a valuable on the roof of my house. Can you grab it?
You got it up there, you can get it down. How do I get up there?
I appreciate your help, slayer. Is this your house? Yeah, I just- that's right, that's right.
I just killed a dragon and instead of being led into the village, I have to play matchmaker
for like eight-year-olds and get a frisbee off of a roof. Can't make this? Oh, right
here. I can't skip this one, guys. Don't you understand? I can't. Shit. How do I crouch?
What is wrong with your house? God damn it. Why would you build it like this? Why would this guy
have his house like this? Is it gonna take an hour? No, it's not. This is a really well-made
experience, but this guy's house definitely shouldn't be built like this. He has just like
a weird stairway to the top of his house. Take- it's actually a bottle boot. All right,
well here you go. I'm gonna- I'm gonna jump and press fucking R1 and hope I fucking slash
him. Thank you, Slayer. Please don't tell my wife. No, I'm not Mr. Meeseeks. I'm gonna get this
one done. How did that get on the roof? Yeah, he just grabbed it by the handle and like
he threw it as hard as he could up there. Look at me. God damn it. Look at me.
I've been chasing my dog for hours. Could you help me catch him? Usually I kill wild
beasts like your dog. Why would you say that? He's fast. I have gone dizzy running in circles.
He's right behind you. Where'd he go? Just grab him. He's right next to you. Grab him.
He just hit his head on the wall. Come here. I'm just gonna wait in his path.
His AI path goes this way. I'm just gonna wait there. Get him? Thank you. I'll make
sure he behaves. All right, only two more. You put- I tripped him. Yeah, I stuck my leg out.
I did like a Tom and Jerry. I can't go- no, that's where I need to go.
Drink the snow. You can't drink the snow. Where's the last two quests? There was one
up here, right? I know. This is not supposed to be a Slayer Scrolls stream. I'm aware of
that but that's what it's turning into but I just have to know what happened. It's the
dwarf, right? Did I kill this guy?
Yes, I killed him. Yeah, so there was a dragon up there. Maybe that got him.
Yes, I think he regretted his life of crime and left for a new life. You are the first
dwarf I've seen in years. There was a dragon up there. I think the dragon may have got him.
So he really is dead. I always knew his life of crime will end this way. I'll miss him
but I'm glad you told me. I needed closure. Without him, I've decided to use my axe for
honest work instead. Good. Look, I killed him. The dragon killed him. Somebody killed him.
That's all he needs to know, right? Doesn't matter if I killed him or not. He's been
killed. Yes, it does. Yeah, but he was a criminal. He just, okay, he killed somebody.
He literally robbed a guy and murdered him and I got vengeance for that person that he was
robbing and killing. Does it really matter if I got him or the dragon did? I heard you've
been helping the people of this town, Slayer. I need your help too. Oh, by the way, I'm a
Slayer. I'm not a negotiator. I'm a Slayer. It's in my name. It's in my first name.
Monsters have shown up in the crypt below town. The other guards have sealed it shut
but I keep worrying what will happen if they get out. To be honest with you,
being the first woman of the town guard, I feel like I have to prove myself.
We're both going in. Yeah, let's both go in. Follow me. Do I have a weapon? I don't even
have a weapon. Can I have a sword? We have to go down into the crypt. Oh, shit. Oh,
we have a new card now. Spring forest. This is where we went. This almost looks hand painted.
Gun blood. Point your gun in the air when ready. Aim. Fire. What? Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Aim. Okay. So, aim. Enemy AI is activated. Connective. Was that just?
What? Hey, you didn't give me a second. Oh my god.
Okay, come on, please. He's so much faster than I am. Did it. Okay, I won. Slayer scrolls.
Enter the crypt. This crypt is older than the town. It has been here for ages. Now,
all of a sudden, the dead in the crypt have risen. I can't imagine what will happen to
the town if they get out. We will clear the crypt of these monsters. Did she just get crushed?
Did we both die? No. A little place in outer space. Is that it? L1. This is trippy. What the
hell? Oh, I just have to activate all the objects? This really is Mario Galaxy. Yeah,
this one, this one's really, really awesome. This is really cool, but it's gonna, I'm
gonna throw up if I keep playing it. It's gonna go slow. What the fuck? Is that where I just,
whoa. Don't look up. Don't look up. Ever. They always say don't look down, but in these 3D
spherical games, don't look up. Did I make it all the way back around? This is wild. Which
way is up? I don't know. Ready to go home? Yes, I'm tired. Slayer scrolls, scene eight.
Crypt fight. We still live. All right, we ready? Where's, um, where's my companion?
Did she get crushed by the rocks? Holy shit. Oh, they're coming to life off the walls. Those
eyes are terrifying. Where are you? Behind me? Shit. The music for this stuff is just baked in.
Wait, that's her. Where have you been? I was so scared. I hid over here. I am sorry,
Slayer. I am just not strong enough to be a guard. The other guards left this threat under
the town. You are stronger than the rest to have come down here. If it helps, all you guards are
puny cowards, not just you. That's so, well, yeah, that dialogue, that's just so mean and
rude. Okay, we've been nice the whole time. Let's see what the, what the rude path is.
Oh, I killed a monster. I can't wait to tell everyone. Crossing over. I can't wait to tell
all my friends I did it. I slayed a skeleton. Ultra realistic FPS prototype. Okay, ultra
realistic. Hold it. Inspect weapon. So this is ultra realistic. Eliminate the target at apartment
24 lane. You got it. The story continues after launch. Make sure you mark this one. 24 lane.
24 lane. There's an invisible wall here. I can't go any further. It's 24 lane. 24?
I think that means that it's not done. 24 lane is not available yet. I can't, I don't
think I can shoot the gun. No, there's an invisible wall. Oh, just you wait. When this
launches. Upstairs window. Oh, I can't even fire the gun. Window, window, window, what?
What do you mean window? Door, window, door, window. I can't shoot the gun. Whoa, whoa!
That's a person's head, right? With their ears. He's looking out the window right
now. See his ears? Fucking controller aim. My god. Beautiful stone wall town. No, it can't
be. Wait, they've burnt the town? Who burnt the town to the ground? This is really, really raging.
It can't be. Don't walk through the fire. Um, what do we, how do we, what do we do? Um,
do I have to jump it? Can we talk? Fight the fire. I don't, I don't even have a
sword anymore. Is that, is there another exit? Eat an apple. That didn't do anything.
Oh, it gave me extra health. Uh, I think we may have gotten to the end of this one.
Didn't I kill the dragon? No. Right through her head.
I heard there might be a fellow slayer in stone wall. I expected more from you,
but thank you. Slaying a slayer always brings me great pleasure. Nice rhyme.
She sells slayers on the seashore. Slayers and pleasure. I want you to know slayer as
much as joyous I get from this massacre. I do not think do die out to this for fun.
This was all written on a scroll. Holy shit. That's insane looking. What a twist. Yeah.
That's really, really awesome looking. Okay. I, uh, cone ball. I need to,
this is too much fun though. It's too interesting. We got to make something.
Even if it's something stupid. Move, jump, charge. Released when charged to slam.
Jump and slam down for extra power. Move, jump, and then charge. Okay. Goals to win.
Here we go. Oh, fuck. Hold on. Slayer scrolls. By life took lemons. The saga has
only begun. I can't wait for slayer scrolls 2 to come out. I have a cone ball. Let's go.
After credit screen. Three, two, one. Action. Oh, I'm red. I thought I was blue. Didn't I
select blue? I selected blue. This is just rocket league or soccer. Not everything is
rocket league. Rocket league is based off of playing soccer. So have I really become one
of those like millennials that doesn't even say the name of the thing that it is. I reference
to like, it's rocket league. This is not rocket league. It's football. God damn millennials.
Millennials calling shit when it's not supposed to be called. That doesn't,
that doesn't count. Look, if I, if I play basketball and I go under the hoop and I throw
it up, so it goes under the bottom of the net. It's not a basket. Fucking millennials.
What is this called? Polarity. Press X to start. I thought X jumped. Apparently not.
X turns you blue. Press X to repel from blue platforms. Oh, press circle to repel from red
platforms. This is really interesting though. This is neat. I can't wait to make something
neat like this. How do I get that? Nice. All right. This is going to be odd. Finish.
Paddle extreme ultra DX. No way. This even pong. I'm not very, I'm not going to pong.
I told you. This is just rocket league. Oh cool, dude. You're playing pixel rocket league.
No, no. You call it what it's supposed to be called and that's pong.
It's not pong though. You're using the boomer rocket league terminology.
I know. I'm aware of this. It's tennis, but we called it pong when I was 12.
Just kidding. Can I just go once on this guy? You know, a friend of mine actually taught me
how to play pong well and it's hard to do, but actually it's pretty good tactic. You should
never look on the right side of the screen when you play pong. You should only be looking on your
side of the screen. That is what I was told to do and it actually is the way you're supposed
to play because it makes it so you can adjust very, very quickly. Never look at what the
ball's doing on their side of the screen, but you know, that's not, that's a great tip
actually. Somebody said that was a bad tip. No, it's not. This person that told me this by the way
never lost one game of pong. They could go for like four hours. They had like one of those
high scores where it was like a two to three hour long experience. This is all made up.
None of this is true, but take my word for it that you should be looking at your side
of the screen and it's okay. I'm just gonna go this way. Marvel us. Marvelous.
Oh, I get it. This one's called I.
All right. I like we're getting these terms of service. End user license agreements.
Don't fade into the dark. Reach for the light. Created by disarmed. Move.
Gun. Added to inventory. Inventory. Um, okay. Neural chip and weapon pistol.
R1 is flashlight. Wizz gun. Your health is represented by the health stability.
Maintain this by using health objects you find. If it goes below red, you will die.
Use your ammo wisely. Okay. New path unlocked. Environment. Green grass groove.
Oh no. But it's just a ball. Green grass groove. Sonic. It's just a sonic meatball.
Pretty good job with the sounds though. And I like the terrain. Good job with the terrain too.
All right. It's a time to start to start to make something. I want to see what I just want
to check out the tools and it's time. We got to get pretty good taste. We'll do one more
after this. Can I do any other moves like sonic moves? You know like the sonic dash and
shit on his chest. I need 15 coins to open this. What the hell is that? Wait, did I just
unlock that? I think I just actually that's mine now. All right. Let's take a look what we can do.
Last one. This is called 2. So we need to see this. Find the code for the keypad. Hold L1
to sprint. I don't think I want to do that. That kind of hurts my head. This is so cool.
This is even possible though. Do I have any bullets? Pain killers. Oh, I'm stable now.
Can motion blur be turned off? Well, this is on PS4. I don't know if it can. Let's see. My
preferences. Display. Visual feedback. Menu position prompts. Accessibility. Controls. No,
it's PS4. As we all know, you cannot really change any graphical options on the PlayStation 4.
Or any console for that matter. It's just locked in. It is locked in. Where do I go here? What is
this? Power? Power to what? Well, it looks like we're going to follow this. Yeah, this is PS4
only. Can I pull this chain? Can I just interact with the door? I can't interact with
the chain. Oh, the keypad. I don't have the key code. The game already exists on PC. It's
called Unity. Yeah, but like, you'll see when we actually get to the creating aspect of it.
It's not, I mean, it is a game engine, but it's not at the same time. It's also like an
art set. It's like painting and sculpting and I can't go over here. It's like a little big
planet 4. It's like they took a little big planet and said, you know what, let's make
this 10 times more elaborate. Turn on. Well, new path unlocked. All right. Well, what the
hell is that? Connected. Is it like a monster now? All right. It's time. Oh, all right. Here we go.
Perfect timing. Auto surf complete. You experienced 30 creations. Let us know what
you thought to help us with future surfing. Oh, okay. We can go through and rate them.
I remember this. This is, we already had this one. What was this one? This one was pretty
cool. What does it say? This has been thumbed up 14,000 times. PT. I'm going to
give PT thumbs up, but not all the PTs. Please hug me. That was cool. Uh, curiosity. Curiosity
was really, really technically well done, but the game there was a little just, I don't know.
I think I already rated this one. I forget what this one even was. Oh, this one. I like that
one. Yeah. Thumbs up that one. Super Mario got a thumbs that one up. Dark dungeon, dark soul.
Yeah. Let me through the thumbs that one up. This is the guitar hero one. Yeah, that was
good. Ramp 3D. I don't know. Yeah, no, it was good. Slayer scrolls. Absolutely thumbs up.
Oi, what are you looking at? Thumbs up. Uh, I'm not going to rate it because it wouldn't,
it wasn't bad, but it wasn't, it was just kind of a little demo of the environment.
Is the Zelda forest book of the dragon working portal gun demo. I'm going to give
you a thumbs up just because PlayStation home. I don't, I didn't really, I'm not going to
down rate it, but thumbs this up. What did it? Oh, okay. I already have it rated.
The encounter is well done. Art gallery. I don't need to rate it. Gun Blood is the,
the duel. Here's Mario Odyssey. I'm not going to rate it, make me almost puke,
but it was still cool. Uh, ultra realistic FPS prototype. I'm not going to rate it.
It wasn't anything really there. It was interesting environment though.
Cone ball. Yeah. Polarity was cute, but I don't know if I wanted to give it. I'm
going to give rocket league. Uh, I'm going to give 1980s rocket league a thumbs up.
This is the Sonic one. And then this is the currently bugged version of visceral.
All right. I think we're good. Very, very cool. All right. I leveled up.
Innovation, audio, curation, design, play art. What did I do? You are level three.
You're still finding your way in the dream. In verse. So we can't assign you a person
yet. We should have a better idea of who you are by level five.
Okay. Uh, it's my personality test. So we got, we did auto surf, haunted mansion with kitchen.
All right. Let's just go back and actually do dream shaping. See what we can do.
I'm very, very ready. This is dream shaping. Here. You have the power to manifest anything
you can imagine. Music, a story, a piece of art, a whole game, even something there is
no word for yet. I'm excited. Create things from scratch using the dream tools. Here
comes a 10 hour tutorial to remix something another dreamer has made.
Maybe not that long. I'll take you to the dreams workshop where my friend, the dreams
architect will introduce you to the secrets of creation.
How is that not porn on this yet? How, what are you talking about?
Go on in. He won't bite. Promise.
It's been up for like four days. Relax. Or what? Like a week? Not even? No, no,
no. Don't relax. Like relax as in it's not going to be here. Okay. Start dreaming
one tutorial to unlock this feature. Wait, what? Okay. We have to do the dreams workshop.
Master classes and techniques. I'm ready. I'm so excited for this.
So you want to learn the ropes of dream shaping, but you don't know where the
tools are on the shelf or how to use that intriguing gadget. Or you want to know what
that strange contraption over there does. Architect, assist us. I think it'd be easy.
Hello architect. Hello Queenie. Why am I a squirrel? Just a temporary physical form for you.
I like it. It's cute. Well, thank you. It's better than the last one.
Now show this dream shaper how to unleash their creative power. Done. Follow me,
dreamer. Oh, it's so exciting that you're here. I have been really looking forward to
this. There is so much to show you. Gameplay, animation, art. There's no limit to what's
possible. Give me the tools. This is the dreams workshop. We got a lot of
so guys, we all I think can be comfortable knowing that this is going to look probably
and do this for a while. Start dreaming, gain the power to make your own dreams come true
by first getting to know the basics. Two months of streams. Oh Jesus. Are you new
to dream shaping? The start dreaming tutorials are your entry point to creating. Here you'll
get to know the basics of edit mode, navigating scenes and the assembly tools.
There are eight steps. Part one, step one of probably 50 to 100 parts. You're just
doing a labo. Going blind? You guys can't do that. And I physically can't do that
because I have to complete this first. No, I'm going to do this. I've been waiting
a long time for this game. I've been waiting a decade for this game to come out. I've
been waiting longer for dreams than I probably have for the winds of winter. It's a long
time. So I'm going to start. Find quantities first. What's going on?
I've got some spectacular tricks to show you and some that are just all right. Make
sure you follow the steps carefully if you want to get the most out of this. I need
to start drinking. No, it's not just about getting to the end. It's the journey that
counts. I'm going to start drinking. You'll be in edit mode, creating and editing your
own scenes. First, I'm going to show you how to move around a scene. This is the scene.
I don't get it. I'm done. I'll see you tomorrow. You can see that we're in edit
mode because the assembly mode icon is in the top left of the screen. If you ever
need to remind yourself of the controls, select that icon with the X button. So we're
in assembly mode. And select it again to hide the controls. You can also see
the assembly menu at the top of the screen. That's where you'll find all the
tools and modes you need to construct your scenes. The assembly menu is opened
and closed by pressing the square button. You won't need it just yet, so go
ahead and close it with square. Okay. First, I'm going to show you how to
move around in edit mode, as it's a bit different from play mode. To give
you something to do, I've hidden a puppet somewhere in the scene, which we'll need
in later tutorials. I've left some clues to help you find it. It's probably
behind this. Before we search for the first clue, let's start by looking
around. Left stick. In front of you, you can see a floating island with some
shapes on it. I can. If you move the right stick to the left and right,
you can look around the scene. Is there an orange cone around here?
Um, um, you found it. No, I didn't. There's a blue cube around here
somewhere too. What? See if you can find it. Oh, they're talking about in the
outer space. Now try looking up with the right stick to find the pink
pyramid. That's the one. Okay, let's turn back towards the shapes
floating on the island. My first clue is hidden somewhere on this island.
My first clue. Yeah, I looked at it already. This is your clue.
I already knew that. There's the clue. It's right here. Circle it.
We're almost done.
Okay. That's what I'm gonna do.
Maximize it to watch in instructions view. Maximize the video? In instructions view,
you can see more information about the steps.
Once the current step is finished, press the arrow button to move on to
the next one. Three fifty two. Done. Second to do.
Did you find that clue? It was on the back of one of those shapes.
Looks a bit like a rocket. So this really, yeah, this really does
treat you like you're four.
Alright, anything related to rockets.
Okay, island in the distance. Those shapes look a lot like the ones in the
clue. They do.
Remember, push up on the left stick to move forward
and use the right stick to change direction. And don't forget,
you can recalibrate your imp by holding the options button.
Yes, and make sure you do a loop. Two loops wrap around and pull
to keep your shoes on. Alright, what do I do now?
Make sure you're looking right at the cylinder and the cone.
When you're ready, move on to the next step. Oh fuck, that was all I had to do?
Well these steps are really easy though, so we're going to blow through this.
Think back to the first clue. The cone was on top of the cylinder, right?
How can you move them? Well in edit mode, you interact with
everything using your imp. The very tip of your imp's pointing mark.
He's going to show us how to make a porn game.
I don't believe that will. That shows you what tool the imp is using.
Right now, it's the arrow's icon, which means the imp is using the
move tool. That's the default tool in edit mode,
because editing a scene means moving things around a lot.
Let's see the imp in action. First, grab the cone,
hover over it with your imp, and hold R2.
Now your imp has the cone. Use the controller's motion sensor function to
move it around. Try to put it on top of the
cylinder, just like in the clue. Use the left stick to move the cone
backwards and forwards. Objects in scenes can intersect and
overlap, so it doesn't have to be perfect.
Get it roughly into place, and I'll show you how to refine it later.
Once for done, you're ready for the next step.
Now that looks pretty good, at least from this angle.
The 18 scenes in three-dimensional space
means that you should always look at your creations from different angles.
That's such a shitty job. No, it's not. The easiest way to do that
is with the grab cam. See, I didn't even know about that.
Instead of moving the objects you grab, grab cam moves your point of view
around them. Try it out on the cone. Grab cam. Hover over it, then press
and hold R1. Pushing the left and right
sticks moves your point of view around the cone.
Easy. Okay. Now that you can get a proper look at it,
check that the cone is on straight, unlike mine.
Let go of R1 to stop using the grab cam,
and use R2 to make any adjustments you need.
Here's a little secret called nudge. If you don't press R2 all the way down,
but just hold it lightly, you can move the cone
slowly, giving you finer control. Perfect. Once you're happy the cone
is straight, you can move on to the next step. That's perfect. I'm done.
Hey, did you find the clue? Another clue.
It's a molecule. I know because I put it there. Just play along with it.
Okay, there's the clue. What do you want me to do with it? Why don't you look
around with the right stick and see if you can find another
molecule? There's one over there by that island.
You're hot on the trail. I didn't even look and he told me.
It'll take forever to get there using the left stick.
Luckily, you can use the grab cam to get there faster.
Give it a try now. Hover your imp over that orange cube in the distance.
Hold R1 to grab it with the grab cam.
Then gently push up on the left stick to zoom right over.
I get it. Just keep holding R1 until you've made it all the way to
the island. Come on, come on, come on, come on. See, told you it was quicker,
but there's an even faster way to zip around scenes.
It's just like the grab cam, but you'll also need to hold L1.
You see, L1 is a very special button. Tell me more.
You know the way that on a computer keyboard, holding down shift
changes what some keys do? Well, it's a function key.
Holding down L1 changes what the other buttons do.
Maybe it's best if I show you. You see that rocket you built earlier?
Hover your imp over it. Now hold L1 and then press R1, the grab cam
button. You don't have to hold it or use the
stick this time. So you can just fly around.
Just skip the shit out of them. Try it out again on the return journey.
Hover your imp over the orange cube and hold L1.
Then press R1 to zoom right on over. No, fuck. I want to go forward 10
seconds. Now, that looks like the initial space is with the grab cam.
Just hold it lightly. You can move the cone slowly,
giving you finer control. Wait, what? Oh, this is the wrong one.
Hey, look at that. Find L1.
Whoa! Hover your imp over it. Now that you know how to move around quickly,
I gotta, okay, find the clue on the island. All right. Yeah.
Remember to use the grab cam to look around the whole island.
Once you've found the clue, you can move on.
Underneath? You want to, is that, I found a trash can.
Did you find the last clue? It was on the back of the orange cube.
What on earth could it mean? Trash can. If I had eyes, I would wink at you
right now. Hmm. I can't see any other green
trash cans in edit mode using the triangle button.
Got it. Just hover your imp over the cube,
then press triangle, and it's gone. These tools are powerful. Delete the
orange sphere next. If you change your mind or delete the
wrong thing, you can press undo, which is the left
directional button. How many undoes can you get?
Just press the right directional button.
You can undo and redo pretty much anything,
not just deletions. Oh look, there was a clue
hidden in the cube. It means to go up. An arrow.
Nice. Hmm. Perhaps there's another one like it nearby.
Look around with the right stick and see if you can spot it.
Found it. Once you've found it, you can move on to the next step.
Excellent. We're almost done. That was my final clue telling you where to go.
The island right above us. I know you're an expert in moving around with the
left and right stick. You're an expert in moving with the
left stick. Remember that holding L1 changes what
the grab cam does. It can also change what the left
stick does. Sure. Normally it moves you backwards
and forwards in the direction you're facing,
but if you hold L1 at the same time, the left stick will make you move
up and down instead. That's good. Cool. Get up to the last island.
I'm on the last island. Position yourself so you're looking at the orange arrow
which is pointing up. Oh. Now hold L1.
When you're ready, move on to the next step.
I will. Right. Here's the puppet I reserved for you.
Almost done. Let's call her Connie because she looks like a cone.
We need to help Connie walk through the door to complete this tutorial.
R2. To do that, we're gonna have to switch over to play mode.
Finally we get some new info. Finally some new intel.
You're in edit mode. This is where you create and edit your scenes.
In play mode, you can experience the scene just like a player would if they found it in the
dreamiverse. You can't make any changes in
play mode, but you can take control of characters
and try out what you've made. Switch over to play mode now.
Just press the options button on your controller.
Play mode. Hover over the controller icon with your imp.
Then press X to select it. I just did that.
To control a puppet in a scene, you first need to possess it with R2.
Now I get to play the game with whatever characters are here.
She's full of beans, isn't she? I gotta play something. I picked her just
for you. Walk her around a bit, then take her
through the door to finish this tutorial. There's no stairs there.
Oh, looks like the door's too high. Died in tutorial. Died in tutorial.
She might be able to reach it if you make her jump
by pressing X. Wait, I just did that. Oops, I remember now. I'm like 20
seconds ahead of them. Better head back into edit mode.
To switch back to edit mode, just press options again.
Then select the pencil icon. Tools. Modes.
Animate. Gadgets. Did you see those stairs on the island below us?
Those might come in handy now. Straight down to them with L1
and the left stick. If you've deleted the stairs,
you can use undo by pressing the left directional button.
Just keep pressing it until the stairs come back.
Okay, press and hold R2 to grab them. Now, without letting go, hold L1 and use
the left stick to strafe back up to Connie.
I'm already ahead of you. Place the stairs in front of the door
and let go of R2. There, that should do it.
That's, it's a little shitty, but it doesn't matter. Back to play mode now.
Remember, press options, then select the controller icon
with X. Tutorial one done. You'll be switching back and forth between
saving tutorial progress. Thank god. Don't have to do it again.
Start dreaming part one of four. Well done. You completed this tutorial. You'll be
able to return and replay any of the steps.
Only a few more of these. Use reward. Continue tutorials. Imp quest complete.
Use, what is this? Use reward? What do I get for this?
Home space editor? Is that what this is?
Ah, the home space editor. A great place to start your creative journey.
We're still working on this right now. In time,
you'll be able to put things you've made. So this is not done. So it feels
like your own. All right, so not done.
Look at all the wonderful things you found.
There's lots more where these came from. Prizes. And look at the things
the folks at Media Molecule left for you in MM style. MM
characters. Collection of characters created by the MM team.
Contraptions. Sculptures. Okay, what's this thing?
Fancy. Where's nice for it to go? Definitely so I can get, I want to
unlock this. I want to get this thing and put it over
here. Like down here, right? So I can jump.
Oh shit, I just placed two. All right, that's good.
Oh whoops. It's okay, I can fix it. All right, I can get that thing now. Let
me get this thing. Okay, give me over here. These have
collision, right? I've got another toy. I might as well get
this too while I'm still here. Whoops. Wait, can I just pick you up?
No. I'm gonna do the stairs. I might as well just do the stairs.
I can't jump. Can I not jump up the stairs? That was weird.
All right, back to tutorial. Dream shaping.
Level four. What do you get for leveling up? He's still finding a way. We
can't assign you persona. Level five. Now to explore the wider
world of dream shaping. All right, I can browse and create. I
feel like I need to know the other things.
Let's just see what happens. Go in raw. In a moment,
you'll be creating and editing your own scenes.
Recreate PT. Scenes are like levels in a game
or scenes in a movie. They're made up of
elements. Elements are like props, sets, music, effects, and characters.
Hey, this is gonna be bizarre, can't we? Anything that you can build inside a
scene and save the dream of us. Scenes are connected together to form
dreams. And these dreams can be found when
you go dream surfing. Recreate the tutorial. That would be
pretty hard. Scenes are like scenes. All right,
collection. Store, game scene, single player, co-op, puzzle, interactive
experiences. Features, shorts, visual novels, sit back
and enjoy. Galleries, playlists, expos,
characters, sculpture, contraption, music,
sound effect, instrument, vehicle, animation, effect, dreams. Oh my god.
I'm gonna pick instrument, I think. Soft piano, create.
How do I- dreamers. Make a dating sim. Well, hold on, if I first-
Sub sound? No. Strings. Very string playing techniques too from
legato to coal. I'm viewing the music? Where is it? Is it up there?
Whoa, um, what? So you can do C, A, F, volume? Spice?
Bend? This is why we need the tutorials. Holy shit. Okay, that's it. How does
that sound? How do I play it? Rewind and pause and
record. The perform tool. You're in sound mode.
I need perform tool. Play mode? Because I can't select that.
Perform tool? You know, if only there was some way to
learn all this. Yeah, I know. I'm getting out of here. I can't even
leave. Effect field? All this stuff. You can spend a thousand hours in this
game and still be figuring out how to do it.
Vehicle? Sound effects? Hold on. Underground catacombs? Air horn?
Really? So you can just- so you can upload sounds then?
Sports ball? Okay. You can make your own music.
Contraptions? Sculpture? Character? Game scene? All right. I'm going- I'm doing
the tutorials. I'm just gonna do them. You know
what I mean? You have to. You cannot go into a game like this
blind. It's not- it's just not possible. So here we go. Two out of four. Making
things bigger and smaller. See you in 20 hours. It has to be
done. I can't just not do this.
Because Connie's friend Cuthbert fell asleep in the Dreamiverse
and got stranded. Yes, he's a cube with legs.
Connie didn't choose her friends. I did.
So we need to fix these platforms if she's gonna reach the flag
and get to Cuthbert. Before we start, you can switch to play mode to see how
a player would experience this scene. Yeah, it's already all screwed up.
You'll always need to test things out in play mode. I can't- I can't jump to
this. Bad design.
Then select play mode with X. Its icon looks like a controller.
I know. Once you're in play mode. Oh dear. Looks like it's too far for
Connie. Move that first platform closer. Yep.
To do that, head back into edit mode.
Pull this over here. Open the options menu and select the button with the
pencil icon. Move this back. That looks good. Once
you're in edit mode, move on to the next step. I can go
like this. Rotate. Sit you back here. Is that good?
Looks all right. Sort of. Yeah, that's fine.
And then this one has to be grown. Look, I'm gonna see if I can figure
it out on my own, right? And then, so for instance,
resize. Makes sense. That. Okay. It's a little- it's a little
tilted, but that's fine. All right. Now let's play this. I'm
gonna play the video. We're gonna do it fast.
Ready? We have to do something about these platforms.
Move your view side onto Connie and the first pink platform
strafe up and down. The imp has this equipped by default.
Move tool. Move it where you- I moved it. Over so it lines up with the pink. Yep. R2.
Use the left stick to move the platform back. Yeah. By pressing the
directional button. Okay. That's because their auto guide gadget.
Wait, wait, wait. Auto guide gadget. What is that?
You may have noticed that objects move more freely here in edit mode than in
the home space. That's because their auto guide
gadgets are disabled by default in the guides menu.
Okay, well fine. I'll explain more about this in another tutorial. But for
now, you don't need to worry about it.
It just means you have more freedom to dream shape.
when the platform is in the right spot you're ready for the next step okay and that next step is to
play it now that the first platform's in position let's all right hold on hold on guys i'm gonna
level with you here because i have to do these it's probably gonna take at least three it's
probably gonna take at least two or three hours to do these tutorials right so here's the plan
okay here's what's gonna happen i am going to i'm going to do the tutorial off stream
because this is probably going to be a solid like two plus maybe three hours to do this all
so here's the here's the deal i'm gonna go p i'm gonna play this tomorrow we're gonna make
something tomorrow when i turn the stream off tonight i'm gonna do all these i'm gonna spend
like four whatever three four five plus hours doing it and then we're gonna make something
and i'm gonna have all the knowledge i'm going to be prepared completely so tomorrow we will
play the creation portion of dreams for the remainder of today because it's been about
three hours we can either go back and do some more dreams change over to sam and max finish
that third episode but you will see a i'm going to be making stuff tomorrow okay i'll
give you a poll because i can definitely foresee that this is going to take a large chunk of
time and i know people don't really want to watch tutorials maybe you do but i'd rather just come
and have a bunch of stuff to have for you tomorrow you know what i mean we'll see and may
i could be wrong here so let's find out i'm gonna put a poll in the chat i'll give you
some good options okay here we go i am extraordinarily excited for this game but i want to
know what i'm doing there you go i am gonna just go p i'm gonna take my first break
we'll see what you guys want to do i will be right back stay tuned all right hey how are we
doing uh we are a bit too close to call right here 400 to within one percent
goddamn tutorial voters three all right this is this i might have to just remove the tutorials
one then but it's just the top two because if that this is within that this is within six
this is within six votes maybe you'd be inclined to vote for sam and max or surfing if you didn't
want me to do these tutorials i don't know all right let's eliminate the tutorials then
you guys you guys are always happy you guys always do this it's too close
it's four like look at this 427 428 430 to 430 do you see how close this is every time
look at this the division here all right new poll we're getting rid of tutorials
and this is it i'm gonna call this i'm gonna call this dream surfing or salmon max you know
what they are the title is required oh shit there you go this one's not gonna be as long
this one's gonna be like less than two minutes germa lied about minecraft vr thanks for the
five community subs thank you because right now if i go back i'm looking at the first poll
the first poll has 42 to 41 percent not the tie i'm gonna i'm gonna finish sam and max episode
three so don't worry i'm gonna do the whole season another five community subs for germa
lied about ace attorney i don't these are a bunch of things that i haven't lied about
why don't i just make sam and max in dreams all right i'm closing this in 10 seconds
it looks like by a very small amount we are going to stay in dreams we're going to dream
surf for a little while longer going back to the first poll dream surfing did win this poll here
it is currently sitting at 460 to 449 in favor of do more surfing so it looks like on both
poles dream surfing has won even with the removal of the tutorials all right so we're
gonna go dream surfing but i'm supposed to be almost by the same amount too it won both
poles by yeah all right let's back it up and those of you that really want to see sam and
max do not worry sam and max is going to it'll probably be the day after tomorrow i will probably
do sam and max on wednesday it's just what you wanted to see right this second so let's do some
more surfing people that wanted the tutorial also wanted dreams that's true but that dream
surfing did technically win that first poll so it didn't really matter all right i'm gonna
get out of here let's go back and let's dream surf this time i'm gonna actually look at some
of these because they're instead of doing the auto one battle tops haunted mansion so this is
an entire story with the thing in the top right mean how many scenes it has and what does that
mean the second one dogs run solid gears are metal with a car drift jump souls do you
accept the challenge this is nothing for non-dark this is nothing for non-dark souls player
you will die very often but don't give up all obstacles i'm doing it
jump soul how do you even get that in the game i'm doing all these tutorials
my controls making all kinds of fucked up noises right now find your soul with it
resurrection
is it a side scroller respawn so this is just they just jump okay they disappear
did this say this was easy for dark souls players or hard for dark souls players
this is hard for non-dark souls players right but how does this have to do with dark souls
oh fuck did i get it on the internet for saving us the internet's dying no
fox is pissed i wanted shaman max turn him off damn it no why are we why is this happening
god talk ceo in chat he's just sitting there so he wanted he wanted me to finish
standing max is so pretty bad turn it on if you go back to shit
all right this is like this is insane that the hitbox is so large on that thing
well i can't wait sorry i'm not paying attention paying attention to my dog
shit internet and stand on this one at least i got that god there we go all right
i'm souls veteran oh fuck why do i have to go all the way back here
i've got that 500 times no i haven't oh wait not that means all right i did it jump soul
oh come on all right i'm about to next this one it's really it's good but okay never mind
good that wasn't fair i couldn't see what it was from there we didn't go fast enough
how do i get out of here
here
exit creation very fast games how do i get out of here reset progress scoreboard or continue
send to follow creator report oh i said that circle a night in paris was this one
i'm gonna play a night in paris oh shit that's me hey what you guys don't even know i'm
off stream here i'm gonna make a fucking ton of things i'm gonna spend all night making
things in dreams you guys don't even know what you're gonna see tomorrow is that it
am i just like a lost chipmunk i don't get it it's very pretty have the viewers make fan
games no that'd be yeah that'd be awesome is there a way we can set up like a playlist
for that does anybody have this who has this not me no no well i mean maybe maybe
if somebody has it we can oh there's a prize here oh well minecraft 2d platform based on
the good old pixel art games and the 8 and 16 bit eras i'm always updating but you still
find glitches let's try it oh this looks cool level one okay what is this you collect coins
and find bubbles kill blue enemies by jumping on them i'm gonna make a game like this i'm
gonna take oh i can't wait double jump sounds dangerous no way for us to screen them i don't
think you can put anything up here that would be considered a bad demons penance teaser
poster for an upcoming game how do you touch you do this so elaborate painting tools
i just took a sip out of my coffee and i swallowed like four hairs
so this is awesome i miss slayer's roles read me hello everyone some of you are asking if my
book of the dragon puzzle scene will be a part of a bigger project to be honest i was just
learning sculpting tools and testing how detailed i can go with the art of dreams
still in the phase of exploring different techniques and getting used to making things
here results are quite satisfying and your wonderful response exceeded my expectations
beta will be over soon but our adventure and dreams is just getting started
writing uh what you're looking at it right now is the very first artwork for the game
adventure uh youtube.com slash me i'm never gonna be this good beach pool you can make pool
i'll have a toilet simulator i can't wait to play this one best idea early access
bite size up leave turn off the light previous next music no wait what do you mean no are you
serious hi welcome to 2025 just kidding it's expensive just expensive toilet oh wait a minute
hold on a second what did i just look at what what did i just see that i don't know what that
was oh god damn it this is 2500 thumbs up the rake what could go wrong what's this one
points lost that's it iq points lost what was this the whole goal here there's nothing else
here besides stepping on rake temple treasure hunt button smashing all right let's try button
smasher button smasher score press x to start speed buttons per second oh i get it
two bucks now you can't mash it's only takes one input at a time it's not called button
masher it's called button smasher get it right that's pretty good okay i can't do this
anymore i'm done that's cool though flappy bird it even has it through the speaker this
is okay this is a lot different than the original flappy bird it's a lot it's floating this is a
boomer game this is not a boomer game this is the shit that kids were playing at their desk
in middle school like less than five to ten years ago a boomer game kids were getting like
in trouble in school because of this game guys boomers that implies boomers know how to
use their phones or any device that's electronically powered no this is like this is like an early
millennial i mean like late millennial zoomer right yes yes it is the boomer equivalent of
this guy's is like a crossword puzzle yeah i get to get at least five oh my fucking god
i can't believe i just did that whatever one more now pit cross is not a boomer game either
all right i got it i got it that's gonna get to 10 okay now i'm done that's six is fine
hurdle wars a nod at the classic button mashing olympic style game stop killing my
internet god i go i take like a vacation and i come back and then it's worse than ever
hurdle wars and this is a button masher i can do it pretty well why did i move somewhere
with such data internet internet is awful across the entire country of the united states the
united states has just shitty it doesn't matter where you go everybody complains about it
internet's terrible everywhere there's like four internet companies in america all of them suck
they're all terrible there's cox spectrum comcast and like century link there's like four
companies in the whole entire country pick which one they're all awful it doesn't matter where
you go this and there's like google fiber in like four places or verizon verizon files in
like three places but that's the thing about internet right here so let's let's do the
internet rant here i sometimes you see people that say what are you talking about my internet's
fine i mean you but you're probably not noticing it right so what you get to see when you watch
like a stream is a live feed of how bad their internet is it's just a consistent online feed
of that person's internet there's no way to tell how bad or slow your internet could be
running sometimes because i mean my internet's still on i could go to a website right now
just fine but the way that it goes through the cables and to the plant and out to the nodes
and i think i think i'm off i think i think it turned off so it's it's not how do i jump
what's okay l1 is jump i'm going as fast as i can possibly go i can only go 10 i can't go
higher than 10 does this end i did it eight penalties that's not bad like speed does not
mean stability and that's the problem american internet it's actually you know fairly fast
but it's not stable really anywhere you go some people luck out some people get really
really really stable internet most people have at some point issues with stability
oh pinball i want to try this oh this is awesome i want to make my own can i shake it i don't think
i can tilt it real boomer game yeah you just bring like 40 dollars and quarters to the arcade
it's so cool you can even do this though i wonder what kind of just weird workarounds
you have to do just to get this to work sure it's fun all right that was cool let's
change the channel the adventures of let's head seinfeld for a second i was like what
my four-year-old told me a story so he made it into a game what is a
penis pot what let's find out what that is what
why is it called the penis pot why is it exploding what did you put in there you put
like utensils in there open i gotta get i'm going in the water i didn't listen to the
story yes i did it was too full is that what the thing's called
does somebody come over eat this jesus why is there one of them that's big that's an apple
what was that recorded on is what i want to know that was not a cell phone that was like
an old honk-a-phone from the the 20s that's what it sounded like all right i'm gonna have
to give thumbs up to uh paint this book llama quest we already did this one didn't we
super mario 64 one two kingdoms in dreams collection hold on a minute are we about to
read the i get copyrights from the game make sure you follow me officially licensed
nintendo 64 really okay i mean they got the copyrights for the game
super mario n64 slash ds can i grab his face uh start bottom bottom to start what is that
saying use r1 to use them what is this one to press pull zero pull bottom back out of page
x pull bottom of x pull bottom two of other page this triangle
loading six seven eight nine ten what is it loading is this going to get to a hundred
what oh this is definitely not allowed this is definitely not okay but you do you got the
rights to it right options sound for level music mario sound star sound three time allow
you to switch to one out of three pages what's going on with my hands okay let's get yeah get
out of here options page two is brighter darker do they have to save one one he has a bomb
battlefield oh that's the punches that's i get it okay i thought it authentic i would have
flying level is this gonna go
this is a one-to-one remake come on no i can't get it this is this is a way everyone that's
asking how did i get him here is that um synced up there's no actual level but this is
fully redone super mario 64 and 64 mario let me go check something else i think i gotta get out of
here it's a nightmare thing tutorial help with you controls and going in cattle and going out
cattle and in the room for level in the game okay attack flip okay r1 go in and out the
cattle l1 open door to the room to level wait formal door zero star to room for level
um can i do anything big star to room for level power fight and level to the power fight
it's hard to understand what they what they say
you can this is they actually made it didn't they no way where am i why the huge what's with
the camera i'm like 45 feet tall i gotta get to the top of the mountain get up there come on go
this is so cool this is this is great it's unfortunate this is probably gonna get removed
in like three days oh no there it is there's the t-pose we found it we found it i don't
want to thumbs this up because i don't want to be associated with like the illegal activity
right i mean it's pretty cool crab man destroyer of worlds we have to play crab man
crab man demo demo i don't know it could be anything let's stick to run punch all four
umbrellas to begin walk over crabs to collect them press x button to jump square button to
punch okay collect as many crabs as you can under the time limit the more things you
destroy the faster crab man will go are we ready go i can't destroy the wall what about
can i punch the building cars i can't punch those i thought i was going to go faster the
more things i broke i fell off i didn't get crabs how many are on the level get the crab
get the i just got i just got fucking destroyed i just got detached oh my spinal discs came up
come on hurry come here just you wait just wait till tomorrow i have my games and i have my videos
and my artwork i'm gonna do a whole showcase i'm gonna i'm not i'm not fucking around i'm
gonna spend all night i'm not gonna sleep tomorrow's stream is gonna be fucked because
i'm gonna go on no sleep and just show you all my fucked up shit that i made
mr crab sorry mr crab mr crab mr crabs hey you mr crabs i'm it's already starting to happen
i'm already getting weird it's all right even if i stay up too late and i puke on stream i'll
just mute you won't even know i did it can i play basketball did you enjoy that crab man
destroyer of worlds yes i did comet grab too complicated so uh cat nav global game jam to
the help lost cats find their way home look at this description new year's resolutions
star wars oh what if i rebate star wars follow me duck quacks don't echo this is literally
used in the context of me liking soy milk all right we have to do this one all right we'll
we'll play the soy boy after this duck rpm hold the flashing yellow buttons until the duck
rotates past the megaphone hold the how do i increase the duck's rpm this is this is stupid
but it's like fun oh i see it's slowly going up people with that trickle in i think i'm
playing wario where it's still it's 27.5 the highest it can go no when do i just stop doing
never um it's gonna get probably too fast for me to even react whoa whoa it's like broke
his face no no no no no what are you doing all right i just kind of wanted to get out of
that he ruined it it's fine project dead this is a short concept demo showing some
ambient style i want to use in a future game that's creepy that was all sculpted
otto's misadventure in the wonderverse i have to play this one all right orb thingy zero out of
ten it's a retro mode hey there i know the name's doug doug the cave fixie i'm here to help
escort you to mount olympus where you will help zeus save the world oh i'm so pumped let's do
this
first r2 mid jump to perform a stomp attack it's hard it's hard to control why is it blinking
what the fuck just happened what just happened to me stomp attack i know i know i know i know i
know i get it i get it i get it i know i know i know i know i know oh shit um
oh is there an attack button he doesn't know you don't know either hold r1 while approaching
branching pathways oh this is cool should i go to the cave he doesn't know why none of us do
telepooch what did he say he's doing the chad walk i mean not really not really no he's
not you are s this looks nice though this is really well made let's go this way i can't jump
why not oh i have to i have to actually stomp them thought i could just mario them
well i need 10 of these no that's not the chad that's just your arms don't have bones
oh what's up little man let's move on to soy no well anyway first person or whatever that i've
met here anyway i'm supposed to wizard yeah you were looking for a wizard
oh
i didn't make this
don't die i died this scarecrow still talking
this is zeus is zeus fighting me too
oh
what the hell is going on
what am i supposed to do
oh no zeus is dead i don't think i can do anything about that is it an orb right here
and i don't jump up here of course i can thanks for playing more to come turn back
to continue hunting orb thingies continue to save score missed eight yeah well i'm a
how am i supposed to jump over there this is where the oop comes in i can't get over
soy i play soy after this way
pipe oh come on
oh
actually walking the path
is that easy you did it now try again your time was bad oh all right i hope i don't fucking
regret this yummy do you enjoy your your change track this is what it is this is it
it's actually just a thing of soy milk that's it there's nothing here
ep well there you go that was bad it was all right it's the soy soy boy it was a soy ost what
else we got bug report there's no nothing okay beat man gold valley pig detective season zero
the first adventure of pig detective your friendly neighborhood private investigator who
is also a pig and you kind of have to see what this is beware these are these are the dark
ages of pig detective also known as beta a time when the creator didn't know shit and a
clever game mechanic so the last thing he learned proceed at your own risk and don't
fret there will be a better gameplay in the future okay so pig detective no shit no no go
back back back yes yeah this is sam and max it's a mouse it really is sam and max hello pig
detective can you do is about the case wednesday that doesn't happen this is doesn't have is
bioshock infinite this is what happens in bioshock infinite right don't you like a
flashback so if somebody has a flashback to like being detected i don't know whatever this is
i mean the famous pig detective oh i have to answer um no you use a flashback you'd get
no say in this i'm gloria i own the cheese palace how can i help you my bouncer butch
he got arrested but he is innocent and the best bouncer in town case accepted he's got
spawned in um all right cheese i brought you cheese what a pathetic try to pick up a mouse
and you talk to butch i've not talked to butch he is at the police station remember
before you go leave the cheese on the table can i go in the bath i am just kind of naked
aren't i all right any items to pick up cheese all right there you go why did that i just turned
on a button the cheese was the button to open the elevator that's a duck cheese palace look
at how cool this looks rat hole and pub rat hole and pub you will never find a more wretched hive
of scum and villainy go in it really is sam and mac sorry the cat is a bit buggy since
the beta this doesn't affect the gameplay officer cat who is in there it's the cat police
i need to talk to butch visiting hour is over buddy and i'm not in a good mood so please go
away go away step away from the cell i want to talk to bush probably have to get a donut or
something i need a donut or something something the cat likes cats don't like cheese right
get the mouse cats like cheese sometimes can i pick up a wrap i don't think i can pick anybody
donuts there we go these people are terrifying donuts good evening jack give me a box of them
donuts thank you you too jack have a good day i wonder if i can record my own voice and put
it in here and stuff too i'm gonna make my own adventure game do you think i can download
and install all the knowledge to be able to do this whole thing in the next 24 hours
i ain't going to bed i'm gonna lose my fucking mind go talk to the prisoner if you want
okay gloria sends me you have to get me out of here i ain't done nothing
tell me what happened okay one night i come to work and the police is already there
say i have stolen from mr cromwell but i never i don't even know mr cromwell
you have to believe me pig detective time to visit mr cromwell
i'm just realizing right now what the fuck i'm playing this is absolutely bizarre
where's mr cromwell mr okay mr cromwell is he a taxi cab driver i don't know why my
voice did that too is he a taxi cab driver all right mr cromwell cromwell manner there's a
lot of content here for this being we haven't even seen any of the loading screens
it's a long walk though that's really far away anybody there uh this is interesting
i have to go track him down puzzle puzzle what am i doing i don't know i'm doing that
is he a bird owl pigeon snowman i'm pig detective and i'm investigating the case
yes on mr cromwell what case well you say here you were robbed
a probable crime my most prized possession gone it was stolen from my safe in this very house
yeah well let me see you about that well i oh i'm here to find out who did it
culprit has already been found my client is not so sure about that who was your client
that's for me to know and for you to find out partner would you expect me to help with
your investigation was that really wise was that really wise it was that mouse who owns the
cheese palace right worried for her mad i look around the house if you really can't help
yourself i'll be in the music room matches i have no idea how to build an inventory
inventory i have no idea how to build an inventory if you want to know what you have
write it down that's amazing at least they're honest that's so funny piece of paper with a paw
print write that down matchbook piece of paper with a paw print piece of paper with a paw print
say that five times fast piece of paper with a paw print piece of paper with a paw print
piece of paper with a paw print piece of paper with a paw print piece of paper with
a paw print piece of paper with a paw print got it bird nice birdie hello birdie
that clue you can't do anything with the piano with the dog painting it's an octopus chewing on
a mop with wings okay where's the last clue clock i would think the clock would be a clue
let's say that five times fast i think that the clock would be a clue no i'm not doing
that again where i couldn't i can't go in this door no yeah i can all right here we go
fruit on the table no fireplace it is a letter too burnt for reading but clearly signed by
mr sharky this looks like the qrs house yeah it does
mr cromwell i have something for you i've finished snooping around
can i ask you a few questions i suppose if you must
rat hole mr sharky paw print bird in a cage bird in a cage that is a pretty bird you have
in their cage there why does everybody go on about the bird in the cage
is because i am a bird myself what about mr sharky how do you know mr sharky mr sharky the
infamous lone shark i've never heard of him bullshit i've got a piece of paper with your
name on it nothing is sure fishy here there was this piece of paper with the paw print
in your place the robber left it so everybody would know it was him
common criminals do that kind of thing how else would the police know who to lock up
what have you ever been to the pub called the rat hole of course i do not frequent that
wretched hive of scum and villainy you work for a mouse and ask me if i associate
with rats you seem to be obsessed with rodents in a way i'm fed up with you right now
don't get my regards to your boss does it mean i'm gonna get shot at or something
is it what just happened the missile just dropped a meteor just hit earth we don't seem
to care it's called lightning that was not lightning that was a meteor all right rat hole
so can i go in the rat hole i think we're at the end of the locations here i don't know
what it is about that i feel like i've seen these mice somewhere before what movie or tv
show or game these that mouse right there it's freaking me out bar key hello pig detective
hi andrew the muppets yeah i think it's yeah it's a rizzo the rat maybe uh
as a bartender i cannot answer that question what do you as attorney i don't know you
don't expect you to rat on the customers do you give me a beer
rushing waterfall you just shotgun to that hey pig detective hold on let me change this
i want to change this from uh the shire to renaissance rats that is renaissance rats
well how about country rats that's better the rat gang good evening gentlemen
you need a rat do you know where the toilet is the toilets comes here all the time and doesn't
know where the ratting loo is he's trying to rat with us he's acting suspicious what are
you hiding mate have you seen mr cromwell around here mr cromwell that fancy dude in
here you must be joking bike how do you know who he is then how do we know he's in the
ratting paper 80 got his thing stolen rat an expensive thing should have been us stealing it
right boys uh sure you're right ha ha ha i really need that toilet now order am i gonna go in the
urinal i'm not gonna take something out of the urinal who the fuck is this am i about
to get murdered by a final fantasy character i'm dead oh that's it next morning i'm getting
too old for this i drank one beer is pig detective getting too old for this for what and who is the
mysterious early morning caller find out next time and the next is done with a pig detective
the uncaped crusader what a cliffhanger you'll have to find out eventually thank
you for playing so far hey thanks for making it that was good episode zero come on
coming soon you make a wrestling ring okay that's all i needed to see in space anything
else coming soon all right pig detective season zero well it wouldn't be episode episode zero
season zero only 871 thumbs up that's that's not cool dragon showcase the quantum donut
you find the donut you eat it makes you fat it also doesn't okay let's see what that is i'm
gonna say it before anybody else does it's john from garfield i said it first
i thought i was supposed to eat a donut this just looks like a platformer okay world's softest
mud minus sink huh i guess if you just keep going this is down to the donut i assume there
it is it's a donut eat the donut free will is an illusion duh of course oh this guy wants
to eat the donut too did you just eat my quantum donut do you know what this means
well i'm a scientist and i created the quantum donut you just ate eating the quantum donut has
put you in a state of superposition in which you are both fat and skinny simultaneously that doesn't
sound like real science follow me to my secret lab and you'll understand what i mean oh we're
invested now press square to toggle between fat and skinny oh shit
the quantum donut is that it to be continued project will be finished when the full game
releases wow skinny jump hold x while fat to bounce while fat to do a speed boost okay
see if you can reach the platforms probably not no i want to get out of here okay dreams
came out a week ago most are still demos oh yeah i'm surprised people have been able to
make this stuff already not even a week and a half later gork help gork to catch his son jack
that is bizarre i'm getting inspiration though that's a that is a big ass
that was a pretty huge ass reveal
oh yeah can i run faster than this like does it might just come on and get up there
but but come on let's if you no no no no no no you can't tell me i'm not allowed to
have a reaction to that this dude's wearing pants like four sizes too small i gotta get
up here what is that is it a animal is nothing alive
that's terrifying it looks like one of the aliens sitting at the bar
in star wars the cantina i have lost sight of the sun i have no idea where he is
oh my god how the fuck am i ever gonna reach him
oh what are you saying this really is a dream this thing would just give the shit out of me in my
dream why does he keep going
i'm never gonna catch this thing where is he going should i just wait till he comes across
is he gonna go to the volcano i have no idea how to run faster i guess i just have to make
it to the volcano this project spark no this is actually good it's kind of mean but
okay it's funny because this isn't that good
i'm just kidding project spark was fine it just was too complicated
i'm dead all right whenever i'm gonna catch a gork i'm so close to the volcano
no don't
i need a better view oh fuck off i'm dead
okay slow no i can't i can't go slow slide off i'm so sick of here to do that
okay now over here
and then up here i'm gonna beat this one oh come on
god damn it man
i'm invested i have to at least try no don't do that
what my finger in there i'm not gonna put my finger in there
all right checkpoint give me a checkpoint right here
where is this kid what does it say sorry for any inconvenience but the volcano was closed due
to refurbishment those bats gargoyles did he go in here welcome to the volcano please put
any litter in the bins provided there's another portion of this game did we get the
reason why the kid ran away in the first place this is actually pretty cool there he is
do you actually think that gork has lore i don't know how the fuck am i supposed to know
maybe no no i went the wrong way fuck i'm kind of sick of gork i'm not gonna lie
but i have to finish gork
all right i will but maybe not it depends if i die like three or four more times i won't do it
thank god i can start here
what am i supposed to do down this way but things moving around
you're telling me my four-year-old son did this
out of all the good games that this is the one to get invested in what we i did pig detective
we did that one we need closure we'll get it all right i need to go now
and then for god damn it no
this is too much
jump come on gork i did it where is he where's the kid oh give me a fucking break really
can i even jump on this
this i got saved by frames there the hitboxes didn't trigger there
who knows what the hell this is gonna put me if i miss this it's bad i can't even get up here
this is too hard i can't get
fuck this oh i don't want to do this anymore i really don't want to do it anymore but i have
to this is something that you guys will never stop saying this is gonna be the floygan brothers
again shit i'm going backwards what what do you mean i'm going backwards what are you talking
about they both look exactly the same i was going backwards what no i wasn't i was going
the right way right i have no idea you guys just got in my head so hard i don't know if i'm
going the right way am i supposed to go oh my god no god damn it i can't take it anymore
oh no you have to beat gork you have to finish gork what oh it's really easy to fall off this
shit like that see who cares about gork you guys really want to see the end of gork
nobody does only maybe two of you do all right almost there okay stay on it
oh why what what did it do that for it just why i didn't throw i did yeah oh my god i'm
gonna fucking lose my mind over dreams gork no one cares about gork please in all capitals
please please all right how do they fuck this up like do i have to jump from here to another
one to there see oh that's not that's not cool that's not cool i think i have to it just pushes
you off is this the donut one no it's a different game what the hell am i doing wrong i think
i have to jump to that no what you stupid crystal just you wait i'm gonna make a game
like gork and it's gonna be gork too all right you just have to stay on it it's really hard
to stay on it's already fucking up and trying to kick me off see like fuck you it just
does the same thing every time oh god i had it too oh i have to see the end of gork i have to
is this gonna be one of those scenarios where i download the mario maker level and make it
completable i don't know what happened there no why i can't uh
uh this is harder than zekiro
okay don't i have to i have to keep jumping is what has to happen here
i gotta jump forward when we get to about right here forward forward see how it's trying
to do it already all right no crystal don't get hit by the crystal they're starting to
distract me a little bit don't touch see see what happened come on i did it that's it i
didn't find my son apartment etf no it's just a doom of the dreamiverse a bad dream oh yeah
first person horror game warning this game contains supernatural themes and may be unsuitable
for children get out of here any kids here out turn camera interact and laugh my ass off
it's just pt can i turn lights on is that if you search the kitchen for a knife and
investigate the noise upstairs um found one i love this dreams because it's almost like a
never-ending especially after when it comes out and when it all launches it will be a
never-ending place to just kind of do this play and just experience a bunch of weird
fucked up shit fun games little short movies and just like little big planet oh yeah this
is gonna be great all right investigate upstairs non-finished games yeah the games
you know it's only been for like five or six days you can't make an entire i'm not this is
remarkable for people that have uh let me just like eat all my sentences per second
this is pretty cool shit for only a week so what is up here is that the closet door
is just closed should i open the closet i'm gonna get jump scared there's nothing in here
bathroom mirror jump scare in the mirror what is that uh okay did we just load the
monster into the game is there a monster oh yeah yeah i'm gonna make a horror game
i say that but i want to make everything those hands all right that scared the shit out of me
and i'll tell you one reason why it didn't come out of my headphones it came out of the
controller i thought there was a insect on my hands or something on my hands remember press
and hold options to recenter your imp i don't have a flashlight this is really what the hell
is that there it is hiding down into the basement it's supposed to be cthulhu i don't
think a knife is gonna work here just throw the knife at him oh fuck didn't even hit him
with the sharp end what was the point of the knife a bad dream how do i always my thumbs up
i want to thumbs it up no i don't play again that's which which means i did thumb it up that
right not suitable for children yeah it's not too scary all right give me back this is called
radical bowling bald wizard travel the world in search for the gem of hair like doom doom
okay all right all right all right all right of the dream reverse make sure we have to have that
connie wakes in a strange and frightening place feeling not at all like himself
i've never seen such a strip it actually is the doom soundtrack
i'm not feeling like myself today why am i a hot dog
push you i'm not gonna comment on that i'm scared i'm scared i'm a tree i'm scared
i'm scared
what is this anorwondo uh what the fuck beta mode so this is dream within a dream within
the game dreams that's what i'm gonna assume here approach what the calculator
a giant calculator with the tape in it okay this is just getting a little odd
uh welcome to media molecule this is the place where your home the dream reverse was first
created why do the employees in media mall who walk around naked this is not real and where
you were first spawned we have noticed that new characters and worlds have been gone to emerge
but there's no doom connie nothing to fear your world is simply expanding as we invite
more dreamers to create with us i hope that makes you feel better now what makes me feel
better is reporting this whole office to hr because this is just not appropriate yes it does
i can't wait to explore the dream verse and meet new friends splendid stay and visit as
long as you like when you're ready to go home just walk into the light oh i went home
connie wake up uh winter search warmth on a desolate mountain slope death's holiday
rat city bowling all right fine bowling rear-print camera toggle neon mode i don't want
that on pin camera cool um i grab um something i grab one out and uh strike strike get a strike
come on come on neon mode fine shit uh it's gonna be stuck there forever we can't grab it
wait wait watch this rocket league not everything is rocket league guys strike this is cool this is
cute come on spin spin spin oh give the ball some force it's kind of hard to do
because i have to do this with my gyro that's brutal it's pronounced gyro no the my gyroscope
get there get there come on no it's pronounced gyroscope it is not pronounced gyroscope
no one times i've ordered a gyroscope before i've got one pink ball never misses bro do it
all right here we go this one's a good one to check that out as a force for you
you're not very good at bowling actually i am not good at bowling at all bowling for me is
mini golf and i'll explain myself they're the only two sports the only two activities on earth
that enrage me they enrage the fuck out of me i don't know why i'll go mini golfing and it's
i start out fine and everything's just dandy and i'm having a good time and i will i will go
over i will get like 12 strokes on one hole and want to leave i will bowl and i will
gutter ball twice or something or three times in a row and i'll just be like i don't even
fucking want to be here i hate this something about it i don't know what it is mini golf and
bowling both really pissed me off i think you know with bowling i think it's like the real time
score that's up on the screen so people will know how bad you are i used to like it back
in the day they had the thing on the table it wasn't up on a big screen people can walk
by and look at your screen and see oh like the funny name you put up like hot dog right
has like 34 points it's embarrassing by the way the only reason why i said the word hot dog
is because we were just a hot dog on the screen what do you mean no one looks at that i do
when i walk by i and i always hate when they put you next to the fucking good bowlers
i walk around i i request a lane i walk up and down i look okay there's two here
there's one in between two other uh parties bowling and you look at their screen they're
at like 180 200 average i don't want to be next to that person it'll be that would embarrass me
i will gutter ball three times in a row and watch them hit strikes and it's just like move
me i don't want to be there 200 isn't good what what are you what planet are you talking
about 200 is great imagine being insecure about bowling no it's just bowling in mini golf
because mini golf the same thing happens somebody two people will go in front of you
and they're they'll get like a birdie it's like a birdie sick man oh nice man my turn oh cool my
turn everyone watch me now i i thought i missed it's okay i can i get it in i can get it enough
now i went over a lot in way too much like it was terrible hold on i can still get parts okay
everyone's sitting there with their arms crossed waiting for you to finish you knock
it back you miss again and once you get to four or five strokes you start to do the thing where
you drag the fucking ball around and just drag it into the hole angry just because people want
to play speaking of which why am i still here that was fun if you don't like people seeing
how bad you are then why are you a streamer what do you mean i'm not i'm not bad did you beat
sick hero yet i did that like two weeks ago i died i beat the real true final boss in secure
how can i be bad at the game and still do that it's impossible beat secure on stream dark souls
three on stream you know the fucking joke i don't even say it chef versus chocolate from space
kind of need to play this one you always get high scores at all the wrong things
what does that mean look at how cute this is what i have to do secure is not even that
hard i mean yo look you you can say that if you want but secure started like a massive
debate about how hard video games are somebody tuned the piano for the love of god somebody
tuned the piano that's the funniest comment all night how do you tune a piano can you even tune a
piano okay is it weird let me tell you guys something it's not like fucking weird thing about
me i'm scared of instruments add that to the wiki and i'll tell you listen i'm gonna hear me
out on this i am terrified of an acoustic guitar do you know why i don't know what it's something
weird about it those strings are so tight every time i had roommates in college that would play
the guitar i've had friends i had guitars and you would they'd pick it up and they'd tune it
and it would be like like it's getting so taught it's gonna snap and it's gonna hurt them
i had to get up and leave speaking of leaving i would see them just sitting on the couch and
it'd be like and that's when i get up and like i think it's gonna break it's gonna hurt them
same thing with the piano it's just really tight strings tight wait didn't we already do
this one you are not supposed to be here bald wizard okay fine that sounds like a good one
also you guys know about the balloon thing i'm scared of balloons look i will be the first
person in line at the haunted house i will do all kinds of scary dangerous shit but if you blow
up a balloon in the room that i'm in i'm going to leave the room you could fill a room with
cockroaches and i would roll around in the ground and be like this is fun this is nothing
there's nothing nothing a problem here you could bury me in sand up to my mouth and like have
to tie like i i would be fine i'd be like ah this is kind of weird i'm like but this is
like you'll dig me out eventually right i would like jump i would like i would go like skydiving
no you blow a balloon up in the room i'm sorry i have to leave it's that the balloons blown
this is the story of bald wizard his only goal in life to grow some hair he has tried
everything he can done vast amounts of research read many books but he could not find a way
to get his hair to grow that is until he found out about the gem of hair a magical stone said
to grow hair anywhere one desires the only problem is the bald wizard has no idea where
it is located he makes his way to a village he's never been to before he decides the best
place to find answers would be in a tavern so he makes his way towards the tavern
as he gets ready to begin his journey in search of the magical stone that will help him achieve
the one goal he has in life to grow some hair this is the beginning of a long journey
so okay we're in the bald wizard things don't scare me like haunted houses scary things don't
scare me a clown could be in a dark room my lights in my bedroom could be off and
there could be a clown in there with a huge long face blood coming out of his eyes and
two knives in his hands and he walks up and goes right in my face while i'm dead asleep and
goes like and i would go whoa hey what the fuck man whoa get out of here dude what the
fuck it wouldn't scare me that much i'd just be like get out of here i'd be like the fuck
away from me idiot i'd like push you and be like fuck out of here why am i saying you
i guess if this is one of you guys oh god why is it you that's fucking terrifying anyways um
uh but if that clown was just no makeup on take the makeup off the clown he doesn't
even have to have it on i feel like this mechanic doesn't work okay get the clown
in the room with the bloody eyes the two knives and the scary laugh take the makeup off take the
knives away make his voice normal don't laugh hand him a guitar and have him tune the guitar
while i'm asleep same scenario i'm asleep i will wake up screaming clowns make balloon
animals no that's fine too actually no it's not fine they put that shit in their mouth
nope i saw a guy make a balloon animal one time and he was like
putting his mouth and tying it with his teeth and like i hate that sound i don't like it
and it always it's right before it's about to explode it has nothing to do with the damage
inflicted how am i supposed to do about this because okay if a balloon pops in your face
it's just going to be weird bring that over here it's not going to really hurt you i don't
know why i have this weird image of a balloon popping near somebody's face
and it like daffy duck cartoon fucking exploding cigars in their face i don't know why i think
of that i just do can i make this jump i don't think i can do i have to drag that all the
way across why why is this not moving can't bring it over here because i definitely don't
make this no well there you go i'm like a snake if i was an animal i would be a snake
i would well well i thought you're gonna be a rat no i'd be a snake because snakes aren't
afraid of anything except if you make a loud noise really quickly or if you tune a guitar
in front of the snake x and r2 these flames launch you in a specific direction do they
okay well yeah you lose momentum there snakes don't know what sound is
what do you mean they don't know sound did i get i think i won i think that's the bald coin
no snakes yeah snakes has no sudden movement so right not sudden noises what's the animal
that doesn't like sudden noises an elephant a horse okay yes yeah okay i'm thinking of a
horse i'm more like a horse all right this one was fun frogs frogs aren't scared of that
death's holiday all right keep going torch top the hollow kingdom come open world strategy
game where you run and build a fully functioning kingdom build empires and fight other nations
what how does this work search for germa can i is this actually possible uh this is
gonna be this is really awesome this is really really awesome it is but i don't i don't have
time for this i do but a bit of that this looks great i don't have time for this okay
there ain't nothing there let's auto surf embarrassing why would it be embarrassing
press triangle to drink absent um i don't think i can play this it looks beautiful but
the shaky screen no good that's really great that was really cool that was just a moving
art piece that was great no there's more is there more i don't think there's more i think
that's it that looks so oh that's so cool battle tops title screen well we're not going
to see that yet a haunted entrance nice this is by the ever talented mr sandwiches
i can run x's run oh shit we're on uh ferrovia it's gonna be a top down it's one of these
wow this is cool it's cool wow exploded are they bad what is up there
okay this is bizarre can i talk to people it's completely gonna hurt me floating candles bells
let's go up here see the giant monster whatever this is this skull what is that
oh it's kind of scary eyes oh my god leave a saw blade in his chest what did he say apple by
aw mall 2019 apple by this guy painted all these apples press square dogs run
now we saw this before we're open it looks like suzy's home bark
can you play this on the playstation too a version of it yeah
good to see you again i prepared some snazzy upgrades for you
you'll like them dashing double dash mago matic that's a hundred coins i don't have enough don't
be detected this is the metal gear solid vr missions press x to switch between prone and
standing wait what didn't even see it ah
it actually is the noise too that's pretty cool he's not gonna see me here right
oh shit it's not the exact noise it's pretty close um how far does that go
there's no what does the camera go just aims that way on the wall
whoa wait wait wait wait wait wait wait is that the camera doing that
these cameras aren't like even set up correctly oh if i didn't get stuck i would have gone
right through it ucqc if i had it i would use it he's trying so hard i know you know
like i know that ha ha thought i was trying to jump oh get in there oh you gotta be kidding
me i couldn't even see couldn't even see it i'm supposed to be able to do that i can't see
you through here poltergeist i just got knocked out of the room this looks beautiful find your
this is the dog one this one's unbelievably good find your bone
i love the bark i wish you could pick the dog though so much better you could pick the breed
this is the kind of shit that i'm gonna try to make i'm gonna put a bunch of time into a
bunch of skill a bunch of technical prowess i'm gonna hire like 15 people i'm gonna i'm gonna
spend like 20 or 30 000 on tomorrow's stream you're gonna still fail thanks for the confidence
man and still fail fine i'm gonna put my money where my mouth is tomorrow this is really well
made i'm gonna all right ready for prediction i'm gonna spend so much time i'm gonna fucking
learn everything it's gonna be i'm gonna have like a bunch of stuff to show i'm not gonna
do anything tonight i'm gonna sleep in tomorrow and be late to the stream and not have
anything done let's put that as an expectation so i okay i can at least meet or be better than
that dog has a flashlight on its collar okay this is great did an employee make this or is
this not an employee let's see no this is not an employee this is just somebody that has the
game gonna be there oh it's bone you found the bone i did it in three minutes it's my total
play time three hours
secret waterfall i think so yeah two bones no nice this one's called car drift
celebrate break shift up and down handbrake boost camera view lights shift up what did i
just do i drove into the garage all right i gotta i gotta shift down i think i broke the car
trying to shift and uh it was interesting yeah we're back in the haunted mansion i think i'm
gonna pleasantly surprise a lot of you tomorrow porto show controls we got jump pick up object
throw object stand in place now it's gonna be one of these little puzzle games he's not doing
a chad block yeah this is nice too i wonder if there is the end here's the interesting thing
right some of these look like they have a different almost like a different engine or
something this looks different well i have to get up here first this doesn't look like
the other games it almost looks like the frame rate is different or the
howard's process looks different maybe the lighting yeah what does this do uh okay oops
cool grab another one oh i can only have one now we go this way
oops the perspective is a little odd the first book all right it's kind of odd i collected them i
don't care why is this pre-recorded what the hell are you talking about what do we do with
this really this is bounce back and be in the face good throw it was an okay throw now
this go what's over here i like this one this is really good one there okay i have to blow the
wind machine there's proof that this is a pre-recorded stream i would love to hear
your proof i'd love to hear it what proof do you have there it is high speed hovercraft demo
work in progress this looks cool you can go really fast my god it still works am i upside
down headlights look back handbrake drift headlights turn music on and off well it's
pretty good actually okay brake drift handbrake drive over this jump you got it now we're in
the catacombs from we're still in this haunted house i think this is satan devil or something
can i talk to the devil uh i don't think so hold square to open but wait all right that's
a tail thank god i don't think i can die make it multiplayer bring it to pc yeah i don't i
think this is a sony exclusive i don't think you'll ever see this on pc this you guys are
gonna get terrified i'm gonna make the scariest shit imaginable you guys are gonna get jump scared
it's gonna be unreal is that it what's going on is this just the end oh pool okay
we still have the music from the last one playing so then how do i is it just x show
controls okay slow aim shoot aim guide okay now i'm not gonna turn that on people make fun of
so shoot is r2 demonic billiards all right we're gonna go with a green ball
in the right corner pocket there i thought i was gonna scratch i was about to instantly exit the
game it's gonna do the thing i do when i play pool with anybody just hit it into huge chunks
and then whatever you get in act like you tried to do that in the first place got it all
right i'm stripes now like it matters oh you're one of those guys huh yeah for instance see
this over here i mean i could try to get that but why wouldn't i just go like this
crawling across the table i'm on the table i didn't realize that i'm standing on the table
get them both it's that easy ah what do you mean foul this ain't basketball
fuck you get in there i'm trying to get that red ball out of there pretty good i think if
you ask me all right see that ball all the way down there we're gonna get a good spot
check that oh fucking come on what the hell view from westminster christmas 1893
merry christmas too good to scratch nice why is it getting scary free roam health bars yeah sure
tactic shooter tps how do i use uh equip pistol rifle aim shoot damn this is actually
pretty nice pistol nice too that was cool neon part one this coal puts you out here
the camera's in the same spot something's following me that's that's the something is
waiting and looking and trying to find out well no never mind this is called chinese
new year at the temple just fucking dropped it's a wallpaper it's nice all this is crafted
this is this is beautiful fireworks go off that's cool treasure hunt collect all this
is probably a pretty oh i thought that was ice what i was gonna say is this is probably a template
that a lot of people do for their first game maybe it's just easy to do the run around and
collect stuff how do i get unlock more coins yeah i'm gonna put time into this i'm gonna
give it at least one real shot we're gonna have a giant viewing experience those of you that also
have dreams and you want to make something and maybe we'll play it tomorrow because tomorrow
is the creation day this was just stick around and see people have made maybe we'll make a
certain tag that you can put on the your creation right like the edges like germa dash
something or story of whatever it is it'd probably be easier to do it that way so i can
just search for germa right this is a neon part two is it gonna have vr support it's only 2.4 gigs
yeah they really condensed it down what give people time to build stuff well look uh okay
let me be completely honest and not joke around here uh i'm gonna do a bunch of
shit tonight and i'm gonna try to show something tomorrow but if it's very clear that it takes a
very long time to do anything then maybe i will just say hey in like a week we're gonna do like a
green screen part two green screen movie night part two but it's dreams and give a tag yeah
i would just do it just a hashtag germa or have germa being your title or something
what the hell is a roller coaster that's cool there's no more track is this the end
do we just fall off neon part three whoa what the hell oh i i revealed the cool game mechanic
before i was supposed to what is this can i pick this up i'm not exactly sure what i'm looking
for here but maybe i'll find it i guess not portrait i'm gonna draw a bunch of shit too
i think we already saw this one yeah wait we already did this another roller coaster
this has to be by the same person right
oh okay that was pretty cool wow neon part four is that me that's me doing what i did earlier
anything else i can do can i go through the window we could have watched all the tutorials
by now no way and plus here's the thing there's a diff well this is there's a
difference between watching tutorials for three hours and enjoying a content that people have
made also these tutorials are pretty in-depth and i'm going to assume it's probably gonna
take about three hours to do most of them i also want to understand them too somebody made a good
point where this is really cool uh somebody made a really good point that if i do tutorials
on stream it's kind of just i sit there quiet while i focus on how to play the game for
three or four hours so i'm just gonna do it off stream purple pants beta celebration dance
who is god i would call this unsettling that was it that's the whole thing time corruption
time has been stopped to prevent further damage agent intervention required one find the time
control bracelet activate the power nodes enter into the powered singularity to restart the time
take control of the agent maybe there'll be checkpoints right next what are these checkpoints
for not tron i like the design of the floors it's almost like made of chalk found the time
bracelet forward in time oh okay let's see what it's doing very cool oh never mind all right
wait what's this so close them up okay back here flip them hey look at that in this one
i wonder when you actually know how to do everything and use the tools correctly i wonder
how long it takes to make something i guess it really depends on what you want to do you can
probably do dancing uh disco diaper guy oh god damn it you probably do that in like 30 or 40
minutes a day of work yeah let's see what i can do oh god how many more of these are there
i'm not controlling this
okay lovecraftian horror intro the most merciful thing in the world is the inability
of the human mind to correlate all its contents as by hp lovecraft that's it that was the intro
it's a nice snow scene i'm gonna get addicted to this game and want to make all kinds of
crazy shit i know i will i can already tell something that i'm gonna want to do just sit on
the couch and make shit for like five straight hours paris purple rain he's back again please
don't just play little big planet why would i do that when this is their new game this is little
big planet with like 10 000 times more content you can make everything you can make in little
big planets
fuck anybody said i'm not sure i can go anywhere i believe this is a tech demo in the building i
guess so well maybe we'll see what it is it's like clay but not clay it's a clay and wood
together whoa here's the outro small glimpse of what's to come follow if you wish to discover
what lurks beyond okay we're gonna be making these living comic books and shit
i don't even want to see that one mini golf i'm ready oh you're hitting the little guy okay
all right with the flag oops water bad all right i'm gonna hit it over the trees
shortcut let's get it through here that'll be good okay just gotta go right here let's get a
good putt all right come on don't be angry where's my putter no i gotta need to chip it
over here just give me a wedge god damn it i didn't mean to do that i'm about to be over
par here 50 meter putt i'm gonna get angry here i'm gonna be over par i only got one
more chance before i break the fucking thing in half golf is a dumb game bear study praying
showcase imagine somebody in the pga tour did that that looks great wow that's fantastic
i'm gonna try to recreate some of this shit it's gonna look so bad i'm gonna try though i'm
really gonna try i promise i definitely give this one a thumbs up that's really great work
shifting islands oh wait it's me i'm kirby those are kirby's eyes i know kirby's eyes and i've
seen them double jump it's rayman kirby it kind of is yeah oh different hats 12 seven
what is this what does it do powers no just cosmetics when you jump they disappear
however it needs to be like this that's pretty cool it's not a bad mechanic that's fun
is that from 3d world make it on top no i don't think i need to
oh shit right i was blocking that okay i'm gonna reset it all right now go like that
some more money for hats which one this party hat right here yeah oh now that's a color that's
me oh shit they brought more into play here all right careful all right didn't get a diamond
it's okay this is fun this is fun just playing other people's shit i could just sit here and do
this but i want to learn i want to learn how to do everything what's the goal the blue
double jump of that up again go up come on go now what oh fuck okay this is well made
now i have to go over here when we get to there oh shit okay and then uh oh hey that's it
i did it oh i felt like that was gonna happen i knew that was gonna happen i don't know why i
knew that was gonna happen i knew it i could just feel it for some reason whatever it's fine not
gonna happen again almost happened again this is a camera was it all just to take a picture
of myself it was that's cool well i gotta give a thumbs up no i gotta go wait wait wait
i want a thumbs up oh that's too bad how much this costs 30 bucks 29.99 for what is potential
to come that's a steal okay this is the grape escape level one jump and double jump press
and hold r1 for guided line oh it just really i could just i just cheated there's only one
way to go and i pressed it wait what happened what happened to the link costume is this a
different kukiri forest there's two of them there's more than one well no link model in this one
though shops and stuff what about here does it work no i think i need work this is so cool
this is really well made can i go down here no the deku tree it's been a long time since
i've played zelda i don't really i don't know where where that is sit up there see
the other side it's down here right you go through the little forest hallway you're supposed to
instantly know that wow how do you even make this let me in yeah let me in that's
sure i can get in oh this is beautiful job well done thumbs that one up it's still like
the paint tools i have to assume that you can probably use the move controllers right it's
probably easier to use the move controllers with a lot of this stuff maybe i'll charge
him up and get him plugged in i guess i'm using the guy but i just want to see the game
stop cheating it's not cheating if it's a developer implemented device to help the player
get to the end i didn't have to hack this i didn't put in game genie i didn't put a cheat
code in yes it's an easy mode but it's not uh not cheating come on so does the model of
the grapes in the game or do you have to actually do you have to make it did you did you make this
that's what we already made maybe top job most of the models have been made by the users that's
really awesome a lot of platforming in this one the first one was just getting out of the
house oh god for that goddamn mode it's helping so much i would have just been stuck that was
weird warning as this was made in the beta there will be bugs and glitches please enjoy enjoy the
ride the controller the horror transforms stand up i want to zoom view objectives
icons be marked with a white icon to be interactable all right song of betrayal will set you free
if you're hearing this you need listen closely someone something into this mess
now i wasn't able to get my stuff out and maybe you can leave
follow the recordings follow the notes live all the recording follow the notes
need a key is there a key there's a key this one's pretty cool though we used room key 205
security room what does that say no escape hey you shouldn't have to keep posting on a board
that no one even uses anymore i'm tired of cleaning up your messes either help me find the
spare monitor room key or at least buy the hotel a fire axe dummy that's from jay no way out
picked up bear burdens was this 208 bathroom board on subject 31b maris summers patients
seem to be stable sleep for now but she's getting restless about a music box we're
currently cleaning that thing so she can keep whining about it anyway we are now closer than
ever to a new milestone if we keep this up we will have this project locked up by the end of
the week i'll update you as we move ahead dr olfan dig in uh fish of failed pasts
you see those failed fishes nice leave now sin that's supposed to be me i don't think i have
a weapon or anything what wait wait is somebody chasing me somebody's coming this way oh god how
do i get out of here i don't have any what am i supposed to do i don't know what the code is
what was the code code it's not the door number sin five one hey whoa what the hell is that
i don't know it yet check the fuck off my god
three one five
which was especially the pierce hotel everything seems to be in order a few broken locks here
in there but nothing i haven't seen on hotelings before the only thing that concerns me is the
two locked rooms 210 and 211 they were unwilling to let me in there still renovations
i have my doubts if i the rest of the message is unfinished there's a germo one guy over here
kind of a few broken locks yeah yeah i already got it okay dog of sorrows hey y'all bet you're
wondering where the exit key is well it's in this lock box solve my riddle and find the
items silence is golden three animals were locked in a hotel dog took a break from escaping
the fish means for survival were down the toilet and the bear climbed up a tree to
see an escape route out a window i already have all skip for fuck's sake i'm shaking and
crying and pissing i need to fucking calm down is it me doing that hey oh this one's
actually pretty good hey hey yeah let me let me stop this guy hey hey oh wait i got closer
so close what do i do what is this key for oh look at that 10 i can't it's blocked up
i have no idea solve the riddle and look for something to break the boards with
well what i don't know i'm gonna pee can i do anything with him oh wait past sins will let
you in past sins will let you in sin now the ritual is complete it seems the old gods have
accepted mara as an offering this is great news now we just wait for our divine gift to
be granted to us as for our little sacrifice seems like a side effect of the ritual were
horrid white boils on her skin oh well it's the cost of progress room 208 key
it's kind of creepy 208 is um over here around fire axe use equipped item with r2
i think i'm gonna have to fight oh god kill him i'm gonna try i don't i don't think that's that
i don't think that's the guy i may have bugged the game out somehow now what music box
collected what do i have what whoa all right that was weird music box but there are more
boards to break over here toilet security room key we're almost done it's all the way back here
dude i'm fairly sure that thing's supposed to be scaring me he's supposed to be popping up
behind me i think i may have broken him though computers is password protected oh i just
fucking burped and choked as a valued customer we want to assure you the best in quality
from our amazing team of experts we have set up the lock on room 211 as per your request
the code is two six one three patients what the hell are you doing what was that
what the fuck was that that was just pretty scary i'm so sorry they roped me into it forgive
me i think it's huge this is a good one boss told me to dispose of the key to the server
room guess he doesn't want anyone opening the lock to 211 more of his obsession to make sure
no one destroys his little experiment i'm over at the stench permeating for this place's foul
through the key in the boarded up stall in the bathroom yeah we already got it
no don't fucking sinks sins manifest here guys that's not me making that noise it's two six
one let's go out out out out out song of sorrows collected i got it so what can i leave let's go
come on
did you guys like that i'm trying a different voice for you guys project hill redux special
thanks pat dax quinn all of them no that was good that was good that was a really nice
beginning middle and end it was great this is kind of morbid but the great the rape escape
level three is a gummy ship level and i'm gonna skip it because that will actually make me puke
gone rogue lightsabers this is a star wars game pw power 87 errors zero i think it's
a little short film slice maybe come out of freeze frame and slice i think they have a
lot of errors press play on the movie we're watching it so wait hold on i think that may
that may have been it gone rogue maybe there's more is it just playing again i think it's repeating
we're watching it again all right we're gonna that was cool i think we already saw spring
forest and let pretty much it looped yeah the red guy stands we're gonna get a download of
this video it's so hot internet somewhere this is really pretty all right i think we're
going to be getting to the end of the stream here and the end of this auto surf i want to
go back to that unknown island in the indian ocean so i'm going to spend the rest of the
evening i'm going to get some food first i'm fading i don't know why i'm going to make a
bunch of shit as much as i can for tomorrow if i run into a snag we'll see then we'll do
salmon max but i'm gonna try this is nice stream legends yeah we'll do stream legends in a minute
i'm gonna i'm gonna get battle royale do a full stream we do finish season one that's probably
the plan because we got two and a half episodes through last time i'm assuming we'll do two
and a half episodes again let's go away all right am i gonna play mordhau yeah i'll do
that later this week i think that's the end of that fireman mega man and fireman pick
up after your dog max penalty is 50 coins what where's that dog shit i don't see any dog shit
my turtle didn't do anything wrong that was a blind jump i should have done that
so is mordhau any good it looks really funny it's like another chivalry right
but not chivalry all right let me i gotta look hard to do that i can't see where the
jump is it's just a fall off that kind of a little spike oh i did it auto surf complete
30 creations let us know what you think all right what was the best one starry night was
great that's thumbs up already battle tops i died too quickly haunted mansion i didn't really
it was all right this one was cool but i died too quickly dog run is a thumbs up already
another solid now car drift uh this one yes comes that one up pool is already thumbs
up view from xmas now no this one was cool it was really well made that was a cool background
treasure hunt i don't really remember what the hell this one was uh roller coaster is
this a kinetic one no purple pants surprise episode five no no this was great already
thumbs up this one was also great and i want to make sure i thumbs it up great escape i
remember this one project hill right yeah this one was this that was the one that was good
gone rogue top 10 i mean top 10 i don't know what that means number one oh there you go
two serfs i think i leveled up to level five which means i can probably do all the tutorials
this is your aura your creativity grows and evolves your aura will change to reflect your
activities you can become a specialist at one aspect of dreams what or dabble in every area
as you like i have to pick a specialization so you can combine your talents and make something
amazing together oh no what am i going to specialize in level eight yeah but i only
you like to play you're an explorer of digital worlds you may not spend all your time
playing but it's what makes you special in the dreamiverse without you our dream
crafters would have no audience we salute you my specialization is watching tv all right cool
all right guys i'm gonna put some more time into this and i'm gonna get some stuff done
see if we can get at least a couple interesting things for tomorrow if not if
i still want to put time into it and i want to work on it then we'll see by tomorrow
i will do sam and max instead or more how whatever is you know more interesting to me at
the time and we will set a date if i open this shit up and it's like no way am i going to
finish this in like five days play rat city i'll play rat city who the hell is it i'm
probably going to search for it rat city rat no not rat k rat city welcome to the bustling
metropolis of rat city found it you're not finishing day one what do you mean probably
not but it's worth a try it's worth a shot am i cat or am i a rat i'm i am a rat okay
can i do what can i can i do anything uh i'm not sure i could do much here oh no that just
toggles noir mode okay anybody have any quests or anything for me maybe not it's just scenery
yeah that's what it looks like still cool though make a community dream that would actually be
really fun like a community dreams game i think it has to be out for a little longer though
and it actually needs to release when does it even release i don't know oh this oh nice like
apartment rat apartment nice that's cool why am i wearing a diaper i don't i mean i think
that's just kind of a rat and get out of my way everyone's just hanging out sleeping
the arts night that it's been built nice too this is cool well we got i mean we have to see what's
all the way up there can i sprint or anything so here another apartment dice this really is my
home huh i'll fall off if you push me off i'm gonna be really mad he almost did what else
we got go down up let's go up jump jump jump half life are you aware that the rat song has
been used on tiktok a lot lately really why oh that was it i escaped rat city give it a thumbs
up of course i will very cool you're not getting royalties no i don't sell it i want to get
royalties but i don't sell all right guys i'll see you tomorrow if we don't do this we'll do
sam and max or something else we'll figure it out i'm gonna see if i can put some stuff
together see what i can get done by tomorrow but regardless there'll be a stream tomorrow
i'll see you tomorrow thanks for sticking around it's good to be back the mom vacation went well
it's getting a little late so we can uh we can end here we'll go through the bits
i'm gonna pee one more time because that's probably a good idea you know so i'll see
you guys in a little bit be right back have a great night if you're leaving hey so uh let's
put this off of brb and on to g2g what do you say see you tomorrow let's go back a little bit
in the bit department this is from about six plus hours ago now jess you got it thanks for
the 250 was bestowed the gift of the flu this morning happy to see you back to ease the
sick hope you enjoyed the time off i did it's already here that you're not feeling well
get some sleep have some soup i would say those are the recommendations but thank you for the 250
uh thank you oh my god taeyon for the five dollars hey germa been a been a while since
i last donated but i promise you i have been abridly and that's the wrong one just uh stream
live just jumped up right there it's this one during your time off i came to a very
important realization i love you germa every day you were gone was painful and agonizing
can't imagine my life without you thought about this long and hard and i could only
think of one solution so here i go jeremy elbertson will you marry me no pressure
or anything but if you say no i'll be very sad uh well i'm gonna have to respectfully decline
because i um i i don't marry people i don't know it's probably not a good idea
so i'm very sorry evil streamer marry a stranger that you've never met to do it
if you marry them you'd get to know them i guess that's true but thank you for the five
dollars why dna thanks with 10 bucks dad is back i have returned have returned thank you
the ten dollars why dna really appreciate it thank you also thank you dork cube for the 250
hope you had a good time away i actually took the opportunity to see my sister this week
uh this weekend and we went to this exhibit with preserved human bodies
with like guts exposed and stuff germa discussed anyway i'm glad you're back um preserved human
bodies i think i know what you're talking about yeah it's like an exhibit uh i forget
what it's called they have a bunch of organs and a standing up kind of body worlds yeah yeah yeah
it was like uh it's i remember i remember seeing advertisements for it they had it here
for a while i don't remember how long it was here for it seemed interesting i feel like
i've seen it before too a long time ago yeah hope you had a good time good to be back
um bodies the exhibition that is what it is thank you too slashta slashta for the 10 bucks
germa just wanted to give you some thanks for the many years of entertainment you've given me in
this awesome community much love and respect man and i am always excited to see what you have
in store for us next germa hart also want to let you know that you're popular enough to
make it on an outro for a future funk album which is actually why i had to pick up this
record future funk album what does that mean wait what let's see here what is somebody sample
something just make a damn album already i i'm not talented enough to do that it's over what
drugs are you on today where's my audio why is it coming through my monitor that's weird
speakers there we go why is it it's over now this is not coming through here uh you know
what it's off i'll tell you right now no i'm gonna put my foot down it's off what drugs are you on
today it's over well there you go all right that's cool very cool what wasn't on any drugs
it's called uh enough sleep i guess uh thank you tadoff swiftler for the 50 dollars
50 earlier i missed it but thank you for the 50 bucks it's a lot of money they say hey germa
donated a month ago during securo but somebody one guy got mad at my name and reported me
so i got banned for 30 days here's some bits back keep up the great stream
wait hold on if you got banned for 30 days how do you still have the name
they've banned you for 30 days but they let you keep the name that seems a little odd
well uh that doesn't make that doesn't make very much sense but thank you for the 50 dollars it's
a lot of money and you got refunded for the bits maybe he's still banned i don't think so
but thank you so much for the money that's a lot of money where's the donate option
uh i don't do paypal donations or anything bits or subs i don't do the paypal thing
but thank you thank you tyler mike for the 250 hey germa last stream i mentioned that
vinnie had complimented you and it seemed like you hadn't seen the clip so here you go it's
very wholesome also if you watch it make sure to watch the entire clip uh i think we have seen
this one vinnie i'm sure someone already told you but one of his favorite streamers
i hear germa's doing an ama at the moment so i want to pay back the compliment i don't
watch a lot of live streams i watch more youtube videos these days
but germa is one of my favorite people i've ever met that does what i do and he's also
one of my favorite streamers he's also drunk okay he probably won't mean that
no i do i did
no i do i really do mean that so anyway goodbye for now you can't preface you can't be like
oh he's drunk though i was genuinely upset when germa was not at pax this year as stupid as that
may sound but he's a really good dude we get along it's a new york boston thing i think
no i think he's great now how come i because i had a few drinks all of a sudden that negates
literally everything i said now i stand by it i mean i meant it you've ruined his pax
experience well i'm sorry i just couldn't i couldn't go this year but thank you tyler
mike ferodian weapon thanks for the 250 hope you enjoyed your vacation good to have you back
yeah it was good it was very good spend a lot of time with family so it was nice lo-fi space
cowboy thanks for the three dollars uh four dollars actually am i ever gonna play monster
hunter again i don't think so i don't think i'll be playing monster hunter again uh i
completed the story off stream i got kind of what i wanted out of it and even if this dlc i'm not
sure i would go back to it monster rancher though monster rancher that's a different story
you'll probably see that again because we have to beat it but thanks for the four dollars
lo-fi space cowboy millhouse 701 thanks for five dollars rat movie the game it might take
a while but i could probably throw something together we'll see i'm not going to get too
over my head with this i just know that i want to try princess universe thanks for the five dollars
there's no waiting for the soy boy we did it we did i i showed it meath pleable thanks
for the 250 hey germo kind of a sad donation tonight uh but my sister just got diagnosed
with colitis any tips for her thanks big guy you'll always be the best streamer i'm really
sorry to hear that it's a really really annoying illness uh the best advice i could
give to somebody that gets diagnosed with colitis is to have a a more basic diet for a little while
and kind of start introducing foods again to see what kind of throws you off what
makes you feel better it's hard to tell if you just kind of keep eating the same things
you normally eat but they've come uh they've come pretty far with the whole colitis and
medicine and there are things that can really keep people in remission for a while i'm sorry
to hear that though hopefully hopefully um she can manage it thanks to the 250 i missed another
fifth what how did i miss this many oh i know why it's because my uh playstation 4 audio is
pumping through not my desktop audio it's another 50 dollars from lorag thanks to the
50 dollars 5000 bits is this the guy who beat gork on stream it is it is but thank you lorag
sorry i missed these uh usually pretty on top of that he's a god gamer thank you dude
thanks for the 50 bucks shallash ashka shallash ashka thanks for the 250
252 i may be being a one guy but i think you could make a castle griffin steed
two with dreams i don't know i probably could or at least a castle griffin steed one epilogue
because that would take a very long time to have i think like a full 30 to 20 30 plus
minute experience we'll see bingo sunshine thanks for the five bucks glad you're back
germa long time no see but please consider revisiting oblivion smooches to auto oblivion
yeah oblivion just sits in one of those weird spots where i can't put it anywhere and i can't
do it because there's always something else that i think i'd what i'd rather do
eventually i'm gonna run out of stuff that i would rather or start doing and oblivion is
gonna come back some of these games that i haven't played in a long time good guys once
we play them all what happens when i play them all what happens when i play all video games
i'm gonna have to play oblivion you know like another 500 streams i'm gonna play every
video game i'm gonna do everything i'm gonna have to play at some point but thank you
i do think about oblivion sometimes but not recently uh clowersy thank you clowersy
or clowers for the three bucks they say germa lied about enabling pog also enable ayaya or i
will literally scream at you for not being cute much loving kisses to you streamer with a
strange face why do i have a strange face i'm not gonna put i'm not gonna activate
ayaya i'm not gonna enable pog i already have pog i've got a we've got a good pog already
we've got two pogs here i need to i gotta go back i'm gonna go to half remotes there
look yeah we've got look at that pog that's a good pog we don't need another one
but thank you thank you so much for the three dollars let's get the credits rolling
there were a lot of resubs tonight i've been gone for like eight or nine days so there was
a lot of resubs thank you guys for continuing to support the stream even though i wasn't even
here so thank you look at this a bunch look at all these people that just resubbed this is
just today so i really appreciate that guys thank you even when i don't stream the stream
is still supported by a ton of fucking people so i thank you for that that's all i can say is
this is i think this is the fastest it's gone in a long time so many old man did low thanks for the
ten dollars here's your bits can i mow your lawn now why are you paying me to mow my lawn
shouldn't it be the other way around that's not a good business opportunity there you're
gonna run out of money let me do your dishes no i can do my own dishes no you don't have to
do any of that but thank you for the ten dollars old man old man did low i really appreciate
that thank you i want to make your bed no i don't want anybody like touching my bed my bed
is for me and only me i don't want people to touch my covers no no no no no let me open
up stream legends because i know people were asking about it let me get you guys your
food for the evening what do you say extensions my extensions stream legends there it is
ready three two one open gift has gone out let me cook you breakfast no can i clean your i don't
even know what that is i know i'm not gonna say that let me cook you no can i wash your car no
just watch the stream that's all you need to do you don't even need to do that you don't
want to can i clean your ears no i feel like that's weird can i wash your stream let me
clean your teeth can i wave at you politely yeah whatever you're just figuring out that it's weird
kind of all right guys that's it let me be your plumber i don't need any plumbing work done
you forgot the ads no i'm not running the ads maybe i'll run them tomorrow no ads you know
no ads tonight uh-uh not gonna happen all right good night guys i'll see you tomorrow if we
don't do dreams tomorrow then i will we'll set up like a community event where i'm gonna make
stuff and whoever wants to make stuff can make it we'll put a tag on it put a playlist up
but you're gonna see dreams part two tomorrow the actual stuff that i've made in the creation
aspect or mordhau or sam and max episode three or a coffee brewing stream where i just brew
coffee or that's it take care good night much love to you have a great fantastic rest of your
evening see you soon good night