Tennessee Boulevard. There's somebody eating strawberries in Tennessee Boulevard.
You know, known as the fruit bandit. We've seen this guy. No, no, wait, wait a second. Wait,
what the fuck is happening right now? What kind of car is this? What kind of fucking car?
I didn't even come pick up the trash on my sidewalk. Fucking trash company. That's what I think about
you. I don't want these boxes. Who put these boxes here? I don't like these boxes. $1.99 for
a slice of pizza. That's a fucking rip off. It should be two cents. We got chairs that don't
match my tie. Get out of here, orange. Fucking bullshit. What's this? Stainless steel? Yeah,
that's a fucking clock of shit too. What's this chair? Sale. Oh, we got a sale going on now.
Was I not supposed to punch that guy in the face? I was not. Sale? Oh, we got a sale going on now.
Sales are stupid. Gas companies? Gas companies are always trying to rip us off. They're always
$5 a gallon now. When are we going to get solar powered cars? That's what I'm talking about.
When are we going to get nuclear powered?
A beer. And I'll explain how the world really works. Who gives you the slip?
A car dealer, dog. By the name of Simeon Yattery.
By the name of Simeon Yattery. So this businessman, he look legit to you?
Fucker.
Well, is this overpass going to kill me? Let's see. Place your bets.
Is this going to instantly kill me or am I going to get under it? Nope. I'm dead.
Guys, this guy just had a problem from the very second I saw him.
Nice punch. Let me show you how it's done. The first person punching is just ridiculous.
Will you get out of here? You're going to get run over.
Don't ever take your eyes off the fight. That was your first mistake.
Actually, that was like your 10th mistake. Not entirely sure what you've done
to get this to happen, Franklin. There's no stars. So that's not what's going on here.
There's a cop that is just an absolute psychopath over here. I'm not sure what he's doing.
Yep. This makes complete sense. First thing I want to ask is, number one, why is this happening?
And number two, why is Franklin still alive? He's just this guy's shooting with a shotgun
over and over again. And he's just like standing here completely fine.
Is this guy shooting like funny bullets at him? Like, I don't get it.
He's like, taking cover. I'm going to take cover around the corner. What are you doing?
He shot him like 12 times. Franklin's not even doing it. Oh, I've got to dive over the bush.
We've got to get out of here. This is still happening. Is this guy going to run out of bullets?
Hey, everybody. It's Mr. Sneak Man. This episode of Mr. Sneak Man's movie is Mr. Sneak Man holds
middle finger out the window and it's not real sneaky at all, now is it?