Hello, I was where I get I don't think maybe I didn't open my mouth for a long time
But when I just opened my mouth, it was like my mouth was glued together going on. Yeah, sorry
I'm late. This is on me a couple things came up that I had to
Give a solid real look to auto had to be taken care of
Uh, I had to eat a 10 milligram cbd
Edible brownie that part didn't happen because you don't always tell when i'm lying when I make that here comes a live voice
It's my tell i'd be so bad at poker
I would lean in on poker like i'd have like pocket aces
And then go around the table. What do you want to do? Oh
Oh
Oh, mr. Albertson. What would you like to do?
Uh, I'd like to I'd like to raise
That's my tell that's my live voice. Apparently he's late. He's like, I know i'm late. You don't think I know this
I'm looking at the clock. Oh, I gotta mute
I said they're staring at the clock. Oh, fuck fuck
Fuck i'm gonna be in so much i'm gonna be in so much trouble. Everyone's gonna be so mad
I'm here i'm gonna play custom robo
the game cube
You're right. You're gonna get him in detention
this game is
one of the greats
That i've never played
When I bought the Wii and I bought this it's been sitting there for a while. It's been on that shelf for at least six months
custom robo
I thought you said sucks
But people i'm gonna tell you right now. This is the welcome to the stream today
20% of you are gonna be like, oh fuck this game 20% of you are longtime fans of this whole series
you're gonna be fighting those people and then
60% of you
Have me in a tab anyways, and you don't even care
Like 60% of you guys have me in a tab and the second that you start hearing like the live voice you're like
All right, let me tune in. What's he lying about today?
I'm gonna go this way. What the fuck is that thing?
And let me tell you something guys, let me tell you click over click click click click click click click click
Okay, i'm ready. What's he doing?
Okay, it's only like 5% of you
I hope
All right, let's go
This is custom robo incoming. I don't know anything about this game
At all. Hope you can hear it because I can't
You hear it? Yeah
All right, this is a game about customizing a robot you put them and they fight
They battle you battle other people's robots. It's like pokemon except you actually make shit
You don't just like steal animals and put them into a fucking ball. It's pokemon, but the person has to actually work
And and actually do shit
No, that's not right. That's not real
All right. This is a new journey. I'm ready. I'm excited for this
Hello
You hear a phone ringing and it could be anyone nobody can do keeper southerland, but him that's another guy that you can't do
Oh, you're there good
Dad, is that you?
I can't talk long son. Can you come outside right now?
Yeah, okay
sans sans when he's older and he's talking to his son sons dad
What's wrong dad? Why aren't you at work?
It's your birthday, isn't it? I brought you a present here. Hold out your hand
Is this where like dad makes you pull his finger or something?
Wow
It's the watch you promised me
But don't you need that for work?
They're very special watch sons
There's nothing else like it in the world and I want you to have it. They're serious. You're really giving it to me
Thanks, dad. This is so cool
Cut to the watch is broken because the kid dropped it and stepped on it and smashed it and maybe dad
You shouldn't give like an eight-year-old like a 14 million dollar rare artifact watch not a great idea
Like I said, it's very special and I need you to take care of it. No problem. Dad. I'll take good care of it
Good promise me one more thing
Keep it on you always don't ever take it off even in the shower
Even when taking a bath, uh-huh. You got it dad. I'm never ever gonna take it off
Think of me when you wear this watch take good care of it
Even when you're all grown up, I want you to keep it safe. It's not gonna fit anymore
It's gonna be embedded in his arm. Don't ever take that off and don't ever adjust it either
I'll know it's gonna be a big red embedded infected fucking thing on his wrist. Uh-huh watch ringing
Look at the time
Dad's gotta go. You'll be a good boy now. He's gone and he's never coming back
Huh, you're leaving but you just got here
I'm sorry son, but I have to uh, there's some work that only your old man can do
I have to go and get cigarettes
Goodbye son. Why are we getting it? I'm gonna get cigarettes meme
Remember think of me when you wear this watch take care of it. Don't forget. All right
Is this even my dad I won't but dad, where are you going?
Far away
I have to go to a place. That's very far away
Prison
I'm going to prison son, and I don't want you to know
Dad
That was insane
Why would you do that in front teaching you kid all this fucked up shit wake up?
But you got wax in your ears. I said wake up and get out of bed. What the hell am I in a hospital?
Honestly, just because you don't work doesn't mean you can sleep your day away
Do you even know what time it is? It's past noon
You were supposed to start streaming 31 minutes ago. Don't you have a job interview?
What was that place again stale horse? You need that job if you're gonna pay your rent
Now get up and get that job
You heard me get out of bed and drag your lazy behind to that stale horse interview
Geez good morning to you too, and it's not steel horse. It's steel hearts
Whatever just get up and get out of bed
You need that job
Oh and good luck. What kind of room is this?
This is a hospital. I still have the watch on. Well, these are interesting clothes
Holy shit. This is awesome. I don't even I wasn't expecting this to be running
Half-life, uh to get two open door sounds, right? Whatever someone's to say whatever
Wait, did I do it? Can I do anything in here? Can I touch anything? No new part data, please come back. It's kingdom hearts
Yeah, this this character exists in the kingdom hearts universe somewhere
Look at you all gussied up and ready to go. Now. Don't you come back here without a job?
I've been worried about you
And not just because of the rent, you know
You worried about me?
Well, we've all been worried not a single word from your father for years and then that letter come
It must have been a terrible shock to find out about his death like that. Just a lettering of will
uh
Did he crash his car?
eight years ago
Just curious
Telling me to become a robo commander. I know it's weird, but I hadn't seen him for so long
In fact, the only thing I really remember of oh my dad
Is the watch he gave me
I don't remember anything else
That's beside the point
I need to worry about the future now
That's certainly true. You've been living off your family savings for years
It's about time. You got a job
I'll do my best. In fact, I'll do whatever it takes to become a commander
Isn't neat
That's what your father wanted. Isn't it? At least that's what it said in his will
You're a good boy, you could go for any job you wanted but you don't want to let your father down
But you could go for any what I mean, you're a good boy. You could go for any job you want
But since when does being a good boy
Represent skills in a field
You go to a job interview
Now, what would you say your skills are? Well, i'm a good boy. Holy shit. That's the first one we've heard today. Come on in
We only have bad boys here. They all have tattoos all over the place
They have neck tattoos and they wear leather jackets to work. Oh, thank goodness. We've got a good boy. Finally
Yeah, I wonder why did my dad want me to become a commander?
I don't know why it was so important to him, but I'll give it a try at least, huh?
I like to see his last wish fulfilled a commander, huh? Yeah, I can do it
Uh, what's a commander do commander's a person who controls a custom robo
No, i'm afraid. I just don't follow that. Could you say it a little less green?
Anyway, don't think of me as a landlady. Think of me as a friend
If you need any advice just ask
Thanks. Well, then you go get that job and become a commander at stale horse. I'll do my best
Bye
What just happened to the game?
Nobody move nobody move
Nobody move. All right, is this the stale horse?
One day i'm gonna join the police squad and use my robo to fight crime
What are they doing?
I'm gonna keep practicing with my custom robo until i'm a big and strong bounty hunter
these kids in timeout
This looks like
future timeout
I don't get what are the what are they doing?
My wife told me the kids would need a robo. They were going to get anywhere in this world, but
Those things are expensive. I have my needs too, you know
Hi there neighbor job hunting again. It must be rough out there. Good luck
It's not burning. All right, we have to go to the stale horse. This is like pokemon
Wait just a second. I said you could treat me like a friend. That doesn't mean you can go poking around in my office
Right left right left right left
Where is this place?
Whoa. Oh, it's doing it automatically. Okay, that's good. Oh, here comes the first tutorial battle
What do I talk to first? All right, let's talk to you
All right, what do you want? All right, you're here for the interview
You see that scary looking guy over there. He's the guy you want to talk to he's the boss
Okay
I how do you i mean, what's this one? That's weird
It sounds like a trash compactor that's on a person talking
So you're here for the interview, right? Let's get this over with
You ever work a bounty hunter before?
Of course
No, it's my first time
I think I have no it's my first time of course. No, it's my first time
I think I have no it's my first time
And don't be cocky
Look forget it moving on next question. You got a robo
I lost it. I can't afford I lost it. I can't afford one. You got a spare. I can't I lost it
I can't afford you got a spare
That was perfect. I don't have to do this one
That's just how the guy laughs. That's okay
You're funny
Anyway, i'm sorry, but I need an experienced guy with his own robo
I just can't afford to hire an amateur
My watch is going to turn out to be a robot, right?
What are you talking about? We can't afford to hire anyone who's not an amateur
Besides i'm being the new guy. I'm sick of being the new guy. We need someone I can push around
I'm sick of dealing with the chief on my own. What'd I tell you about these bad boys?
Hey, just a quick question
You wouldn't happen to be a good boy, would you?
You got something to say
Listen, even if we did hire you we don't have a robo or a spare
Oh, you'll need to get on get one
Make a good impression
What should I say?
I'm a good cook
Oh great. I'll call you when we're going after the sinister spatula and his bake sale bandits
None of this really matters though
The simple fact is we don't have the money to buy you a robo
And so that's why I can't hire you
Does he have a booger hanging out of his nose?
Oh, but but but
We really need some fresh blood around here chief
We've got too much work and not enough people
Can't we get an old junker robo for him to use?
You don't pay the bills around here
Sorry pal. You look nice enough, but you might as well forget it
Whoa, we've got a call. Maybe it's a job
Yeah
Steel hearts your one-stop bounty hunting shop. This is earnest
How are you today? Are you sounding lovely as usual?
Lovely. Yeah, is that a woman chief? You got a girlfriend?
Shut up you
Oh, yes. Yeah, and of course
No, we'll be uh, yeah. Yeah, right. Yeah. I got it. I got it. I got it. Yes
Understood
I'll send someone right away
Got work to do harry standard burglary and the police squad's fighting theme
Police squad's fighting them now
We need more we need a bit of theme music. Hey, you said you're a cook. Are you awesome a musician?
I don't want to go if the police squad's gonna be there
By the way, who just called?
I'm whatever
Shut your yap and get going head out to the research lab
Request comes from the lab director
linda
I'll go i'll go leave it to me
Oh, i'm harry
Take the kid with you
Once he sees what a real fight looks like he'll tuck his tail between his legs and run home
Wow, oh man. All right. Come on. Let's I just don't get in the way
Somebody say reddit walk
I thought was linda on the phone. She's the director of the robo research lab
Something going down at the lab. It's really gorgeous smart and compassionate
Really? She's the perfect match for me
Okay
I think of her like an older sister sorta. I mean not really but oh now that that's weird now
That got weird
That got weird really weird. In fact like weird where that just made me uncomfortable being in the same seat
As you
But you were not sitting together
Don't try anything funny with her. You got it
Yeah, I got it
I make no promises
What do you mean funny
You know like hiding behind a wall and then jumping out and scaring her stuff like that
Oh that this is that they're in like thought battle. This is a fucking banger. It's those bottom feeders
Don't be mean
We're bounty hunters
Whatever you all pray off the lowest of the low you bounty hunters are all bottom feeders
Don't give me any static. We're here on an assignment. Oh, yeah, nobody here asked you for your help
I did
Uh for a bunch of grill marks on her legs
Well, what we got this covered
Looking good as always linda
Thanks harry
I need you to take care of those crooks right away
They're after ray01 our newest robo. It's still in development and it was top secret
Top secret. Oh, that's so cool
Yes, but there's no telling what could happen if it were to fall into the wrong hands
We can't let them take it with your skills you should be able to take care of them easily
But that's what we're doing. They're stealing our newest robo. One can't be too careful
That's right. You heard her. You can't be too careful and that's where we come in
I can't imagine if my window was open and like my neighbor was listening to this
I'm realizing this now
Hearing this out of context this person
You know what this you know what? I would be happy with it completely. You know why i'm writing a screenplay
I'm like doing a screenplay thing
Holy shit that guy's up there acting. Oh, he's he's right. He's writing a screenplay. That's definitely what that is
What else could the fuck that be?
There's nothing else that makes sense with that that situation at all. That's a pretty cool screenplay that guy's doing
We're gonna get involved but you know, you can't always rely on the police squad. Some jobs are just too important
Okay, then
You wait here try not to get in the way
You just watch linda, but you just watch linda. This one's for you
Good luck harry burglar why are the burglars wear those on their faces?
What do you want? You don't look like one of those police squad guns
My name's harry and i'm a bounty hunter
bounty hunter
You mean one of those
mercenary scumbags i'm just doing the other guy
So what do you want with me? You want me to fight or something?
bingo
Man do I feel sorry for you? I feel like this is me
He just said I feel like this is me talking
And man, I feel sorry for you. Your luck just ran out
For the love of linda. I harry of the steel hearts will be your undoing
wait a minute steel hearts
Oh, you mean those bottom feeders?
We're not bottom feeders. We're bounty hunters
I'm counting on you harry
Please hurry up with the tutorial and protect ray one and teach him how to press a already for god's sake
Uh, we're trying our hardest, you know
Um, excuse me
What is it?
What are those people doing?
What are they doing? They're they're fighting of course
Fighting you expect me to believe they're fighting
Uh, yes
But they're not doing anything
They're just staring at each other
No, no, no, no, they're using their custom robos to fight. Can't you tell?
Huh?
Well, I don't see any custom robo anywhere
That's because they're fighting inside the holo. Museum
a holo zam of course
holo zam
It is a thought battle. Yes. A holo zam is a fighting arena created in a digital environment
The custom robos fight within that virtual battlefield
Hmm. I think I get it. Please stop spinning it though
Oh, but yes
Where's rayo one?
I haven't seen any robos at all since we got here
Well, the custom robo remains in cube form until it is released into the holo zam to
Wait, you're teasing me, aren't you?
Surely, you know all of this already
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I've never really seen though
You do work with harry. Don't you aren't you one of the steel hearts bounty hunters?
uh
Steam coming out of my I mean, yeah, i'm with the steel hearts. I think
Out of my ears
Well, then get to work go fight some burglars. What are you what are we paying you for?
Take a look harry and the police are having a tough time. You should be helping them
Uh, why don't I just go punch one of these guys in the stomach?
What are you talking about?
I mean aren't these burglars right now completely engrossed in their digital world
What if I just went and stabbed them all in the back one by one?
No, no, no, that's uh
I mean you could try I don't think it'll work
Yeah, yeah, I guess i'll help
All right, is there one that's not fighting
This guy here is pretty strong
Just pick one of these up and overhead hit him in the head with it. What's I don't understand the problem
Harry i'm here to help you
What did you?
Ah
Oh, wait, there's the cube. Oh you idiot. Don't talk to me when i'm fighting. I lost the fight because of you
Yeah, that's what you get for not paying attention
Oh, I think I hurt myself. Oh shoot. They're gonna swipe that new robo
harry, uh
Why don't we just shoot him? Let me help
But you don't even have a robo
Oh, yeah, that's right. Should I punch him in the face? I could punch him right now in his face
Let me borrow your robo. I'll use it to fight
It won't work. I've already done my eye scan registration. I'm the only one who could use it
Eye scan registration. What the heck? I got no time to explain
Whoa, can I go now?
I mean if you two were just gonna fight amongst yourselves, you really don't meet me here. Do you?
And even the crooks are making fun of us. If only you had a robo and a scrumptious cake
robo
Hmm. I guess I take this one
What's this box?
Huh?
There's a button on the back
Better press it. I better forget it
I'm gonna let me check. Maybe all right. Let me show you a cool trick. I'm gonna smash this off my head
It's gonna crumple up like a can but i'm gonna do the bar thing where i'm trying to describe
The thing I want to describe to you guys, but it's hard to do it right now
Well, it's starting to buzz
Well there did you just do an eye scan registration?
You still haven't told me what that even is
Eye scan registration is when you look directly into the robo's sensor while pressing that button
Okay
But there's no time to explain that
The point is you're now the only one who can control that robo
Hurry and die
This is a robo
Shut up and do as I say beat that burglar
Think about a kid you should think about this kid
You sure you want to go up against me even though you never used to cut the robo for your entire life
This wise guy thinks he's too tough just because he hasn't got lucky against me
Captain he's definitely not going to be lucky against you
And make sure to be in the mess hall for dinner
Now listen your robo shoot from the robo cannon on the left side
Nobody knows what that is
I'm not even gonna say what it is. Oh, yeah, there's a lot of new people here
Oh, whatever you'll figure it out
All right, your robo will shoot out from the robo cannon on the left side
Robo cannon this machine that shoots out the robo cube
The robo cube transforms once it's been fired. All right, so I shoot it out of a cannon and it turns into a robot
Custom robo 101. What is this link?
All right. This is like this is whatever i'll show it
This is better. I gotta make sure this is not the chuck-e-cheese kiss image
Okay, because i've all right. It's not
What the fuck?
There you go. I got it for you
All right, when the robo cube counts down to zero it completes its transformation. Do I actually run around the robo?
Press the b button to fire your gun
Use your gun to blam blam blam your enemy's energy down to zero and you win use the control stick to zoom zoom
Zoom around and use the b button to fire
All right, i'm just gonna do it
Fights made him weak you'll do just
Boom zoom zoom bang bang
Buzzwords
Enemy. Oh shit
All right
That's that's the enemy
Paints parts and model types. All right. Hold on customized robo. What do I have?
Oh, he's so cool looking. This is ray01
fighter model basic gun
Okay, come with basic capabilities fires three rounds at a time aerial and ground shots are the same medium range
standard standard bomb standard pod standard everything I don't have any I
Oh shit, okay
There's 13 pages of guns
I'm sorry that was that that just came up
All right, let's go
It's an american game
What do you mean american game?
All right, ready three wait with the what?
You you have to throw them out like dice
How do I get out of the cube? How do I get out of the cube?
Holy shit, this is actually pretty cool
Reborning zoom zoom zoom around
I don't have a zoom zoom zoom. Oh, he's gonna beat me
Do I have any other buttons or weapons?
Wait, he's he's
Oh wait, there's a double jump
Wait a minute. All right, I get it. Oh
That's missile. He hit himself his own missile
Use the terrain to my advantage
mashing buttons
Oh, that was a dash move. That was like falco
All right. That was cool. That was pretty fun. That was just the basic tutorial
That just he landed on his neck
Good work. Oh one of the police guys just blew it go over there and clean up his mess
Yes
I like the soundtrack
Oh, come on. I knocked that loser out. Don't deserve a break
All right. Listen up that guy ought to be worn out from his fight, too
If you listen to my advice, you should be able to beat him
Use the r button to fire bombs and use the l button to launch an attack pod
Okay
Firing your pod doesn't stop you from being able to move freely
Run at your opponent and keep on pressing the l button use the r button to drop the bombs and use the l button to blast
the pod
Sticky bombs
One more thing if you get caught in your own pod blast you're gonna take damage drop the bomb blast the pod
Enemy we just look at it pod bomb
Just easy enough. Just throw just just drop bombs. All right. I'm still confused about this part
Have to tap a
Why does he have an advantage?
Wait, oh
Well, they're kind of like homing missiles in a way
Why would you come over here? My fucking specialty is mid-range dude
Shoot him in the air too, right?
Fuck him down and then do it this game's cool than I thought it was gonna be
Uh-huh
Okay class
Can we can I get an apology now?
No
Why?
That's just kind of hard hit
Right there boom
What this game's worse than evolva. What are you talking about? No. No, it is not
It is not even close by the way that game wasn't even bad
That game was actually kind of fun. You guys just wouldn't give it a chance
Not bad for an amateur
This is way better. I mean this game is like a classic video game
We lost another cop take the next guy
Up up the police squad ain't nothing still I break a sweat
He looks pretty tired. If you listen to my advice you should be able to win
Try using the a button or jump you can do I know i'm going to neelix again. I know but it's it's fits for me
I don't know why
No, it doesn't fit this character at all though. I just it's what i'm doing
You can do an air dash twice I learned that already
You can charge with the x button. Yeah
Nice. All right. I get it
Rubble can't move when it's down
Use the a button to jump and the x button to charge crash
Got it. Got it
You only do a charge when you're on the ground. It won't work if you're in the air jump and crash
Volva 2 waiting room that game doesn't exist
happen
And these people
Make it I can't make a game. All right, get out
I'm just gonna overwhelm this guy. All right. He has a much longer countdown than me doesn't he? No, he doesn't
Yeah. Yeah. Yo, yo, yo
Yo
Why does that happen?
Look at that juggle
Look at that around the corner. That's a mario 64 battle team shit
How would you get that close?
Hey, yo, this game's fun
I really like this
And this is just this is the tutorial got a lot more to see
With 13 pages of guns, you now have access to the twin flank pod f
Go visit a parts generator
You want rayo one and smash?
Um, not not really no. Well, I think you still need some work, but well done
He was an assist. Yeah. I mean, I I don't know him enough. I have to get to know this character and see if I like it
Before you take them on go over to the parts generator and get yourself some new parts parts generator
I'll explain later just stand in front of him press a you'll get a new part
One you can use right away
Okay, go in front of that machine and press a
Yes, go press a
Thanks. You could have said that in one panel. We've got a twin flank pod f
Nice. Okay. So what does that mean?
What happened here? I turned my back on one second and all my men get wiped out. I'm worn out, but we need that robo
Last guy's exhausted. This should be as easy as a scrumptious cake still you'd better listen to my advice
Use the control stick to change the direction of the robo cube when it launches
When the cube hits the ground the number shows how long it needs to charge for the transformation
To speed up the charge tap the controller buttons rapidly. Okay
If you transform before your opponent you get to attack first
So I didn't know that use the control stick to aim the robo cannon where you want to shoot and then tap the buttons. Got it
Got it
smash mash mash mash
What why are you linking with this? What is it? Why the I don't get this?
This is shitty picture of me too like right about to start laughing with like eyes. I hate that photo
turn
Tappity zoom zoom jumpity jump bang bang boom boom clam crash
To the porn ads love it. Can we talk about that for a second?
I was in a second porn ad. Is that what you get?
Because I know there was one before
Is this number two? Yes. Okay for those of you that have no idea and i'm not gonna i'm not gonna link it
I don't want to give any attention to it. It's like why would I do that?
uh
Somebody used for some reason
people use this
Me laughing and talking like six years ago or five years ago, whatever this was
And they put it on top of like it's me interacting with a girl online
It's uh, it's like an interact with a girl fake. I didn't do it. Like they just use it
I I have I don't even I have no idea
Yes, it's real and this has happened twice
This is not a one-time occurrence
It's ridiculous
Somebody all right. Somebody said are you soon?
uh, okay, hi
Okay, let me let's go over the amount of effort that it would take for me to get into a legal battle with a porn ad
Well, i'm not gonna what should I lawyer up? All right, i'm gonna lawyer up. Let's do I don't what do you want me to do?
I don't even know where this company is bay. I don't know who this I don't know anything about these people
It's not worth it for me to do that
I'm just waiting for the day that I get hit up by somebody that I like
Haven't talked to in probably five ten years or something like that
Hey, dude, are you like doing porn now?
What's this? What's this ad? Are you what's going on here? Did you see this and i'm like, yeah
I should say yeah
Yeah
Is that all right with you?
uh
Um, yeah, I I just was care. That's you. Yeah, it's me
Okay, man. I do. Yeah. Hope you having a hope you having a good you have any kids or anything?
No, no, do you have any kids?
Yeah, four. Cool. How are they? They're good. All right. See you again in 10 years when you ask me another question
Hi
But I have to customize plus if it's not based in the u.s. But yeah, it's just
And I look i'll be honest with you
It doesn't that doesn't I don't care. I really just don't care. All right, where's that new thing basic?
standard
Where is it? Is it already attached? What was it called? It's a pod. Oh, it's the pod
One flank pod. Oh wait mash
I wasn't mashing. I wasn't mashing. It's okay
Yes, it was but no, I don't care really. I don't
Look, okay. Let's let's go over this if it was like
something
Egregiously awful that I was in like you guys all know I have the green screen shit and the green screen shit is literally
I don't care what anyone does with it
Except
you know
There's some things that I would not be comfortable with my image being put up, right?
It's very few things
But let's be honest. I think you all know what they could be
That's how you juggle
Wait, I can aim this
Holy shit, this changes everything
It's got like little mice
What about a penis enlargement pill advertisement? No, I don't care. You have access to the three-way gun
Omega low that's actually funny. Okay. Yeah, I I don't
there's a line right and
The line when you if you cross the line, you know, you're crossing the line
It's not hard to determine that I don't think so
There's a very clear line. I think of what like all right, don't fucking do that. Wait, who's this?
God, when did you get here?
Why did you hit your head
Listen, the reason you got beaten is because you're not properly trained
I've said it before and i'll say it again
You need to get out of the mercenary business
Start studying get yourself a class a license and join the police squad
Oh, don't start on that again. I told you I wouldn't be caught dead in one of those tacky uniforms
Look, i'll pay all your exam fees. It won't cost you a dime. What do you say?
It's not about the money. I just don't like studying
Captain mira, we've sent the criminals over to hq. We ought to head back to their ourselves
I can't believe we needed help from those bounty hunters. I'll make sure that all police squad members presented this travesty
We'll hit the training room hard
After mira
We should get back to hq
I'll be waiting at the front gate. See you harry. I'll be working late. So don't wait up for me
Get some sleep
Keep yourself warm when you go to bed
You don't want to catch cold
stop
Stop, stop. No, stop. You're ruining her for me. Stop, please
That's not what it's ended up here in my head. That's not what she sounds like. Stop doing that
You always treat me like i'm a kid
Is that your brother? Is that your older sister? Is that your girlfriend?
Is that your older sister?
Yeah, jeez. She's always acting so macho. It really freaks me out. There are nothing's in your business
Harry are you hurt?
Linda yeah, i'm okay. I never felt better
By the way harry this person's weird. I would not want to talk to this person. It'd be weird
Look, i'm i'm i don't do this in in real conversations with people
When i'm like one-on-one, i'm not like hello. Yes kim. We're gonna go get a nice delicious steak
I don't i don't i don't do that
Um, and I do sometimes I do sometimes all right a few times i've done that
I yell up the stairs and i'm like honey
Um, can you come down here for a few minutes? I do this all the time. Fuck. I do this all the time
But not that often not every sentence maybe like once every few days
Well, he's got what it takes to be a great commander someday still. He's got a long way to go
Oh, I totally agree linda. Oh, you're so observant like that. It's incredible. Yeah
It's not like he got the best robot that exists ray. Oh one. It's like the most strong robot
You gave him like a uh, yeah
I I have a regular default hearthstone deck and he has every legendary in the game. That's not no, it's fair
great commander sheesh
Harry i've got an idea. How about letting him use our new robot ray? Oh one
He adapted it pretty quickly
And i'd like to gather some data on his usage and control. Can we can we talk about hearthstone for one second?
I know everyone's gonna be like
I played it recently
And holy shit how much that game has changed
I was doing like the solo adventure stuff and I was like, oh, this is kind of fun
I remember when they they did this stuff
the amount of like
Throw up eight minions on the board wipe eight minions throw up eight minions on the board add plus four plus four to all minions
Wipe all minions eight minions on the board. When did that start happening?
No one asked
Yeah, but I I decided I wanted to talk about it. It was three years ago
What happened? Oh, that's probably the last time I really tried
You have no free will. Oh, yeah
Are you sure?
Are you sure it's not you that doesn't have and there he goes purged
Who has the power here?
MonkaS
Wait, this guy he's not really he's not with us. He came by today looking for work
The chief doesn't want to hire him though
Oh really i'll recommend that earnest hire him myself then
I can't wait to see his face so we can go ahead and take this ray-01
Sure, go ahead. Of course. He's already registered
So he can only use the one that he's the only one they can use it time to read
Yeah, I know dang if only I had made eye contact with it first. Wait, what?
That's weird
It's an eye scan. So what it it just it attaches to anyone that it looks at its eyes first
So what if a baby looks at it first?
Like an infant just happens to match eyes
Is that is that it we have to wait till that kid gets old enough to like think?
We just put it in the shelf good link good link omega lull good link
Of course, you always say that it's always good link omega lull and then I click it and my nose is stretched by 20
What is it? Did you did you photo? Who is this?
What is this? No, i'm okay. I'm done. I'm done. I'm playing the game
I'm not showing i'm not showing anymore like chuckie cheese and I i'm not doing that anymore. We're done with that
Oh another great question. I completely forgot to ask
Oh, uh, nothing. Come on. Tell your name
Oh, what's my name?
Well, it's um
What is it not jacks
paul
Oh, my name is paul in all capitals
It's important. Otherwise this lowercase is not my name paul. Oh one. It's weird that
Oh, I should make
I should make a cheeto
Oh
Dale, huh? I'm lynda. Nice to meet you. Don't worry dale. I'll talk to the chief. Oh fuck. It's lowercase d. Whatever
Ain't that great dale and it sums
Oh
right
By the way lynda, do you want to grab some lunch?
Oh, i'm sorry. I've just got too much work to do the whole lab's a mess. Thanks to those burglars
Besides your work here is done. Don't you have to get back to the steel hearts office?
I'll give earnest a call and ask him about dale later. You know what I mean?
See you later harry
Load the saves. No, I can't load a save state. I don't have a save state. Don't tell me that exists by the way
She knows i'm a busy guy. She's got a lot of class that linda is awesome
Poor women or something
I almost forgot dale. I was going to tell you about the parts generator
Me that machine i've got one in my apartment
What
What's a parts generator doing in your apartment?
You don't have a custom robo. You don't even know what if well they you don't know what they are
It belonged to my dad. I never knew what it was supposed to do. It just kind of sits there
Yeah, well, I guess i'll just have to skip that accidentally
Anyways, I was about to explain about the parts generator registers new part data into your robo cube when you buy a robo
It only comes with the standard parts
You won't have access to a lot of parts if you don't collect enough battle experience when a robo gathers battle experience
The internal computer records the battle information when the parts generator automatically reads the record and gives you the new part
Any new parts you get you can use them in the next battle. Whatever parts you want to use
Is up to you. You can customize as much as you'd like. That's it for the hard stuff
It's best to check the parts generator after every battle your opponent
Sorry your opponent's not gonna wait for you while you make a quick run to the parts generator
Obviously, you can't slip out during a battle. That's why it's best to check with the parts generator after every battle
Even if you forget to check after a battle, you can still get the part afterwards
However, if it's just waiting for you to pick it up, why not go get it as soon as possible?
The more parts the more you can customize your robo. It gives you I look I know how to I'd get it
That was last thing was important. It was just a hundred words of nonsense and then one important line
Also open the customize screen before a battle if you press the r button in that menu
You can practice with your new part cool. You want to get out of practice mode press start and then retire
Oh like that guy germa985 in about four years
Well, if you don't understand press start while you're walking around let's get back to the office. All right, let's go
Hey dale before we go. Why don't you ask these lab guys for some info? They're robo researchers
They'll probably have plenty of stuff they can teach you
Give me a holler when you want to leave you're done already
I don't want to hurry back. We get back too quickly and earnest will just give us more work to do chill out
What I told you I was ready to leave. Okay, here we go
I need to clean this place. There are parts all over and I've got no clue where to start
Custom robots are composed of five parts a body a gun a bomb a pod and a leg unit
Commanders have the freedom to customize any of these five parts in any way they want
The custom part comes from planning a robo design based on battle situation. Thanks
Those criminals nearly got away with ray01
Robos ray
They're in the hollow museum. Wow, go look in the museum one day go look in the museum. Isn't that cool?
I talked to all the people
Wait, so you're the one who's taking ray01 from us and you already did an eye scan whoever makes eye contact with a robo
First is its registered commander the only one it obeys
That's what eye scan registration is all about
Thanks for helping us. We're good at science, but not at fighting
By the way, did you know that people who are trained to pilot robots are called commanders?
You're not even doing any work. What's what's your pro? What's what? Tell me
Most commanders become better at fighting by mastering each of the robo's abilities
By fighting robots customize their programming and develop ability to operate on new parts
That's why robots don't come pre-installed with all the parts
Custom robo needs battle experience in order to alter its code and learn new parts
Parts generators read your robo's battle log and install any new parts in your robot. Excuse me for a minute
Install any parts your robo is able to use
That's why you should check the nearest parts generator. Yes, check it all the time
Yeah, you want to know about the lab? There's a government funded robo research and development lab. You've already met linda, right?
She's the director of our lab. She's the director cool
I feel like if all these guys just ran as fast as they could into each other
Fucking full sprint smushed and smashed into each other. They could just be one guy and he could read me all that
I mean, hey, you're gonna have two maybe but you're done already. I am done
Oh, you got a three-way gun
Did I miss somebody?
It's a secret go on without me
That's it back. No, don't take us off course. Don't take us off course, man
I'm gonna um
I'm gonna abbreviate everything that's said from the next few minutes
guys talented chief
I don't know what happened out there, but linda called i'm supposed to hire him
Hey, you got a cool robo
All right, you're hired
We don't pay very well. Oh man
You got the job go home. I'm going home. Thanks tired. Yeah, see you later. Good
Do net the netflix dub
Wake up, sweetie
You don't want this to be a complete and total voice acting stream where you just read dialogue and everyone just goes
Yes. Oh wake up and go to work already. What the fuck are his pajamas?
What was wrong with them?
Time for you to wake up. Don't you start work today? Good luck with that
I'll do my best
Now i'm a little confused about all of this. What does a bounty hunter do? Is that like a mercenary?
It's hard to explain basically we hunt down criminals with their crimes and robos
But isn't that what the police squad does?
We take requests that the police squad considers too small to bother with
Sounds almost like those private eyes from the stories. Are you like a detective or something?
Well, I guess all that really matters is you're a commander just like your father
so hard work
Uh-huh. Bye
Oh
Look at me. It's all the same voice
Yeah
Catching on they're catching on. What do I do?
Go check in with earnest. He doesn't act like it, but he is the boss around here
Oh, you're here. We don't have the manpower to spend long training you we need to get you up to speed quickly
Say earnest, where's uh marcia?
I mean the new guy gets here right on time and she's nowhere to be seen. What's up with that?
Marcia is on duty right now. She's not a slacker like you harry
Huh on duty this early
I called you this morning, but you didn't answer
Really? That's odd. He ought to know I never answered my cell phone before I knew well, that's why I said marcia
Let me go help her i'll go
Thanks for the offer, but there's no need marcia. It'll be fine on her own
Marcia is a skilled commander not quite as skilled as me, of course
I heard you blew it pretty bad yesterday. Got yourself hurt in process
That was dale's fault. He snuck up behind me and
Anyway, uh like I was saying before you have to be ready for action at a moment's notice
Harry, I want you to take dale to the gym
Have him do some warm-ups
A little training, huh? Gotcha. Let's go down and keep your cell phone on. Yeah. Yeah, I hear you
You have to go to the gym together
That wasn't mr. Satan. This is mr. Satan and that's how you do mr. Satan. That was not even close
I got more than four voices. Come on. I got at least eight. This is the training gym
Ernest got us a group membership here so we can train whenever we want. Okay, let's do a round you versus me
two max
This table here is called a holozam deck
It's a machine that projects all holos and some commanders like me can create their own holos and some can't just the way it is
Commanders who can't just use a holozam that's built. I thought that's bullshit
Commanders who can't just use a holozam. Oh, that's bullshit
But they use holozam decks like these to make one for them. Okay, before we start i've got some pointers for you
Probably notice this but you can change the direction the pod fires in. Mm-hmm. Yes
If you don't tilt the control stick, it'll automatically fire in the direction of your opponent. Yes. Got it. Yes
Okay
I know you messed with the mouth
But the eyes those are like my real eyes and it really does look like my eyes are made out of clay
Like that's somebody's art project
jeff the killer
This is his robo
All right, let's put on my new parts
Ray one
That's all we got right now basic
freeway
ours three rounds and three rows
Aerial and ground shots are the same
It's easier to hit your target when shooting from the far so try to stay away. Yeah, let's try it
for this guy
standard
twin flank
Always one pod left and one pod right deploys two pods at one time
Right standard is all we got. All right, anything else?
Oh, let's just check this out
You can change the color too
Get into that
Mash buttons, right?
Okay, good jump on you. Ooh, this one's nice
Odd right
Ooh
This is the mouse thing the guy had
Get him get him get him get him get him doing missile spam
I'm not doing missile spam
But this is a fan art stream
This is not a fan art stream
Shoots more missiles, but i'm not sure I like it more
All right. No, i'm no more length. You now have access to the standard bomb s. Oh, okay, cool
All right, open the game up for me. I want to start customizing fighting and leveling up
I'm gonna rest for a bit. Why don't you just go up against the computer?
No, I don't want to go because the computer
Is he putting me into the room with the bots?
Wait, I want to go to a parts generator. It's the only entire house that doesn't have a parts generator in it
Was saying
Where do you think you're going? I want to there we go. All right
standard bomb s
Oh cool
Somebody said you're on an emulator
Shut stop it
Once a robot stops moving it takes time for it to reach full movement speed again. Okay, cool
No, I own the game. I own the disk. I own everything. I own the wemos. I own the game cube controller
It's right there
I own it. I this is I own this game. I own it
I own it. I own the whole thing
Don't stop moving
Do you understand? Yeah
I am playing custom robo right now. I own the game cube. I own the disk. I own the game cube controller
That's I just I own it. That's all i'm telling you. I own this
Whatever. I'm fine
Stop it
Others, okay. What was it called? There's a red. It was a bomb right
standard s
basic functions fly straight forward
Launches one bomb at a time it mobilizes target launch as often as possible. So your opponent cannot hide behind walls. Cool. That's right
Why don't you prove it show your ankles ban that guy for at least three days
All right, here we go
All right, should I spam now?
Good. Oh what the spawn protection?
Shit i'm gonna lose to the plot
Around around around around
I don't like this standard b
I'm not a big fan of standard b
It's too spread out
Destroy him i'm trying
It's the normal one, but it's better
I don't like it. I don't like it
No, please
Good no, fuck that rebirth shit. No
Games good speed pod. Wait, so can I just farm pods?
That was the wall. That was the tutorial wall
Speed pug let's see what it is
You got a speed pug
Okay, what does it do though?
Hey, where do you think you're going? I told you to practice. I just did I just kicked his ass
I'm done training you
Oh, you become vulnerable after you fire a gun use a slide shot to cover this
You press the b button while moving you can fire your gun while sliding in that direction
You use this skill properly. You can shoot while moving behind a wall
a slide shot
All right, i'm gonna change some things here
Let's take the uh
speed pod right
speed d
Quickly fly straight ahead can deploy two pods at one time
tons of speed
No homing, right?
Standard s or yeah, we'll keep standard s
All right, let's try what's with game cube games and
Revoice tutorials
You know
You know, I got three seconds on them already. All right, let's make this happen play right
speed pod
Fast cpu
Fast vtuber versus what?
Damn it. This game's kind of challenging like in a fun way
Get him down. Get him down. Get him down. Get him down
Fuck you
Hey nintendo, what the fuck are you gonna remember the series? That's kids. What are you saying?
Somebody did a spam and I couldn't read it
I'm doing the slide shot. We're not doing it. Well
All right, right here
Hey nintendo, I can't read it
Hey nintendo, when the fuck are you going to remember the series or remember f0 for more than aesthetic callbacks?
When are you going to remember kid icarus nintendo? Stop fucking around bring back the underdog games
You now have access to the criminal
Okay, cool
What's the criminal?
You got a criminal. Wait, what?
Is that a new robot?
Allow me to explain the trick flyer model
My robo utilizes this body type the trick flyer has excellent aerial ability. However, it moves slowly on the ground
Doesn't jump far, but it can do a quick air dash up to three times
When using a trick flyer, you should approach your opponent with an air dash and then attack
Get it
Oh, this looks cool
All right customize ray one. I got criminal
agile while airborne
Extremely slow on the ground
I kind of want red
Red blue that's not blue. That's
Green yellow
Marine I like this one better internet speed d
D is fine
standard legs
I'm fine with this
All right. So this guy I can move very fast
Basic is just worse though. I know it is worse
Cbd what you want to do cbd
Holy shit, this thing's awesome. You can go so fast in the air. All right, don't don't waste it actually kind of hard to do
He's horrible on the ground
It takes a okay after you fire it takes a full like two seconds before you can do anything
Uh, I don't know this guy sucks. I don't like him
Characters terrible turn in the trash just snap him in half at the torso and just put it in the recycling bin
I don't care about the trick flyer. I'm gonna kill you with ray. Oh one not criminal. I want ray. Oh one
Yeah, he's better and he's green. I want blue ray one by the way
The speed thing no
Not a big fan. I like the the actual bullet bill travel ones
No
I'm using cover. I'm gonna use cover to my advantage now
shit
Losing already. I'm fine
Fuck i'm definitely a standard b guy. I'll tell you that
down to down to
I hate that rebirth stuff. There's no standard b. Yeah, it's standard b. All right
What do I want right now? I want something. What do I want? I had some food earlier
M&I bomb p
Not food. I want okay like another coffee or
What do I want?
water
M&I bomb p
This is the last one here
You should take caution to prevent your rubble from being knocked down
If you receive a powerful attack or repeated attacks in a short period your rubble will overload
It's knocked down and vulnerable to attacks for a short time
However, you'll be invincible for a short time if you get up while your robot systems reboot
If you tap the buttons quickly your robot will rise more rapidly
Fuck your stomach get a milkshake. I'm gonna get a milkshake right now
We're gonna make a milkshake
Go open and get a blender put ice cream in it put some milk in it put chocolate syrup
It's gonna take like 12. That's gonna take like 15 minutes
I don't want a milkshake
What's that new item?
M&I p
Launches a split bomb towards either side of your foe
Launch two bombs at a time lingers for a while the blast target blows target sideways. I'll try it
I just punched you i'm sorry
He's lactose intolerant. No, not really
just have
issues
How can he already have been able to go does it look like?
M&I p
Hard to tell i'm gonna wrap around this side and then dash him
It sucks
Oh, it's it spreads it out. I get it
Yeah, i'm not a big fan of it
What was that?
Oh, come on
This is homing
He's dead
Wow late again, huh? I I I don't even know what it said
Use the grenade launcher what is on the ground to linger
And you get hit multiple times you get the cockroach pod
Expertly done. All right. I did it. I see the tutorial is over
On the phone who could it be?
Hey, oh, where's harry that idiot turned his cell phone off again
Tell harry to call me back right now. Got it
Cockroach pod. Come on. What's your phone number?
You want my phone number?
I could fool around. How about a date?
Hey, what is dill? Ernest wants me to call him back
Oh, man, I was totally gonna get her number
Yeah harry here. What's up? I'm kind of busy right now
Well, why isn't jina went smash? I don't know. I wish I knew
Do you have to use language like that chief? Yeah. Yeah, I got you
Hey dill, we gotta work
See you sophie. Let's go on a date next time. Oh, you gotta go. What a shame. Good luck with work harry
Woo
This is where the number the number comes back
It's like harry. Um, uh, i'm thinking i'm gonna be busy forever
Yeah, just don't call
This is a don't call me, please. This is your weirdo
You better believe i'll be back
Okay, dill, let's go. I'm all pumped up
This is you button this person every time they call
On the first ring because you don't care
All right, we're going for hub park
a park
Yeah, you know the park with all the roads circling around it chief said something about a couple of young punks
Dooking it out with their robos
Yes, some girl called us up asked us to make them stop
Sounds messy. We should get moving
You're right. Come on. Let's go
All right, which one are you?
There they are wonderful what they're what they're fighting about. I wonder what the why do I care about this?
Why do I have to get involved?
Oh my god, no, uh, she's mine
She's my date
Okay
That were the land of the creeps. Okay
I'm the one who called you these silly boys are farting over me because i'm so cute
Well, I mean, I guess I did tell them to go out
I did tell them i'd go out with them on the same day and time
All right. This all right. This clearly is like a 45 year old dude that wrote this dialogue
But I didn't know which one to cancel so I thought I'd just come out and see what happened
And while I was waiting they saw each other and they started fighting over me. Well, what did you expect?
So anyway, i'm like freaking out here. I called the police but they said they didn't have enough men
I think you've got more than enough men already
I'm not worried at all that you're here
And so i'm gonna go home. Okay, i'll leave the rest up to someone now
You're gonna there's gonna be two more people fighting over you
You've just increased the amount of people that are fighting over you now. There's four of us here
There was two you've just increased the amount of humans here i'm gonna go home
Hey, she left but what about her dates?
They're so mad at one another that they haven't even noticed that she dumped him
Oh, well, let's face them one on one to try to chill them out a little
They'll pick a guy i'll handle the other. What are we fighting for?
What song is that
It's a mario song what the hell is it it's the water theme. Yeah, okay
Oh and I suppose you've got a date with her too
Okay, i'll straighten you out now. I'm gonna get kind of specific here on combat techniques
Here's another tutorial for you the longer you hold the a button the higher you'll jump tap the a button to do a short jump
You should try it out. Got it. Okay. Thank you
Just do whatever you can do to beat it. It's a t-shirt. All right, what do you got?
That
Nice, okay good. I put my thumb up good dude. Good fucking job wicked. Good job
This is gonna be easy
And then I put the fucking vr helmet on all right. Keep ray
Give an ip. I don't like it. I want standard
Standard only standard. I like I like the standard shit. What's the cockroach normally flies slowly
Quickly increases speed when it spots its target. I'll try a cockroach
That's boring to do standard everything. No, it's efficient. You're a basic bitch. Okay
All right, get in there. Oh they're little cockroaches. It's awesome
Get him
Oh, that is pretty nice
Come on. What's up with that?
Get him get him get him dash dash dash dash. He's so close. Get him
bash him
dash dance dash dance
I'm working on it
That was pretty good. It just didn't hit him
Sorry, uh, no no date for you
Oh, man, yeah, you mean
Losing in a fight against some dude does it you mean I can't date her now
What does she think about this?
Well, I do like you but you lost in the battle. So now you're my boyfriend
What the what?
Good grief, let's get out of here
Yeah, nope. Uh-oh
You'll pay for this
Thanks marcy. He saved me
Don't mention it
Oh, you must be dale our new partner, right? I'm marcia
That takes four or five cans of spray
Hairspray to get that to be like that probably more it's probably glue. Oh, um, well, I have class b license dale
Say dale, what's your license class?
If I tell you if it's if it's under b, are you not gonna date me?
License was that I mean you have to do that
License who was that?
What?
You don't have a license
He's an amateur. Of course. He ain't got no license
But if you're a bounty hunter and you don't have a license you can get arrested
That's right. I forgot
Harry, how could you forget something like that?
You know that that's why nobody's got any respect for the steel hearts for getting stuff like that. Give me a break
I just slipped my mind
Well, okay. I've got a problem. Let's head back to the office. Harry is low-key stupid
Uh, he's high-key stupid new party member unlocked a license. Oh, yeah that I guess that's not such a bad idea
But licenses cost money money we don't have yeah, but no matter how good you are if you don't have a license that will arrest you
Well, that's your own business. It's not my fault if you guys get taken by the cops
I could have sworn that the law places full responsibility on an employer of a robo commander
What are you serious?
All right, then
All right. I want you to take take him and get his license tomorrow
What me again?
Okay, he shouldn't have a problem getting a class d license a class d license that's burned in my brain sure
Sure. No problem
Hey, are you aware of what you're having to go to do with the test?
Anyway, uh, you take that class d license test tomorrow
If you don't pass that license linda's reward is out the window. That's right. I'm not gonna get anything
That's not to mention that it'll get you arrested
You're gonna go to jail. You're gonna go to jail for the rest of your life. Listen harry
You've got to absolutely got to make sure that he passes
It's impossible. What do you want a simple assistant like me to do?
Stop complaining. It's not for rick
Stop complaining. Uh, I don't want you to come back until uh jail passes what?
You don't want me to die
Oh the test right
Which reminds me you're class d too. Why don't you take the class c while you're there? Wait, he's class d
No way, who do you think you're kidding?
jay jameson
I want those photos. I want those photos of spider-man and I want them tomorrow
You understand me peter get those photos of spider-man or your job is toast
I got out of my office
As long as i'm in this business a class d license is plenty
Hey, isn't it about time you took the class a test? How many times have you tried?
I'm so scared of something
This isn't good. Hmm
Everyone's worked hard today. You can all go home
A little lazy fuck you can even get up and walk
He left
You should go home, too
Let's come straight to the test hall. The place is called the custom robo departmental licensing
Neil don't let anyone make fun of you for being a steel heart
Yeah, I won't by the way
Do you have any tips on that test i'm taking?
This is john stewan john wick the whole time. I'm realizing this is just keanu reeves
Right. Okay
Any tips on how to pass the test tomorrow? Yeah, that's what i'm doing. I've been saying that
I didn't see what you're doing
That's not even close
He uses reddit. Okay. Yes, I guess I do. I guess I use reddit. She doesn't beat around the bush does she
Yeah, make sure you come straight to the testing hall
Okay, we're done for today. What are you doing after this?
Uh miku, what are you doing?
I'm tired. So i'm going home
See you tomorrow
Yeah, don't be late. He said it
I mean it was the best obvious reference to make
This is my voice acting audition stream
Oh, you have that lying test today
You better get up if you don't want to be late. I was lying. It tastes good
No, really
Keep babbling about wake up wake up wake up wake up. Wake up jeremy wake up chucky cheese is here
What the hell am I talking about? I forgot that even happened what a wild day. You got a reflection pod
You got a long thrust leg
What I want something I want something do I want should I okay?
Ones in the chat if I should get a coffee who's in the chat if I should eat a cvd edible two two two two
Both no, I don't do both. Fuck that good morning. Good luck with the test
Yeah, thanks
What a fucked up broom
What do you have to lie about?
No, it's not a lying test. It's a license test
How many times do I have to tell you that?
I don't get all this robo mumbo jumbo
Order to work as a bounty hunter. You need a class d license
I'm gonna take that test
It's all crazy talk to me, but it sounds like you don't pass this test you don't keep your job
Yeah, that's right
Oh, that's terrible hurry and get going
Yeah, um, where was it again?
I think it was some place called the department of licensing test hall
Oh, well, it's pretty easy to get there. Just go to the right when you leave
Are you sweeping the lawn?
Uh grandma, I think needs to go sit down in a chair. That's weird
No, I don't want to drink coffee. No, that's that's bad. All right test hall. All right. I gotta I gotta
Oh my fucking god. So your name's trish. That's a cute name
Oh, come on. How about it? Tell me your phone number if something were to you know happen to you
I could rescue you. I even give you a discount a discount. Is that supposed to impress me?
Still you've got kind of a naive charm
See, I am charming here write it down here
Oh, sorry. I didn't know you were there dale
Just getting every single woman's phone number in the entire world
Everyone I talk to wants to give me their phone number. What did what did you do today?
I've got you registered leave the rest to me. Take your test
Stand in front of the exam machine and insert. I thought it was gonna be insert your eyes
To put it simply press the a button. Yeah, here's your exam card. Don't lose it by the way
Um, could you write your number on it? So where were we? Oh, yeah, write your number down there
Oh this guy
In order to take the test insert your exam card and robo cube into the test machine
To begin the process simply stand in front of the test machine press a
Thanks kid
Will you start the test?
I'm ready
Welcome your test begins immediately. This is a test for a class d license. The first test is knowledge
Wait, it's an actual test. Please select the right answer. What's the name of a person who controls a custom robo?
a commander
What is it called when a person in his robo become one?
Um
Synthesization a drive a drive a dive
Alive a dive. What does it call when your robo is in its easy to carry form robo, dude robo tube
robo cube the robo cube
What is the custom robo research center also known as?
laboratory
Laboratory or the laboratory the laboratory
There's a bunch of dogs in there which license class do you need in order to join the police squad?
uh-oh
see
Uh-oh, what is the name of the arena where custom robo's fight a holoseum the name of the machine that transfers custom robo data
Parts generator the parts burdenator the parts generator so the following is an actual custom robo part
odd pork or butt
odd the proper name of this testing hall is called the custom robo
Department of licensing compartment department of licensing department of fish and game
What question number are we on now? Okay?
That's not fair. Yeah, that's not fair. I i'm gonna i'm gonna say person
camera
Man person tv. It's eight ten end of questions knowledge test complete. Please wait for your results
Oh, I failed what was wrong with my computer?
All right, somebody put that into wingdings and see if there's a bunch of swears in there
Thank you for waiting your score has been calculated
90 it's an a minus
You passed. Yeah
The next test is skill. You will have to fight a custom robo under my control before that. I will give you some advice
Never just run into an open area without a reason
Okay
It's good 2.6 gpa. Yes, I did. I had a 2.6 gpa. What's wrong with that?
The computer just say take it easy on me. No. Yeah, 2.6 gpa. That's fine. All right. I want to keep the freeway
Keep standard. I actually like the cockroach. Wait, we got some new stuff
Reflection doesn't chase your opponent but travels around for a long period of time
Hmm. Try it. We got boots long thrust
Increases your dash distance features no descent augmentation
That's right
2.6 gpa won't get you into community college. It did
14 years ago
So I didn't just guys I didn't just go to college yesterday. I didn't just get out of school
I've been graduated from college for like 15 years
It's been a very long time 2.6 is
That's not the gpa that I had to get in to college. It's gpa. I had in college
And look, we all get the same damn diploma. Okay
Good start good start
unbelievable start
and oh
Average grades
Yeah, guess what? I still I still got the diploma every one thing. It was like, oh wow 2.6 gpa
Oh, no, you didn't make the dean's list
No, okay. And who cares?
I don't like greet people
That i'm just meeting for the first time like 15 years later going. Oh, yeah, jeremy elbertson. Nice to meet you. Ah dean's list
I don't fucking care
You would if you were on it omega low
No, all right
I'm gonna be real with you here. I remember getting the dean's list
It was like oh here by the way here are the people on the dean's list and it was just like fucking it was just
Like a thousand names
Sorry, I didn't get put on that list
It was like it was like the credits in a movie
Nobody that gets that paper in the mail
Scrolls down and goes who who is this? Who is it? Who are you? Ooh, jeremy elbertson
He made it. He made it. I know him
No
You show it to your parents your parents go excellent work
And then you forget it existed ever again
And then your parents forget it existed
Like a month later like six months later. It's like oh, you're just like you're just you're just a person now
He's mad. I'm not gonna get my intelligence
just
Killed here. I just got a class d license. He's getting clapped
What?
Cool, so i'll give you a call tonight
Yeah, you do. Did you pass?
4.6 doesn't even matter
See you later trish
What you should be caring about is not about how high your gpa is
But what you are retaining from the shit that you want to learn
That's the that's way more important than having like a 4.0 gpa
How much are you taking how much are you retaining? How many skills are you developing develop some skills develop some brain power?
Oh, I didn't get I got a d on this who fucking cares. You got a d on that test who gives a shit
What did you learn?
When when my son or daughter goes to college and they come back and they're like dad
I got like a 2.1 2.2. Let me see that i'll let me see
Okay. All right. What did you learn though?
Show me what you've learned
And then they'll pull out like a piano and like start playing a fucking beautiful song and i'll be like there you go
That's what you've learned. Whatever you're doing. I don't care. Whatever it is. Good work
What are you retaining not what are you remembering? That's way more important
think about that
Tests a test. What are you retaining versus? What are you remembering?
Short term to get a passing grade
Keep that in mind. It's very very important. It's too bad employers. Don't think like that. Some of them do some of them do
omega q
Okay. All right. Do you want to talk about like productivity and like what makes a good employment environment?
Which this should be a four-day work week
You know how much more shit people get done not spending five six days a week
You get way more shit done
But you get a 15 minute break every eight hours here at the job
Oh, you you bet you're stressing out. You've got too much stuff to do. You're not being able to take breaks
Your your mind can't function that way
We need a four goddamn work week. I'm not talking less work, by the way. I'm not talking everybody should do
Don't do less
You get way more done when you have less time. It's weird, but it's true
When you're working for less time, you have more time to spread out your brain and be able to actually
Develop your brain off work. It's trust me. It's scientific. Look it up not 14 hours a day
No, same time less days unionize your workplace. Thanks for this five subs
We're not talking about any we're not talking. I'm just talking about productivity. All right
And why do you have the mods work a hundred plus hours a week? Shut up
Hey, um, i'm kidding
um
You should no dude you got that's i'll we'll talk about that later. Good job
I've got some business to take care of. I want to leave right now
If you two are going to be partners, you ought to spend some quality time together
Chat on the way home and get to know each other partners. Why can't marcia be his partner?
The marcia can't handle herself
And you're the one who told me to hire dale in the first place
Why does everything bad always happen to me?
I think he's drinking his own tears
He is ugly crying
Okay, uh
I gotta be honest. I was not hey, I was not retaining any of that information
I was just saying it or remembering it short term. What happened there? I don't know. Where am I going?
I didn't retain any of that
Not even short term
I didn't fail the test
You would take you were talking during it. It's talking during the test. Where would we need to go training gym?
It's a square root of what's a square root of what's the square root of 16?
um
I don't know
I don't care
Wait, where were we actually going?
I was not paying a single attention at all. Is it the training grounds?
It's about go to marcia, right?
Go home
All right, spend quality time with this person. All right, let's let's go bowling or something
Don't tell him. I mean don't tell him tell me
Hmm your dad, huh? And that's why you want to work
Well, everyone's got a reason
Anyway, as of today, you're a full-fledged bounty hunter. Do your best. See ya
Okay, gotta get back home and call trish
Is that trish's number?
Is that the comic relief there that that's the number that he dropped? I guess yeah
Dale get up
Hurry up and go to work
The person only has two outfits
That's sort of strange
feather legs
Which I can fly
What do you call this?
I don't know
They're being awfully loud this morning
Do I care?
I know you're curious, but it's not right to go poking around in other people's business. I'll do it later
uh
Okay
Good morning
Now you just got here dale, but I need you to go back to your apartment
Huh?
There's a married couple fighting over at your apartment building and they're using robos
They got a call from the landlady. She said it's out of her control
She requested you specifically
Oh, I thought so. Hey harry go with them
And i'm fine. It sounds like a crummy job
Dale can handle it myself
I'm totally bummed today. I had my chance yesterday and I blew it
Stop complaining and go
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I'll go
Oh tritch
Oh, where did I put that note with your number on it?
Harry
All right, dude, come on. Hi. Thanks for coming back. Dale
When did you call earnest?
Right after you left. It's so awful
Oh, who's this?
Hmm. Oh, that's harry
Oh, really? Is he a stolen horse too?
Oh
That's what our hands are doing. He's quite a hunk of a man. Get me his number. Will you?
It's sweet of you
We talk about the job here of what's going on. Oh, right, right. Walt and his wife are fighting and it's getting crazy
They're using their robos to fight and their children are crying. I tried to stop them, but
I don't know a thing about robos. You know that I didn't have a clue how to stop them and that's why I
I called stolen horse
I also wanted to see what you like when you had work
Thanks
Dale, let's cut the chat and go stop them. Yeah, you're right. Good luck turning into roger
Man, this is bad. Let's wrap this up quickly
I'll stop the husband
You go handle his wife. They're all it's turning. Yeah, it's either roger or neelix. It turns back and forth somehow
I've turned the safety switch on so that nobody gets hurt
What's a safety switch?
It's a switch that describes decreases your robo's power to prevent you from hurting your opponent
The switch is on the robo cube. If you turn the safety switch on and dive the safety mechanics will automatically kick in
It won't look any different
Okay
Can we get should we do an investigation?
Man, let's get along
Yeah, stop fighting
Holy shit
What you're taking his side
Don't mess with me
Be your opponent my metal ape. It's a metal grappler
little grappler
Got a little excited there. The metal grappler has extremely high defense
It's hard for it to get knocked down. But since it moves slow, I have a hard time dodging it down
I can only do one air dash
Oh
I'm gonna lean in real close. I usually focus on attacking rather than worrying about a little damage
Got it
Huh?
Why am I explaining all of this to you?
Yeah, why are you telling me this?
Got a cool sword
All right. So just hide I like this. I currently like this
Battle
Yeah, I wasn't a big fan of that line by the way
Hey, you require my assistance. Let's see. I could do a better job than that. You require my assistance
your battle
That's better. That's what he sounded like in warcraft 3
I would have done just replace it
What an ego maniac
Don't say that don't say that or you're gonna get fucking banned
All right. This the dash is way better
Send out the mice. We just have to dodge. This is an ape type, right?
Knock them down
Good volley
Thermal punching. Fuck you
You don't don't use me against me. Okay
Don't forget. That's me punching
I'm gonna punch myself
Careful with that emo
There's lava in this thing
Stop hitting yourself. Stop hitting yourself
That was clean. Thermal slaps himself. Why are you doing that? Nobody has raided
We don't have a raid
Why are you embarrassing me in front of a raid that doesn't exist?
vertical gun
Ow, ow, right that burns me up
That was a waste of time. Let's head back to the office
Oh, oh, oh
Are you hurt dear who hurt you?
That crudely dressed punk over there
What are you talking about? You're hurt because you've gotten a stupid fight with your wife
I only calmed you down
How dare you hurt my hubby?
Get up, dear. We'll defeat these evil villains and show them that our love is strong
That's right. I love you
I love you, too
What does this happen to happen to me? I'm just some guy
Hey, Dale, come here. We're gonna beat him up
You never had a two-on-two battle before have you it's when two people team up on two others
What are you doing?
Sorry, just wait one minute. I have to explain to the new guy
Hey, Dale, listen carefully. I'll explain two-on-two battles
At least they're aware, right?
Basic controls are the same as the one-on-one battles, but there's one difference
The arrow on top of your robo's head locks onto one of your opponents
You want to change your target? You have to press Y
Okay, good thing I didn't skip that
You're red and i'm blue and our opponents are green and yellow
Every time you press Y the colored arrow above the changes and it goes that way. Okay
I told you i'm blue. What good does it do to shoot your own partner?
You can't fire your gun while you're changing targets
Are you done yet?
Sorry, there's just a little bit more one more second
Your opponents have colored arrows over their heads, too
Those arrows turn red. That means that they're locked on to you
Got it got it got it. Now listen
Look carefully at the colored arrows and see who's locked on to who?
Keep that in mind while you fight
All right nightbot just said i've been live for two hours and 11 minutes
I thought someone was chatting saying germa. It's been two hours and 11 minutes resident sleeper
Actually, this is I like this. I'm gonna stay with what I got. I like it. Oh by the way tomorrow
Tomorrow is part two of dlc movie night
And watch the rest of the playlist
I'm already up
Wait, is that my friend?
No, that's not this is a little confusing. All right, i'm gonna i'm with this guy this guy down here
How are you doing over there?
No, no, keep attacking him attack him
Yes
Take out the big guy first focus the big guy
What are you dumb?
All right, that's it
Don't even let him get up
I'll just rain missiles. You just do all the work
Good job. When does this guy take off his pants?
You're talking about me. Um, that doesn't happen on stream
Oh, I got access to the metal ape
spider pod
Do oh, do you two have to be so cute? Give me a break
We've got our safety switches on and they're going at it for real. This ain't a joke
Are you two okay?
What are you doing here marcia?
The chief was worried about you. He said
Where's this going? I'm not sure where this is going. It's going somewhere
I don't know where it was. I guess we're just gonna do this
The chief was worried about you. He said you weren't your normal self today. Hey great. Well, you've got perfect timing. It's all over
I see
But how do things turn so ugly so quickly?
That's what I like to know man. What a mess
He was washing my husband's clothes this morning and I found a note in his coat pocket
There was a phone number on it. I didn't know what it was. I called it and a young lady answered
I was certain that my husband was cheating on me
But honey, I told you I just found that note out front this morning
I believe you you never do anything like that. I'm sorry. I lost my temper. I'm sure it was only a prank
Really? Who would have planted that thing out where you'd find it like that?
Prank or no prank. I I hope you're sorry. We're bruised up because of your stupid fight
Harry, please stop. There are children here and you're scaring them
I'll get them. I'm the murloc. What's from the
The game heart has done
What's his name? Sir Finley, right? Sir Finley
I've played look every stream is the every stream is the last thing that I did
Okay
The last thing that I did you guys are gonna hear about it all day every time. What do you want me to do?
It's just up there and I can't get it out
And I don't like it. I think the game's stupid now, but like I played it and that's all that's up there. I can't help it
This is how memories work
Fucking boomer loser
All right
You get some leeway but all right, that's time up for 10 minutes i'm out for 10 minutes
Who's ready for some adventure?
see
CBD CBD
I'm going to get a water relax a glass of water and I got some coffee just a little bit more
Weed infused coffee that would be I'm not a fan of that kind of stuff
I don't like just i'm just gonna just give it to me just someone want to eat it
I don't want like weed infused fucking like salmon fillets. No, I don't want that
I don't want like a weed infused coke product. No, just I just just give it to me. I'll eat it
If you're into that stuff, cool. They're cool. That's i'm glad you are
I just want to eat it
Weed and cocaine mixed together
No, don't do that. That's a terrible idea
Don't do that. We found this in front of our front doorstep
Don't we stop blinking me though like mustache hair guy. I saw it
It was written by a girl. She has cute handwriting
Cute, let me see
Whoa
I'll take this as evidence. Give me that
Modded 3d movie maker characters got it figured it out. It's taking me a while. That's what this is
It's nothing. I can't let a helpless girl carry around a heavy load, you know
It's just a piece of paper. It's great. Everything worked out. Don't they look good together and they lived happily ever after
Harry are you all right?
Uh, what do you mean?
Just a second ago you were furious, but now furious. Oh me. I've made a love. Hey deal. You need to lighten up
Married couples have their reasons for things. You gotta give them some slack
Got it
Okay kids
Are you scared your parents are fine now? Everything's all right
Listen to me when i'm talking what i'm talking we're talking to the children now harry
Stop
Come on. Let's go play over there
Marcia
So you both want to be commanders when you grow up? How about a custom robo game?
Sheesh, what's wrong surprised to see marcia being nice to the kids
Um, I don't I don't care. I don't care at all. Like that's cool. Nice. Why would you not be nice to kids?
I don't care
Come on. Hear me out. She's actually a nice person. I okay
You see
Time to lure dump on you marcia's parents passed away a few years ago
It was just her and her big brother her big brother was an elite member of the police squad marcia got along
Well with her brother real well her brother took good care of her
But one day marcia's brother up and quit the police squad without a word and then he just disappeared. No one's seen him since
okay
um then
Okay, not only did marcia lose her parents, but she also lost an older brother. That's
I don't know this like this is the appropriate place to do this
Like in this house here
And now she's alone. Yeah, that sort of sums it up
I've said this is like a situation where you we leave and you pull me aside
And say hey, just want to let you know a couple things
He's doing he's like just monologuing in this person's living room
I feel the same way for a long time marcia has been gifted with a strange power. Uh, oh
Uh-oh
That girl's got a strange power. She's like a god. She has god powers and and she I got it. I got it
Because of that she's always been the quiet type. She used to be a lot happier
And now she's lost her parents and her big brother shut up from the world and unable to reach out to anyone
She's gotten a lot better though
The reason marcia wants a class a license is because she wants to join the police squad
Can't join the police squad unless you get a class a license. How was I supposed to know that I failed that on the test
She probably wants to track down some clues on her brother herself
Hey, laugh, how do I uncook luigi? I accidentally dropped him in the deep fryer
Uh, well, you're gonna be in big trouble because that's half of uh nintendo's like entire
fan base
and library
You're gonna have to come up with a solution for that
What am I saying that somebody said somebody said that
I didn't say that
Will you guys think that i'm saying this?
Oh shit, I did say it like I just said it
Yes, they did say that I will find it right now before I get still lost in the chat
I'm just like insane and i'm sitting here going okay. How do I uncook luigi guys? I dropped him in the fryer
I I gotta find it somebody fucking really said that and it was fucked
Like yeah, it's gone. Okay, let's head back to the office awesome. I got trish's number back
Yeah, so germa owns the game and he'd rather emulate it. Am I wrong?
Um mike listen sometimes some games have problems being captured
They become uncapturable happens with a lot of them actually
Try to pull it through a capture device and the audio might be all messed up
It could be a huge problem. The disc could be scratched
Doesn't mean you don't own it. I know not all of them. Excuse me
Excuse me, not all of them only like three ever
Hold on. It's on the phone
Hello chief. Yes, harry and dale took care of it
Hurry up and hover a bogey's cafe marv's there more characters
Show disc I I don't have to do that because I know it had
God, I know this is a gaslight bullshit. I'm not doing it
If we catch that marv, we should get a big reward
The police squad gets there before you the rewards gone. Hurry up
You need to show us the disc you need to show us the disc. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, let me show you
Hold on folks. Hey, here we go
Dick reveal incoming disc reveal disc reveal stop
Have to show this I don't have to do anything
What I I looks like i'm going to right? How does my headphones get tangled prepare to screenshot? Why does what does this matter?
Uh, where's the camera?
My camera is broken remember from yesterday. Hold on. What the fuck? Why is it so tiny?
You guys see me
Why is this so small?
All right. All right. All right. I got it. I got it. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good
I know everyone's gonna freak out. I'm wearing the same shirt that I was wearing yesterday
I don't care
I'm wearing the same clothes as yesterday. What the fuck do I care? Why am I like a ghost?
Why am I a ghost?
Okay, here we go. You ready?
What do we have here? What do we have here?
What is this?
Hmm
This looks like a gamecube disc of custom robo, doesn't it? By the way, here's the controller
Here's the controller is the gamecube controller by the way
I don't want you to see this
What's this fucking thing?
What is uh, what is
What is this?
Is this a is this a wii?
Looks like it
It's a router
I have that that's the netgear 2000 man
Not plugged in not plugged in
Not plugged in I have the disc. I have to prove that to people apparently
I'm, sorry everybody that was waiting
To play the game. I'm sorry
yell at them
Flexing on your viewers but proving that I own the game the console and the controller
Okay, here we go. The chief wants us to go to bogies
That guy is the reward
All right. I'm gonna do us all a favor
Uh
I like my cup
No skipping miku. No
How do I unpoop my pants?
Waddle over to the toilet
Take your underwear off and just take the underwear and turn it upside down and dump it into the toilet and then just
Throw the underwear in the trash done
His name is evil
Harry and marcia. No, I get a bit of harry and marcy. What's going on? Oh great. Not him
Harry harry harry still have the manners of a kindergarten. Eh
I assume you're here for the notorious outlaw marv
I'm sorry, but you're too late dark blue. Oh more specifically. I
Evil have already captured the rogue
Darn it
Dark blue got the reward
How did you know that marv was here?
So you want to learn my secrets you hope to benefit from my wisdom perhaps. Okay, i'll tell you
One of something weird about voices and acting and just hearing people talk very loudly
I'm gonna ruin every single thing for you ever
You are now going to hear
all the huge intakes
of air
When people do voice acting now, it's all you're gonna hear
Even when you watch the news, you're not gonna hear the breath
When newscasters talk especially anchors or reporters
Just listen
So we are here live on the scene and i'm here
You'll hear it
It turns out the car drove past all these
Yeah, that's just how it happens now
That's all you'll hear
Don't listen don't listen
That's not how normal people breathe. Just listen next time i'm gonna drive somebody insane
Because he's gonna people are gonna be like no, no, he's right. It's the only thing I could hear
Bogey here officially requested the services of my little mercenary crew dark now i'm freaking out because you're gonna hear it
What bogey why?
But you told us you always go to steel hearts when you've got trouble
Well, your boss has been here all day sucking down coffee and
And what and he was sitting in a dark corner all by himself?
Writing poetry and occasionally weeping
How can I rely on you guys when your boss is such a space cadet poetry i'd be worried too
Young earnest is a poet and you didn't know it. Oh, this is too shit. It's all I hear
I did it myself
Hmm. Well now aren't you the kid who came in looking for a job with dark blue not too long ago?
Of course, that's right. Your name's dale
You apply to dark blue too
Yeah
I applied to lots of places
I applied a lot. This is not me making a joke. This is real life now
Don't act coy evil knows your name. You must have applied at dark blue
So you couldn't get into dark blue and we're next on your list fine with me
Oh, what is with you ceaseless blathering harry. Are you saying you know dale too?
Wait
Don't tell me
Did steel hearts hire this amateur?
That is rich
Shut your face
Dale has tons of talent and someday he'll be an excellent commander
At least that's what linda says
I have to stop paying him. All right, i'm gonna I need 30 30 seconds to recalibrate and just forget about the thing that I just
Told you guys
It's it's it's fucking up my brain
I've got an idea somebody somebody somebody sounds like a skipping cd
Oh, he sounds like a skipping like what did you say breathe and blink manually stop it
Why did I do this to myself? I casted a spell back at myself accidentally
And all of you in chat are going to have one arm now
And it bounced back in a mirror. Oh shit
I have now I have one arm now
reversed
Yeah, i've got a few verses for you right here
Oh very witty harry. Have you ever considered a change of career? Perhaps as a clown?
Enough chit chat. We're leaving now
Dale if you do turn out to be a worthy commander we'll make you an offer
Don't make a hearthstone reference. Don't do it. I'm gonna do it. Don't make the hearthstone say it. Dr. Boom fuck
Harry let's go back to the office. We need to report this to the chief
Yeah, you're right
The last thing I did is the only thing i've done
You minus two suck minus two. You can't do two. Come on. Come on
All right, we get to report back to our stupid chief. We didn't even I didn't get to play the game
That was just a ton of exposition
steel hearts
What
So let me get this straight
Not only do you
Not catch marv, but you let dark blue nab the ransom
You know, that's why everyone keeps making fun of us if we'd caught marv. We'd have gotten a huge reward
So one of the world took you some her knee good palms lately
Hey, what?
bogey called in dark blue
Bogey said he didn't want to hire someone who'd rather write poems than catch felons
What?
Well
These things happen good work everyone. Let's call it quits for today dismissed
We go to business now
He got away again
Let's go home. Gotta call trish gotta call trish
Dale, what are you doing after this?
See you tomorrow
the future gamer chair
Ring
Who could be calling me this early in the morning? Hey, yeah, which me harry you awake
Uh harry. Yeah morning. I'm up. What's going on?
Showtime partner seems like there's a robo fight at the diamond chinese restaurant earnest wants us there as soon as possible
There you mean at the office?
No, he wants us to go straight to diamond
That thing at bogey's yesterday has been bugging him. So he said he'd meet up with us there
Okay, got it diamond, right?
Coolio see you there. All right, so every resident sleeper. I see you one cent goes into the resident sleeper bank
You know, that's you get that you know that right? Holy shit
vertical gun
spider pod
Anchor up him. No, no, i'm talking about you guys
I'm talking about you
Not me. Yeah, you're scared me. What happened? You woke up on your own
No, no, no harry called me. I've got work to do. Oh, and i'm so proud of you having woken up yourself at once
Oh, yeah, right
Look, I have to go. I have to get to the diamond chinese restaurant. Oh damn it. That place is the best
The owner's a great chef. His name is dandodon. Tell him he said it
You can make anything ramen gyoza fried rice sour pork egg mani's pizza. Oh, it sounds delicious. I'm making my song
So where's him?
You don't know just go north in the lilies
Sorry, I had times to that on the youtube video diamond. It's time for a fight. What happened here body on the ground
Okay, this has happened. It's terrible
Hey dale, you're here. We were too late seems poor guy. He was dead before we came here
Looks like mental shock must have killed him
You could take real physical damage in a robo battle. If you die in the game, you die in real life
It takes a tremendous amount of stress to actually kill someone. I go to all the trouble of coming here in person
And this is what I get
How many layers down was he in the dream?
Right. No, i'm kidding. It was a joke. It was a joke. It was made. It was just deliberate farming
If it's a deliberate farm, it's not a minus two
It's an equals two
Equals two if it's a deliberate farm, don't you get that?
Cops are too busy to solve a murder. Apparently it was already too late when we arrived
We're late things have gotten pretty bad here
We have his cube
Harry, what are you doing here? We got a call, but it came too late. Whatever happened. It was over before we got here
bounty hunters, ah
We got it from here. So why don't you all beat it?
Hey, what we've got a job to do and you bounty hunters aren't a part of it. Oh, it's that show
Sure, you show up for these cases, but for the small ones you don't even bother. That's easy for you to say
You bounty hunters are free to pick your missions, but we police have far more responsibility
Where's the law then when's there? Where is it that regulates average folks needed? Huh?
Can't be bothered. Is that it?
You're not looking after the people who need you. Why do I even waste my time on a waster like you?
You're nothing like your sister
you
Leave it harry. It's out of our hands now
Harry, let's go. Come on dale
Wait, you got a minute
Roy according to the witness the victim was fighting some sort of
Autonomous robo
What did you say?
And when it killed the victim it fled the scene
Sounds like trouble
You really don't have a clue what's going on. Don't you an autonomous robo moves itself without having any commander dive into it
It was designed for manual and repetitive labor. I've never heard of that one fights
Oh
Which is why I have to ask you for a favor marcia
I need your help
What me?
You know what i'm going to ask you
I need to do a hack dive and read the victim's last thoughts
Skip the dialogue. Okay
You call that asking respected fellow law enforcement for help say like you mean it
What do you mean? No
Thank god. No, fuck you. What it was one guy more than one
What?
Shut it harry
I see your business is business
If you think you can take it and give the cops a hand
I don't know earnest
I haven't done a half dive in so long. I'm not even sure I still can
I'm not sure i'm following this but I don't think marcia can help out here
We need her to help though. There's no one else who can we can turn to
I see we understand if you can't do it if you fail, please help us for a bad audition
This is we're a tv show that I want to be on
Imagine coming in
Through an audition and you have an audition for one character
And you step in you can have these big sunglasses on you like no, no, no, no, no
No, you don't have to read from me. You don't have to get anybody to read i'm gonna do all of them
You do this
You is this impressive to an audition or is this like uh, this guy's kind of fucking weird
I don't know if I want this guy in here. All right. Let me concentrate
What's a half dive?
Uh, I know they just told me what a half dive is when they go in and they can pull the data out
What are they gonna do?
Just watch it's marcia's special power
Lord, I told you a while back marcia's had this special power since she was young
Marcia can dive into a robo that's already been registered by eye contact
Doesn't mean she can control a pre-registered robo though
However, she's able to read the commander's remaining cognition
So whatever the commander saw through his robo's eyes she sees
You can even read that guy's last thoughts gruesome. I'm an unboxing youtuber. No
No, all right, she's gonna half dive
Marcia, what's wrong? What happened?
Hey, i'll calm down. I'll explain later
How'd it go? What did you find?
It just cuts to like he's at the drive-through
It's weird boring shit
He's ordering like a number two or something and then he just comes in here and lies on the ground and dies
He wasn't fighting a custom robo
What do you mean?
Didn't look like a robo. I've never seen anything like it. It was like a living thing
That's ridiculous no living thing can enter the hall as am
You're right. It's just not possible
Everything about it is different. It doesn't move like a robot doesn't even look like one
You see what it was?
Only vaguely. It's just i've heard enough. There's no way that could happen
Shut up broy
Marcia what just what?
I've never felt such
overwhelming power
Come with us to hq. We'll want to make a composite sketch of the robo you saw
Hey, whoa there look at her marcy is in bad shape the stress of the half-dive is getting to her
I see what she has to go through every time she does this
We're sorry about that. But as a citizen she must comply with any and all police squad orders
unlimited power
Why we're asking for the cooperation not their resentment be civil
Forgive me
As if look at you barking like a dog
Still taking orders from my own sister loser
Harry you're out of line
Thank you for your hard work marcia
You must understand that this is extremely important and we desperately need your help
I know you're feeling a little weak, but we won't ask you to do anything strenuous. I promise
Please come with us to hq and tell us more about your power
Please hq marcia. Are you all right? You can rest up if you're not feeling up to it. Yeah
Just don't over exert. We'll be all right. We got you back. Bye
Hey harry, let's go
This is a visual novel people happy
Marcia
It kind of is yeah, but okay, it's a visual novel with really fun shit sprinkled sometimes in the game
It still has my attention. It's taking marcia so long. I wonder if she's okay
Marcia will be fine. She's got a strong will she's not like you
It's not nice marcia was so willing to help those cops. I mean she hardly argued at all
Hey harry, what's so special about a half-time? Why can't anyone else do it?
I don't know. It's a rare talent. I've never met anyone who could do it
Really, but there might be others. I've never even heard about a half-dive before now
Well, according to my sister marcia is the only commander. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you can do a half-dive. Whoa, that's insane
Well, she's something all right, but it doesn't sound all that great. Her power makes her extremely sensitive emotionally speaking. I mean
Oh, so for example, you ever have times when there's something on your mind
Would you get worried?
well in marcia's case
Take those worries and multiply them by a hundred
She gets so stressed out. She just freezes
That's pretty sensitive
Uh, yeah, she's been like that since she was a child. Okay
That's why she seems so distant. She needs the distance to keep from getting hurt by people
See it's like this
I see his big brother always used to protect her
It's rough being that sensitive and losing both your parents and your brother
Yeah, she really sort of hit rock bottom. It took a lot of work for marcia to get to where she is now
Uh, hey, that's enough out of you
I even catch you guys treating her differently because of this. I'll whoop you both good. It's the phone. Maybe it's marcia
How sensitive is she?
I don't know
Barry I got I think she's pretty sensitive
Jill hearts your squeal you squeal will deal is his artist. Uh bogey. Sorry about yesterday
Yeah, I knew he was a wanted man. I forgot my robo. That's why I couldn't catch him on the spot
What oh I get it you gave dark blue the job yesterday. So now you're handing one down to us today
Thank you
You're absolutely right. I'm a very loyal customer. Your cafe has great atmosphere
Oh, you're starting a poetry slam night
What makes you think that I write poetry?
You saw that
Well outside the boy's over right now. All right, we've got work get over to bogeys pronto
Tutorial this is not this tutorial. It's been three hours
Seems like there's some guy making a killing on battle wagers
Oh, he said the guy's incredibly strong and he's gonna put bogey out of business if this keeps up
Oh, you're not coming earnest. I don't think so. I feel like a bad luck right now
I got some light filing to do. Yeah, sure. Hurry up
Oh go go go go go go go go bogeys cafe. Here it is time for a fight
Thanks for the call at your service
Well, hello
I've been waiting for you harry and you too dale. Oh great. Not you. Here you go. Let's fight
I'll give you the tldr
bad guy versus good guy
Trying to teach why is his hands up?
We would have resolved the situation right away, but bogey insisted that we gave you still hearts fellow a fair shot
In fair spare of course, we're waiting till you screw up. There's fair bogey called us. Not you. This is our job
Oh, please harry. Are you even listening? We're mercenaries. The job goes to the fastest team
We're a generous group we dark blue mercenaries. We'll fight. How about two on two?
Nope, did you hear all those breaths?
I want to see the new things we got
Vertical this is so cool. There's 13 pages of guns
But unfortunately, there's 13 pages of dialogue as well between every single scene. I want to try vertical
Keep standard. I like the standard. I've got a new one of these two tonight
Good spider remains in place when deployed and homes in on a target that approaches
That's right
What is a vertical two rounds straight?
And two more vertical
Oh, okay
You can clear walls the vertical one's clear walls. All right, that's awesome
What does the feather do decreases jump speed makes you less vulnerable to attacks when landing?
Also makes to help make sharp turns on the ground. Let's try this
It looks pretty cool
All right, let's do it
Six seconds. What?
I've been mashing
Get over there get over. Oh, whoa
Wait, the spider
Spider is weird
Do a live commentary. I'm almost dead
How am I almost dead? No
Get out of the tutorial. I'm trying
we're like
like
Eight tenths of the game's dialogue is not much I can do
Where's my partner? What is he doing over there?
I'm gonna lose
We're dead
I think we're supposed to lose
Scripted
Celebrating how is it for you? Did you learn anything other than the meaning of shame scripted?
Let me tell you a little bit about two on two and a two on two battle
You partner's gunshots and charges won't hurt you
Still take damage if you get fight apart. Yeah
I got it. Will we get a second chance?
Full throttle, let's go
Sorry, he's new
All right. I want to go back to what I was using before
Tim and ip get the spider off. I don't like it that much cockroach is the way to go feather get rid of it long thrust
That's my guy right here
Wait, I got I have a new robot
I'm sorry. There's so much talking in this game that I forgot that like I forgot some stuff that I actually unlocked
The you unlocked this thing is one sentence squished in between like 300 sentences
I think red
red
Uh, i'm gonna keep this one. Yeah, let's try him
Bam, what the fuck? Why am I so slow?
Those cockroaches out
Cockroaches cockroaches cockroaches. You gotta bully this guy back here
Holy bully bully bully good
All right, this guy's toast
Yeah roaches the best for sure knock him down. I'll get him with this
I'll come down knock him down get a knock down
Cockroaches are by far the best item in the game
Let's get back to the story already
I
Got two more puns
Oh exhilarating how best to measure one skill than to permit him to have victory. Did you learn something?
Certainly. Hope you did
Why don't we talk about my story?
You see when I was a young boy
My father left me and my mother left too and then I decided I was good
Thank god. I'm gonna go off script. No, i'm going i'm staying on script but quick
We beat him can't even own up to it. Anyway, that was a nice little waste of our time
Now we'd better get back to work
Okay bogey, where can we find this guy you're after?
How's that door?
oh
That's a false wall. There's a door hidden there. We hold robo battles in the back room
This guy's been winning every match and i'm losing money
Stop pretending to read don't read stop pretending
Okay
Well, I mean what is illegal? Anyway, I mean it's such a vague term, you know
I get it. That's why you called us instead of the cops. You didn't want to get busted
It is 3d movie maker. This is the same exact
Restaurant and in fact, it's like the same actor behind the counter. This is the same shot
Maybe when you're older, you'll understand
Listen, don't tell anyone. Okay
Harry, all right, what's in it for me?
I mean I could be quiet about it or I can be real noisy
Hey, hey, don't be that way. You'll get paid. Well, if you pull this off
All right, keep your mouth shut dale. Let's go. I appreciate your discretion
Is that for all
We should chat up the crowd for some info before we sign up
Left flank bomb. What else do I get?
ain't pod f
pretty cool
Let's chat up crowd
Mentoring the next tournament. I'll probably bump into one of you depending on how they mix up the entries
Pardon me, but are you the one who's been winning all the matches?
You got the wrong person buddy. You want to talk to shiner?
He's in the waiting room right now with the other combatants. Mm-hmm
Okay, I wonder who he is
Okay, it has probably has to be you. No, it could be you. It's probably you one of you two back here
No, it can't be you
Can't be the only person with an actual video game model that was made. You're not the guy
No, I have the phantom of the opera thing in front of my face
No, that's not him
I keep betting on the underdog, but shiner keeps beating them. I'll never break even now
The guy over there hasn't placed one bet. He's just been sitting there watching the battles
What's he even doing here?
Wait, is this not the guy?
Shiner's been winning all the matches. So it's no fun to bet. That's why it's slow today
Hmm
You might as well just write
Mua h mua mua ha ha ha
Today just ain't my day. I'll barely break even if I bet on shiner and he's the odds-on favorite
But nobody's gonna beat shiners. There's no point in betting on anybody else
Is this shiner? You must be harry and dale
Mogi told me you'd be coming. Are you ready to fight?
No, not yet. He needs some time to talk to all the creeps around here. I understand i'll be ready when you are ready
I talked to everybody already
Day in my day did I talk?
Sorry guys, but i'm gonna take shiner down and claim the prize
Who did I not talk to?
If you enter the battle tournament, you can win big and get badly beat though
Day in my day
Shiner's been winning all the games. Where is he?
You must be harry
We're hosting a battle tournament with 16 commanders. I was just making the entry list for the next tournament
16 I hope we get to play
I'm determining your entry position now. Hold on a moment
All the way at the back of the mario kart line, right? Uh-huh
Dale is number nine which one's been winning all the matches
Well, that will be shiner entry number one
He's number one. I'm number 16
And dale is number nine
Dang according to this he we won't get a chance to face him until finals
That means that dale and I have to fight each other in the semi-finals
What season two of every anime ever the season fucking the entire season is this whole thing
You can skip season two of every anime that's ever existed
What?
Can't we change?
Sorry, everything's done by computers. It's totally random. I can't change your number for you
I start messing around with the numbers. The guests will think i'm fixing the matches
I thought bogey set this up for us. Oh man. Well, I guess we'll just have to win your tournament
Please wait here. I'll call you when it's your turn. Please call me when it's my turn
Is it my turn?
We can't leave
Uh, excuse me. Is it my turn yet?
Are you ready to go? Make sure you check the parts generator. I'm ready. You said you were gonna call me
First battle will be dale versus paulie
That's right. It's me paulie your original character
You thought you could say make paul and then just delete him no
I exist
Go for a deal. Don't worry. I've got tons of advice to get you through this
Tons of advice. That's not fair. That should be disqualified. I win by default
Hey chill. I'm not fighting. I'm just watching
Hang on. Aren't you a cop?
What's an upright member of the police squad like yourself doing in a place like this?
Not so loud. How could you tell?
You know, he's wearing his uniform
Wait a minute. You're those guys who busted the lab burglary
You must have recognized my distinctive features
More like your distinctive uniform pops all look the same to me
So wait, that means that you're one of those guys the burglars beat up
And you're one of those guys who shuts up
Insurance didn't cover any of my bills. So i'm trying to make some scratch on the side. Okay
Listen guys, i'm sure you've got lots to catch up on but we're trying to hold a tournament here
I'm gonna do better this time this time i'm in it for the money
Yeah, whatever you say
Okay, my advice for you is to beat this guy up but good
enough dialogue i'm trying
This guy's using a strike vanisher model. Let me explain
Like the shining fighter the strike manager's model
The bullies are well balanced but the biggest difference is that it has a stealth function
Stealth function if you do an air dash this function will make your robo disappear
Dodging incoming gunfire compared to a shining fighter model it moves slowly
I just i'm i'm like yawning now you guys made me yawn because you said yawn
Wouldn't everybody if you're going to use a strike manager take advantage of its stealth ability to dodge got it
Why?
And one more thing is a holoseum called a diamond cell that the police squad use
There's a magma zone in that holoseum. So be careful. Oh, yeah, it's that red stuff. Don't step in it
How's that irony though? You're not a crook, but you're fighting a cop comedy
Harry can I play the game now? Oh, yes. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Yes. Yes
The gatling guns took it up
I like the ape
So much stuff. I wish I would just be able to play and unlock
All right faint f stops in front of its target and to play two at one time
Can I get another one?
I mean, you kind of have to try everything once right? I did vertical. I didn't like it. Let's try this
All right, don't stand in the lava mash
Ooh
These are kind of cool. I like these
What the fuck was that? He just lagged. Oh, that's the stealth feature. Okay
It's a shitty connection. I don't even know what that does. I don't lose don't lose in the tournament
Play smart
shit
You're gonna lose in the first round. I'm not gonna lose in the first round
If I lose in this round, I will get 25 000 subs
I'm good. Don't have to do that access to the javelin. I couldn't have drawn an easier first match so much for paying my bills
Skills like those. How do you ever get to be a cop?
That's like pretty sad, isn't it?
Why shake hand this guy a hundred dollars?
Right
That's I feel bad
All right next fight
That's a new uh, that's a new
Robotype
Javelin strike vanisher model. Oh, this is one of the stealth ones. I'll try it
I'm like the criminal one
All right javelin and yeah yellow
Hmm
I'll try to get this to work
Remember, what do I do with my channel points?
Um, you just hold on to them forever
Pretty much what's gonna happen?
Uh cockroach
Holy shit, I can do that
All right, let's go
round two
No, not this shit. Not this just don't do this
This is like the only thing you guys use channel points for is the one thing that I haven't disabled
And that's the purple text that takes over
It's the only thing that you can do besides the emote changes and it's 1200 and I know at least
Two to three thousand of you have like 20 million channel points. So this could go on forever
You could this some of you guys that this is
Like a nickel to a lot of you guys
All right. I won my first match too shine. I won his match
We're going to because this is dad again
Have a clean fight
Isn't that the one guy who got in a fight with his wife? Yes, it is
What are you doing in this place?
Well, it's like this my wife handles all our money and I don't get much allowance
So I figured this would be a good way to make some extra money
You want allowance?
You better believe it by the way, I have a favor to ask could you take it easy on me, you know
So I could win
No, I want to win
Highlight my message. I have to delete channel points. I think where you're going to fire when you use that pot
You can do all kinds of things with the pod pod pod pod pod pod. Yeah
Uh-huh. Thank you deal
Wake up i'll say it again. Oh no
We just made him do it again
Remember you lost the chat hours ago
Did I?
Did I lose the chat hours ago? I feel like I didn't
I don't think we've been talking
We've been having a conversation. We've been hanging out
That's a cool type. Was it a super type? That's a that's a dr. Robotnik type. I want that one
Let's try the javelin beanbag sonic robot. Yeah
This is a cool area too. All right. Why am I not being able to get this?
Just draw here. All right, go
Here we go
And this thing actually works pretty well when it's a slow
Holy shit, this is awesome
vertical with the sky
Oh just get him rebirth. Hey. Hey, what speaking of rebirth?
Wasn't there a new binding of isaac thing that's supposed to come out like two years ago? What happened to that?
That out
Go get him roaches go
Yeah, like redemption or something or
Repentance or something whatever it's called
Yeah, come on. I'm gonna get in closer to drop these roaches
Get him roaches. You can do that three times. Holy shit
This character is really good
We need to play x-men origins
What do you mean watch the movie on stream because I can't do that left five-way gunner?
I'll never afford that lovely toupee now. What was the name of that robo game that I played? Wait, what'd you say?
What was the name of that robo game that germa played a while ago? That was almost like this. It's called gotcha force
And it is incredible
That is a fantastic video game. I love every second of it
Semi-finals are going here. We go
This is worse than that
Are you implying that gotcha force is not a good game because if you are then that is a permaban on this channel
And uh-huh permaban. It's gonna be like a minute. No, no, no, no like you are removed from the you are removed forever
Yeah, I will I will make sure that you are banned permanently and you don't get to chat ever again
Like oh, yeah, that's really funny. Like i'm gonna ban you for like a minute like we no, no, no, absolutely not
You make you say gotcha force sucks. Be careful playing with fire
Everyone's gonna be banned the higher you jump the more vulnerable you become same goes for an air dash
Me versus you
I didn't watch that stream with a happy face
Edit your comment and make that a sad face
or
You know what that is
I'm gonna keep this. I like this. Wait, what was the new thing I got?
Five ways something right?
Fires five rounds that spread to the left side the rounds turn in the opposite direction when fired from the air
That's right
Give me mod privilege and i'll edit it
Yeah, i'll give you a mod dude
Fucking hell freezes over
I like this one. Holy shit. This one's perfect. This is the spreader from contra three
Most satisfying weapon in any video game is the spreader from contra three and it's in this game
Get him roaches get him. He's got roaches, too
It's got good spread, but it doesn't do very much damage
I get a hit
I have to be on that stupid thing
Hurry and get him. I just hit myself with my own bomb
Shit. Oh, no, he's just styling on me now
the health
Lost to harry pepe low
That's my it's a new guy I haven't played with him do I lose the tournament
You're still a novice. So i'll give you just a bit more advice the higher you jump
Wait, is he gonna give you another chance?
So I can't lose the tournament. Let's go at it for real this time
Yeah, the game is save scumming for me
All right. I know I I know his little bullshit watch this
back to the ape
green hulk ape
Back to vertical. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no. No. Yeah
flank h
Cockroach is all right, but I think I want speed d for this
Guys, he's pretending to know the strategy of the game
Do you hear the confidence in his voice?
That was my mistake. He's not using this
Why did mine hit the wall and he's been over the wall and i'm speed
Close
I didn't say shb
Where's the juggler
pirate
Eat that shb. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Heard that one before
I win
Monkey always wins the boost pod and we're gonna fight the guy i'm the fan of the opera mask
I think you'd be so good. I've trained you well
I didn't feel like going full strength on you. Heh
You're our man. Make sure you don't screw up because this is an important job
All right is shiner gonna let me win
if I lose
boost pod time for the finals
That's shiner. It's time for the finals. You have between shiner and our newest star. I've never seen this guy before
Doesn't matter what you do. Everyone will bet on me. I'm the best
No one wants to throw away his money on an obvious loser
You know what? I don't care about all these losers make this place a profit
As long as i'm to waluigi
That's not even close to waluigi
Even close
As long as i'm making money and the masses go weak at the knees when they see me i'm happy
That's such a stretch
So tell me are you jealous of my skill?
Do you
Hate me
Hey, what do you say?
All right. What was that? We were busy polishing our robo cubes. What is wrong with this guy?
Excuse me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
It's a laugh. I'm the one who's gonna eat him alive
I'll show you the power of breaker my lightning sky robo
Lightning sky. I don't know what that is. Can you explain to me what the lightning's lightning sky model is?
The newest addition to the custom robot line it can attack and change directions while doing an air dash
It can only air dash once but it travels for a long time. It almost looks like it's flying
However, it moves really slowly on the ground. It's got a low defense and it's that's that's weakness got it. Thanks
There are 13 pages of this shit and every one of them we're gonna get an explanation
All right, we've got ape
What do you got a flame cannon a straight g?
caboose x
This is like really cool looking actually. This is a really cool looking robo
I was a straight g pretty straight ahead
six rounds
Lame. All right, i'm gonna keep the ape. What's i'm gonna check caboose x
we'll see
huge attack and huge size
Hire's in the opposite direction of where you aim
Okay, well that does a lot of damage. Let's try it
Where's the one that stays there for a let's see
Mip, right?
Yeah, I want you to have an ip
I'll keep feather on change the color
Um, I think I can but I like the green
How did you get first hit?
Holy fuck. I just knocked him a million years in the future
It was in the opposite direction. So I got to run the other way and shoot it this way
easier than