Hey, what's up? It's been 90 seconds. It's only been 90 seconds.
Confirm what kind of bug you'd be. Um, I don't know. What bug would I be? I would probably be a...
Yeah, I don't think it'd be a beetle. No, no, no, no. I would be a big ant.
Yeah, one of the big ones too.
No, dude, you'd be lice.
I don't think I'd be lice. I think you know I'd give me... Hi, hello. How are you doing? It's been a while.
I've been a very busy boy.
But it's good to see you again. You'd be a grasshopper?
Hmm. I don't think I can move that quickly. No, I think big ant is a good one. You'd be a cockroach. No.
No, I don't know. Maybe like one of the... I don't know. Maybe a beetle. All right, who gives a shit? Hi, welcome.
We're gonna be playing Gollum today.
I'm gonna be playing Gollum with a twist.
Okay?
I've heard this game is pretty...
bad.
But I did say that I wanted to play it.
I made a very, very important point
a week or two ago when I knew this was coming out. It's like I have to play this. I... How could I not play this game?
Uh, so...
I'm going to give myself a one hour and 55 minute timer
to get as far as I can in the game as fast as I can.
I'm going for a speed run.
I'm gonna see if I can speed run
the Lord of the Rings Gollum. Do you think I can do it in two hours?
What do you think?
No, no, not even close. No, that's fucked up. You don't think I could do it in three hours? What about three hours?
He wants to refund it.
I just... I'm just saying, uh, how far can I get it in two hours?
I just was... I was curious how far I could get in exactly one hour and 55 minutes.
The game is like 10 hours long?
What?
Is it actually? Oh shit. Well,
let's see how we get in a couple hours. We'll see. I have to play it.
I... Look, even if we're gonna play it for like an hour, I don't even care.
We're also gonna play Street Fighter 6
at some point in the next hour or two. I want to play that single player mode.
I'm going... I'm doing the single player Andy on Street Fighter 6
because that open world seems really really fun to me.
So we're gonna play that.
You're way too old for this game.
Wait, you're saying I'm too old for Street Fighter 6?
Why?
I don't think I'm too old for that game.
All right. Well, anyways, uh, I do have a...
I... You might hear a fan in the background. It's really hot.
It's like a million degrees right now. So you probably hear a fan in the background. That's the way it is.
If it gets too distracting, I'll turn it up even higher to get rid of a bunch of you.
Okay. Million. We can't hear the fan. Oh, nice. That means my...
All right. Well, are you ready? And look, I know people want a face cam, but I'm sorry.
Sorry, you're not gonna get it immediately. I don't know. Maybe you will later. I don't know.
We're just gonna play Lord of the Rings Golem.
All right, I am opening it, which means I have to start the timer. I have a 1 hour and 55 minute timer here.
I just want to see how far I can get.
We don't even have to follow it. I just want to know how far.
Okay, you ready?
It's opening.
Okay.
Almost there.
Okay. Can you see it? Why can I not hear anything? Okay.
Why is the game quiet? You're gonna waste time sitting around idle? I don't think so.
Now I can hear it. There it is.
I can't waste any time. I actually have to start right now. I have to start right now.
I don't know. Whatever's happening, I gotta go right now. I'm gonna speed run this game. Clock is ticking. Let's go.
All right, let's turn the timer off for now. Well, not off, but get out of the way.
Skip?
No, I want to see what happens.
I have to see what happens.
You're wasting time. Am I?
But it wasn't roses, my precious. Not roses.
Time lost. Time lost.
But what if I don't know where to go?
I am wasting precious minutes, you're right. Okay. No, we're good. We're good. It's gonna be a bad split. No, we're fine.
Do you get a sword in this game? Do you get to actually use a two-handed sword as golem and just like start slashing people?
Let's see how he responds to some light.
The darkness grows beyond our borders. My people are growing anxious. We cannot let this evil linger among us.
We believe that he went to Mordor.
That's what I feared.
Where does this take place in the timeline?
I wonder he has to say. That's too bright.
All right, there we go. We got plenty of time. Why don't we start with your name?
Your real name, not the one others have given you. I don't have to actually put a name in, do I?
It's not a what is your name RPG segment right now, is there?
I kind of hope there is. Very well. Let us try someone else's name. Oh, it really is.
Yes.
Yes, you remember him. He found you more than 60 years ago.
Oh, that's when it takes place. Deep underneath the roots of the Misty Mountains. He took something from you.
A ring.
Following the books of J.R.R. Tolkien. You were looking for it, weren't you?
Following the books. You left your home in the mountains.
Worming your way down the hills, always hiding from the moon.
Tolkien shits his pants if he saw it.
All the way east to the Lonely Mountain.
But then you stop, turn south.
Something must have drawn you away. A voice calling you to the land of shadow.
Whispering your name in your dream.
The Lord of the Rings. Gollum. The Adventure.
That absolutely no one asked for. No one wanted. But here it is.
Very well, Smeagol.
Now, let us start at the beginning. What amounts to a small stealth section.
Hated in every video game we turned into an entire 12-hour experience.
Gandalf, the all-going.
Uh, let's see. Ah, plenty of time. We're good.
All right, let let's be fair. Can I be fair?
Is this game that bad?
I have no I've been so completely disconnected from the universe
For the last couple of weeks. Is it bad?
Let's go in with an open mind. Okay, we're gonna go in with an open mind.
I'm telling you the second that I hear
Oh, the misty mountains. Oh, I'm gonna give it a full letter grade
Okay
All right, go go. I gotta I have to hurry. I gotta go now
I said see we just did a little bit of research. Remember you suck already
I didn't do anything
Is there a punch button?
There has to be a punch button, right?
I he kind of has like the face of like a coca melon kid
You know what i'm saying? Like, I don't know. There's something weird about the eyes. I don't know what it is
bar jump
Oh nice, it's pretty fluid
What can hurt why did he do that? I don't know I'm fucking having fun
Dude, he bounced mountains of shadow. That is where you are hiding
Why does it sound like somebody's hand is like wringing his throat
It sounds like somebody's got a nice throat holding his throat
All right. What's wrong with this? What what's wrong with this?
I don't see a problem with this game so far
What's wrong with this?
Seems kind of fun
What's the problem?
Why does everybody have such a problem with this? How do I get up there?
Golem can really move
Gandalf is fucking strangling him. Oh, sir. You talk to the orcs, huh?
I don't know about you little that's what it sounds like. It's only we're hearing this
No, get up here grab ledge below, okay
I just hit my chin
Hot cut scene
Oh
Is that a refund timer?
No
It's a
Test it out check it out timer
That's what it is
I just keep seeing Gandalf leaning down with both hands around his neck
Leaning in and what next tell me
It's just both both hands are around not just one
Look at drawing. Did I do this? I must have had friends one of family
Is that my health on the lower left, okay, so I have a health bar
It was ours
Yes
By the way
Hold on
He cannot sleep now
But I shelled him the light or you up and get the sword and the armor
Okay, can I do it?
What is it? What was that?
I paid four dollars for that
Does he dance
I have I bought these
How many are there?
Hold on. I paid three. What was the three or four dollars to have him get scared by bugs sometimes
Why did you do that? I don't know. I was just what this is a testing period
And for only $3.99 you can get the golem and the bug comedy pack
Belly laugh out loud while golem gets scared of the beetle
Laugh with your friends while the beetle puts golem on his back. That's really what that is
I thought it was gonna be more than that. Is it six emotes?
Why did you do that? Why did you why did you buy that? I don't know
Okay, just in case anyone was curious was potentially thinking about their purchase
They could see what was available
I'm this game is I think getting a lot of a bad rap. I think this game's getting some I don't I I don't
We'll see
I'm playing it. Let's go. Where do I go? Is there is there a map?
Oh, there is a map but it's kind of awful. What do I where am I going?
Over here
I I wasn't paying any it is this way
I have to hurry up. Am I going the right way?
No, didn't I come this way? Okay. Oh shit. I just hit the ground. Oh my god. He just like broke all his bones
Holy shit, that sounded terrible. He was falling for a long time
Oh boy, okay
Where am I supposed to go?
What am I even looking at here? Does anybody know what i'm doing?
The map I can't read this map
What is this map supposed to be telling me?
Oh, I got it
No one except back inches hunt the spy. All right, let's go
Okay, we gotta catch the bird got it sprint towards the wall he whoa
Oh
Am I right? Why did that almost kill me? What golem can move like this?
It will tell the wraiths
That was a minecraft llama hurt sound what oh shit careful hold on
Where are the orcs
How do I get up there
Stop making so much noise
Ow, what was wrong? What just happened to me?
I have to jump
ow
Shit
You're backtracking already. I am what do you go up?
I'm running out of stamina. How did I what do you mean? Did I actually go the wrong way?
Didn't I I was already up here
Okay, so from here, I gotta go. All right. Well, I was listening. Whatever
God fucking damn it. All right, just like a funny time. So how did I get so turned around? What happened?
He's alive. They're gonna do this again. I can go. Oh oops. I'm sorry
Can I jump on their back and bite them in the neck?
You stay there that's it that's all that happens. I actually kind of like this game
I just fucking ran who cares
All right, watch out for the orcs oh I can go whoa
Uh-oh does this count as a bush go
I made it. Wait, what left? What was that? I think that was scripted
And that's how far you ever went
We never never left the clouds why is it asking us and then you ate the bird in one bite
Two of them two little croaks
What's going on here this game is awful got a long way to go
Oh the frame drops they are pretty bad. They are pretty bad
Mountains
Oh look, we don't even need a base cam he's already on
Thank you wicked funny, huh? You think you're wicked funny?
Thank you. Wicked funny
Why did I do that? I hope it starts talking
Okay, would the game be a full letter grade higher if the bug?
Oh
No, never mind. That's right. Okay, just reporting all the orcs
It's two of them this is an escort escort quest
Because you're on an escort quest and I have to watch you do the escort
Why did he tear oh because i'm holding down right trigger stay in the shadows
They don't hear oh shit, I know never we're good
Who's there one of the buildings stay close to them precious. How there's two guards what?
Oh shit. Okay, so they never caught you. Yeah, then why are there torture marks on your hand?
She could help us we get a timer check. Yep
Yes, all right stay up here
First lure them into her webs and then what is the top of them? What is the mini? What's that thing saying?
The thing at the top. What is that? Is that an indicator for?
It's how close
Is that my face?
Oh
It looks like your face
Quiet
Sneak up an ambush. What?
What
Is this work
It's a worse orc ever that was a worse orc ever
God fucking damn it. I was looking to chat
Can I just do it right now? What's the best brand of root beer? Um, uh
I'm gonna say i'm i'm a mug root beer guy
All right now we get the second one take stone
Wait, you can throw rocks at people. This is actually pretty good
Dude mug fucking sucks
Excuse me
Can I not
We're on team we're on team mug
I I mug is frothier. I like a frothy root beer
Foams up a lot more
That's a great thumbnail photo
with a spider
I mean, honestly if you slicked back
If you slicked it back, it would look fine
Just put it run put your head in the water slick it back. It would look he would look great. He'd look fine
I don't know these beetles
Uh-oh
Smash it smash it. What if it's friendly eat it don't let it terrorize
What?
We have to make a decision
I'm not gonna kill the beetle because I like the beetle
No
I'm not gonna i'm not gonna kill the beetle
Why would I do that?
Kill it. No now convinced golem
It just looks for pollen
Pollen yes, it hasn't been following us has it this is so weird
Smeagol won the argument
That's I kind of think I like that. That's funny. We just had a huge raid come in
Oh boy, the big one. Thank you. Joel. Welcome everybody
We've got a 2 000 person raid just fucking coming in right now
Thanks a lot joe. Hope you're doing good
Welcome everybody
I can't believe there are 21 000 people here watching this
Me either
Yeah, i've been trying to figure that out for the last like
Five to ten years
Look out
It's a what are they called?
a
Death eater
Is that correct?
What are they called? I don't know
Wrong universe
You're a fake fan
I mean, I I like lord of the rings. I think it's cool. I think it's a really cool franchise
You haven't even seen the movies. Yeah, I have but it's been
It's been like 15 years
Jesus thank god. I put a limiter on
Find something to eat
Mushrooms do we have to cook food if we do it's a four letter grade higher
Why did he just do he just ate that like a weird bird he's why did he do that?
He puts his head up. It was like a fucking gopher
What was that?
Use golem's intuition what oh I okay, of course, there's a
Of course, there's a detective mode there has to be use golem vision to see
With our new golem vision technology. You'll be able you'll be able to perceive the world like golem does
Where do I go?
I don't know
Oh weird violin
weird violin
What supposed to I think it's scripted scripted
Yeah, wait, what?
No
Look at me. The only thing that was missing was the last three piano keys being pressed every 15 seconds during the
Look at me they brought you to him didn't they the dark lord?
What did you tell him?
What did you tell sauron?
everything
I told him everything
I told him about how to crush mushrooms and eat them and it'll eat dirt off the ground. I'm sorry. Can't help
I told him everything I know
Oh, what the fuck
Really?
What the fuck? Oh, I also bought the
You can have it be the different language. I don't know. Does does golem speak that language? What is it called?
I bought that too. It's the elvish language. Yeah
No, not the japanese language
It's like uh
I thought that was gandalf for a second. I was like holy shit. What are you doing? Who's in here with us? What's that?
The key
Why is this just open it's your number four
Lay down I just leave
I can get I can get the the door is open guys. I think I can get out there. I can get out there
Do not be fooled
All right, you can't I thought I could
That I could get onto the lip
All right. So let's all right now go to bed
What's this it's your number four
Lay down
How do I lay down the time we're at we're good
Honestly, I don't even think the graphics are that bad
day one
Stop complimenting
No, i'm not. I mean this game is not good at all
The graphics are fine. What's wrong? I mean, what are the graphics?
Graphics are fine
I
Need to turn on the other language thing report to the beast master
Just keep your head down do the masters tell you hold on a second. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait
Where is it? How do I turn it on?
Okay, elves speak. Wait elves speak elvish. It's not everybody. It's only the elves speak elvish
It's not everybody. Oh, that's kind of disappointing. I thought it was gonna be everybody would speak elvish
I guess why would that happen? All right, let's go
Just keep your head down do the masters tell you
What is that thing not a dwarf not a goblin for either of them
Yes, my king. They're talking about me
Wait, we have to like escape a beast or something
Oh, i'm gonna imagine we're all not gonna make it
Okay
I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready
Whatever we want to do
What to fight this way fight the beast
Golem you're going to die down here golem my advice
Make your death count. You have to get the boroks back into the pens as fast as okay
They let you starve if you're slow
the beasts
If they run at you find cover get to high ground if you can they don't have the best eye
He is walking really fast
Then quickly like really fast
We're moving way too quickly
Cool
The gate is not for us
Okay, first things first slaves chase the cattle chase the cattle
What you are the bait?
Okay
Lure the animal into the pen and then quickly shut the gate
Those beasts love to break the levers
That's why there is another one on top
Uh-huh now down on the other side carefully
That's it get his attention and run golem loves beetles precious beetle
Get up there. Oh shit wrong button go up. That's it. Did I do it? Hold on. No, it's not
Very well. There is another pen back there. All right. Do I have to get both of them in here?
The way is long and the boroks are fast
These ones are bulls so I wouldn't trust defenses to stop them
If they get too close try getting to higher ground, okay
Let's go. They're not even that fast
They can't even get up here. Can they can you guys get over here?
Oh
All right
What's going on? Come over here
my precious
All right now come over here break through this break through this one, too
Oh go
He swears
What the fuck is all this shit, I don't what
Don't they run away?
All right. Whoa, I thought they were already I thought they weren't in here yet
Whoa, i'm gonna make sure I get that tuber gameplay are you wearing headphones? Yes, I actually am
Smeagol has promised he'll find the precious for him
He swears. All right, so I gotta go over here
God damn it. I fell off
I'm doing all right
Not too good either no more work down below though
They want me to keep an eye on you their new scheme to humiliate me, I suppose
next the mines
Okay
Jeremy you look you seem like you like powdered milk
I don't
And plus powdered milk is actually part of recipes and shit. So
I mean, it's not like I like powdered milk, but it might be in something I like
I don't have to enjoy I don't enjoy powdered milk
I had to be an ingredient in something
All right, so we're gonna talk to we're gonna talk to these people. Is it asking riddles? Don't listen to her
There's a reason she's in a cage
Is it a witch precious does it know curses he's definitely perhaps coats himself in powdered milk
No water no no nice water
Disgusting
Honestly, they should have gone completely full just wacko mode with this
They should yeah, I should have a two-handed mace in my hands
And a suit of armor and stuff just go full comedy take it out of cannon. Who cares? It would have been so much more fun
No
Please
Sneaker doesn't know doesn't know the words does he
No, and what does a good slave do ranger a good slave that doesn't know the words
He learns
Maybe you should run little slave
We want to be done before the third horn
Don't worry
Okay
This is yawned
Oh, oh games didn't no game didn't crash. We still we got an hour. I don't want to hear any complaints
This is the whole game
Now there's more to this
No, there's more to the tags like the one they gave you eight
Find eight tags
These are the mild parts
And when you pick up a tag
Be careful because after two
Slender man will start to follow you after three he speeds up
After four he can teleport so be careful
What am I what am I doing
God I can't play this. There's too much
I need to get eight notes. Can I make this jump if I try?
I can do it
I just see that
You're the guy lying down over there
All right. I just gotta get down there to pick up one of the notes
Watch out for the bubble
Okay, just be careful. Oh shit. No, we're good. He's incredible and now he's coming here. It gives me shivers
Okay one out of eight
Okay, I gotta get seven of these why does it hurt every time
I want rocks
Jump in the lava
I don't want to start this over again
How much time do I have left?
Oh, that's not I don't know if there's enough time to go in the lava
Why don't I get back up? It'll be really funny
I don't know if it'll be really funny. I think it would just be moderately
chuckle inducing
I don't think it'd be funny
Three a three
This is not bad timing
You already missed one
What I can't get up there?
I missed one. How do I get the hell out of here? How do I get the hell out of here?
I'm not actually soft-locked here. Am I?
No, I think okay. There we go
What's that? What is that for? Oh, wait
He's I'm not gonna fall in the lava
I and it was it was perfect setup for me to do that. But
Well, it was just really funny
It was wicked funny
But that's what you have to do is to get it, right?
Okay, so
What happened there?
Okay, I can't grab I cannot grab that
Whatever. Let's go. Oh right over there. Okay, all right
There we are
all right now
Where's this other one?
cross
Shit, I don't know. I want to go down
Okay, is there one across here?
Oh my god, i'm fine
How do you like the game so far?
It's uh
All right
I mean it's
It is
Get on the ladder
Remember somebody said dude, don't even play it. It's not even funny bad. It's just a bad game and I was like, you know what?
I needed to play it
I promised you guys I would play it
The day that I the stream that I came back. I told you I was gonna play it
You know what? I'm happy
If this kills me i'm gonna uninstall the game
Okay, I need to cut this shit how much time do I have left i've got like an hour it's gonna be fine
I just i'm just so impatient
I'm just actually completely impatient
I need
I need like a punch and a kick. You know what I mean?
Take the elevator like i'm supposed to you cannot just jump
Okay, this one there and this one there i'm gonna go this way
What the fuck just happened?
What happened?
What actually just happened?
I can eat
Okay, this one down here
Okay, five
Got that one
Oh fuck thank god, okay
All right, where's this other one down here?
I missed one
See made it down die. It's too hot. It burns our skin
I'll keep forgetting. That's health
Is the one here water take tag or leave?
Um, aren't I supposed to be taking tags?
Sleep now much work for one day
That's number six
Two more over that way
We only need two more tags
I just have so
I was done like an hour ago, but not really. I just need to give it a chance
I was just so done an hour ago
But what if it's fun? What if it gets better? It could be fun later on
Uninstall refund
No
Don't refund
It could get much better
Precious is our home. What is that?
Looks like a frog
Don't listen my love
Can I push you off?
All right. How do where is this other one down here?
What the hell?
This where is it?
He's gonna quit not yet
Not yet
Sorry, not yet. Um, i'm gonna die if I hit that
I don't know what the hell i'm going
I have no idea
Okay
so
Around here
Why does it keeps changing on me?
Wait, hold on. All right, only one more
Last one
There people thought I was gonna leave before doing this
Everyone thought I was gonna quit before that
You were wrong, i'm sorry
This is the entire game by the way
But you don't know that
You haven't played it
You watched the review video they gave this a two out of ten you didn't see the rest of this
Yeah, I know we we I I you saw the review video
This game got a three. All right. I I know
They're sending the week up to the tower
40 more tags
You sound like you're what
It's my turn
Hold on. I have to I have to put my hands together and say precious
My precious
Don't go precious
What are you gonna do if I
You gotta do something about these bugs
What are you gonna do? You're gonna you're gonna hit me with that if I don't go
What are you gonna do? You're gonna you're gonna you're gonna hit me if I don't go
So wait, is this golem telling this story to gandalf?
This is a long story
Skip to the part where you
Met up with Frodo that time. I don't care about anything else in the middle
Only relevant information golem. I I don't really care about anything else you're saying
And then we picked up seven tags master
What
Uh-oh turn to your cell and end the day
End the day
How do I get out of here? Wait, it's probably a secret in here
Yep
We could use that
Nice
Um, I can't get I can't get away
Get off of me
Is there a skill tree in this game? I hope there is i've seen people sit there all night staring out that window
hatching out plans
Good clever plans all dead and gone
What are you looking at the bridge?
the gate
Oh, yes
That beautiful gate
Leads straight out of look boards. They say
I feel like if you were
Opening to the chime of a bell. This doesn't sound like frail man
Frail would who lives in the tower be like the master of the black pits
It sounds like put together but you know the orcs just call him candle man
Maybe they think it's him who's light burns in the tower
Alas, there is only one way into the tower of light
The one that our sick friend darrymon took today. He lost his hope long before he lost his life
as most of us do
You're just doing your dark and darker wizard voice for the tower he was obsessed with it
A great collection of maps. He told me
Stored somewhere in the horrors of grond in a building made of steel holes of ground
I could show you the way if you want to see for yourself
Don't listen maggot. No brains left in that old scrag
He's been down here too long. Oh do I have to choose who I want my companion to be?
Me instead. I know how to get around and i'm scrappy too
right
Okay, so what's day two's task?
Is it is it actually get tags
mines, okay
How many days are there? How long?
was golem in
Prison in mordor for wasn't it like decades?
Wasn't he in here for like 25 years?
100 years
I told you how do I get water? I don't have water. What if I get water?
You can't hurt me anymore
Masters can kill masters always finds a way to hurt
Canonically, I think more than one day. I think it was a long long long time
Joe the timer
We've got plenty of time
Now it would have been really funny if okay. This game is like this
But there was actually eight or whatever how long eight years ten years
Five years, how long was it?
Imagine if it was like three thousand days you had to play
That should be kind of funny. All right. What am I allowed to go through?
Special honor for you today
Some of our little crackers didn't go off last night some dirt eater needs to crawl down the tunnels and light them up
Am I gonna explode?
I'm gonna explode down there. Stop staring shaku
I hope there's an opportunity to make a mistake down there. You know what I mean?
That's gonna be really funny slaves. They deem useless. Come on this way take a light
It's going to be dark
How is the game
That's a four
I would say this is like a four or a five
Now they send in the most like five
Workers already place the explosives lighting them. That's the dirt eaters task at the end of the tunnel
You'll find a barrel full of out of ten go down then run for your life
Okay, when you smell the fumes, you'll know why no marks centrist andy strikes again
A five is a failing grade
A five is an f
I'll keep watch
It can't guys. It's not a one a one means you put your name on the top of the paper
You get a one for that
Two is you put in random answers?
right
Three is you got one question, right?
Four is you got like two questions correct, but you tried
Yeah, I all right. Yeah, I think that's fine
guys
Teachers don't hand out ones and twos. They don't I don't know. I haven't been in school for a long time, but
When was the most last time you got a two on your on your paper?
a two
Okay, so I have to light this on fire and then run you got it smells like fowl eggsies
Is it safe to do what i'm doing?
I got it, right? Okay. So when do I have to ignite?
something down here
Most professors give us zero if you don't even write a full page
Wait, what?
I just want to see how long it was. All right, get out now
Why is it so slow?
Why is the music getting oh escape?
escape what
There's no danger
Why is the music playing like this? There's nothing scary going on
Oh, it's gas
I didn't talk about gen loss
We'll do that
Lizzie that saw I was on uh
day two of ranboo's show
It was really fun
It was hold on. This is actually on a timer
Oh shit, it is right there
Secret let's finish these tunnels first come this way
There are more of these garrison things. Uh, yeah, I had uh
Wait, what?
Smeagol wants to go home to the river nice cold river. Well, you can't can you yeah the prosthetics I was in
Uh, i'd never done something like that before
but
I had to get my whole face casted
And the way they do that is they put this stuff all over your face
This like silicone stuff and cover your mouth and your almost your whole head
But not my it didn't do the back of my head or anything
It was just my entire face and I could only breathe very very slightly out of my nostrils
It was it was an experience. It was like, oh shit
and then
They sculpted on that mold
It's really really really cool
Did you shave? Oh, yeah, I had to there's no way it would have actually been a bliss day on my face
Oh, I gotta go now
Did you get to keep the mold? Yes. I actually did i'll show it
um
Unfortunately, it is not here. I need to get it. I need to get it sent to me
But I will show it. It's terrifying
It's just a one-to-one complete replica of my face with every pore
every
every wrinkle
It is a snapshot of my exact face as a 37 year old man
Sell it, uh, nope
No fucking way
No fucking way here finish the last tunnel then meet me back upstairs at the cages
I ain't selling that
There ain't no price on that one
You could make bank selling it
There is no world where i'm gonna be super happy and like, oh, yeah, that's that's awesome
Yeah, so new merch drop guys
a one-to-one complete replica
down to the pores
Identical of my face
complete
better than hd
Real life. It's like real life. It's better than hd. It's real life
I'm not selling that
Have you tried using face id with your phone with the mold?
That's actually kind of funny, but no, I would not i'm not gonna sell that
No fucking way
In 2 000 years, they'll dig it up and reconstruct you no i'm smashing it with a hammer before I die
Do you know what I mean?
like before I die
One of my requests in my will is smash that fucking one-to-one realistic face
Smash it with a hammer to a million pieces
Give it to your grandkids. No, they're not getting shit
That sounded bad. That sounded bad. I mean they'll i'll get why can I go in here?
That sounded kind of bad. I mean, they're not gonna get any like weird shit like that
They'll get
They'll get money
Whatever's left I guess
I'll get some money, right?
They'll see what I have left and they'll be like why did grandpa do all this shit?
How much money did he have and you're telling wait he put on a dollhouse
What the fuck are you talking about?
Where's the money?
And they send you into the light
That's when you can sleep. What did you spend? You you spent seventy
Thousand dollars on the family guy game grandpa. What the fuck are you doing? Why didn't you just give it to us?
Get a gold cast of the mask
Oh, that's a brilliant idea put the inheritance inside of the face mold so they have to smash it to get it
Here is better here
Remember the dwarves I mentioned earlier
One of them told me something once those buildings out there above the bridge make a gold bust of your face
That'd be so funny
But that would be a lot of money while he knew where the guards watch if oh shit
Now we're good and hide them in a cave near the bridge
Just one stone each day so the guards wouldn't notice
Why why do you think what happened?
well
One day he slipped and fell
Yeah, that's not a nice story
I suppose not
That's all i'm saying
I'm going to go back
Um, what do you think you're talking to?
Awkward sleep more quiet if we was his friend
Is that a threat?
Are you threatening me? What are you gonna do?
Oh that I guess
Days later knocked you out for days
Stay close to me. I can show you
This isn't very good
I I thought it was gonna be I was gonna be running around outside and hiding in bushes and
I don't know why it's gonna be doing tasks
I could see if this was a section of the game
Is this the whole game
Yeah
Uh
Is the story any good?
I mean, it's hard to tell
When you realize your relatives have to smash both your head and the bust of your head when you die
Oh, that's true
That's true
No, I didn't there's a lot of new people here. I think
Do you guys remember that?
Should we talk about that really quick? Um, okay, so
When okay, let's talk
When you die
Nobody really knows what happens
but there's this prospect
that your brain
Is kind of still going
You're kind of still going and just
What happens in there?
Does time slow down?
In your head and do you essentially live?
potentially
Hundreds of years up here because of just like you're kind of dying and you're going and you're but you know what i'm saying
There's been theories. There's been theories about this
That like maybe your brain is actually still active for a while and who knows how long you'd be trapped up there for so
I don't know. What if I like don't want to be in there? So I made it a jokey reference to the second that I flatline
like
Because it could be a thousand years at that point
You know what i'm saying? Like that one second could be a thousand years after that
I just crushed my head with a cinder block the second that it's like
What the fuck what what did just make the noise I just made
What the hell?
Stay away from her you imbecile
Can you imagine it's in his will you don't understand
I'm going to send you. Yeah, uncle. Uncle frank has to run in with a cinder block. No, you don't understand. It's in his will
We have to crush his head
Somebody get security. No, i'm sitting there in there
You're under arrest uncle frank
No, shit, i'm sorry jeremy. I tried
The feeds the beasts of mordor when you leave the ditch you'll see the rattler
The hoist with all the bones remember
The rattler will take you up to the halls of grond
If you ever get there alive
Who knows just open this for you
Why do we sleep right? What the fuck is going on?
Why do we sleep?
What do we do? We just disconnect from the network
for hours at a time
Why do we sleep?
Our brains have to turn off. We get we get disconnected from the network
What did I how did I die? Did I die?
Oh
It's rest and restoration
Yeah, but isn't that so interesting that our brains effectively are a battery that has to be recharged at the end of a of a 20
hour period
You have an iphone battery there. That's interesting. It's incredibly interesting
What's down here? Is there anything I need to get up here? What's the timer? We got plenty of time. Relax
No one said it was like an iphone battery
I I did I don't mean you have an iphone battery into your brain
I just mean isn't it interesting that we have to turn off to recharge?
We have to literally plug ourselves in to a different network to recharge ourselves
I don't have to explain myself
Can they get me?
You don't come down here, right? Do you will you jump after me? You kind of don't even look scary
It's kind of nice actually
I've heard it compared to clearing
Where am I?
What's going on?
Where the fuck am I? What is going on?
Am I underwater?
Um
What how did I get in here?
Where the fuck am I going?
Okay, that was
That was very weird
Okay
I got the camera went
freezing
Yeah
What
What the fuck is going on here, okay
So far away
Guys did golem win the argument or did schmigel it was schmigel. I'm a good guy
Oh fuck a category
Caragor
Blasted caragors
What if he watches us the dark lord?
What he sees
A tiny schmigel so many things for him to watch mountains enemies spies
No lord is looking for the precious
He wants it wants it. Who is he talking to?
Okay
We must do what the lord says what he says. Yes, but he says save the precious and who has the precious
Baggins baggins
Not here. Is it the nasty trixie hobbit?
How can we protect the precious when it's so far away?
We got 20 minutes
I think that's enough to get to act
Three where we're going
I must be patient my dear must be very very
Be careful
Wait, I don't have to get in there
20 minutes for what 20 minutes until um, i'm gonna determine if i'm gonna play the game anymore
This is nice. This is cool
I know that was my fucking centrist voice, but just please
It did it that it was
Can somebody give me a rundown of the entire lord of the kings story?
Well, it's lord of the it's this
I don't think I could even tell you what happens in lord of the rings
I probably could but i'm gonna get a name wrong. I'm gonna get a time period wrong and people are going to scream at me
i'll try
Like 10 000 years ago
there was this
monster
It was a elf. No, it wasn't a monster yet. His name was sauron
He's an elf
He had a buddy that made shit. It was a blacksmith. His name was kela brimbor. So sauron says to kela brimbor
Hey
What's up, dude? So here's what we're gonna do. We're gonna make a bunch of rings
Rings of power because we want to you know, obviously the world we have to make sure we keep it in balance and everybody needs to
Have this powerful things and powerful jewelry in case we have to fight
We can you know, shoot fucking beams at each other from the lasers from the ring whatever we do
So now there's a bunch of powerful rings
So they made a bunch of them and they were different, you know all the different people though that were on earth
Whatever this place is called
So you've got nine went to the humans six went to the dwarves
12 went to the elves
And then five were put in storage in case they were you know
Just in case there was more needed later on down the road just in case anybody else wanted more
in secret
Sauron made kela brimbor make another ring
Essentially all those other rings I talked about were fake. They weren't like that strong. They weren't really that cool
They didn't have like the fucking serious drip that the one ring has so sauron asked kela brimbor to make
An and a super powered ring in secret in private. So kela brimbor says, oh this is
Uncalled for so after he makes it
um sauron punches him in the face with the ring and he does like this ring punch and it's just
Like shatters his skull and kills kela brimbor. So he can't tell anybody the real secret. So sauron goes on to
essentially destroy
Um all of middle earth he kills everybody and it takes over there everyone's like what the fuck's going on
Our rings aren't even good. Our rings aren't even powerful
and that's
where
uh bill bow baggins gets it eventually and
They have it's like hey this ring is too strong. We have somebody has to we have to destroy it somehow
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Like this is not even that far
This is really not that far of a drop
Right, what?
You skipped three votes
All right, so then bill bow baggins
ends up meeting
golem
Who at some point the ring gets lost because I don't fucking know
There's a big battle and sauron loses. He gets his finger cut off
And during that whole process it falls down a well and goes down into this rocky area
And golem finds it
Golem puts it on and for like a hundred years is like the coolest person in fucking mordor
This is a stealth game
so
eventually
Eventually frodo
No, I don't know
I could tell i'm i'm paying attention to something else
Okay, so bill bow baggins
Has the ring
Oh shit, this happens before frodo is first
No, frodo is after because he's like an older guy and he does that. Let's try to get the ring off his neck
Turns out okay. No, hold on. I don't want to get caught here
Turns out six of the rings were very powerful
And what they end up doing is the humans the dwarves the elves they all come together and they put their rings together
And they summon what is effectively captain planet. It's um, it's gandalf
When gandalf ends up like cleaning up a bunch of litter and stuff
And tells everybody to you know, cut the shit and make sure you recycle your fucking plastic bottles
And then he oh my god
There's no way to get out of here
Is he gonna see me can you hear this
This
It takes way too long to kill somebody
It lights off
Did I make it? Oh fuck. No, i'm good
Oh, come on. Where the hell do I go?
You gotta be kidding me
What about sourman? Oh, that's right. So during this whole process
There's there are many wizards, right? There is
the two blue wizards
There's the one gray wizard. There's the brown wizard. There is the
Um, I don't saruman is the white saruman the white right
Radagast the brown
There's like five of them
And only one of them really gives a shit about anything and it's gandalf the others don't care
The others actually don't give a shit about anything
They have to be convinced to give a fuck and it takes all the way to the very end of the entire franchise before they actually care
That one's true
Is there a way to actually don't think I can go this way? Maybe I have to lure him over here
Any news on the black legion?
Marching to dolgul door soon. That's what kushnach says
The targs is doing proudly on our doorstep
Not for long
So anyways sourman ends up this is spoilers for the lord of the rings, by the way, if you don't care and whatever
I um, you know what we're gonna play street fighter in 12 minutes. Anyways
It doesn't matter if you get the spoilers completely wrong. Yeah, that's true
But anyways, there's a mountain that they can get rid of the one ring to make sure nobody gets powerful and corrupted ever again
What they don't know is this is a fantasy universe
At all you invest we all very very clear and as we all know
They could just open up a fucking portal somewhere and it doesn't matter. They'll do it again
You know what? I mean, they'll just open up a fucking portal. So that's all that matters eventually
He's shooting me with a fucking
Okay
I don't want to play this game anymore. I don't want to play this game just to keep the countdown up
It's stuff. It's stealth. There's what is worse than stealth encounters?
I could do it
No, if I could just
Yeah, this is like the lover. Glover was actually good. This is not
This is bad
But sorry, I can do it
No shit, okay. I just don't want to play this
This is obviously wrong so let me run him back here
Is there anybody go that's when I jump up here
There's got to be a way I can hide in here or something, right? I don't I mean is this guy just stupid
That was dumb that was kind of unfair
All right, it's time to play street fighter six am I hidden? Oh my god, I am hidden
That was weird
Shut the fuck up. There's no come give me a break, dude
You go
Is he still looking? No, we're good. All right. All right. I finally made it
um
Nice
Can I dump this?
No, I can't
There it is
I think I can get there in just one go. Well, I'm done. Goodbye. I actually can't do this again. I refuse to do this again
That sucks
And am I doing it for a joke half the time maybe
Probably subconsciously I would say I think that's correct
God damn it. I
How much time is left seven minutes? This is where vinnie gave up on the game, too
Really? So nobody knows what happens after this
Has anyone gotten that far?
Okay, we're good
Don't be stupid this time
What do you go investigate the rock go investigate the rock he did it last time
You gotta be kidding me. Now what throw it at? Oh that thing. Yeah, you mean
Can't grab me now, can you?
Okay. Now this time just don't jump off and die instantly go do it the right way if I hold go here drop here
Okay
Very cool, and I don't I can't die here
so
Be very very careful. Don't be stupid
Goodness, um, oh my god
Ah
I thought I was gonna I don't know I was gonna try to break his neck
Yeah, that's it. I'm done
Right on time
We're good. So what I want to do in street fighter is I want to do the open world single player mode
It was I tried the demo. All right, that's fun. Yeah
That was the lord of the rings golems adventure. I just want to check it out. See how it was you like stealth
uh based games and you enjoy um
I cannot I can't
Yeah, I can't
Yeah, I can't you like, um
stealth based adventure games if you're a fan of lord of the rings, uh, read the books and
watch the movies for a 15th or 16th time and
Get the get the prequel book and read that one. And I mean shadow of war or shadow of war is great
Those are really cool
I don't know. Maybe if you want to see the story of what happens to golem during his time in mordor
I'm gonna recommend that you do
Some of your own research on this and if you want to check it out that you're you can go and do some research
and um
I'm still in the game. By the way, I actually am still in the game. Yeah, I have to get out of the game
We're good. All right, i'm gonna be right back gonna pee and get street fighter six set up and let's see
Cool. All right, i'll be right back