Hi. Hello everyone, German985 here. Just kidding. Hello everyone, German985 here.
Oh well, you can't lie to them like that. What's up guys? Did anyone believe it?
No one's even here to hear it, so. Yeah, there is like
15-20 people already here. Oh, you're on Twitch. My bad.
I am on the Twitch-itch. Anyways, happy Saturday.
Happy Sunday if you are from a different country. And let me
shout this out to people. Actually, I gotta write
at MLC Stealth. Oh, come on.
Hold on, what? How come I can't bring up Brett
as like an at mention? Maybe he like blew up his Twitter.
MLC Stealth. Wait, can I not even do you either?
What is going on here, Twitter? Twitter, what is going on?
Why are you being like this? I'm gonna tweet too. You could retweet what I tweet.
We can all tweet. You can pick your nose. You tweet, I tweet.
But you can't pick your friends' nose. We all tweet for JermaStream.
With at MLC. Okay, that was weird. I don't know why it didn't work before.
I wonder who that is. And tweet.
No, no tweet. Don't tweet yet. I already tweeted.
Oh, no. Oh, no, no. I was talking to myself, not to you.
I was telling myself, because I was gonna hit the Twitter button,
and I didn't even put the link, so I was like, no, no. It has been twittered.
And yes, it has. There's Twitter.
Now I'll go to YouTube and post that.
And then get out of there, because it's not necessary.
And Saturday Stream. Okay, good evening.
We're gonna play some Team Fortress 2, and then, if you guys don't know,
they just put out a huge, huge CSGO update.
So that should be interesting to check out, for sure.
It's like one of the biggest, they've added like, they had like five maps.
I would love to express my enthusiasm for that, but alas, I cannot.
You don't have it. I don't have it, no.
Oh, wow. Yeah, I think they're gonna, it's, release is coming soon.
I think it's coming soon. Otherwise, the update today was pretty huge, so.
You know Valve, though. It's gonna be months, probably.
Yeah, yeah, true. Very true.
Good evening, everyone. All of you that are saying good evening.
I bid you good morrow and good tidings.
So let's get rolling.
MLC Stealth is here, but he's currently, he's currently in the bathroom.
And that's all we're gonna say about that.
So let's, we're gonna find a server that is empty.
Do we need to wait for him before we join a server so that he can play?
Ah, yeah. He's gonna have to deal with it.
Oh, there you go. There he is.
Perfect timing, sir. Thank you.
I was waiting for the right moment to enter, and that one seemed pretty good.
No, I was watching clips from the Ellen DeGeneres show.
Why, why are you doing that?
She's funny. Sorry, I'm late.
You're supposed to be in the stream.
Now let's get into this server. Let's try and find a 32. Here we go.
CP Badlands. Eh, I don't know if I wanna do CP Badlands.
This is 28. That's 2-4. That's trading.
Oh, here we go. That's 2 out of 24.
Alright, you guys ready?
Uh, not quite yet.
Oh, you better hurry up.
I'm, I'm launching it.
It's already on that screen. It's already on.
I'm already, I've already got Xbox connected, my console.
Ready to go.
Wait, couple seconds.
Oh, by the way, if you guys may, everyone knows who Stealth is,
but some people may not know who you are, Italics.
Go ahead and give an introduction.
Hey guys, my name is Italics, and I make YouTube videos.
And my channel name is Gamers Descent,
which you may know me by instead of Italics.
That is where I hail from.
Yeah, you come from the mountain top of Gamers Descent.
What time is it right now? It is 15 after six.
People were just saying that.
Alright, I'm ready.
What are we going to say, Italics, before I cut you off?
I don't, I don't know.
I guess to further introduce myself,
I'm a machinima realm director.
So I'm on, I'm on the other side of the chasm
between the two machinima mountains.
I come in peace.
Here we go. People are already starting to join.
Let's do it. 68.177.101.44 colon 27016.
You better go.
Oh, that confused me. It had 16.
I pressed six first.
Well, you better get in there.
Those team numbers always confuse me.
Hey, I think, so it still says, oh, I'm playing,
I didn't even update the dashboard either.
And I think it's still correct.
Actually, I'll have to change it right now.
Oh. Put TF2 MOAB hunting.
TF2 MOAB hunting.
All you're going to do is get 25 kills in a row.
That's very difficult to do in this game.
That is not an easy thing to do in Team Fortress,
to get more than, more than,
I'd say more than 15 kills in a row,
10 kills in a row is even like a pretty big feat of strength.
The only one who could do it is a, like, an engineer.
Yeah, a heavy too. Heavy can get a lot of kills.
An engineer if nobody is, like, smart and going
demo mannered over medic.
I went on to see a red team.
How's the game audio? Let's take a look.
Yeah, it's all right.
How's the end game audio, guys?
Good. I cannot tell.
Are you going to tell them what your name is?
Uh, people will probably figure it out by now.
Dick Simmons, the dump champion.
Oh, where's the scout going?
Oh!
That's a pretty nice flare gun, dude.
Oh, I thought that was you.
Oh, watch it. Watch out.
What's up, Stil?
I forgot fire kills me.
Going up pretty well here.
All right, what do I have for a melee right now?
I don't even know.
Oh, actually, I got the postal pummeler.
All right, let's try and get some postal pummeler kills.
Yeah, you, no, you're not a spy.
I need a medic.
Oh, yeah.
We did it.
Game over.
Oh, we did it, guys.
So we can do it again.
Pretty cool.
Oh, we're changing.
I wanted to play on Upward, too.
Oh, I love Upward.
I know, I love it, too.
Upward is one of my favorites.
Upward.
Oh.
What are we going to do now?
My most kills is only 25 as a sniper.
I would have only gotten one MOAB.
I have no idea.
Oh, Thunder Mountain. Good. I love Thunder Mountain.
I like the first two stages.
Thunder Mountain.
Jerma, can I be has in a hug?
If you're asking for a hug, here, ready?
Internet hug.
There we go.
He has him in your hug.
Here we go.
He has been in.
Here comes the internet hug.
You just received internet hug.
Worth $15.
You've got hugs.
That's actually pretty good.
You've got mail.
Oh, I have a new item.
Oh, I got a new item.
I'm giving away my backpack.
I finally got some new stuff.
Why am I even running?
Waiting for players.
Where are we going?
You guys, no one's got to give me stuff.
I mean, items are one thing.
I have a nice plan.
As you probably saw in my latest video, if you haven't,
I'm going to do a crate unboxing video.
And whatever I get in those crates,
if I get an unusual or something,
it's going to be given away.
Any unusual I get in the boxes is going to be given away.
And if I get strangers, they're mine.
I'm keeping them.
Oh, we got a false server.
I will probably...
Is this 24?
Yeah, this is five spectators.
I'm sure some people are kind of stuck in spectator right now.
But the unboxing video will probably be next week,
I would assume.
A duel, you say?
Dick Simmons, the Dump Champion.
Yeah, that's me.
Wait, did you put end quotes on that?
I think this is just a parentheses.
That's all I know.
Is Shibby on this stream?
I don't think so.
I've been wrong before, though.
All right, I closed my door there.
Shibby is not on this stream.
Not in the chat, anyway.
No, not that I can see.
High five.
Thank you.
Can I just kill somebody already?
We got to wait.
It's setup time, man.
I want to blow them underneath the fence.
Will I ever play Dawn of War 2?
Oh, man.
I was a huge Dawn of War 1 fan.
I don't really like what they did with Dawn of War 2.
I'm not going to lie.
I wasn't a big Dawn of War 2 person.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I forgot, I don't have a shotgun.
Still pretty good.
Oh, thanks.
Covered in the G.F. Rowdy.
I'm going to puke because I get...
Gerardi makes me puke.
Oh, my God, Gerardi, get out of here.
Conqueror.
Conturer.
I can't believe how many no points I got right there.
Oh, no, damn it.
I thought I had more rockets loaded.
S-H-I-T.
What does that spell?
Shoot.
Gosh darn it.
Oh, Goose Jr.
That's what that spells.
Ba-boom, ba-boom.
Who am I streaming with?
MLC Stealth and Italics.
Two bros.
We play games.
Therefore, we are special.
Sometimes we play video games.
Occasionally.
Sometimes we laugh.
Sometimes we cry.
Sometimes we share valuable moments together
that make us better.
Oh, he's going to get away.
I refuse to let him get away.
He's going to get behind everybody.
He's going to get behind us all.
I think he already is.
Oh, he's gone.
Oh, nine health, and I'm jumping off of high surfaces.
Oh, how do I survive?
Give me that health.
Can you donate an unusual?
I thought you were about to say, can you dig it, sucker?
I would rather you hang on to that.
I don't need anything.
You don't have to give me stuff.
Booker T.
Especially an unusual, because an unusual is worth a lot.
And I don't want to take stuff like that from people, so.
Oh, did I make it?
Oh, my God.
That was a good shot.
That guy caught me right when I was coming down.
Boom.
I got to take off the Conqueror.
Conqueror is a cool, not feeling the Conqueror.
Not right now.
Oh, damn.
That was in the face.
I'm taking this off.
I'm going to put on, what am I going to put on?
I'm going to put on the shotgun.
The strange shotgun, I still have to give these away.
I have given my third.
I've given 33% of the backpack away so far.
Two more people I have to get in contact with.
And then after that, start all over again.
All right, I'm going medic.
Yeah, we could use, we only got one.
Oh, actually, you are the one.
You just switched.
Actually, there's two, I think.
Ari's medicing.
Oh, OK, OK, OK, sexy, sexy.
Which one is Jerma?
I swear, it's not Dick Simmons, the Dumped Champion.
That is a spy.
Oh, no.
OK, if I see Uba, is it Uba Charge?
What classes are you guys playing as right now?
I'm soldier.
Oh, no.
Oh, so little help.
I am the sniper jam.
What are my video settings on here?
I'll show you.
Video, 1280 by 720, because I'm running in a window right now.
It's going to be able to stream it.
But I play on high, high, high, simple, medium, disabled color
correction, and then all these other things.
I don't play with anti-aliasing on.
I feel like the amount of resources
it takes to the amount of gain you get
is not really that noticeable, at least in my opinion.
At least for a game like this.
Oh, my word.
Thank you for putting me out of fire, Pyro.
I always play with Vsync.
God damn.
Always.
I'm changing to engineer.
Do I play any commonly hated games?
Oh, backstab, turn around, spy.
Do you guys play any commonly hated games?
He's outside our door.
Any commonly hated games?
I call a duty.
What would fall under that?
That's probably number one right there.
Yeah, stealth.
Answer is yes.
Stealth does play commonly hated games.
But actually hated, literally bad games, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't think I play any really hated games.
Oh, there's the sniper again.
We still got a level one up.
Oh, I think I'm about to score.
Oh, come on.
Is this guy hacking?
I see a spy on their team running around in his taunts,
and he looks like a wax figure just moving around,
skating around.
It's probably a glitch or something, I don't know.
Yeah, I saw that earlier too.
I think it is just a glitch.
But even when he was disguised,
it was just walking around, like not moving.
Like arms in the air.
Oh, I gotta change this.
I don't gotta change that, what am I doing?
You gotta change it.
Oh, I gotta hurry the hell up.
Oh boy.
I was a second behind.
I threw my games off, rollin' off now.
What is this, like an RTS?
I've gotta catch up.
My actions permitted is only 100.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's do a hoot.
What's the best scatter gun for the scout?
They're all good.
It depends on how you play stylus.
Mid-range to long-range, you use the shortstop.
Close range, meat shots, force of nature,
and everything else kind of in between.
The regular scatter gun's probably the best,
at least that's kinda how I see it.
I like that one the best.
No, I gotta go over here, what am I doing?
Oh god, I've already screwed this up.
Can I salvage this is the real question.
That's the real question, can I salvage this?
What am I doing?
I don't know where I wanna put it.
I don't know what I wanna do.
I'm so torn right now.
Because this guy's right here now,
I'm puttin' it right here.
Dilemmas, dilemmas.
That was so torn, my brain couldn't
not handle what I was just doing.
Oh lord, oh this is going down in two seconds.
I am absolutely.
Oh lag.
Oh yeah, I got that too.
Super lag, is that the real MLC stealth?
I hope so.
Yep.
Oh, I'm gettin' a lot of lag.
Thank you, Engineer, for helping me build this.
Appreciate it.
Let's reload.
Is that the real MLC stealth?
Oh yeah.
All right, I got some catching up to do in points.
This is kinda getting embarrassing.
Oh my gosh.
Here comes, oh there goes the dispenser.
Oh my god, oh he's up top.
Oh, that just ruined my life.
There's the spy again.
Unmoving.
Yeah, I got him.
Or maybe he did run too nice.
We're goin' this.
I like this better.
So I don't feel as bad when I lose all my stuff.
I was spy, doin' his thing.
I think that, oh my word.
He is doin' his thing, isn't he?
Get away, roommate.
He's still alive.
Oh, he is not dead.
I didn't get the,
dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
I'm gonna duel with him right now.
Oh yeah?
So I didn't get the dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
I don't know where he went.
Find him!
He's on the cart.
Oh my god.
You're all right, Doc.
Oh, run away.
I wanted up here.
They're about to get to the point.
They're almost there.
Oh, crit thing.
Oh no no no no, where is he?
He's, oh, oh no!
Give me the help.
Oh my god, run away.
Oh, this guy's so gonna get me.
Oh no.
Oh, I can't believe I'm still alive.
Additional time.
They got it.
No, I was dead.
I was toast right there.
I was toast!
uh... what what your toast
what's name tag i think that it did
the jeffrey's for anybody else that the chat brosford that somebody is coming
to you
uh... i don't think the chepros no i was looking at it and i was like wait no
uh...
all they're going to
they got a heavy medic right here
get rid of that medic
but what they could
uh...
but all else fails just
ducking cover
well i'll just rather than are you like sounds that stuff
than a prominent things
uh... you can find out i think
so there's a lot of
fishery of sp
their spies like surfing around in the
our base there's two spies i think sitting outside our doors
all dot he's over here
not wait but that's not in my
that's not my century
really lose it here guys
i break in and i will do it
get out of my way
no no no
uh... just barely saved up
so many people
so much death
tried it's dispenser
all of the time i know you're not good
because
while i don't know
okay i'm going to make sense
someone to get toasted out there
or it's probably going to be is that you get
was a u s is a walk right next to it was that uh... spying that you richard
that that's me
uh...
radio record
uh... get the medic
other i went from like last place like fourth place in one line
but i thought
but i don't
but we don't
i've had to spot
uh... well
uh... high
what i don't know what i want to be cool
so i was talking to my man
i'm gonna get back step that's a spy
uh... well shoot
are going to go this is what i'm talking about
al
one of the scoreboard boys
i have faith in your germa
i wonder if i will play you think uh...
wonder if you're going to make the hell was that
what the hell was that
just get a nice gun emplacement at the end of that hallway right there
and that's right i can turn it
that you destroyed it
because of the little
uh... i probably will play zombie fortress at some point
probably not a little what
zombie fortress
i'm just going to punches on it here
room i'm not going out with one punch
you'll get knocked out
all come on feel the pain
i would kill them too
one-off
boxes from a quick one shot
uh... set the next level through a lot of changes are at this anyway so
one
well that answers that question
we're changing server
just uh... people want to know germa what is on the fortress
i uh... i don't know i think it's like i like
ever all my
everybody plays
i would think it was mainly except for small group people
somebody's planet
also it's like infection on halo
i hate you're not me
whatever that game was called
i think i know what you're talking about
yes it's it's like
it's kinda like a zombie boat where everyone runs around the lake separate
small group of people that don't have
to go like the not zombies
wrong somebody please correct me in this in the chat
i know it's something like that
that's probably right and they said it's like halo infection much of spies
how they are taking out everything i got to be a little bit sneakier these
centuries
and that's going to blow up and kill me
and that's going to die as far as
right
go i'm going to go
i'm going to s sounds are you playing as heavy
i am playing it's heavy
seascapes what i've reached with ads by cycling around
i start a scalp and then i'm like okay i suck
moving on to the heavy where i can actually kill people
i'd like to set up a stick
well i heard backstab
i'm standing in the corner
uh...
uh... i don't think he's dead maybe it's uh...
there we don't have any engineers do it
white what just happened to me
which is even happens
headshot from across the map
uh... my god
on the other side
our battle is
about what about the words
yeah there's two spots on the point
on the card we lost
but what do you guys know that i was
how many spots are on that day of team
uh... new uh... new server
not gg
no no no s e v
are pv
party
go to
uh... national you know i'm gonna
screens go black for one second
because i'm gonna change uh...
and change some real quick
why do that
i'll be ready for about ten seconds and you'll see what my parents
well because for some reason when i was
doing excellent in the game mode it was like in my game a lot of life
sometimes i guess it does that
yeah are you using uh... it's like uh...
screen area
or the other one i was in the game source from the game that was like
lagging my games or
uh... try screen area
i'd add is that it's a nice change over
explicitly supposed to be like the release
uh... let's go to
because of the simple
because of all of our high tower i've heard zero out of
hopefully stuff gets back soon
allies is going to be a good trouble
to delay for him
when we were doing the test
i was using game source and it was working fine so it just seems like
on again off again
here it is that that's all i got still
that's it that's your only uh...
that's my only delay
right
delt
that are up
uh...
it so germa how things going over here today we go from pasting it
already got video and a stream just ballin like a youtuber does
straight ballin
right stealth really that's all i got now
now or never man right sixty eight dot two thirty two
dot one seven seven
dot one oh five
colon two seven zero
dean
sorry stealth you weren't here
but you missed out
that's the i think that those of you are wondering
and some of you know i don't think uh...
now he's not making it
there's no way he makes it
uh... and it and there's no way you make it here there's no way to make it
i was gonna say i have some bad news bears
dinner is ready with my parents and i should probably go eat dinner is served
let on like
throw me out of the song
all right well
see you later dude thanks for coming
do you know problem
uh... still i'm going to miss you but it makes me think about the spring is
making a mess
but i think
won't for uh... having a
see you guys later
i'd say that's a lot of those because i was me myself are you really get it's
just
you your uh...
itself
all right now
now who should have hosted
berber
and although i think i missed that so i can do it again and this again
i will play until you decide that you want to play a cisco and i will bow out
as well
thanks for coming off
tell my wife i said hello
hello wife
on the stream of the stream comment
why is delt why
still popular to be
so it could
the while
all this a lot of spice
that is what's going to a hundred feet in the air
that's optimus prime
is a mess around
i'm running away i'm running in the spot
you can't get the spot
or a text message
do you have a problem where like you hit him or something to change your
loadout and then it opens like
the options menu
uh... it does that sometimes yeah
just curious
that is an issue and i'm gonna die right here
that is an issue so i should get a tissue
you know what i'm gonna go straight up
no
i'm trying fire over a month of an
uh... great luck right now
uh...
all my god what is
what is going on with the avatars
what the hell is going on
why is everybody like a party
wait what
the hold on tab
for a second here
uh... is every single avatar pony for you
you know i don't mind in yours
uh... why
what and that's all i can see it
well that's uh... i have no idea
uh... everyone else in the street can see yourself so i think that's good man
no one has pushed our cart past the like spawn area here
i cannot even hit this person
you're getting
absolutely dominated are you going up track
where's his viral
god i'm doing so awful
all my goodness
no but it's a lot
stay alive
that act all right let's get on the start let's do this
right for some reason no one ever wants to go ahead
if you get backstabbed all the time
but what does that cart really all the way over there right all my god
come on coming
they have the cart all the way at that last point of you
kidding me
holy crap
yeah that was kind of thinking
how the hell did they get that there
i have no idea under my street by the guy who turns up
what's
blue team
uh... bravo
my god
with this with this insanity going on here
while
there was a spy idling in a corner and we were sitting there like pummeling him
for about ten seconds
biggest must have to stop on the cart
get the all-come-on
that's it we lost
game over
i can't
i can't help but not the stock in over
all of what i do what i do have it
well i don't
well that got
it on that dot
i am is i am as paranoid as it could possibly be right now
i can you know what
i was i was literally
i was turning around to check for a spy behind me and he got me
like i was
my most was
on my brain was telling my most to do that and like i got back
that's why i went by row and it's like spraying everywhere
but there's a lot to do that
paranoid what's up guys
you know i'm sorry and again that with the spy even though i was the fact that
again
all-white
god people are just everywhere
i don't have a sandwich
all i can get it they're gonna get it
during the play that's right now you're playing as uh... heavy
but we're all set
six shot
whoever that was
that that that's got off
germa do you know
do you know
now that i can't dance
that's a song right
i would think it
in the shower
uh... i'm not going to be on credit tonight
i'm going to be doing it
that's gonna be a lot of promise to straight-up video
probably next week
get out of here you're not dead
and i know you're not that i'm jumping away i'm gonna get
all of you
help of the white
spot check everybody in my team
whatever works
i see a pierced by
you little sniper you crazy little sniper
nice try on your stair step but it didn't work did it
that that that that that that was not by that that all dot
all-white
cover it up
the way
i'm going to go
heavy outstanding
but they're all on the
they're all on the car to say it was made over
all my god i don't know i don't
i just went through a fight pyro on only at least one
i think i got to eat this so i can run fast
uh... they're going to almost there
they're gonna get it so that means i can run away because i think this
there's three people on it
well they're definitely going to get it
that's how fast i'm running
but but but but but
you won't get the satisfaction of keeping it
uh...
actually kind of did
he got to get the satisfaction killed
too late
i am good now i have to
uh... do i go medic
i'm gonna let's like
i'm still too paranoid man just like
i'm spraying inside the
on the area that's how paranoid i am
now that's paranoid but
they all blew up
you are our spot
fairly i am dueling
but but but but but but but but
all but
what
i i don't know what you see happened i was like checking around to
i'm going to medic
best thing to do right now
uh... out out out out out
spot
i'm going to go to you about medic
and make sure everyone stays alive and i have my back to our entire time
do it man
the entire time
uh... we have two parts of the right now we like three earlier
people were just so paranoid
are you get
get caught up here
uh...
and it was by
cut away
it's always somebody out there
step-by-step
i can't believe it
how he's gonna kill me
god i'm a lucky son of a bitch
i got away
i'm i am on what is it on
bullshit no i don't want to do that
for a couple of people
i was like trade with somebody
do you know what is pushing our cart including myself
over the last
it's still like right there
he's still right there
right there it's fun man
actually be quite honestly that was
most success i've had all game
is with that matter
and i can i feel like two people
that you
uh...
uh... suicide medic
office guys toast
all of the time i think it's which i don't know how many spies are on their
team
to account it's it's got to be at least three
if it's not that i'm
i think that you know it pick up its group
quick fix
no trades
i don't take the trades right now
but that was a terrible starts now supposed to be a scottish accent guys
how terrible is that
that's fine
i am certain of this
no i guess i'm wrong
all barely got me
and i'm like getting people killed objected to spot car
tonight
you'll decide
they've got four pyros on our team now
the people they're listening to like
enough of this nonsense where i getting shot from i don't think that you know
if it's coming from
it's almost like they're coming out of our spot
i'm going to hire on easy mode right here i've got like the back burner so i
don't even have to think
spray
trying to use the uh...
fix fix
you know i'm gonna hear you was going to run up like the dickens
uh... right away
look at all the what
those are all spies
but i think that this is the worst thing ever
all-time but they are
it brought
all right
god do it
they're going to like the same heavy i'm glad i got up on plants by
we are trapped in the spawn area right now
where are you coming up from left right for a center
i'd keep all that because i'm a medic so track or the middle
that's a really just kill me so i can
get a backstab feel good about myself look at this look at this chaos
you gotta be
s i i can't say
i'm so upset
let's make let's make some statues
although i'm not
i want like your team
now he knows i'm a spy
uh... jeez
all right
i can't get up on the event
this is a
because forced to kill people
as soon as i said there were four
i was everyone's switch back on our team
who can always
man i get
blasted right there
all right after this we're going to another server
because
we need to scramble these teams
uh...
they've got a century gun right next to our cart
that's not cool
you know if you're also got all
what do you have
what you got
and they're already winning again
god down
hopefully so
all these ponies
you know what when all else fails
you just wish is at least
two people idling
well at least
when all else fails
you go straight-up demo night
and that don't work
i just speaking of your life
and that's what i just went
uh... well before you said that all right
jobs
and father
i'd just charged out of spawn
and i feel like five thousand people
well as
come on let's get them
it's all up to you
and he did it
he's a champion
artists there's a good respond right here
out-of-town
i got i got one of my last night
although i've got
uh... no
server change
time to change service
go to i want to go to the server we can win on
well i'm just kidding i want to go to a server
bold rush sounds good
are you ready
yes
the what's going on
seventy two
dot nine
dot one forty six
dot one eighteen
colon two seven zero one five go
you almost lost me on the colon but i think i got it
colin two seven zero one five
with the professor
what's the password with the best
that's a pretty easy password
deal with it
yeah i mean a
by you to password was one two three for a long time i'm sure
told me i had to change it
i don't drop due to spot what they said we went in there first how that how is
that possible
uh...
that's
sorry those of you that is that how does that make any sense
we were on our we were on our way in for a really good the game
well i apologize to those of you that just got into that server but uh...
exchange
so ninety eight
dot one five eight
dot eighty seven
dot two two six
colon two seven zero forty
right now i'm going to wait a second for a good stuff
if they're they're probably listening
yet but it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's like a ten
second delay though
yet still
there's there's somebody out there with this ridiculous internet speeds
yeah they can just
come pipeline
payload yesterday angel of that this is italics plane
you are correct
hey guys
a strange love
how's it going so this is the server
wait that
what way hold on a second
that already fill up
we are a full
i didn't know somebody else put it okay thank you to report that
appreciate
i thought you didn't join that's what i thought at first
this is like a jellyfish server
like the screen is more like a jellyfish for me right now
we don't like everybody is
look at this i feel like it's like
oh my god is claymation server
what's his name let me see what
well uh...
all look at that hangs mind goodness gracious
everyone except for me and you is like
a hundred plus
it really looks like a click stop motion animation
like that
all you know i'd like to put
so it feels like i'm playing at twenty frames per second but i'm not
but i'm not
uh... sorry guys
look at we got a change again because this is this bad
this is not this is not against the people who are here this is one of the
people who didn't get it
you know it's right if you don't even look at the street and see what what i
see right now it is like
pretty much like a watch in a cartoon on drugs
uh...
all right well how do you have looks like nobody could even get into this one
there's only
seven on eight
i apologize
i sorry
news service
take three
uh... third time's a charm
but i want
uh... to
uh... three crunch
so it's like it might might
it's not really a thirty two person server
hope i can
but it would tell i get that server will be okay
i want to serve all the cool kids have one
all right here we go
sixty-six dot fifty-five
dot one five four
don't two three four
colon two seven zero one
by
and we paste this in a second once we get in
i do apologize that we have to do this twice now is the third time
hopefully this one is going to be the
they pasted it in already
told you it it was like literally two seconds after you said i thought pop up
in the chat
as fast
well
lightning fast even you might say
you can say that
uh...
well
i'm going
demo night
give them actually found
uh... sorry what
as a demo mom i was just
uh... relaying what you just said
i actually found a sultan ceremonial the other day
i was very happy about that
so now i can have a legit demo night if i wanted to give up my grenade launcher
but
so tough call
for the for the booties
and we got steady
wicked sick at
so i have to do this right now
because somebody keeps sending me
very inappropriate
message and hopefully that stops that from happening
i don't think it will but i at least right
oh
we've got a full server now
good to go back out
just in time it's off the railway
everyone
also over at the same time
all my god you just
totally pretty aggressive
shot guns soldier
alike
did you see that
yeah
but i'd love to tonight
yeah i've only so far given one third of still waiting on two people so
eventually i will be giving
a hundred percent but i have to wait for the other two people to get back to me
that hurt
old yet i did quite a bit
someone on the other team is announcing how many spice they have therefore
apparently
what a good trader he is
uh... how ironic is that
so he's a double spot yes if he is it he's telling us about spying so he's
spying
on the spot
for his own spots
as someone in the comments will undoubtedly say
spy section
absolutely
problem is maybe he might be
more suspicious
maybe he's a triple spy
he said i served no one
he did
don't trust anyone
like i like your attitude
that's spying star
ticket ugly he's got a chance to step in i already know this
arin alice
but a lot of times
you are not a standard
you have to go that way
or cut the political
uh...
the
seen where
the old and all the other people bird by rolling around here at the back of my
when you're just
are you higher up
well they're almost a man they're right at the edge with seven minutes and forty
seconds to go we can do this we can do this come on i would have had i would
have
i would have
i was being sarcastic by the way
i don't know if that's how you spell it but that's what i'm doing
i love how the highest score
scoring
player on our team is four points it was like a four-way tie for four
me included
yeah four four four four four three
auto-scrambling the teams
well that's one way to do it
well
arts i don't know
on the bike with
you change your name
added
did you guess who i am
so i think that's not hard yes
because i can see uh... right
henderson incorporate
we sell carpets
floor finishing
where do you go up with your names you just look at something and say okay i'm
gonna take that
this is what i was in my brain at the at that particular second is what it is
i tried to high-five
so this is going to be the last round of tf-two and i'm going to move on to see
us go for a little bit
i gotta make a count then
or did you have to you have it right
i don't have cisco
that's what i was saying i'm gonna have to bow out when you switch games
it's going to have to play for about an hour so
still still has it but he
and he's i mean he needs to be eat i mean
he's eating macaroni and cheese and like dog food whatever he eats
it up don't you make me hungry man
macaroni and cheese and dog food
although i don't want to be
but over
oh my god that guy's killed
every single person
so stuff must be watching the straight
why is he responding
uh... strange what you said he's here
like he's even got to know that they at this parents
matches as it is a laptop
i should have done the book and i really should have
all man
i can't talk about
all of a cool if i had that go off
just get the teleportable terrible
you should be on the winning team now
although it might be a few bastards
i can't believe it turned around
how about i just did too crazy i think i don't think that what the hell it's
going on
i just played it like six
it's in the sky
holy crap
that was ridiculous i've never seen that happen
both hammering on the other guys
we got a great story now
and
all there's four demo man
them a bit of a thing no wonder
i'd like to say that the women's life
but not really
right for sure
for sure
no
uh...
is a really bad idea has been around for
that you know
come on
all
uh... that is that sad to face in
that is that they said
but i had an explosion kill
could have what it should have
i'm trying my hand all you guys are about to win you got like
three pyros back here just camp in our spawn hardcore really
uh... man never want to have
let's do some crazy rocket jumps here
here comes rocket i think i got like one kill
do you have to do a job that's we go back
i did some job that's a little
all rights on the street said
germa place
play tribes ascent
what they said
and i'm making that up
uh... i think it's the i think it's a uh...
c s go just had a big huge crazy update
go and check that out
but the answer your questions in the comments
tried to send this free play
so it is
and it's now
totally open it's not invade anymore it is out now
it's out
it's going to release it is fun
so that's uh... i'm going to move on from
tf2 now
played about an hour cf2
so before i go i have to tell you it
have to do something to stupid and this here we go let's go up a spy
and i'm going to just
this is this is the goal here guys the goal is
to try
and blend in with the other team
so it's gonna be hard to lose
people watching the stream but this could be interesting i want to try to
do this at least once
why is there a floating scout
stuff here
oh no i missed the high five
so they get the the goal here is to try and blend in let's see how well i do
see how well i do
are we going to stop them
come on get them
all my god they're coming the cut because upside down what the hell is
going on with that
is a sign that we must get them
all right
although they're they come the coming out of the right door now it's
no i'm gonna all you figure me out
that i don't even think
again is going to build my stuff right here
it's going to build some stuff i'm trying to build my uh...
by teleporter my century it's all good stuff
let me just uh...
build that up thank you for the overview of by the way i don't think
it's not here
i guess you know i got
all i gotta get back to my post
these bastards they've ruined everything
no one can't do it
all my god i got i gotta get back to my century but if i could build my century
well that is that's me right there
okay cool
uh... sniper
and here we go on this night
all right let me get back my sniping post
here we go
just like another any team is coming out here watch out guys be careful
let me slide with you
uh... who's the real one was getting right next to each other all you got me
shits
all
road bike
that's what i get angry
uh... right that's uh...
that's going to be actually i'll i'll run the uh... around out why not
why not as disguise as an enemy
sniper it's the best way to do it
and just sit in the corner
be like oh i'm sorry
uh... try to get the three hits
uh... cradle crit with the
complete almost got it off
it's it's really satisfying
uh... you didn't get me
uh... uh...
all
come on
no no
okay good good
let me get my sliding skills
i found an ambassador
i don't have an enforcer really difficult come on
just try to snipe
but if you guys don't stop spam chat most are blocking some people
knowledge of
they followed me out again
uh... we get the the wrath of the bar coming down
uh...
that's my last life
that i'm moving on to uh...
counter
stevenson
great opportunity
i'm tell you how you have taken the teleporters by
at level two of a real bad bastard of a real bastard look at this
level two teleporter i'm taking it as a spy what a jerk
i wonder if i can uh...
just killed people up from up here
all for the love of god
i just can't get the mail it
uh...
well that's what the worst engineer ever
i can't bring my spread
that's not cool
but yeah i don't have a spray i need to
be a cool one
i am going to change to saw cisco
swing of this guy over and over again
always one more life
yeah this is really the last life
i'm not this is not a joke no more no jokes this is the last one
i have to back said at least one person
and that's not the guy apparently
and that's not the guy either
going to be not that i think that's it
now i can't accept anybody
might as well pretend
all of it
you have to pretend there i am
mom get that night but all my god
that's the end for me
uh... that's a play does to you
uh... we want to since you know it's a go-go
you know what i'm losing every round
i'm the only common denominator here so i take full responsibility for that
i've been on every losing team so far
my bad guys
my bad
well at least uh...
at least you got
play on
the crazy
teams that would
getting beat
uh... i didn't that what's uh...
you're reaching for that one that really was actually i was doing two things at
once my brain was kinda like where where am i am streaming
so i play like a three two three rounds of cisco
just to check out the new update that one check it out
so screen is going to go black
in a second here
and uh... thank you for coming here
just gave it to you
if you stick around to see us go then it's gonna happen like
four seconds well not really but
you get the idea
screen is going to go black
in
screen is totally not like bro
or not because
now it's black
no it's not
now it's not a lot of that's not because i did screen region forgot
i pulled up the screen region
now it should be on
probably in the summer
get into windowed boat
uh... cheese okay anyways guys it's been fun
thanks for owning me
time and time again
it's how i get my kicks
but i'm just kidding it was a lot of fun
and uh... enjoy
see us go i will uh... catch you guys later
thanks for coming man
always a pleasure
going into region
and ha!
okay
let's play a couple rounds let's see what they did
huge updates let's find out exactly what they did
in this update
uh... uh... uh... i've watched south park
i used to love south park
back in the day
it's one of my favorite shows
that's right they did add a server bro i gotta check that out
if i can even get in here
still searching huh
let's try this again
find a game
there we go
retrieving data
yeah i'm probably only going to play
maybe two or three rounds maybe
ten twenty minutes or so i just want to check out the new update to be honest
okay so this is the new map no maybe not this is not one of the new maps is it
i think i've already seen i've already seen no maybe not
maybe it is a different map
we'll find out won't we
trying to pick up a headshot damn
so this is one of the new maps safe house
there already is another one like this isn't there
this game is not free to play it is in beta right now
it's in closed beta
alright i gotta stay alive next time
no more screwing around
and the terrorists won
will they be punching pie
i can't we can't buy
why can we not buy items
i thought that's what it said you could do
i'm gonna go around this way
see if i can't
pull something off here and i don't want to climb up there that's a bad idea
now i just saw somebody
there we go
all i'm dead
all dot
find these behind me
it's done bombs down here
it's only one of them left
you know that's a teammate
henderson cooperated for most of the nation's
uh... we got my name is henderson incorporated
the clickety clack
at this game will do that
you'll get a big clickety clack
but somebody popped ahead of the i have any grades
nobody nobody oh my god i'm getting stuck
he's right here
well well well well
that's hanging out of a window
that was legit like
floating out of the window
what do you think i don't like this car
auto is upstairs right now he is uh...
i think he's created in the kitchen the honest
can see some he's a wild dog
somebody tells everybody
who's also
auto is my uh...
my little dachshund chihuahua
doberman pincher breed thing
he's a real cute
i don't play league of legends
too much for my brain to handle
i feel the same way about week as i do about starcraft
and that is
is already
teammates are now i guess in a forever
i feel the same way about legal status starcraft is starcraft is
is everyone's is really really good
to be able to play that game you have to also be really really good
that by probably won't be playing that game anytime soon
well this is dot or just sit here
i'm going to play gone game after next round
is gone games more action
and i can actually pretty good at going to
see that this is this game or not that good at
that the general
c s go i'm not that good at you know we're going to play a game right now
to me
finding
arms race
don't matter which one that's the plate
it's not gone game
sure is
gone gay
don't mean arms or arms races the
technical term for it
i love this map
it's so interesting
you're like a row i love the girls man
favorite bands
by far
from behind off
it's right here
finally moving on moving on the world
all this to any of them
boom boom
that keep in mind i'm playing this in a window
like half the size of my computer screen
so it can be kind of difficult to play this game
how many bolts does it take
no i don't want to do that
al
right
uh...
yeah i i wish my computer was good enough to
play games in full screen and stream them
but it is uh... it is almost impossible to do that
and i'm i'm getting destroyed
my god
the whole team is like eighteen fourteen and this way i'm going this way
town
you know that has shot god damn
yes not the it's not my internet it's uh...
my computer just
probably would not be able to handle it
and i guess internet to
to stream at like ten eighty
or seven twenty it takes a lot of them so
now i was i don't
that this this potentially is the worst i'd like the worst game i've ever had in
this entire game ever
like ever
uh...
is making me look
embarrassed now i don't care
i'm just playing for fun as much a company stuff
my favorite guerrillas song is
probably style
i love style
i don't know that i even was
al
let's get a string of people together
now it's already got it
uh...
uh... seven fifteen
flip that score out and you got a great score
at this time to be different
this time will be different
you need to pray to the bruins
all-powerful bruins gods
please
shine upon me your strength
my sensitivity might be wrong
no it's not
that's an excuse
that's just an excuse
keep the ball rolling here
mercy up top or or
uh... get away
get away
old and well when you come from
when that do would come from
uh... going for the headshots
not get them
pb ninety and one
i think that's what i just said
this is the shoot guns all and i cannot go that way
i'm gonna wrap around this way
no how is he not
die
look at his health
what i even hit him with like a sock
i don't know i don't understand that i have like in eighty percent health
and i have a little wet sock apparently
she's like
god
that's instead of every single time
not that i guys that i was invincible
how's that i just invincible
somebody explain that to me
there we go get out all
no longer die
invincible
on predictable
we've talked
see buddy where they spawn
where the hell are you guys
uh...
as puked in my mouth
i don't know if i go across the map they did this is like spawned over here
my face in your face
uh...
this guy's twenty and nine right now
my god
what
that's too many of them
at least one of the number one of the team
did did did did did did did
stop puking
that took a while
at least one of all positive
that's all i care about
is going positive
about being freaking out right now
this guy's gonna get a knife level in two seconds
yes gold
uh... hurts to die in this game
where's everybody
that did not kill that guy
all my god spawning right next to me
sponsor wacky in this game
people just like up here next to you
uh... light machine guns
now come on
no somebody long