What if I just turn the stream on, turned it off, waited five minutes, turn the stream on, turn it off, wait five minutes, turn the stream on, turn it off, wait five minutes, and then did like a 72 hour stream after that.
Would it be like the boy who cried wolf? Would people be like, all right, fuck this, I'm out of here. Like you missed the 72 hour stream. Hi. Oh, I didn't tweet. There we go. Today we're going to finish Dead Rising. And those of you that were here last night.
Oh, I'm ready. I've prepared. I have multiple timelines in case something goes wrong. This is doable. I'm ready. I spent some time making sure I was ready. It's got to be good. It's got to be perfect, but it's doable.
I looked at the map. I planned out a route to save as much time as possible. I have a save point right in front of the boss essentially. And I got the blue chainsaw with about 17 minutes to go. It's got to be good. It's got to be perfect, but I can do it. I'm planned. He cheated. No, I didn't cheat. I just after the stream turned off. I got some food. I came back upstairs. I was ready. I was getting tired, but I was like, you know what, let me.
Let me plan out some routes and see if this is humanly possible. I tried one timeline that didn't work out so well. I went and got an Uzi and try it. Nope. Not possible with that one. I tried to go through a shortcut. Didn't happen. I spent about 45 minutes to an hour to get it right. And I got it right. Show your face. Why would I do that? He played off stream. You don't play off stream. And my control was fixed. I got that taken care of too.
To see your tired eyes. I don't want you to see my dark circles under my eyes. No, I'm playing Dead Riley. You owe us that content. Why is my face content? Imagine somebody sends you like you go to like Disney World or something with like your family. And you go through the photos afterwards and you show it to like the grandkids that weren't, that couldn't go. And they're like, this is some good fucking content.
It's nice content. I could see both your faces. You got any more content? What do you want? Just a close up of your face. Okay. Got any more? Face cam. No, I don't do face cam. You know that. I do it like once in a while. I don't like it. I don't like it. You do it all the time. Yeah, but when I don't want to do it, I'm not going to do it. So what's going to happen is after about 25 minutes, I'm going to get pressured.
It's turning it on. And then you're going to get a shitload of content. Here we are. Content, please give us some content. No, the reason why everybody wants face cam so bad is because on the off chance that like snot like a booger shoots out of my nose and into my mouth. It's on camera. And it's like I have that now forever. That's why and that's happened probably a few times since I've streamed. I've like accidentally squirted mustard in my eye on stream, but I wasn't on camera. So it's like not a thing that you have clipped.
That's by design. You already slapped yourself. There's nothing to lose. I've probably done that more than once too. All right, here we go. We're going to get going on Dead Rising. I we're in the current timeline. You ready? I have to be very, very, very good about this. So I'm going to let's see if I can do it. I planned it 123 already fucking walked into a wall.
Just kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Just kill me. Kill me. This is not in the right save file. Where is the right save file? I told you I was ready. That means I was doable. Where's the one where I actually have to do it? Oh, did I save over it? Day two. See, I'm I told you I got by it. I got by it. I needed to make sure it was possible. I read on a forum somewhere that even if you beat Isabella, the game will still end if you don't have enough time. So I needed to make sure that that wasn't going
to happen. I played for like an extra four minutes. Okay. Which one of these is it? 2328? 2311. Might be this one. Let me try this one. Wait, it's one of the 20s. It's not this one. 2331 day two. 23. It might be this one. It's not this one. Is it this one? No, it's the wrong one. Where am I? Fuck. This is the wrong one. Where is the actual save file? Is it save two?
Save two is level 21. No, it's I have the chainsaw right out front of her door. Did I just not give a fucking save and not care that I beat her? Was I that irritated by this point that I was like, I don't care. I'm just saving it. That may have happened. I think that may have happened. 2245. No, that's way far away. 2311. It might be this one here. Is this it? I think this is it. This is it. This is it. This is it. Okay. So you
guys I Mario maker the level. It's possible. I just want to prove to you that it is. But the thing is I still have to beat this on screen for you to prove it to you. And I'll be honest with you. It was a huge pain in the ass. I was so angry trying to do this even with chainsaw. But it's possible because you've seen the future. Okay, here we go. Fuck. I have to do it perfect. Otherwise, I'm not gonna do it. I blew it already have to do it again. You have to like turn and swing turn and swing. I still might be able to do it. What time is it? I have
five minutes to do this. What? What? I lost. Yeah, it's all right. I got I swung through her for four times. What do you even fuck this? Yeah, let's pretend I've been here all night. I'm going to talk with a good fucked up voice. You already would get a good grab a good grab radius.
All right, here we go. No, I think if I honestly, I think I just have to be perfect with it, and then I'll be able to get it once I it's back swing back swing. When she drives by you, you have to back swing or is no you're not gonna be able to hit it. Okay. I'm sorry, guys.
Yeah, you have to get Yeah, no, no jokes aside, you just have to get lucky to like that like that like that like that like that like that. Whoa, my voice is back. Hello. Hey, whoa.
Don't I have to hit her one more time? Come on. Don't you fucking dare. I need to prove I did a Mario maker this. Oh my god, I hate this encounter more than anything. This is so stupid. All right. I lost. I didn't do it fast enough. Game over. Yeah, that's how stupid this is. I did it too late. Okay, you saw me killer. I don't care. You still have to do it. The truth got snapped. So it's did you see how possible it is? I
just have to do it. And if somebody grabs me, it's not possible anymore. Not possible anymore. It's not possible anymore. No, I have to just I have to get all the hits. You just have to get lucky and spam the chainsaw on her for me to do this. And it is it's possible because I
already have it done. So I ain't getting stuck here. I'll watch the fucking cutscene on YouTube. I don't give a shit. Get the fuck out of here. I did. You know how many times I did this off street? So much more painful than you could possibly imagine.
I didn't have that chainsaw. I tried to run to the chainsaw. I tried the submachine gun. You guys have no idea. This is actually attempt number like probably 70 or 80 in total.
He has all the answers. Carly don't you're talking about that guy that took potshots at us with a sniper rifle, aren't you? Who take me to him? No, not now. He's injured and in no mood to talk to anyone. I'll bring him to you once he's recovered. I hope I don't die here. I can persuade him. I'm his little sister after all. Why should I trust you to bring him to me? The zombies are a message from Carlito.
What does it say? He's saying, look at me.
Wait for us in the store next to the camera shop in the North Plaza.
Why do you have gunner optics on? Those two not even remotely look like gunner optics. They're just like regular sunglasses.
And I promise I'll come back.
All right, I did it. And that case is done. Case number five coming up from 12 a.m. on September 21st. The next case will occur at 12 a.m., which is in like 40 minutes. Hey, and it's a promise to Isabella. You've already seen that because I cheated. Well, I didn't just where I stopped last time. I was like, all right, but let me paint you a picture. No, Don, no paintings. I got a I wouldn't even admit it. No, I can let me paint a picture for you.
If I didn't like have a point where this was saved, and this was like I soft locked myself somehow. You know how angry I would have been? All right, I don't want to die. So that's important. So give me a board. I don't want to use my chance. So let's go. I only have to keep this timeline secure. I can I have to go here quick. I only have how long? Okay, I've got 30 minutes until I fail again.
Does somebody fuck with my screen brightness last night? All right, here we go. I have to go in here. And I need to be in here for the next 30 minutes. It's 12. All right. So welcome, everybody. Yeah, why is my screen brightness so low? Save the game? No, I can't because if I have to be here when this the clock strikes 12. I have to stay right here. Oh, it is my antique shop. I'm not going to be able to make that. Close the door. Can you close? Okay.
I spotted a guy in the cosmetics shop in the entrance plaza. It looks like he's trying to get out of there. But someone's taking shots out of save the old man. Look at how much time there's left. That's like two minutes. No, I have to secure the timeline. I have in game. This amounts to like 45 seconds. Let's let's let's find out how long is 15 minutes in game? What? How long is 10 minutes in game? We can find this out. Okay, five seconds is one minute. There you go. I'm wasting time. No, I'm in the exact
place I need to be. He's stalling. Whatever. That's fine. I ain't messing this up. Practice by swing. This is not the wrong store. I'm waiting. All right. It's almost midnight. And here we go. See? I told you I knew what I was doing. Zombie. Zombie. Oh, no, no, don't fuck it up. What? Okay. I know jokes that I don't have any time for that. If she dies, I have to do the whole thing again.
Did I do that? You dislocated my shoulder and I'm missing seven teeth. Okay, this is where we go. Case five two engaged. Save the game. Do you wish to override a save? I do. Okay, so I'm gonna let's just go ahead and say just for the record, if I fail this, I have
and I have a complete exit strategy. Understand? I was prepared. I wasn't fucking around today. So I'm gonna go up to the top. Number one. That looks good to me. Who cares? I have to do it. It is saved there. Number one. I have to get you somewhere safe. I never meant to shoot you. It's just like we never meant to shoot you. Can I give you anything? Can you take me out? No, you can't take anything. Can you? No, I just
have to carry you, right? Let's go. And then I remember this. Hello, Kendall. It's nice to see another human being around here. Well, alive one at least. I have to put you down because it's just follow me. Let's go. You're looking for a place to meet real live people. I know a place. Nice Isabella. The security room safe. What am I supposed to do there? Be safe. Sitting around a locked room. We both have the same idea. There's a helicopter coming to get us. I
why can't we just talk? Walk and talk. That's the one thing I don't understand. It's coming. I guarantee it. Trust me. All right, I suppose I could check this place out. Okay, good. You have a shotgun. So you need to be my you got to be my guy. He doesn't really aim very well from the cheating timeline. Let's go. You have to take the shots. In fact, just I can't command you because Isabella is on my back, but I need you to take some shots here. Very thank you. Keep going.
This way. Go across the phone. Keep going. Come on. Go, go, go, go, go. Don't stop. Is this pre-recorded? No, if this is actually the pre-recorded one, I killed Kendall and took his shotgun. Because I just wasn't going to wait around for it. So this isn't this isn't a new timeline. Let's go. Shoot. You still with me? Jerma, say the word slime if it's not pre-recorded. It's not pre-recorded. What? How? When would I have the time to pre-record this? Can you imagine doing yesterday's stream?
And then where am I going? Oh my god, I went the wrong fucking way. So after yesterday's stream, I just kept playing and then like what I just like pass out or something and just uploaded this. Yes. I have to take the shotgun from him before I deliver them to their destination.
Face cam will prove recorded. It has not been 25 minutes yet. Yes, the stream has been live for 25 minutes, but I have not been playing the game for 25 minutes. So sorry. Shaking my head. S.M.H. Shaking my head. Come on, Kendall. Easy, easy, easy. Bait him out. Bait him out. Nice shooting. Actually not that good. This way. Get close enough where I can open the door. Close enough where I can open the door. All right, we're good. Keep it up. Hug the right side.
Zombies on the right side. I need a shotgun shot right here. I need a shotgun blast right here. One more. One more. Another one. Another one. Shoot. Get back, back, back, back, back. No, no, no, no, no. Come here. Go. Don't get stuck. Kendall. Uh oh. Not good. Not good. I could use a chainsaw for this one. He's getting his ass kicked. Hold on. Stay there. Come on. Move. Keep going. Let's go. No. Why would you push me? Jokeless stream. It's going to stay that way until I am secure.
And then I promise I'll tell you like a funny joke. This is not secure. I'm in the same timeline as I was before. This is incredibly, incredibly difficult. I remember reading on the forums, people saying the part where you have to transport Isabelle. Oh my God, man. It was so hard for me when I was 14. Because that person wrote that when they were 14 because it was in like 2006. All right, let's go up. Oh my God. This is the part. I read about this part. She doesn't get up. Come here. Dirk.
You jerk. Almost there. Good. All right. Almost safe. Almost. I say that very, very loosely. Don't. Why? I saw that in slow motion. Okay. Shoot somebody. Just come to the door. Oh my God. Give me the shotgun. Okay. Now. Here. Do you want a nail gun? I'm telling you. You're better off with this. Give me that. Okay.
Shoot me with it. You can walk, can't you? Just a little bit. I think she can walk. No. All right. Use that nail gun effectively, please. The reason I have the shotgun is because when the elevator door opens, I need to make sure it is clear. Thank you. Good. Nice. You're much better. You're more of a precision guy than a just launch weapon guy. All right. Let's go. Isabelle, come on. Come on, Kindle. Okay. This is important. Important. I don't know why I thought that was a zombie.
All right. This is here we go. Over here. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't give that back. Get that back. You stand right here. Give that back. This is it. One, two, three. And got that. This is that was a stressful part because look at the time. Okay. Well, now let's talk about something funny. Where's that fucking content?
Webcams are not even plugged in.
I don't want to plug it in. My crashed computer. Not enough like bus spaces on the motherboard. It'll crash.
Okay. There were some nonbelievers here that didn't think I was going to do it.
I stayed in the post stream chat last night and I saw somebody wrote a paragraph and they were like, he's not going to be able to do this guys. He's going to be kind of upset about this. He's going to be like pissed off.
Should we need to tell him that he can't do it? And then I stayed up for four extra hours and didn't case five complete case six starts at three a.m.
I got a couple of hours. Done. 50,000 pp. 21 sounds familiar. Doesn't it? Take a photo of them. Got it. I got to make. Wait, hold. Very important. Now the timeline is actually secure.
I need to go to the picture viewer. Save that one. That's a good one. All right. I need to save some of these pants is still there. Okay.
Okay. But like the rock bottom off the Titan Tron is like perfect, but I don't think this one is. I can get, I'm going to get rid of this one. Keep pants. No, this was just like weird. I like that one. Okay.
Why? Okay. Wait, this one too. When he's running, that's a good one. That one. Never forget Ronald and the fat lady. Which one's better though? Yeah, that was pretty good.
They're both good. That one's not that good. All right. I think I'm good. Where's the pants photo? It's right here. I'm okay with that. So now I got a little bit of time here. I can photographer surprise. Do I have? Okay.
Three a.m. I have just about one hour, which is like 20 minutes game time at 15 minutes game time, something like that. Do I have enough time to do it? Save it first.
I wonder if there's enough time to be back here in 15 minutes. Change slot. This is going to be now. This is the real one. So this is slot two. Okay, sick. I don't know why I just thought this had game sucks. When it got to the first see, I'm like, what the fuck is going on?
All right, photographers pride. I need to be. Let's see if I can get there. I have a good shotgun. Explore the roof where the elevator is. I'll do that. Well, there's a button there. Okay, what about this way?
So explore the roof. Anything up here? Face cam. Now it's been 25 minutes. That's not true because I've I had to rewind two or three times in different safe slots. So we've only been like 17 or 18 minutes on the real actual game.
Anything over here? I don't see anything this way. Can I get up on top of the roof? I feel like I can get up there. Hmm. He hates his viewers. He's just finding right now this out. MonkaS. I'm sorry, I could do that better. MonkaS. I can't just stand this up. I can't jump up that. Slime him. I don't think I can do anything about this.
Warehouse. I'll take the call. It's kind of weird, but there's a group of freaks and raincoats gathered in Colby's movie land. They're wearing matching masks, too. And they're really giving me the creeps. I've noticed I already know who these people are. I noticed stop calling me on my novelty soccer ball phone.
I've been up here before, but I mean, they're the toolbox. What can I do with the toolbox? Anything cool? Fuck it. Wait, what was in there? Sawz? Ooh, that's cool. Sludge hammer. Soccer ball. I'll keep the soccer ball for like a funny moment. Keep the oops. Well, I got to be back here anyways. I can do photography sprite again in a little bit. There are actually sawz here though. All right, sawz. Get off of me. Yeah. Okay. You know how some things in games.
Just something about them. The way they happen. The animation and the damage. For some reason, the you get grabbed and bit by a zombie just makes me angry. It's just every time it happens, I'm just like, fuck out of here. Soccer ball. What was that? What was that noise? You guys hear that? That little like, yeah, I'm just gonna get back up here. A strange group. I still have time. All right.
Do I have any supplies? Let me have a couple. I have a squash. Just eat it. My supplies aren't bad. You didn't do anything. Well, I just, I checked out the, somebody said, check out the roof. You can't really do anything in like 10 minutes. All I can do is sit here. Check out the roof again. I know I can, I have to be back here in like six, I have to be here in like five minutes. It takes five minutes to go down the elevator and like out the door. It's been 25. Caving. The definition of the word cave. A small dugout.
On clove. Inside of a rock. Making a dark, damp space. Other definition. Being forced to turn on your face cam on twitch.tv. Verb. I don't even know where this is. I have like wicked bad villain here today too, so you guys will love that. Okay. I just have to wait here. It's desynced. What do you want to do about it? All right. It shouldn't be desynced anymore. Patrick Bateman.
Why is my water wicked cloudy? Do you see this? Look at this. It's really cloudy.
Tastes like the lime juice I squeezed in it.
MDMA water?
Wait, Dr. Barnaby is going to be turned.
Oh wait, no, he's just normal.
Shotgun head. Shotgun head. Shotgun head.
I did go kind of all the way to the end there. Like shotgun head?
You could kick him.
Shotgun head. No, shotgun. This is not good. Now you gotta listen to me.
Dude, shut. No, shotgun head. I think I was right.
Stop drinking bong water.
I'm not drinking bong water.
Yes. Dishwater soap. You guys are going to come up with all these ideas.
Why is he, he's got like these like golem, the cryptkeeper eyes right now.
Accidentally made zombie livestock.
Get it out, Doc. Come on.
So the government's now in the zombie making business.
The whole story about the drug trade was a cover-up.
What do you know?
If I'm like dying or turning or if like something's happening, I'm going to say everything as fast as I can.
Because what if you died?
I would give you, I would say, I would even have heard, I'd scream as loud as I could.
It's true.
At this point you're acting, you know what I mean?
You could be like, the research was necessary.
We had to do it because everyone's eating too much meat and we're trying to, we just.
That so is absolutely necessary.
No, you would get it out as fast as you could.
And then you'd be like, the antidote's in the fridge, in the fridge in the upstairs bathroom.
The fridge in the upstairs bathroom. Get the antidote.
Why do they make it so cryptic?
The only way you'll ever survive is if you find the cure that I've hidden.
Just tell them, like tell them.
Where is the antidote? You know where it is. Just say it.
Just say it to the, just say it to his face.
Just get it out.
If I'm ever in a position where it's like a zombie apocalypse and I know where something is.
Everyone's going to know.
That would be bad though because it would be like a huge fight to get to the antidote.
How much antidote? Why do they always make one like vial?
Why don't you make like fucking 75 gallons of the antidote?
Why is it in a vial this big?
Is this like my like coping mechanism to be like, I'm in the camera?
Okay.
That was fucked.
It had to have gone through my head too.
The camera is going to just fall forward and it's going to be a bullet through my head.
There's no way that goes straight.
The lens is an indicator.
The terrorism is a retaliation for a cruel government cover-up.
Sounds plausible.
Or it could be some serious bullshit in either case.
We have to get out of here alive.
Where's my bomb?
We have to check if she's been bitten. Let me take a look.
Oh, she's been bitten many times. I've seen it.
I'm a medical technician. I could be useful if you let me do my job.
I've watched her get bit like at least a dozen times.
I know I have no right to ask, but please let me help.
If you don't get out of here, the truth dies with you.
Why is that always the stance when somebody's lying on the ground and sitting on the ground?
They do this.
They put their knees up like this and they go like this.
It's in every game.
The knees up, legs to the side and like the arm here.
This is not comfortable.
What do you mean it's comfy? No, it's not.
Sit like that.
Lean against a wall.
That's not comfortable.
Why don't you just sit against the wall like this or like this?
With your arms like this.
Or fetal position.
It's like you're about to go to fetal position, but you're like stopping halfway for some reason.
I don't know why.
The game crashed.
Next case will occur at 11 a.m.
Here we go. Let's just save it.
Maybe in that same slot right here.
Right here.
All right. Now I get time.
A strange group. I got plenty of time now.
Timeline secured. We're safe.
Let's go to a strange group.
It's free roam time.
What was the intel on this one?
I need to get food too.
You're in the worst spot.
Save? I just did.
The game just saved.
Oh, I could do the gun shop too.
Where is the strange group?
Remember I walked in the gun shop and there was that weirdo in there?
All right. Here's the plan.
The plan is to do the skip.
Where's the strange group?
I don't remember what it said.
All right. I'm going to get the chainsaw.
And then I'm going to go up to the gun store.
And then I'm going to come back down.
Give me the sledgehammer.
All right.
So now I'll get chainsaw.
I need to have this. This is important.
When I don't have the chainsaw, I do not feel safe.
I got plenty of time.
I got a lot of time to run around.
Let's go.
Oops.
No.
You all did the same move at the same time.
All right. Fuck it. Just leave them.
Oh, that felt good.
Stringer.
Check out Dead Rising 2.
I've actually played Dead Rising 2 in co-op, but we didn't make it out of the elevator, I don't think.
I don't remember playing that game past the elevator.
Me and Star played it.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I think we didn't get out of the tutorial room.
Let's go to the point there.
I could go to the gun store.
Movie Plaza is...
It was like the actual movie plaza.
Paradise Plaza.
All right. I'm going to go up from here.
I'm going to save it. I'm going to go to the gun store.
I think that's a good idea.
So it was this way, right?
Yes.
Question marks of scoops.
All right. Well, that's fine.
I got to get guns.
I don't want handguns.
It won't take long.
Like this is not a gun.
This thing sucks.
This is fun to shoot.
And did I pass it?
I did. God damn it.
This is what happens when I just walk and talk.
Eat boogers. Eat boogers.
Wait, what the hell am I doing?
No, no, go back.
I'm just saving the game in here.
Not going all the way back.
Eat boogers.
I'm trying to like navigate.
Imagine you were driving somewhere
Eat boogers. Eat your boogers.
Eat your boogers. You're going to miss your exit.
All right. It's happening again.
All right. Straight up.
Just don't read.
That's true. That's a good idea.
But it's compulsive. I have to look over here.
What did I just do?
I did not want to pick that guy up in like a fucking scoop slam.
And now I have no help.
This is great.
Is there any? There's a grocery store right here.
I'm going to hit up the grocery store
and then the back this way to the gun.
And then we'll go from there.
I don't want to use this yet.
I also want to get a book for this thing.
For the chainsaw.
It's the tools book.
So I got to go to the bookstore too.
Eventually I got time.
I don't need to rush.
Pause for the special moves.
I can't. I don't have any time to pause.
What?
I have a motorcycle now.
All right. This is important.
I need to eat a bunch of food to fill up.
I can ride the motorcycle.
All right. Is there any like orange juice?
Is it better food here?
Besides just the junk on the shelves?
I don't want to eat melons.
I mean I will, but I don't want to.
Queen?
Shit. Where?
Right there.
Give me the queen.
Oh God. It's.
Are you all just standing on it? Where is it?
Where's my indicator?
Where's the fucking queen?
Get it!
All right. Frozen food aisle.
Two queens.
Can I eat frozen pizza?
Oh, I can eat uncooked pizza.
How much does it heal?
Only two.
Oh, I'm so sick of you motherfuckers.
I swear to God.
Get the fuck away from me.
All right. I'm going to eat.
I'm going to take.
Get rid of this.
Two uncooked pizzas.
That should be all right for a little bit.
Wait, is there wine here?
Chat, tell them about the wine.
Condiments?
Meats?
It just triggers an automatic hatred response.
Back here?
I don't want to use this though.
I don't want to overuse this.
Oh, fuck. There is wine back here.
Holy shit. Okay.
Get rid of this too.
One, two, three.
Three wines.
Three wines, chainsaw, shotgun.
Two queens.
Let's go.
Why am I taking my eyes off the exit?
Curse.
Where I'm just like, all right, I got it.
It happened.
I'm in my demonstration.
Okay, I'm good.
You hate streaming.
No, get off.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I need a safe point.
Can I ride this?
How do I ride it?
Okay, it's right trigger.
This is so fast.
All right, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Which is this way.
Gunshot. So come out here.
Bang it left.
Straight down the little narrow hall.
You got it.
Okay, down here.
No, wrong narrow hall.
A little bit further.
Where is it?
Fucking missed it.
Oh, God.
Hello?
Not the same guy in there.
I took a lot of bullets though.
I took hundreds of bullets into my body.
Why would they do that?
So I'm not going in there.
I'm not going in here.
You have to shoot them from outside the store.
It's impossible.
Wait, hold on.
What did you say?
It's this one, right?
So I'm going to use the shotgun.
Where's the motorcycle?
I didn't walk by it, right?
It drove off.
Instant fucking anger every time.
He's going to grab me.
Okay.
Here we go.
Down this way.
So you tell me I have to, I can't go in here.
Well, there's zombies everywhere.
What if I have the gun ready?
Will that make a difference?
Look at how many people are out here.
This is like fucking ridiculous.
What?
These guys aren't affected?
It's like, guys?
What do you mean, Alyssa defected?
She already was defected.
She's fucking killing me.
I'm so confused.
What do you mean, she's friendly?
What do you mean, wrong one?
Get me out of the store.
Out of the store.
He's shooting.
Why can it stun lock?
What the fuck?
Hello, anybody in here?
What?
Read this.
That was inhuman.
What if I walk away?
Will he see me and run out?
I have to do it again.
Holy fuck, I just annihilated him.
What is he doing?
Where's my chainsaw?
No, I need to be behind him.
What's going on?
What do you mean, he defected?
What?
Oh, the sign's gone.
New sign, I need a new sign.
Like a dad playing.
Just kill me so I can do it again.
It's physically impossible to go in the store.
So, shoot them from the outside.
I'm going to run out of ammo.
This guy just stun locked me forever.
They're friendly.
I walked in and they fucking started shooting at me.
Go in and go out.
I scared them?
Because I'm holding the fucking chainsaw?
Kill the crowd outside.
We're going this way.
Yes, we are.
To be fair, you're barefoot and running around with the chainsaw.
But there's zombies everywhere.
This is not out of the ordinary.
I'm going to kill the crowd outside.
I don't want to use all this though.
It's the only thing I fucking have.
Plus, it's a gun shop, so I should be okay.
What?
Usually there's like all the raincoat guys out here.
Dude, for being shitty zombies, they sure can hold the fuck on.
Like they lumber around like they have no idea where they're going.
But they have these like fucking like landscaper hands to just like grab onto it.
I have alcohol.
Here he comes.
Brett, here comes another one.
Are you breathing?
I wasn't supposed to know that was going to happen.
There's a helicopter coming.
It'll be here on Friday.
I thought you might want to ride.
Where is it supposed to land?
There's zombies everywhere.
And a heliport on the roof.
Just fall away.
But the security room is sealed tight.
A dead end.
I saw it.
I know what I saw.
There's a duct on the roof of Paradise Plaza.
I just gave everybody all the info, huh?
Okay, so.
What? What happened?
What the fuck is going on?
What do you mean kill it?
What the fuck was that?
Not that I trust you completely, man.
What do you think?
Why do they stop talking?
You heard the man.
Let's firing squad him again.
Can I talk?
Go find your duct and take a picture of it with the camera you got.
Then we can talk.
Okay.
What a waste of fucking time.
Come on, buddy.
PP sticker.
Alright, so I have to come back with a photo of the duct.
This thing is almost empty.
Well, I have to go back to...
I'm going to go back to Paradise.
So I have to leave out here and just go through the plaza.
See if I have time to do this still.
I'm just going to heal.
I only have the shotgun and the one hit left on this.
I don't really want to use it.
Just give me a shitty weapon.
Like something around.
We're on our way.
I hear somebody crying.
Who's crying?
You hear that?
In the store?
Somebody in here?
I heard somebody crying.
Is there nobody in here?
This is like a hardware store though.
Anybody here?
What is this thing doing?
Nobody?
This is a sick fuck.
I don't think anyone was there.
This is a weed whacker?
What is this?
Is someone there?
Hello?
I wouldn't trust this person.
Hold on, there's a photo.
That's a horrible photo.
Let's get a close up.
I don't think there's anything in here for me.
Anything in the box?
Well, that's a fire axe.
That seems pretty great actually.
What's in the box over here?
It's actually kind of slow.
Chainsaw.
There's so much shit in here.
If Hansen made it out of fucking fly paper.
You know what?
All of you fuck off.
Just do it.
What's over here?
Tool box.
I want to get the thing that's up there.
What the hell is that?
Japanese radish.
Why is it up here?
I can't go in here?
Why not?
Use the Japanese radish?
I don't think I can.
I'm starting to get to yellow.
Is there anymore axes or something I can grab on the way out?
I guess I could take...
Is it a pickaxe? Can I take it?
No, a sledgehammer.
What do I want to replace?
Just get rid of the radish.
What am I going to use this for?
I'll take a sledgehammer.
I'm out.
I can't take it outside.
Oh, they're back.
When was the last time I saved the fucking game?
They're all the way down there.
I'm going to paradise though.
I have to go over here.
Damn it.
Now I'm going to have to cross that path.
They aren't that hard.
Well, how many shots do I have in my shotgun?
I don't think I have very many.
Use the scoot.
The scoot.
Can I just sneak up behind them and shoot the guy in the head with the shotgun?
Will that work?
I haven't saved in a while. I'm not going to try it.
I'll come out here after I save.
I have to make sure I can do that.
Let's do this first while there's still time to do it.
Okay.
So now it's just over here.
A strange group.
I think I found him.
What the fuck was that?
Get away from me.
No, get away from me with your explosions.
Give me that card.
There's food over here.
Put that down.
Hamburgers and shit, right?
No, it's just condiments.
Baking ingredients.
I don't have any food in here.
How do you not have food in this restaurant?
Ronald ate at so every other.
That's right.
Okay, let's go.
I still have a full heal.
Movie land.
What's up motherfuckers?
See what?
Save at the bathroom.
Those who reject salvation.
Embrace ignorance.
I got a shotgun.
I'll kill him.
This boss is really annoying.
Don't tell me that.
Don't tell me that I'm going to go back to where I was saved in the North Plaza.
Now I shall return your tainted blood.
Foul earth that has spawned you.
Just shotgun.
I can't climb that.
I can't climb.
Why can I not climb that?
Run, run, run.
Why is?
Oh, he baited me.
Knock it, knock it, knock it.
I literally can't even fucking move.
Fucking every boss stun locks you in this game.
Oh shit.
Motherfucker.
You motherfucker.
Do what I'm telling you to do.
Missed a fucking shot.
Apparently I double tapped.
I hit it.
Remember every make, make, make.
I'm not even going to complain about it.
Really?
You mother.
People in fucking multiplayer games don't even do what you just did.
I'm dead.
He jumped.
Oh my God.
It's so.
Jesus Christ.
So I need to use this on him.
Does every boss you just kill with the blue chainsaw and just don't even play it normally.
Thanks for the content.
Just kill every boss with a blue chainsaw and don't even deal with it.
Okay, done.
I'm going to go just kill him with a blue chainsaw.
Fuck it.
Why do anything else?
Wait, was this before?
I think I have to do the plaza thing again.
I think I have to do the gun shop again, don't I?
All right, I know what to do there.
Get a lightsaber?
In this timeline, did I already do it?
Just go back with the picture?
Yeah, that's, you know, good plan.
I like how you're thinking.
Good plan.
I'm going in and just blue chainsaw, just swinging him five times and win.
I'm going to go and get him five times and win.
Yeah, I went in the hardware store.
I got like distracted.
Let's just go.
I think I should have enough to kill him with this.
I still need to get a pair of shoes too.
I still have shoes on.
Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin.
Okay, let's go.
Movie land.
Save it.
Over here was the bathrooms right here, right?
Literally just walk across, save it in the bathroom.
Wait, am I going the right way?
Yes, get a movie land costume.
I would enable cheats that makes it so you can't be grabbed by zombies.
And I would not even think twice about enabling it.
I would just turn it on.
I just, I don't care.
There's a drink for that?
I think there is.
All right, game is saved.
Don't tell him.
Look at that alpha nerd neck.
Well, you made me a skexy from the crystal, whatever it is, the dead, whatever that, you know what I'm talking about.
Okay, I am ready.
I am ready.
I am going to not heal yet because that takes too much.
All right.
Now I have to heal.
Oh, it hurts every time.
Did you seriously just body block me from walking?
Get the fuck out of here.
That's what you deserve.
All right, I don't need the shop.
Okay, go to movie land and get a costume.
I'm not going to use, why I use the card?
Use the double lariat skill.
Okay, this powerful skill calls upon the art judo.
When grabbed by a zombie, push left stick downward repeatedly to toss the attacker.
Okay, so I've done that.
I know that.
So I get to do a zangief?
Press and hold left stick and then press X.
Did I just lose the shotgun?
I didn't know I was going to fucking throw the thing.
Okay.
Is it going to be there if I go back?
No, because there's a cut scene in between.
I can't even walk up this ramp.
It doesn't exist.
Okay, I'm going to get some refreshments.
I have plenty of time.
I know what's over there.
Touchable.
At least true power within.
No one can touch you.
So that was a bag, a snack.
What's this one?
Quick step.
All right, we're going to make like a Cheetos smoothie.
Spitfire.
What does spitfire do?
I think I've even used it.
Okay, wait, wait, hold on.
I got to break some stuff.
There might be food in here.
There is.
Okay, there's lettuce and there's another one.
Is there food?
I don't have any other food.
No can of drinks, I can't.
Damn it.
Well, I'm just going to eat the lettuce.
The wine.
Oh, that's right.
So I do lettuce and wine.
I'm going to do lettuce and wine.
And that is quick step.
That's a good one.
Okay, then I'm going to do.
Can I put the queen in there?
Jeff, five community subs.
Thank you, Jeff.
Still got plenty of time.
The stick sucks?
It's okay.
I'm assuming the costume is here.
Can I get shoes on in this place?
Oh, that's an awesome superhero.
I might dress up as Mega Man.
Is that what you want me to do?
It's a Nerf gun.
That's so cool.
What was that?
I don't know what the fuck that was.
All right, I don't want this thing.
This thing just shoots Nerf balls.
Give me my rat stick back.
Oh, I have to bake it through.
And I'm going to go like this.
And let's go.
Do the lariat.
Hold, left stick, lariat.
They were nice enough to leave the Mega Man helmet on.
They have to be standing still for that to work.
They're surprisingly calm.
Now I wish I had the shopping cart.
Because that's going to be paying the ass.
I know, I know.
I know.
Get the rat suit.
There is no rat suit.
I don't want to use this.
I'm going to try to use the stick.
I'm just going to try to jump through.
Holy shit, this thing sucks.
They did it again.
They got me again with the fucking spray.
They just spray.
Did I get the question wrong?
Sorry.
You didn't do it right.
That's your guy's button.
He didn't do that right.
Curious George.
Man in the yellow red hat.
Whatever the fucking thing is.
Yellow red McDonald's.
Maybe I'm hungry.
Maybe I should get some McDonald's.
Alright, I'm going to get the cart.
I'm going to run through.
And then I'm going to kill the guy with the sword.
Sounds like a plan, Jeremy.
I think you should do it.
That sounds like something you should do.
Do a McDonald's review stream, part two.
It's not very good.
But I still eat it.
It's awful.
Alright, go.
What did I do wrong?
I did that right.
How was that incorrect?
What theater is it?
Which theater is it?
Let's go.
Don't get cocky.
It's just like fucking that game that I reference every other.
I thought that was a person.
Should have secured that with a few sandbags.
You obtained the movie leeeeeeee...
Wait a minute.
They have guns?
No, no, no, no, don't let them spread out.
Don't spread out.
Do I get any grenades?
I'm going to save the people but this is bad.
He's going to explode.
Don't get sprayed.
Okay, we're good.
Let's go.
jump into danger okay that sounds good to me I'll have it I'm gonna keep that
that sounds fantastic hello you what's your name how do I get you out of here
am I safe now I am I'm safe okay Michelle joined right I don't know who
you are but I sure appreciate your help and there's one more there's Nathan
Nathan oh this Beth to this for you who the hell are these freaks it's just
his son of a bitch wait wait wait wait where you guys going Beth I have to get
back damn it why they have to tie me up so tight totally left marks all right
would anybody handle a weapon Ray I'm giving this to you Beth take this sword
no no give that to Beth I bet is there any other weapons in here let's go let's
go close the door what's wrong with the door I need to save the game hold on we
go out here down out of movie land save game and then we're right there other
door other door other door this door what's in this door hey please they're
gonna kill me they want to sacrifice me I'll do anything to save me okay let's
go first of all I need to open this box first so I'm gonna take this is there
anymore stuff at this propane tank because I've already picked that up
somebody take this okay sounds fun I took care of those goons you're safe now
you did really come on that's like drama going on back there I can't no wasting
time here we go again another one of these stupid okay everybody go over here
how many we have one two three four where is she let's go their leaders
finished though there may be a few underlings left this place is dangerous
you ready to blow this joint thanks I'll follow you anywhere all right we got to
go now let's go all right just stay with me I only have I do have a bug I got
bugs you got a gun good who wants the gun Michelle who wants the gun who
should have the gun oh I don't know Nathan absolutely not you raise gonna
chainsaw Beth Michelle Cheryl Beth she understands no I don't trust Nathan with
anything let's go like so I'm sorry like a horror movie like fat guy with a
mustache is always the one that does something crazy and gets the whole
thing fucked up well what are you talking about I unlocked the door to get
the soap from inside the inside the storeroom and it's like Nathan what the
fuck are you thinking man oh I must admit me when I came back no here take
this all right now we're gonna go out here watch it except for Ronald Ronald
ate all the food that is an absolute fat guy with a mustache thing to do what are
you talking about got everybody all right we just have to go here that's it
you ready follow me slow we don't go far everyone's good nice swinging and I have
bees in fact I'm gonna use a bee up here everyone good watch out behind you
behind you somebody else my gun all right somebody else get a gun handgun you
who doesn't have a handgun Nathan take the gun Nathan Nathan take the gun
Nathan Nathan take a gun Nathan take a gun Nathan take the gun Nathan take a
gun Nathan take a gun Nathan take the gun what if I need my sword where's my
sword Nathan take a gun why can I not highlight Nathan's name there's too many
people it's a who fucking cares let's go out out out just fucking who cares
don't figure it out it's right here Nathan is the thing we have to test his
blood we safe through the water come on then up here make it Cheryl Cheryl
Cheryl Cheryl Cheryl you're doing great you're doing great Cheryl I don't have
time for this Cheryl Cheryl please Cheryl oh just Michelle stop getting in
the fucking way Michelle's gonna defect if I hit her again one two three four
five we're good got everybody one two three four five follow me all right I'm
running out of juice here we're all here go I need the sword for the for the
elevator we're good this sounds like a lot of people in there one two three
four five here we go help help me help help somebody help got them all and
where we still have some time left to all five of you get up here take a
picture good photo Cheryl Jones I'm all dusty what I
wouldn't get for a shower I'm gonna get a lot of this oh yeah 250,000 PP that's
pretty good new skill we might have to take a look at it level up again life up
nice knee drop more stock oh yes perfect okay I need to save for a second I
forgot that happened save the game and then I'm gonna pee my pants it's been
two hours every two hours into a stream I have to pee really badly and then I'm
fine for like the rest of the day just happens to be at like 4 or 5 p.m. every
day picture of the vent no that's right you're right all right I'll be back all
right let's keep going I'm back ready to go so what's the last thing I did this
is getting kind of crowded in here is this when everybody does their pre
programmed sim animation I need to get everybody in the same picture 386 p
that's not bad all right picture the duct and is there anything else going on
oh shit I can still do this I can still do this right that's gonna go up there
all right the game is saved right I saved it did I yes it did let's get a
picture of the duct that count I got this guy I got this guy Otis up there
you're gonna love them air duct okay let's go I can still do the photographer
I gotta save this one too so it doesn't get deleted because I will can you guys
hear me okay I need to save save them both just in case there's a problem you
still have the other ones all saved yeah check the new move that's a good very
good idea okay roundhouse kick unleash a powerful kick just as you land with this
skill press X at the exact moment you contact the ground following a following
a jump or drop him a high plane nice that's not that's not it there it is
cool all right I'm out of stuff I need to oh the torso right torso is the best
item in the whole game remember everyone is telling me to use it let's see let's
test it let's test the theory torso I'm willing to give it a try
spotted a guy with long hair over one of the women's clothing shops in Wonderland
Plaza okay I don't think I'm gonna have time to do it so the Molotov cocktail
what okay long-haired punk is actually there's plenty of time this thing
actually is pretty good so I got a lot of time to do that let's do the
photographer's pride first and then I have to make sure I'm back for the I
can make sure I'm back for the actual story mission try to do the kick holding
up here all right what is this part let me I'm gonna have to go back um all right
Otis what is it don't forget the gun shop yeah I'm gonna do that and at the
next story cycle I think photographers pride so is it not available yet what
time does it happen sick man what was the actual time noon shit so but this
one has this one's gonna happen first Frank stop it now I'm gonna make some
smoothies while I'm here double pie pie smoothie untouchable that's the one I
wanted any more food I can use something else on the ground anything soda now
I'm just gonna eat this thing what does this book do all right I have to keep
this as long as I can I wish I could can I make my inventory less cluttered
what's my favorite banana cream pie is the best pie without a doubt it's
actually the only pie I think I don't like after pie I don't like blueberry pie
any fruit based pies that's not a banana I don't find appetizing at all
banana cream pie is all right but I mean that's what I just said chocolate
cream pie is pretty good but if it's not banana cream pie I don't want to eat it
I don't want it um do I have enough time to do any of these other things I don't
think so I'm gonna miss this shit where was a sick man I have the vent picture
yeah but I have to go all how much time do I actually have to get back for the
story mission I could go in the skip and appear over here I start here and then
go down is there enough time to do it vent picture no I have I have the vent
picture I'm just not sure I'm not I just don't have a scenario where I get
locked in and I do this mission and I can't get back in enough time to do the
actual case mission I'll save it and try it we'll see what happens I'll make sure
I have like a don't soft lock me please scenario all right so I gotta go this
way I still have a gun even grab me they just like magnetized to your fucking
body and it's making me upset all right I think let's make a scenario that is
no I can't fail which is right here so this save no matter what is like the you
know in the time travel movie wherever there you find that one spot that you
have you can go back to and stop everything that ever happened that's this
point right here so now I have to actually use this teleport let's see what
you can do all right sick man get the chainsaw chainsaws a must excuse me
excuse me wait somebody in here to Susan oh shit Susan really uh Susan you're
gonna have to wait you have to wait get shoes all right I'm gonna go into shoes
of a lifetime and I'm gonna get a pair of shoes can I not wear any of these how
can you have a store named shoes of a lifetime and not have me able to have a
pair of shoes from her all right Susan I'm coming you don't want to eat me
between my hip and my dentures I'm half plastic is she's no late trying to jump
on his head all right Susan look what I just did for you all right let's go come
on ma'am follow me you'll be my personal escort what a polite boy yes we have to
go upstairs personal Susan wall she's joined all right come with me what the
hell are you doing all right we have to make a quick pit stop over here what
happened to a sick man what's wrong with Leroy it's too dangerous to be out here
hey hey you startled me don't do that okay well you look a little sick you
feeling all right I'm fine just a scratch no problem he's been bit he's
gonna turn you're hurt where show me don't mind me guys don't mind me I'm
just I'm just having Leroy has joined your group I have to heal wait what's
this red I only just changed my hair red all right granny can't use anything but
Leroy take a knife and granny you're not gonna take a gun when I'm gonna be
Carlito now I've gone and hurt you I have to get back we have to go now come
on Susan I kept up can I just pick you up yeah I gotta go I need to go through
the skip the bathroom skip back to paradise which is up here chainsaw
chainsaw chainsaw all right chainsaw chainsaw chainsaw chainsaw chainsaw
all right you guys just have to stay somewhere Susan if you die you die I'm
sorry I don't have time to do anything about this just go like over here and
just stay there for a minute I'll be right back nice you have Leroy has a
knife Leroy come on just all right stay alive Leroy that was his broken jaw all
right stay here and thanks for stabbing me right in the fucking back quick step
I'm back let's go come on bathroom up here bathroom running out of time
running out of time running out of time come on Susan Susan I have to hold hands
you're way too slow let's go I'm not going the right way again yes Leroy can
defend for himself come on Leroy she's infected why would you let go of my
hand sure is it gonna I'm gonna have to be for another time it looks like he's
running around in circles is he know where he's going we're in all right let's
go all right now this is a different timeline so that's the one that's safe
we're gonna go one up from that this one is just in case something horrible
happens all right follow me I gotta hold the hand but it's all right come on out
of the bathroom I don't know what just happened why do I have to hold your hand
to get out of here are you this stupid the basic human survival instincts but
just I'm about to literally pick her up and just throw her Susan you're really
making me very annoyed here give me the fucking chainsaw this is a joke go oh my
god straight down he hates the elderly well her AI just keeps breaking like
that just stay with me and I lost I lost Leroy Leroy you're the you're the huge
guy with a weapon how could you possibly let this happen oh my god you're dumb
holy shit people is everybody in this game on drugs yes it has to be something
like that they're all just like it's the I wake what are you doing move and then
you'll give him a weapon and they go and they swing wildly and hit everybody in
the group in the face I'm not gonna hold your hand anymore if you die you die I
don't care even with this close and I've read I actually don't care if you have
off and let him go doing great doing great Leroy the fucking like handful of
pills you just took like before I picked you up a really working well for you
they're kicking in get over here hi God thank God I got stopped get you can I
just like go like this fucking throw her over oh no I don't feel so good anyone
what okay all right I gotta go gotta go I gotta take this mission holy fuck
so maybe just like just pick her up and just runs this last resort
oh that's painful
damn what you're thinking the explosion would send parasitic your pants he
plans to spread zombies outside of the city is he insane that bomb goes off
there'll be nowhere to run the zombies will be everywhere what'd you do with
your hair try a new look he's planning to flood the area underneath the mall
doesn't dye your hair and is all the apocalypse the fuck are you doing why
are you doing that there's a chance we could stop the explosion let's do it if
you got time to dye your hair you got time to do anything got it okay
k72 from 11 a.m. so let's save it in the safe spot which is the top one game is
saved bomb collector get away from me was there is there a fight going on in
here what just happened why did she fall down Kelly what are you doing why is
she going all ring girl on me right now this is freaking me out what do you do
why is she doing this just wanted to you know you could have just said thank
you you don't have to stare at me and follow me around okay a simple thanks
would have been nice through the window don't lose the gun who cares it's fine
bullets say I got the game saved photographers pride I'm gonna do for
cop photographers pride first mannequin torso it's too late it's too late it's
too late I can't go back
mr. West I owe you an apology
that look on your face well got a better laugh in the clown
what the hell is going on here I hate this guy hey I don't have anything
can I take wait I can I take he's kicking the shit out of me I didn't even
get a I didn't get a chance to do anything um was your plan to take a
photo was you plan to tie me up chain my neck to a pole and beat me to death
that wasn't part of what photo did you take all right this will take me straight
to the top and then he got like way too into it and fucking murdered me like
what are you doing like relax easy psycho you all do in the elevator you
all have to put somebody has to press the elevator button and you have to get
in who's putting you in why are you all getting inside the elevator I got no
fucking idea and it's full of people every time all right so what actually
happens here is this something I can I just not do this because I got
photographers pride is just let me let me do this again I'm just curious as to
what so I'm just here why does it automatically started last time the
story mission is timed I'm gonna get soft-locked I still have time for it
though but what how do you complete this I got that safe I'll be okay all
right you were here so it's not late so he's gonna do it anyways I'm gonna get
telltale if I'm tied up to a polite no don't take a photo of him don't die here
give me I get his camera that's gonna achievement that says peacekeeper
look camera to get a 100% bonus to PP resulting from photos okay now you trad
tad you want to come do a mission with me what's up with that freak the plenty
time to get pissed later we don't have time to stick around to get chatting so
let's go you and me you're coming with me it's safe place that you will not be
safe yeah I hate this place now okay tad tad you are now you you are party
member from Star Trek every episode you're just the guy that is just there
and I'm sorry I'm not gonna save you but it will not be completely for me all
right where do I go let's see where is this actual taking place wonderland
park so wait no down to the entrance Plaza is there a quick way to get to
the entrance Plaza but I guess just walk down save him you took the longest way
around just saying red shirt yeah well I mean come on I'm gonna get soft this is
the wrong way we mean wrong way wrong way that's not it's not the entrance
Plaza one it's not this one here I thought this is the one that's the the
long hair guy right it's in the it's in the park really I thought it was that
that scoop down there gonna get the tad ending who knows he might live long
enough to do this whole thing with me in that case you know good for him so then
why am I going through here why would I have just done like the
shortcut this is a different spot to go you have to get it into the tunnel okay
down there I see you mean come on Tad you can run faster than that I see what
you're saying well I have two full heels and I have two torsos come on let's go
spin around with a little bit of hustle please
cat shooter he just aimed just until she was on the ground
shooter tab that way hurry up mister keep with me stay with me to the right
right side you got it you know what you're doing don't be like the others
Tom Tad Tad Tad Tad pull I don't know why but I feel like that's accurate Tad
are you ready to get in a car Tad oh Tad we got a cruise come on Tad let's go Tad
crank some tunes if you want just me and Tad having some fun time into
I can't drive through this why would I have a car are you serious I need to get
the motorcycle god damn it Tad why don't you say something yeah I'm Tad let's go
on the bike you and me Tad oh you are all so dumb how many drugs did you take
out of the glove box oh get on how am I going the right way I don't know is this
correct I don't think this is correct it's here what do you stop doing that
just zoom it out okay so it's down here so outright right go back to Tad he'll
find his own way I can't believe we couldn't take the car I couldn't take me
and Tad couldn't do that right right then bang a little doesn't matter just
right again save Tad or right he'll maybe he'll still be around it's possible
why is this long-haired punk thing selected I didn't do that bang left and
then I'm there the bike is not gonna explode right in this building it's
right there why is it selected get all it was on bomb collector I didn't change
it I didn't put my watch up can I go in there with a bike I'm gonna try you
think I'm gonna lose this shit not happening right now the hell am I going
there five bombs what do you mean five bombs Todd Todd Hawthworth is dead I
know well now I know what you guys mean by it's time bomb you obtained a time
bomb is for can I drive this I get it need the motorcycle back what the hell
are you doing here I'm not gonna be able to do this he just drives a car what
real I have to reload it that was my only means of transportation you dick
okay so holy shit I photographer is done but I I kind of don't care you know I'm
saying I got I got I'm just gonna go I do well if I that seems like a long
mission you know what I'm saying that seems kind of like a long thing to do
just once I want to open that and there's nothing in there just once I just
wanted just one time I'm gonna open the elevator there's nothing in it takes two
seconds all right okay I'll get Tad and then he's dead anyways like what do you
want to do I can't bring him with me and I can't return him save him I can't save
him these zombies have a like 88 percent wrap rate bring him home fine I'll save
Ted and I'll bring him back I'm gonna do it it's a kick me right in the groin
I'm trying to do a flash again that's pretty damn flashy if I don't say so
myself get it good done in the book tap tap what's up with that freak yeah okay
yeah funny time to be pissed off later this safe place not far from here yeah
I hate this place I'll go with you okay let's go just got to go through a door
am I going the wrong way no thought I was it's empty good I can get another
uh one of these things get shoes I don't have time I've never I haven't had time
to get shoes since yesterday I saved a tad save I sure hope you don't snap one
day and freak out like the other photographer guy I won't say again it's
a lot of PP row distance increased let's save it this one's going down to the
bottom just in case of is a nightmare scenario all right two torsos and I'm
gonna try this mission again it can't be worse than Isabella well here's the
problem with what you just said it is a car mission there's a mission with
somebody driving a car around trying to kill you two of these I have two heels
boosts on them okay bomb collector through into the inside of the world the
bike can break it's not good bomb collector I said bomb collector it's
saved right here too bong water collector is there like a cart or
something I can get on drive what are these other ones do this one is camera
and okay people are no longer fearful that's good
Otis just wants to wish you good luck well Otis is really fucking irritating
all right I get full health that's good in the garage oh fuck they're standing
in front of the garage do not car battle car battle let's go
except I need to they have a gun on their car I don't have a gun on my car
all right what is it can you hear me it's not wait whoa whoa I've been spam
called so many times the time bomb should be located inside several trucks
parked in the maintenance tunnel as far as I can tell from security monitors it
looks like they split into five locations he slashed the trucks tires so
you'll have to transport the bombs by hand hurry to the maintenance tunnel
Frank I thought you were Otis the whole time so that's why I wasn't answering
phone my god and that was every piece of information I needed to hear wonder who
that is all right I just have to find there's a girl in the CD shop okay just
I have to go do I just find them okay so the first one there just I'm just gonna
go to all the corners do I have to do them in order or just find them just
find them whatever it's parked truck look for park truck park truck down here
park truck this is a slender man scenario where the more that I pick up
the more he's gonna like attack me all right making note of it I got the one
down center in the I got the one center but down okay right right around the
rotary first right the rotary right again okay truck down where's the truck
straight ahead the bomb just explode whatever my bike whatever the bike why
did it just turn into Legos okay I got middle bottom right we're gonna go
straight up what the fuck man I need a shopping cart how the fuck am I supposed
to do this anybody have a no bike or a shopping cart or where's the car car
what's his name Carlito quick step I don't have any quick stuff I don't have
quick stuff it's the white one I need a shopping cart oh there he is beep beep
here he comes hi Carlito welcome oh boy this is fucking gonna be fun I have to
dodge a guy in an ice cream truck well he tries to back up over and kill me
yeah by the way did you notice this guy with the fucking flytrap hands
spitfire what's it mean what's it do what's it do what does spitfire do tell
me what does it do shopping cart no that's I need that cart no it's a car
over here this car is gonna explode get it all right where's it there's no truck
back here did I miss a truck I didn't see a truck back there okay so I got
bang bang we're gonna go all the way up here turn right truck right here all
right slow down I gotta put this in a good spot so I can get the fuck out of
here oh no just a fucking trillion people here okay where now one two three
four up here five down here top left and then middle left right here right I'm
kind of freaking out right now okay yeah that one right there so we're gonna go
right left go not that one that's pink and then right now now now top left bang
it left straight left no I don't see headlights no headlights no headlights
no headlights no headlights no headlights no headlights I got checked in
gym class no headlights get in get in get in where's the bomb other one hey
oh shit I got fucking jebaited I got jebaited oh yeah yeah yeah how do I get
out here right right right right in here that's where I'm going right right games
like the game's fucking lagging the games like glitching out all over the
place right right right right oh my god I just have to leave how do you get out
of the car oh no I really didn't want to do that again I'm so glad I didn't die
no don't nice lock him up get him the hit knife oh we're gonna see the death
of a main character oh that's not good that means he's gonna have to fight a
hundred thousand zombies by himself he's gonna be surrounded this is gonna be
sad yeah I still don't have shoes I've wanted to stop for shoes for like six
in-game hours how do I like the game I mean I knew I was gonna like it it's
okay hold on important done from 5 p.m. case 8 next case would be occurred 5 p.m.
I don't get a safe point holy shit I need to save this game right now it's a
safe point right here where I mean this but this is north how do I get there
quickly from here get Brad with one health bar go back for breath save bread
I don't know if I feel safer in the truck or use my heel I don't have one I
don't have a heel go to the food in the park okay I'm gonna bury very carefully
here guys go back this is gonna be a fucking disaster look around the parking
lot for a second is there any food what's that food in the toolbox all right
food in the toolbox come on it's gotta be like a cabbage in there or something
right just give me a cabbage I can't eat these I have to leave okay this thing's
smoking give me the other car okay I have to save now I'm so I'm like
actually my I'm like scared I have to go quick what's the quickest place to get
to a safe point from here save bread what was that okay so if I go straight
through to Paradise Plaza and then save point oh yeah yeah yeah where's the food
oh I can go no I'm gonna try it use the tunnels you're gonna get shot in the
park so can I go through here and like actually go up through the like the
maintenance tunnel no yes okay oh shit okay I can go up here go to the food
court all right we're gonna go right straight all the way to the end go to
the food court I'm gonna clear everything I don't know if I get grabbed
once I'm saying this is that hamburger meat you know you know I don't know if
that is but I'm not gonna get it it's hamburger meat it's hamburger meat thank
fucking god damn it okay where's this elevator go to no I don't want to use
the old air right I need the maintenance tunnel key to open it what Brad's gonna
die it's too bad don't you normally just like doing the face cam yeah I got
pressured into it 40% of chat told me this I had one all right I I'm now I
know feel safe that I can get back I'm gonna take this car out and I'm gonna
drive it out of here and just drive through paradise in fact fuck no I say I
gotta I have to save the damn game man I've got like a minute to do this next
thing I've got to get the fuck out of here where's the exit right here right
forget about Brad I'm sorry and the car is dead I'm sorry Brad that's just the
way it is you didn't get all right Brad you didn't give me a safe point so
therefore I what am I gonna do lose I'm just gonna lose now I have help I'm
gonna get in the car and drive out of here thank you very much back to
paradise let's go sorry Brad nothing I can do about this so it's just straight
across right just straight across good okay back to the where's the next
mission jamming device save it first save it first save it first save to
bangalore something horrible could happen on the way over there I could
walk and just get smoked on the way back and that's gonna be horrible you're
gonna see some real real sadness I'm already getting sad and hadn't even
happened go the top one game safe whoo all right what was I looking over
there for I told you I told you this is gonna happen I got like my my like
nervous anxious gamer skills worked and now that I became confident that I was
safe I just got hurt like five times let's get some batteries nice get rid of
this shit I don't even need it this door sneaks up on you too shoes no time for
shoes I was fucking dead again in that queen that was a courage scream okay
good to go hi guys save it in here with one health though that might is that's a
soft lock potential I'm gonna do one down go to the gun store and show the
picture I don't have enough time I've got like I don't I'm not gonna make it
back don't get food on the roof kill Brad save Brad kill Brad all right so
this is it is for it's four o'clock what is it 430 for this no way for me to get
food up here you go to the heliport all right let me look up here food weapon
I'm a what's that nothing up here what about up there can I get up that I think
I can climb that on the dumpster and then over it's so badly wants me to be
able to do this nothing even up here there's nothing on the roof well then
what the hell am I doing up here why did I come up here this is the final battle
arena what about the boxes it's kind of annoying Brad is dying and you're just
letting it happen yes yes that is that is exactly what's
happening oops sorry I just that hurts what time is it all right I got like 30
minutes to do nothing because it's not it's too risky and I don't I need food
but I don't have any food so I know I don't I can't really do anything it's
shoes on save Brad I'm gonna laugh if Brad's not even savable yeah I'm not
comfortable going out there right now not with one cheese square I'm not going
out there with one single cheese slice I'm sorry I had to do that I had to do
it again you're a bully you can get some more craft singles on the way yeah on
the way to the next mission I don't want to miss the case what do I have
left status is there like a yeah go to case file so I'm on case 8 this is the
last case and then I have the facts oh shit I got the last is the last case
let's go I've had it I've had it I've had it I've had it so this game would be
really awesome and don't spoil it but tell me if I'm right at the end of the
game you have a final showdown and everybody that you saved was all one
group and you have to do like a big final showdown that was pretty fun and
the more people that you save the you know the more power that you have in the
final fight that's pretty cool for Dead Rising 5 do that I still forgot there
was even a Dead Rising 4 all right so what do you think I'm getting like the
end of the game here is this a is this well maybe like another hour or two but
still you want I think I'm just gonna do Dead Rising 2 I think I'm actually just
gonna play Dead Rising 2 I'm having fun it's it's holding my interest
completely yeah we'll put Dead Rising 2 on the list I'll do it you know yeah
there's a Frank West campaign in there which version of Dead Rising 2 the one
that's on Steam I already own it is that the right one off the record all
right it's five o'clock see what happens got some bad news about Brad
no nothing but the bombs Brad news I'm sure there's plenty of information on
it can you take me there to his hideout leave it to me that's case one done
case two fuck man I think we're almost at the end of the game hideout Mindy
Baker is dead Debbie Willard is dead who are these people scoop oh wait does
have to come with me oh she does this is gonna be fantastic can't wait for this
one she's already broken I know I have to activate her this is a gun all right
so am I following you are you following me which one is it face cam I in like
another five minutes she even down here oh we're paying the ass I killed
everybody in this elevator and you tell me that they got in I don't have
anything else to how are you filling up the elevator get in here what are you
doing don't have to talk to her again get in the fucking elevator get in the
elevator yes you have to get in here okay let's go let's get moving yeah there
it is he set the line he said the title finally what took you one second this
time all right you have to do some work here yeah let's go all right well
thankfully she's kind of on her own she has her own mind I need food so we need
to go through well I'm just gonna put the hideout thing on just because I lose
her that was a loud scream I get fucking sneezed on it's gonna be over drink the
paint whoa this is horrible I'm in such deep shit I need food I need like a
smoothie bar upstairs I'm going to make a smoothie she'll be fine all right two
pies just just hang on I need to eat something I'll be down in a second
come on you didn't need my help you got out either way I need that back how did
I stab you twice did they she can't defect right she's like an story NPC
that's useful and got to know that not save this I'm probably gonna be shoot
somebody seriously wouldn't be surprised if I and this is like a big boss fight
and have to shoot we're not actually going this way are we why are we going
this way just hugging this wall all right another Queen dark over here so
where's this super special hideout oh shit that's empty I'm out I need a rake
any rakes over here this escort mission sucks total asshole so I really hope
this is not that hard to do I think you got him just go what are you waiting
for I'm just an NPC just okay you have a full path you show that guy the head 10
times all right face cam go for every two hours of face cam I have one hour
of no face cam that's the deal that's what you agreed to feet cam not in a
hundred million years all right no get up she close enough all right there's a
food is it food nice all right what do we got something behind the counter
batteries for the camera food or something there's no food here good it's
like a cantaloupe okay that's great that helps any weapon no board right
here I should save it if we're going up here I'm gonna try to save it right
there do a mouth cam those games too hard for that bring back the nose cam
yeah I can't like stop right now it's like a stressful hard video game that
cannot have a nose cam attached cuz that means I can't play the game at a level
that is expected of me which is a nose cam makes it like a 4 out of 10 and no
nose cam makes it like a 5 and a half to 6 out of 10 shit we're going to the gun
store we are going to the gun store this does not seem like a good idea this is
the secret hideout all right this is gonna go up to the hardware store did I
already find this there's any stuff oh shit so the shitty hideout not very
glamorous his dog his mother's birthday family stuff that's the power Frank
what's this thing do don't unplug it then you got to get the evidence out of
it well I have to go back Jesse's discovery I have to go all the way back
are you kidding me oh all right all right bye I'll take I'll do the wonderland
skip gun store do I still have that photo there it is take a picture re take
a picture re re you didn't take the picture you didn't take the picture okay
yeah did you picture ready haha ready yeah that's what you guys wanted
fucking cretins let's get out of here save the game so I'm going to first I'm
gonna do the gun thing cuz I have the photo hopefully I can get back to it
fast enough here's the gun shop in fact I yeah I can't fuck around here I'm just
dropping one I'm dropping I got a ton of them that's good hey it's me I'm the guy
with the picture okay yep no I want a handgun I want something bigger than
that sneeze here coming was the real shit shotgun sniper rifle sniper rifle
shotgun get rid of the handgun listen here this handgun was there an assault
right sniper rifle shotgun shotgun handgun nothing else nothing else there's
nothing else here take all of it okay I'm gonna take give me another give me a
shotgun and then give me a another sniper rifle okay two shotguns and give
you another shotgun drop the pamphlet remember you fool you dropped food it
was a fucking cabbage it's gonna be like one health it's I don't care all right I
gotta go there's a can of food what I have to leave where is it what does this
one do anymore shotguns handgun fuck no hang on I can't take any more shotguns
I have to actually use this to make my way
back okay now I'm gonna go from here I have to go where the hell does this want
me to go where's this trying what is this taking me save in the hideout save
in the hideout save in the hideout save in the hideout save in the hideout save
in the hideout save in the hideout save the hideout save the hideout Car
hoes hideout which one of these like rundown rooms was it in this one where's
the safe point I didn't know this like rug was a safe point all right I need to
picking up the slot all the way down to the bottom. There you go, I got it. I'm
on the wrong way! Panicking. This is just panic the video game. It's not good. All right,
what is this one to go? Oh my god, I hate you guys so much! Fuck, there's so many up
in the north area. Canned food. You guys are the worst. Really? Un-b-lievable. You
made me go back and pick up the canned food and I can't even eat it? Oh, you guys
are un-b-lievable. Unbelievable. What's this? Un-b-lievable. Canned food. Canned food. Wow, you idiot.
Pick up the canned food, dumbass. Dog laugh? You mean the dog? Oh, was that what you
wanted to get? You too? Oh, sure, thank god. That's my way. Jump! I'm trying to jump on his
head. Oh my god. I'm trying to jump on his head. Oh, I can go up to the cafe. He's going full
tuber at this point. Not quite. Hit the bell. Did I still even have the bell on YouTube? Why
did I not jump on his head? Explain it. I want a full, I want a paragraph from
everyone, everybody here. There's a why that didn't jump on his head. A full
paragraph. I'm not seeing very many paragraphs. This is going to be bad. Here comes a
terrible scenario. Terrible scenario. Terrible scenario. Terrible scenario. Here
it comes. Fuck. We're good. Who is that?
I have to go all the way back there. Forward, back, forth, back, forth. You couldn't have put these
next to each other. Oh my fucking god. I gotta save the damn game too. What the fuck? I'm not
gonna make it down there in time. I don't even know which one of these is good. Is it in the middle? I
have so many different timelines. Okay. What's the fastest way to get there? Butcher. Am I gonna be
able to do this? I just came from there. I have to just run through the park. Run to the parking
lot and then drive. I don't have the key to open the doors. Go through the tunnel. Go through
park with bike. But where's the, there's no bike. The maintenance, I don't have the maintenance
key. Remember I tried to go up from the tunnel and I didn't have the maintenance key to leave?
Well, let's see if I can get, I don't even, I need health too. This is kind of a disaster.
He's entrapping us. Well, let me see what happens when I need to get food through the tunnels. But
where's the key? I don't have enough time to do this. I think it's over. Make a quick step? Yeah,
but by the time I make like two or three quick steps it's over. I definitely have time. Do I though?
Oh, how is that even possible to miss? Why would you shoot up and to the right?
I might, this might be the beginning of the end here. I might be soft-locked.
It's very possible because I got to get up there and I probably have to kill the boss in this
timeline. Food in the box near the elevator. I have plenty of weapons. Is this not on my list
of things to do? Get it on! Tons of time. I got to get up to the cafe. What the fuck? What the fuck?
Oh my god, there's a fucking million of them. There's a million of them. There's a million of
them. Ah, what do I get rid of? A handgun. Oh shit, okay. Wait, wait, wait, two orange juices.
What does that do? I don't have time to figure this out. What is, I don't even know what this is.
Nectar? Okay, drop the sniper rifles for the orange juice. Okay, that's good, right? I have to leave.
Okay, I have to, I have to, I have to leave right now. Bye. Out of time. Drink one. Fuck. Go. Should
I save it? No, it could be a disaster if I save. Oh, I have so many shotgun bullets. There's too
many. I just got to get there and get a shopping cart and run. There's a motorcycle. Does anybody
know what the actual time is that I need to beat this by? Why is it telling me to go this way?
Wait, why is it doing, why am I going this way? You have to take the tunnel so I get the car.
I get the motorcycle. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Okay, motorcycle. Do I have time?
I have to go, but I don't, I just, the save point is so far behind us.
Okay, now go which way? Which way, which way, which way? Get off my screen. Straight and then left.
What's this GPS bullshit? I did it. I have to kill him in like 30 seconds. I have like three
shotguns. Is it enough? That guy, I mean that meat. This is good meat, huh? We just got it in here.
It's fresh. You just wait right there, sir. In a moment, you can try the best ground meat you've ever
tasted. Whoa, ground? Wait a minute, listen. I had something else in mind. Zombies! I can't
my customers spoiled meat like that. Keep this guy alive. Have a reputation to uphold.
I mean, he'd be a pretty good companion. Huge meat flavor. He's turning on this machine, which,
can I push him in? Or do I just have to kill him? Shotgun, shotgun head, shotgun head,
head shotgun. Okay, you got it. He's got throwing knives. Wow! Ow, that hurt. Am I shooting car,
Carlito in the head? I tried to dodge it. Oh, please! Oh, sorry. No invisibility frames.
Was it enough? He's crying, you frick. What are you guys talking about?
I know it's the end of the movie, but why would I ask that at the end of the movie?
Hey, that's the password. That was an easy password.
This was just chapter one. You've got three more chapters after this one. If you thought the butcher
was annoying. Wait till you get to the... I'm trying to name something that wasn't in this game,
but I can't think of anything that wasn't in the game. Like police officer. Clown, you know,
both in it. Like psycho guy with mask on it. Demon, probably. Pants, yeah. Astronaut. This is
probably an astronaut in the game. It's probably one of the psychos. Done. The facts. Case 8.4 done
from 10 p.m. The next case will occur at 10 p.m. Uh-oh. Where's that one? Where's that one? Where's
that one? Um, I have a meat cleaver. I gotta go. There's probably something cool in here,
but I don't have time. Save the game? Where? Where's my car? No, there is a car.
Oh god. Why? I have no time. Where do I go? The hideout. Oh shit. Um, okay, so can I get... I can't
get up this way. I have to go out and to the park again. I have to go right, right, and then I have
to take the car and then out to the park into North Plaza. Right, left, left. You can get the key in
the tunnel here. In here? I don't have... Guys, there's no save point. I think I have to go with
what I know. I'm gonna go right. I'm gonna go right. That's all I'm doing. That's what I'm doing.
I gotta go with what I know. And that's all I know. Do I even need to get out of the car?
Stay in this one. Good. No travel time. Good. Frank, this Cheryl girl, she just wants to talk
to you about something. She's kind of cute if I were you. Otis, look at the clock. No, no, no,
no, no, no. Don't drive. It's this way. It's right here. Get out of the car. Get out of the car. Out.
Out of the car. Please stop the car. Stop the car. Cart? Chopping cart? No, fuck the snacks.
This... No, chopping carts are a good spot. You fuckers. Do I have a nest? I have a bee's nest.
Where's the cleaver? Go. Go hurry. What the fuck are you talking about?
Leave me alone. Turn. This thing's got some dog shit turning. Where is it? Get away from my penis.
Where is it? Where is it? It's left? It's in the gun shop? Get this thing out of here.
No, I need that. Where is it? Help me. I'm fucking panicking. Is it the gun store?
This person has mowed a fake lawn. Oh, son of a bitch.
Get away from me. Give me the nest. Give me the bee's nest. No, fuck. I didn't want to do that.
Right here. Go, go, go, go, go. Up, up, up, up, up. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Why am I panicking?
Because I have like three in-game actual minutes to get there. She's high as fuck.
She's been up here just doing drugs the whole time. Ah, damn it. Can you just hold my hand?
Now she's going to pick up. I'm going to give her like an axe and she's going to swing it twice.
Her eye pupils are going to be like the size of fucking footballs. She's going to bump into
walls and shit. That'd be the game. Is this the end? He said there's something inside that you
really would like. She opens it. It's like fucking like drug dust. There it is. Drug? I
would say cocaine. Am I going to not? I can't say cocaine? Is that against the law me saying the
word cocaine? Why do I feel like I was going to get in trouble for saying cocaine? Is my mother
watching? She might be. Yeah, it's my mother's own personal terms of service. Don't talk about
drugs. Don't talk about anything like sexual, Jeremy. You're better than that. I got a personal
mom T.O.S. That's right. You're right. That's right. She just snorted it.
I was actually right. That's pretty good. It's like latte art for cocaine and shit. Nice.
All cases closed, but. But what? What does that mean? Saved. Cheryl's request. I know I was wrong.
He harmed too many innocents and thought only of himself. Even so, I got a long time to do this.
It actually is chapter two. All right, let's go. I have to be on the roof at the right time?
Well, what time is it right now? It's 10 20 on the 21st. What time do I have to get on the roof?
Frank, the emergency line's been freed up. I'll give headquarters a call. Hang on. Roof now.
This is agent Jessica McCarney. We have an emergency situation.
Huh? All right. What? Why did you put me on hold? Do a suplex. Hold on. Skills.
Roundhouse kick. Okay. Lift up. Lift a zombie and give them a toss with this skill.
Press X and A without pushing anything and then press X again to throw. All right. Knee drop.
During a jump, press X while pushing down. Grab your opponent and send them flying,
facing a standing enemy's back. Press X and A without pushing anything.
Well, that's awesome. All right, let's go. I need a shopping cart.
Get more guns. Is that necessary? Well, I wish I had this before. What's going on?
It's over.
Contacted headquarters. The government has decided to deny all knowledge of what happened here.
Special forces will arrive for cleanup at midnight. Midnight. They'll take everyone out.
So I steal the helicopter that they landed. People. Everyone. That's easy. Oh, fuck. What's
wrong with me lately? I can't even mute. It's just power that comes out of me. I can't even
stop it. I can't even press mute in time. Go to the roof right now. I'm not going to make it.
Just leave the mall laughing my ass off. Well, I don't have enough time to do this.
What time is it? I got like an hour. It's turned around here. All right. Everyone,
just leave me the fuck alone. I need to go this way. I'm going to get a gun. All right.
The Yoshi stomp is seriously so good. It was in the middle over in the door, you fucker.
Okay. Guns. Here we go. Shotgun. Sniper rifle. As many shotguns as I can grab. That's not a gun.
Any more shotguns? Isn't there one leaning over here? Just take the other sniper rifle.
Fuck it. All right. Let's go. How did they all get in here? Did you seriously? Did I just get
stopped? That takes priority? This is a fighting game? All right. I got some guns. Still have
orange juice. Unbelievable. All right. Out. Back to the helipad. Give me a cart. Face cam for the
ending. All right. Fine. Not yet, though. I do want a cart. Let's go. By midnight, right? I got time.
I didn't know what just happened, but I'm okay. I never did took care of these guys, did I?
Did it seriously just stop? It's broken already. I was going to say, give me a break. What's wrong
with this thing? I can't use it outside. I got, I have time. I'm okay. I got ammo. I got decent
healing. By decent healing, I mean none, but I'm going to go in here and I'm going to go up and
I'm going to make another smoothie. Smoothie. Smoothies with orange juice. And then I'm going
to try to get the blue chainsaw. You feeling me here? You understand what I'm saying, right?
Okay. I got to go up every time. Leave me alone. You guys are just fucking aggravating me. Just
aggravating. Time check. Close. Let's go. It's a lot of fucking time. I don't have time to get the
chainsaw. What are you doing? I need a sword, weapon, something, a weapon of some kind.
Fuse the smoothies together. No, I need a weapon of some kind. A katana. Where's a katana? The
sword is next to you. It's right next to me. It's over the ledge. You kidding me? Like over here?
Where? Holy shit. What is this? A katana. Which thing sucks? Okay. Let's go. All right. Now,
what time is it? Where do I go? Just back to the maintenance room? What's over here?
I have to go to the helipad. So just to go back. Okay. I'm going to slow down. I just have to go
to where... leave the game and just go upstairs, right? Like go back to the security room and go
upstairs. Okay. I want to make sure I get this right. That's correct. Okay. I'm okay. Don't
break on me now. I have to save the damn game. Okay. I'll do one swing. What's going on?
Jessica McCarney, talk about your close calls. You contacted us just in time. Your boss thought
we should have a talk with you before the operation begins. We'll be taking you into custody.
If you sign an agreement to keep your mouth shut about all this, you'll be free to go. I don't know
why I thought that was me. I was like, is this like a cut scene where I got dressed and got a gun
and everything? Uh-oh. Well, that's not good. Pretty good observation. Yeah. That was not good.
I got 15 minutes. Jesse, you all right in there? Are you just taking out some anger
against like a punching bag or the wall? Are you just unloading a clip into something?
If only Brad was alive. Time until hello. Oh, I have 12 hours and 13 minutes. Well, I'm here.
Wait, is everybody turned? Is everybody a zombie now? That's not good. Is it the thing I said
before but not the thing I said? Just like the reverse what I just said? Everybody's a zombie.
Guys, that's not a bad photo. I got our head upside down. All right. Let's get out. I got to
do this right. That's okay. That's I'm trying to zoom. How do I zoom in with sniper rifle?
To hold the button down? How do I shoot it? Oh, okay. That's how. Okay. What? What happened?
What happened at 12 hours? They're clearing this out. This is fine. Uh, anybody left in here? I got
some bad news guys. There's nobody here. Um, okay. I'm gonna change this slot to right in the middle.
There's a note on the table. Frank while you're out some crazy people snuck in from the rooftop
and started snatching people. I heard a hell of a racket coming from the monitors where the
monitors are. So I'm taking a talk taking advantage. I might not look the type but I've got a small
aircraft pilot's license. I haven't seen Jessie. There's no time to look for her now. I've got to
get out while I'm getting good. I hope you don't think I'm a coward. If we meet on the other side,
I definitely owe you a drink. Good luck Frank. Otis Washington. Really? Helipad? Is it me and
Otis gonna just take off? I'm out of here. Let's go. Wait, he ditched me. He left? What time is it?
Well, what the hell am I supposed to do now? Just, can I just stay in there for 12 hours?
Yeah, I have until noon. Okay. So I guess I'm just gonna go out here and see what's going on.
The mall is now my oyster. Yes. Yes. I feel so good. Wait, there's people in here now.
The random dickhead with the katana is not going to stand a chance right here.
Crazy guy with a katana. Oh, fuck. What is happening? Okay. I'll take one of these. I'll take
two of these. I'll take three of these. You know what? I'll take four of these. Sounds good to me.
How cool is this to use? Pretty cool. All right, I got 11 hours. Let's just have, let's play. Oops.
All right, I'm gonna go get the chainsaw. Nectar. Still haven't figured out what this does.
Does it spawn a queen or something? All right, I'm gonna save it. Put your cam on. I will when
there's one hour remaining. Wait, Isabelle is still up in like the room, isn't she? All right,
I'm gonna go get the chainsaw and I'm going up and I'm gonna go talk to Isabelle. Oh shit,
they're right here. That's kind of awful. I mean, like these guys are awful. There's
iframes on that so I can only shoot them like once. What was the, I just got achievement. What
was the achievement? Was there somebody in like a flannel shirt? Anybody know what that was? I
didn't see it. I just saw it pop up for a quarter of a second. All right, I'm good. Now we're going
to go up to Isabelle and see what the hell she has to say. Going the right way, right? No, absolutely
I'm not going the right way. Go get the book. Shoes? I can't take any shoes. This is the one
opportunity I have. They don't sell shoes here. Give me that gun. I hate this fucking streamer.
Bug? Not even worth it. Oh fuck, there's somebody behind me. Where did you guys come from? Thanks
for letting me drink the whole thing, dumbass. Okay, so I'm gonna go up. We're gonna save here
and I'm gonna go to the hideout. All right, they're dropping in from there. It's kind of
hard to see. I've got an itchy fucking whole face. My entire face is itchy. Where's the other guy?
There's another guy shooting. From where though? I can't see him. I hear it. Where is he? Where is
he? There he is. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Yeah! Bullet point achievement unlocked. Straight ahead.
Left. Bullet point. What's that mean? Isabelle at 10 p.m. What is that? What are you talking about?
Okay, so I got... Oh shit. Okay, so I have... Isabella is down... straight down here, right?
Like right here? It's right here, isn't it? Correctly. What am I catching your breath?
What are you taking a breather, Frank? Oh for the love of god, why do you have to fall on the ground?
Is this the one over here, right? Oh fuck. Oh fuck, I didn't know they were gonna be here.
Get up! Get up! Did I make it in time? 10 a.m.?
Sexy and incoming Jerma, seriously? That's one of the most absurd things I've ever heard.
I've lost all track of where these save points are at this point. I have to be back here at 10 a.m.
Nothing's changed at all. They never admit when they're at fault. They didn't at Seneca Bay
say they won't know. She's right. If we die here, the evidence will be covered up and the truth will
stay in the shadows forever and nothing will change. That's why we got to survive. We'll let the
military to their work, then make our move. All right, what time is it right now? It is 2 15 a.m.
p.m.? 2 15 p.m.? So I have to be back here at by 10 a.m. So then just live, just hang out,
just survive until 10 a.m. Talk to her and then by 12 be back on the helipad. Got it. So in the
meantime, I have time to... I don't even know what the hell I want to do. Go to the grocery store?
Make some smoothies? Save Brad. Find shoes. Save Brad. Is that even possible at this point?
Where's Brad? Okay, so I'm going to go to the grocery store. Where's that grocery store? It's
a huge grocery store, is it? It's back here. Should I even... 11 a.m. not 12 a.m., please.
Wait a minute, what do you mean 11 a.m.? I fucking hate these stupid zombies. I have to go back this
way. That lady just fucking blocking me. Honest to God, why don't I just like stand in that room for
four hours? Where's the other one? The one dead? Oh my God. Where's the other one? With... Excuse me?
Excuse me? Really? Oh yeah, yi. Okay, left. I was distracted. That's fine. Okay, level up apparently.
New skill mastered. You mastered the hammer throw skill. There's a bike here.
All right, I'm gonna just hang out in the grocery store. Is there a blender in the grocery store?
Just get a bunch of milk? It's not a bad idea. Is that it? There can't be any more of these guys.
Seriously. All right, this is... I can get orange juice. I think I'm going full on orange juice.
Yeah. All right, two full guns. The chainsaw. Give her the clean. Pretty nice throw. All right,
so I got insane amount of health. All right, I'm just gonna drink... I said muc. I'm gonna drink
milk until I puke. Time check. This is the most military I've seen anywhere. They're all in the
grocery store. Is that 10? 12 military in the grocery store? Okay. I bet that guy die. Shoes.
I'll be taking this. No, no, I won't. Motorcycle. Where am I going? He's just driving around a
circle. I forget where it is. It's over here. Did I get actually stopped by like the ribbons?
I have to save it. Four. Hey, I'm back. Shoes now. Shoes now. Shut. Helipad at 11, not 12.
I'll get there. Go get the chainsaw books. Nice fish at the end. Thank you for that.
Where are the chainsaw books? Grab a zombie and give them a good shove.
Press X and A simultaneously while standing at a zombie's side. What? Did I do it?
Oh look, that's me in the zombie apocalypse. Remember from yesterday?
Jeremy, you have like no awareness. You would die. Yeah, this is what you think I'm gonna do.
Not that. You already saw it. This. Now I'm gonna turn around. I'm gonna go... I want the motorcycle
first of all. Motorcycle time. The military respawn, I would assume. Oh my fucking god.
Get the hell away from me. Suction cup zombie, the video game. They're like octopuses. No, I
want to take them. All right, let's go. I want the motorcycle, which is down here. Straight ahead.
I looked over and glanced over and just read, are you going to pee before playing Dead Rising 2?
I'm just sitting there thinking, uh, yeah, probably. I would think so. I would hope so.
Should I get the second chainsaw? I'm gonna get the second chainsaw. Uh, let's replace.
All right, I have room for it. Okay. I got on my neck. Frank, you got so far.
I'm stuck. No, shit. Oh, fuck. We got a backup. Oh, you got more backup. How many are gonna come up
here? The fourth? You're gonna get like six? How many? Okay, this is number four. Any others in the
area that you'd like to call for? I'll wait for it. Found him. Where's the fifth guy? Come on.
Let me have this. They're leaving. All right, I've had enough. He has his watching. Is that it?
That was a stream sniper.
Oh, that's fucking funny. All right. Can I actually not get this out of here?
Hi. That's okay. No, I can't. It's over. Shoot metal. All right. Well, I just Wario'd my bike
from Smash Brothers. Are you happy? No, I was standing here. All right. Time for... What are
you guys doing behind in the toy store? These two guys are just hanging out behind of the cache here.
Okay. Leave them alone. No, it's time to get shoes. What time is it? Five. I wish I had that
motorcycle. That would be really great right now. Shoes. What about over here? Food court. I'm gonna
go back. I'm gonna go. I'm gonna. Yeah, I'm gonna go to the food court. Almost a little 32. Where is
he going up there? I'm gonna make a couple more smoothies with the orange juice so I have more
room and then I could do... Oh, hold on. I can do this. Wait. Oh, hold on. What about... Okay, zucchini.
Okay. Hear me out. Zucchini and corn. All right. Let's try that. Keep the guns. I'll get... Don't
worry. I'll have plenty of them. These guys are lying around dead everywhere. All these guys do
is just request the emergency dunces. Okay. And bring the wine too. All right. I should get
something interesting out of this. Fuck. You guys. Are they just spawning? I think they're spawning.
More stock. Any more wine? No. Can I please just blend in peace? More corn. All right. Oh,
let's get rid of one of these guns. There we go. Blender. Here we are. All right. Here we go. Let's
do corn and orange juice. Zucchini and orange juice. Corn and zucchini. Corn and orange juice.
Wine and corn. Corn and corn. Let's do corn and orange juice. It's a nectar. How about zucchini
and corn? That's different. Spitfire. I still don't even know what this does.
How about... We have an ingredient in here. How about flour and orange juice? How about... That's
a big knife. I got enough. Okay. I can get two guns. Knife and chainsaw. That's not how this
works. All right. So I have wine and... I gotta do one of the things. There's gotta be one other
ingredient lying around somewhere, like right here. There we go. Wine and corn.
Cash register and gun. Oh, there we go. There's a quick step. That's very useful. Energizer.
Although... So I got one, two, three, four, five full heels, two super chainsaws, and a huge amount
of guns. And we got six o'clock. I got a couple hours. I'm gonna head... I'm gonna make my way back.
Let's go. I'm gonna go back to Isabella, because that's the right thing to do,
because it's gonna take me a little while to get up there. Straight up. Save the game. Up there.
If there's a place to get shoes, I will get them. And they have to be actually on the way. I'm gonna
replace this cleaver, by the way. I actually don't even have a cleaver. Never mind. Shoes. Casual
gals. There may have been somebody in here at one point. Shoes of a lifetime. I can't take any of
these shoes. All right. Save point. I went to two shoe stores. Am I hitting the wall?
That's the threat. That's what you should have been shooting at. Good work.
The zombie walking around at one mile per hour was the real threat. Not the guy unloading a full
magazine into your body. These guys are great. Shoes! There's no shoes. No shoes. I'm sorry, guys.
Save point right here. All right. All the way at the top. The first one is the real save point.
I have to go to the dressing room? Yeah, but it doesn't take off all my clothes. I don't want
to lose my red dyed hair in my white suit. Leave me alone. I got the... Now this is gonna be great.
Check this out. Actually, I don't want to use any heels at the moment. Let me slow down. So then,
I'm gonna get the motorcycle and ride it back. Could be good, right? In fact, I'm just gonna go
to the grocery store and just drink orange juice until it's time to go. That sounds like a pretty
good idea right now. The military? Just making sure there's no military. There are military,
but they're not here. Let's go. All right, I gotta get in the corner here. Yeah, just drink.
I just got this shit out of me. All right, there's a lot more in here. I gotta get a gun.
Where are they? Two more coming down the aisle. There they are. Uh-oh. Where's the other gun?
I killed them up here. Come on, where's the machine gun? Hurry up. Come on. Here we go. Bitch,
get out of my way. Fuck me. No, don't you dare! Where's this other guy? This military dude? There's
two over here. Dead. All right, is that it? Is this what I have this whole place to myself? Now,
I'm just gonna eat bread until I shit my pants. All right, done. I do want like two more orange
juices. Raw meat. I'm worse than a zombie right now. All right, I'm good to go. The plan is to
leave here with two machine guns. Take an orange juice. I'm gonna test it. So replace. Give me...
I need a better one than this. All right, there we go. Good. What do we got for time? Seven,
almost eight. Uh-oh. It's getting to be late. I need a machine gun with 150. 150 in both. Good.
All right, motorcycle time. And it's time to go to Isabella. And the motorcycle actually will
not be there when I get back, will it? So, hmm. Try jump. How do I not do the down stop?
Oh, I want someone to explain it to me, right? That's what I usually say. All right, I'm here.
I'm gonna save it. And then we're just gonna hang out. I'm at the end game. I'm almost at the
finale. Eight o'clock. Face cam. I will. You know what? Let me take this opportunity. I'm
gonna go pee one more time. I'll be right back. You can just watch the clock. I'll be back by
nine. See? I thought you'd be back before nine. This is kind of nice, actually. I've been so up
against the clock that all I have to do now is just wait. We want hair content. Can you imagine
somebody telling you, hey, can you meet me back here at 10 a.m.? You say, yeah, that sounds like
a plan. I sure will meet you here at 10 a.m. You go, all right, bye. See you later. We're gonna do
lunch. And you get, you like go, standing outside like the restaurant, just going like this
for two hours. And you show up like five, 10 minutes early. And the fucking person is just
standing there going like this. And you're like, hey, you want to start early? And this is like
in their own world. Or imagine like, hey, I'll pick you up at eight. Or I'll pick you up at 10.
Meet here. And you just stand here and do this. Oh my god. Okay, nine a.m. Wait, can I fight up here?
When your villagers want to come over in Animal Crossing, you just sit there and just stare at
the clock. Wash my hair. I actually used a different conditioner today and it's like weighing it down.
I won't be using it again. When you talk to her, there's just a normal text box.
Okay. Somebody just gave money. Ishanji gave 5,000 bits. Thank you, Ishanji. And they say,
very, very, very good stream today. You didn't get flaccid locked at all. Terminator 5,000.
Thank you for the 5,000 bits. Thanks for the Terminator bits. Is the new Terminator movie good?
Is it out yet? No, that was the most unanimous no I think I've ever seen.
Usually one person in chat will be like, I'm gonna be contrarian and say yes. I think that was like
600 no's in a row. Damn. But thank you, Ishanji. Thanks for the 5,000 bits, man. Wait, I have to
go through my photos and see which ones I like. You know what I'm saying? Delete. Hmm. This is
just terrible. This is just, I don't like... That one's okay. This one's better because the
neck is like turned completely upside down. It's like when a dog hears a strange noise.
Or when you start talking to your dog and you start talking in a weird voice instead of going
like, hey, like Otto, you go like, hey, you're Otto. And they're like, what the fuck are you doing?
They get gamer neck. I'm like, hello, Otto, Otto, Otto. And he's just like, can somebody tell me
what happened? I was in the shower and didn't see what happened to her. Oh, that's a spoiler.
It's just blood. This is the girl that fell down. I actually quite like this. I like that one.
I like this one too. I like the guys on the left. This is a perfect photo of how the AI in this
game is fucking stupid. It's every person is doing something else that was aggravating during the
course of the game. Guy on left just standing staring blankly won't move. Lady with the sword
in the back that has a weapon that's running in a completely opposite direction scared. Person with
the gun in the middle that you give the gun to hoping they'll do something. They're looking at
the sky and a gun is pointed towards the floor. Lady in the front is angry and pissed off and
won't listen to you. And guy is hiding behind her to not get killed. Or in fact, you know,
that person might just be stuck in the middle. Keep this one. This is my favorite picture of
the whole entire game. This guy's Peyton Manning. Nationwide is on your side. There he is again.
Is that an explosion over there? Why is Nathan always just somehow sort of in the picture?
It's like he doesn't want to be on camera. He's like dodging. Keep that one for sure.
Keep them both. I like this one because this is this is like me and you decided to do like a shoot
and I'm doing different angles and telling you to do the same pose.
I'll keep Ronald. Keep the mirror. Keep, okay, keep like the transition into pants.
No, this is just a dream he's having. All right, I want to keep like the dream.
Rock bottom off the Titan Tron. Absolutely. And I've had this one since the very beginning.
And it's the first like photo I took. I think those are keepers. I kept this one, right? Yep.
Take that. Wait, do I? I might need it. No, I don't. The game's over. Okay. Did I just
burn some time or was it paused? Am I gonna play Dead Rising 2? I would say at this point,
absolutely yes. We'll see where we can fit it in over the next like month or so. Dead Rising 2
sucks. I don't remember being bad, although I did only play like two or three hours of it.
That's the one guy. That actually kind of was a one guy opinion. Yeah, you're right.
I hope you guys weren't lying to me and I hope this is really actually gonna happen.
What about Dead Rising 3? Once we go past 2, we're really gonna have to see if people are
exhausted with Dead Rising. I'm gonna try to break them up to a point where it doesn't happen
immediately, but I don't remember Dead Rising 3 being very good. That's when they made the change
to like new generations, right? Like Xbox One. 3 is meh, 4 is bad. I remember playing one of them,
maybe even on stream. I think I did stream the fourth one. I'm getting like these weird
flashbacks of actually playing the fourth one on stream. I made a video on the third game,
but the fourth one though? I remember there was a guy like you have like this machine gun
and there's a person up on like a rafter and you're shooting like a minigun at them and I
remember saying this game sucks. I remember being like this is fucking stupid. This is terrible.
It was at that moment is what I remember. That's 4. Okay, almost time. You made a video on the
fourth one as well. Maybe that was like one of the last. Yeah, I'm sorry. I just don't remember. I
remember like if whether it was a video or stream, I just remember doing it. Save it right here.
Never played this one though all the way through. I'm gonna go all the way to the bottom.
I wonder if they'll do a Dead Rising 5 after people are just like meh. Like the last two
weren't very good. I wonder if we'll get another one. You can't throw stuff in Dead Rising 4. Now
that's a reason to just refund the game immediately when you get it. Maybe we'll get a like back to
Formula Dead Rising 5. That'd be kind of cool. Have they talked about it at all? Almost 10. All
right, I'm ready. I got the face cam on for the final like fight. 4 was basically a soft reboot
and they fucked it up. Yeah, that's unfortunate. They advertised 4 as back to Formula. There we go
and two hours. Well that's kind of what they're saying with like Diablo 4 and I mean that game's
like four years out probably. Hey, we're going back to like the, you remember Diablo 2? You loved
Diablo 2. Remember how dark and scary it was and how much blood there was? It's like, I mean yeah,
I kind of, you loved that game and we're gonna go back there. It's like well okay, we'll see
what you do in five years when it comes out. All right, 10 a.m. Let's go. It's almost time. Don't
worry about me. Save yourself. Is that, that's what I had to do? To the helipad now. All right,
I'm gonna grab motorcycle and I'm gonna get the hell out of here. Can I go there? What's the
fastest way? Straight and then straight. You had to do this or else a guy doesn't show up.
It seems a little strange. All right, motorcycle. Give it to me. The one guy? That was definitely
not one guy telling me to talk to her at 10 a.m. If by one guy you mean like one collective group
of humans that were all in this chat at the same time. Please tell me the motorcycle's still there.
It is. The lights are all on. All right, let's go. So we're gonna go straight out this way.
Yeah, just around the corner. Okay, straight. And then through the park. Is it this way, right? Yeah,
okay. Can I leave here with this? I can't, can I? Oh, that's stupid. All right, whatever.
At least it took me far. It took me far. Bang a left. Yeah, no song. Everything's dead and no song.
I'll save it too before I go through. Nice and sunny out though. That's a good thing. All right,
and then straight this way. I'm gonna save it right here. Shoes. No shoes in there. No shoes in
there. It has to be on the way. I can't put on anything. I can't. What am I trying to do?
All right, we got a save point right there. That was literally a shoe store.
The old toy box and toys for children? They're on. First time I've worn shoes. All game. Now I'm
ready to absolutely destroy the end of this game. One hour. Let's go to the helipad. Just a clean
run. That's good. Although I kind of want some to eat. Well, that should be fine. Is there food in
this box right here with food in it, right? Yeah, not very good food, but it's something.
Let's go. Am I gonna play Luigi's Mansion 3? Probably not. Not on stream at least.
Actually, I can save it here too. Any more notes? I mean, it looks all right. It looks fun,
but I hadn't played really the first or the second one. So it'd be like kind of just jumping in
to the third game. It's not that I don't want to play it.
Okay, that's good. Now let's go up. Which way is it? This way? How the hell do I get up? Here we go.
Eleven o'clock. I'm here. I'm ready for the helicopter to pick me up. I missed it. No, I didn't.
It's at an hour. 1101. I did miss it. No emotion for one hour. Nice to be a weirdo. Nice kill count.
3412. That's not good for just a one-off playthrough. I do have lots of heals though.
I should be fine. It's because daylight savings time. I'm just gonna hide up here.
All right, do I have to wait? Do I have to be physically standing on the helipad?
Yes. All right, I'm gonna go right in the middle of the H. 1120. Actually, that is like a stupid
thing I just did, but it's not an actual like organized inventory. You know, so I can act like,
oh, melee. I'm not cycling all over the place to find stuff. I mean, it's categorized.
Juices aren't organized next to each other. I did it by type and then color. No, that looks
much better than there being. No, it's like orange. Four orange in a row and then white,
then dark blue. Opposite ends of the color spectrum. You guys don't know color theory?
15 minutes. Slime him. He said orange. Not today. All right, what would it take? What would it take,
do you think, for me to throw all my items over the edge? Just throw all my healing and the,
just throw everything over the fence. Don't do it. All right, I'll throw one orange juice.
There's no way. Don't. Don't do it. Don't do it. I'm gonna throw the orange juice over the cliff.
I have five minutes to decide if I'm gonna throw the orange juice. Did I do it? I did it.
Where's the helicopter? It's gonna be Otis. The orange juice gets thrown back over.
Let's go. Boom! Missile. Right? That's what happens in these games. This is the setup for these
deaths. It's over. It's gonna get shot down. I knew it. I told you. I knew it. Do I have to fly the
helicopter? Way too much celebrating before anything. Way too much yeah, yeah, oh yeah,
oh yeah, yeah, yeah. It's over. I lose. Way too much yeah, here we go. Like, get your hands on the
wheel. I don't know. Something was in my view. Something distracted me. It looked like an orange.
Did I actually lose? So the whole game is based around the helicopter pilot doesn't get bit by
a fucking zombie at the last 30 seconds. I don't get out. What? Yeah! Nice work everybody.
Wait a minute. The guy from stage right is gonna bite me. You wasted three days.
We told you not to throw the orange juice. It's not over. I have overtime. What? They're gonna
get another helicopter? What did you do? I didn't do anything. It's not the end, really.
That's so funny. This five endings, you just got the Brad ending, but this ain't bad.
That is the canon ending. Why didn't you get more erotic points? Does it count how many pictures,
like how many points I had? Jeremy's a prude. No, I took plenty of photos. We'll just put it that way.
You did great, Jeremy. I'm proud of you. Thank you. All right. Was more? Let's see. I'm willing to
give it a keep going. Oh, by the way, now we need content. You've been looking at, yeah,
I wish you could see the faces I'm making right now into the camera.
Nope. Okay. Exclamation point. Turn on cam. It's going to be an actual, a new command that if it
happens 50,000 fucking times, the webcam will turn on. Oh, you guys are really hammering this,
huh? All right. Hey, hey, PP earned two million ending a bonus. 50,000 PP, zombie kill count,
15,000 PP, photo score bonus, bonus current. I just got a lot of survivor chart. Am I playing
guess who? Brad is up there. Barnaby's up there. You, Barnaby can survive too.
Who made it? Tad, Alyssa, Jonathan, and Brett, all dead. And if I'm honest,
good. I don't remember coming. Oh, Ronald dead. Wait, why am I dead? I'm dead. Frank is dead.
What? Wait, I'm dead? How did I die? Brutality, 29. Drama, 44. Erotica,
eight. Take what? Horror, 76. I didn't take any.
That's funny. End? Special forces boots have been added to the security room. Overtime mode has
been added to the title screen. Choose save game slot and save Frank's status. When you begin a new
game, you can play with Frank's current status. I got, I unlocked shoes. Wait, what's the matter
with me? Oh no, he's been up here. He's been up here for two days and he's only had orange juice.
Why didn't you bring any meat or any vegetables? And what's that I see over the balcony? A full
orange juice. It wasn't easy getting you back here by myself, you know. All right, Frank's still
alive. Lapsed on the roof. Wait, does that mean? Why would I not remember this? Didn't this happen
like 42 minutes ago? Orange juice overdose? Orange juice hangover. I don't know. I just don't remember.
You have gotten yourself infected somehow. That's the way every character laughs before
they do something insane. The time between infection and zombification differs greatly
from person to person. You're lucky, Frank. You seem to have a very high level of resistance.
So, uh, so what you're saying is that I get to spend longer waiting for the inevitable. Is that it?
You know, I'm not sure lucky is the word I'd use. I can't wait to get the super boots.
Are they there now or do I have to actually go to a different game mode?
A helicopter crashed. No one's coming to help us now. It's over for us. What we do. I can't believe
that I unlocked super shoes. The game was taunting me. What if there was some way to impede the
infection? I feel like you guys made that happen. Could extract and administer a large dose of
hormones from the corpus alatum of an adult queen. It would potentially hinder the growth
of the larva in your blood, retarding the zombification problem. Hang on a sec. I don't
understand a word you just said. What are we supposed to do? I'll need certain supplies to
get this to work. And queens. How many queens? As many as you can get your hands on. All right.
Uh, can you, can you say like eight? Sounds like a plan. It's sitting around here waiting to die.
Did time go backwards? 24 hours remain until frank zombification. What do you mean 24 hours
remain? All right. I got, uh, that's 33. All the way to the bottom. So I have to do this.
What in the name of God is going on here? Um, first aid kit, blender, coffee filters,
magnet. Let's go. All right. Cold spray. Where are, okay. Let me see where these all are.
I'm going to say we're going to grocery store down and we're going to wrap around a complete
circle. And we're going here this way. Grocery store first. Bang left. What is this? This is
not over time. This is, there are drones. Wonderful. Are they military too? There is.
It's just military and drones for the rest of the game. I'm getting the motorcycle and just
driving around. I hear a drone. I hear drone. I hear drone. How do I stop the drone? Holy
shit. That was really easy. I need to go into the grocery store. Turn around. And then I'm
going to go down with the motorcycle. What if I just don't even care? Just run. Ooh,
I got to kill this guy. Get in. The motorcycle is still here. All right. What was, what is actually
in this though? Oh man. I'm a pain in the ass. There's no better way to kill these guys than
just to unload like this. All right. What am I looking for? A chainsaw, but they'll shoot me.
All right. Pharmacy. Save the chainsaws. Yeah, I think so too. Okay. First aid kit. There it is.
You obtained first aid kit. Keep going. Grab motorcycle. Go straight down into the jewelry
store. It's as easy as that. Emergency backup. This is going to fill up. I'm going to drink the
milk and get an orange juice and then leave. In fact, get two orange juices.
Is that attack increased to 200%. Does that include guns too? That sounds like a lot.
All right. Take another orange juice. Two is fine. Let's go. I got plenty of time. So the idea is
just to go bang a right and go straight down. Hopefully keep the motorcycle with me as long as
I can. And then where's this next one? Down or up? Looks like it's just to the right.
I'm just looking at necklaces. Good. What am I looking for? Right there. Magnifying glass. Got it.
Um, you're going to think I'm crazy for this, but I'm not going to save the game because I'll lose
the bike. I'm going to save the game when I'm at the last place. All right. Food court. Straight
ahead. Blender. I can't make any more drinks. Keep going. Come out out of here. Wrap around.
All right. I think I have to lose the motorcycle. Yep. I think. Yeah, I do. Go straight through
down the entrance plaza. Pick up the bike. I can't pick it up. Okay. Now I've got a save
point to the right. I'm going to use it. Quick step. Not yet. I don't need it. Where's the drone? I
could hear it. Where's the drone? There it is. Not reaching. Yeah. Get on the treadmill. Get on the
treadmill. Get on the... Got it. There's nothing in here. It's all in the entrance plaza. Essentially
I'm as bad as it could have been. So this is just a way for you to just keep playing and messing
around. That's kind of cool. Although the one thing I would say is... Holy shit. Holy shit.
Holy shit. Holy shit. Not a chainsaw. Drink. Oh, it's two hits. You gotta be kidding me.
You gotta get real close though. All right. I get to replace it. That's so awesome.
Makes me so happy. It's like I didn't even do anything. Let's go. 22 hours until zombification.
I guess there's a couple places here. Drones. I hear it. Where are you? This one's definitely up.
If they took inventory slots, this would be pretty much impossible.
It wouldn't be actually impossible, but it would be sort of impossible.
Where is this up here? Cosmetics. There it is. Perfume. And then straight down.
There's a save point in there too. Who cut the lights? Gotta go all the way down. All the way.
Oh, my little fetch quest. I actually would rather there be zombies. Because these guys are annoying,
but their danger only actually comes out if there's more than two or three of them all
aiming at you at the same time. They just sort of walk in straight lines. Where is this person?
So they're like a zombie. Yeah, but these guys can do like four cheese slices of health in one second.
Takes a lot longer for a zombie to do that. All right. This door right here and then right across
the street. What is it? Tie? Shirt? In the back room. Yeah, just be glad they can't grab you.
That's true. That would suck. Am I in the wrong store? Is it below me? I think it's below me.
Groomens? Hammer? A bicycle? How have I not found this at all this whole time? Did I get distracted
by the bicycle? What was it? It's right here. What is it? The shelves? Camp stove. Okay. Give me the
bike. This is gonna end very badly. Can I jump? All right. It's the one. It's upstairs. Can I ride up
the stairs? Come on, you off-road. Let's do it. This is like the 7-Eleven? Which one? Someone buy me.
Where the fuck is it trying to get me to go? The exit door? Oh, fuck. I didn't even know they were
up here. Die. Go in here, I guess. So it's in the security room. In fact, I should probably put it
as cold spray coffee filters developing solution. Oh, like a developing solution, not the solution
for what you're trying to do is currently developing. Where's this trying to get me to go?
Coffee filter? It's right here. Coffee filters. Where are the boots? Are they right there?
Yeah. I lost my clothes. Yeah. They're behind the vent? Where? Go back? Yeah. Yeah. They have to be
in another safe. Speaking of saving, they have to be in the new game. That's all right. No. No. No.
No. No. What do you mean no? Do you see boots? I don't. There's lockers back here.
Yeah. Well, that's all right. I'm glad with this. I'll take my grandma's rug. Yeah. Oh, but what
about the red one? I got red hair. Yeah. What about the snake? Yeah. Yeah. All right. Good.
Yeah. No. This is just default. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I had on. And new glasses. Yeah.
My hair. Fuck. It's all right. I'll just go with the grandma rug. Well, I don't, I don't see them
anywhere. I do not think they're here. So let's go. I have 24 hours to live. I don't really,
I don't really care about my hair color right now. Under the table. Lockers behind the stairs.
I just used these. I just did all this. All right. I'm out of here. I'm leaving. Where are the last
two? There's one right here somewhere and then there's one down. Cold spray developing solution.
The camera store is the other one. So let's do cold spray. Reload. Reload. I see what you're doing.
Wait, is it in here? Oh, this is actually not good. Don't I need queens? Oh shit. I need queens.
Cold spray in the skateboarding store. Really? That's stupid. Okay. All of a sudden,
it's like a party in here now. Okay. Any queens? Only one more thing to get. It's below me. It's
the camera store and it's developing solution. Camera. Hey. No. Next one. Got a ball. All right.
Let's finish this. Now I got to get back to up here. What's the fastest route? Wonderland up.
Yeah. Bathroom shortcut. Well, I'm guaranteed at least two queens. At least. Watch out. I don't
get swarmed here. So now I just bang right and go straight up. On to part two. I hate this new outfit.
This looks uncomfortable. I know what this feels like. It's gonna be itchy and hairy and spiky at
the same time. I'm gonna get some more juices. Is this even worth doing? It's not. Straight on.
Go straight on. I brought the ingredients. Help me. Help me. Help me. Help me.
I just dump them all. I open up my giant fucking dad smoking jacket and they all fall out.
When I was working in the medical lab, my brother asked me to research a method of suppressing a
parasite. Of course, back then we didn't extract the hormones directly. We synthesized them in the
lab. So he was looking to protect himself from his own terrorist scheme. He wanted a way out. Is
that it? I don't know. I know he didn't bring the drug with him here. I have no idea what he intended
to use it for. You think I'm just making excuses, but Carlito kept things from me.
Even if this is ugly, the whole thing is this. I could handle the jacket if the pants were different.
It won't completely cure me. It just looks like I got run over by a car. I have like tire tracks all
over me. I got run over by 15 cars in a row. The parasite will develop as it normally would,
continuing the zombification process. You look like a bad couch. Yeah, not just a bad couch,
a couch that's sitting at the end of somebody's driveway that just says free on it. What happens
to all those free couches that nobody takes? They just go to the same place, huh? Into the landfill?
Just how long do you suppose your drug will prevent me from turning into a walking corpse?
During my research, I was never able to conduct proper clinical studies.
To a certain extent, the period of effectiveness depends on each patient's physiology.
Maybe only a week. There's no way to tell for sure. They're skinned for suits. Well, that makes some
sense.
You had to say they're skinned for sure for suits.
The material on the couch is not the couch's skin.
It's a layer on top of the padding.
To find homes for a large group of children. Want to guess just how many?
Showed all those names. These are the people I saved. You're saying he infected these kids
and then gave them your drug? He made 50 little ticking time bombs? I don't know.
But you have to go find them. They're all scattered around the mall.
These kids are spread all over the country. Nobody up in Idaho, though.
Right. The entire country could be crawling with zombies by now. Just head to Idaho.
Just make your house out of bricks and cement. That we don't know for sure that we can't warn
anyone about. Oh Wyoming for that matter, yeah. We need to do right now. Prepare the hormone
and get you taken care of. Okay, so what's next? Oh no, the generator's broken down. I can't work
without power. Go turn on the generator. There has to be a backup generator somewhere. Carlito was
using the clock tower for storage. Maybe he left one in there. Check out the clock tower. Oh no,
the generator. This is a filler episode. You don't go from there are 50 children spread around that
are all like ticking time bomb diseases to like infect the whole world to go turn the power back
on. Unless you're stretching it a little. How far away is this? It's not that far. It is overtime.
Let's just get out there and do it. Every game has this exact level at some point.
Why is there, what's with the power situation? In every universe there's always like a generator
you need to turn on. Are we just automatically assuming that just all electricity just goes
rotten? It's not like raw hamburger meat. It just stays on. You just need somebody in there to like
keep it turned on and to do maintenance to it. Okay, that's why a face cam's not on because
fucking boogers just shot out of my nose. It takes like a thousand people to keep a power plant
running. Actually I'm getting a cold I think. It started developing right when I got back
from the east coast and it hasn't gone away. It's still here. I haven't got a full-blown cold but
it's not, it's just halfway. A little bit of a scratchy throat and some stuffiness but that's
it. Stay away from it. Just come here for a second. Get away. Just don't come near me. Just come here
for a minute. I'm not infected. I'm not. I'm not. Let's just talk really close. Like shake my hand
and then shake like 10 other people's hands. Can't get in there. What happened? What did the
satellite crash? Oh fuck that's a helicopter. Why does the satellite just crash? That's a stage light.
This is the Truman Show. I know it's bullshit. Okay I've had the generator. It's time to leave.
So I can just leave now, right? That didn't, that seems very simple. Snacks. Imagine dropping your
gun to eat potato chips. You don't have to imagine for very much longer. Straight up. Get queens.
Should I just take a nectar? Take a nectar and just start spraying? Terma not yet. Don't do it.
Don't do it. All right fine. Wait. Nah that's not worth it. Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. How fast do you think I can string the syllables
together? I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going
to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. That's pretty good. Wrong way idiot. Wrong
way. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. Toy
boat. Toy boat. Toy boat. She sells seashells on the seashore. She sells seashells on the seashore.
She sells seashells on the seashore. She sells seashells on the seashore. She sells seashells
on the seashore. She sells seashells on the seashore. I tried it. I did it twice. I don't
know why I just go. What's another one? Give me another one. Give me another one. I know there's
at least like three or four of these that exist. I've done this already. Yeah but what's but how
much wood could a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood? How much wood could a woodchuck
chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood? How much wood could a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could
chuck wood? I'll take another hard one please. Unique New York. Unique New York. Unique New York.
Unique New York. Unique New York. Unique New York. Simple. Any others? Red leather. Yellow
leather. Red leather. Yellow leather. Red leather. Yellow leather. Red leather. Yellow leather. Red
leather. Yellow leather. Um looking at my watch here it's seems like a way I don't know no hard
one. Rubber ducky. What was it? Peter Piper. Peter Piper. What is it? I need the whole line.
Peter I don't know how to. Peter Piper picked a what? Peter Piper picked a pack of pickled
peppers. Peter Piper picked a pack of pickled peppers. Peter Piper picked a pack of pickled
Peter Parker picked a pack of pickled peppers. I had it. I tried throwing a Parker there. Peter
Parker. What is it? Peter Piper. Peter Piper picked a pack of pickled peppers. Peter Piper
picked a pack of pickled peppers. Peter Parker picked a pack of pickled peppers. I'm wasting time.
Thank god you found a spare. Now I'll get back to work. Let me get back to work. If all goes
plan I should have just about all the equipment I need now. Bring me some adult queens and I can
get started. All right. Wristwatch. Hold on let me save this. I'm not saying that. I'll say that
really fast. Oh yeah let me go for it. Now I'm afraid that saying that wristwatch one and me
saying it three or four times in a row is gonna be something fucking horrible coming out of my mouth.
All right here's a queen. One queen. I need at least 10. Are you serious? Where am I gonna get
10 queens? I have to go out to the park, drink nectar, and then mow everybody down. How many
slots do I have? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. I have 10 slots. That's enough
to hold one weapon. Just run zombies over in the tunnel. That's not a bad play. I'm gonna go this
way. Nectar smoothies. Nectar smoothies. Nectar smoothies. Nectar smoothies. Smoothies. Nectar
smoothie. Nectar smoothie. Nectar smoothie. Nectar smoothie. Give me another one. Get off me.
Why did I just pick this up? Why would you ever give this to me? 18 hours remain until you die.
Nectar is just orange juice right? Fuzzy wuzzy was a bear. Fuzzy wuzzy had no hair. Fuzzy wuzzy
wasn't very fuzzy. Now wuzzy. Fuzzy wuzzy was a bear. Fuzzy wuzzy had no hair. Fuzzy wuzzy wasn't
very fuzzy. Wuzzy. Nectar at the uh grocery store. I need to pay attention to the video game. Hold on.
Going into this place I'm gonna get a bunch of orange juice. Orange juice is you can combine
it with anything that makes nectar. Right? Wrong. What? What are you talking about? What do you mean?
Oh fuck. Don't make a joke. Spit fire. I'm not spitting fire. Fire's not coming out of my mouth.
Aim with your fists. This is dumb. I'd rather have a machine gun. Yeah yeah yeah. Give it all.
Stupid. O.J. only. O.J. only. O.J. only. O.J. only. Yeah he really isn't. He's vibrating.
Attack. Attack. Attack. Okay orange juice. Orange juice. Not milk. Disgusting. Orange juice. Okay
I'm giving up one of the chainsaws. No I'm not. Those are very necessary I think. That's five
nectarines. That should do it. If it can't then I don't know what to tell you. To the cafe which
will go down into wonderland. Take the teleporter. Cafe. What do you mean? What am I doing? Why do we
go here? To get this orange juice. Which is at the cafe. Wait blender. Blender in the market?
There's a blender in the grocery store. A blender in the grocery store.
Well why didn't you say so? Why didn't you say so? This is a lie. Is this a is this a is this a lie?
It's a fucking lie. Of course it is. It is. We made it out. Yeah of course we did.
I can't believe I just took one like 10 percent of FHP. I'm I don't even need it anymore. The
battery's over here. The bathroom's over here. I just violently coyote that guy. He's gonna run
into Hogwarts. Maybe. Where are these? So now we go down up. Cafe. I'm gonna sneeze again. I don't
know if my allergies. I don't even have allergies. I made that up. I don't have allergies. Oh my
allergies. I did your toys as well. All right. Pie orange juice.
What? That's what he does. Listen. Why is everybody getting so disgusted when I do
it but he's been doing this the whole game? And that's you're not disgusted by that one.
What do you mean that's me? No it's not. I'll prove it. Ready?
See? See? Why would I mute though? See? Who even cares about this? Nobody. There's so many.
What happened to my gun? I can do one more. Okay. I'm gonna drink this one just to be able to run.
So let's drink this and then where am I running to? I am running to the inside the park over to the
garage. What are you guys doing over here? German WWE. I've seen this already. I've seen it. Just
get queens now. Get queens now. I only see one queen. I have to wait for the nectar to end.
Can I just start killing people with the nectar activator? And does that increase the spawn rate
or am I just making this up? That's not real. No it just spawns. Okay so I need eight more.
One, two, three, one, two, three, four, five, six. Okay I need two more. One, two, three, four, five,
one, two, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. I need to lose the chainsaw unfortunately.
Just kill zombies with it while waiting. Not a bad idea. Why do I hear something? I can't believe
you need ten of these. I hear a queen. Okay. Now queen. No? Come on spawn another one. Marathon
runner achieved. What I run like 20 miles or something. Use my new skill. Oh no. No queen.
The wall kick. Still no queen. This nectar sucks. Idiot spring. Boy. There we go. I have three. I
need six more. So here's the plan. No I can't. They're all dead out here. Never mind. Zombies
that have the hands above their heads spawn the queen. God damn it game. Why?
When shit breaks don't you think you should have like a fucking second. This other chainsaw is
gonna break too. I can always get another one. Give me a queen. Just go farm with the car. Yeah
fuck this. I'm going to the car. Give me the queen. All right do not break these. Do not. I
hear another one. I still hear one. All right I'm close. I'm getting close. All right maybe I don't
need to do that. Just keep killing stuff. Is that guy's hands above his head? That's a queen guy
right? I hear queen. There we go. Let's go. Lucky. I need another gun. I don't have ten. One two three
four five six. I need four more. Ten. What are you talking about? You already gave one. Yeah so that's
one two three four five six. She said I need to give ten more. You dare Jeremy. Don't do it.
I gotta find some more military. No. I gotta kill somebody. Oh somebody with their hands in the
air. All I have is a knife. Hands in the air. Of course the guy shows up right now. I got it all
right. I need one more. One. One two three four five six seven eight nine. I need one more. Let's
get it on the way back. Yeah I need a weapon though. All right teleport. Teleport save.
Like a guitar or something. Hands in the air. Got one. Bye. Although I don't have any. I have
no weapons. Nice job. You fucking. Maybe they'll sing songs about you. Just fuck it and run.
I do have one drink left. All right. Just have to turn right and go straight up. Hopefully I don't
get shot by anybody. Get the motorcycle and we got all the queens we need. In fact I'm gonna drink
this. Wait. Wait. Where is it? Wait. Wait. Wait. Okay. No get on the bike. Get on the bike. Get on
the bike. Fuck it. I was gonna get a katana. Turn it in. Here you go. Bring me more queens. More.
Can I just put them all in the same jar? I'll take another five queens please. Keep it up. I should
be able to make whatever it is we're making. Two more. Three more. Do I have three more?
One last specimen. This is it. You're gonna inject me with that huh? Okay doc. Let's get this over
with. At least I won't have to worry about turning into one of them for a while. That just accelerated
it. Okay. Next on the agenda. Figure out a way to get the hell out of here. While I was isolating the
hormone I managed to identify. I really hope I don't have to go get like 10 frozen pieces or
something. In other words the zombies don't like the way it smells. If you give me a little more
time I should be able to produce some of this pheromone. They think it smells bad? I'm gonna
smear ourselves with the anti-zombie juice. To keep them away from us? You can just walk right past
more queens. 20 this time. That would be horrible.
It's a nice blender. It is.
Experiments will only have enough to use at once. Or 100 times. As long as I save before it happens.
I did not save before it happened. Good. Considering how many of them keep pouring out of here
it must be connected to something. Just throw the bike in the tunnel and just flirt. Any other way
out of here is guarded by the military. If we're gonna get out of here and put a stop to Carlito's
plan we've got to go in there. What was the last time you saved? I'm doing a thing where I
get three save points. I used my last one yesterday at some point. I'm doing like a kind of a hardcore
thing like hardcore night. I think I got it though. I'm going through the same five chat
jokes Jeremy. I'm getting tired. Why do you have to just go through the same jokes?
Whoa. Save game. Did I do it? Are we covered in this? She just holds this magic scroll.
I don't have any weapons. I have like a leader of orange juice. Okay I gotta rock. I gotta
pick up like all the rocks I can. But where do we go from here? Just run? Is she gonna open the door?
Where do I go? Where do I go? Use rock. That looks like I could go in here. Can we open this up? Okay
we can open this together. Are you? Oh she's gonna use her like immolation aura. No I want a German
soup like somebody. Rock good. Rock all I have. Used all inventory slots on orange juice. Speaking
of orange juice I'm gonna need to use it. A queen's gonna spawn. Where's the queen that spawns? We're
drinking a nectar. Why did it? Why am I jumping back here? Hold her hand? I just tried to.
Come here. Give me a queen. We keep getting separated. Dude this game with the hand holding.
You held hands and if you touch anything you just. Oh my god I hate this. Get off of me.
What are you doing? I'm holding her hand and then you. Oh sorry. You held hands but then you.
I'm just gonna run. Hey come here let's hold hands. Hey what do you say we go this way? I have to go
all the way around you to make you go this direction. Let's go. Oh sorry I don't hold
hand anymore. Let's go. Follow me. Give me a rock. At least I got my nectar. Come here. Come.
Knife. Oh it's a pickaxe. Now I don't know why magic is she won't let go.
No there it is. That's right when I say it. Come on. Walk forward. This was the worst vacation ever.
Isn't that what I was doing here? What was I actually doing here? It's okay honey these are
all actors. Really crazy. This is zombie apocalypse. Yeah they can't touch you.
Don't worry if they touch you you can sue them. I'm fucking suing that guy. Are we going here?
Oh shit. Oh honey. I'm gonna have to get all my lorries as well. They're fighting back.
Don't worry honey. I learned this in zangief school.
Get over here please. It's a queen. Give me the queen. Okay okay. What a tough what a stupid
bait that tunnel is. Wait there's more of this shit? This game is fucked. Stay with me. Why would
you let go of me? No you're making this so hard on me. Please come here. I thought I just picked her up.
Queen. No not on top of me. I can't even grab her hand. Press the button.
Stop letting go of me. Why are you letting me? Mr. Queen. It's too late. Does this stuff even
work anymore? This stuff doesn't even work. It doesn't even fucking work anymore. I'm gonna die
here. Did you let go? Hey did you let go? Hey did you let go? All right did you let go again?
I didn't mean to get the ass shot. That's all I can do right now. I just want to hold your hand.
Just please let me get through this ending segment. Walk slowly. I am. I promise. I promise I'm
walking slowly. That's actually a pretty good opportunity for a photo. There's like a million
faces. Yes I am. Yes I am. Yes I am. Yes I am. Oh is that the problem? Trying to figure out what
the issue was. Kill them. Kill them with your scent. You watched it happen. Imagine the smell.
For them I guess they really don't like this. Like a little bit of enthusiasm would be nice.
It's like you don't want to be here. Like you're the one. What did I do wrong there?
I did wrong. She ran the fuck away from me. She fucking ruined it. She just bolted from me
and now we're getting overwhelmed. She's using me as a shield. This is not okay.
Come here. We can't even fucking walk. All right it's time for a zangief. Let's go. Let's go.
Okay good good good good good. Give me a rock. Come here. Right side. All right this is. You got
stuck here last time. You idiot. We somehow went higher up on the rock. How do we get all the way
back up to the top of the rock? No I don't want to go. Stop. No don't. Leave me alone. Help me.
Please. Don't just hit me. No stop going backwards and they all just get on top of you.
Isabella you're going backwards. Are you drinking out of that thing? You're using it as like an
inhaler. All right I made it. Queen give me the fucking thing. Is this thing out of juice?
I've yet to understand what's going on right now. This is unbelievable. This is unfucking
unbelievable. Just run ahead of her? I tried to do that last time. It's over. I have to go get like
guns. I can't just leave. Just save the goddamn game. Use the meat. Yeah easiest have been done.
Why can't we just drop a bomb in here? Instead of making something to make me like live another
three days, you should have made a bomb. You should have made like a bunch of fucking grenades.
I'm doing it this time. Don't let go of my fucking hand.
Wow real hard huh? It took me fucking five tries. How dare you say that and have that happen? How
dare you say that and have what you just saw happen? How dare you say that when there's this
rock here? How dare you say that when this rock exists? How dare you? Somebody just told me to
stop going through the zombies and that's what's working. It's just running is in them right into
them. Oh my god. Let it be over please. What did I just do? I just like Captain Falcon'd over here.
What was that? All right I'll take it. Oh why did you fall? Oh I don't have any weapons.
Hands on your hips really? Don't give me that shit. Hold on let me just stop and push someone.
Is someone going to make that my fault? Unbelievable. Now do it again.
Yeah we have to do it again. I don't have any weapons. I had a whole beehive with me.
I hope so. No don't just do it in the cut scene. Don't make me do this.
All right. Don't make me do this shit. I'm gonna go back here. Did you fall off? Um exactly what
we're doing. Why? Why are we holding hands? I could have just picked you up and been the set.
Why would we need to hold hands for this part? I can't believe it. I want to remember this moment.
Why couldn't I just put her in? Can I be the gunner? Can you just drive?
This doesn't seem fair. I'm gonna keyboard keyboard mouse for this one. Does this thing
overheat? I'm just shooting at the blinking lights. Holy shit this is gonna take forever.
My hand is getting tired. This is stupid. This is so long. Don't lose it now. I'm going fine.
Is that the end of the damn game? These automated machines are no use at all on the battlefield.
Switch to manual control. Phase two. That means if I lose this I have to do that all again.
What now? What? Oh this is gonna come back and just rain fire down on me.
Aim main cannon. So what have we here? I gotta get at least a decent photo before I die. Where
are we hiding when my men mopped up the mall? On a mission in which the number of targets is
unclear. It's difficult to ensure absolute thoroughness. You have imagination. That's
what drives you in your quest to run, quest to hide. His cigar is not lit. As prey you and
much more stubborn than the zombies. That's not. How much do you know about the
zombies? It's like a cinnamon stick. I commanded the Santa Cabeza cleanup operation.
If we had fulfilled our mission then we wouldn't be needed here now to take care of this.
All right I don't have any weapons so can I like beat them with charisma? That's all it was to you
huh? Do I have any dialogue options? What about those innocent people who had to pay for sins
committed by our government? Our mistakes have not begun with this operation. I think I actually
have a piece of meat, a rock, and a knife. Can I beat this guy with a rock? It's self to be quite
adept at making mistakes. Hell it's the only thing we truly excel at. Well then I'd say this mission
isn't quite over yet. Don't you agree? Is the tank alive? Does it have thoughts? We're not gonna have
a shitty version of on top of the Metal Gear Solid fight right? That was embarrassing!
Suplex! What if I go down? It's such a good one. No! I thought I was the cutscene. All right how do I do
moves? Oh wait he's fighting. Will he come down here? Wait a minute. I'm gonna pick up a zombie
and throw it at him. Isabella. Isabella can you fight hand to hand? That's a good photo. Can I like
what's the game plan? Just just do the the stomp. Jump stomp jump stomp over and over again.
Yeah just I'm gonna knee drop over and over. Here we go. I can't do a suplex. All right I'm ready.
That doesn't work guys. He blocks it. Shit. Why don't I have a block? The spin move?
Okay practicing. He's gonna block it. He's gonna block it. He's gonna block it. It's gonna be bad.
And I'm giving myself. This is making this really hard for me.
Just block home. Okay I'm gonna Spinning Lariat. Middle school fight tactics. Get away from me you
bully! Let's go. No don't bite me. It didn't. Get rid of the zombies. Get rid of the zombies.
Kill him. Kill him. Bite him. Somebody bite him. No not me. Oh this sucks. He's stuck. Wait a minute.
Okay easy. Slow down. Take it. Take a second here. I just have to get back on the fucking thing.
Like this. Like that. Okay. Spit on him. This is not gonna work. This doesn't hurt anybody.
Does this hurt? No. I think he's getting hurt by the zombies.
Kill him. His health is going down.
This is. I gotta get a photo. That's right. Farm photos. Oh man that's a lot of photo money.
This is so much.
This is thousands of XP. How much health does he have? I'm level 35.
Get Isabella in the picture too. That's not. Okay good. Let's try that.
She has to be facing the right way. Got it. Can I reach over there? That one's a pretty good one
too. Okay right here. Don't move it. Shit. Kill him. Is there a taunt? How do I taunt? I might
have to get the last hit on him. Otherwise maybe he'll just die. I don't even know what to say
anymore. I've spit out all the fluid in my body. Yeah that's right. All right. Fighting. Fighting
him. I have one HP left. I think I'm gonna be close. Almost got it. Almost got it. Fuck this
is intense. Come on. One more hit. Uh oh. I have to finish him with a spit. I have to jump and
land on top of him with the stomp. Get out of here. He can't even believe it. He can't believe it.
That was ridiculous. Now he epically falls back into the zombies. He did that four or five hundred
times. The last one. That's all I got. I'm going all the way back. Epically. That could have been
really bad. Wait hold on. This is not like a part two part two. That's bad ending? There's a
comic that explains what happens afterward. That's the real ending. No that's the overtime ending.
That's the true ending. Has to be right? Does saving Brad actually do it? Thank you file actor
Lich for the hundred dollars. Ten thousand bits. I missed it. It was fifty thousand. Five thousand
twice. This is the funniest thing I've seen in weeks. Jerma getting rejected. She doesn't
want to hold your hand dude. No we're supposed to be protecting each other. And then is this
what Japan thinks what white people are? No it's Frank West. They keep bringing Frank back.
Well good he's the original. Are they dancing? This is what Canada thinks America is. Well
that was a trip. If that's truly the end. That that was a wild one. I'm surprised I've never
done that before. Let's do Dead Rising 2. But is there another episode? No I'll let you see.
It might be a small little cutscene at the end right? It might be. That was fun. Some of it
for me that was a little all over the place. But pretty damn fun and ridiculous. I look forward
to seeing Dead Rising 2. Play Dead Rising 2 off the record if you want to continue with Frank.
Is that a DLC campaign or is that a main story thing? DLC? So should I do
Frank West's campaign first? Infinite Mode has been added to the title screen.
Do don't do off the record first. Frank West managed to escape the town of Willamette with
information pertinent to the incident under his belt. The news caused a fervor throughout the
world leading the US government to admit at least partial culpability in the livestock research
program. However no connection to the Willamette incident was acknowledged and the events that
occurred there were deemed to work of a fringe terrorist group. The people of world as could be
expected from the modern culture of new- what was that? Soon let the Willamette incident fade from
their minds. The authenticity of Carlito's chilling plan to be utilized the orphans
as his pawns has yet to be fulfilled and yet he complained that his belly was not full.
Right at number one. Nice. Very cool. That's it. I defeated the evil. That's gonna be the end of the
stream. Pretty good place to stop. It's been over seven and a half hours now so I think it's a good
place to call it. The next time you guys see me will be on Sunday for- wait for it- Community
Content Night. Hope you had fun. I did. And I'll see you guys on Sunday. Let's transition out of
here. See you soon. Have a good start to your weekend. Move that out of the way and we can
move to here. Good night guys. And for those of you staying. Hey look. Hey it's the same people
every time. It's never changed. What- oh that's- that's the person's tattoo. That's still saved
here. Anyways let's do the bits. Let's go back to earlier- where were we? Where were we? Where were
we? Seven hours ago. MVM Matt thanks for the 500 bits. Party party party. You have been sleeping
and then you wake up every night. It's pretty interesting. Jerma aka Bath Bomb Boy. Thanks for
the 500 bits. Appreciate it. Much love to you. Thank you the 500 bits. Means a lot. I love the
Bath Bomb Boy. And it's separated by spaces too. That's the best part. It's like James underscore
aka underscore Bath Bomb Boy. That thought goes into every single word. But thank you so much.
I appreciate it. Much love to you. Thank you. Then we had Stinky Beaver for the 250 bits. Dude this
streamer is fucked. Thank you. Appreciate the 250. Bombination zero thanks to the 300 bits. I left
my cookie and my milk and I'm about to drink it. This sucks. Why did you lie? It's good. Wait let
me completely rebuttal that right now. Do you drink the milk after you eat the cereal? Yes or
no? Because that's what eating the cookie at the end- of course you do. Yes. So if you drop a cookie
and you drink all the milk and the cookie stays in there for like five ten straight minutes,
that cookie turns- that's just the same thing as you drinking the milk. I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear it. How dare you? The cookie dissolves and becomes mush. Yeah but a lot of the
cereal coating dissolves and turns into weird gross sugary nonsense in your milk. I like it.
You don't have to like it. Yeah what you can just throw it into the trash? No you scoop it out and
you freeze it and you make a popsicle out of it like a little cookie pop. Up your game. Gnarly
thanks to the 250. I wonder how you feel when you look over a chat and just see a wall of purple
links. Are you saying oh nice a funny picture of my face or are you like god damn it not this shit
again? For the most part I think it's funny. I mean it usually is. That doesn't bother me or anything.
Sometimes I click on a link and it's just like a simple edit with my face green or something
and then other times it's like an insanely elaborate photoshop. Yeah like the one with
my nerd neck. All right well that's all right. We had five communities have some Jeff. I caught it.
Just want to say it again. Thank you. Here comes the third. Okay we need to talk about something
after this. Okay that is sneeze number four or three or four for this stream. I never sneeze on
stream. Why is this happening now? Maybe once in eight hours. It's been four or five times today.
Don't ask me why. Hey alum thanks for the thousand bits alum. Jeremy it's my 18th birthday tomorrow.
Glad I could catch a stream. Thanks for being awesome all these years. Happy 18th birthday.
You can now rent a car. No that's 25. Happy 18th birthday. 24 24 24 whatever. You can rent cars
under 25. No you can't. 25. The minimum age requirement when renting a car in the United
States is 25 years old. That's correct. Yeah that's for real. You didn't know that. But uh
happy birthday seriously. Thanks for the thousand bits. Hope you have a good one tomorrow or it
might be tomorrow already. So happy birthday now. A phylacteryl itch gave 5,000 bits and I think I
missed it somehow on top of the other ones at I believe 150 dollars in bits tonight which is insane.
They say a squirrel on cocaine wouldn't be as twitchy as you are right now. I just I get
panicky in games like this especially with save points and ways to sincerely screw stuff up.
But thank you. Thank you phylacteryl itch. Hyperactive. That's more so just hyper reactionary.
Let me write that word out. That's incorrect. I just needed to see it first. Hyper reactionary.
Thank you sadvegan for the 250. Glad you enjoyed this game. You missed a lot of special bosses with
the psychos which are really cool and warrant maybe a second playthrough. But honestly go for
the second one. The second one is really good. It doesn't have our boy Frank but it's much better.
Definitely recommend playing that now that you kind of know what you're doing. Yeah it seems like to
actually play Dead Rising through. You need to do it three or four times and just go save other
people and then maybe you can get the timing down where you can do everything. But I don't know if
I'd ever be able to do that. I don't think I would be. Oops don't knock that over. Yeah I'll
definitely play too for sure. Smelly boy thanks for the 250. I recently asked a girl if she wanted
to start dating. She said yes. What are some good first dates you can recommend? Guys what is it?
Come on. I've talked about this before. No no I talked about this. No not the carnival. Yes
food network. You put on food network. One of those just diners drive-ins and dive shows.
It can it just it bleeds into itself. You can always talk about something. People are connected
so heavily by food and I'm not even talking about going and eating food. Watching food. You could
eat food too. And what even is a first date anymore? What even is dating a date? You're just going
somewhere. You just you guys are going somewhere to do something. Making dates is like added
pressure for both people I think. Just watch 15 episodes in a row of diners drive-ins and dives.
After you hang out and you're comfortable with each other after like a few times then go bowling.
Because look when you go bowling this is let me listen to me. When you go bowling you are going
to think about every single thing you're doing. You're going to think about how you're moving the
you're going to you have the ball in your hand. How stupid do I look right now? Did I knock down
any pins? Am I going to lose? Should I lose on purpose? Should I try? Should I really go for it
but are they going to like that? Do I look dumb right now? Do I look stupid? Did my mouth open
weirdly when I turned around to like to say hey I got six pins? Don't eat either. Don't go to a
restaurant. I will hit this hammer on the head of the nail over and over again. When you go to a
first or second date to a restaurant someone's watching you eat for the first time. You're like
scared to eat the food because like oh fuck like I don't like I don't want people to watch me eating
and then all of a sudden you got somebody across an incredibly potentially intimate relationship
and you're trying to you you don't want to like stuff your face with a hamburger. You have to
talk to this person. Oh so when did you go to school? Oh fuck I just took a bite. I shouldn't
I just took a bite and I have to speak. It's like being at the dentist. Something easy. Unless what
if you're going somewhere that you can eat with one hand. Maybe ice cream. That's easy. Nobody
looks cool eating ice cream but you're supposed to look cool eating a steak. You are. Oh let me
take out my fork and okay nice nice. So this meat is super. Have you tried this yet? Yeah let me cut
a nice thing and you don't want to be sitting there like gnawing up and down with a knife like
oh I scraped the plate. You need to know what the fuck you're doing. You have to pretend you know
what you're doing when you're eating like a steak in front of somebody. You're gonna accidentally
like shave off the fat part and eat it and then you're gonna have to swallow it because like what
are you gonna spit it out in front of them? Ice cream. Easy. One hand. Nobody cares. Milkshakes.
Easy. Coffee. Easy. Sip. It doesn't matter. Frozen yogurt. Yes exactly and then bring it back to the
house or wherever the apartment or the and watch diners drive-ins and dives. Four episodes. It's
all you need and then hey that was fun. We got ice cream and watched diners drive-ins and dives
because your eyes are focused on the screen and a movie it's like dark in a movie theater. It's like
weird. It's like a first date. It's like pitch black room and it's loud. You can't even talk.
What are you gonna turn and have a conversation to the date? No you need to be talking to this
person. Who gives a shit about what Guy Fieri is saying on the screen? I mean it's incredibly
important stuff but you can interrupt Guy Fieri and it's not a big deal. Clip that whole thing I
just said and then use it. I've gone on this rant before but trust me on that. All right we're uh
that was I have no idea. Oh Smelly Boy. It was Smelly Boy. There you go. Hope you have a good
date Smelly Boy. I'll show my date your old TF2 videos. It's mistake because she doesn't she might
not get it and then you might become the weird guy. Like Bobby Flay is just background noise.
I Bobby Flay is not gonna go like at any point during that show for you to be like
he does that sometimes. I don't know it's like funny I guess. He does I don't think that's that
funny though but he does it sometimes. He's just sitting there on the grill flipping hamburgers
and what's that? We're gonna put a special mustard on this one. Who cares that doesn't matter that's
not embarrassing it's interesting. Put on C-span no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no she sells she sells on the seashore she sells sea seas on the seashore
Listen to me do not put on politics what are you out of your mind? Hey good first date. All right
We and you are just started dating. What are your views on politics? Sit down. Let's watch
That would be like, okay
Hope you both agree. Yeah a good first date. What a perfect first date. Let me take you to a restaurant
I'm gonna order a steak that I don't know how to cut and the first thing I say to you is hey
What do you what do you think about politics, huh?
Like scrape the fucking plate. Mmm piece of fat. I mean, I mean, I I
I
Just ate the whole fat thing. I had to so and he starts sweating and like sweats pouring down your head bad
And stamp on the put like the big thing the big red X
And then it shows like a couple sitting on the couch like and like the color palette is increased
It's not like sepia tone. You know what I mean? It is like a nice beautiful
Big open iris of and in the frame
It is like this laughter a big smiles and Guy Fieri's on that TV and you got two frozen yogurts. What time is it?
Okay, here we go. Thank you to
Doc thank you doc for the 250 doc 3660
German have you heard of a game called pilgrims? I feel like the humor and style is right up your alley and only take about an
hour
Pilgrims, what is this? Oh, actually I did hear about this. This is by the machinarium guys, right? Yeah, it is
This looks cute. Yeah, I'll play it. Definitely good juke
Thanks with 300 bits or 250 actually. Hey
we got a
250 from flug boy Jerma. I hey Jerma went to the Death Stranding
Gallery Expo in New York City tonight and I'm probably gonna go to the midnight release was wondering if you're gonna play the game at
All not on stream, but in general or on stream too. Hope you have fun. That sounds like an interesting time
I will probably not play it on stream just because it's a fairly long game and fairly
I'm gonna say this and I don't mean this in a negative way
But dragged out that and I don't mean that in a negative way. No, the words are not boring
It's just like takes a long time to do a lot of stuff
Thank you. It takes a very long time to get anywhere or do anything
That's that's the whole nature of the game, isn't it?
Isn't the whole entire video game based around dragging something up?
I will absolutely play it off stream, but it's something I probably just sit on my couch and do it's a pizza delivery boy game
Play Death Stranding for your first date. No, I
Honest to God, I do not mean that in a negative way
I mean that in like I foresee myself just walking in a straight line
With a briefcase in my hands for like 25 straight minutes and just cut trying it like what are we gonna talk about?
Podcast here we go. It has eight hours of cutscenes
That's not the type of game that I would stream. Does it actually have eight hours of cutscenes?
That's the entire extended edition of Lord of the Rings all of them. Wow, I've already made that reference, but I'll make it again
But the answer is probably no. I hope you enjoy it. I look forward to it as well
We'll see how good it is. Hey Dino Pulse Zetta. Thanks for the 500 bits. How you been Jerma been wondering
Who do you think you'd want for a DLC fighter in smash?
There's many that I want but I'd love to hear your thoughts PS. There's an awesome Mega Man outfit
You can unlock in the game. Thanks to Keiji Inafune
Being the game designer. I said that name so wrong. Who do I want in smash Scrooge McDuck final answer Disney
Yeah, but the pogo stick the move set the gems
Would make a perfect move set you can incorporate the pogo somehow and he was an original Nintendo star
But he's Disney. So yeah, not inspect a gadget. He wasn't in a love Nintendo game. He had a shitty Nintendo game
There's a difference. What about Gino? Yeah, but I've talked about that before but that's just that's long shot territory
What's the best way to reach you for business conversations? I do not have a way
I lock myself in a cave and don't come out. There's a computer in here and there's
500 Campbell's chunky chicken noodle soups in here. I just don't come out but that's the real answer though
Not I mean that I don't like do like take business propositions not the living in a cave part Campbell's chunky
I love those canned soups. I think they're fantastic
but Scrooge
Nose stuffed up when I said Scrooge McDuck and I said the D and then my nose closed Scrooge McDuck
And then dino pulse again a thousand bits from dino pulse. Oh, it's the same thing
I think it was a double bit message
But thank you for the 1500 bits dino. Appreciate it green 500 castle crashes with Josh Tucker
It was Josh Tucker. I don't know who that is. I've already played through castle crashes
It's four or five times. So I would not play through castle crashes again
I've already done it many times years and years and years ago. It's a great game though. Very good
What do you say we get the
Credits all the subs new subs old subs all of you. Thank you again. See you guys Sunday
For the community content night if there's a problem with it, if I don't think there's enough then we'll do something else
Afterwards, you know if there's only like one or two hours worth of content, that's fine. We'll just do something else after
Thanks again guys. Hope you enjoyed Dead Rising. I did it's a wild ride
Loved it, but there's still a couple more bits here. We have a Bob boy. Everybody loves Bob boy like seriously
five community subs from Bob boy
Thanks a lot Bob
Bath bomb boy lots of boys lots of bath bomb boy Bob boy
Bath bomb boy. Thanks for the 250. Did you read my message Jerma Pluto? Did it not work?
No, I saw it. Yeah, I did. I appreciate it. Thank you flug boy. Thanks for the 250 also yearly reminder Jerma
Watch Jojo. I love you a lot like a lot Jojo's Bizarre Adventure is one of those things that I will have to
You can't say no to this, you know saying I am NOT
No, I'm not gonna say it out loud because then somebody will clip it and put it somewhere and make somebody really mad or something
Let me say something else like if no, I'm not gonna say that I think somebody will put that
Okay, you know the guy with the mustache that everybody loves that jumps around and jumps on people. What's his name? That's the name
Yes, you guys saying all right
So what if I said I I will never play one of those games because I don't think that I don't think they're interesting
I don't not into it. What if I said that how many of you would be angry?
I think a lot of people would be like that's kind of annoying like why would you do that?
Fuck you. So if I said I I'm not gonna watch this show. It's not I don't I'm not into it
I don't want it. What the fuck did you say? So from here on out no more opinions ever again
I'm gonna have to confirm nor deny anything that I do. I love
Mario it's a he's iconic and perfect except for Mario 3d world burn that game
I just said I wasn't gonna give opinions and I just gave a really really really fired up one
I love I love Mario Mario 64 Mario Galaxy Mario Odyssey. Holy shit. These are phenomenal video games
Unbelievable some of the best games I've ever played just like it in the top 20 always
Super Mario fucking 3d world is not one of them
I'm sorry, that's my opinion
Rock goes through my window
WarioWare, I wish they'd make a new WarioWare like hurry up already. You know something interesting. I've never played cut the music for this
I've never played Super Mario Sunshine. I've seen it played. I've never played it burn the witch play it right now
Play it on stream. I've never played it. I've seen it. I
I think I've held the controller for like a few minutes is better than 64
I just almost that hurt. What what did you just say? They're right. There's so many video games. Hey wizard rivet
Thanks for the 500 bits term of watching your videos for five years
Recently, I signed into the Canadian military and I'll be leaving for basic training on Saturday
I won't be able to watch your streams for a while. So just wanted to let you know how much I love them
Good luck. Thank you so much for being around look forward to seeing you when you come back
Thanks for being around as long as you have good luck to you in the military
Much love to you. So I'm gonna say it's hilarious if you think any Mario game is better than 64
mmm, I
think
People put Mario 64 just at number one like s plus tier always even if they don't believe it because I think
Super Mario World is
Probably
number one for the Super Nintendo
Hmm. Yeah, it probably is Mario 64. But every well, what's the best Mario game ever made?
People just call Mario 64. Obviously, did I have more fun in 64 for the first time or
Mario World or Galaxy or even Galaxy 2 or Odyssey?
Interesting question paper Mario. I have to play that too
Mario RPG. Yeah, but I'm super biased on that one. Yeah
Alright, see you Sunday. And then we had wizard ribbit gave five community subs. Thank you wizard ribbit
Congratulations to all the people that got the subs take care guys. Have a great rest of your weekend
See you Sunday for community content night. See you soon. And why don't you why don't you play us out? Good night guys
Wait home before what is this Nightbot command mods calamity thorium
Antiharis magic storage potion seller auto trash. What is this?
Somebody delete that
Like one of them I had just to get rid of that because I think it's terrarium mods
All right. Good night. See you Sunday
Take care guys