Hello there. How you doing on this uh, fri- Thursday evening? Is it Thursday? It's Friday.
Uh, a little late today. I'm sorry. I've been so good too. I haven't ever since I opened up this
window with the three to four. I haven't been late for like six or seven weeks or something. It's
been great. But, uh, we're working together with Italics today. So we're kind of bouncing back and
forth. Hey, can you hear me? I can, I can't hear you. What are your audio levels like?
So we've been setting up and we're gonna play Risk of Rain 2 co-op. Everyone's talking about
this game. Apparently it's really good. I have not played it, but it looks very, very fun.
Risk of Rain plus two. It's very addictive. It's that's so, so I've heard. Did I play the original?
I played. No, I enjoyed the original vicariously because I like, I think I've played it a few times
randomly. I don't think I own it though, but I've seen people play it and I've watched people play
it and it looked really fun and I vicariously played the game through other people. Never really
gave it too much attention and I attribute that to the fact that this one is a third person 3D
perspective and the other one is the 2D side scrolling perspective and I like this
approach better. First game is apparently phenomenal and it looked phenomenal,
but no, I did not really play it. You know that the item effects stack and don't have a limit,
right? I have no idea. Italics is going to pretty much be here to be the guy that answers every
single question. So if you have a question tonight, ask Italics because he'll be able to answer it.
So for the purpose of the stream, if you have a Risk of Rain 2 question, please put in your
chat message, hey, it's Alix Dash, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, and I will ask him
because I don't fucking know anything. No, questions that pertain to the video game, okay?
I'm not going to relay, it has to be a gameplay related question and if it's not, then mods,
clean them up. You know what I mean? Clean them up. If you don't know, clean them up is
germ of mob talk. Forget them out of here. But I think, oh, let's see if he's ready.
Hello? Are you here? Hello. Are you with me? I am indeed. All righty. Hold on, you seem a bit loud.
Right click me in Discord, turn me down. How about like right there? Okay. I'm not on a webcam,
Mike, right? I don't think so. Remember the whole time I was on a webcam, Mike? No, I'm not. No,
I don't think you are. However, do you want to check your dashboard and click the accept button?
Accept button? Where is it? Oh, this is just squads, man. Yeah, you are super loud. Hold on. Dude,
we're in like a Twitch squad right now. We just like squatted the fuck up. What does that even do?
All right, Chet. What that does is there's a button at the top of the stream
that is going to show our scores. No, we're hiding that information. Oh, I don't want to embarrass
you. So you don't want to embarrass yourself. I mean, that's that could happen too. You can like
click on the squad button up at the top and then it shows both streams at the same time like
multi-twitch and you even stay in the same chat room you were already in. What? But you see both
video feeds simultaneously and interchangeably click between them. Wait a minute. Wait, you lost
me here. Hold on. Both streams at the same time? They call it squads because when you're playing
Apex with your friends. Yes, you just said the Voldemort word. Now everyone's going to want us
to play Apex. Yeah, well, we'll go ahead and stop you there. So this is Risk of Rain 2.
All questions, by the way, please put hey italics dash and then your question because I won't be
able to answer it. I won't read it because I'm not in your stupid chat chatters. It's a nice chat.
That's kind of an unbelievable thing to open up with. That's fine.
Everyone's like, oh my god, stop it. All right, you ready? Let's try this out. So
this is a game about collecting items. It's a game about, I think, collecting bugs. Collecting bugs.
So we have to be the same character, right? We both have to be the same character.
There are six classes available, but they have to be unlocked. Okay, so double tap. Let's shoot
twice for two times 90% damage, which is 180% damage. Interesting. Okay, 180 damage phase round
fire piercing bolt that hits all enemies in line for 230% damage. Okay. Well, no, that would be
two. So there'd be like three and a half damage. How does it Hey, it's Alex. Hey, how does that
work? I've never played this game. Oh, right. I didn't even play the first game. Wait, hold on.
You didn't play the first game either? No. So we're both just total scrub assholes then.
I went through like a long, long tangent in the very beginning. Normally, I would be a good guide
for a new Wow, this is not good. This is not good. I do. He's usually the guide. He's usually like
the game guide. Everybody tell told me like, why haven't you played risk of rain? And I said,
because it's ugly and it's 2d and it's pixel art. And I hate those kind of games, as everybody knows.
Right. So now that it's 3d with graphics, I thought it's a perfect time to play. Well,
you missed out because it was I watched the streamer beat it. I'm not going to say names
here. But the name was star. They beat it on stream. And it was great. It was great content.
So we're playing on the rainstorm difficulty, which sounds very thematic. Okay, cool. Quote,
the way the game was intended to be played. Okay. So those of you guys that have not paid
attention at home, we've got a cross here. Sounds good. This is what is the $34? What's that mean?
It means we need. Oh, I have 16. Remember when we linked our bank account when we installed? Right.
Right. Right. Right. So it's just constantly cross referencing and checking and find and
activate. Basically, there's a direct line of credit to the loot boxes. Okay. So you get money.
Do I have to collect to collect the money or just is it just happening? Okay. People are starting
to come out here. Okay. That hurt. That's a dodge roll. And this is like a super shot. Okay. And
that's a phaser. So yeah, you have your default shoot. One of them is like a stun. Yeah, you got
like a three round burst. So does dodge have iframes? That's all I care about. I think you
just move so fast. It's physically impossible for anybody else to hit you. What I get personal
shield generator. I got a recharging shield now. I think we should probably leave, right? Oh, you're
like, I'm over here. I was just standing in like the starter area. Oops. So I don't know what any
item does. We're just going to pick stuff up at random. Shift is sprint. All right. So is there
like a we should probably stay together. That's great. Recharging shield. So just there's boxes
all over the ground. There's boxes all over the ground. And we're killing things and getting
money. There's also boxes on the ground that have money. Are you up? I'll come to you. So this is
the teleporter, right? Our goal is to find the teleporter. And whenever we want to activate it,
so we can stay here and grind for as long as we want. Really? The longer we stay the meter
at the top right. Sticky bond. It says easy gets progressively more difficult. Oh, interesting.
We're basically trying to superpower ourselves. And then when we're done doing that,
we move into the next levels. Yeah. So is it based on levels or is it? Hey, it's Alex. Hey,
is this based on levels or is it based on to just try to grind as hard as you can in one area?
Both, I think. Okay. All right. Do you got how much money you got? Have you? I've been
opening everything. I see. I'm going to come to you. I do like dodge roll. I have like a war
banner. How did you even get up there? I think I used a jump pad. A jump pad?
I'll activate teleporter. Don't touch that, right? Not unless we're absolutely ready.
No, we're not. Right. Are we ready? I don't know. How much money do you have? I have 72 bucks.
I have 34 dollars. I just bought something. I just got gasoline. Drop a war banner on leveling up,
giving you great strength. Okay. That's what I got. That's what that is. So if you like fight
inside of that, you get like bonus stats to everything. Interesting. Like attack speed up,
maybe damage. We should just hang out up here then just grind money.
Who cares? Well, if we run around the map, we can find more boxes to
purchase upgrades. Cool. Jerma thinks he's good at the game. I'm like asking questions. I'm asking
like, oh, okay, so we do this. What about this? What do we do about this? I think she's fucking
good at the game. I'm like asking questions. What'd you just do? This is an E3 presentation.
So what about over here? Hey, Taliesin, watch out for those skulls. They're dangerous.
You literally cut off. Hey, watch out for the...
Dying main character fails to communicate most important line of dialogue to new supporting
main character role. Easy. Am I gonna die? Oh no. I thought I just got killed. All right. Here's a
box. Open it. I do like this money system. Fire a swarm of missiles. I like getting paid all the
time too. Okay. I think we may have just spawned everything. Look at over here. One lunar. Okay.
We just spawned everything. Did you do like some kind of mountain? No. Like cursed item? What is
this? I don't know. I don't think so. I just picked it. I just picked an item up. You definitely did
this. I didn't. I swear to god I didn't do anything. It was a trap up here. I pressed the... I opened
up an orange case and got a new item. Can we stack these war banners? Do they like... Somebody said
apparently everything is stackable in the whole game. Really? I think so. So the whole point is
just becoming more overpowered. I guess, yeah. People are saying activate the teleporter.
Should we do that or should we wait till medium? I don't know. I guess we can just do it now and
see what happens. I mean we're pretty close to medium. I think we can handle it. Noticing more
elites popping up. Is that what the flame on the head means? I think the flame on the head. I have
like an ability that sets it on fire. Deleting elite monster items. 3D printer. Oh I think I can
just deal extra damage to bosses. Cool. So are there headshots in this game? Now obviously these
enemies are only head. Yeah. It doesn't feel like there is. They might be. They might be.
But I don't think there is. All right. Teleporter. Are we going to just activate it?
Might as well just see what it does. Hey there is fall damage. How bad is it on a scale of one to
ten? Uh two. Okay let's say I was like one is I jump off of the ledge and ten is I jump off of
like a building. Um can you can you go over that like scale again? How bad is it? The joke the joke
is that... Scale of one. The joke is... Jump off of a ledge. The joke is that is the scale. So like
it would be like four and it was fucking hilarious. You should see my chat right now. I activated the
teleporter. No most time when like somebody says something fucking dumb or weird you see like a
bunch of question marks. I don't know about what's going on in your stream but that's like a ton of
laughs. All right so that's the boss. Stone Titan. I don't think the question marks are laughs.
Chris Vanguard. Uh he's killing me. Just don't die. Uh okay I'll deal with the adds. Don't don't say
that. What? What would you classify these as? Are we running ads right now? No don't say that
word. Don't do not say the word add. No but like you said it in the context of like the advertisement.
Are you dead? Can I get you? I'm dead. How do I revive you? We should have done it earlier.
We should have activated the easy mode earlier. Easy mode. They got fragged. Enter the teleporter.
Hold on but is there a way I can get you back or are you actually just dead? I think I'm actually
just dead. Interesting okay. I come back at the end of the level so good luck. There's no way I'm
gonna beat this. I can 100% guarantee that this is not going to be completed. Just line them all up
and get a collateral. I mean I'm trying. Okay well that was a good try. You did go narrowly right
through every other. Hey it's hard when you got fucking 100 people. What is this? What are your
like fireworks? It's my special move. There's too many of these heads. This is not even the boss.
Is this why when I looked over everyone was saying teleporter teleporter teleporter teleporter
I'm minus one health. Oh that means I'm dead. Good now I don't feel so bad.
We can die together in eternal bliss. Medium on the first level. That apparently was not a good
idea. So can we just keep going? Yeah I think we just try to get good. All right let's go. Let's
do it. Let's get good. I don't know if you know I just I just beat Sekiro on stream like last week.
I don't know if you know that but I mean obviously you know that. How many times did you die? Because
that's how many times we have to die here before we can beat this game. I act like we didn't talk
about it downstairs. Yeah I was just wanting you to repeat it for everyone else to hear.
All right you out of your egg? No. Well come on we gotta go. It's like it's time. Okay. You can't
just sit in there. I'm going. All right we gotta find teleporter and win go quick. That hurts by
the way. I don't think we're supposed to find the teleporter first. There's actual team damage.
You know what I'm just gonna blame the RNG. Okay the drops the drops were terrible.
Now blame the fact that we didn't we were supposed to just activate the teleporter.
Keep going. This is a game about speed. We have to split up a little bit because we have to find the
teleporter. Yeah we do have to find the teleporter. You're right. There we go. I'm just trying to get
some money. Imagine this game on insane difficulty. I didn't have a shield like you did. That's why I
died so fast. Can you imagine this game on insane? That definitely is an insane difficulty. It has to
be. There is one higher than this. This game is a race against the difficulty. This is what twitch user
uh I don't know what was their name. This game is a race. I don't know. Please cite your sources.
Thank you. That was that was your homework on Wikipedia right now. What was their name?
Taco Tangler. There's no enemies in this game. All right so if you have a if you have a question
ask Taco Tay. I want everyone to add to preface their questions. Hey Taco Tangler.
Yeah we're using MLA or Chicago style. Chicago style is the hot dog? What did you just say? Foreign
fruit heal on use. Interesting. I told you to cite your sources. I didn't know which one you were
using. We're doing hot dog style. Oh all right. We let's go. We're gonna find no more like funny
jokes. The teleporter is right here. All right let's activate it right now. Why not? Can we? Yeah I get
it. We're so weak. But let's go. All right you asked for it. See now we kill it. There's not we're
not going to get overwhelmed. Kill it quick. Headshots only. Giant ant. Told you we were
collecting bugs. What is this thing? Speaking of bugs I have like a bug that's healing me or
something. Hold on I'm gonna go stand over here with your heal bug. I think I have. That hurt a
lot. Is this a heal bug? Oh god. I just used my heal and nothing happened. I think I'm gonna
heal right now. Am I dead again? Oh you're dead? All right let me see if I can do this. Told you we
should have done this. Well look he's at like 40% HP. My heal did not do anything. Oh my god.
I thought we're not ready. We gotta have more like power-ups before we activate this.
Oh that was a personal shield. We might we might actually maybe I just killed my healer. All right
personal goals for today. Beat level one. Personal goal. Complete level one. I'll get it. It's harder
than Monster Hunter. Come on give me that heal. Give me that heal. How funny would it be if it was the exact
same problem this Monster Hunter? This is like four player difficulty. I'm dead. The bug doesn't
heal. The bug doesn't heal. Well I I had an actual heal in my pocket that didn't heal. Hey Taco Tangler!
Uh what's what are we doing wrong here? We're on the wrong difficulty? I think we just I think we
need some more power-ups. We gotta split up. Get money. Let's let's say like open at least five
boxes each. All right five boxes each. Minimum. Just get more items but don't let it go all the
way into like medium territory. Okay yeah five boxes is too much. Be fast. What does Taco Tangler
say? This is a he's the expert. Grab a few chests and level a little bit before activating the
teleporter. Then once the event is over you can get the remaining items. All right that sounds good.
Thanks Taco Tangler. That wasn't even Taco Tangler. Somebody else. Wait Taco Tangler left.
Taco Tangler didn't get enough credit. All right we gotta hurry. No they're still here.
All right let's go. I'm going this way. I'm gonna bang a right. The little boxes that don't cost
anything have money in them. Yeah so it's a race against the difficulty. You gotta get a couple
items, couple levels. So are crits random? I think there's something that can influence it.
34 bucks? Shit I don't have enough. 55. All right 34. Let's go. I went to a dead end. Okay that is
extra. I got an extra jump. Okay that's pretty useful. Small natural crit chance. 23 bucks.
Don't got enough. What is that? I almost just jumped off the ledge. I'm so glad you did.
Okay teleport is by me. Chat's a natural hazard. Okay there's a lot of items over here too. Okay
teleporter right next to me. Okay I haven't even got one box yet. Offer to shrine of chance. 23
dollars. Okay you offer to shrine but gain nothing. Thanks. Middle click is a ping. Oh shit. Okay
well that's not what the teleporter is but that's a ping that you can see. You gain nothing. Wow.
Twice in a row. Shrine of chance. Las Vegas baby. Dude RNG in this game is a little like wonky.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Why the fuck am I getting swarmed in here?
Holy shit. Remember when I said five boxes? I'll settle for one. Jesus there's like there's a few
boxes over by me. I almost got enough money to do it. Somebody's like a sniper rifle over here.
Let's go back to this robot. All right I got a lot of money now. Let's go. They have to make these
boxes 69 dollars on purpose. Like that's not that's just part of the development cycle. All right I'm
gonna have like three or four boxes by the time this is done here. So this is uh dealing damage
heals you. That's pretty amazing. Okay oh god. How much does it heal? Can't really tell. Kind of heading
towards you. I've only got one box so far. I got two. Did you actually just hit me out of the air?
Oh this is this leech is incredible. Like I'm every time I get hit it just heals back up.
How much money you got? Uh 50 bucks. What's the uh purple dollar sign for? I'm not sure.
Gain temporary flight. Set okay missile launcher swarm of missiles. All right I've got three items
now. Four items. Sticky bomb. Chance on hit. All right I got I have five I got five items.
I got like the war banner thing. All right I now have two items.
Deal extra damage to bosses. I like that one. Okay I you know you almost ready to go here?
69. What is this one? I got it. What the fuck? I can jump three times. Okay everything stacks.
Assuming we win you get to keep that for the next. That's amazing. The next life and you just keep
getting more powerful. Is there like a soft way to land? Although I guess I have temporary flight so
I'll just activate that on the way down right? Probably yeah. Okay I'm just gonna get another
item. Here we go. What does this thing do? Well that was sick. Teleport. People are screaming
as to do teleporter. They're saying we're gonna run out of our opportunity here. Okay um are there
any more leftover boxes down here? Uh I don't there's one over here I think. And get did you
activate it? The teleporter? No. Oh god. Because I still have 70 dollars. I just need I can't spend
my money. All right well you can save it. All right let's go. Yes you can yeah. Turn on the shrine.
What's that? Oh boy. Monster tooth. Drop a healing orb on kill. You can do it again. What did that
just do? What are we gonna activate it? Yeah let's go. Oh god I'm not ready. Just kill this
last robot and then spawn him. And we're gonna do it man. We gotta go. Oh is that the boss up
there? Yeah it is. Yeah those are the bosses all right. I'm gonna get some distance. Whichever
that's like a big explosion I think. Oh my god there's so many. We gotta focus on one of them.
Focus on the one with the less health. I know I was just running away. We're like running into the
corner. We're so dead. We're gonna die again. You understand that right? Hold on. We're like
fundamentally doing something wrong. One of them is dead. One of them's dead. Good. So am I. Oh
you're dead. We are fundamentally doing something incorrect. Because he's not even at 50% health.
Get all items first. Well doesn't that make the boss harder? How far can I run? Wait I can share
items with you? How? How far away can I go? Okay not doing anything wrong. It's just a really hard
game. Okay I see. I'm gonna fall off the ledge. This game sucks. This character. All right taco.
No no no no no. Somebody said this character sucks early and is more geared towards late game.
But it's the first character though. That's not what I was trying to say. Stop sniping me. This
game sucks. That's not what I was trying to say. Turn the game up a little. Unlucky boss.
Unfortunate. Wait is this boss just like ridiculous? Just like a weird hard
RNG role of a boss? Why is the teleporter only at 57%? Yeah people are saying that this is this
boss. We kind of got like a bad role for like early new players because he's just like annoying
and hard to deal with. You might still do it. Oh god look at that like caravan of people behind
them. Yes I see all of them. There's so many. Oh they're behind me now too. And by the way we
have to stay inside the bubble around the teleporter to charge it. Oh god. We need to stay in the
teleporter sphere. So do you have to kill the boss? Yeah I think so. What is this ice demon?
No you almost got it. At 99% charge monsters stop spawning. Oh that's a huge deal. That is a huge
deal. That's good to know. Wait is that not true? Is somebody just lying? Somebody just lying? Okay
I'm definitely dead here. Says a lie? No it's true. It is true. Okay monsters will stop spawning at
99%. You're on medium difficulty now. Help me. This game's crazy. I'm dead. I was so close.
So people are asking why we're not playing the star. Because we're dying on the first
level. And we're dying on level one. And he has like a hundred hours in the game.
So you think you think he's gonna want to play with two chumps that are starting out in like
the noob level? We're dying on level one. He's like he has like 150 hours in the game right now.
Push continue. Maybe when we get a little better maybe he can jump in. Let us get through like the
first level first. I guess this is we got it this time. This time charge inside. So we're on like
the regular difficulty. Learn on drizzle. Drizzle is too easy. Play drizzle until you get used to
the game. Says weeping and gnashing is replaced by laughter and tickles.
Drizzle is baby mode. I don't think you're allowed to stream on that mode. I think if you stream on
that mode people laugh at you. Yeah I think something goes bad. But it's okay because okay
let's do like a few more attempts on rainstorm and if I'm all right with doing the drizzle mode.
I think we can do it. I think we were pretty close. We just have to lock it in.
Yeah let's lock it in. Let's go. We'll be laughing at you no matter what.
I think we're starting to understand the basic elements of the game. Starting to figure it out.
Yeah I felt like I actually did a lot better last time. Yeah charge the pod. That whole
enemies not spawning after 99% is actually a big deal. This way try to get some money. I got 34.
Why would we spawn up here? RNG man. We won't laugh at you guys for playing drizzle. We'll laugh at
you when you die at the first level on drizzle. That's fair. Okay that's actually fair. Yeah
no that's the decent terms. I could agree to those terms. I'm afraid to agree to those terms though
because I feel like when you agree to those terms if something goes wrong and you lose you have all
your credibility is gone forever. But then you have to just play again but on the hardest difficulty
and then win. That's the only way you could get your credit back I think. There's nothing over here.
Your gamer licenses have been revoked. Take it like this. If Sekiro had a drizzle mode would
you play on it? No. Uh-oh not this conversation. We already talked about this last night. Oh we
already wrapped around. Where hang on where's where are we supposed to go? Uh I came down
okay well we got we both have money. Have you gone down here already? Yeah but not all the way down
but I just got exploded on. Sekiro with guns baby. Lost on the first level. Come on give us a break.
We're trying we're trying to figure it out. This is we're brand new risk of rain 2 players.
Yeah don't push us away risk of rain 1 veterans okay. You want people to play your like fun
franchise? This is this is how you do it. I got the bandolier chance on kill drop an ammo pack
that resets cooldowns. That's pretty awesome. What's this one? Your offer to the shrine is
rewarded. I get a hundred percent crits for eight seconds. That's actually great. What is that?
I found the teleport. I got a friend. I have like a turret friend. We have like a new party member.
Oh it's it's star. Star just joined the game. He's like a turret. He's a mini sentry. Does he move?
I don't think so. There's a turret yeah that turret's pretty awesome though. We could like
lead because the teleporter's right here so he's gonna help. Yeah we'll just lead every enemy to
that thing. All right we got to keep moving. Is that a health bar? That thing is amazing.
It can it die? I assume it can get exploded. It has a health bar. What's this one? This one's smoking
60 something. Is this the same level we were just on but everything's different or is the
level actually randomly generated? Spawned on here. Taco my turret. I need help taco.
Yes yes yes doesn't help. I asked two questions. I got a healing drone. I have a lot of like robots
with me. All right come down here. I feel like this is the spot to be. Oh no I have to choose
which one I want. Yes no. It's slightly different okay. All right what about how much money do I
have? 55? What do I need? 60 to open this? Drones are a huge deal. The generic layout is the same
with some doors and bridges that have changed. Okay what is the launch? Each level has two to
three variations mostly static items are random and I assume also the layout. Oh my god do you
kid me? Got two turrets. All right I got so much money I don't know what to do with it. I guess
I'll spend it at this shrine. I think we're gonna win. I think we're gonna win this level just
because of the turrets. Crowbar. Dude these guys are gonna be the first level. Are you kidding me?
I was here. World first. All right give me this thing. So you have a heal drone too? Yeah. You
have two like drones on the ground and a heal drone. That's pretty sick. That's got a guitar.
And his music. What is this door? It's electric. What? Nothing. What does a ukulele do? Are we
ready to pop it? Pop it. We gotta stay in here though. I don't see any more chests but I have
like two hundred dollars. That's the best item. I don't know what it does. What does it do?
Taco. Taco Tuesday. What does it do? Probably like plays music. All right you ready? I'm going. Here
we go. All right we got just gotta stay inside the red. Where are they? Oh it's that guy. It's a big.
Where is it? It's the big guy. He's a big jellyfish. All right get in the red. He shoots
like a slow moving zappy orb. Oh my god. And then a then a bunch of fast ones.
Going for max crits. I think you can stop those. Just just be careful when they get to the
destination. All right I did a ton of damage. Eight seconds of crits was pretty sick. That was
awesome. We're doing it. Watch out for that orb. I don't know what this is. Just run. What does that
mean? I don't know. I don't know but it did a lot of damage. E3 pretend gameplay. Watch out man.
Nice work. He's dead. They did it. They beat the first level. Now we just have to charge the
teleporter. That was way easier than the other guy. He really was. What's this? Chance to fire
a missile. Chance to fire a missile. He oh he drops a bunch of shit and I just took it all.
I'm a greedy fuck. Oh I see how it is. The drone guy. I thought I just I saw items and I pick them
up. Someone took both boss items. Yeah I did. I'm gonna be the cannon. I didn't know what it
did. That was how the game. I just saw an item on the ground. I have a shriveled mat. I'm not
showing you an item. This game's old school. You have to like get to really test your friendships
okay. Everyone's saying shame on you. Not personal loot. Yeah okay guys. This isn't Diablo 3. This is
called fucking snooze you'll lose. All right are we ready? How do you kick someone from a lobby?
Taco how do you kick someone from a lobby? Open oh open all the boxes. Oh I think after the
boss dies we can go around and pick up all the we're on medium difficulty now. We are on medium
now yes permanently I guess. Okay well it's because we're not going fast enough. They should
have just risk of rain like rain's not that fast. I feel like it should have been called risk of rain
you know to indicate the speed. Oh never mind. What's hitting me? Oh all your money gets converted
to experience after you get into okay all your money gets turned into experience when you go
into teleporter so you gotta spend it. Don't hoard your cash spend it or maybe if you need
to level up. Oh so all my money's gone from all your money every cent you have is gone it's
experience now. Wait it turns into xp? Turns into experience. Turns into experience? It turns into
experience. Why is the ammo on the ground even doing? All right 82 let's go. Why is he jumping
so much? 3d glasses chance to critically strike. Oh it wasn't charged. What the hell was this thing?
Heal all nearby allies after standing still for two seconds. Turn around. I'm a healer now.
What is this thing? 72 I don't have enough. Come at me. This is gonna be easy. What's this thing?
Oh a little lance. Change to bleed. So everything's way more expensive now but are enemies worth more
money? Uh looks like it yeah. I assume so. Pick one. Yeah I picked it. Oh how you doing? You get
nothing. How am I doing? Yeah. Pretty good. Um I've got a crowbar times two. It also can heal you
apparently. Lunar. What is lunar? I think it's like a special type of currency. Okay so it's like a
special kind of currency thing? Is that what you're just saying? Okay I see this game is serious.
That's why that's what I've heard. That's fine. I plan on taking it seriously. There's an uh box
up here. I see where you are. What's that? Look at that. What's down there? Uh what are you talking
about? There's a ton of boxes down the swamp. I have no idea. Are we just throwing boxes at me?
What the hell? Oh no it's you. I want my lucky item. I get it. That's cool. Lunars stick between
um runs and are quite useful. Um I'm trying to mark stuff with middle mouse. If you see something.
Oh that's cool. Yeah the only reason why somebody told me that is because I looked over and I saw
oh my god Jeremy like 30 times. Personal shield. Did you get this? Use 30. So 3D printer. I marked you.
So does the 3D printer can I just put something in there? How do I choose what item goes in or
does it just show up there? Whatever it is. I have no idea. I just checked. All right I got a lot of
bleed power now. Have we found the teleporter? Well I don't think we have. There's a lot of boxes though.
I have no idea where it is. We probably should think about doing it though because we're about
to move into hard. Yeah it's probably not a good idea. We're gonna move into hard difficult. Is it
just it's just hidden somewhere. I don't know where you've been. I guess I do because all these
boxes are open. It chooses an item that's the same color to exchange it. The teleporter has orange
particles. Little heal but if you have 116 boxes a heal bot right here. I got it. Get two heal bots.
All right let's we gotta find this teleporter. We're both gonna move into hard and then we're
gonna get laughed at. What's this? I need one of these. The orange one I think is active items it
is. Yeah it seems like it. Um look for orange particles floating up. I need like nine dollars
taco lend me not money. I teleport where the fuck is it? Over here I see little particles.
There's a little like orange particles here. I got it. It's right here on me.
I'm going full boss killer mode. All right um should we do it? I guess we just punch it. I don't
know I guess. Punch it let's go. Before it gets too hard. Before it gets too late. All right let's focus
the boss. We're in a bit of a corner back against the wall. It's jellyfish too. We got this.
Jellyfish sucks. We can kill this thing. It's too bad we have to look through the water to do it.
Get rid of these guys first. They're kind of just causing a problem. Yeah I do so much boss damage.
Here's full crits. Got it. He's dead. All right easy. Now wait wait wait wait there's like boss
items here. I'm not gonna Diablo to you. I'm not gonna like kill bail. All right well you got the
last two. I get these two. All right you. Oh but but but what about me? They're both mine. All right
come on. I accidentally bailed you. You got the first two. That accident doesn't matter. We're even.
We're square now. They're two bandoliers. I was the asshole that killed bail and everybody's
computer freezes but that person somehow got to click first. Eye for an eye. Justice has been
served. I have a chance on drop the reset cooldowns. It was always such bullshit because it was the
audio loading his death animation and what would happen is you'd get some sorcerers that would come
in and just melt the fuck out of him before he did his first line. My brother zoo will not die
and it would load his second audio clip and crash everybody's computer and that one sorcerer's got
to take everything. It was bullshit. They kill him before he got his fucking second line. All right
do we have any more boxes or are we ready? Um there's probably boxes but we're in hard now.
We are in hard yeah. The cusp of hard mode. You only knew this because you were the sorcerer. No
I know this because I was the victim of a sorcerer. Why are they locked with like tendrils? It's money
money money. Spend the money quick. Yeah but the the boxes were locked. They had like orange tendrils
around them. All right we're going I'm going to teleport. What do you mean you're going to
teleport? What about the boxes? I'm entering the teleporter. Oh shit. Oh my money's all gone.
I ran past three boxes. They're all locked. You can't loot because the teleporter's charging.
Well everybody we were saying let's go get the boxes and we were both left the teleporter.
Before you say anything man hold on I mean snow level pog. We're already halfway through hard.
All right get that wasn't my decision. I didn't make that decision. He did.
Whatever here comes the angry chat. Bring it on. I deal I deal with cross-eyed angry
little people like you every day chat. You understand? Well tell me how you really feel.
Give me your rage emojis. Okay they feed me. Dude pay attention to the game. Next to you I know
you'll be talking about like lemon basil lemonade. God like focus. This is gonna hurt me. That's I
don't like that. Return this game. I'm gonna refund it. It's been two hours. This thing has so much
health. Look the only boxes we missed were active item boxes. Everything else has been looted
because we're just too good at this game now. All right I can pick an item. I can pick either like
baby lunchbox or bullets. Which one? I'm gonna do baby. Chance to block incoming damage. This
thing's fucking crazy. These guys have a lot of health. Yeah they do. Oh he hits you from the top
too. It's like balls and shit. We're yeah because we're on hard. We're about to be in very hard.
Yeah we're just about to lose basically. Faster. All right okay fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck.
Find the uh find the teleporter. We're about to get destroyed. It's also like ice enemies that
slow you down and freeze you. I have so much money though hold on. Is there a box on the way?
All right the particles are this way. Yep there's a teleporter right there. Taking damage all right.
Um I don't know I mean it's wearing very hard. We gotta do it now. What's the hardest difficulty?
What is it? Does it cap or does it just keep going to like very very very very very hard?
I don't know. I think we could afford to get like one or two more boxes. I have like 500 bucks.
It's a wood banner. What the fuck are you guys doing? Why is everybody laughing so hard? What are
you doing? Everybody is laughing. Why? Um what is going on? They're just laughing preemptively
because they expect us to die. Oh that's the name. The hardest difficulty is in all capitals.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. Oh I see. But apparently there's like 20 difficulties.
This is so cool. Yeah now that we haven't like kept dying the third time in a row
we're actually playing the game. I'm gonna hit every single one of those auto attacks.
Yes I just called it an auto attack and I'm sorry. Somebody's gonna be like what is this?
And then I gotta get my last hits in. All right I'm gonna I'm turning it on.
What? Should I turn this on or should we get more stuff? The teleporter?
Yeah. I'm pretty far away. Well just try to get a couple more boxes. We gotta
we're in very hard now. They're being very greedy with the boxes this time.
When do we unlock a new character? All right go ahead and turn on new stuff. Do we just buy it?
Well at this point I would call this an item run because I don't see any more boxes around.
There's like a money box. I almost just died to a default enemy. If you if we can complete this
teleporter here we will unlock a new character. This is two thousand six hundred and sixty six
dollars. It's gigantic. Do you have that kind of money? No I got nine hundred. Can we pool our
money together somehow and buy this mega thing? Look at this drone man. That's two charges of
your utility skill. That sounds kind of good. How much is this game? Nineteen dollars. That's
pretty good. Twenty bucks. Nineteen ninety nine. Twenty dollars. This is also only the first
character. There's like six total characters in the early access right now. All right we gotta
go turn the teleporter on. There's no more boxes here. Holy shit I can do that twice. All right
let's go let's go fight. Unless you want to grind another like thousand dollars and get the super
drone. I apparently I get this is cool. All right let's go. Let's we gotta turn it on otherwise
it's gonna get too super hard. It's on consoles at all or just PC. I don't know. I have a triple roll.
Wow. All right let's do it. Oh boy. Yep. I just rolled off the edge. No I didn't. Thank god.
Uh we got like a lava worm on the ice level. Is that the boss? I don't know but I'm trying
to like clear. We all right I don't know. Yeah it's the worm is like flying around.
God there's so many fucking enemies here. Oh dear. He's just flying around. Oh my I'm gonna die.
Oh there's too many enemies. Are you all right? I'm gonna bring my drone over to you.
My drone just found me finally. This week is gonna last.
Whoa. This is not a race. Oh you're right on top of me. Oh god. Uh what are we at?
59 percent. Ow. My drone can't heal fast enough. There's too many people. Uh there's so many.
74. Uh so many heads. 89. No. 94. I got it. All right we got it. We got it. All right he's
doing like a third. Enemies no longer spawn. All right so focus on the adds then. Yeah. Oh my god.
I'm dead. Are you? Oh yeah. I died inside this. You can do it. I will try. There is nowhere for me
to go. All right I think we're good. Almost. Do you choose who's rockets or is it just a random
chance? I think it's random. Wee. All right you got this. Uh this is fucking crazy. I missed every
shot. Stupid idiot. Sorry. Because you can't look straight up. I know it's true. I just figured that
out right now. Oh my god. Wow three rolls. Yeah. I am very jealous of that. That's like huge
survivability. I know it's great. There we go. See you later. We did it. How do I revive you? Oh
two guitars. You get both the guitars and then I come back. You get both of them yeah. His music
was electric. Wow all right so should I just pick up stuff or should we just go? Um up to you I guess.
Uh let me just see. There's something in the vicinity. There's something right here. Let me
just get this and we'll go. There's a couple things here. Let me just pick it up. That's a
heel thing. What's this? I haven't really noticed the uh med kit working. Yeah it's weird. Sprint
faster. Can I buy more than one? No. All right there's a couple blocks this way. I wish we
would have found this cave before we uh. Yeah seriously. Because I think we both went in with
like a thousand bucks. Yeah all right after I get to the top here I'm just gonna drop down.
Yes guys I know I won't get the third. The character unlock. Too bad I'm never gonna play.
Yeah apparently you only get it if you kill that enemy but it's too bad I'm never gonna play this
game again so I'll never get another chance to unlock it. You don't you don't unlock that even
if you're in like the party. All right I'm just gonna. Apparently yeah I guess I'm just uninstalling
when we die. But what an uninstallable what an uninstallatable game you know what I mean?
Did you know if you die after the third level both of us the game uninstalls itself. That's what
people in chat are saying. It's so like. And you never get to play it again. It's so relatable to
uninstall it. It's an uns. I don't even know what the word I just said was. Well let's just go. This
is like our first real run might as well just go uninstallable. There it is. All right so um for my
chat I want you to notice the different look press tab and just look at the itemization there.
Yeah what about it. Look how many more. Well I still. You've got than me. Yeah well it's called
I've been I've been buying only two of those items that were illegal items that I got for free. You
also got two items. I wasn't making any accusations. I was just merely pointing out. I feel there's a
dramatic difference there. You got two free boss items. Remember I. Yeah I'm not complaining. I'm
just saying I think it's funny. That's it. Oh yeah I just think it's funny. Yeah I'm just like
want to point out. I think it's like kind of. Listen what would my complaint be. I'm not saying
you're like sniping items. I'm saying that you've just got a lot more. I'm just kidding. But I mean
if I had to point any fingers I'm just kidding. See now it comes out. Well guys all this takes
is time. All it takes is like a few minutes of prodding and you'll get it out. Whoa these jump
pads go. This is a very vertical level here. How do you dodge that shit. Just to run away. He's
gonna do it again. This level looks crazy. Yeah when he does the big laser beam dude you have to
just line aside something. Oh yeah. I'm gonna die to a normal boss. Something behind me.
Yeah this is just like a random like elite enemy huh. We're on impossible difficulty now by the
way. Yeah we are. That's why it takes so long to kill one person. All right do I have enough money
to buy shit. A mask. I can summon a ghost if I kill something. It's like some Luigi's Mansion music.
I like it. Another huge guy. Oh that's one of my ghosts. Okay I get it. Where's the big dude.
Down here. Whoa. Watch out for that shit. I need this. My god they're everywhere. Yeah I'm pretty
much just gonna die to regular like elites at that moment. Very very high health. I'll be happy if
we can take this guy down. Uh oh I just prayed to the shrine of combat. It was a huge mistake.
Chance to stun on hit. Come to me quickly. Oh you. Oh my god. Yes right now. I'm coming I'm coming
I'm coming I'm coming I'm coming. What do you need. I just need you to shoot everyone behind me.
Okay. Oh god. We have like two mini bosses here. Should I not have done that. I just pressed it.
Oh no. Oculus HD HUD. Oh wait did I just press it. Okay I you know. Okay I get it. I go. Oh my god
we're dead. Well it was fun. It was fun. That was good. Well yeah hold on. I was out of my element
there. I'm not dead yet. Yet. Minus a hundred and three health is what I ended with. Oh god I'm dead.
Yeah well that was a good one. So today I learned praying to the shrine of combat is a challenge
and if you pray to it you must be prepared for the elite summons. All right so we unlock stuff.
Monster lock. Beetle. This item will now randomly appear in the runs. Advancement. This item. So we
unlocked a few more items. Elder Lemurians. Cool. Cool. All right so to be honest the commando kind
of sucks. Well he is the starter character so. This is cool. That's that's what I've got. Now
there's the huntress behind me. Yeah so there's a stray fire seeking arrow for 150 damage can be
used while sprinting. Laser glaive. Glaive that bounces six times. Damage increased by 10 percent
per bounce. Instead of a dodge it's a blink. And then arrow rain. Cool. All right I got I mean
I got I'll try it. It's Freudian's birthday today. Happy birthday happy birthday Freudian.
So this is like a bow and arrow. I'm so ready for this. You've got different powers now. Yeah.
You got unique abilities. What's your uh basic attack obviously at the bow but I wonder
I think everyone's basic attack is different. Let's find out and maybe it's not a burst fire
maybe it's just one shot. It is. Is this like EDF? Yes. Um what it's a homing shot. It it really
is just you get aimbot. You just do you have aimbot now. You just have to put the cursor
somewhere near them and then press the button. That's pretty awesome. Uh yeah I give me. Is it
like weaker shots to compensate I guess probably. Well you shoot it's less. It's like one two three
instead of like no me. All right we understand what's going on here. Let's get it going.
It's like the glaive right? Cool. Now what does this do? Whoa rain of arrows. That looks sweet.
That's the dodge. That goes a long way. All right let's open up some boxes. Well here's the um
teleporter. What do I get? Rubik's cube. I feel like I'm getting the same power-ups. Uh the range
though. Here's the thing about I cannot physically shoot a the weapon if somebody's not like in
range. Oh really? Yeah they have to be like within range to hit them. That was that box.
I already got that one. Where's the other one? I was standing right next to it. Oh no that's just a
jump. RNG baby. See I have the same loadout. All right um cool. All right boxes I need open. 55.
That is a gunner drone. Oh you can sprint while shooting too. That's cool. Oh that is pretty
handy. Where are these glasses? Which one of these do I want? Give me this one.
Healing orb on kill. All right what do you think? You can blink up too. Well that's kind of insane.
You ready to start this? Um I guess so. Let's get this party started. Hold on I'm running towards you
pretty far away. Coming back into the fray. It's a beetle queen. Need more money.
Wow that hurt. All right where's the boss? Oh there it is. Back here. So bugs are bad. Bugs are bad.
Oops how far does this go? It goes pretty far actually. How much damage does my little piercing
shot do? 44. Nice. That's pretty good. Can you believe we died on this level? Yeah well we didn't
know what the hell was going on. Yeah but like now it seems like a foreign concept. I don't
understand how because I feel like I'm not trying. I picked up one boss item. All right you get the
other one. But you also remember like we just installed the game. Yeah we did just install it.
It's an onion. Beetle guard. All right box time. We have plenty of time. We're still in easy. Is
this your friend? I don't is this your guy? I have like a beetle friend. What? Yeah it was one of the
boss items. All right can he die? He's doing like aoe like he's a third character.
All right 148 bucks. If you have the money. I keep shooting him thinking he's a bad guy.
Resets cooldowns. Yeah if you hold tab you can mouse over the items too. There's another. I've
got a healing drone now. Those are so useful. Healing drones are so good. What about one of
these like shrines? Reactivate it. Which one? There's one down here. I don't have enough money
to do that now. Yeah I do. I don't know where to go from what boxes. What is purple money? I don't
think we have purple money yet. All right I'm ready to teleport. Hold on. I still have 160 dollars.
Whenever you're ready. I don't want to 3D print this. That's an RNG shrine not an item shrine.
Cool. Good to know. Oh is it changing my items into med kits? Oh that's what that does. Oh I'm
changing my I'm changing my good items into the worst item in the game. I see. Uh oh. Yeah I like
the extra challenge. Ready to rock and roll. I had no idea of what that machine does. Gamble from stuff
at that shrine. All right time's ticking. You ready? Hold on. I'm gambling. Easy easy. I'm gambling.
I got an evil teddy. Dio's best friend. Tie the clock. We're gonna get to be 75 years old when
I get to hard. All right. Go go go go. It's about facing your fears and racing the time. I get to
come back to life once. I have a cheat def. Nice. Activate. Oh nice. Here we go. I can see why
people think this is really fun. This is just like. You can see why but you don't think so personally?
No. Yeah I agree. No. I'm joking. I think it's fun. Oh well I just kill stole you. Sorry. Sorry
Gab. What was his name? Gab. What was his name? Bring back smite. Yeah. No Jeb. That was what it
was. All right. Do I have money? I have money. Let's buy some stuff. So what was my other item
that I got besides the teddy? You can attack speed up. All right there's a lunar item here
on this part of the level. All right come on. I gotta hurry up. It's all about speed.
There's too many places to go. There's too many things to see. Okay there's another one of these.
Chance to bleed again. It's a gab bush. Jeb down. What's a safe way to get down without dying of
fall damage? I think you can dodge right before. Really? That's what somebody. I think I may have
just accidentally read that in chat and I think. No it's true. It is right? Yeah it works. I got
knowledge. Sometimes. Thanks taco. Enough money to buy this? Yes. What did you drop? Did he just drop
a box? Or is that just here? All right we're in medium now. That is the way I like my cheeseburgers.
This is not this was not wise what I just did. I just got two med kits. Look away chat. I thought
I could move. All right we gotta find teleported. I'm spending too much time here. Listen. I looked
over the chat and it was just like you guys are fucking idiots. Stupid fucking morons. Like hurry
the fuck up. Like it's all I see in the chat. It's kind of like crazy. Like they specifically
keep calling out you in particular. They keep going like italics. God damn it. And like they
capitalize the damn it. So it's like really like emphasized and rude. Good tell them to say it to
my face. Oh shit that's the wrong chat. Sorry. I was in your chat. Sorry. Oh that makes more sense.
Like I'm just in your chat. That's reasonable now. Not as far fetched as it once was.
Do you have you found the teleporter yet? No. Oh I'm trying either. Look for the orange sprinkled.
The orange sprinkled dust. Yeah there's a lot of items down here. What is this? What's this moon?
What's the moon thing mean? You see that too right? The moon? It's got a question mark.
Offer to shrine of blood lose 50% HP. No. You do that. What did it do? It didn't do anything.
It gives you money. If I do it it's 75%. Oh shit I got money. Okay it gives you money.
So like do you get your health back or is it permanently gone? No I have 279 HP.
So if I do it I'm not going to. Whatever I'll do it. Yeah you get 100 and you get gold. Turret
down here. Um 3d print this. I like that. What about this? He's helping it. All right I need to find
more boxes. Come over here I got something for you. Oh I got the rope. We're gonna have to get
over here. We can both have a rubik's cube. Okay. Right there. This? Yeah get it. It's inactive.
But I have eight seconds of crit so which one's better? Oh shit I don't know. Maybe I should take
them both. Yeah I don't think I can carry both. All right we gotta activate this. I gotta find a
fucking teleporter. Is crowbar good? Uh yeah I think so. Does it take a random item in the 3d
printer? I still don't understand how that works to change to the thing or. I'm sure we'll figure
it out. Takes a random one. What is it? I think it's first in line on the left. It's slow. I would
lose my shield. What is this? Another fucking cube. I already have one of these. Have we even found the
teleporter? It's gotta be up. It's a random item. We're almost in heart. Random item of the same
tier. Yeah we're spending way too much time here. Random item of the same tier. Printers take random
items of the same rarity. Preferring duplicates. And it's a random item of the same tier. What's
this one? Stun grenade. There's no order to it. It's just random. Good to know. Uh where is this
teleporter? Good to know. Where is this teleporter? Turn invisible. I'm taking heavy damage. That's
cool. It has to be right. It has to be up. It's gotta be. Yeah it's gotta be like on one of these
platforms somewhere. It's over there where I'm pointing. Where? Point at the screen. Point?
Just draw a line with your finger. You guys like. With your greasy fingers.
And like cosmic knowledge. You know what I mean? Like if every single one of you there's like
there's like what? 3,000 people here. 3,500 something like that. Total. If all of you point
at the same part of the screen. Like will I sense it? Because like we have to have the heat map on
for that. You have to turn the heat map on right now. Turn on smart click. Yeah that is what it
would be. Uh is it down here? I think I see it. Uh I don't I don't know. I haven't seen any orange
sparkles. Down here? It's down there. Maybe maybe maybe. Oh come on. We actually missed it. Is this
bugged? Fail the shrine of chance three times in a row. We missed it. We went down here already.
It's not a nice achievement that I just got. Any other items and boxes and shit down here?
I gotta we gotta turn this on man. We're gonna be in hard.
Four in a row? Come on. Is this bugged? Did you get that achievement? No you did. Yeah I got it um
for that. I activated the shrine of chance and failed four times in a row. I lost three hundred
dollars. I just went to the casino and then came back to the stream. I have so many little drones
everywhere. A coin. What? A coin? Coins? A coin. All right you ready? Wait wait wait. Literally a
coin. Where? Get the coin. What I what do you mean coin? Where's the coin? Do you see a coin?
If I did what I tell you I would just take it. Is that it? All right I found it. Oh there is a coin.
There is like a giant blue coin. Yeah there's a coin right there. Oh did I get it? Does this
travel with us? Uh Tanner whatever your name is. Tano taco. Do I have to spend this here?
All right we're gonna turn this on man. This is gonna be we're gonna get overwhelmed.
Well what are you waiting for? I just turned it on. What is it?
Beetle queen. Oh the beetle queen. Is this dumb thing? That's a ride. Where? I don't know. Beetle
queen. Maybe she can't fit down here. Anybody see a beetle queen? Keep shooting your stupid companion.
Oh she's back here. It's a very nice companion though. Don't be mean to my companion. Don't worry.
Okay I won't. I just I forgot this is not a dodge roll. I just may have just killed myself. To be
fair though your companion is blocking my permacritz. All right what we got? What do we
got for items? Uh I don't even see any. A couple over here. There's one. There's a green and a
I'll take this one. All right I'll take this one. This is another jump right? I want my own beetle
guard. Yeah we're gonna have two beetles. So that's good 74 percent. I keep forgetting I have an extra
jump already. You have to scream for crits like Mike activated. Beetle queen is so easy compared
to others. All right well we'll have a second. Is there anything else to open down here?
Something else. Come on. I don't think there is. Nothing nothing nothing nothing nothing nothing.
Are you at the teleporter? Hey you can do a 93 percent HP. I dare you. What? That uh blood
pact. Yeah but we don't have any money to spend. I mean we don't have any. I have 500 bucks I don't
know where to spend it. Yeah this box is maybe something down here. These are all open. They'd
probably be the ones like elevated ones higher up. Just turns into XP. Yeah let's just do it.
We're we gotta try to get through the next thing before it gets it very hard. Back to it. Do the
shrine. Didn't do chance shrine. No I didn't. Yeah I can't spend any of this money. We gotta go.
Yeah we have to get out of here. We really do. On my way. Chance shrines are good. We'll do it next
time. Chance shrine is always worth it. Well that does not feel good but. Do it now. We'll do it
next time. We'll do well I'll do it tomorrow. All right this is where we got one more after this
right and we died on that one. We got we were insane at that point. Let's really try to clean
this up. That hurts. Dear. So the levels increase base stats I assume. Uh I it looks like it yeah.
Okay items. It's always like a dollar away. I don't I don't know what that is. Why am I shooting him?
He's my friend. What is this? Fungus heal all nearby allies after standing still for two seconds.
I had that one earlier and didn't use it one time. Everyone said it sucked so I just. That's
unfortunate. But I thought oh well. That's too many. What is what is this what's why does this
have a broken clock on it? 9 59. Somebody unplugged their VCR. What does that mean?
There's my friends. You need to get to this level before 10 minutes. Oh enemies on hit. There we go.
What is this thing? Why is it only 60 bucks? Is this like a Amazon drone? What is this? That was
that's crazy. 15 minutes on multiplayer. Oh it's like a booster. All right I'm looking for one of
those lunar boxes. So you can spend your lunar coin? Yeah I mean first time we've ever had it.
Might as well see what it is. I was thinking about maybe giving it to you. I was thinking about
gasoline. Well you shouldn't have. This is hurting me bad. Okay they're really keen on the bandolier
right now. Wait save coins for a new character. I found the uh teleporter. Wait you mean that
currency stays forever? Yeah this the currency stays forever. Forever. Forever. What the fuck?
Okay that's good to know. I hope you're enjoying my scarab friend down there. I assume he earns me
money actually. Yeah I think so. That's pretty awesome. All right give me some boxes. We might
consider turning it on here in a minute. I got the stupid heal thing again. And 316 bucks. Should
I pick the missile launcher or the cube? Missile launcher. I'm talking about actives. Probably the
cube. Yeah it's kind of nice having the black hole for crowd control stuff. Yeah it is. Chance. Oh
I got the happy mask too. You have that? Oh I had it last time. It was pretty good. Chance to bleed.
I have a couple of these don't I? How many of these do I have? Two. All right partner what do you say?
Yeah I think it's pretty much go time. You're kind of far away though. Yeah I'm coming back.
All right might as well uh turn it on. I got dibs on this chest real quick.
This chest real quick. I just need like 30 more bucks. Why not? Just I'll just open it for you.
Here take it. Oh let's go. I'm like hurt. I'm gonna use this now like I'm fucking I'm actually
hurt. I need to like not die. All right what is it? Clay dune. It's a big machine. Oh they were all
grouped up for that. I love it. Did you say that is the bomb? It was great. Just keep doing that shit.
So he's he's in the air. I don't know what that means. I'm pretty much just focusing the boss
right now but also dying. Oh my god. Whoa. Oh there's more than one. He's split. He's just pulling
us in. Can I can we out range that? He's got like um mechanite tendrils. All right one dead.
One down. Oh my god why'd I do that? I didn't mean to do that. I'm just gonna stand still.
Are you getting healed? I am getting healed by also my own body. All right I'm gonna come over
here. Let's see what this does. Stand in that circle and how good is the heal? It's like actually
worth doing. Uh I don't know. Oh probably not. No. Well that item is um questionable at best.
Stand still for two seconds. You got this. You're doing good. You're doing great. You're doing
great. Is that like 10 percent? 15 percent? Come on dots dots dots dots man. Four percent. Two percent.
Hit it hard. Hit it hard. Cool downs. Warrior. Hey my turn to get the achievement. All right
these look the same so I'll take one. The fungus is nicely done for out of combat. That makes sense.
Why is he still alive? I don't know. Good question. You can take both. You can take both since you're
dead. I'm dead. Take them both. You're dead? Yeah I'm dead. Wait when did you die? Uh when I screamed.
Remember I was like let me try this. Let me stand still for two seconds and I was like
you getting healed by that? I instantly died and the meteor hit me in the head and killed me.
Oh okay well let's I have 1400 bucks but I don't have anything to spend it on because I searched
this whole area for boxes first. So let's just go. If you got the cash then spend it. There was
nothing to spend. All right well we're good. All right this is where we got to last time and I'm
already halfway dead. We are now on impossible. There's a weird is a hard balance here with
trying to pick up items and going quickly. It's cool. I'm oh yeah I don't know man we might have
taken too long. Yeah but probably I mean I'm fighting like a boss as a normal enemy. This is
our wall right now. This is our like newbie wall. Going quickly is way more important. Yeah
we got we got mechanics down pretty closely now. We should probably just try and do a uh
like a speedy speedy run to the first two areas. Oh my god. Yeah there's like a dinosaur boss in
here. That is who has been pursuing me. Slowed. The inability to shoot straight up is very annoying
against that guy and there's some kind of turtle guy. The 10-minute chest is a weird item. Also
Geb is useless right here. Geb does not know how to path find. I'm dead. I think I caught fire.
You dead? I'm alive again though because I had an item. So that's pretty cool. Okay this that giant
snake thing is around. How do you stop burning to death? Roll. Like every video game right? That's
what I think but it didn't seem to be doing anything. Well that's really great. Wish I had
that earlier. I can dash twice three times probably. All right we're just like circling
everybody and just killing enemies. Oh we're so fucked. I'm trying to kill this one like lizard.
The fire lizard. We're so dead. All right looking for the teleporter. He's dead. That was big money.
Big money. Uh orange flakes. I don't see any orange flakes over here. Wait I see an orange
flake right there. Orange flakes. All right I got it. It's down here. We're going from impossible
to I see something. I see dead people right. Teleport is right here. Should I just turn it on?
Um I'm not gonna tell you not to because I just don't know. Well here. I'm gonna die with that
with or without it. So apparently I'm missile guide now. Maybe we'll get lucky. All right you're
ready. I'm just gonna turn it on. Who is it? Imp Overlord. Imp Overlord. All right I'm coming to
you. Thank you. No I thought he's coming to you. All right he's doesn't have that much health.
He's pretty weak. Just burn him. Hold on I'm not I'm not even I can't even see him. So I'm coming.
I'm on my way. Yeah I am super jump missile guy now. All right I'm helping. Where's he going?
He's invisible. Ah cancelled it. I think we're gonna do this. Uh he's he's focused on me now
and here he comes. We cleaned up a lot of enemies there. Just watch. So he's intangible while
invisible and cannot be heard. All right we got a lot of enemies coming in. Big skull man. The boss
he's almost he's at like less than a quarter. I'm about to go full crit. Oh and he just went
invisible. I'm trying to take care of the adds. There's so many of them coming in. They all found
us at the same time. We got it. Kill him. He's almost dead. Yes. All right clean this up.
We're good. 97 percent. Uh shrine of the mountain. Someone was like wait till they
pray to the shrine of the mountain earlier. So I'm gonna wait until we're done to like press
that button. All right so that's good. You're not gonna debate me that easily. I see you. All right
I'm gonna get this one. You get the other one. So uh we can move on. Do you want to pray to the
shrine of the mountain and possibly die. Um somebody said it won't work now.
It won't do anything now. Well then I can still pray to it though.
You've invited the challenge of the mountain. Oh so we were debated just not in the way we
thought. So it doesn't do anything. Apparently it only does stuff before teleporting. It affects
the boss fight. Let's spawn this guy. Holy shit man. My heart is fucking racing. We got it.
Holy shit. I can't believe it. Have you been through here? Uh no. The new difficulty is I
see you. Uh challenge of the mountain makes the boss fight harder with more rewards. I see you.
Hey chat. I see you. And he I got a lot of money. Well rub it in. That took a while for me to
understand what you were saying here. This is a useless tunnel um for my 1400 bucks. Is there
nothing there? Absolutely zero. All right well. It's a very sad tunnel. Some developer worked
really hard on this. Well it's procedurally generated. They probably worked hard on the
tunnel portion but not on where it was gonna end up. I can't believe Notch made this game.
All right I'm pressing the button. You ready? Oh no no no. And after I pick this up. Okay I'm ready.
We haven't seen this. Detonate enemies on kill. Only three people made this game.
Okay let me guess they're all in chat right now. Probably uh what's this is interesting.
Distant Roost. Loop back to the first stage. Loop back Deja Vu. Should we beat it? We beat it again. Nice.
Well that's one that's one way to deal with early access. Am I right? So now we just kind
of cycle through and it gets harder. All right there's um okay um ha ha ha the loud laughter is
coming up in a minute here. Oh I thought that. Oh yes loud very loud laughter. Holy shit these
guys take so many hits. So is there something after ha ha ha? I guess we'll have to survive
long enough to find out. Uh the answer is no apparently. Struggling to kill one beetle.
Bounce it bounce it bounce it bounce it bounce it. Level up. Man these guys are so tanky.
It keeps getting harder but there's no new name for it. Okay. So it's like a progression thing
right? Yeah I think we did the equivalent of like finding of Isaac beating mom or something
for the first time. So the idea is to try to get to this point by like hard or very hard
and just cycle around. Other people are saying in risk of rain one like this
though it's optional you can go to the end game or loop again. So by saying the end game do you mean
like start over or is this endless mode? Oh every teleport increases difficulty by one so you can't
do what I'm describing. Okay that's cool. Secret item glasses. Oh that's the crit. I gotta remember
that. Here it comes. What'd you find? The ha ha ha. Oh we're there. I wonder how many people are
gonna get timed out. By nightbot automatically. At some point after you loop back you can open
another portal for the end. What is this? You are embraced by the healing warmth of the woods.
That's a lot of money for a heal. Well it looks like we already have the heal. I think it's on the
ground. This must just stay. It's nice and centralized. Whoops got overwhelmed. Yeah those
are my friends. I'm just gonna stay in the heal. Never mind that's a bad idea. Move fast out of
combat. That's a joke right? No I need to open a box. Fine I'll activate this one too. Oh we're
we are in ha ha ha zone. We should probably mine the teleporter huh? It's probably. I think
it's right here. And just see what ha ha ha difficulty teleporter looks like. Well it's
right next to me. You want me to press it? Yeah it's right up here. Uh let me open one last box.
Ooh what's that? Cheat death once. I get to die once. What is this? Gunner drone? All right I'll do
the gunner. I'm ready. All right let's do it. It is the beetle queen on ha ha ha difficulty.
So there's two healers down here. It spawns three of them actually. My bad three
beetle queens. So if you start getting low go down into the heal fields below in the valley.
Will do. Oh okay well I'm doing that now. Can we make this better? I don't think so. Yeah that's
pretty good escape to get down there. What do these bugs do? I think that they like have like a weird
AOA field. I thought it was a heal at first but that's definitely not what it is. Oh god. Somehow
I'm just right in the middle of all of them. There's so many of them. Their circles are taking
up so much screen real estate I can't even see through them. What's going on? Suck them all in.
Oh my god there's so many people over there. There really are they like can't move over.
Look at that. This is all damage numbers. That's awesome. Look at them flying around too.
I'm going retreating back to the heal. Who's laughing now game? The game's going to continue
to laugh I think until until it's over. It's going to it's a continuous laugh out loud.
That is very is very funny. Oh god. How am I negating so much damage?
It's like one of these laser. Because I'm standing right next to them like.
Whoa! Oh my god I'm dead. I just got rained on. What just dropped on me?
Why am I alive again? Oh fuck I can cheat death right. Are those bugs dropping those?
I think they might be. Maybe. I just got fucking wrecked. All right two out of three are dead.
Whoops. Whoops. No actually that's a good thing. Holy shit this is gonna be fucking wild.
Where are all these bugs? Dude this is fucking insane. Are those your bugs? No. Oh I'm dead.
No. I wasn't gonna be dead but then I died. I think I went from half health to zero.
Got one shot. Oh my god there's so many things. Please. I did most of the work for the.
Oh no. There's just no way man. No way. We got to see new stuff. That was cool. What is the red pub
zone for? That's the teleporter charge zone. You just stand inside the red to charge the tele.
Kills. We did good. That's right. We've come a long way from dying on the first level. I unlocked
a new character. Like you. The character's fun. I kind of do miss being able to aim and shoot though.
I feel like when I play this character I like the AOE is amazing but sometimes when I'm just
holding the button down it's kind of hard to tell where who I'm even shooting at but still. Yeah
because the bolts just kind of fly off into a random direction. Yeah. It makes sense. It's
the only character with auto aimed. I'll go back to this guy. I'll switch off. Okay. Let me read
my abilities first. Is there a way we can see how to unlock enemies? I mean classes? I can't really
scroll over anything. Go to the log. Log book. I don't have to go back though. I don't want to
leave the menu. Wait am I still in a party with you if I go back to the menu? Looks good. You can
look in the log book to see how to unlock these apparently. Yeah let's just do that. On the main
menu. Let's just do that might as well see. Oh this is cool. All right survivor. Complete 30 stages.
Yep so we're probably not too far. I mean we're probably like halfway. Free the survivor. There's
somebody we can free. Suspended in time. Obliterate yourself at the obelisk and complete the first
teleporter five times. Okay well we'll get this one and this one probably. Yeah the second and
sixth for sure. If you're gonna play Huntress the best part about it is you can shoot while
sprinting so just keep that in mind. And we'll check it out. Items and equipment. Okay this one
and this one while talking to him. Now he knows what I'm talking about. Yeah I know this is the
second and fifth one. The one where you do so many levels and you do the teleporter five times. Yeah.
Right. Yeah oh yeah. On the same page. He's got it. We're on the same page. All right I'm ready. Is
there any customization? I don't think so. I think they're like I don't think there is customization
but I think the thing I remember reading they were most excited about for 3D was every item you pick
up in the game is on the character somehow. That's cool. I didn't even know that was happening until
you just said it. Yeah so now you can look if you pick up the ukulele you get a ukulele if you pick
up the crowbar you get a crowbar. What a fun fucking game huh. All right let's play with our new
friend. All right let's go. The huntress who seems a little squishy. What's your base health? 110.
Yeah so I get 20 less hp. So the theory is let's try to just get this doing this as fast as possible
get a couple get one or two items let's go. Let's try to burn through this. Find the teleporter.
I love making me the boss killer. I got enough like what else do I have a right click.
So many boxes right here. I found the teleporter. You have you ping it? Yeah.
Why are you like right next to it? Yeah right here. I need a box. There's some over by me.
I feel like um like Artemis. Is that why you were getting like the smite vibes? I feel like I'm
playing Artemis and smite. There's little enemies all right cool. All right I say we go for it.
Yeah let's go. I'm doing this. I just did the thing. All right three two one open.
Beat the coin. May as well stand in the bubble here. Oops oh that's okay that's first time I
push that button. Watch out for the poison in the ground. I can't click it fast enough. I need to
be way close. Oh I did it anyway. That worked nice. I'm just trying to help out with the adds
so we don't get overwhelmed too early. I leveled up right next to the boss which is kind of scary
because she does like a aoe really close but I have the uh war banner down.
There's a bunch of people behind us. Be careful. Oops forget that I have a teleport. All right
clean it up. Sick. All right and then for the loot which I don't see. Is there no loot in the ground?
I got a lunar coin. It should be. Where'd that come from? All right okay I see I got there's an onion
and there's a vr headset. I'll just you want the rare one or you want the let's go it's a beetle
guard. All right boxes any boxes left that we didn't get before you keep going. I definitely
have money. Yeah we just move. I think we just gotta go. We're still in easy. Just rifle through.
Oh yeah just activate it. We don't get time. What the teleporter? Yeah we don't get time. I just
found like four boxes. You would have made me miss out on so much loot. Well we gotta go gotta go
gotta go gotta go. Okay wait wait well hold on wait hold on wait wait wait. So let me understand
this. When we go in this teleporter it's going to just go to medium automatically. Uh that sounds
right. So we have as much time as we want. No no people saying no. Yes. No yes. No I think so. No
yes. No well let's just go. Okay I'm ready. Look at the bar press it. Yeah well hold on
you're the one down there. Oh well I thought you were sorry. All right so let's see what happens.
We're halfway through easy right now. We're halfway through easy. We're pouring on out.
I think it just goes up yeah it just goes up some. Okay so it goes up like a almost a full one of
those pieces of bubblegum band-aid. It just goes up a tick. It goes up a full band-aid. Have we
done this yet? This looks new. Maybe it's because we actually beat the game on the other thing and
we get a new rotation in like a nice desert map. It goes up by one of those quadrants. Quadrants
means four sorry. It goes up by a basketball period. Exactly oh that's what that does. I have
like um the queen bee but evil. Like your friend but bad but mean. It's you but stronger. Okay I'm
seeing. Oh getting shot. Also known as a third. Yeah it is it is broken up into thirds. Yes I
was gaming. If anything it's uh more damage to healthy enemies. It's a freezer. 151 dollars for
these robots. I need some more boxes. Seems uh pretty sparse out here. Yeah it does. Um I'll take
some help. This is one of those shrines over here. All right I got 145 bucks right there. 125 dollars
come on. It better be good. It is. Wow what is this thing? Is it bad? All right that's kind of weird
because killing an enemy like pulls out my fov. Uh what's your special? It's I get like a frost
aura when I kill something. This actually is pretty awesome. All right good good pick up.
All right we should probably get started here. I've got like one box since we got here.
Oh okay. I found a shrine of combat if you want to come over here. Oh yeah let me just grab this
one box and I will join you shortly. This is not a box. I already picked that up. All right I'm coming.
You can get melee. That's pretty awesome. Extra damage to bosses. Nice. What is this thing?
There's two shrines of combat here I think. Shrine okay there's a shrine of the mountain right there.
Oh boy. Do you sure do we dare do that? Maybe. Should we go for it? Maybe. All right let's turn
it on. I'm gonna activate it. All right the boss is gonna be harder. Invited a challenge to the
mountain. All right come to me. We're still in early game so it's not that big of a deal apparently
so should be good. Whatever they're just trying to take away from our accomplishments future or past.
No they're trying to help. Yeah it's not that big of a deal. Okay I do that all the time on super
hard mode okay. I have a I have 120 hours in this game already. 120? I got a lot of money. I need
something to spend this on. All right come here. Now you know. Turn it on. Activate this. I'm here.
Is that the thing? Is that the challenge cube? I don't know. I guess. Did we just get like a bunch
of money? I think so. I mean there's more stuff here. That's yours. That one's your guy. There's
another challenge cube though. Press it? Over here I guess. All these boxes are open. All right
that spawned. Yeah who did that? Okay that spawned this guy. These guys here. Oh lag. Yeah I got the
lag too. We're just gonna we just get a bunch of money for this. All right we should probably do
the teleporter now. Uh yeah I got we got a lot of money. Where are we gonna spend it all? I don't
know. I don't see any more boxes. Rock music. I'm just gonna have to convert. I don't see anything.
Um do I want to go really fast? Teleport is this way. What he doesn't know? What do you mean?
Wait what? He knows. What do you mean? He doesn't know. Should we tell him chat? Should we? All right
there's a ton of boxes over here by the teleporter. Oh one. I meant sorry. I meant to say one box.
I thought I thought there was more. You ready? Three. Is ready because we're probably ever going
to be. This is one. This is soup. This is a hard boss mode. Oh boy. Yep there's multiple uh robots.
Just try to focus on the big one in the middle here. That's a bunch of robots. Yes there are.
No. What did I end up? What just happened? Oh fuck. Okay. All right. I keep like falling off the
fucking edge. Oh this is bad. This is real bad. What is even hitting me from behind?
Oh that edge. Oh this is bad. Okay. Oh we're dead. We're dead. Game over. Oh you're dead. Oh yeah I got
destroyed. Yeah it's not good. Good luck. Thanks. Shrine of the Mountain sometimes makes an elite
boss too. It adds a boss. Okay so Shrine of the Mountain adds a boss to the level and the boss
can be elite. Oh boy. I forget that teleport only goes forward and I'm used to like dodge rolling
backward. Are there three? No there's only two. Help me. I don't I don't want to go back into that.
There are three. They're standing inside of my fun zone. Wait so we got two by default and then one
extra or one by default and then two extra? All right goodbye. Good night. Yeah we got two extra
bosses by the way if you're curious. I need to get in there. Oh no it's two by default. Oh 11, 14, 15
health. Oh very solid attempt. That was a solid. Very sad. I had the frost aura too. Later on you
can get like nine bosses at once with three shrines. Wow that's ridiculous. Well that was
certainly a challenge. They were just trying to help clear the level for me too yeah. Later on
you can get nine bosses with like three shrines. You can spawn nine of those things. I guess we
need to go. We do. We do. We do. We do. Thank you so great Canadian fuck love 10 community subs.
Thank you. Thank you so much. All right dips. Hey dips. Thank you for those subs.
You're welcome. Hey thanks Tal. Thank you Tal. That was me. That's been you the whole time. Yeah I'm
anonymous. I don't believe that. Dropping subs. I gotta get there. All right play good for a minute.
I need to do something. Play good. Okay I can steal all the boxes. But no thank you for real.
That's a lot. I'm just going to set up a key line so I can mute. So I don't talk over.
Why can I not set this right here? Oh god damn it. Whatever. He's muted too. All right move off.
Okay that's a nod if I haven't seen. Move faster. Just in general not even while sprinting. Just a
generalized move faster huh. Yeah just I have like a cast on. I love double jump. That's probably one
of my favorite ones. What is that? Healing drone? All right I want that. Come on give me like another
two dollars. Three dollars. Yeah the right click is crazy strong on the huntress. Yeah it bounces
around too. It's really good. You can stack 10 of those and have speed hacks. That's insane.
That's the best item in the entire game. If you get like three or four of them.
We got something down here. Lots of boxes. Lots of boxes over here. Three boxes over here.
Oh it's okay. What happens if you fall? Because it makes me feel like I'm going to insta die.
It teleports you back and you lose health. Okay so it's just like a slight health loops.
That's good. Any bear? Around the porter. Did you find it? There's a couple boxes in case we want
to pop it. I'm out of money so there's like I would say I'm ready. You ready? I mean I'm as
ready as I'm gonna be I think. I need more money but there's a health hurt yourself thing here.
There's a health hurt yourself for money thing. There's a hurt yourself for money thing over here.
Um I think that's like a different part of Vegas. All right give me give me give me give me.
It's bollying over here. Where the hell did you guys come from? There's the boss. It is we don't
we don't leave this place yet. There's about four boxes over here we can open but this is all said
and done. Don't leave. Oh don't worry I'm not going anywhere. Good. That hurt. Anyone behind
me? Yeah there is. Always check behind you. I don't know if the arrows can actually hit airborne
enemies like that but I'll try anyways. Oh god it's coming to get me. Is there damage fall off
from far away? There is. Uh good question. Yeah there is. Definitely. What the fuck just what
happened? Um I believe we stayed too close to the jellyfish and uh got exploded. What happened?
Because it does like a charge up ability where you have to get out of the circle.
We I thought I mean I was standing on like a cliff. And we both were inside of its area of influence.
Holy shit. Well that was too bad that would there was a lot of items there too. I'd rather die like
then and it's kind of like dying first floor just get it over with rip the band-aid off
and just do it again better. Stand behind so I didn't even know he it was coming at me. Okay
well that was weird. So just line of sight when he does that. Look away for two seconds dying on
level one. I'm sorry. Just look away for two more seconds and you wouldn't have known that we died.
What if you turn around and look the other way? Based on your sight? What if you just don't look
at him? If he's not on the screen he's not real. That's true. Occlusion. I think that's how game
occlusion works. If you don't look at him he's not loaded in so he's not affecting your frame rate
and thus cannot hit you. What the hell is it? What whoo oh these things. Active ability over here.
Gain 100% there it is. That's the thing you've been getting. Uh oh I almost died. That would
have been very embarrassing. Teleport is over here. Oh oh sorry I hit the DPI button on my
Razor return it death adder. Why do mice even have DPI buttons? It's just a gimmick. Nobody
actually uses them. Uh I gotta teleport you. You want to just give this a go or you want to try to
look for more items? Uh yeah whenever's fine. Let's do it. You have to kind of go through a cave to
get here. I need one penny. One penny? I got it. Uh where's teleport? Uh through the cave over here.
Any more items to get before we go? Uh not that I can see. Did you did you select them all?
I may have selected them all but all of them is like one of them. Yeah there's an active ability
one down there. Let's just go. Where is it? I still got like caught on the teleporter.
Oh it's the jellyfish again but he's in an even more difficult area. Well just like stay in the
cave. Oh no that's a probably bad idea. Yeah it's a bad idea. Uh what if he does that in the cave?
My god yeah that's we're gonna like just get eaten alive. I'm just gonna if I see him charging he's
doing it. What? Okay he's fine. All right we have a giant uh cylinder right we have a giant like
pillar to hide behind. We do but I'm not I I don't trust it to actually block. Why not? I feel like
the damage is just gonna go through. Well that's everyone in chat so that's why you just line aside
it. Here it comes. Well yeah it is it's like infinity distance so it is line of sight. What
is fucking killing me? What is killing me? Was I like burning? That guy was just burning me?
Okay that guy was just burning me. Yeah I think you were just on fire. This is the this is the
worst area for that enemy. That guy was worse than the boss. Okay he's dead. Uh these items are the
same. Dealing damage heals you. That may be the best thing I've seen all day. That's pretty good.
All right ready? Oh we have to charge it still. Uh do we have any items that we can get or do we
just go? I don't think there's any items. I think we just go. I didn't see any leftover boxes unless
there was that. Did you get the active item one? Yeah I did. Okay well then I'll say let's go. I
got the crit one. What is killing me? Gamers I need help. What is killing me? Leech is really
good with commando. Yeah it is. Lots of potential hits. All right let's speed it up. Saving money in
risk of rain. I'm not saving money. I'm trying to just get as much as I possibly can and I'm just
gonna abuse this right because I heal on hits. So why not just abuse it? Oh that's a good idea.
Right well you can only abuse it so much. I'll also take 75 and now you have to do 93 so good luck.
Okay why can I do it? Do I have to have the health? Yeah you have to have it to give it up first.
Okay it's apparently still don't have it. Okay if I get hit once I'm fucking dead.
That's dangerous. I would laugh. I don't like this thing. How much? I got another one. Fucking money.
Yeah I don't like that. That feels weird. I have enough to get a bunch of items though.
More damage to bosses. Yeah I'm like heal boy right now. There we go. Okay I'm fine.
The trade is 100% health next. Why would you even do that? For the lord be so funny.
I mean maybe if you have a thing that brings you back to life. Yeah I guess so. I find there's a
bunch of them over here. If you feel like doing 75% money. I mean they're over here. We have the
leech ability so it's not stupid. Yeah and I have health orbs on kill. You need to spend this money
though first. First and foremost. 75 is not bad. No 93 though is a little scary. More bosses to
damage. It's okay. Good choice on this one. Getting a lot of items though. So many. There's a lot of
boxes on this. Healthy enemies. Is this gasoline? What's this one? There's a ton. Increases attack
speed. I have super shield. Did it decrease? It doesn't feel like I increased very much attack
speed here. Over here. This rinds this way too. This is a. What is this duplicate? I could have
infinity banners if I wanted to. I didn't get anything. I think one banner would be fine. Okay
cool. I found the teleporter. I mean you probably already saw it but there it is. I dropped the
banner right on top of the teleporter conveniently so. I don't got a bad build. Yeah I'm feeling okay.
I don't really do a lot of damage but I have a lot of survivability. 117 bucks. All right maybe
we should ping where you are right now. I pinged the porter. Oh you got it already. Yeah so it
should be highlighted. I've got a bunch of money I don't have anything to spend it on. There's a
few boxes back here but we probably should just get going. We're not even halfway to medium so
it's not the worst. Too many elites over here. Okay what was that? Nice. So you said there's boxes by
you. There is one. There's like two. Oh I see it. I see at least one. There's a chance thing over
there. This is addicting. It is addicting yeah. What's that? You just want to make your character
like super powered. Detonate enemies on hill. And see how strong they can get. Move out of combat fast.
Move fast out of combat. Help me out chat. If you pick up two drop orb of health
and they stack is it a super orb for each enemy or two small orbs from each enemy? Looks like
one super orb. What is this? What is this shrine? Okay it's the chance shrine.
It's four hundred and like seventy dollars. Four hundred seventy dollars. I'm about to spend all my
money on whatever this is. Four hundred seventy dollars dude. A gold orb appears. What does that
mean? I don't know. There's a bunch of beetles over here. Gold orb? Go through the portal. I
don't see a portal. Portal? Gold orb portal? Where? I don't know. Apparently there's a golden
orb somewhere. The portal shows up when you kill the boss. Okay let's go kill the boss. All right
let's go do it. We're already at medium so this is gonna be a challenge. It's all right. If we die
everyone's gonna be pissed. Well that's okay. People are like I've never seen a gold orb before.
Here we go. Activate. Who is it? Stone Titan. I don't think we've seen this yet. Stone Titan.
I think it's the big stony guys. Just a bunch of them. Where the hell are they? Up there? Okay.
I'm dying already. Whoa! Okay hold on a second. What the fuck? Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow.
Oh I'm I'm I'm dying. I'm dead. Holy shit what the fuck just happened? I didn't even see the
stone titan. He's like I got shredded. I don't even know he's like up top. Fire elites they suck.
Jesus. Yeah I don't think you've seen the people that killed me yet. I almost got out here. Yeah
this is bad. I can't really go anywhere. I need to like wrap around. Okay hold on. Safety. Where are
they? Oh my god will you leave me? I had to do it. I do a lot of damage to bosses. I just don't want
to go in there with like. Okay he's over there. Is he the he's he's launching like volleys or
something? Dude he's okay he's he's I I he's he's there he is. Okay hold on. I I might be all right
here. You might be all right here except enemies are still spawning in and you're almost to heart.
I know. Oh no never mind. I'm probably dead. And then there's that guy. No no no no no no no.
It's cool that I can see your cooldowns. No I can't. I can see you're active but I
can't see your ability cooldowns. Geez. Okay hold on. If I can just farm somebody for health
for a moment. Look at all these fucking people coming over here. This is bad. It's these fire
elites. All right I'm doing okay. We're almost at heart though. I almost have a chance it's not.
I'm gonna stop the spawn. The spawn is what's killing us. He's up there but you know what?
Forget it. I'm really surprised you're still alive. Use that uh war banner. Yeah I'm just trying to
dodge around it. 99% all right. Super shot speed. Done. He's he's doing it. Okay just sniping from
back there. Fuck it. Well easy. Don't be. I'm just getting like cocky there. That was pretty dumb.
I don't like that underwater thing. Like I can't see when I aim up. Yeah I hope that
they like make it so that the camera bounces on the surface of the water or something. Yeah look
at it. I can't even see what the hell I'm doing. It's strategic. You got to think about your
placement. I'll get this. I mean we're gonna be at a very hard. I can't get down to you. He can't
shoot you. No he's. You kind of stand perfectly still and spam. Although I don't know when he's
doing his telegraph move because I'm under the water. So do I get to go through the gold portal
if I'm dead? Or do I have to watch you do the gold portal?
I guess we're gonna find out. You go ahead. Wait no I'm dead. Items. Dealing damage heals you again.
Twice. Wow. Let's do this. Go ahead. This is gonna go through. It's gonna proceed through the tele.
What? I just pressed it. How do you activate this? It said E enter portal. Oh you're going in. It's
probably loading. Oh do you come back? Are you alive? Yeah I'm alive. What? Hidden realm.
Gilded coast. At least I get to see it. All right. Just like that. Here we go. Oh my god. Rebuild the
Halleycon. Seven beacons we have to touch apparently. Oh really? I guess. Look at the top right.
Rebuild the beacons for money. Oh it's money. It's money. Oh I see.
Basically can never stop sprinting as Huntress. That was pretty sick.
Fieldbot finally got up to me. Nice. Are there i-frames on the dodge? Probably not. I don't know
why the hell I asked that. All right I got one. I'm helping. Okay. I got 388 bucks. What do they look
like? Uh they're like little staffs. Like little staves in the ground. I got two out of seven.
On the lunar coin. Do I get to keep that through death? Yes you do. Oh nice. You get to keep it
forever. That hurt. Uh I got another staff over here. Going for it. What is it? 270? 200? 300?
They're the purple in the top left. Oh nice. 278. 278. Okay there's three. They're just
I'm just gonna go along the outskirts and just activate them. Can we fall? I think you just fall
down there. All right. I got another one. We got four out of seven. Why do we have a boss? A boss
has just spawned. He's immune to everything. Immune. Immune. Immune. We have to turn off all these things
I think to be able to kill him. 297. All right I'm gonna activate this one. All right I'm activating
this one. Five. You got it? We need one. Okay easy. We need uh where is it? It's definitely on the
outskirts somewhere. Oh he's immune. Oh yeah I see. Yeah we can't. There's boxes down here too.
Maybe we should not activate this yet. Nice. Move faster. That's what I need right there.
Okay I'm moving. I'm running. He's too close to me. I don't like this. I'm out of combat right? I
should be going faster. Where is the uh the last staff? I don't know. Oh here it is. I don't have
enough money but it's right uh right there. How much money do you have? 139. What is it 270 right?
Yeah it's like 270. Oh no the rock just fucking no. That's gonna do a lot of damage to me. Hold on
I'm gonna do it. Come on. I'm gonna do it. Stupid rock. I need one penny. I did it. All right.
Defeat the boss. We're doing it. Oh god. Oh god. Oh there's like a giant dinosaur chasing behind me.
That's why I was hurting me. He's like just too far away from my little gold thing to matter.
That underwater shit is gonna drive me crazy. I'm dead. Oh the like crosshair sink underwater
thing. That thing just fucked me up bad. I don't even know what killed me. Oh just spawning more.
You need an insane build to handle this area huh? Well it's it seems kind of manageable. He's a
munigan? Rebuild the beacons. Oh oh my god. Just kill me. That's a joke. Never mind.
That's manageable. Apparently you missed a coin. Whatever. You go get the coin chat.
All right. Hold on. Give me one second. I need to change this. You want to get the coin? 1999 on
steam. Keybind. I'm this guy. Make it uh. You can be this guy too if you can. Let me test and see if
that works. I don't know who this guy is though. Okay ready? Hello. All right so just making sure
I can mute. Um we've done this yet? What's that? I'm surprised we haven't done the uh do the first
level three times thing or five times. I don't know. I got this guy. So you do have that guy.
How how can we both don't have it? Um I think I know why. What happened? Because I cheated.
You cheated? Yeah when I first got the game I have never played Risk of Rain so I did the only the
first area to see if I wanted to stream it. Oh okay. I am one ahead of you. I see. I got cheated.
You got cheated. I didn't even read this guy's abilities. Oh shit. That was kind of my fault
though. All right that was fun. 23 bucks for the chance. What do you got? Uh looks like there's
some decent boxes down here. Can't have been the freezer. Oh boy. That was all that was in those
two. This is this guy's crazy. Yeah good. And by crazy I mean I don't know how. What do you mean?
Manx Shrine of Chance. I love you. Like his movement is. Is it a good character? He's got wheels
and he dropped bombs and stuff. Move faster out of combat. I need more damage moves.
That's my alternate fire and then that's throwing the wee bombs. Uh rolling in. So wait can you
can use two? You're so cool. You look rob. I do look like rob. Apparently you can hold two active
items. Really? I might just be making that up. Is that true? I'm currently injecting myself with
attack speed which is the of course thing that this character needs. Spray and pray. You can.
That's cool. You're like grenades the way you throw my canisters up. Oh that's insane. Uh so I do this
then I can do this. Same same gun but alternate fire. Watch out behind you.
Whoops. Wow. As piercing too but you have to go so slow. Oh stunning. What's the weakness?
I feel like I'm so slow. You look pretty slow. You look like you're having looks like your wheels.
I also have a giant hitbox. I love how we're just kind of I'm kind of circling mindlessly around.
Yeah we probably should just like shooting these guys. Big hitbox. Okay shield. Uh it might be time
to get this going. Yeah it might be time. Where's the uh where's it over there? I'm struggling here.
Shit I want that. All right I'm gonna come remind me to go get that. He jumped over me.
There's two bots here. Do we know where the uh thing is yet? Not yet but I definitely want
to come back and get those. I assume you already went through here. Wrapped this way. I think I can
get one of them. Damn it. Did I miss it? I probably did. Yeah it's like right in the middle. All right
you got the stuff. You ready? I am pretty much ready but. All right it's a go. It's a go. I wanted
to get one of those heal bots. Stone titan. There's quite a few little stone friends over here.
Ow I could not dodge. I go so slow. Get away from me buddy. You can call me Wally not buddy.
Wally where are you stone titan? Back here. He's behind the pillar. He's just hiding. Yeah hiding.
He's line of sighting us. Oh that's fine. Keep doing that. I think I remember reading that they're
gonna make the teleporter easier to see because even though chat probably can see it without any
problem whatsoever uh they're gonna make it at least easier for streamers to see. I think that's
one of the first patch notes. For streamers? Yeah we've had some complaints that streamers can't see
it. Streamers are having trouble seeing it. I'm stuck on top of these guys. This is the uh streamer
update. I really do think they're changing that though. That's fine. Because like risk of rain one
you know you just go left or right. It's either left or right. Up or down. Where's the z-axis?
Doesn't exist. I have money to get my heal bot. Where the hell is my healing drone? There he is.
Almost dead. I don't know when to use oh my god. Good. When do you snipe mode or when not to?
We both. Ukuleles. We both can get it. I want to get another one of these. So what does that do?
Does it electrify shots or something? I believe that the ukulele does a spreading zap move.
Oran fruit. Heal. So it's just a heal. Cool. Probably pretty helpful. It's yeah it's a chain
lightning. I want that of the drone and then we can get out of here. There's a box down there too.
I'll get that on the way back. Let's see. Wasn't it over here? I'm just walked up the edge. Yeah
it's right here. Yeah I just uh I just turned him down. He was low and now he's he was high and
then he's I think he should be in a couple final boxes and things up here to spend money on. Sounds
better. We're gonna struggle with the next level though. There's one more box here. I need more of
these goat hooves. Cool cool. I got two drones. All right whenever you're ready. I'll be ready
in three two one. Can I will I die if I take infinite fall damage? Yeah I'm ready. Surprisingly
no. Send us to the next zone. We're on our way. Do I die if I take infinite damage? That's an
interesting question. Yeah we're getting some good stuff. What's the question? Uh no you said do I
die if I take fall infinite fall damage? Oh well because the robot doesn't have a teleport or
dodge roll. He just goes oh he just goes fast oh and then rams into things. So I was curious
since I don't have like a stop. We're going to make this a quick one because we're in medium
already. Yeah. Your moveset looks kind of cool though. It seems fun. It just it seems like
they overload you with HP because you're going to take tons of damage.
Ah my character has 560 HP right now. Let me go this way. 72. Another crowbar.
Oh a different teddy bear. Chance to block incoming damage. How much more do I have?
That jump is really generous. It jumps across the whole game. Come over there.
All right we've got to consider turning the portal on here. So if your healing drone dies
does it like recharge or does it like what happens? Probably not. I need 72 dollars.
That's really really good range. Will we get a raid coming? Who raided? No money. Where are the
enemies on this one? Drones just die when they're killed. Good to know. Got another coin. I got two
coins. Tomato? Tomato raid. What's going on tomato? Hope you had a good stream. I don't know what you
were doing but it was fucking awesome. So is it better to get the chests that are on the ground
that are the same price or the ones that have like the three tubes? You know what I mean?
Oh that's a good question. We both seem to give I think similar gear. The three tubes you choose
what you want. Oh I had just been walking up to them. Like it may as well be because right we
don't know what anything does anyway. Taleks and I are playing risk of rain 2. Depending on which side
you're on. Yeah we don't know what anything does anyways guys. We've not died once. We've never
played risk of rain 1. We haven't died one time yet so welcome. Now you ready to activate this thing?
Yeah I just can you ping me? Uh oh I thought you're just over there. Yeah I'm like at the
furthest end of the map possible. I didn't find it yet so. Oh well that does change things. Sorry
I was uh I got raided. Got raided by tomato. Sponsored by fruit. He came in swinging with all
of his fucking friends. Uh okay I should just give me something. Come on nothing twice in a row?
Three times in a row. Third time's the charm. There it is again. All right why are you linking
that clip? Of Cheeto? Why? What is that stupid item that sucks? So we don't know where the
teleporter is. Oh that's very interesting. They're really gonna make a streamer mode
so we can see it better. That's what I'm saying. Yeah I'm ready. I am for fully embrace the stream
mode. Yeah I got like a little uh helicopter buddy. I got a I got a lego set thing. All right well
whenever we find it. All right look at all right down I got I got I got it down here. Follow me
over there like behind that guy. Behind that guy. Yeah behind Tommy Pickles guy. It's here somewhere.
Oh yeah there is the orange right here on this strange platform. All right you ready? We're on
almost hard mode already. Almost yeah. Wait what are we looking for? Stone titan again.
Stone titan again. Anything a lot inside any small rocks? I'm just gonna stay here and do damage I
guess. Is this a big enough rock? I don't think so. What kind of a person cries about farts? You know
you have to be there. I can't I cannot defend that clip unless you were sitting here watching that
stream two days ago. Uh something I should know. It is no way I can explain it. Doesn't matter.
It's impossible. All right what do you drop? Uh I picked up a thing that I didn't know what it did.
I now have a titanic neural. Why not do it? This is this is actually going pretty well.
It's just a strangely fun word. It's an inside joke. It's not even an inside joke. I just
couldn't explain it. It would take about 30 to 40 minutes for me to explain what happened.
Try. I can't. You try. Call somebody into your room right now that's like at your house
and explain that to them. Okay. Hey. Derma. Come over here real quick. I gotta show you something.
Well I can't be on your webcam because I don't have any clothes on. Everybody thinks that's
bullshit. I don't have I don't have any I have no upper body clothes on. All right ready well
actually I got money. Bullshit. You got a hundred you got a hundred eighty four dollars.
Uh yep. Come over here. I'm gonna activate that. Like no activate like this thing.
Oh trying. Well I don't have a hundred and eighty four virtual dollars.
Oh you don't? I have a hundred and five. That's not enough. All right we got it. Let's go. We're
kind of just uh anymore boxes like right here. No hold on. Not yet. No yeah. I think I'll have
a hundred and eighty four in a second. All right. There it is. All right. What is that? What is
that little fireball? I spent a hundred and eighty four dollars to see it. Somebody said you're so
greedy. I'm a simple man. I cheat. Box I click it. Wait can I trade um what is this? I'm a simple
man. I'm a shwee. Oh it's actually not bad. All right. We gotta get out here. We have to get out
here. We really do. I'm teleporting away. Take us away. But he said it. He said the thing.
All right. What did he say? I said the s word. Right. It's it's a horrible square.
It breaks like Jeremy terms. It breaks German on eight five terms of service when you say it.
Um not sheet help. Let's find this thing quick so we can be ready for it. Do you see it? I have so
much health. It's insane. Anybody see it? Help the streamers out. We need streamer mode engaged.
I'm moving around 278 dollars. Oh here it is. It's there but we haven't got a single box. Is
that okay? But just be be ready for us if we can just get over there quick. It's taking me a long
time to kill anything. Yeah that's kind of what I'm also experiencing. How many bits for more
sheeto? I don't do that. Explain this thing that you keep saying. I I doesn't dude is no way.
You and I could sit downstairs and like like drink a bottle of whiskey over the course of like would
it require a bottle of whiskey? No but I'm saying like it would be like a let's have like a six hour
conversation and like hang out and like swirl around our fucking whiskies over ice. It'd take
that long. It's a long time. I know. Yeah I would have to give I would have to give you a swirly
before for you to understand. What a swirly. Yeah um that bolt that was kind of sad. What
just happened there? Okay getting blocked. All right are we activating this or no?
Um what is this? Get milky crystal? Sounds like a serial advertisement. Gain temporary flight.
Oh I dropped that. I feel like this just makes you more vulnerable to any attacks. You just have to
press. I'm activating. It's very hard. All right we're activating this. Wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait. Oh shit. I'm I'm at with my heel. Why did I even pick up a stupid fucking mosquito
wing? Seriously. Ow. Look at this. All right we gotta focus on one. Left or right? Extra damage
to bosses is in that 3d printer by the way. Yeah. Like right next to us. Oh I gotta move.
This is gonna be right in my face. These elites are ridiculous.
Where'd my missile launcher go? Somebody's shooting us from behind. No that's you. I think
you just shot me in the back like five times. Apologize now. That's for the swirly. I didn't
even give it to you yet. Dude I don't think I could even lift you up off the ground like upside down.
Oh my god. Is that a fat joke? Okay I'm getting sucked into the vortex. Is that a fat or a weak joke?
I'm dying. I'm taking that either way. Guys I don't know why I couldn't move.
Why did I fucking do anything? Why did I just get double sucked? Double sucked? I couldn't.
I there's nothing I could do. Dodge roll didn't do anything. I was just in it.
How do I use my tactical missiles again? I think I threw them away on accident. Good. Switch to real
gun. No that would require me to let go of the left mouse button. Yeah I got pulled I got too
tethered. No button did anything. It was just time for you to die. Grab your wings. Anything else
with my $1,300 I should get before going? You have to switch your weapon apparently.
Game's done on switch. Everyone likes the robot. Which shoots faster chat? That one
or this one? You know we're up against time with it right? I'm just curious. Do you want to
wear that? Is there like a taunty mode I can do? Like hold on. Shake my robot ass like that at the
camera while you spectate helplessly. Here we go. Mad because bad. Mad because bad. Mad because bad.
Passive aggressive streamer. You know what I like doing? I just want to make sure you're aware
there's a time limit. Do you know that? Oh we're on insane already. Yep this is gonna be it.
I didn't want I was gonna hold this back from you but I decided to tell you.
I picked up a second coin. I also have two coins. Well yeah how come you didn't tell me about the
second one? I did. I told you both times. Check the Vaughn. I'm gonna watch the whole Vaughn to
make sure. Insane and then after that is important. Imposter more like. Insane important and then
whatever comes out. All right I'm not touching like the dragon claw. I'm not convinced this does any
damage. Shrine of combat. No I ain't doing that. This is like a boss. Dodge rolling. This guy's
juking me around. He's acting like a flayer. Oh man this is gonna be rough. This is bad.
Touch it. Touch it. I'm not gonna. Guys look at how much we're struggling already here.
There's a giant dinosaur. There's like a monster rancher enemy over here. I'm gonna die. Jesus
leave me alone. I'm dead. I don't like this character. This character seems incredibly
vulnerable. Are you dead? Yeah oh yeah I died. Oh sorry. I took like 75 percent of my health in
the two tenths of a second. Oh well then let me just. What'd you do? What'd you do that for?
Because I didn't even get. I wasn't even close. I don't even know where the thing was. What about
our statistics? Game knows. Autosave. Well I unlocked the robot too. See autosave. Let me see.
That's too much. Too many words. I don't want to do it. Too many words to retool and rapidly
fire nails. Are we gonna do double robot? Um it'd be different. I mean we could do it. I haven't
been commando guy in a while. It's a stun canister. Basically you're uh gonna get yelled at for using
the wrong weapon so just get ready. That's all right. No matter what. That's fine. By me. I'm gonna
be the one yelling. Don't. You don't yell at me. I'm gonna. Switch to sniper. Am I okay? Am I crazy
or is the taskbar button for this game Planetside 2? Taskbar? Like on your taskbar.
Yeah it kind of is. It's the big number two with a font that I'm pretty sure that I downloaded from
dafont.com a long time ago. You didn't. All right let's see. Blast canister is a launch of stun
canister for 220 uh and then a weird symbol I don't recognize. It's like a bicycle. It's like
it's a top. It's a butterfly. Do you want me to unlock so you can read? 220 butterfly. Too late.
I don't know what that means but. We're going it. Yeah let's go. I'll figure it out.
I'm looking over here. Really? What? Nobody. Nobody liked that one. They all didn't like that.
Which one? I said something stupid. So this is now you can charge that. Okay.
You can actually just tap left click I found out. It feels like you have to hold it down though.
This is like the sprint around mode. So that's sprint around mode. This is the switch mode.
Double switch. Now where the hell's an enemy? This game's supposed to be hard. Where are the
enemies? Speed run. Where are the enemies though? Well I'm awful with this character.
Uh it's kind of difficult but you get a lot of health. Look at your health pool. Oh I do.
You're right. Uh spam right click basically and. Right click. Can I hold it? Okay I can.
It's like a stun bomb. Hey uh does anyone see the teleporter? That is pretty generous. I hope they
make them like a little bit easier to find in the future patch. Okay I got double shield.
Actually kind of fun to use this. It's one hit kill for a lot of enemies. Yeah it's like really
good at just chomping on chumps. And this is the how long does this last for? Do I cancel if I
jump? I do. Not even a fucking good game. Oops. Whoa. Um. I was waiting for you to come around.
We should probably. Activate. Activate. Yeah. It's just like a shitty run. This is like a wash run.
Not gonna you know what I mean? Yeah it's a reset. So what's better to use like this or this here?
Probably this. Uh this I think. Between the two. Like when the stupid stone guys get stuck
and they just sit there and jump in place on the trampoline. Now does holding it do anything else?
Or is it just kill? Oh hi. It's the boss. Oh dear. This is not a place I want to be.
Does it go through everybody? I think it does. Oh that's actually really good.
Oh another coin. All right the boss is dead. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. We got to the. All right cool.
Red whip. All right we each get to move fast out of combat. That's a boss drop. I'm disappointed.
That's still all right. Boomer reference. You know you guys say that but.
You want to try the money machine? You laughed at it. Money machine. Oh yeah. Fruit. I'll save you a
box. Is there a box here? There's a box. Box. Right there. Why did that look like I was going slower?
I also busted the other money machine. Just for you.
The mask of inferno. I like prepped that for you. Yeah you like you sat at like the slot machine.
I sat at that machine. And spent like five grand and lost everything and I came over and put a
dollar in. Thanks. Hey. Let's go. Hey. You have money? I have 14 dollars. No I don't. Granny sniped
your slot. Yeah. Cool. You guys should be nice to your elders. Right off the bat. We've got a hurt
me machine. I'll take it. You can do it too. Oh thank you. What about over here? How much
gold did you get? I got 110. Which one of these do I want? Why did you get more money for losing
less health? Rapidly heal outside of danger. That's actually kind of good.
Oops. Oh he turns into a ghost. Right. Two luck. It feels like two luck sometimes.
Fuck it. No I'm not doing it again. Let's go nine luck. Ah yeah. Too bad it's a med kit.
So there's an initial burst on that isn't there? That's cool. That's why you should
switch between them. On the right click? Yeah for the robot. Okay. Oops. I keep thinking that's
right click for some reason. Got some money? Wait people are saying they can't see squad mode
because it's not working. Has it not been on the whole time and nobody said anything? It says it's
on. Yeah it says it's on. It says my squad. It says my squad. Maybe twitch just fucking it's a
new feature and they're just like fuck we don't know what to do about this. Here I'm gonna leave
and then. Squad mate. Whoops I just invited someone else. Hold on. Dude come on bring him in.
Invite him to the squad. Okay there we go. I just sent you the invite. All right well hold on.
We can refresh. You're gonna have to protect me over here because I need the light. Um not even
close. Uh let me see. My squad. Uh I don't see anything. Let's see. Except we're in a squad.
We're in the squad. Apparently we're in a squad. Timing on that. All right does it work now?
Uh I don't think so. I don't know what people are saying. I don't see. What are people saying?
Nothing. Nothing. It's pretty simple on our side because there's literally you type in the name.
Send an invitation. They accept and that's supposed to be it. Well it doesn't seem to be doing its
intended function. All right what is the uh any sign of the thing? The squad button is kind of
hard to see to be honest when it does work. It's like above the stream and to the right.
No we don't even need to be in a squad. We're like we're our squad in game. Everyone knows us as the
squad. You are taking way too many of these nails. I need a box please. Yeah I need like uh
something to spend on. Nothing. Come on. Come on. Really? I can hear you losing out across the map.
Yeah I did. I'll be able to do it one more time here. Then we got to activate this. One fifteen
was it? Do you know where the uh teleporters? That's over here I think. Oh shit I can't do
it anymore. Oh did you take this one? Oh you did. I did. I sniped it. What about is there
another box or something? All right we gotta find the thing. We're gonna find teleporter.
I'm just gonna go speed mode. Well um see it over here. Go that way. Yeah okay. I'm just gonna head
there. I think we're ready. You good? Ready to give this try? Yeah I'm just popping this last uh
money machine. I'm ready. I'm ready. Wait how do I cycle my active? Oh I get it. Okay that makes
sense. That's not just cycling my cannon. That's cycling everything. Excuse me. I missed my super
boss damage. Ow. I'm getting killed by these like bells. I have a lot of health. This thing. I was
scared. I was gonna just tank most. I'm the one gonna die. I'm coming to you. There are a lot of
these. Oh there's a lot of bells. Oh my god. I'm gonna take the bells out from afar. Boss is almost
dead. Oh jeez. Oh boy. Oh jeez. There's so many bells. Boss is dead. Boss is down. Nice. This is
really a million of these things. We've never seen anything like this before. Uh oh. Because we're
almost on hard on the second level. We took too long I guess. We took too long. Teleport is ready
though. It's the name of the game. We took too long. Yeah that is the title. I don't think
there's anything else to spend money on. Is there nothing else to spend money on? I don't know. I
don't see anything. Maybe we gotta we gotta yeah we gotta just get out of here. Might as well take
us out. No you take us out. Uh you take us out. No you take us out. And you take you you had play
us on out of here. All right I'll get I'll get I got I got I got I got I got it. We both did it.
We both pressed it together. Good job. Okay cool. Uh do you want should I get a drumstick or what?
No. You know I pushed the squad button. See if it works. Come on. There was a hidden button.
What are you talking about with the squad? You have to like actually it's not enough that we're both
live and that we do the invitation but we also there's you have to like initiate it. What? It's
active. So chatters unite. Only took three hours but you know what better late than never.
Name of the game. What's the name of the game Shad? Took too long. All right here we go.
Uh we got we have to activate this **** like now. We're in hard. I hate these time boxes that really
are like you're too slow. Sorry you can't open this. There's a mega skull back there. There's so
many shrines and no boxes. All right I got money. I'm going this way. Rapidly heal outside. I feel
like I just want to go. I need some of these. If you see an equipment box could you let me know
because I have a thing that lets me double charge any equipment but I haven't found any.
I'm just gonna find the teleporter. Hey there's one. It's too bad it's temporary flight again.
I'm gonna say it's over here. What is going on? This is one guy from that far away really just
do all that ****. All right it's right here. It looks like you see the smoke. The smoke?
It's the boss one right? Yeah I see it. It's up there. It's right there.
There's a little. Oh this thing costs one lunar. Is that worth it? Is it worth it for a coin for a
coin of the order? I don't know considering we've been here for a while. This this run might stop
at the next stop. No that is a meme. Okay that's kind of mean. It's a save. Don't do it. Okay do
we know where the oh it's over here. Yeah it's right. You're right. It's on me. We're gonna lose.
I mean I don't have any offensive capability whatsoever. Oh my god these guys are unbearable.
Let me help. It's this thing. Okay we did we got this exact same thing at the same level
already. We had to do this **** already on the cliff here too. Oh boy. Oh god.
This is where we died last time. Yeah I'm getting the hell out of here. Try and stay inside the red.
I'm gonna try. No guarantees. Stupid temporary flying nonsense. Oh my god no way.
This is nuts. Goodbye. Yep I'm dying. I'm dead. They can shoot through the bottom of that rafter
which is kind of stupid. You take damage. I'm so slow. I'm gonna get just collapsed on here.
I don't know if I'll be able to kill this thing. I will try. Oh my lord no way. I can only turn
into a box so many times. Oh you've only got to do 22,000 more HP damage. That's not very much.
No like each shot does 198. So somebody just map that out real quick. What the hell is this
thing doing up here? We'll find out how many basic shots you need. This is a cut. Okay where's the
boss? I'm just gonna try to get the no more spawning. Oh they're over there.
Oh that's probably it. That's it. That's it. You tried. You tried. I did. I really did try.
I'm gonna go back to uh go back to hunters. All right I'm gonna go back to multi the multi
tool. Can I pee? Yeah you want to take a pee break? Pee break would be good. Pee break. Time to pee.
Co-op pee break.
We'll be right back. Squad pee. I'm gonna refill my drink. I'm not back yet. Refill. All right
we are back. Sort of. Uh soda. Where are my ads? No ads. But uh tomorrow we're gonna we're not done.
We're gonna keep playing but just to let everybody know. Tomorrow is the scratch ticket stream
and the germa slots stream. If you didn't catch that from the last couple streams
should be fun. Let's try this again. You back? I don't think he's back. Let me take a look over here.
Uh let's try you again. Heart effects coming soon. Hey hey Midas was having some technical
difficulties. Midas was having technical difficulties. All right let's try this again.
You gave him a swirly.
Titanic Plains. Let's go. All right fast. I'm not being fast. This is a new have we done this first?
I feel like we've done that same uh area first every time. Well that hurt. Oh hi hide in the egg.
What happens if you never leave? Can you take damage in the egg? You just stay in the pod.
Yeah if you stay in the pod till ha ha ha. What happens? Maybe an achievement. You just win.
All right I prayed to the mountain. This is level one on easy. We can go for it. 40 bucks
couple of canisters down there. Give me something. This is huge. Oh that's new. Turn invisible when
you take heavy damage. Two in a row baby. Nice. I got the ukulele from a luck shrine. That's good.
That's good to start with definitely. That's pretty sweet. Okay 54. Give me some long range
supporting fire. It's a healing drone. Give me. Those things are very useful. Look at his little
shield. All right hold on. I need to give Midas his treat. Yeah Midas. All right there's a ton
of boxes over here. Where are the enemies? Where are the enemies? I believe they are flying in the
sky. There's two of them. Three boxes over here. Yep. Like you said. Yeah there's just no way to
get money. There we go. Faster attack speed. Nice. Give me that like three or four times. Yeah I
think faster attack speed would be a game saver. Keep right clicking for some reason. We might
consider turning it on. Do we know where it is right here? No but we gotta go looking for it.
It should be. I see it. It's over here. Thank you SIG for the uh SIG Buur for the five community subs.
Thank you. Thank you SIG. Appreciate it. Dropping five subs. Attack speed is awesome. Oh by the way
I activated the mountain thing. I did. I was standing right next to you. What I activated the
mountain thing? Oh I thought you meant activated the. No we got the uh we got two of them because
of that. Extra rewards. It was worth it. This piercing? Wow. Oh that hurt. Yeah these fire
enemies gotta go. Oh oh oh this is going so well until about five seconds ago. Geez. Heal me bot.
How are we doing? We're okay. Back? Okay. Whoops. Oh god. I'm so sorry. I got cocky. Sorry. I'm
really cocky. All right I guess I get the one on the right. One with less health. One down. We're
gonna get four items aren't we? Uh I don't know. Do you get I guess you should get something for
beating the uh the mountain challenge right? Yeah you just do but we'll just double it up.
I don't know. There it is. Yeah there's four. We're gonna do rock paper scissors over who gets
the yellow. Well the yellow is just the beetle so it's beneficial to both of us. Um hold an
additional equipment charge. That's really good. Do you have an equipment? Because I don't. I do
not but well uh you grab the beetle then. You have like the buddy because you're slower so it looks
I am very slow. It's nice to have some backup. All right now we look for boxes. Coin? Where's the coin?
Oh there's a coin right there. Yeah there was a coin. How many do you have? I have two. All right.
All right ready? You got it. Rock paper scissors shoot. What'd you put on? I have three. Oh you can
have it. Thanks I would. Thanks I win. All right anything else? I see a couple of things right
here isn't active. All right I got three charges of the cube. That's pretty good. Is there a box
back here? Wasting time. And this is actually really good. Yeah we should probably just get
out of here then. Oops I forgot to look in the different. I didn't know what bustling fungus was
anyways. Now I know. Never pick the fungus. Cube. Uh any more boxes over by you that are not open?
Um not that I see yet. I don't see any either. It's good for a special build. Ooh there's one
more box up here that I'm going to get. Grab it because we're about to be medium. Going as fast
as my little wheels will carry me. Let's go boss damage. Ready? Yep. One two three go. He's grabbing
me. Cube is the best item in the game is it? Let's make this quick. 100. Turrets are not the station
the stationary turrets are really not that great because they just stay in the same spot and they
don't come with you. The healing ones and the little floaty guys they do. I guess maybe in some
scenarios it's not a bad idea. Is there no key item anymore? Was there you had to get a key in
the first one? I guess. How much does this cost? 72 dollars. Well I can't believe they're charging
that for an early access game. 72 again. Outrageous. All right 71 72. I'm taking it. I'm gonna take it.
That's good. There's another box here for 72. Another one there. Boss damage. I'm gonna go this way. I love my little
shield on my rope it. Nice sight there. Um praying to the shrine of the mountain. Oh god you're bold
Very bold. Go big or go home. 116. 72. Yeah. I want to go up there and get the money machine.
Sticky bomb. Oops I missed that one. That was a misclick. Got more boss damage. Any sights on the
thing? Uh I see orange. I see orange. It's like in this area. Here it is. Uh you ready? Um I guess.
I need to give you some boxes. I've had I got some. I'm uh kind of far away. It seems like I have a lot more items.
Um you kind of do but that's all good. Um I'm gonna activate this. I got 140 bucks now. I think
there's another box over here. Right. Where's there where's there a box? I got money. I'm saying right
on the thing when you're ready. I need one box. Ah just do it. All right it's gonna be the super
one so good luck. Yep. Stone two stone titans. Oh that's gonna be that's gonna be nutty.
I should do really good boss damage though. I should. Whoa where's the other one? Did we even
get another one? Yeah he's up on the rocks left there. Let's try to kill the one on the bottom
first. See if we can just get rid of him. He's like stuck. Geb just deflected my own. We'll get him.
He's going down. Dead. All right one down. Now the one's up top right? Yep. Well I can't. That's
oh okay there's already boss loot. So I picked up one. There's more though. I almost just steam
rolled over all the boss loot. Well at least somebody would. I was in my speed mode. I'm
getting hit. We get it. That's double. We got double loot twice. Yep. That means we should do
fairly decent this time. All right I think they're all the same so I'm just gonna take two and you
can have the other two. It's invisibility on heavy damage. Okay so how heavy does it have to be?
I don't know. It seems fairly generous. Well for you to stack it I mean. Does it make the attacks
lighter? All right we got money. Let's move to pick up some stuff. Yeah. It's generous. It is. Okay
that's good. Come on give me something. There was another shrine to the mountain. Oh there were two.
It's technically random damage. That's weird. Yeah I found the secret box stash up here.
Is this a box? Yes it is. More sticky bombs. Drop healing orb. Good. This is a luck shrine. What is this?
Nice. So um when you get a war banner again does it just make the war banner even better?
Probably. It was a 137 dollar uh luck shrine that I primed for you if you wanted. Where is it? 137.
I marked it. Dude I have. I failed twice in a row. I have so many drones. I have one two three four
five like five drones. All right I'm coming to you for it. Three healing drones and two gunner drones.
Nothing. All right I'm going. Yeah activate it. Yep. Going home. Oh there's a blood shrine up there too.
Can I get it before we go? Nope. Don't even need it. I got it. No I didn't. Shit.
Damn it. All right let's move. Look at the money. Quick money. 120. Get the timed box. Is it oh
it's a timed box. We have like we have like 40 seconds to get it. Where is it? Where is it? I
don't know. It's in like a. Is it over here? I think I saw it here before. How many seconds?
Is it too late? No it's minus 4 30 for this time box. Oh. We're uh it has to be 10 minutes.
Oh we were close. Somebody said it sucks anyways. No. I don't know if that's true. Maybe they just
said that to make us feel better. Maybe. Somebody said I thought it was 15 for co-op but apparently
not I guess. And all right it's more healing outside of danger. What is this? This the luck one?
No that's the other shrine thing. I'm gonna go look for it just so we can know where it is
because we're only on hard. This is not terrible. Look at all my little buddies flying in. You're
annoying. Die. Bleed damage or super banner three. These crits are insane when they hit. They hit
pretty frequently. Lots of money too. All right money. What is this? Reactivate fan.
Oh rapidly heal outside danger. That's a pretty good amount of shit over here.
242. Oh faster. I want some more damage. I have a lot of weird utility upgrades.
Oh I'll go this way. Another large blocks up here right.
Oops that should be enough to get something. Oh glasses. New reactivity fan again. I've got
rid of mushrooms for glasses. That's pretty odd. Hey there's a glass. I'm just gonna get
rid of everything for glasses. Can I do that over and over again? I don't know.
There goes the knife. Thought I could get him. There goes I don't know what that is.
Probably should go up. All right four pairs of sunglasses. You have four pairs of sunglasses.
Ten glasses 100% crit. So what you're at like 40% chance to crit? Yeah I'm at 50% right now.
I'm going to I'm going for 100% crit chance. I'm just getting rid of everything. Oh my god. All
right. You have to experiment. It's the glass's chest. Duplicate the same item seven times in a
row. All right that should be all of them right. Is this bugged? Yeah come on. That's bullshit.
There goes my banner. 150 gold to do it again. All right I have 10. So you have a you have a
100 chance to crit. That's correct. Well hopefully we can see the end of the game. No
that'd be nice. I don't know which is faster damage or not. Come on. I got it good. No I
have so many slugs. 100% unstoppable crit. I can only just die. I don't know what I had to give up
to get to this point. I have so many. How many slugs do I have? All right where's the stupid
thing? It's time. It is time. I don't see any up there that way. I got streamer eyes. I could see
it. Did you get the patch already? Yep. Oh I can die once. I'm allowed to die. Yeah it's up here.
Extra jump. Very nice. Up here. Oh got it. You want to turn it on? Get ready to go. Hold on I
got to come to you. Now if you can find harvester you heal every time you crit. That seems the same.
No that would be really good. There we go. All right I'm ready. One two three. Who is it? It's
the imp overlord. Imp overlord 20 000 health. Eat this. Just spam it all out there. Just eat it.
I don't know does that damage stack? I have a lot of like tingly crit noises going on. Tingly crit
sound. It's like it's like a sleet. It's like hail lightly falling on your tin roof. It looks really
cool. Look at the look at his health bar. Look at his health bar. Yeah you're just melting him.
Holy shit. He's dead. Well that's one way to do it. Whoa I almost just ran into that. We have a lot
of money though. I left the boss item for you. Thank you. That is yours. Okay uh we have we've
got a lot of money. I didn't see any boxes though. No you don't? No boxes? Really? Um just this one
right here. Literally just this one. Ah just grab it. I'm gonna just check down here one more time.
I gotta wait until we teleport charge because otherwise we'll never be able to pick them up.
Wait does my lightning crit too for the ukulele? That's a fan. I'll stay here in charge while you
search. There's a canister here. Nothing. There's a timed one. Uh yeah I got one here. What is it
what we want? This one. More boss damage. What else? Anything else? What about inside here?
I gotta increase attack speed. Oh are you? Not yet. Hold on. Okay I got a crit chance.
There's like one no. Double crowbars. So oh wait that's gonna stack. Deal more damage to healthy
enemies with super crit is gonna stack for sure. I got the gamer glasses now. Whoops. So now me go
get 10 glasses? Wait can I use that machine that you were using? You can but you have to give up.
Random stuff. Well. So it could ruin your build potentially. I mean my build I don't really have
one. How many do I have right now? All right he's like a sticky bomb. So I have like sticky bombs.
Let's do it. Let's be let's be the crit brothers. Crit brothers. Super lens glasses. How many do you
need? Ten for a hundred. Yeah get rid of the slugs. All right I'm at 60 percent. 70 percent.
Oh I lost a pretty good item. Well might as well just go. Oh my god I lost two of them. All right.
Uh oh. Was it worth it? It's not worth it but with both 100 percent crit.
Let's go. What'd you lose? Uh everything. Everything. You have to say it dramatically.
Everything. All right get us out of here. I lost uh two boss damage things and I lost some really
Is it possible to get 11 of an item? 110 percent crit. That's kind of how would that work?
You ready? Somebody said that's yeah there's the reference for this stream.
True ride or die. All crit all the time. Yeah let's see. Okay let's just not get popped here.
Just don't instantly die. 121 damage a hit. Oh holy shit this is actually pretty ridiculous.
Uh we should do fairly well. We should yeah I mean you have auto aim and auto crit so like
all you have to do is sprint. In theory. I don't have enough money here. This dinosaur used to be
so obnoxious now. All right 157 225. Let's get it. Stupid fucking heal. Extra damage to bosses.
That's what you want. Oh I thought your guy was a bad guy. Yeah I did the same thing all the time.
Another stupid healing slug. Two in a row. Oh I uh see the dust. If you want to rush before we
get to impossible. Uh we probably should. I mean at this point we're almost at impossible.
What do we need to activate this? 150. 150. All right uh you ready? Uh yeah might as well just do
it. All right crit. It is the stone titan. He does do a lot of damage. He does do a lot but if we
all DPS him it should be fine. There's other people fucking flying around here too. No bad.
Very bad. Very bad. I gotta get out. All right one's dead. Need these heal bots. Holy shit. Melt
them. Melt them. Your turn. I need a breather. There's so much going on. It's like a rate. Like
an wow rate. Oh fuck man. He's spamming that at me. He's dead. Oh wow nice. I'm almost dead.
Thank you heal bots for keeping me alive. How many do you have? Uh I think they're yours. I think
they're like I got hours. I have three. They're very very helpful. All three of them can heal me
as well as you. Do the heals crit? That'd be cool. What are we at? 87. All right now we got money.
We just went right through this man. No enemies. So we can spend some time here after this.
That was a good idea. Yeah. All right left uh your boss item and we each have like 1600 bucks.
Okay boss item is what is it? Another fuel cell god. All right what do we want to buy?
I don't know. It's like being a kid at the toy store. The whole map is available.
Okay more damage to health. Four rose bucklers right now. Does a missile drone follow you or is
it stationary? Like is it worth picking this up for the future or? Um I don't know. I know
the gunner follows you. I assume it follows you. Damn it. So we'll get another drone. I'll spend
my money on a stun grenade. A co-op. Damn it. Damn it. Yeah only the turrets follow okay.
Sunk cost fallacy. I know. I know. What is the sun? I lost all my money gambling.
Okay it's gone. You have 400. No well. Wait hold on. I might be able to whoops. Come on.
Come on. 176. 180. There's so many. I'm so stupid. Why did I gamble? I shouldn't have gambled. I
should not have done that. How much is it to gamble more? Like 500 something dollars. I need
there's like two. This two boxes right here like in between there. It makes you feel better. I
gambled and won on the first try. Yeah because I'm the old person that sat down and spent like
five thousand dollars here. The five hundred dollar one. That was at the one hundred and fifty dollar
one. None of these I can. 450. One lunar coin. These minimums are too high. All right I'm ready.
We got to go to some different tables. There's so many boxes here that I could have opened at
least two or three more boxes. I'm so upset with myself. What's this blue portal? I can win it back
just you wait. Do you hit the blue portal or the teleporter chat? Blue portal. Stay alive for 30
minutes. Blue portal. The portal goes to a shop world. We just spent all of our money. What?
Let's go to the shop world and at least see the new stuff. I have a hundred. Well we don't have
any money. Do not do blue yet. Somebody just said in all caps. Well we're not. We don't have to buy
anything here. We can look. I just fell down. What's happening? I fell off the fucking mountain. What
happened? Hello? Hi. You okay down there? I don't know. I just went off. Do I have to go down? Am I
never gonna be able to come back up? I don't know. They didn't think about that when they made this
game 3D apparently. They're like what if somebody falls? Well it just like spawned me and I just
moved for a second. Well you can like can you die and I you can just spectate me because there's a
bunch of stuff people in chat do not want me to buy that cost lunar coins. Okay I technically
should have probably. Where am I now? Okay. Reforge items. I'm back so we can forge. Where to fight
this guy? Hold on is this the character? He has a health bar. Is this the character in the ice right
here with the 10 lunar coins? I think you have to have 10 lunar to unlock this character. This
character? Yeah on the right. He's right where he says 10 lunar and he's in a block of ice.
What about the dragon? The dragon is like he's selling him. He's like the slaver. Reforge five
items. Dare you. No why would I do that? Look is it still counting? Why is it counting in the shop?
Uh oh I'm coming for you. This shouldn't be counting in the shop. Time should freeze. The whole
game is time. This is one big stopwatch. No I can't. I was gonna do one shot and then run.
All right we're going back. This is all too too confusing for us at the moment. We apparently
it's bad to buy anything with lunar coins until you get this lunar character.
So we shouldn't buy anything till we actually get to unlock the guy in the ice.
We have cycled right? Technically. So that's like the kind of goal right now is lunar coins.
Right so stop missing them. Basically. This game's gonna feel so much worse later when we
don't crit every single attack. I'm just realizing this now. What that we've completely ruined the
game? We've ruined the game for ourselves. There's a jellyfish boss just hanging out. I guess the
first level enemies are gonna feel so easy that it's like we have perma crits right?
Top them like that. Doesn't he do the big explosion thing? Yes. We need to be aware of that.
We might just kill him first though. Oh it's happening now. All right we did it. 700 bucks.
Damn. Too bad all the chests are like 350. Let's go on a goddamn opening spree. Another healing
drone. Question mark or? Firely. Bombs on enemies. We'll go bombs. Dude I'm just the healer. I marked
the teleporter for future reference. Okay let's start opening boxes. No another one. Should I
is it uh should I just have like 10 healing drones? I will never die. I'm gonna do it.
I have too many healing drones. Let's fight. I am over by the teleporter when you want
to go. Yeah I'm coming over here now. Uh yeah let's just do it. Might as well
get it going. There's another drone another heal drone here. I have one two three four five five
can I get do I have six healing drones? I have a lot. Let's put it that way. Well I got another one.
All right good. We've got a full party on the left. I don't think they're even on the screen
anymore because there's too many of them. All right what's it gonna be? I can't even count how
many drones we have. How many? Two three four. Oh he's dying real fast. I'll take the one on the
left. All right let's see you can kill him faster. It's gonna be you. Mine's dead.
That like rapid okay we got a lot of fucking niddies but hold on I can't suck them out of
their little tubes. I can stay invisible for so long. They're going all the way across the map.
All right the bosses are dead now I just have to not give me that give me this. What's wrong with
me? Found a coin. Wow all right we're pretty good at this game now and I want to savor this moment.
Savor it savor the moment of the fact that this is probably the only run we're going to like be
able to do this more than once. Be like gods. This is like when you finally get that Isaac run
where you just walk into the room you push the fire button everything dies.
Kind of. Did you uh did I get it did you pick up the item? Nope okay get it. I forget if I wait
did I? Maybe not but you actually you know what you should be picking if there's like damage items
they should be going to you if I'm completely honest. Well the pandalir is just ammo pack to
reset cooldowns which is more your yeah but I kind of just do dps but you're if they're like
do more damage to boss if those bullets show up that you should be taking them.
I'm invisible for so long after damaging the all the heal bots swirling around this chaos I love it.
All right let's go time to loot. I will go the other way. Oh five bucklers that reduce damage
while sprinting is pretty cool. Anybody see anything? Uh shrine of chance. Gunner. I had
to do it. I did. Oh god. Sorry. Just move faster out of combat I think I already have a couple of
these. I also got that. This is very fast. Can't lose them all. Going for broke at the casino.
Me too. I got a fucking what is it okay what is going on? Who's dropped who is dropping this
shit all over me? Okay all right I activated another drone for fun so that's all my money.
I got faster sprint. Ready? I'm ready. Did you get a squeak? Yeah what was that? It's like the soft
landing. I think chance to block incoming damage teddy bear squeak. People throwing rocks down at
us. Yeah I thought I just died. This game is just laughing its ass off at us. It is. It's going to
have to send enemies with enough HP that it's okay if they get cribbed every single time. What have
we got in here? Stun. None of these are worth it. Where's the casino over here? Did we? No we do
not dare activate the scary thing right? No no way. Probably not. I mean we could. No no this is
such a good run. Let's play it safe. We need to play this safe. We have to like try to get like high
as high as we can. That hurt. Well we're in the right city to do that. That probably if I didn't
have the heavy damage thing that probably would have been an instant kill. I would have dead. 400
what's in here uh the unknown the unknown sure it's gasoline man the gambling is getting
significantly more expensive yeah it is the super crates are almost a thousand each uh the
teleporters over here this way we can activate it if you'd like to do it and then run around
but uh there's like a fire elite enemy over here it's gonna be a big pain in the ass
hold on i just want to open one of these boxes then i'll be ready yeah this guy right here is
gonna die okay i'm ready this like fire okay yeah yeah yeah yeah oh dead instantly holy shit i'm
dead instantly okay yeah that was a 100 health kill did you come back to life yeah i got had
the item that maybe brought me back you gotta kill we gotta kill that fire thing
jesus i ain't fucking around with that anymore dude bye just oh my god look at this aoe are you
dead again yeah oh my god fire guy's dead yeah i'm gone got melted all right so i guess i should
just activate the thing where is it you might as well just activate it no you have 1200 health
that's right yeah because that thing was one hit killing me it is it where is it uh but it's
things below you but it's like to the bottom left below yeah down there it's like underneath
there yeah so much is that fire guy still alive maybe it might be able to do it you have like
100% crits it's possible oh my god the drones stay right so even all the drones that were
purchased get to stick around i spent my whole life savings on all these healing drones i hope
they help you can i go under here no that's too thick holy shit 58 you're doing like 600
damage a shot with that thing wow you might actually do this if you you know me that's at
36 it's gonna be hard but if it is very possible if you just kill both bosses and just oh there's
three you do so much fucking damage though you really do i don't have any more healers
they're just spotting so many around me they're there the drone army is being
depleted there's only three about two hit drone army is gone two left out of uh like 12
i'll just go this way and cruise for a minute if that's cool
i'm gonna hang out over here on the lovely side of the map you had like 20 what you leveled up
why would yeah but oh my god oh hi oh if only he had some slugs he'd be doing just fun if only
i had any healing survivability whatsoever there are two healing drones somewhere apparently
are they like stuck somewhere because they have full health
oh we knew it was coming yeah we knew it was coming that was still pretty good that was still
fun yeah we made the loop so how do we unlock the other uh three characters let's take a look at
the main menu yeah let's see because we got one of them complete 30 stages is the other one
we should be on the way itself requires pause what the hell is obliterate yourself at the obelisk
mean okay i'm gonna have to mute for a second because uh mute for a second where does he go
uh but uh what does that mean what does that mean what do you do you have to get to stage seven to
spawn a portal you unlock four of them by just playing normally the other two require you to
spend 10 lunar coins and get to stage seven okay obliterate is completing a run will we just on
level seven you kill yourself in a portal okay that was six we should do this pretty soon though
i wish it showed you how many you've done can i see that information to feed the teleporter
boss in under 15 seconds uh there's more page defeat 3000 enemies reach 300 move speed
some crazy things are crazy things are happening yeah what are you good what happened um
somebody just misclicked and uh gave 100 gifts up oh a hundred subs oh good nice holy shit that's
fucking crazy a hundred a hundred i can't refund they're mine now complete 30 stages so we're
we'll probably get this 30 stage thing uh probably next or one or two more maybe
italics has asked you to play risk of rain i'll try i'll try it i've heard it was pretty fun all
right i'm gonna yeah i'm gonna stay i'll stay decline decline it who should i be um i just
don't i don't i'm not a big kind of default character i like the default weapon but i
don't like the move set yeah i enjoyed getting super crits as multi but um we could do double
huntress probably not a big deal i haven't played huntress in a while i would like to try it
yeah let's do double hunter okay all right let's let's go hurt yourself shrine got it
mm-hmm 39 dollars boxes quick come on somebody enemies die got it 27 30
oh air shot what the fuck was that nice aim all right there's two more over here
why am i not doing a face cam i don't do face cam i do face cam like sometimes i don't i don't do
face cam i really haven't been doing it much this stream either games like this are really good for
it because you're like your tongue is being chewed between your teeth and you're like we're trying
hard yeah you just like you mashing down on your tongue you guys want to see me just fucking chewing
on my tongue no i'm gonna be lie to you i don't i don't really do face cam i do it sometimes
that's not a lie that is a truth all right we probably uh let's get this started probably
the best damn it that's a drone 55 ah all right let's do it is it right there oh jesus what the
hell happened here he's having a bad hair day the jewel the joke there is every day is a bad hair
day right um so we ready i'm ready i'm turning it on all right let's do it it is jellyfish
kind of a bad place yeah well it's just a bad it's a bad enemy for us because we can't use our
fourth does this count as lines i don't think arrows hit right no they do they do i hope these
count as line of sight you're doing it whoo don't do it don't do it yeah the mouse too for this
class is amazing oh i thought he was doing the super that didn't hit it in what world are you
doing it this is the super that almost insta kills me that's good oh what do you drop the hell is
this they're kind of in weird spots aren't they you link the image they're just like hanging out
up here that guy's too far away i don't care about uh what about any more boxes yeah we killed him
pretty slowly dude where are the boxes for this particular one down this way i mean we weren't
95 philabias is taking so oh yeah did we just we just so good at killing the boss i guess we
not just standing in the teleporter that whole time i feel like we've been here for way too long
there's so many stationary turrets on this one and nothing to spend yeah we just gotta go i'm
ready to hit it and you're ready uh one sec coin where's the coin coin the coin spawn randomly or
is there like one on every level i don't know i feel like it's random all right we're gonna
we're gonna be in medium on the second yeah i think i've spent as much as i can we get two of the
kind of slowest damage characters we might get screwed here yeah dps a little low we're going
to the desert though abandoned aqueduct is that a hurt yourself item no there's a fish item what
is it what's the fish do combat nope 67 dollars such a vast landscape and no money uh give me
something ah yeah i feel like this takes forever to kill anything we really did spoil ourselves so
bad critting every single time and then just like yeah yeah yeah yeah three four five dead
a lot of enemies over here i've got money now can i buy something oh what is the bottle flame
too expensive is what it is all right okay do you get the impression that some of these maps are
way too big sometimes yeah i feel like this these maps in particular are just enormous
and it doesn't really add anything um well it's probably a time thing right they make it bigger
because they want you to spend more time on this area i guess trying to figure out where to go
uh any sign of the teleporter yes i have a sign of the teleporter by me
don't want that don't i don't want any of those uh whenever i get like the bounce right click it's
like jubilantke this really is just smite welcome to smite uh you ready for the teleporter i guess
yeah kind of just hovering in its general area looking for a last box or two i still have money
but there's a lot of secrets on higher areas of maps uh i see uh at the tp let me turn it on you
seem to have spawned a lunar coin which i grabbed oh good how many do you have uh i have four
okay so i have five yeah we're pretty much even it's always this guy huh apparently
dying quicker than the last thing was there's a big elite beetle next to you oh yes there is
oh he's killing me too where's my healer oh god damn it i thought he was gonna say i thought
i was gonna run towards me yeah this guy refuses to die they're nice and group fighting two bosses
get up there that's the tether be careful almost got him this game is just kenshi with
teleporter it's what i don't even know what that means kenshi with teleport i don't even know what
that means is because it's a desert is that the that has to be the reference are there any more
boxes some lucky stones i guess that was a joke about another person's comparison now i see
i don't see anything over here nothing if you have 242 it's almost a guaranteed lucky shrine
up here almost guaranteed i got 700 i'll try i'll give it a whirl no well hey i got an extra jump
hopu feather attack speed good is this 160 come on yes let me know when you're ready because i
spent all my money gambling i am ready i have two of those bucklers so is that just straight up like
10 damage reduction 20 um i don't know it's a chance it just says reduces while sprinting i
don't know what the percentage is 127 yeah we have such a little dps yeah we're already on hard
i want to get that other character though yeah we just have to complete stages right i guess
yeah we have we have to be close we were at least 70 plus percent of the way there did you could you
see how many we completed in the log it doesn't take you there's no number but it's like a bar
i see what i got money so i just need to stay sprinting the entire time
it's kind of hard to aim when you do that though when you beat 30 total levels i wonder what
jesus i wonder how far we are we probably at like 28 no bad oh god how did i end up in here
where are you oh there we go kind of just stuffed inside of that thing
opening a chest will launch fireworks oh okay i'm getting killed here i'm gonna get the hell out
of here there we go the fireworks is actually kind of cool even the little money chest huh
that's crazy the hell is on the ground here okay like 10 monster or environment logs good job
i feel like i'm getting destroyed you look like you're getting destroyed i'm just getting
hammered i'm kind of leaving you alone so it's also my fault but there's stuff up here that i
need and i have enough money to open something this is a big map isn't it just keeps going and
going all right i'm gambling again i'm going for it i'm gonna do it ready told you did you get it
i did all right we got it we're gonna we gotta go we're gonna die at this boss we this boss is
gonna fucking destroy us yes i cannot deny it but i did find the uh the spot at least i have
equipment yeah you ready uh where is the oh it's over there by you i was just over there yeah we're
in very hard mode now into uncharted territory yeah so the what is the red down arrow that's
stun or slow the red i think the red down arrows attack down maybe it was slow yeah maybe
i don't know all right let's do it pump it up might as well let's spawn the
it's the imp the imp overload apparently slow the teleporter oh shit oh that's a lot of people
so many lasers pointing across it's also difficult for the huntress to get kills because
the auto aim if any enemies get in between yeah it is you do that really good aoe though
yeah be very helpful and you can sprint faster than these like robot lasers can catch up to you
pretty much just sprint circle shoot oh damn it yeah we're doing so little damage it's funny
no well they're almost not spawning anymore so that's good yeah i mean the teleporter is
almost 99 then we just have to defeat the boss so it should be doable now almost dead
some of these balls running around okay 99 god damn always right when i do the aoe teleport
we're like at the halfway point it's like half dead our basic attacks is so pitiful
oh need a bop bop character need to bop bop did he go all the way across the map
uh he's all the way down here he went all the way down here time is still ticking too wait
teleporting back is he coming back hey teleporting bosses gotta love him what oh there he is he just
kind of fell oh die yeah double aoe doesn't mean a whole lot right now not really really with 75
left coming back to hell all right to be honest we should just go all right you get both of those
why i don't know because you have two of them already just get it what that that's something
that does uh explosions right detonate on kill yeah you got three of them now okay so there you
go so now you got three are we gonna stick around to loot or do we pretty much get everything um i
think we have solidified the fact that we're going to lose so i would say we should probably
just complete it and try to complete the next one and you know try to unlock the other character
that's what i would say hey well i found a couple boxes you tell me when you want to go but go ahead
we are going to be an insane i wonder no not yet we're gonna get on the next thing we do we're
gonna get it what what are you talking about on the next character on the next thing we're
gonna get it on the next cycle we should get the new character oh was that the 30th stage
not that one but we're very very very close huntress is worst class in my humble opinion
hunter seems like a really good class to not both be at the same time so i learned my lesson
maybe seems like a great support doesn't seem like a like a main yet i think we need to unlock
more items i think we need more cabbages you say cabbages we need more cabbages
every class but the huntress is the worst class true i'm gonna sneeze and i have no way to meet
up society oh again last second no sneeze is always coming pairs though they do and you're
right because here comes another one thank you i'm trying to eat it i can't it's hard to eat a
sneeze i can't kill anything there's no there's no enemies character need to buff
it happened it worked oh it worked they heard my cries whoops wrong buttons those are all the
wrong buttons well that's a big guy whoa you go big guy i'm gonna come back and help you
i try to get away post for the fans oh boy i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead boy you're dead now i'm
alive i'm alive i live which one is it i live probably not for long though hey more firework
chests huh kind of a weird focus that i have for this run i open stuff good get away from me
get away from me what is that 3d glasses uh i'm on teleporters over here i wouldn't spawn any of
that until this big guy's dead though okay probably for the best he is dead all right i wouldn't
spawn that until we're ready to grow and we're probably we're an impossible all right i'm ready
impossible yes so it says but i don't believe it let's see if it's possible mega oh it's the
magma worm we haven't seen this in a while i'm not sure whether to be real dagger okay got
ceremonial dagger i'm going for ultimate crits i can't even see what the fuck is going on
honestly i have no idea i know these enemies the whole screen is red and glowing sometimes i
right click dude we can beat this magma worm it's really hard oh boy big guy over on the left
he's here huge huge monster a cyclops guy so many boxes just sitting right up here too
trying to help with the cyclops guy yeah i'm dying i'm invisible so i'm gonna run too
i think we'll get it yeah i think we're gonna get it we're definitely got the 99 so that's good
now we just have to do magma guy no don't jump up please i assume he's a lot harder in 3d than he
is in 2d so is this just a 3d reimagining of the first game i believe yes 3d remake my god he's
coming is he dead uh he's like jumping higher he's deciding to jump much higher now he's there we go
proceed through the teleporter uh we did pretty well do you want to look for boxes let's look for
boxes yeah what do you want the you want the beetle is it a beehive or okay okay i'm dead i'm dead
i'm dead something's killing us what's happening i was just my my health full i'm dead well thank
you for uh donating your boss relic you're welcome oh see that i i was is that i just got rained on
isn't these guys it's these there's mortar craft apparently low enemies i just got rained on
that is the rhythm right chap you're right good pun apparently there's apparently there's a
legendary chest in the middle in the middle define the middle they have global range the middle
where was that it uh legendary chest cost four thousand dollars well we will be passing on that
we will not be doing that one it's between two structures in the ground level uh cube or crits
i'm gonna say cube maybe okay double crits let's go yeah teammates revive on the next floor
now he's dead forever uninstalled if you die again we are not friends weird that that also
i'm like a frost boy now those fireworks are cool i got frost relic killing enemies surrounds you
with icicles every interactable spawns missiles that's fucking hilarious um is there a reason why
i can't move what's going on okay that was weird my keyboard took a second to not lag
well that made quick work of them yeah i have two active charges i guess you went to a combat
challenge over here yeah for money there's a guy oh ow ow ow hurt pain missiles got a lot of money
that's what combat challenges are good for that is so much money two thousand dollars right now
that really wasn't a big deal at all uh teleporter is also here we got gasoline
ow what the hell was that was the big guy move even faster probably not a bad turret spot
what is this uh 3d printer for i don't know more fireworks on interactibles cool i could
help with some more stuff man i got so much money some stuff over by me two ish three ish chest
ow he can shoot backwards that's not fair gasoline bleed yeah i'm not the biggest fan of
fungus either all right there's an extra damage to boxes is nice that's fucking money i have
i feel like there's a lot more chests here than there have been previously do you need an active
no i got missiles there's one there's two right there actually there's a box oh no boxes over here
almost killed me i mean is that you guys ready for this i am so spoiled by like
this movement how many of these do i have all right i am ready i'm just going for speed
i'm gonna do like 100 more faster speed wait what is this this is just oh that's yeah i have like
three of those already i'm gonna get as many as i can oh boy i'm pretty happy at three i'm going
for like a hundred percent speed build oh my god that is kind of insane i want to go have six
feels like using cheats i'm gonna get 10 that's gonna see what it looks like he's throwing he's
throwing we're on ha ha difficulty all right we got to start this thing one more all right
god you can start it hold on i'm gonna give you a second to get over here shouldn't take me very
long true hi all right we're in we got some friends we're doing good damage though this is
actually kind of crazy this is really fun oops just run forever yeah just try and like outpace
him the lasers are still homing though which is kind of annoying you can't even touch me what oh
that's bullshit dude that they are they call they stick right on your body no matter how fast you're
going you're right i sent uh two orbs in there and just mass killed everybody the black hole
arrow rain yeah that was a sick multi-kill i'm trying to freeze them i don't know if you can
freeze bosses but i have a freeze aura freeze god damn it why we're doing surprisingly well
i should be able to outrun that ouch ouch ouch ow it hurts i just took fall damage there
i can like not hurt anything though oh boy all right 89 teleporter getting there
there's so many of these guys oh my god yeah there's a ton
jesus oh man trying to freeze them all down oh we got a blue portal which apparently we don't need
they dead boss is dead teleporter is active um did i pick up the boss loot already
uh what was the achievement we just got there's another boss loot here
uh i didn't pick one up yet i don't think yeah i picked up chrono bobble too i don't know what
that is so do we have enough to unlock this guy there's a coin where's this coin all right you
got five you get five coins right uh i have five coins so you also have five coins yes cool oops
all right i don't think there's any more chests here to be honest no we've i kind of went around
the whole map i have like 10 000 gold yeah you need you each need 10 oh yeah okay there's some
boxes back here no let's see if i can find any all right we're gonna look we're gonna check it out
i don't see anything all right could try it what is it something good cube uh i like the missiles
i sound like a bunch of horses i don't see anything else i think we're good to leave
there is a way you can end a run after a loop interesting you can leave whenever okay well
we're gonna get some levels though you should go on the portal or should we just leave uh probably
just leave okay just go yeah your move speed seems to make your uh teleporter like your dash
go much further portal is if you have 10 times move speed then you've got to be teleporting like
crazy i think we just fucked ourselves i think we have we were supposed to go on the portal
for like the win condition why i think we can like win like end the run or something when
not i thought that was the shop we went there last time and we did it as a waste of time
yeah wait why is everybody freaking out last time everyone said don't go there
all right i'm just gonna find the portal i'll just be i'll be portal finder okay or uh i mean
the finder of is a now there's a boss over there fire a nice power it is here it is currently
being guarded by it's a giant jellyfish over here i actually have decent attack speed no
giant jellyfish huh there is a big jellyfish this way hello i'm gonna get some items that's
the slug all chests are like 531 very very expensive do like one more chest and then open the
pandora's box i'll help you with the jelly jellyfish more equipment
fire yep the burning ticking damage is like the worst defender out of everybody i think
yeah the fire fire damage seems to be super super like over tuned yeah you can just die like in a
second if you hit by far oh oh oh are we good i think i think i missed it because i was in the
air i got caught out this is not even the boss no oh my god did i want to whoa whoa wow oh yeah
sorry fire hit me oh you're dead i'm about to be dead i think i got hit by like two fire blasts and
it was just doing it yeah that fire damage is a ton at least it got to be fast that was fun
so they run around like that again is this a line of sight all right i guess i will try
good luck just say we did it
oh my god ah i pressed the wrong buttons yeah the beetle queen is really well poisoned but
you have to fight all this yeah like i can't look at all those robots they can't even move this
stuck okay that was that was seriously like diablo 3 level of numbers in the screen yes
accurate uh people are saying you have fungus run away and regenerate if you get low um okay
that's like like like run away like far away i don't know how accurate that is but seems pretty
accurate we're doing it why is italics doing so much more damage uh because i traded all of my
items for boots to run 100 faster and ran around in circles i'm not i'm not done yet
like i haven't i haven't won yet you know i got a little damage i do to this guy
this is like another boss that just spawned in okay i guess i fly now yeah wait okay do you
are you invulnerable when you touch that teleporter or does everything have to be dead around here oh
god oh boy if you touch the porter are you immune oh i think you can touch it and
run away and it'll just port you wherever you are trying to heal okay god they found me i guess
yeah you're not immune but you can just run the wisp is so good with this many mobs yeah that's
why he has like three or four of them what's the wisp the explosion thing right yeah just touch it
touch what touch the teleporter and run it'll just pull you out wherever you are
although you know you might get one shot here there you go huh there's like a small probability
possibility of dying and we're back yeah what and you're almost dead what's that
that wasn't fair you better run what the fuck was that
why is everyone spawned into enemies they were just sitting there waiting for us
all right uh we see we ain't gonna make it past this one what's that thing
uh there's a big ring oh what is no that's just a guy we are actually in hell now yeah we kind of
are well i want this box yeah now there's just bosses in the level with us naturally like from
the beginning what i get i already have that 700 bucks huh if we make it past this level i'm dead
if we make it past this level i'm dead i can't do it what the hell killed me was fire sprint faster
well what do i have to lose right all right burn the boss there's only gonna be like six of them
don't worry there's only one two three four five there's only five of them don't worry
not to mention the one that was already there okay well hold on a minute how are you as fast
as i was because i have three of the boots and i have sprints faster there's a goes faster and
the sprints faster so ten goat hooks is not as is the same speed as three goat hooks and sprint
faster i'm not i think i still was going faster than you what is this a sonic race like am i
knuckles right now we haven't heard like a tails race i just don't think it was worth it you know
you can do it you can kill them and then we get to complete the cycle
give it everything you have everything's on the line oh you got tethered you got tethered
i'm dead no no you're back you're back he's back he's back second win gotta go fast
you're at like 40 percent 35 percent 30 oh my god i gotta hide
oh there you go there you go come on come on so if you beat this there's gonna be a portal
that you're gonna go through instead of the teleporter and that's gonna give us both
100 gold there's still one with full health 100 that's a lot you're so close to getting rid
of one of them and that's there it is okay that's 33 percent less annoyance all right i'm gonna go
back over here chill for a second they heal during the suck phase okay i see where is he
there it's right there i'm so glad i just fed you those two items and then i threw all mine away
ow oh you could just play it slow play it simple i need full health for this guy because those
rolling chase things if i didn't go invisible i think i would be dead yeah did he do the suck
phase yet watch out for the rolling bombs why is one harder than everyone else you know what
i mean like why is it there was five of them why was that easier than one because it's the illusions
it's just the one of them that's the real one you killed all the illusions he's the illusion
my apm is probably so high right now come on dude you like give you get the boy scout badge
for doing this wow he like spawned right on top of you so close oh god
oh 55 minutes you got it 55 minutes oh my god 55 minutes all we need we're gonna see the cycle
that will be completed let's get the chant going here we go italics oh here we go here we go indeed
i think i got chunked for like 33 percent that was so close though you did so good
jingston here we go i didn't ruin it i didn't curse it there's no such thing as curses
it's no such thing as ghosts i got cursed oh that's all right oh damn let me see how close we are
he was the last guy yeah but that was fucking insanely hard like that was very difficult to do
all right let's see we how much all right we we seriously need to do like it was back here before
we'll get it here maybe next time don't ruin your build with goat feet well we have what we had to
see it you know what i mean i just wanted to see what it did all that work all right this is the
one you ready are we away from success uh we are probably like three or four levels away
so like one run probably one run one run from new character i think we can do it yeah well we
i'm gonna i'm gonna okay here we go i'm gonna try really fucking hard this time okay i'm gonna go
multi this time i feel like i did good with them last time i think i'm gonna go robot i had a really
fun build that was probably the most fun hunter's build yep there's like fast darting teleporting
let's give it a go this is the one oh yeah i have to invite you again my bad yeah there's gonna be
sweat pouring off my body i'm gonna go robot you going robot or do you want me to do double
robo one might not be that bad i could go commando if you want we could have one of each
double robo double robo double robo wait hey i don't know i'm gonna go either way on that one
double robo here we go now watching me like like run off the cliff like a funny thing
let's go oops forgot how to play all right let's just do this here we're here yeah let's go
challenge all right really you go okay that was dumb beating up dying on the first level
man the stun grenades on these groups are awesome i'm missing every shot so i'm gonna switch to
no miss smug no miss all right we get there's still somebody alive i feel like the ram should
do more damage okay uh there's still one of those enemies left he just threw is there yeah he
like really ran down here maybe he's dead i don't know okay boxes oh a coin oh nice up to six
oh you just killed him okay uh we got an activation here for the scary monster at the end
uh the mountain that's double loot man starting like a vanilla isaac run after being a literal
goddess i feel so slow it works pitiful all right well there it is oh that's better how you doing
good you found the uh portal yep yep right here by me well i am ready whenever you want to activate
all right here we go you ready yep i'm here two one activate what is it it is the
two of these things so is chance to stun amplified by scatter shot mode oh that's
like since you're shooting more bullets do you have more chance to stun or is it more damage
equals more chance i don't even know good question why are you doing that trying germa
what because i wanted the fireworks to come out and do some damage behind us careful one of those
robots if nail gun prox every time that would be completely op fair oh i shot you you look like a
bad guy oh sorry i'm screaming now okay what the fuck uh this is very bad very bad i'm gonna die
oh it's happening again this is a very bad position to be in how do you heal in this
game i'm dead oh okay i'm joining you in a brief moment well like i'm doing that you have to like
okay so this is like giant open area you have to like hide under a fucking log
well that didn't work out as planned game over game over too slow too slow it was the mountain
shrine that did us in may have been you want to be huntress and i'll be multi no you want me to be
commando i think i think double robo is not a good strat i'm willing to be commando i think we just
got screwed because we did the mountain thing we're both the slowest character and we had to fight
two of the please stand behind a rock or you'd instantly die he's the slowest character first
level death but we did do challenge mode so it was two level ones he moves the same p
he's stampede he's bigger though yeah see i'm sprinting and you're sprinting we're going the
same to going to same people on st pete oh all right hey thanks for the coin hidden free money
there's a hurt yourself up there is there for fun sure why not remember what these do oh that's a
75 percent you touched it i did yes everything's fine i'm all right accurate oh god damn it i did
shortstop it that is true all right now i need to heal damage while sprinting i was saving up for
that one let's figure out anything down go for the active what's in the active nice crit strike
there's another active right here yeah there's two anymore boxes which i don't need i marked a
crit for you there's a heal right here though i want the heal bot all right i guess we can go
ahead and fight and then search afterward something like that is there any more down this hallway
this is 34 right yeah heal fruit uh we should probably activate how you doing over there
coming back heading back start whenever let's go my accuracy is terrible what are we gonna get here
queen the ant friend queen bug oh that's a lot of you here oh god where the hell did you come from
damn down to half there's a lot of fire bugs a lot of fire i'm gonna die i'm gonna die it's been fun
damn this is going to be two in a row versus getting destroyed on the first level
jesus there's so many what the fuck why are they this many out of my way all right i'm back in the
circle it's not looking good oh god oh it hurt ow ow doesn't feel good what i can't go up those
stairs what the hell come on all right we got 99 big anna's dead all right whoo i can breathe
so we got an extra jump feather cool i forgot to use my crit the whole time
i just like it extra challenging um let's see are there any of the boxes i don't think there's
any more boxes he tried to run a shopping cart up the stairs yeah but like come on he's got legs
up top is there one up there i got uh two up this little tunnel all right we gotta get out of this
yeah hey we're doing pretty good we're just now getting to the second half of easy but yeah i'm
ready uh somebody said also well teleporter is charging the chests are red and they're easier
to see that's true that's good point they're red but we can't open them yet but we can see them
we can see them they're much easier to see on the map
hmm hurt yourself money machine yeah who wants to go first you can go first
sure there's almost no reason not to use those not really especially if you have
any way to heal yourself and we got chests i'm gonna go for the gamble here we go it worked out
no it didn't because i don't want a cube you can get two bonus items do you have an active
yes is it a cube i have the crit would you like it to be a cube no i'm happy with the crit
i think i just need to use it more i just need to actually push q oh wait i can have two right
right right right that's the point of this character's cool move exactly now you've got it
wow utility his name is multi remember that i won't all right i need to open a box
what are these little slugs coin you have uh how many coins you have uh six oh i have six too
i'll take it wow we're neck and neck do i dare do this again no what gambling no no no the
93% help i don't want that what's this i don't want that either
oh i can't believe that roll worked and what about the heel uh yeah but but if it's but it'll go on
keel down and i don't know if i quite a lot of uh stuff this way i'll claim as much as i can but
no idea where the porter is well i can gamble again you know get the fuck away from the guys
get away get away not even close to you no nothing please yeah the first dink on healthy
enemies is pretty good uh enemies hello well uh i'm gonna check down here um i see no signs
i have so much money teleporting friend is stuck in a wall all right there's some over here
hate these little fire guys we got worth no money just small annoying missile thing
uh i have like i think i have two or three of these now two huh what is this is this is this a
bleed build you have bleed i'm tempted there's a lead printer here i'm tempted by it slow enemies
have to be sprinting while that happens though bleed is bad why don't you tell the developers
or make their second game maybe they won't make the same mistake twice a lot of enemies over here
too i can take care of that like are they copying all the stats one to one like all the damage
numbers too i don't know good question but if i just get 10 bleed items and i bleed every hit
i think it's by that's percentage based or something somebody was saying i got all this
money and nothing to spend it on so are you ready to uh uh i have i'm i'm almost ready to do whatever
you'd like to do which is start because we're already like all the way up to medium
yeah we are like almost a heart this is true oh this is okay we're it's this thing yeah it's
that thing it is this thing goodbye just get like just suck them all up coming around to help
i'm almost dead though that you with the vortex that was me with the vortex
nope double jump is really good against these guys you just jump right when they shoot and
they can't hit you all right one's dead two are dead ouch god damn it fire guy fire fire fire
no no no fire bad fire very bad my god almost there jesus good all right bosses are dead
boss is dead now just the babies fuel cell an additional charge not too bad
it's good that's what the boss relic is next to you very cool what cost 67 dollars over here
why does the teleporter cost 67 bucks because they decided to start taxing it um they realized free
teleporters were bad for business and this way if you pay for your teleporter they can make more
teleporters in the future i don't think there's any more i have 800 dollars so do why but you can
take a quick look we're already almost at hard nothing that way i don't think yeah this was
pretty dry for boxes well all right whenever whenever uh it was an item okay you got the will
of the wisp yeah it was it was a box underneath hidden under the teleporter it was okay it was
like stacked on top of each other hey we've done it we've done it we did it we've unlocked the
engineer oh cool okay new character okay money money money money hypnospace what do you mean
hypnospace the engineer apparently is insane i guess uh oh do you see what i see what i see
unlimited crit run do you yeah is it possible for unlimited crit run is it worth doing it
should we take is it worth it this is if you want to ditch literally everything i mean maybe i don't
know i don't think i even have 10 items yeah i was gonna say i don't feel like i have 10
i might give up a couple yeah i'll do it like three or four times what did i give up i didn't
even see let's see what am i gonna give up here ow um i don't think the machine works
i think the machine's broken the machine is broken i don't do i not have any items
i don't think i have any items i can put in here what i apparently all your items do you have any
i don't have any white items somehow okay this is gonna be bad so group them up yeah we're like
really weak right now for some reason i got two glasses i'll go for like 30 seems good
have fun with it i hope you love it all right i need to get a box 40 is reasonable that's a lot
of games is the teleporter berserkers pauldron enter a frenzy after killing three enemies in
succession okay do we want to go ahead and pump this or we're already in very hard so we may as
well explore which one i would probably save that bad option there's not been a good loot
box rng run oh they're all here i think yeah we need to have more stuff they're not yeah i did
yes i'm gonna go get more crit i'm go this way what i have any other boxes i think this one in
here i didn't pick up the item all the stuff finally something over here okay time for more
crit and then we can start triple jump now uh it's being a crit you want to buy a crit 133 bucks
there's another there's one over here you can buy you want to buy that you can eat how much money
you have i want to buy what there's a crit for 133 dollars you can buy another crit oh right over
here it's on my marker coming to you now i will have 90 percent you could use i have to lose my
hooves so i'm now very slow and you want me to just buy this all right well i'm just gonna buy
this i have 576 yeah i just got pushed into it i was standing there and got pushed into it
what the fuck all right let's go push the thing oh bm i didn't mean to do that there was something
else up there too i don't know what it was now uh magma worm oh even sure it was easy
so stacking my crits on my crits probably doesn't do very much suck them all in still 80 percent
crits is pretty solid didn't mean to press that button but i did the key is kind of just always
because he just kind of idly chases you a lot of money holy shit that's so many things up there
that's bad oh my god there's so many of them holy shit oh god it was all going so well until it
wasn't all right we should be fine oh no sunglasses rip i didn't mean to push e where did they go
i died that was uh that was real i've kind of told i kind of killed myself
with fall damage i may have fallen to my death as is want to happen the good news is
you're almost got it i do and you need more items than i do anyway so you can just have both
he's dead he has been killed two guitars ukulele one guitar two guitar we don't have enough to do
the portal right i don't think so no so you're free to go whenever you want uh well we probably
should just go portal portal portal portal everyone's screaming portal portal use portal
get in the portal might as well check out portal okay we're going into apparently going in the
portal the bizarre between time i just fucking fell off might be able to convert some items
for something good should we try this like item conversion i don't even know how this works
yeah i don't understand how it works either that's the buckler and i don't know what that item is
10 lunar alien head all right chat wrote alien head in all caps so i'm just gonna push e
wait what'd you get how do you do it i think i think you're doing it are you doing it i think
you just did it twice i don't think i'm doing it you have to have five green items i only have
oh two three i have three green items i see so how is it white items for the green one then i guess
oh i see it's sort of green text so germa should do it germa do it don't do it okay
germa get up there do it do it don't do it don't do it don't do it do it you should do it
it's not worth it it is worth it duality all right you ready you're gonna jump in the pool
it's scary well good thing we went here but i guess it's better to look except it's not
because now we're gonna be an impossible difficulty don't do it it's op but do not do it
whatever just kill the lizard it reduces cooldowns but you don't rely on cooldowns okay
look at this bad spawn bad spawn unbelievable that doesn't interrupt them i feel like it should
why did you spawn right here this is insane mode so you have to be apparently crazy and
unexpected i love these green mushrooms growing from my shoulders so bouncy so there's a i don't
know if you want to do this is a party i don't know what a party party shrine i want to go to
a party combat shrine probably should we do it uh yeah combat shrine might as well what is it
bad guy five clock bell friends what i didn't hit that even i feel so weak even with 70 70
percent crit i'm dead that's why yeah i'm dead oh no i feel very weak fire damage killed me
there's no way i can bring it back new well i have two thousand four hundred dollars should i just
go open the chest i have almost three grand damn i missed it three thousand four thousand right
you have two double jumps i know i know i'm just not using them so where's this magic legendary
chest apparently it's in the middle of the map it's literally right next to me oh you're standing
on it 3,700 bucks i mean you might be able to buy and see what's in it in a moment or i'll die
time for you to carry me i got it okay what's in it what's in it what's in it what is it it's
it's borderlands 3 it's the ceremonial dagger oh killing an enemy releases homing daggers i've got
this at a regular chest like three times have you yeah i have never gotten that item
that's this was four grand well all right that's worth four grand that's three that was 39
of 3,700 bucks i have two of them you have two daggers right now that's what i'm saying i picked
it up like a random buck those daggers are gonna murder people all right let's find the thing let
me see if i can just kill the boss this is gonna be nightmare it's right here these belt things
are gonna be a pain in the ass i already know it here we go what we got stone titan right next to
it's it's two holy shit jesus i don't know what this is but i'm gonna grab it oh it's a heal bot
fuck trying to jump up here and he's having to keep spawning the things underneath me
all right here we go let's see if i can get some daggers here and oh no fucking way i got
melted good try well let's try the uh engineer the new character yeah see what it is the engineer
bouncing nades mines bubble shield auto turrets oh baby so it's gonna be
10 characters i guess six in the game now looks like it eight grenades three thousands of mines
so you can put down a bubble shield that's weird he's very boring but he's op very boring huh i
don't know if he's apparently i've ever said that about a person who places turrets everybody likes
placing turrets right well i want to see it well we got to try it out mine eight bounce nades
super mine there's so much to look at let's see oh this is cool what eight okay
okay so right click mine now can i activate these no okay they have to recharge very slowly as well
so then what is this one what is that that's a shield oh nice bubble shield now we're playing
edf apparently and then what's the cooldown on the other one on turret so we can shoot out but they
can't shoot in the best kind of shield uh hold left click down to shoot this seems like this
game just got 45 easier did it with i mean you can put two turrets down that seems fucking amazing
we had five community subs from rin the cutest thank you rin wow i'm liking you one shot enemies
with left click i guess you can do that as the um thank you so much for the subs multi as well
five bring them in thank you and you can just kind of spam this around huh seems like it
okay have you seen any boxes yet uh that's the drawback engineer 45 less boxes no loot
only lucky shrines in play can you throw them okay you can you can kind of toss them a little bit
nice all right well don't forget to put down your teleporter and dispenser
will do and also sell my unusual for real money is there one box on the whole level
uh there have been zero boxes i'm in favor of just restarting let's just redo it
i go to hell let's do it again because that was dumb though we also were playing around with the
move set yeah but like i didn't open well i didn't see one box you can attach mines to germa hey check
your steam man turrets also get the effects of your items that sounds insane hold on stand still
how much damage does the shield mitigate oh you all right go all right i'm gonna go
i'm going for it wait let me do that to you here oh yeah hitting airborne enemies is miserable
all right we're supposed to restart dude no don't oh my god let me die oh it bounces my own bubbles
what about from in not from inside give me some stuff active what is it slug flight
i feel like that would be okay i miss my movement ability i just do hover guy at least i never get
my feet wet flying mines why would you put it just carpet like drop all right what the
fuck is hitting me stupid elite oh fuck off those things are so good come on right into my mind
come on can you stick a mind to yourself oh no that's what's going on your minds are blowing up
it's because you're throwing up more okay that was just freaking me out i was like why what's
going on to me what's happening my character yeah i guess you can only have like 10 at a time
uh period i found the portal so they activate pretty quickly so question the things like bleed
and such stack with your turret uh area items stack with your turrets apparently mushroom is
super good i don't know which one of these to pick yes they do so i don't have a move i can
stop from her getting hurt from falling uh good question i don't think you do the turrets can
proc bleed sticky bomb everything fungus is overpowered on turrets because they just heal
infinitely that's kind of cool so as fungus what is the slug is that fungus engineer does not have
any mobility movements okay good to know sluggish heal out of combat okay okay let me look for chests
yeah i can fly with this i can't just forget i have it how much was this one this class seems fun
everybody who's saying it's boring well that's probably used to just a hater i can see that
though because you really only have one move you can really even do you can like i feel like i
only have one move with multi this card it's kind of hard to hit this too
if it's a boss probably uh you want to get it started what are you fighting over here i just
like shooting the like burst of uh of little bombs and let's activate this thing engineer is the boss
killer oh gold per bullet the crowd funder gotta get more money i'll try this there's a gun on my
gun probably that didn't work sword do it again and shields do you have an active i do i have
the money gun uh we gotta get this rolling all right we gotta go we gotta go we do have to go
where i think i found it already what the hell was it yeah it's it's like right over here i think
at least i thought i did so right i'm just gonna stop at the luck shrine or some quick gambling
anything else no all right i'm ready let's go preemptively put down turrets
how long do the turrets last for though i don't know wait how many can you put down two two
oh you missed your turrets but don't worry i got them you can stick it to people too oh that's cool
all right what does the money gun do oh ow ow it's shooting all my bullets all my money
okay where's the other guy hey repair your torch where's the other wasps isn't there where's the
other boss greater west where is it uh he's flying somewhere i guess uh okay oh
i just got air shot twice shielding the bad guy why do the bad guys have a shield i'm gonna die
because oh my god give me a break where is this boss what i don't know but we still have to do
the teleporter anyways we'll sit here no he's not what he's back here he's like blending in
with the grass okay they're dead okay okay we can proceed all right turn invisible on taking heavy
damages behind me there for you i'm gonna die where are you i just kind of flew up here to go
look for boxes i use my hover jets which i feel like is not a very good invention considering how
big they are and they can only get me one foot off the ground did i spend all my money with my
q gun i don't think i have any boxes over here this is an active how do you turn it off well
hey if you want a box i'm standing right next to one i think i found two boxes over here this money
gun is a trap i don't know if that is but it's mine the crystal yeah i don't have any money so
it's all yours um okay i just picked up something called the crowd funder yeah that's what it made
me go broke oh i have that that's the thing that sucks yeah well i don't know if it sucks but it
steals all your money so don't get it how do you turn it off once it starts using your money
yeah i toggle i toggle it off after the first time i used it apparently it didn't nothing that
didn't happen hey germa i was hoping i could be the one guy you're cute and bad in the game
i appreciate 50 percent of that comment all right where's this buck you talking about
it's like way over there i'm looking scanning there it is uh hopefully you don't kill don't
kill me don't kill me don't kill me how long is this wing's last four not that god damn all right
uh we can you just press the button and get us out of here otherwise why am i is it still on
it you definitely can't talk it off by pushing q chat it's still spending money literally as
fast as i can get it you can't turn it off i'm hitting he's just rising
you can't turn off the money gun no i think the money gun just always siphons money
i think this run is over somebody said you can turn it off i don't know what he's doing
what it's really easy you just push q chat see money gun sometimes it doesn't want to go off
though see like it glows when i shoot grab your item before i delete it thank you you left my
minds behind why did i let you have that i don't know why you didn't press it that's why i saw i
was like he's not gonna press it is he okay that was my poor teleporter the mines seem pretty
effective hello give me money 57 come on oh it's right here found it you want to try to kill it
now well there's no enemies here what are you talking about that found the teleporter it's
right here oh uh maybe spawns or anything we just try to kill it right now just kind of smoke it and
then be able to run around uh let me grab one item on the way to you okay i'm running all right
just don't push q do not push you drop it i don't think i can the queen kill it we have two shields
is better than one anybody that gets in here is gonna get mine well we are shredding bosses
well you kind of had to do that though we've run out of time all right we got boxes few boxes
maybe wait are you supposed to be able to charge your uh gun while sprinting that seems like
maybe something you're not supposed to be able to do i don't know but you total fyi you can left
click then sprint but the game doesn't want you to know that okay i've got a kiosk over here
just looking around okay see item that way this way you kind of just stand here huh we do have
to literally just stand here did i pick up that item what is this did you get yours already
yeah i got mine it's just the invisible thing again all right we're good all right there's
something over here why am i doing that i don't know this one attack speed that's kind of good
come on down there two down here beautiful slow enemies no one they really stuffed them back here
huh all right how you doing uh i found a couple chests nothing that's gonna make the run i see
one i can't even get to up there i'll get that one all right pray for me what are you gonna do
this three oh you can fly one liftoff uh what the hell is this don't go outside it's a lunar it
needs a coin needs a lunar coin all right let's get out of here that is dumb quick quick dude hurry
up you gotta tap as fast you can jump down this hole weirdly enough i didn't take any damage why
this is the slowest character in the game so far are you ready for me to press this
yeah so how did i not take any damage may as well have used my money gun there's a chest
all right find it there i feel like mines that are underpowered find it come on lag what's going
on with that lag some of these annoying things is hanging out here well turrets are pretty awesome
they really are this view oh a kiosk what do we got oh we got oh we got uh this one uh found the
thing we're looking for i don't teleport you know mines are good up people stand on boss fights
because you can just slap them on there and it's pretty much as impossible to miss
true there's extra damage 266 this character is kind of fucking insane yeah it seems that way
uh it's right here oh nice another equipment charge for my money gun that i do not want
sticky bombs all right how you doing uh started hanging out looking at the meter about to switch
to very hard in a moment yeah that's what i was thinking attack speed again cool i feel like the
teleporter is always in that same spot on this level it's always like kind of back here isn't it
you ready yeah i think i'm already come to me one second it's 260 i'm pretty much here all right
you want to you got what do you cooldowns look like uh everything is refreshed and ready to go
all right here we go it is the imp overlord where are you there you are turrets are getting
beasted on now yes they are fly away maybe not let me just stay in here there's a fucking cow
in here with me all right i gotta get the fuck out of there well we're doing a lot of uh oh
she's not happy oh man i'm dead she's not happy with my turret spot god damn it just couldn't
really get out of it yeah he teleported on top of me oh dear yeah he that's what he did to me
money gun money money money money nothing bad can happen in here right oh boy you're in trouble
turtle inside the crate the classic strategy well i spent all my money but you know what
i forgot that it happens when i left click money gun is the worst on this because you have to charge
up hide this is surprisingly functional and i got some money back super jump
okay all right you've had your fun i just need this one chest risk of turtling
sometimes hey you gotta do what you gotta do i am playing we are playing the engineer
yeah it's not like we're playing um the gunslinger oh sorry all right let's get out of here slowly
this is level three this is uh i think so so advancing before insane i think is pretty decent
fairly lukewarm fairly lukewarm fairly like lukewarm into average somebody said read this
comment you got it no no i did and there's a super chest here no i did there's a there's a
super chest 3300 bucks keep in mind all right it wasn't worth the last time it didn't seem like it
would it be worth it this time hey new active i'm just gonna stand here until i get 200 bucks to
switch it over which may never happen do i need how much uh the that that first chest has fungus
and apparently we can just have infinite fungus and have our turrets never die
that is what i have heard that is currently what chat just simply can't stop talking about it
so so excited so fungus you will you want me to 3d print all my stuff how much fungus should i get
i'll take the fungus i'll take the fungus i'll take the fungus all right who the
fuck is doing this to me let me alone exclamation fungus get like five you done
uh i'm getting like i'm getting like how much do i have five i'll get i'll get seven i'm waiting
for my turn at the fungus uh machine all right i'm done are you sure have fun stay away from my
fungus no no what do you know yeah i thought you guys didn't everyone just say get like between five
to ten you mean like five too much back up did i pick it up did i take yours no this is my fungus
all right have fun with your fungus seven is not too much okay well just get a fruit we gotta do
the meme build i mean we just have to stand in one spot and have our turrets do everything it's a
self-fulfilling prophecy everyone's like this is the most boring clash it's because when i find the
fungus machine oh my god okay everything for ultimate fungus build that's a huge huge area
and if we have four of these and we can stand still all right i have nine fungus you have nine
i got seven so if we stack our turrets one on top of the other okay um what the fuck is killing me
right now did you pick this up what is this what what is what is going on with the fire damage in
this game i don't know it's kind of crazy just put down a turret all right let's go find the thing
and then just stand on top of our turrets just stand let's create an aura of healing turrets
it's over here where it's over there oh what happens if you go all the way up here
oh how do you get down it's a good question what's in here okay we've got if i jump from
this height am i going to be dead be careful this seems dangerous i don't i can't i don't
know what's happening but this seems really really really powerful i think we found the
build that we're both going to have to uh beat the game with all right where's that mask
wow the aoe is gigantic after killing three where's the uh teleport going to a friend
teleport is very fine oh let's activate it all right let's ready put down your shit make sure
we make sure you put them in the same spot so we can all get like we can stack on us
it's the magma worm dude this is i am i playing overwatch that's what i feel like i feel like
this is eight you are now so who said we'd be unkillable because one of my friends is already
dead you liars stand well you have to stand still too right do i stand still i think i'm invincible
i think we all stand still oh my god okay no no wait wait that's probably not a good idea is it
a good idea we should stand still stand still right next to each other um i don't know if i
like this it feels a little terrifying yeah i'm taking a lot of damage uh yeah oh my god we didn't
plan this we didn't plan this good enough we had we should have stuck on top of each other okay
i'm here here's a shield i'm gonna stand still now here's my turret okay good yeah magma worm
probably is not what was intended this is overwatch with mods this is just remember when
they used to do the arcade mode yeah well that sucks oh you've got to be kidding me
what just fucking happened right there i'm flying you are you serious right now what was i got
another turd in we have four turrets now i hope that they can do good deep so why is fire damage
like times 500 times damage you're dead no i'm almost dead i'm coming back into the heels the
delicious heels i'm healed i gotta hold still it's bug if any one of us panics and like runs away
it's like we're breaking the herd immunity oh the devs know it's broken oh fire is actually broken
like it's a broken mechanic oh like it's actually like actually like they're patching it because
it's broken okay well that makes sense i was gonna say what the fuck you like see look at that
are you dead you did yeah you just you just healed through like dying how are you dead
because he launched me across the whole game and i died to fire damage i didn't realize i was alone
in this he knocked me in the air and put a dot on me and it was doing like 200 damage a tick
and then i died from the fall all the turrets are getting healed too oh that was bad that was a nasty
one you did it did i hey i did it now where's that legendary chest uh how much money do you have
slow enemies on hit that's probably good uh 3043 that's not enough i think it's 37 what was the
required amount i think it was 37 was 34 80 all right i'm just gonna pick up like this one thing
and then come back you need 300 more i believe these are green feathers a jump right
this game's fucking bonkers always go with the random item could be anything all right
is that all there is for me to get uh well yeah i think so unless you want to do the challenge
mode right there that's okay surprisingly little to pay for over this way turrets are still having
a good old time so wait if i die my turrets just stay there uh yes that's strange they do indeed
all right well ready to fight another day so i feel like that strategy will work on every other boss
now if unless they can one chunk you yeah if they can hit like kill you in one that's 120 120
that's 120 times six so that's how much help is strong enough to actually kill things quickly
yeah let's uh clean up quickly did you just eat those is he eating these
excuse me i would like to ask a question is there a reason why he i can't hit this guy
what what are you eating that was weird that was strange he was just inhaling them let's go
over here minimum arming distance probably something like that something weird they're not killing
them fast enough oh i got a slug too and even more attack speed so this is back to level one
right i believe so the level one loop wow that hurt oh it's a fire guy wow i got super slow on
him let's get away from me you can only i can only do oh this is there's a boss up here it's
like one of those boss characters all right any sign of the uh thing uh not yet yeah that's like
there's four or five of those oh my i mean it's not a boss but it's one of the boss those boss
characters and you fight five of them at the same time right what if i turn this on and didn't even
tell them what are you doing i'm not going to do that this is our first like actual reel we might
actually beat the loop maybe i'll uh come down to you because we don't want to get to haha level
when we do this probably this like feels like i shouldn't be doing this but i it's just so
counterproductive to move it's counterproductive strange it feels so weird that's how i feel every
day chest nice oh any sign of it uh i don't think so oh yeah here it is ready no no way we let we
need to we need to like get this situated we need to be ready we have to be in the same spot i only
have one turret available okay here's one two i'm standing here and i have five seconds for the next
okay are you ready to stand still three becomes my last one here we go we have to activate this
before we get to ha ha ha okay so it's just this thing just stand still and spam am i hitting them
my own what the fuck why what was that was that his i don't know what was just happening i only had
one portal down now you've got a no but why was it bouncing what a what a pro strat this is oh and
then you fly as long as you don't fly too far here he comes he's gonna step on us now oh that
hurts i'm so scared i feel like i should need to move i'm on top of them one down one to go
we're not even in ha ha ha land yet this is fucking the rancho relax strategy
this really is like the meme build
um where is he over there where's the other actual i can't see there's too many fucking
rhinos too much green goo there's too many winstons on our team i don't know where we are
it works until it doesn't is this trap yeah that's true any where is the actual bus we got to 99
charge i'm gonna move i know that's not allowed really you are moving okay fine let's go let's
find him uh is that him over there yeah it's him all the way down there all right move we're
gonna pick up shop we're gonna do the same thing over here uh oh uh oh gotta get some heal babies
down oh we're separated um we should be okay your shield is deflecting all my attacks all right i'm
moving up moving it why to you because i was behind you plus we heal each other we did it we
did it now all right pick up the pieces now just maybe a few more items we just got to ha ha ha
difficulty we did all right there's a ukulele here for you oh yeah i'll get that on the way
out boxes all right we're in ha ha ha we this is we have one more after this right i think so
so the ideology here is to get to the portal as fast as possible and do our impenetrable fort
yeah before it gets too far down the ha ha ha tree i don't i don't see any loot so i'm just
gonna come to the thing by the teleporter yeah let's just get the hell out of here we'll level
up a few times let me grab my boss gear it's right here and let's get the hell out of here
oh right that way i got some good max hp all right tactic go find as fast as possible
find the teleporter and then set up shop and let's get out of this let's do it good tactic
i like being up here and we can see down i don't see any particles what's hurting me what's hurting
me what is hurting oh did i go out of bounds you can go out of bounds in this game yes watch for
the red rope all the way around the edge keep gotta keep looking here so far i got nothing
it's over here it's being blocked by a titan no my god are you gonna be okay i don't know
what is that rp talk like i don't know i just don't know what's that oh um oh i think uh this
thing yep slug okay it's right up here all right are you ready sorry i got the correct
hall's goat hoof for move faster i don't know why you would need anything that useless oh god
we gotta get over to that thing where is it it's over here oh fuck we gotta do the strategy
we're useless without the strategy oh yeah definitely ready i'm on it i don't know where
you are come to me ping oh i got it pink okay you know where we are close yeah i'm just gonna
i'm starting strategy a oh god i'm like left behind in the zombie apocalypse i'm coming
this is oh my god i need you i'm here i need you i need your other heel all right i'm gonna stand
still oh jesus they've breached all right press the button one of the engineer turrets is dead
oh my god it's too spiky damage is too spiky hold on have faith hold i bought us some time with with
my uh oh it's totally dead well we did hold the line we will definitely get some kind of metal
for that i think god damn it why uh it works until it didn't that was so long uh what time is it
11 seven hours oh yeah that's so unfortunate not much else we can unlock except you'd have
to get the 10 points which would probably take like a few hours obliterate yourself at the obelisk
is that the like you beat all the things guy i think that you that's when we beat that i think
we go to the obelisk i don't even know what killed us what even did that much damage that was just a
it was like it was just an explosion yeah seven stage is the portal option for obliteration that
unlocks a character that's cool there's three greater wisps shooting at the same time a beetle
queen bomb oh well that was fun yeah that was fun for something in early access that just came
at early access randomly for just there it is uh that was good yep and there's still two more
characters and i guess four more to be added and i'm going to 20 bucks fairly reasonable as well
i would obviously we'll probably see much more content yeah added in the coming months yeah it's
good stuff no that was cool it's really smooth the only complaint really i had was the like the fire
damage but that's apparently a bug so yeah the uh it's just really addictive getting like a super
build yeah that's fun and the co-op seems smooth i think we can disband the squad what happens if i
do this i'm still in the squad oh you're still in the squad you're never going to leave the squad
i'm i'll always be in the squad rip squad but uh anyways that there was risk of rain two co-op
that was italics go say hello go get him a follow oh if you haven't already i was like where is he
uh you're here yeah we're at i'm sorry to say this but we're disbanding the squad yeah we're
gonna um cut the house in two and draw just a big line down the middle the squad but yeah thanks
for playing after the microwave gets caught then it's always a pleasure mr italics end of squad
and i will see you to alex in like 30 minutes or so uh when we both like eat snacks downstairs
all right well thanks for having me guys i've been told i've been very loud i'm sorry that's not my
fault i turned you down i've been told i'm turned down very quiet not my fault i did i hold on but
if i could do it over again i would be even louder i tried i turned him down he was i got confirmation
that you were fine that would be at least twice as loud what if i had the choice i i we talked
about it like two hours three hours ago and they were like turned down a little i turned you down
good night guys see you next time so wait was he really loud that whole time because it on my end
it looks like he was fine the first couple hours oh he was fine oh they just you just fucking around
okay i know for the first couple hours i think he was a little loud but i uh i turned him down
halfway through all right come on man you guys are making me feel crazy but that's it
i let me get this off the screen here i will see you guys tomorrow for the sakiro scratch off if
you don't know what that is tomorrow i'm going to be scratching 221 dollars worth of scratch tickets
for every every dollar every death in sakiro it's going to be just to hang out just stream any scent
that is made through that i've picked the charity i'm going to be using that i'm going to be donating
now the charity is going to be the nevada humane society very highly rated charity and regardless
of how much money is made on that stream at least 221 dollars is going to go to the nevada humane
society because if i get zero dollars on these tickets that don't matter if it's 50 grand
beautiful and then after that to keep in line with the gambling thing uh i'm gonna make sure
that it works it should somebody made a germa slots game that is a full game that has a bunch
of mini games in it it's like a full experience and we're gonna play it should be an interesting
day and that'll be starting around the normal time of three to four p.m. thanks for joining
tonight a chill stream where we just kind of play it's fun sometimes just to kind of turn the brain
off and enjoy a game with your friend and with that we can go ahead and go like this pull up the
vets thank you for joining me again see you tomorrow i can't wait to see him win a million
dollars that would be insane it was the max possible win on a five dollar ticket i really
don't know i really don't know i know that the more but the higher the denomination is let's
say if it's a 20 ticket you get that the chance to win is much higher but i really have no idea
what the maximum is i don't know oh let's be right back that's incorrect hey there we go the ticket
will say the max price on it yeah it should it should but uh it won it won we thanks to the five
dollars hey jeremy hope you recovered from the fart and screaming noises wanted to keep you updated
on the vinyl i'm getting the songs back from the mastering engineers this weekend and the
artwork has been sent to the pressing plant jeremy on vinyl will be a thing soon oh my goodness
that's so fancy that's crazy that's i look forward to see what that entails jeremy on vinyl thank you
though it won the yellowist thanks for the 350 i was gifted a community sub during monster rancher
and just didn't want to be a complete bum go blow this on the slots you're not a bum if you
participate in this community then you participate in this community and you're great don't worry
about giving me money thanks for the 350 though lazy luke thanks for the 250 what's going on lazy
luke hope you're doing well uh five dollars from frodean weapon thank you frodean hey jerma thanks
for streaming on my birthday let's get happy birthday again frodean hope you had a good one
uh none of my friends are around to party tonight so this is a good way to celebrate on my own
can't wait to see what crazy ideas of yours come to fruition as we approach the summer months
hope you and chad have a good night much love happy birthday frodean a very valued member of
the community been around for a long time happy birthday and yes the summer months will bring
hopefully some very interesting streams we will see uh adventure dan adventure mf dan thanks
to the five dolls hey jerma i'm visiting vegas next weekend any cool things i should do keep
on rocking uh it depends on what you like to do because vegas has anything you want anything you
desire is here it's just here concerts casinos some of the best restaurants in the country
it's got anything arcades bars clubs the best thing you can if you okay if you've never been
to vegas before the best first thing to do is just to kind of walk around and just take a look
walk the strip or at least part of it because it's about two hour walk to do the whole thing
there's a lot of interesting things to see there's the fountain at the belagio that has
to the down the dancing fountain to music it really depends on what you want to do there's
so much to see that's hard to recommend you could open up like ticket master right now
and just see the dozens of shows and concerts that are going on this week i heard you can gamble
there you can it is you can do it but hope you have fun hope you have a blast there's no shortage
of things to do here you'll find something but thank you for the five dollars i also want to
say thank you to the tomato rated with like a thousand people earlier thanks so much tomato
everyone that came in from tomato stream thanks for coming out thanks for sticking around
wish me luck on this quiz good luck on your quiz on monday you're gonna do just you're gonna do
great solharv solharv thank you for the two dollars and 50 cents hey germa an actor from
the quiet man left the following comment on the second germa video what okay i'm the actor that
plays the birdman and father and i had a laugh and a chuckle with one snort over this nice job
that's so funny what that's a it's about a good sport right acting well i don't think was the
a major problem just the game was just all over the place that's so funny what a good sport
they really commented that's that's cool i think that's cool but thank you so hard for the two
dollars and 50 cents the guy that plays the father hey creepy teeth thanks for five bucks thank you
for streaming today thank you for watching today welcome smelly boy thanks for the 250
seeing you seeing as you are a gamer how much do you identify with the joker also doing work
impression what's with the orc impression how much do i identify with the joker i don't really
identify with the joker i think i'm more of a riddler if you ask me uh do an orc impression
job's done that's a peasant peon right forget it uh thanks for the 250 freudian weapon 250 happy
birthday again you know i honestly couldn't think of a better way to spend my birthday and having
some drinks and watching my favorite streamer i say it all the time but thanks for being such
an inspiration you in this community have the uncanny ability of cheering me up when i feel
the most absolute like absolute garbage garbage i read that wrong and you got me back into making
art awesome so for that i thank you if i can inspire anybody to do anything that's fucking
incredible thank you i'm honored and glad that you are getting back into doing something that
you'd like to do thank you for being part of this community thank you for the two dollars and 50
cents that's awesome i'm glad you're doing it keep doing it thank you so much freudian weapon
and again happy birthday pika banana thanks for the five dollars fun stream today can't wait for
the scratchers for charity tomorrow should be interesting i'm looking forward to it juno
upsetto thanks for the 250 someone in the discord wants to know how to solve this what is this uh
how do you solve that i don't this i gotta work backwards i i can't i how am i gonna do that
without working backwards is it not solved how do i solve this six one two three four five six seven
two i mean you obviously i think you obviously you got something going on here in the middle
that 14 space four that should be connecting shouldn't it or not solve it for him i can't
you can actually look up the game guide but thank you guys here come the credits i'll see you guys
tomorrow for an irl stream into a slot machine stream it's a gambling day tomorrow but it's
not i mean it's like it is but it isn't gambling streamer do i have does that mean i have to go
into the category on stream the gambling casino category uh do i i think i do this be irl opening
loot boxes the name of that title of that stream should be germa bare minimum loses 442 dollars
put it in the secure category that's fucking hilarious uh but here come the credits thank
you to all the subs see if you can see your name it's gonna be blown by here in a second
put it under dwarf fortress why would i put it in dwarf fortress don't you still need to pay
income tax on lotto winnings no i don't think so because i was talking about this uh with a
few people casino winnings are just taxed i don't think they count as income so let's okay if i
win a million dollars on a scratch ticket i believe a portion of that like 20 to 30 percent of that
is just taxed i don't think it counts as income on my like tax return is a lottery ticket income
are gambling winnings income gambling winnings are fully taxable and you must report the income
on your tax return gambling income includes but is not limited to winning some lotteries raffles
casinos includes cash winnings income is it how do gambling winnings affect if your winnings
are reported on a form w2g federal taxes are withheld at a flat rate of 25 percent
okay but does that mean we'll fucking figure it out i'm pretty certain that if i win a million
dollars on a ticket tomorrow 250 000 is goes to the irs and then that's just it that's i
believe that's correct i don't think that affects my actual like income for 2019 and then okay so
that's gonna be strange so okay if i take in let's say it does affect income so if i win a million
dollars on a scratch ticket and it affects income okay you know so you made you made a million
dollars in 2019 and you donated 750 000 to charity i'm gonna have to like i'm fairly certain that's
not how it works donations are deductible so what i had like i had 750 000 dollars in expenses in
2019 just mail them the ticket they'll deal with it win the money then go to h&r block on stream
and say what do i do by the way this is assuming that i'm going to win a million dollars on this
what like a gambling fallacy i'll be lucky if i win like 100 bucks tomorrow but there's a
possibility that i could win like 50 grand and then 50 grand that goes right to the nevada
humane society what if you win one dollar it gets rounded up to 221 double or nothing after
tomorrow's stream i know people are already going to be saying that i'm not going to do
a like scratching for sakiro deaths and then whatever is won for charity
and win nine dollars and send nine dollars i mean like it's we're doing like a whole event here for
this like i'm gonna do at least 200 i'm gonna give at least 221 dollars don't even worry i'm
look i am going i'm gonna hit like a thousand dollars tomorrow just watch i'm gonna hit like
fucking two or three grand on these tickets tomorrow but anyways i got one more bit to do
we got one more that uh trickled in here and it was who was it it was something or other thanks
to the 250 it's a terrible day for rain remember to bring your umbrella i never have an umbrella
i just run wherever i need to go outside in the rain i just run as fast as i can same yeah a lot
of people do that and then at the very end snooze and copter thanks for 250 no wait garfield the
monday killer just came in but thank you snooze and copter since we're in such a humble mood
right now i really appreciate this community too i've been a fan for a long time and i watched
the streams from the very beginning but i've only really been really involved in the community for
like two years getting in touch with the nicest people now holy mack was so kind to commission
me to draw a few thumbnails for second germa like the lethal league one yeah i did that
and i'm really happy i can give something back like that yeah it's amazing what people do in
this community it's amazing that people can all be collectively in the same place think the same
things are interesting and make a bunch of great shit it's awesome but thank you snoozing copter
for the 250 and your contributions to the community you know i did that somebody did and then finally
garfield the monday killer for 250 this is in all caps for some reason i don't know why you're
screaming at me garfield's coming in here at the last second to say hey it's fat albert and garf's
gonna sing a song for you and derma's gonna tell you a thing or two hey germa the llama have you
ever been to bedrock usa it's a creepy ghost town model after the flintstones it's honestly eerie
since there's weird mannequins and cavemen costumes it's weird i got a ride called garfield's
nightmare my nightmare is the bit cap being increased careful garfield i might make it five
dollars i'm not gonna do i'm not doing that kidding i'm kidding i'm just not it's not gonna
happen but thank you garfield i don't i've never heard of bedrock usa seems like a fucked up place
and that is my time tonight see you tomorrow i have a fantastic rest of your evening and get
tucked in tonight in bed and get like cuddled into the blankets it's gonna be cold out there
see you tomorrow for sakira scratch off in germa slots have a great night no i'm not gonna run ads
good night i will do stream legends though that is you know you got me there that's true here's
your stream legends loot that was risk of rain 2 for early access that seems like there's a lot
to do it's pretty good pretty fun here's your loot for stream legends see you guys tomorrow
goodbye okay all right all right all right all right all right all right i did promise that i
would do it here you go here's your ad see you tomorrow