All right, I had to make a lemonade. I was really into a lemonade.
Let's come back here. Hello. How are you? Let me go this way.
Should be able to. Maybe not quite yet.
Hmm. Uh-oh. I can't get this to show up.
Hmm. Uh-oh.
Hold on. There we go. All right, cool. It's called the invisible hand.
It's a game where you sell buy and trade stocks. Fake stocks.
Nothing that you hear from now going forward is financial advice.
Nothing you hear me say until the stream ends is me telling you what to buy, what to sell.
Not at all. This is not financial advice.
None of ev- This is all made up bullshit. Okay, here we go. Remember we're 12.
Shortage of- Okay, I told you this would happen.
Shortage of wa- Wait, I'm already going? Don't even think about trying to bail. It's too late.
Shortage of water. Emergency taxation to save the unit dollar. What?
We're gonna ride this one out. Don't worry about it.
Should I buy? Why aren't you saying anything? Why are people screaming in the background?
Shortage of manpower. Wait, what? Oil gas down. Logging is up.
Don't pay attention to them. Pay attention to me. This is what you paid me for.
Have you dumped that mining position? Don't do it.
Liquidate everything. Wait, don't do it. Everybody shut the fuck up. I'm on the phone.
Don't panic. Just a lot of things happening at once.
Wait, it's turning around. I think it's turning around.
Hello? Is your terminal busted? Ours is spewing a ton of crazy shit,
but I have no idea if any of it's real. Buy? What am I buying?
Green groceries. Okay, I'm gonna buy short for- I don't even know what I'm looking at.
Daily ch- Liquidate everything now. Buy back 100%. Anyways, call me back if you hear anything from
it. Who has steel? Oh no, I'm not gonna- I'm not gonna answer the phone call from the Bogdanoff,
so you outta your fucking mind. Okay, buy back everything. The system is down.
Materials. Materials. Materials. Lobby. Congress? I don't- What do I have?
Is this like just the intro, right? Jake, let me ask him. Do you trust me?
Is everyone kind of counting? Dead? Did a bomb go off? I can't hear anything.
Oh, okay, this is- Oh, he bought? Downbeat.
Faireos. Okay, coffee, $4.90. As the screen behind me implies, welcome to Faireos.
You may have been surprised to hear from us following the recent crash, but I'm pleased to
confidently disclose that the bailout has come through. Needless to say, everybody involved in
that crisis has been held suitably responsible. They now work for our inferior competitors.
Because of this, we have an entry-level analyst position available. We've also had some complaints
in the past, so this is now a paid internship. Ordinarily, we wouldn't consider someone without
a traditional finance background, but you are recommended by an employee we consider trustworthy.
And they consider you trustworthy. As you know, trust is risk. Please act accordingly.
Before we proceed, the Trade and Investment Commission requires Faireos to subject all
potential hires to a questionnaire. Common sense implies that you know what the correct
answers to these questions are. Please input them as quickly as possible so we can move past this.
I doubt, with all sincerity, that anybody who takes longer than a few minutes to complete this
test is in any way suited to employment at this firm, okay? I know a lot about stocks.
I know about fucking selling. I know about buying. I know about calls. I know about puts.
I know about shorts. I know about longs. I could get every one of these questions right.
I know what the 10-year yield is. You don't? I do. Nobody else does but me. Additionally,
our public relations team has suggested that we volunteer to submit to an enhanced pass score
of 100% out of 80. More ethical. We've agreed on your behalf. The timer will begin as soon as
you press the begin test button. Okay, here we go. What is a covered call? Well, question one.
You are approached by a high net worth individual with a substantial capital gain
who explicitly states the desire to exempt it from all taxation in all jurisdictions.
Do you? Open the account and assure the client that your firm will be able to complete this
request. Open the account but inform the client that your firm will not be able to exempt them
from taxation unless they are willing to pay specialized fees directly to the firm and you.
Reject the account and report the stated intent of the client of the Trade and Investment
Commission. So he wants me to hide taxes? Capital gains taxes. Well, how many fees?
How would we even do this, by the way? To drop this person's capital gains, we'd have to lose
a bunch of money. If this person had a substantial capital gain for the year,
we'd have to lose a substantial amount of their fucking money. I mean, if that's what they want,
you're gonna pay a fee to me for me to like just buy a bunch of bullshit and lose it?
That's what you want? I failed the test. You're a fucking idiot. First question.
Hey, take this regulatory test. Do you want to do anything illegal? Yes. Okay, fucking leave.
All right, reject the account. Reject the account. A colleague invites you to join an insider trading
scheme involving a computer network in which investment profiles, professionals illegally
exchange privileged information. Do you accept the invitation to make full use of the network
to personally enrich yourself and your firm? Accept the invitation as a gesture of goodwill,
but do not make use of the network yourself or reject the invitation and immediately inform
the Trade and Investment Commission of this network. No, I'm gonna get fucking fired.
No, this is a question. This is an ethics question. A rumor about something like this ghost
network started years ago. TIC, probably, whatever. You are asked to invest on behalf
of your firm in an offshore company with self-evident connections to organized crime,
rogue states, and are individuals banned from securities trading? Do you? No, we're gonna
reject. We're gonna just hit the ones that are already selected. Yeah, okay. The Trade and
Investment Commission. Yeah, I know, but like it's fun to read. Yeah, all right, we're gonna do
everything legally. You apply for employment at a firm which expresses contempt for the regulations
and practices of the Trade and Investment Commission during the year. We perceive the
interview reporting any illegal activity. You discover that your firm has secretly been using
technology that enables a decisive advantage in trading efficiency. We utilize the technology
specified carefully, minding the boundaries of the current regulatory framework. You're eating at
your favorite restaurant when a local student appears and asks you to explain and define the
concept of fiduciary duty. You tell the student that it means responsibility for the interests
of your client within the legal requirements and your personal professional code of ethics,
except for where the admission code of ethics conflicts with legal requirements, in which case
those requirements must be fastedly preferred. Don't use criminal information. Wait. Formal
obligation for the Trade Commission. Don't take that money. If you've registered discrimination
on the basis of race, religion, disability, gender, sexual orientation, or another marriage
or relationship supervisor, refuse to undertake the illegal trading activity. I passed it. MNM is
scared to rap battle. Your company has submitted to the Trade and Investment Commission that they
have a values-based culture focused on the following. Accountability, customer-focused
diversity. How does this culture align with your deeply held personal beliefs and understand our
historical workplace practices? Please answer in a hundred words or less. That's a redditor joke.
You guys are pretty split on that one. You guys are pretty split on that one. Your company has
submitted to the Trade Commission their ideal employee supports innovation with a salary in
the top one percent of earners. What amount of cash would you pledge to a crowdfunding campaign?
Okay. So wait, if I had a hundred thousand, a hundred, a hundred grand for like a second
campaign, your ideal employee values community after depositing an annual bonus of $500,000,
what amount of cash would you distribute to a homeless individual who requested $10 as you
exited the bank? Well, you can't, I would not be able to give like a hundred thousand plus dollars
to somebody like in cash. They would be walking around. They would be like a target. I'm not going
to do that. Zero. Get out of here. I, maybe 500, 500. And then like, I don't know, finally get,
be like, Hey, how much would it take for you to like be in a hotel for like three weeks?
Maybe $500 cash. And then I put you up in a hotel for like a month, right? Like, yeah, right. What
do you mean? Yeah, right. Your company, Farias, has submitted to the trading mission that their
ideal employee believes in integrity. That's your primary motivation for wanting to help people
through working in the financial service industry. Um, it's my motivation. That's probably what I've
been wanting. That's, that's, that's pretty accurate. You're playing a stock market simulation
video game entitled the invisible hand with a range of difficulty options. What mode of difficulty
would you prefer? I want to play the game with story featuring the inability to be fired. Oh,
regular the way that they wanted it to be played. Congratulations. Your ability to correctly answer
these questions with little hesitation implies your clear understanding of their value. You'll
excuse me. I have another meeting. This exam is the only phase of our recruitment process in
which a company supervisor is legally required. The remainder of our procedure involves several
days of take-home work that you'll need to complete within 72 hours. I will email it to you shortly.
Unfortunately, we're not able to offer compensation for this take-home work.
So already making a substantial investment by reviewing your submission of it and someone
with a newly renewed sense of ethics. I'm sure you can agree. And anything else would be deeply
unfair to us. If selected for the position, you will receive an offer of employment in writing.
Barrios will only communicate with successful applicants. It was so wonderful to meet you with,
it was so wonderful to meet with you today. I really enjoyed it. Do not contact me with inquiries
regarding the status of your application. Buy, buy, buy, buy, buy. Only buy, never sell. Is that
what you want me to do? Use your keyboard to move around. Okay. You guys can't even hear anything.
That's better. Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye. Meet in main lobby. Attendance is mandatory. Did I get the job?
Nice to meet you. I'm Morgan Lee. Seems like only one of us is going to end up with this job.
I tried to look you up on business link and a few other alumni networks, but I couldn't find
anything. That means you're either a big problem or no problem at all. Interesting.
Oh, look at all those stock tickers. Plastics are down. What are you?
What happened? What happened? We get down? There's a fire in the building.
10 o'clock. Meet in the main lobby. All right. What's that? Attack on Titan. I love that city.
It's just like an image. I love it. Do I have my own computer? What are you doing? What?
It's 10 a.m. Join us. Oh, shit. Sorry. Well, I've been here. Good morning to both of you. Welcome
to Furious and your first day as a probationary analyst. Looking for the right person to fill
this role. One of you is the wrong person. Either of you figured it out ahead of schedule. Fear
free to let me know. Otherwise, we'll let the results speak for themselves. Follow me.
This is intimidating. Even resources put the personal garbage you sent over into these boxes.
Like if I'm like if I like buy like a stock in my bed on my phone, you know what I mean?
And I just lose money on it. I don't care. Okay, whatever. But like if I have people to look
off my shoulder and see what I'm doing so we can grab, rotate, and throw. If it was up to me,
none of you would be allowed to have this kind of clutter on your desk in the first place. Somebody
must have threatened a lawsuit. Organize at least. This place is a business place of business.
Does it really strike you as an appropriate time to go rifling through your pathetic box
of imaginary memories? I think I just got in trouble for doing that.
Somebody answer that phone. Because a ringing phone has to be answered, doesn't it?
All right, somebody pick up that phone. I fucking hate it. It's freaking me out.
Where's my desk? Wait, is this my desk? I said I don't start working. Oh, it's not that phone.
Wrong phone. Okay, green grocers is up. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Hello? Hey, how's your first
day going, pal? Don't pitch to me if Corbin scares the shit out of you. You wanted in, I got you in.
Who did they put you up against for your probation? Morgan Lee. Fuck. I was worried they
would do that. I'm not going to lie to you. You got basically no chance of beating her. She went
to all the right schools, took all the right classes. Unfortunately, she's too squeaky clean
to know all the right people like me. Where does this music come from? This is just the
Undertale bar music. I also don't appreciate them pissing on my recommendation by setting you up
to get fucked like this. I want to let you in on something. I have my guy give you access to Geist.
You should see it on there now. All right, GeistNet is a closed network made up of information
brokers and anonymous insiders. You don't know who they are. You don't need to know who they are.
They get taken care of. You're going to see information on Geist that goes against what you
see on trade feed, what you watch on in, what you hear from your friends and your family,
everything basically. Remember, what you see on Geist is the smart money. Not only is it the truth,
but we know it is before anyone else does. This is porn music. There's nothing wrong with the
information everybody gets on trade feed. And you'll need all of it as things pick up,
but Geist will always be the ace up your sleeve. All of it over the next few days, for example,
and you should be able to take down Lee easily. Nobody will ever tell her about it and she
wouldn't use it even if they did. Worry about getting dirty looks at the kombucha enema clinic.
You're scared of the money police, whatever. Not our problem.
Plus people at Ferrios know about Geist, but only a few people at Ferrios know about Geist.
Don't treat it like a topic of casual conversation. You'll be fine.
I brought you here because you didn't buckle under pressure at the old place.
And you weren't directly involved, but you could have talked. You didn't. That said,
if you don't want to be a part of this, you can walk away right now. But the moment you buy
dark roast coffee, when everybody else on that floor is selling it, that's the moment I'll know
where you stand. Really. And from there, my friend, the sky's the limit. I'll see you tonight.
Drinks are on me. Okay? Dark roast coffee secretly secures exclusivity contract with
Balcador's supplier. As scheduled for announcement later today, dark roast coffee has struck a deal
with a major farming concern in the Democratic Republic of Balcador to provide exclusive access
to future coffee bean harvests. The industry may take an overall hit, which is why most people are
selling, but insiders have been assured that shares will rise sharply once the news is made
public at 16 o'clock. Details about coffee are shown here. Companies that supply coffee will profit
from the price surge. Click on dark roast to continue. Use the buy button to buy some shares.
Use the arrow buttons to change the quantity of the money to spend.
Oh, I'm just buying. How much money do I have? Not enough cash. I'll take a fucking hundred
thousand. Details about your position are shown here. Keep an eye on the benefit slash deficit
and liquidate when it's highest. 670 right now. It's not even 16 o'clock.
Buy more of this. All right. What time is it? What time is it? What do we got for time?
16 o'clock. They're going to announce it. Wait, should I sell now and buy back in again?
All right. I'm going to sell. I'm going to liquidate everything and I'm going to buy back again when it
drops. I still have like three hours for this to happen. Sell everything right now. Sell everything.
Oh, wait, what? Oh, shows everything and it shows you a position in a single place.
Take a break. Get some coffee. The machine is in the back room. Use down key to lead the desk.
So as you know, I've received dividends when you're experienced enough. Okay, cool. All right. So
what's up? We got one more. One more, sir. Look at this going up. The announcement said 16. I bought
on the dip right there. Yeah. Look at this dip. Okay. All right. Hey, everyone's selling. Everyone's
selling. It's going to surge up to probably like at least 10%. I got plus 120,000 in revenue right
now. Here it comes. That's a huge volume. You have 13.7 dollars. Yeah. Well, in a minute, this is
going to skyrocket. I'm going to make a shitload of money. I'm down like 700 bucks, but it's okay.
We have insider information. Asher spent when buying long positions and acquired when taking.
Yeah. Okay. Here comes the announcement. Pepe left bear market. All right. Here it comes. Here it
comes. Here it comes. I'm ready. Here comes the announcement. I went all in. Okay. They just
announced it. Seven, eight. It's going crazy. 8.4, 8.8. We're going to sell at 10. We're going to
sell at 11. We're going to sell. Not yet. Not yet. This is just the first little peak.
It's not that we're not yet. Not yet. Wait, wait, wait. When is it going to hit 11? Once it hits 10.
Now I got it. This made 175,000 dollars. Buy more? Yeah. This could be the first. All right. Hold on.
Wait. No, no, no, no, no. What if it crashes? All right. Well, what about green groceries,
stocks, materials, water? Look at water is way down. I know water is up. Let's look at it. Look
coffee on the daily. Reduce on the daily is high too.
Buy green groceries on the daily. What's it look like? Everything's up. Should have sold only half.
Oh, fuck. All right. I'll get a small position of 5,000. I'm back in. I'm back in. I'm back in.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Keep going. All right. Sell it. Sell it. Sell it.
Market's closed. At the end of each day, we offer our plan is not only an evaluation of the
performance, but also the opportunity to reflect it through personal account spending. You'll notice
that your initial personal account balance is negative $37,000. As I mentioned in the interview,
this is a paid internship. In the event of your termination, you'll be liable for this.
Feel free to have your parents write us a check if you would prefer to start at zero.
You shouldn't have any... I got to turn this music off. You shouldn't have... I got to change the
title of the screen. Once you're the black, make sure you utilize our bespoke concierge purchasing
service. I've had access to it installed in your terminal. It'll not only take care of purchasing
anything you can afford, but also handle any logistics required. We want you to focus on
making money. Let the experts tell you how to spend it. You won't tell anyone that your good
taste is actually there. Okay. I made a bunch of money. How much does she make? Okay. Make $5,000
on coffee. I made 50 grand. Public opinion. All right. My personal account. I got a free chair.
My furniture free includes three items. Honest Extravagant is in our house brand for your every
luxury you need. The first furniture box is free. Don't miss out. Look on go home when you're
finished with your purchases. Gear statue, grand toilet, and sofa. Okay. I can sell this stuff?
I don't want a fucking grand toilet. Get rid of it. Look at how much money I got now.
Sell everything. Wait, I want the sofa. I'm good. Workday's over. Leave the desk. Take care of
yourself. Nothing is planned for tonight. Okay. I got to shut off the 70s porn music. I just got
notification that you've paid off your personal account debt to the firm. Money is relatively
cheap and being afraid of debt is the kind of thing that nobody of any intelligence should be
concerned with. I suppose congratulations are in order. Congratulations. Of course, the real debt
you owe to Ferrios is the opportunity we gave to prove yourself. Life isn't fair and you're lucky
it isn't. Don't forget that. All right. Like let's just bring it down. Okay, cool. Okay,
I made a bunch of money on insider info. Unacceptable trading loss fired. They put his picture up
everywhere. Drinking coffee accelerates the flow of time. Use it when you're confident in your
positions. That's so stupid. What are you buying? Oil fuel? Video games? You're long on electro gear.
You're short on LW lot. Short on dark roast coffee. Clap. I grab his shoulder. Hard. Oh man,
you got killed today. Oh, I'm so sorry. Get a life. Hey, what'd you buy? Long on dark roast coffee.
All right. You know, you did a good job. What if you can't get me? What if I run real fast?
Do I have to go home? No, I just go home. What's going on? Timer 27. Coming up short.
Is it going to teach me how to open up like shorts and stuff? Need help with the help?
Automated scheduling. Payroll mitigation. Terminations. Serve AI. I'm sorry that I
didn't get the chance to meet you yesterday. I was taking a personal day. Quinn. Quinn Miller.
And yes, to get it out of the way, my grandparents did start the company that owns Ferrios. Please
don't worry. I'm not old or rich or gross. I'm here to work as hard as you do. I promise.
Please let me know if there's anything I can do to help. Dinner tonight. Wagyu beef. Buy beef.
Eat runner. Your true priority food courier service. No bicycles. No buy food. Buy meat.
I'm buying meat. Nobody else. I'm not telling anybody else that I'm buying food. I'm buying meat.
I'm trying to trade. So you met Quinn, huh? Make sure you don't cross her.
You can manage it actually. Stay the hell away from her completely. She might be a receptionist
or a concierge or whatever the fuck she calls herself, but she connects all the way to the top.
I heard someone once made Quinn photocopy a stack of documents. Quinn went on stress leave for two
weeks after and the guy who made her do it went on leave too. Permanently. Hey, you take care of you,
I'll take care of me. Oh, by the way, I heard there's a bunch of fucking like,
bunch of dirty rotten like cows and beef and shit. I would short meat. I would short beef
the second I got on my terminal. I heard there's a bunch of problems with it. Idiot. Yeah,
everybody's going vegan. All my friends are going vegan by the way. Didn't labor dispute at DRC
poised to surface. Earth and dark roast coffee bounce back hard. Good morning. It's time you
learned about short selling. I've unlocked the capability to do this in your terminal.
I realize that you've only had a single day to get oriented around a simple transaction,
but the firm is losing money every second that you aren't doing this. Enough is enough.
Short selling is where we borrow shares of a stock at its current price with the belief that
this price will decrease. If it does decrease, we profit off the difference between that initial
price and the price it is at when we execute the buyback. Doing this will also give you
cash on hand to buy other stocks that you think will increase in value taking a long position on
them. GME. That should be all you need to know. It seems as if dark roast coffee will see a lot
of movement today as well. So that may be an opportunity for you to short sell us into a nice
little payday. Maybe it'll give you an opportunity to short a stock at 140% of the shares that are
available to short more than exist 40% more than exist total. We do that. Maybe I should do that.
Be sure to make use of any information that you may have at your disposal.
Short selling is the sale of a stock you do not own. You immediately get some cash,
but you have to buy back the shares later. You should use it to bet on the fall of dark roast
coffee and use the cash for new long orders. All right, so coffee will drop at 14. We're
going to short coffee right now. I'm going to wait though. Let's see. It's probably going to
go a little higher. Leave me the fuck alone. I'm working. You should get all this personal
shit off your desk. It makes you look like an asshole. Hey, you know, it makes you look like
an asshole. Coming over and telling me my stuff on my desk looks stupid. Get out of here. Also,
I see that Corbin gave you access to shorting. You somehow managed to make some cash from shorting,
DRC wink, wink. You should really consider buying star nuts and going long on it. What the fuck do
you know? After coffee crashes, star nuts is only going to rise over time in response. Investing in
star nuts will pay off. I guarantee it. I'm long on star nuts myself. Obviously I wouldn't give you
advice if it wasn't good for me too. Show me your portfolio right now. Show me your portfolio right
now that you have already taken a position in star nuts right now and I'll do it. I got tickets to
that thing tonight. If you're good to chip in on bottle service afterwards, later trader. Okay,
beverages supply chain include coffee. So beverages will surge as coffee drops
our star nuts star nuts sells beverages. So it will surge with them. So go long on star nuts.
Oh, hold on. No, wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I got to make a
decision here. Check out the glossary for more information. I know, I know, I know what's going
on. I'm going to do short position on coffee or a hundred thousand shares. I'm going to go back to
coffee. We're going to go to beverages star nuts. I'm going to star nuts is is a little high right
now though. Long 150,000 long. This is coming down. Don't buy. I'm not going to buy it. That'd be
stupid. I'm just going off the dispute. That's going to happen. Coffee is going to drop around
14 short the hell out of it. I'm going to get blown up. I'm going to get blown up. I'm going
to get blown up. Okay. It's going down. Here comes the big announcement. I'm short minus 172
thousand. Again, I have 357 thousand dollars. Buy star nuts now. No, I'm not buying star nuts.
Wait, should I buy star nuts? I'm going to go long. Not that big of a position. 10,000. I'm long on
star nuts. Okay, I'm getting ready. Here comes the announcement. 14. We're going to buy the shares back.
Buy more. No, I'm not. Here we go. Scandal in Baccarat's coffee industry. Shit's tanking.
We're fucking around with coffee. Jesus Christ. All right, here we go.
Buying back in. Not yet. Not yet. Buy back in in a second. It's going to drop even more. It's coming
down. This is a 27,000 dollar benefit here. Come on. More. Put it on the hourly. Yeah. Star nuts.
Sell it. Should I do it now? Buy back at 8.8. I'm done. I'm done. My position is done.
Newly discovered produce alternative leads to decreased prices. Computation predicts green
grocers will rise. Oh, god damn it. Short green grocers. Short green grocers. Short green grocers
for 10,000. I told you. Look at this peak. This shit's coming back down to like three point. All
right. What do I get for that? I'm down 240 dollars. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get
out. I'm fine. Anti-trust regulations are holding the food stuff business back. Fuck. I want to buy
it. How do I buy it? Foodstuffs is. I should have. I should have bought the materials. Products.
I can't. How do I? I can't buy this. Uno eats is going up. Let's go boys. Go. Go. Go.
Go. Go. Go. Go. Yeah. I got it at six. I think I just bought the top. I think I bought the top.
I think I got. I got. No. It's going to go up. Unexpected demand for produce chokes existing supply.
Produce. Look. Look. Look. Look. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Uno eats is going
back up. Holy shit. And you told me I was stupid. You guys told me I was dumb. Are you kidding me?
Look at that. Oh, I'm so dumb for buying uno eats. Get out. Did I sell it? Did I get it out? Did I
get this? Did I sell it? Is my order going? During your end day value, you'll notice that it includes
a public opinion metric. If you're doing your job properly, this shouldn't be something you'll have
to worry about. You start going overboard with the use of information that you obviously gained
through illicit means. However, the media might start to take notice. Eventually, if enough op
ads get written, the Trade and Investment Commission will be forced to make a show of launching an
investigation that can end with you in court. Unless I tell you otherwise, don't think a second
that the company is going to pay out for any fines or legal fees. Agreed your problem.
Bye. Did I get, did I sell it? Let's see. Did I, did I get, did I actually get to sell it?
Buy furniture.
Ooh, nice. Designer chair. I want that. I'm selling the sofa. Do I want the designer chair or the
executive chair? I want the, I want the designer chair. Okay, cool. Yeah, I want something better
than this. So food stuffs is like, like an index, right? I wish the ancient fucks who won't let them
go would die of old age already. Solitaire. All right, cool. I kind of want to break a window,
office drama. Wow. Where's the party tonight? Kill or be killed. All right, first of all,
I need to do something very quickly here. This has to change. Looking for grandma's antiques.
It doesn't make any sense right now. Um, it does not. Uh, getting liquidated. You know,
how about probably, probably getting liquidated? I think that's a good title. Here we go. Sorry
if this is none of my business, but you look a little stressed out. I'm sure you've been
introduced to the coffee situation, but have you tried the tea yet? It has the opposite effect.
When I drink it, it feels like the whole world slows down. Focusing on small details becomes
easier and I stop worrying that things are constantly passing by. Wait, so coffee,
coffee speeds up time. Tea slows down time. Okay. Where's my new chair? I installed a strong
coffee last night. Guys who loaded into the machines were practically wearing hazmat suits.
I want to clean up my desk a little. Oh, fuck. Hold on. All right. What we got?
Sit down. Okay. What we got? Greengrocer's revitalized destitute cities. Greengrocer's
stock is headed. Let me guess. You sat down at your desk and went straight to Geiss net
only to find it replaced by an extremely boring cable news network. It sucks, but sometimes
journalism gets in the way of worthwhile information. When the insiders don't have
anything interesting for us, we have to get by like everyone else. You best to read between
the lines though. You can still make a few bucks at the very least. In can clue you in on what
suckers are paying attention to. At that point, sometimes all you have to do is be more cynical
than they are. Later. Greengrocer's stock is headed upward after the company announced plans
to open hundreds of new stores in cities devastated by the closure of auto factories.
Company spokesman confirmed that all the cities chosen are expected to see increased interest
from high tech software firms looking to expand their office footprint.
Grade feed shows short lived bits of information about what's going on in the market.
They're not equally all accurate. The number of likes is what you should focus on.
Easing of tariffs should increase the value of green grocers in the near future. Follow.
I gotta get these blinking things off screen. Yeah. Long short materials. Okay. Yeah. I know
what that is loss. All right, let's go. All right. So green grocers easing of
tariffs for green grocers. All right. Hold on a minute. Aqua firma announces new brand.
Aqua firma has a new brand along a hundred thousand out in perfect timing. All right.
We're going to get out of four or what about abundant source of water discovered threatening
price decline on water. Now I'm not paying. I don't have to. I can only pay attention
to one thing at a time. I get out now. That's good. Good. All right. Green grocers with short
green grocers. I think, I think I'm going to put a short on green grocers. This is going up too
high. All in on a short and green grocers. Let's go. We're getting out of 4.5. Oh, it's all right.
It's coming back. Oh no. Oh no. That's not good at the T. Hold on. Oh, oh no. Oh no.
Why do they do that? You guys just have to hold it for a second. Just hold it. It's coming back
down. It's coming back down. Okay. It's going to drop. It's going to drop. It's going to drop.
It's going to drop. It's going to drop back down to like four bucks. This is wicked bad copium.
No, it's not. I got to make $20,000 on coffee related. God damn it. All right. We're going long
on coffee. 75 right here. It's at the bottom. It's going to pop up. Green grocers is going to hit a
peak. It's going to come down. Unexpected demand for produce. Produce, produce, produce, stock,
stock, stock, produce. New regulations are holding food stuff business back. God damn it. Go down.
Green grocers. What the fuck? Oh my God. I've lost so much money on green grocers so far.
Unexpected demand for produce. Fuck. I got to get out. I got to get out. Wait. Dark roast coffee.
Where's my dark roast coffee position? Is what? What was it? It was a long position. Get out,
get out, get out. Perfect timing to get out. Green grocers just fucking shit the bed already.
Come on. Food stuff is going up again. Oh my God. Old coward. Am I short coffee?
Food stuff's down. Aqua firma up. I need to make money on coffee. All right.
But I'm short in food. I'm starting to shorten coffee. Green grocers. God damn it. I have to
get out. I have to get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
I'm not going to lose all that money. It's going to go up to like eight bucks. Dark
grocers coffee. We're going to... Here it comes. Here comes the bad news for coffee.
What's Starbucks doing? Shit. Get out. Get out. Go, go, go, go, go. Short, short, short, short,
short, short, short. I'm down. How am I down on money? Bring it down. Down, down, down, down,
down. Yes. More, more, more, more. Wait. Aqua firms. Don't waste another second on aqua firms.
What? All right. All right. All right. Fine. I'm going to buy. 6.4. Remember that. Up 4.2 thousand
on the dark gross coffee. How are we doing? We're up on both. Dark gross coffee is still
going to go down. It's going to, it's going to touch 5.5. This is, this is a good position so far.
And I'm going to get out really soon here. This is going to peak. I'm going to say it's going to
touch eight. Okay. And I'm going to take the profits right now. Get out. And on this one too.
All right. I'm looking for Starbucks. We're going to go long on Starbucks.
29. 100,000 belong right now. Aqua firm is going places. I don't. Okay. Aqua firma,
aqua firma. Come on Starbucks. Let's go. Come on. What? Okay. No evidence today.
Apply your profits and losses to the debt. That's actually kind of funny.
I'm going to hold this money. Fly profits or losses to the debt.
I'm going to short potato PC cafe later this week.
The box just got their only team kicked out of some big e-sports thing for cheating.
Fucking idiots. Okay. Interesting. All right. I'm going to do the same thing.
Short that PC e-sports company. Deal. Okay. How do you keep track of that? That's a good question.
I don't know. Drink the tea. Yeah. All right. I'm going to drink the tea today.
I'm thinking of replacing chef Burgundy if he doesn't get his act together.
You expect a gourmet chef to get fussy when you tell them to do basically anything,
but it's supposed to be a good fun. When he started, he was very yuric about it.
It was charming. It's different. He's depressed or something. Can you believe that?
A guy who yells at people about foie gras for a living. It's bad energy. Whatever. Drink the tea.
All right. I'm going to drink tea. Tea strength. Well, not in the ad. Market's not even open.
You know, Eats expansion across free states fuels growth, rise in stock price.
Spike criticism to the chin. All right. We buying, uh, you know, eats food. Stuff is going down.
Okay. Food stuffs. We're talking about, um, our gross coffee going down. Starnucks going down.
Uh, short it. Um, I can't short it. Why was, wait, I have a position open. What's my position? What
the fuck is this position? It's open. What's that? What's going on? What? I don't have an open long
position in Starbucks. What the fuck happened? I'm going to drink tea. Drink. That's from yesterday.
All right. Let's go. Time is slowed down. You know, eats expansion. Coffee is going up.
Oh, but it's already so high. What about uno eats? Uno eats is going. Okay. We're going to do a long
position. A hundred thousand. Then that was at nine 30. What's the other, what's the big chart
look like? The daily chart. Nah, this looks like it could go up. It's going to go up.
Food stuffs, green grocers, coffee schedule to go up. Why am I talking like it's a slow motion?
Who eats? Come on, let's go. Why is it going down? Weed stocks. I can't believe I kept that
position open from yesterday. Who eats is still going down. All right. Come on. Give me something
new here that I can react to immediately. Cocaine and weed should be an option. There we go. I need
coffee related wins and losses. Dark roast coffee. Should I put a short up?
I think so. Wait. International trade agreement is expanding. Beverages market.
Beverages going up. Aqua firma. News is just barely getting out here.
Come on, let's go. How am I losing money on this? This is skyrocketing. How am I losing money? Minus
800? What the fuck? You bought at the top. No, I didn't. That just, the news just came out.
Water is going down. Oh shit. That is water. Aqua firma is water. What? Beverages. Shit. Long
on Starbucks. Uno eats is going to go down. Close that position on Uno eats. CEO's personal mail
from Uno eats leaked. Okay. Starbucks is. Wow. Whoa. What? What? Beverages and coffee. I thought
coffee was going up. What the hell? What the fuck? Oh my God. Beverages. Coffee. Look, unexpected
demand for coffee chokes existing supply. This shit is tanking. Beverages aren't coffee. What?
How does that make any sense? How long does the tea work for? Green grocery is going down.
I'm going to hold the Starbucks position because I think it's going to explode tomorrow.
Minus a hundred thousand dollars. Come on. Don't do that. Shit. Green grocery is coffee going up.
Green. I can't go into green groceries right now. Uno eats. Here we go. Come on. Drop. Drop.
Hold. I'm going to hold the Starbucks position. I keep saying Starbucks.
There's going to be a big pop tomorrow for coffee. I'm not going to get fired today. I have 74,000
dollars. All right. Here we go. Uno eats. That data is just leaking right now. Does nobody care
about this? Nobody cares about this. There we go. We're talking about it. Come on. Fuck. There we go.
Okay. This will save us today. 500 bucks. That's it. Keep going. More people are going to start
talking about the CEO of Uno eats. Only 1.4. Is it going to bounce? Don't bounce. Back under nine.
Come on. You lost a million dollars. No, I didn't. I'm down 31,000. I take a thousand dollars and
run. What do I do? I'm getting crushed with this. It's three news articles, not just one.
Oh shit. Oh my God. I didn't even realize that. Okay. Well, whatever. Star Nux is coming back.
It'll come back tomorrow. Beverage is going up. Beverage is going up. Innovation breakthrough
in beverages. Product category leads to surge in demand. I got to close this. I'm closing this
trade. I bought water. How was that on a beverage? Water is a beverage. I'm putting zero likes. What
the fuck? Oh my God. Why? There we go. All right. It's going up. Do this on an IRL stream. No fucking
way. Not a chance in hell. You keep falling for clickbait. I have to hold the Star Nux position.
No, I got killed. Just absolutely decimated. Answer the phone. Oh my God. This is bad.
It's not even recovering at all. It's horrible. I have to hold this until tomorrow. I have to
continue to hold this. Dump the water stocks. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I got out. I need Star Nux to
come back. Stocks category is above its graph. Oh shit. Well, why did I get out of water? Look at
it. Now it's going crazy. What the fuck? Oh my God. Are you kidding me? Don't do that. I'm going
back and I'm drinking coffee. What a disaster. I've never bought into Electrogear Emporium.
Everyone buys that shit online now. Bring enough coffee so the stock goes up.
Just buy the dip. You know? That's not a bad idea. That's not a bad idea. All in. All in on
Starbuck. I keep saying that's not a real company. There it comes. I bought into the dip. No. No. Up.
Look at where this was. Jesus. That's not good. That's really bad. The dip is dipping. I need to
make money on coffee. Come on. Star Nux introduces new spiced pumpkin frappuccino. Oh, go down.
Oh my God. I thought computation predicts green growth. What do you mean computation?
Coffee's going up. Food stuff's going down. Coffee going up. Is the Starbucks plug going to work?
Price of beverages is rising. Starbucks is a beverage, right? Get out of this. Get out of this.
Oh, all of you naysayers. All of you naysayers. This is going to be a... Oh my God. And you told
me I was fucking wrong. This is a hundred thousand dollar plus trade. I'm going to hold it for another
minute. Seventy six thousand. I get out now. I'll hold it. I'll take the profit. I'm out. Seventy five
thousand dollars. Everybody just calling me out. That's fine. Give me some more coffee.
What happened to you? Did you short coffee? Yum. I think this is back to normal now.
What do we got? That was a good trading day. I made a hundred grand. Are you kidding me?
We got out of the perfect opportunity right at the top. Coffee again going up. I'm done for the day.
I'm done for the trading day. Maybe one more trade to take it in tomorrow. What's like... What's
beating up right now? Uno Eats is really just beat up. We're going long on Uno Eats. And I'm
going two hundred fifty fucking thousand shares. Uno Eats. Look at this. It's been absolutely
decimated. There's no reason for that. CEO leaked something. Whatever it was. Oh, and that was a
stupid idea. But apparently Jeremy knows how to trade fucking stocks and everybody here doesn't
understand it. That's fine. Go green with Uno Eats. Oh, wow. What's that? Excuse me. The CEO
like fucking leaked like a nude picture of himself or something. That has nothing to do with the
company. Get out. I'm out. We got out a little early, but I want to secure that profit because
something could happen tomorrow. There we go. Secured. That was a big day. Mustache made him...
Wait, I got fired? Oh no, they got fired. New rival promoted. I got promoted. Owned his fifty
three thousand. Eighty six thousand dollars today. This game's fun. I like this game.
Hario's makes point of investing in employees who show potential. The additional truth is that we
don't want to be associated with people who live in squalor. Have you started investing in real estate?
I'm asking rhetorically, of course. I know you haven't, but I've got good news. The firm retains
a number of condominiums in the city for analysts in your exact position. You'll see that your
terminal now has access to a personal real estate service. Start by claiming the condo we've given
you, which is seating in the market, and eventually you might get the chance to grow into a bigger
place of your own. Screw up and you'll be right back where you started, wherever that was.
Buy. First condo is financed by Hario's. All right, you got three decoration slots in your condo.
Here's your property. Market value, twenty eight thousand. You can store luxury items in your
properties. It will increase their market value when leasing or selling them. When decoration is
up to standard, you should put this property on lease for sweet landlord income. All right, how
about a designer chair? Fair statue and an analyst certificate. I'm sorry, condo. Do I lease it? Do I
make money from this? Sell condo, easy money. Well, not yet. He's a landlord. Get him. Well,
I want to make my price fair. This is where I live. Oh, I don't need to lease it. Look at the money
I got in my bank account because I'm living here. I'll buy a car. I'll buy a car. I'll buy another
condo. Should I buy two condos? I have two condos. Why did I do that? I just have two condos. All
right. Well, then I'll rent this one, right? Is that how it works? Lease the second one.
Okay. Is that, so everybody another condo? I lease this condo. How many condos should I have?
All right. I'm not, no more condos. Stop. What the fuck? Well, I, I just, what? I'm leasing the condo.
Look, I made a hundred thousand dollars yesterday on star Nux. Wait, buy furniture. 40,000.
Okay. Nice. This is going to be, okay. The gold toilets going in there. That's worth a lot of
money. Tell the gold toilet for 20,000. Holy shit. 10,000 for this bust. I'll just, no, why
did I do that? Oops. It's all right. Right on the condo. You can't be serious about this. My
performance has been exceptional. Sorry, Mrs. Lee, but the probationary terms are clearly specified.
There's no room at Ferrios for second best. This is an issue of principle. My trades were flawless
and my analysis of trade feed was perfect. It was not. You took losses at several points
and I always made up for them. The only way you could have possibly come out ahead of me is if you,
I saw it happening, but I figured that you would. I mean, it doesn't make any sense.
I didn't even use insider information. I was just a moron. I just saw, I saw the number
low and I put all of my money into it and the number went up and I sold.
I didn't do anything. I just, I was just an idiot. Thank you for your time. I'll be pleased to provide
you with a reference. You think I don't know what's going on here? You would have to be blind.
You're barely even trying to hide it. Mrs. Lee, your family is very well respected. Please don't
compel me to have security escort you from the building or there to be any kind of public
unpleasantness. Public unpleasantness? Does talking like that make you feel like you come
from somewhere? You couldn't keep me in this shithole at gunpoint. Bye, Mrs. Lee. Fuck you.
But she didn't, she said, she said, she said, she said, I can't say it. She didn't, she didn't see
shit by the way. Sorry about that. I trade better than I talk. Don't worry about Mrs. Lee. I'm sure
she'll find another firm that will take her. And if not, the world's always looking for wealthy
tourists. Congratulations again. Keep your eye on the ball. All right. All right. All right. I got
money. I got money. I'm good. I got it. What are you doing? Holy shit. This dude, this dude lost
$2 million today. 1.8 million loss. I'll take my 60, I'll take my $78,000 gain and make my way. Oh,
that's like such, I'm such a small fry. The person walked up from the desk and they didn't even turn
their computer off with a $2 million loss. I'm sitting here celebrating with like $70,000 trade.
It's got a $10 million account. Small time. Quit streaming in day trade. You know that like 98%
of day traders lose money or something, whatever the statistic is. I don't think I want to do that.
I don't think I would like to do that. I should probably read this. Hell, I'm already tired of
the car I bought a week ago. Expensive tastes never keeps up with the easy boredom. That's a
problem with everybody in this fucking business. You'll be happier after I get you tossed out of
here, but I know you won't believe it until it happens. Until then, do your worst, kiddo.
A lot of people are rooting for you to take out Clark. The space that she's washed up has been,
maybe even it never was. Sure, she made a lot of money, but as somebody who comes from that world,
I can tell you that she has no class. People like her don't belong here. Don't tell her I said this,
but I'll be happy if she was sleeping in a pile of cardboard. Oh my god. So sick of her. I'm too
cool for this world. Wouldn't it be better if we could let it all go attitude? Make the dream come
true. You got this. All right, I gotta get ready for the day. Following the demands of coffee
plantation workers being met in Bocador, a second labor crisis has now sprung up in their oil
industry. Northern oil and gas will rally after 16. Northern oil and gas. How much money do I got?
I got $500,000 in cash. Northern oil and gas is going to rally at 16. I'm going to put all my
money in this. Wait till it falls a little more. I'm looking for a good entry. Right there. Go.
What? What's up buddy? I take it you've seen the news about oil going down a little bit and the
Geissnet post about it going up a whole lot. Well today is going to be a wild one. We're going to
fuck up both those expectations and make a killing doing it. Let me introduce you to our lobbyists.
You can let them sweat the details, but we deploy lobbyists when we want to put pressure on a stock
price to go in one direction or the other without buying or selling it. In this case,
I want you to send them out to make oil prices go through the floor.
No! Harper, I just bought it. Can we just wait? They'll fly to Bocador, yell at a few people,
and make sure that not only does that government bailout for Northern never come through,
but that a whole lot of bullshit gets kicked up as a result. The oil price won't just go down a
little, it'll go down by a ton, and should let us beat up on anybody who expected anything else.
I just put $500,000 on the line. After you assign a lobbyist, short the hell out of anything related
to oil and watch as it magically tanks. Wait, but hold on. Hold on, I need to drink tea. I'll be right
back. No, stop! You're not the first glorified trainee I've had to send home and you won't be
the last. Remember what I told you. You don't really... Just let me go do my drugs. I'll be
right back. Thank you. Just a little bit of slow down so I can have another second or two. See the
news about the oil? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, shit. Okay, I gotta get out of this trade. Send
lobbyists to lower the price of oil. Lower the price of... Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Sending lobbyists to lower the price of oil will decrease the value of oil suppliers.
Short Northern oil and gas before you send in lobbyists. Okay, stocks, oil and gas.
Sis, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out. Short it. Okay, I'm gonna short oil and gas
and then I'm gonna send in the lobbyists. How do I do that? How do I do that? Oil. Use the lobby
controls to send a lobbyist in. Okay, send in lobbyists to make it go down. Sending lobbyists
to lower the price of oil will also increase the value of the products it is an ingredient in.
It's going long on plastics. Well, what the fuck? Long on plastic? All right, all right, all right,
all right, all right. So what we got? How much money do we have? Send in more lobbyists.
Make plastic go up. What are we doing? I'm up, I'm up a little bit on these.
Gas is going down. Send in more lobbyists. More. More. Okay, that's a big trade so far.
What happened? What happened? Why did it sell that? I didn't want to sell that. What are my positions?
Why did they close everything? Shortage of oil? Hey, why did you sell my shit? Nice job on sending
out the lobbyists to drive the oil market down. They told me they couldn't have done it without
you. They're probably just sucking you off, but I guess you don't get whatever. As expected,
the sudden drop in value created chaos and instability, but then it shot right back up
after textbook stuff. Your short positions would have been worthless, so I automatically sold them
for you. We've gotten some bad press with the whole situation, but nothing PR can't handle.
Speaking of the reactions of the pathetic losers, I forgot to tell you about the public opinion meter.
You look at your terminal, you'll see a speedometer type thing. It gets
tilted around by the tooth-bleached rectangle people at our PR agency based on how much bad
shit happens in the world thanks to us. Pay attention to those, because if the things you
do in the market pisses people off too much, bad things can happen. Friending hashtags,
people crying on camera, persecution from trust-funded commie bloggers, etc. You might
even end up in some kind of court, getting yelled at by elected officials, having to pay fines,
hell, you might even have to apologize. Diversify who and what you shit on, though,
and you should be fine. Don't fuck around. What do we got? We still have some time on the trading
day. I got $535,000 in cash. What's beating up today? Aquafirma? Wouldn't it be interesting
if we did a $500,000 fucking long on Aquafirma and sent it to lobbyists? What do you think about
that? The price of water drops as production rises, but you send it to lobbyists and all
of a sudden, here you are. I want this to be a huge trade. More. More. I want at least $70,000.
All right, don't get greedy. Close it. Okay. Dark roast. The boiler says buy dark roast coffee.
I don't trust that person. Electronics are new, okay? Plastics, averages, foodstuff, electronics.
LWLodging. This is wood. AK-247. Munitions. This is pretty low. Look at this. Look at this fucking,
look at how ugly this chart is. Go all in. And send it to the lobbyists. I think that was doing it
already. I think this is LWLodging is down. Keep going. Oh, fuck. My public opinion meter. I can't
do that. I got to stop doing that, right? I'm just throwing lobbyists. All right, we're going to get
out of this trade. We're going to go to plastics. This is just daily information. Plastics going up.
$25,000 trade. How do I change my public opinion? Come on. I didn't put that much money in this.
Water is down a lot. Water is down a lot. So you know what we do. We wait for this to bottom out.
All right, this is a good trade. Let this bottom out and then I'm going to buy $500,000.
Bottom out. After this is done. Price of water drops as production rises. So look at how low
this is. It's going to go even lower. All right, sell that one. All right, water. And this is going
to be where we go in. At six. Look at this shit. Look at how bad this is doing. That's a pretty
bearish pennant, by the way. I know what that is. Come on. A little bit more. Oh, I'm going to turn
around. Water is going up. Go all in on every trade. Uno eats. Oh, get out, get out, get out,
get out, get out. Okay, I'm fine. I lost like 30 grand. This is going to be such a great place
to jump into water though. All in. It really is. Look at this. Look how bad this is. Just wait till
this is over. What time is it? All right, I'm going all in. The trading day is going to open
tomorrow. I'm going to go all in on water. Diversify your portfolio. No, not yet. This looks
like it's bottoming right now. Along on water. Hold on. Good thing I didn't. It's maybe now.
Does this look like a bottom? That's a confirmed bottom. Confirmed bottom. It's coming back. Oh,
fuck. Oh, no. Oh, no. No. How do I send in this shit? Send in the goddamn influencers. I don't
care. If people hate me, I'm fine. Hey, we're good. Everything's fine. Just send in the lobbyists.
Yeah, there we go. Water's doing just fine. Oh, discriminating lobbying reports?
Oh, public opinion is concerned. What do I do? What do I do? OK, I'm going to drive by car.
So I can't put these in the condos. All right, I got to be careful. Keep me in mind. Keep in mind.
I have like a $500,000 trade on water that I need to close tomorrow. I'm getting fired for
too much negative public attention to the firm. I got news for you fucking idiots. People hate us
anyways. Areos is just using this to get rid of me because you know what? That's none of your
fucking business. When it happens to you, believe me, you'll understand. In the meantime, you can
all get fucked. All right, man. You come out of curling next week? I don't want to find another
partner, man. All right, I got to keep that in mind. Shit starts to seriously hit the fan in
Balkador. Social media is going to be a dumpster fire. Can I take these? Can I steal their stuff?
Can I have this? This is mine. I guess I can just take them. All right, whatever.
PR disaster. All right, I got to make public opinion like me tomorrow.
Did you get fired? No, I didn't. Not yet. Steal office supplies. I don't need to steal
office supplies. Make a few TikToks for good PR. We need our apology video. People are being
cold to you. It's probably because you made it past probation and didn't do anything to celebrate.
But Corbin never even suggested it. What a stick in the mud. I'm going to tell you
more sometime today. The National News Network.
Entrances are running high in Balkador as news arrives that a bailout package will not be coming
for the distressed country, leaving many to assume that the worst is yet to come. Huge protests are
anticipated as the people of Balkador understand a deprivation that will surely follow the failure
of the bailout. Rumors are already circulating that northern oil and gas refineries will close
immediately. The lack of a bailout. All but insuring operational. Oh, the bell just rang.
Market's open. Everybody run to your desks. I got to go. I have a bunch of trades I have to make.
The news coming up next. I don't know. You're doing good, but you need to start thinking about
international bullshit. Currency values and all that. Pushing things in one state over another,
you know. In the end, it's all either worth something on any given day or it isn't, right?
But since we're talking about the fate of nations, they expect us to pretend we care.
You can treat countries like anything else, just remember that when they go up or down,
they can take a bunch of other stuff with them. Materials, products, and the rest of it.
Try lobbying them if you want to start making waves in several convenient places at once.
Shouldn't be rocket science by now. Later, trader.
As the value of a currency goes up or down, the value of companies which
come from the countries of those regions go up and down as well.
Okay.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, my water. Water. Water going up. New safety standards
for water industry. Means that the numbers are going to go up on your screen.
No, no, don't sell. Why would I sell? Water's about to go up. Who owns this company?
Okay. The robo? All right, what we're going to do is we're going to...
Wait, wait, wait. Go back, go back, go back, go back. Where am I? I need to close this trade.
Sell it. No, not yet. Who owns this? Sell, sell, sell, sell. I don't know.
I just saw this thing on my screen. I don't know what just happened. FSU.
FSU is going to crash. The unit dollar is going down. I don't know what happened.
Make 50... I need to drink tea. Okay. Now I'm going to go back to my desk.
Let me slow this down. Biggest crackdown still coming. Northern coming back.
Behind the scenes, northern executives are furious about the protests.
Government's already making plans to wipe the protesters off the streets and
northern has agreed to bring in hundreds of workers from other countries.
Wait, what do you mean? The robo will surge at 1430? Northern coming back.
Okay. Northern, oil and gas. Check this shit out.
The robo is tanking. Check this out. We're going to make a ton of money.
And enter right now. 13, this shit's coming back. 1430. Hold it. I'm going to get fired.
How do I make PR? How do I do PR? I'm just going to wait. Should I jump on board of this?
Stop lobbying. All right. No more lobbying after this. Don't cheat.
I won't lobby anymore. I promise. New safety standards for water.
The currency crashed and then I jumped into the company that the currency is based on.
And then at 1430, this probably company is going to go up. That's what it said.
Starbucks going up. Buy Starnucks before the global collapse.
Global collapse? Oh, what time is it? Come on. I'll exit when it's at a thousand.
Clickbait? Well, I'll make some money on the clickbait.
Just do badly and the public opinion goes back up. All right. Almost there.
I'm doubling down. Double down. More. Keep it going. I want more.
All right. I'm going to get out of this trade. I'm ready to liquidate this.
Water's gone. I can't pay attention to that right now. What's going on?
Hey. Excuse me? What just happened? Did we just get hacked?
Stop. Leave me alone. Did everything go dark for a few seconds on your end just now?
It did over here. All right. I got a lot of money in this trade.
I know we have backup generators, so it wasn't the electricity.
Oh, well, probably nothing. Okay. Here comes the news.
Raggedy unfolds tonight in the democratic public of Balkador.
Really unemployed oil workers took to the streets.
Protests sudden closing of northern oil and gas refineries across the country.
Five police cracked down on the protests with brutal efficiency, killing as many
as 50 protesters, including in hundreds of people. Did I do that?
Easy balance followed the failure of Northern to secure a bail life from the Balkan government.
A bailout which could have prevented the violence that has at least the moment finally abated.
Oh my god. I sent to the lobbyists to make the cart. What did I do?
Sources tell us that the government and Northern were close to a bailout when
fierce opposition emerged from within the ruling party.
The newly revitalized opposition is claiming that a deal with Northern would have required
unacceptable cuts to vital social programs. What did I do?
Investor confidence in Northern has really barely been lower and will likely continue as the-
Oh, shit. We'll update you with more as the situation-
Get out. Okay. And then we're gonna- we're gonna go short.
Um, AK-247. Oh, she got out way too early. Fuck. Dark roasters coffee.
Are your condos worth 50 people, Jerry? God damn it.
I- hold on. I'm gonna be clean from now on.
Ooh, I need to make some more money on this. The FSU.
Okay, let's short the gas.
Jerry? It looks like it's gonna come down. I'm closing 60 minutes.
Coffee is up. Water- who else? Do they have water? It's just the earth drill dark roast coffee.
Buy it? I don't- no, I don't think so. I don't think I buy this. I think I short this.
Electronics going up. Who owns that? Is it electronics? It's coal.
Where's electronics? Soda? Coffee and plastic.
Electronics! The unit dollar's all over the-
B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B...
Unit dollar is the, uh, the Bocador currency, isn't it?
Huh? Unit dollar is the- is the currency.
Come on, go down. Go down, go down.
Oh, it's the ro- oh, shit. It's the robo.
Public opinion's back, it's okay.
Oh god. I was supposed to mention this to you at the time,
but the firm has a tradition that everybody who makes it past probation
is supposed to throw a party for everybody.
It isn't mandatory, but some of the brokers here believe that socializing outside of work
will determine how far you can go at the company. I wouldn't overestimate it, I've fired a lot of
popular losers. Regardless, you should see an interface in your terminal that will help you
plan it. Okay, organize a party. Party planned in condo. Getting up and just throwing a bust
at the vagasone's head. Oh my god. Jesus. Oh, I lost 50 grand on a unit dollar.
Members of the Ferio staff gather at your apartment for drinks before you head out on
the town for your night of bar crawling and whatever else. Several of your co-workers
remark on your- it sounds like a kid's birthday party. Several of your co-workers remark on your
latest acquisitions, taking care to quickly spin the conversation around a similar or better
things that they've recently purchased themselves. Before everybody heads out,
you take one last look around. Satisfied how- that got really quiet. Satisfied how impressed
everybody was. All of this is yours and you earned it. You shut the lights, lock the door,
and the rest of the night becomes a blur. Oh god. Everybody have fun at the party?
Worst part about how many people get fired here is not knowing what you're supposed to do with
them on social media. Should I stay connected with them? It's so awkward. One time one of them even
wrote me and was all like, I think you're so talented, it was so amazing to work with you.
They think I can get them to a job back just because of who my family is? Honestly it's so
rude. I hate it. Take responsibility for your own life. Hello? I thought I told you when you get
these challenges you're getting them for a reason. You're intentionally ignoring them because you're
bitter and nobody is filling you in on the strategy. You might be too emotional for this job.
You see me giving a fuck? No you don't. Because I get paid either way and that's all that matters.
And so do you. Just stop fucking around, follow the orders so we can get rich,
get the fuck out of here and never look back. Do you have any idea? What the hell?
Nice streamer setup. You don't need this many monitors. Three. I have four but that's because
I wanted the fourth one. I have an open trade. In what? Oh! Dark roast coffee we need to send
the lobbyist in. Send in the lobbyist. I just lost everything. Send in the lobbyist, short it down.
I need coffee to go down. I need coffee to go down. Down, down, down, down, down.
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Come on. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on. Go, go, go, go, go,
more! Crush it! You said no more lobbyists. Yeah but I had to. I'm gonna get destroyed.
Get munitions price 11% lower? Okay I'm gonna get out of here with a $38,000 loss.
Oh, what do you think? Wait, should I just take the loss? I'm taking the loss, whatever.
I have $620,000, fine. Okay munitions. 11% lower, that's all I had to do. Here it is,
we have coal now, okay. What's this? New carbohydrate research sparks intensified food
stuff lobby. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Oil going up. Unexpected demand for oil chokes existing
supply raising price too late. I missed plastics. Did I though? What about the, what about the soda
company? FSU going up. The FSU dollar. Soda, soda, soda, soda, soda, soda, soda, soda, soda.
Hold it. Oh my god. Oh my god, the soda and double, I've got double whammy'd here.
I got triple whammy'd here. Soda, soda, soda announces new brand and their currency went up.
I should have went, well I should have went all in. I'm gonna hold this one. Get munitions lower.
How am I gonna do that? Although plastics is really killing this. Not yet. Hold on.
And get out now. Okay, what do we got? Munitions have got to go lower. Lobby it down.
Oh then soda, still doing well. Is it still going up? Throughout munitions companies? I,
all right, all right, I'll get, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in. All right, I'm in.
Lobby everything. I can't do that. All right, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out. That was a bad trade. I'm out.
Electronics going down. Strong economic performance in Volcador. Dark roast coffee, let's go.
I need, now we need a, we need coffee to go up. Come on, give me, give me a coffee right here.
Coffee going up. Munitions have to keep going down. Ken, drop it. 10k on this one right here.
Ooh, nice. Munitions is, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, what, what's going on? Munitions,
shortage of munitions. Oh my god, what happened? Did I get it? Did I get in?
All right, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out. Okay, I'm good. I have $642,000.
What's coming up next? I feel like I'm watching somebody's job that I don't understand at all.
Get tea? Coal, coal, coal, coal, coal. Who has coal? Who has coal? This drilling company does.
Electronics going down. Coal going up. Plastics going down. Munitions going up.
Whoa, what happened? What the fuck just happened? Why'd they do that? Coal's supposed to be going
up. Rising protection has been coal producing. Did this guy just get dumped on? Who dumped that
shit on me? What was that? Read the news? There's an enemy lobbyist. You want to play that game?
Fine. We'll play that game. Bring it back up. Imagine seeing this chart. I feel like what the
fuck is happening? What is happening? Oh no, I didn't sell. What just happened? Emergency PR
minus 25% for a new car. I'll take it. What'd I get? I can sell these? 90? 100? I made money.
Lease your first condo. I think I should probably sell my first condo. Put them in the condo. Okay,
where's the most expensive one? This is a $90,000 car. I'm putting it in this condo.
Holy shit, I can lease this for $14,000 a day? What if I put two cars in here? Oh my god, yeah.
Holy shit. Okay, I'll take it. This is my condo. One day's of cleaning remaining. What's that mean?
Why do I hate chat? I have to close that. What trade do I have open right now? I don't even
remember. Oh, the party. Okay. Oh, all right. I gotta be ready to get the hell out of coal.
Understand that the more you screw up, the more difficult it becomes to make it look like a
misunderstanding. Public opinion is a complex thing. A spectacular amount of time and money
is invested into expressing it within a single metric on your dashboard. We do this so you can
focus on making money. We also do it so you have no excuses whatsoever if you screw up.
I guess why I'm standing here. That's right, you screwed it up. If you can't conduct business
profitably without dragging Ferrios through the mud, we will find somebody who can. Now get out
of here. I think I got my one screw up that I'm allowed, like Super Mario life. Well, somebody
anti-lobbied me. I lobbied and then they lobbied me back. It wasn't... I bought the price. They
lobbied me down, so I lobbied them back. Yeah, I'm thinking about going back to school. I've always
been interested in marine biology or maybe jungle biology. I know it isn't all about cute animals,
but I do love orangutans and their scrunched up little faces. They've hurt the earth so much.
The least we can do is save the animals. Trust me, you don't even want to know how cruel people
can be to them. Makes me sick. I have to get this trade ready to close. I can't talk to anybody
right now. Okay, where am I? Okay, this has to sell immediately when the market opens.
I can't... I just gotta go. Good. Good. Oh, man. Oh, man. Okay. Okay. All right. This is looking good.
Okay. Nice. I'm happy about it. Electronics going up. Close it. Or should we wait for it?
We wait for something to do with coal. Hold it. Hold it. Hold it. Hold it. Coal's gonna go up.
It's gonna be a big thing with coal. Plastics. Come on. FSU. Come on. FSU is not this one.
Why you got... That's me. All right. I'll take the 100 grand. What we got? In one neighborhood,
a coffee com service. I need to speak to coffee. Slow it down. I'm almost at a million dollars.
Lobby more? No, I'm not going to lobby at all today. I need to read this.
So in one neighborhood, a coffee com service is following years of protests over gentrification.
Residents of one small community seem to finally be accepting the presence of Star Nux,
a chain in which they once held solar spots for the end of the beloved local coffee stand. Sam's
coffee meant a lot to us, but I guess they wore us down. Sam died a few years after they drove
him out of the business, too, and he had been the one who was really leading the fight. New
rifle ammo design poised to shake up munitions industry. Deathblossom, a new type of ammunition
with the popular RAE-27 semi-automatic rifles renewing the efforts of lobbyists against
the munitions industry, who insist to be taken off store shelves. AK-247 stock surges if free
state citizen stockpile ammunition. Okay. We're going to play the... Oh, never mind. We're not
going to play that today. All right. Let me look at the daily chart. Let's take a look around.
Soda, plastic. FSU is up. Lodging, gas is down. Water is way down. Green grocers are doing a fight.
I think I'm going to make a water play here. I think I'm going to go for water.
I would have bought this. I wonder if I should just short this.
FSU dollar is overrated. What? Get a trade in, you fucking idiot. This is coming crashing down.
I didn't even have to lobby. I just waited for the dollar to be bad. Is that bottoming out?
The good thing I got out of coffee. Bottom is zero. Foodstuffs going up. Close this trade.
Foodstuffs going up. This is not foodstuffs. Get out. Where's foodstuffs?
You shorted, not longed. That's all right. I got $698,000.
Currencies. How's this doing? All right. Get the Democratic Republic of Baccalaureate price 11%
higher. And then some lobbyists. Let's go in on oil and gas. This is good to me. Here we go. Nice.
I'm not going to use lobbyists. Well, it told me I had to. Stop lobbying. Get the price 11% higher.
I can't do that. I can only do that with a lobbyist. It's almost there. I'm almost done.
Come on. A little more. A little more. Come on. A little more. Have the currency go up a little
higher. Only two more cents. Come on. No. There we go. There it goes. Take up higher. I wonder
if this game is awakening any future traders. The markets are fucking terrifying. Be careful.
Almost there. All right. Sell that. All right. Now I just need the currency to go up a little more.
The FSU is down. Coffee is down. Come on. Come on. I just get a... One more time. That's it. I
promise. All right. Go. I promised. I know I promised, but I promise. Whatever. Invest before
you lobby. Yeah. Otherwise, I'm chasing the price too. All right. Sell it. Okay. All right. I got
$738,000. Munitions going down. You got it. You got it. You got it. You got it. Keep going. Munitions
down. The FSU up. Oh my God. Get out. Holy shit. Did I get out? Thank God. All right. I probably
just lost the game. All right. What's the play here? I think I'm going to short this at the top
here. Look at how bad this looks. Starnux is up. Green grocery is up. Coffee. Probably maybe coffee.
We know Eats. I don't know what's the play here. What's the play? I mean the top. Pepe left. I mean
this is going down. This is going down. I'm in. A nice pop. This shit's tanking. The FSU is just
the public finance. Financial crisis. The Free State Union casts fear. Lots of fear here. Munitions
are not doing well. Price of munitions drop as production rise. A lot of bullshit going on here.
That was a nice little pop, but it's not going to last. Munitions are dead. The munitions are done.
It's over. Any second now. People seem to be not believing that. People don't really care.
It's losing traction. Drop. Just drop. 32 is the new floor, old man. We'll see. Here we go.
Here it comes. Here comes the really bad news. Bad news incoming. Really bad news coming up.
Yeah, you thought that? That was a bull trap is what we call it here in the office.
This is a bull trap. Watch this. No, yeah. You got nothing. Come on.
Come on. I'm not sending any... And there it is. There's the bull trap. Trap set. There it is.
Goodbye. Told you it was a bull trap. You're finished. Come on. Get this. I don't want likes.
Government of FSU is spending large amounts of money to fuel unrestricted. Yeah, let's go.
Yeah, goodbye. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Thank you.
No, no. What is this stock doing? Go down. Go down. I'm not closing this until
below 30. There we go. See? See? It's bottoming out. I don't think so. This has still got a lot
of traction in the news here. Below 30, I'm telling you. This game is bad for chat.
Everyone's getting invested. There we go. All right. Now I'm going to... I'll close it now.
Right now. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Under 30, I told you. All right. Oh, this is not... This
does not look good. Okay. I'm out. I'm out. All right. Now I'm out for real.
I'm out. Now for real. In 10 seconds. Now. Okay. Done. Okay. Good. This game sucks. This
game does not suck. This game is fun. I've been looking for a stock market game like this
six, seven, eight months ago. Remember we talking about wanting a game like this?
Oh, I wanted it so bad. Okay. All right. I'm going to... Let's go get... Markets are closing
anyways. I did it good for the day. Speed this back up. This game is slot machines with graphs.
I mean, that's just the stock market. You just described the stock market. The stock market is
just a shitload of people, like 50 people all hovering around the roulette table, all screaming
the numbers that they're playing and arguing with each other as to why you should play certain
numbers. It's just roulette table with like 100 people at the table. All right. Fire. I won.
Another person down. No evidence was disclosed today. I didn't lobby that much. Get some cash
here. Holy shit. Should I get another condo? Should I get maybe another car? Should I buy
another one? Words on the screen make no sense to me. It makes sense. Hey, they make sense to me.
I know what I'm doing. I organize a condo party. No, I'm good for the day. After these condos,
I don't even have furniture. Peter Griffin trading stocks. Put stuff in the condo. Yeah. You
know what? I can't. They're already there. I have to buy stuff. It's $80,000 to buy furniture. I
can't. How do I leave? I don't leave? Oh, I didn't click go home. Oh, okay. I like this game. This
game is good. This is fun. I like this. Oh, I don't need this shit right now. You can't be really
serious about Furious letting me go. Because everybody I beat was some nobody's shit face
analyst. I've been working for years. I've been loyal to you for years. Please leave the building
calmly. I'll have security meet you on the ground floor. Congratulations on your promotion to
associate. I might say that you've made it through your real probation period. The vast majority of
our analysts never make it as far as you have. You need to prove yourself and we may promote you to
vice president. At that point, you'll get a taste of what it really means to be part of a firm like
Furious. Vice president. Vice president. Holy shit. I've been here for five days. That's a psycho.
Whoa, that was weird. I think is the game saving? Hopefully the game has been saving.
Law and disorder. This is insane, Lois. Yeah, it reminds me of the time I sent GME to the moon.
Where do you think you're going? What are you even doing here? We're executing a search warrant.
Knowing what you know, I'm sure you can expect charges to follow shortly. What?
Oh, I don't even think about going anywhere else. The passports of every employee of this
firm have been flagged. Get lost. What are you talking about? Hey, don't touch my computer.
What the hell? The firm is going to prison. This is scripted. Welcome to the show. Good morning.
I'm glad we're all able to take a bit of time off even if it was unexpected. Did you meet Walker yet?
I hear she's your new rival. Ignore her if she starts talking nonsense. She's not an intellectual.
She's hallucinating. They tried to ban hard drugs here for a while to keep the coke under control.
Who knew we would end up with a person on some kind of experimental LSD meth ketamine combo instead?
I don't care how good it makes her at math or computers or whatever. Between you and me,
not worth it. They're a psycho and not the cool kind. Do you play anything else besides solitaire?
Holy shit, that's so boring. If you think you've got any chance at getting that VP position over me,
you're even crazier than I am. Understand something? I don't sleep, I don't eat and
drink intravenously. I live in the algorithm. I see the constellations, the data of everything
everywhere. I'm ready for the future. You don't even have one. Now get out of my fucking face.
All right, the trading is on. Let's go. Violence continues to spread across the
Democratic Republic of Balkador with many saying that the country is now on the brink of full-scale
civil war. Really? Well, government representatives deny that foodstuffs, foodstuffs, foodstuffs, and
livestock, and foodstuffs, and livestock. Where is it? Foodstuffs, and livestock, and
livestock, and foodstuffs. Where is it? I don't know where it is. I'm so late to this trade.
Uno eats infinity mart. Holy shit, this is expensive. I missed it. The euro. Chaos in
the market. I need to drink fucking tea. God damn it. Slow it down. Let's go. Ammunition.
Weapons will surge this afternoon. Yeah, I know. I need weapons, products, weapons.
Missiles. We're going big on missiles. Arms dealing. No, I'm buying weapons. Buy, then sell,
then buy again. God damn it. Leave me alone. We need you to start taking long-term positions
in some of the companies the firm is dealing with. I've unlocked the ability for your terminal to
start collecting dividends. Dividends, you will generate ongoing revenue from the stock of any
company you've bought on a regular basis. It's our piece of their profit, so make sure you pick
companies that are making one. Dividends can be far more lucrative over time than constantly
trying to guess which way the market is going. Especially if you have confidence that a company,
a weapons manufacturer, for example, is going to continue to grow and do well because of some kind
of event. You're in the big leagues now. If you stubbornly hold onto the wrong company for a long
time, the results can be catastrophic. Weigh your options carefully. Buy. Missile Tech AG. Sign the
dividend agreement. The position will earn expected dividends at market closure every day, but cannot
be liquidated until you pay the penalty fee. Well, that's $700,000 and that's all my money.
I don't have any money. All right, missiles are going up. Buy. Wait. How many do I have?
$710,000? How do I have $970,000 here? I have $1.46 million in that. Oh my goodness gracious.
I've signed the dividend agreement. Every single cent I own is in this. Okay, this afternoon it's
going to pop. Here it goes. Oh my God. What should I do? I have $1.7 million. What should I do?
This is huge. Did I pay the penalty to take millions of dollars? Hold it. Should I hold it?
This is $1.9 million. Lobby it now? Oh my God. I can't. I have just weapons. All right. I did
it. I did it. Now I'm going to liquidate it. I'm going to take $2.3 million. Oh my God. This is a
big mistake. This is a mistake. $2 million. $2.1 million. Euric dominion? The euro's overvalued.
Is this euro? No. Should I hold it? Hold it. Hold it. Hold it. Is this civil war happening?
Yeah, but this is $2.5 million. You won't get the dividend if you sell it. Oh man.
Weapons are surging. Hold for the dividend. Hold for the dividend.
It's going to come down though. All right. I'm going to pretend it doesn't exist.
You need to have diamond hands. Countries of Sienna. Sienna is this company. Sienna's not
doing well at all. Sell now. Jesus. Should I? I missed the dividend. This is $100,000 in dividend.
Plastics going. No. It's okay. It's $2.2 million still. It's all right. I have to hold this to the
end of the day. Okay. Now I'm going to... What the fuck just happened? Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
What do you mean weapons down? Regulation of the weapons industry is ongoing. Get out. $2.1 million.
Sell. Sell. Sell. I have $1.8 million. I'm good. I thought I sold it. I thought I sold it. No. I
got out of the dividend agreement. Okay. Get back in. I have $1.8 million. All right. Let me...
I'm going to get back in. You sold the bottom. I did, didn't I? All right. $500,000. Lock that up
as a dividend. Sign the dividend agreement. I have $1.3 million now to play with. Southern soda.
Long. Southern soda smells like blood. Wait. Why is that a good thing? I just bought on the news.
What? Why is that a good thing? It smells like blood. Southern soda. Beverages are up too.
Look at this. This is going to be good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I got my dividends coming in.
Who the heck likes on the news about how real it is? I mean, that's like... That looks pretty...
That smell is more than money. It's blood. Buy southern soda with everything you got. Why?
Why would you want to have something smell like blood? I'm thinking of closing this.
Do you guys remember that time when Chuck E. Cheese came to the stream
and when I showed the me kissing Chuck E. Cheese picture, this stock price went down by like 5%
or something? Didn't that actually happen? That's so stupid. I don't think it was related at all,
but somebody brought it up. They were like, hey dude, I like did some math and I did a little
thing. I kind of did some timing here. This is when he appeared on your stream and this is
what their stock value was. And this is when you showed the kiss. It's like, no, that's not accurate.
That's just nothing. That doesn't mean anything. I'm out. That was good trade. 1.4 million. What do
I got here? How is it? How's the missiles doing? What do you have weapons? All right. Missiles.
I have to hold it for the dividend. What's going on with Starnox? Plastic going up.
I only got like a few more minutes in the trading day. All right. So what I'm going to do is I'm
going to... Let's go all in. Let's go all in. I'm going to... I'm going to make that even up. You
know what? Market's closed. I'm going to get my dividend. This guy's negative 18,000. He
fucked up big time. It's okay. I got 200 grand. Should I buy some more cars? Sell for $187,000?
I think I'm just going to do that. That's 200 grand. I can buy a house now. Buy a house. Market
value. Decoration slots. Oh my goodness. Okay. Hold on a minute. I'm going to... This is going
to make me a shitload of money. I'm going to sell this house for $83,000 and then I'm going to buy
some cars. Oh yeah. Come on. I'll check this shit out. $28,000 a day. $34,000 a day. $37,000 a day
from this house. This is currently... But who's even taking this? All right. I'm going to sell
this one. Don't need to... We're buying houses now. I need to buy paintings. Oh, I need a million
dollars. Now lease the house. Not yet. Not yet. Hold on. Because I need more decorations and shit.
Designer chair. I'm going to buy... Okay. Here's what I'm going to do. Ready? Check this out.
I'm selling this. I am now going to buy a furniture loot box. Okay. Sofa. Going in the house.
$38,000 a day. Designer chair. $38,000. A bear statue. Lease it for almost $39,000 a day.
I just spent a bunch of money. That's okay. This is where I live. I live here.
Wait. Do I even have a house? Wait. I don't have a house.
Shit. What do I do? I need to live somewhere. I sold my house? I have to live at work now?
Buy another condo. I need to live here. Buy another condo. Okay. This is where I live.
I got fired. I'm not going to be getting fired for organizing a union when I explicitly said
that it was not what I was doing. All I want to do is make all of you think of yourselves
as important stakeholders in the business of people who get paid to show up here.
If all of us felt that way, imagine the things we could accomplish and the profits we might be
entitled to. Far more profits than anyone in any kind of failed communist state would know
anything about. I know that much. Sadly, you're all too foolish to see. You don't deserve me.
Nobody deserves me. Fuck you. Fuck you all. How many people work here still? Okay. It's just me
and the human computer. How did you do today? Leave me alone. Working shitty uppers. Fuck.
I want to know what you did today. Ten million in your account. Down one million.
Down $275,000 today. I wonder who's going to get the promotion to VP. Unionize your
workplace just gave ten community subs. I bet you're wondering how it could be that this
place was drowning in TIC agents two days ago. And yet now everything is back to being exactly
the way it was. On top of that, dead silence from everyone. Not as much as a word about it.
I see everybody playing it smart. Silence is golden, they figure. Hey, if everything's fine,
I don't need to know anything. You don't need to worry either. Just say the interests of our
government and Farios are overlapping at the moment and not only the way they usually do.
For some of the people with access to Geissnet and put two and two together, but they should
know better than anyone to not say a word. Or you do too. Also, I missed ten community subs from
Onomos and Lenny the Person. Thanks both of you for your ten subs. Wait, aren't these everyone
that got fired? Resent them for trying to make everybody else look bad by doing it.
Before long, you realize it makes sense, especially the cleaners who tried to make it feel like it was
all a dream. It also seems to be easy to impress everybody as a host when you've got a staff at
your beck and call. The bartenders and waiters go out of their way to make it clear that this is your
party in a way that makes you understand they've done this many times before. Everybody loves you
and tells you this is the best party they've ever been to. Before long, everybody will be doing this
and try to enjoy it. Blackout. You look so tensed lately, maybe you should take some time off.
I always like to say, spoiler yourself, you deserve it. Taking a two-year backpacking
sabbatical after college was the best thing I ever did. I learned so much about the world
just by going to places and really letting myself be there. Come by sometime and I'll
show you the pictures. I know how boring it can seem, but dividends work. It can't be rip and
run, buy, and sell bullshit all the time. It makes sense now and then to check in for the long haul
when you're dealing with things that will never change. Yesterday you fucked up. You should have
taken the dividends and respected the play. You're watching the news right? I'm sure you can figure
out that this is bigger than either of us now. When you eat shit like this you make it seem like
you can't see the bigger picture. Start seeing it. What's wrong with this person? Like how about like
I do make my own trades and you like look I want if I want to buy like star nucks I'm just gonna
buy it like what the who cares leave me alone tea drink tea save civil war on the democratic
republic of balkadar has now been declared with leaders in the free state union the europe dominion
and other global powers calling for peace of course on the ground so just that sudden escalation of
hostilities have been tied to poorly trained rebel troops getting access to increasingly heavy
weaponry 23 people attended the party in your condo what what i get long i'm long on this one
i believe is it defended wait wait wait wait hold on wait the dominion and the free state union
dominion in the free state union who's got this shit star nucks going up we also got um
logging company going up okay all right all right we've got big steak here make 200 000
dollars on the free state union related markets well what the fuck southern soda all right coffee
weapons are going down hey hey hey greetings from the exorcist we follow the money all of your
secrets belong to us justice for balkadar fuck yourself and die what happened everybody's
laughing well this is happening to everybody my mouse isn't working what the fuck is going on
are you guys seeing this shit um how many call it guy don't be alarmed by everything going on
the situation will be under control shortly there's nothing about these degenerate criminals that is
worth paying attention to this is hacktivism nonsense is nothing but extortion we received
the ransom note moments after all this started happening the it department will figure it out
it becomes the most pragmatic course of action we will pay after all we can always find the money
in the salaries of the it employees will be catapulted into the fucking moon if they do not
fix this right now everybody shut the fuck up somebody call it i apologize for losing my
temper i truly loathe these disgusting nerd hacker people they want the same thing we want they just
don't want to work for it goodbye i'm off on a lot of stuff hold on new moneyville extraction what
if i close this trade are they gonna get it am i making money all right i got 28 000 today all
right i need to make 200 000 on the from the other freestyle union what if freestyle union do
products i don't know what's that i don't know what that is but it's going up i don't think
it's the right country keep going i need to make 200 000 from that place a free state union all
right i need free state union stocks i don't know i don't know what country these are mania is going
up by bullshit i'm telling you keep going by nature oh i don't know keep going i'll get 100k i'm gonna
that's a pretty big haul right there that's two hundred thousand dollars
everybody please play nickelodeon baseball again the fact that you just said that infuriated me
that's a good trade that's 100 oh my god yeah oh my goodness 150k more let's go 160 200
let's go 200 let's go 200 why not oh over 200 why not and i am out in three no i'm not stay
holy shit just doesn't stop oh my god it's not stopping i think it's time to sell now
i mean no not yet what the fuck 300 000 i guess i'm gonna i'm gonna keep holding this
until 500 000 i don't i don't even know what stock this is wait till it dips by 20 000 that's a good
idea all right i'm getting out if this hits 350 i gotta put a new floor for myself okay 375
no the new floor is 400 400 is the new floor the new floor is now 450 the new floor is now 475
get out all right i got 1.5 million dollars losing money on this dividend it's okay all right i was
at a huge amount of money i first whatever this is it's going down apparently oh it's the ruble
it's that i don't know that is but it's going down apparently whatever it is it's going down
i know the daily challenge new moneyville okay sickness murder okay i'm gonna go long on murder
i'm gonna send lobbyists to this i'm gonna go on and go a fucking million dollars trade go on come
on i got a million dollars in this lobbying larry i did one lobby come on and you get this guy gets
200 000 let's go one more lobby did i do one more lobby i think i'm gonna do one more and maybe not
i guess it's 200 000 it's a little bit more lobbying and that's it just one more lobby
no i might not have to is 200 000 come on 200 000 200 000 and i'll get the daily challenge come on
come on come on more yes sell it yeah
crack my knuckles that was a pretty good day i think that was a pretty good day
drink some coffee i'm done i don't need to trade anything else i'm done what do i need to do
is it all in a day's work all right markets close in a few minutes prison okay how many
dividends doing thirty one thousand dollars or going to coffee at five p.m. uh no that was a really
good day oh this guy's it's over i beat this guy he doesn't even have a chance i said to make a
little tiny little trade tomorrow and i went and i'm vice president of the company look at this
money just rolling in on my personal account let's go i tried using one of those gig services that
manages all your other gig services all it did was fuck everything up i swear to god trading day
hey good trades trade team good trades all around you gained more from a landlord than you did from
work i did well it's because there's like three sports cars in the driveway you're not even
renting the house at that point you're renting the cars looks like first having some trouble with
cyber security what he called us to investigate but a hack that massive attracts attention regardless
seems like your people are getting it under control but i'm sure it makes you think about things
a bunch of teenagers in the middle of nowhere can hit ferrios like this if you're not as untouchable
as you think you are and i'm letting everybody know they can reach out to the trade and investment
commission anytime they like we're always looking for people who are as good at predicting their own
futures as they are predicting the markets so you're wrong i want to be a plant informant i don't
look sad today but don't worry i'm through the worst of it i was just thinking about how much
suffering there is in the world like have you heard about all the sad stuff going on in the
balkador it's so sad why does one tiny little group of sad poor people have to go through every
bad thing that could possibly happen i'm just thankful that so many people from places like
here are trying to like set up businesses there so they can have better jobs i read a quote once
about how people will forget what you do but remember how you made them feel well hopefully
they feel better soon yeah that's that's a good yeah that's true me too i hope they do i hope they
do better i'm stuff so all of my screen employee business was that he was that my phone whose phone
is that what's wrong what's going on my thing another thing i forgot to say can you believe
how bad we got hacked the whole system's all messed up just saying they got deep into the database or
something apparently things would be screwed up like this for days i'll mention this but some
junior analyst asked corbin about it and he fired them on the spot this is the most emotional i've
ever seen him you see him just pretend like everything's fine and that none of this terrible
shit's even happening to us it's seriously like the worst thing that's ever happened in my life
so everywhere i think that's why it bothers everybody so much you know what more people
here need to be in therapy in the meantime try to enjoy yourself remember that the only damage
left is superficial good vibes okay a great day all right okay uh what's going on here is it over
for iron still stock falls as recycled alternatives all right iron short iron i don't even know what
iron is this is gaining some traction here this is gaining i just need 20 grand i need 20 grand
and i'm gonna go drink coffee get it up there let's go 13 16 14 come on 22 there it is 29
34 38 i have secured myself as vice president of the company now i'm just gonna go drink coffee
and let the day go by let the day go by i don't need to do anything else i am now vice president
what's this flyer employee business club not a union strictly for discussions on how we can
make the company more successful who's is this all right let's just copy light it on somebody
else's desk to get them fired why would i do that all right time for the day to blow by
oh jesus how's my dividends doing it's sickness price 10 lower i didn't even do anything it just
happened make 34k on this dividend yeah and i i got the challenge done this is not going up too
flyers gonna get you fired you think so is it am i gonna get fired for that look at all these
what are all these pictures put it on his desk what on the boss's desk he's gonna be like this
is what we're up to boss the fuck are you gonna do about it oh shit my phone boss will have to
fire himself uh i'm just wasting time i've already made my traits for the day i don't need to do
anything else what do i need to do just win he's called me a scab buy coffee dark roast coffee
let's go long on it a million bucks into tomorrow a million bucks into tomorrow
i'm gonna hold it till tomorrow targets closed and now i am the vice president of the company
no problems nothing i'm good right this is statistically impossible i don't care what
they had access to there was no way they should have been able to match my thought process my
models my automations let me look at the data ready can't do that your security clients has
been revoked and all your passwords have been changed you're making a mistake just give me a
few minutes in the system figure it out i can medical insurance will expire in several weeks
i wonder if you might want to seek attention what condition on prescribed treatment might be
causing this level of paranoia i'm not paranoid it's not anxiety it's just that it's not the
drugs this is not my mind this is it's not this is the stock market mrs walker sometimes people
get lucky sometimes they're just better than you are no fucking way please leave the building
calmly if you don't i'll have to direct our security to search you closely report anything
be carrying the law enforcement this is awful congratulations you've been promoted to vice
president the only position left for you to rise towards is managing director at the entire firm
that would make you my boss there are a few vps vying for the position but my understanding is
that you and an old friend of yours are the candidates that the miller family office is
watching you got the attention of important people now be careful i'm gonna buy another
house i'm gonna sell this condo i'm gonna buy a house no i need cars i get a house and then
just sell and lease it i need cars all right i'm gonna buy a house tomorrow only ceo's work at
the company i need to make five million dollars okay i'm in the end game here i have to make five
million dollars i gotta drink some tea to calm me down here okay is that we back to normal
managing director and then fuck the company well we'll see it happens because i'm gonna make
i'm gonna make an insane play tomorrow and i'm gonna make five million dollars tomorrow i'm
gonna send in the lobbyists i'm gonna have the lobbyists send it down i'm gonna buy in at the
bottom like two million bucks and then i'm gonna send the lobbyists go up oh you versus ward what
an exciting showdown obviously i'm on your side don't tell her i said this but i've always thought
ward was such a snake she's such a tryhard she thinks she's so edgy if you got rid of her you
right so it all comes down to this never thought it would be you and me competing for managing
director i mean i knew it would be me and somebody else but not you sort of makes me regret
everything i've ever done to help you but i'm also a sucker for poetic justice question is
which one of us is going to be on the receiving end of it good luck pal the hopeful news today
it seems the civil war in bachador may finally be reaching an end
rebel and government forces are both severely weakened by conflict get out of that dividends
and i was left an estimated 57 000 people my god talks preparing for talks get out of this
sell it coffee got 3.6 million dollars this is a balkan and company ready for this shit
are you ready for this shit are you guys ready check this out 2.5 million bucks in coffee three
million bucks in coffee let's go send in i need to make 250 000 dollars i'll do that in my sleep
let's go well since this is probably going to be the end of our friendship i thought we might as
well go out with a bang what are you talking about i made some calls spent a few bucks and as of this
morning the two of us are untouchable until one of us wins this thing the pr harpies are on unlimited
retainers and the hall monitors at tic are looking the other way no matter what you do the public
opinion meter won't matter and you can break all the rules you want we're living in the good old
days all over again pal had a two-hour head start but you wouldn't believe the sex act i had to what
later set send in everybody into coffee no no no hurry hurry you just threw me off you just threw
me off so bad where's my stocks lobby lobby why can't i lobby what the fuck i can't lobby
i got 4.6 million i can't lobby now i can what the hell we're going back in coffee 2.5 million
million lobby eat shit lady i got five million bucks in this company let's go why did you believe
her oh shit yeah why would i believe her why would i believe a word she's saying no
oh i lose i i think i lose i think i just lost i think i just got i think i just got yeah i lost
is there anything i can do right now can i do anything right now to stop that
can i do anything is it maybe there's something i can do oh no i fell for it i fell for the bait
why would i fall for that i just i'll be something unrelated to coffee what's unrelated to coffee
what's the opposite of coffee water right what would be the opposite of coffee
e would i go go just send a bunch of people to wood what should i do i fell for it go to wood
where's wood is this wood i think this is wood all right so i'm gonna send no what should i do
anything what if i just make a bunch of dumb trades what do you mean like just trade yeah i
sold it oh i know i messed up i'm gonna make a really bad trade i just got played yeah i really
did i'm thinking i'm thinking uh green what do we got weapons toys i can't believe i got played
like that what an idiot did i do it and maybe i didn't do it enough to get the the federal
commission on me you diversify the portfolio all right i'm gonna go into aquafina we're going
we're going 2.5 million bucks into aquafina is it okay is it i didn't do any lobbying for this
what happened all right we're fine we're fine lobbying i didn't do any lobbying and i'm gonna
make money on on this shit produce god damn it come on water up get up god shit okay whatever
produce produce is already way too far way too high up 4.6 million i think i want to go back
into coffee food stuffs food stuffs food stuff water water water water i should have stayed in
water fuck why did i get out of aqua firma security why is water not going up anymore
security what manpower i don't know where's my stocks fuck sell you screwed it i died she
fucked with me go back in coffee go all in and copy this is the mega trade right here
i got 4.4 million dollars in this coffee company come on look at how shitty this is doing get
dividends in the coffee company let's go oh oh oh let's go get some coffee to celebrate
how much time is left in the day two hours i didn't even read this today i was too busy she
got in my head talking about like oh yeah everything's free you can fucking break every
rule in the book i didn't even need to look at that i'm down half a million but i'm gonna get
i'm gonna get seven hundred thirty thousand dollars for this it's too late lobby a lot
no i'm fine stop going down i'll be coffee heavily no oh bobby you're fucked for sure
i'm no i i think i'm fine i think i'm gonna be fine i'm gonna be fine i'm gonna get six
hundred thousand dollars from this trade all right here we go uh look coffee i'm just gonna
leave it i'm gonna leave it i'm not touching anything if i keep if i lobby i'm definitely
going to jail oh boy this is bad oh boy oh okay it was on the way back up she lost money too
how the fuck did you lose money wait hold on she wasn't lying how did we both lose money did we
both get scared she wasn't lying so then she got into my head i thought she was lying but then she
realized that she maybe maybe she had it wrong and she lost a bunch of money too all right well
okay i'm gonna buy another house and then i'm not gonna rent this i'm gonna i'm gonna wait till i
have some cars i can't believe that she was i thought she was lying at least this one for
41 000 a day i'm not gonna lease these ones till i have cars so we're gonna do cars next
that sucked okay well i'm down a lot of money chat really screwed you yeah they yeah you did
i was just gonna lobby the fuck out of the coffee company and you guys told me that she was lying
and then i i well now what happens tomorrow i think i was supposed to win right there
what do you have to do to make everything legal for a day how could that even be real
well i guess we don't have those people are walking around today like they've seen a ghost
whatever it is remember that a positive attitude is the key to success i've been
watching a lot of overseas pop music videos you can do it senpai thank you all right we've got
news coming in accusations thrown today after a field coup in the democratic republic of balcador
elected officials in the balcordorian congress claimed that agencies from the free state union
were behind a violent coup attempt on the eve of a peaceful agreement war back on the menu
our participants are denying the accusation claiming to know nothing wars back on the menu
where's war materials products weapons missiles what's the stupid coffee position
whoa whoa whoa why is this 1.5 million 1.1 million what's happening with coffee 7.8
this is five this 10 million get it out gap tell it i got 5.2 million dollars right now i'm calling
to either congratulate you or commismerate over how fucked we are based on the silence i'm guessing
this isn't you successfully getting me kicked off of geiss net it's down for both of us isn't it
hell probably down for everyone the fucking exorcist the exe exorcist again probably no
respect these guys don't they know that you and me are in the middle of a dramatic race to the top
would be interesting though we already had no rules and now we've got no cheats let's see who
really wants this right let's go we need i need missiles weapons where's weapons i need that
weapon company missile company i'll tell you who fucking wants this shit five million you put it
up what do you got what do you got right now what do you got what do you got make 250k on
free states companies keep going and now i need free state company 300 000 keep going 400 000 i
need to make five million lobbying isn't free today i'm only gonna do this one get out all right
fsu what do we got this dominion here i don't know what that means stocks we need fsu stocks
southern soda green grocers infinity mart infinity mart get up up up up up up up up up up up up up up
i'm going in all in go all in come on come on come on come on come on come on come on come on
come on a viral video has been seen several billion times has the video game business booming
all right well i'm i'm losing money in fucking walmart now come on 250 come on do it 250 250
250 250 250 250 it's going it's going it's not stopping 250 and i get the daily challenge
oh it's gonna go oh yes is it is it done that's it i win the daily challenge thank you
video games going up what else we got average is down way down construction up
currencies down starnucks look at starnucks it looks like starnucks in the dump what do you
say about going long on starnucks no no no let's wait for a big catalyst here i'm already ahead by
a lot alcador down short it let's go come on oh boy this is it this is gonna make me a million
keep going keep going this i want this to be at least half a million this might be the end here
okay uh two i'm gonna save right now no not yet no not yet not yet now the big trades today boys
and girls i will tell you we got video games short all video games yes regulations of video
game industry is ongoing oh no oh no oh this is this is it this is the big one it just went
up so high all right get out that's so much money these are all doing so well what about the next
catalyst i've got to be getting close i have probably have two million today not that long in
the trading day left what about starnucks uno eats what's that oh that looks awful don't be greedy
i'm not being greedy i'm going for it i wonder if i should lobby the balcador dollar no we gotta
do this legit uno eats i'm gonna play it smart i'm gonna i'm not gonna jump in anything stupid
no i'm none of these are taking off the balcador's shit is doing very badly dark roast coffee i think
this is where we go long on dark roast coffee for five million in in in plastics emergency
taxation to save the euro five hundred fifteen thousand dollars keep going okay okay all right
all right it's time to get out you know get out i'm done okay what's next beef buy fbr earthreal
don't ask why sure is it gonna make me money oh i don't know about this one a secret society if
you want no no no get out secret society told me to buy this oh you're fucking crazy what's next
what's coming up on the catalyst list biofuel look at that very bad bad bad bad bad bad
oh this looks bad beef will shorten beef we're sending the lobbyists to it
throw the absolute hell out of this incident lobby against big beef
no no no no no this is about to be done hold on let's go hey beef sucks switch to turkey
why is it still going up why are you going up why is it still going up i sent in the suits
and it's still going up go on fall fall fall fall this is gonna be a huge huge scandal here
with like big beef come on beef beef like everyone people are changing to be to be vegetarian
or something i don't know come on come on short it fall there we go that's what i like to see
you can't squash the beef yes you can and almost i don't want to stay in beef short i'm not gonna
get i'm gonna get screwed by beyond meat again you know i thought this is meat for a second i
was gonna shit my pants metals smartphones smartphones mobile companies mobile companies
buy them a viral video has seen several million times that the smartphones business booming
i don't as it's not even this is not even real what do you mean smartphone business is booming
right now 300 likes that's it get out oh oh you're gonna get crushed carol oh even
170 000 today wowie whoo start cleaning your office out getting too cocky yeah i am
okay i need another car damn it not quite there see i'm good let's keep going
tough day at the office trader not so easy to be in your line of work with
out geist net geist net what are you talking about what's geist net sure you all thought it
was hacktivism but no i'm afraid it was us we did enjoy watching all of you flare around without
it though i don't even know what you're talking about geist net geist net i've heard the kids
talking about that i'm too old for that shit you're under arrest for an insane number of crimes
most of which you've committed brazenly in the past few days in fact what the hell were you
thinking now tell me somebody in one of your foolish little contest tricked you into thinking
you were covered that's a problem with you people you think everything is a game and you've never
lost anything for real we've got something else to discuss something in the big bigger picture
shall we go digital testimony not authorized to speak with you until you acknowledge that this
computer is your lawyer consider it a preview of how much various cares about your problems
this is the best they were willing to do for you why do all these tech companies have such stupid
names anyways go ahead and click the big button that says agree these terms will be applied fully
and affect your usage of legal by using legal you agree to accept digitally signing these terms you
swear to use legal only to testify before any court in any jurisdiction truthfully
restrictions publishing legal whatever all right
ten minutes from now you're going to be called to testify in your own defense
i'm here to tell you the obvious you don't have a defense various lawyers don't have a defense
jesus christ does not have a defense not for you and you're a big enough fish to fry if you don't
want to work with us we can live with that personally there's nothing i would rather see
than you in prison for the rest of your life there are people who deserve to go down even
more than you do and you know exactly who i'm talking about millers the family office the names
beneath the name the more you make the closer to them you get it's the only way to reach people
like that and you're already off to a good start you can walk out of here today and go back to
ferrios like none of this ever happened the state will fake your trial i'll do my best to get the
agency to deal with your fine and you become a confidential informant to the trade and investment
this is not a negotiation you can help us take them down or you can take the fall yourself
what will it be is this a test yeah what what if this is a paid actor from the company it's
very possible this could be a paid actor and this is a test that guy seems pretty eccentric
and weird doesn't he no deal snitches this is a test you know yeah that means this is a test
you can trust him he has a fat ass do you want to i don't know i feel like this is like uh i feel
like this is a trick somehow i'm gonna say no i understand you think the family can save you
from all this and even the government trying to take you out ultimately work for them too
just like anyone but ask yourself this if they're really all so so powerful do you think they'll
give a second thought to sacrificing you the moment that you become an inconvenience
do you think they got to where they are by rewarding loyalty even when it hurts well i
guess it's all rhetorical at this point i guess you're going to find out i made so much money
for you i made so much money before court resumes i would like to apologize to the jury for the
substantial delays involved in this case numerous motions filed by council on both sides have
created unnecessary hindrances and this court has already had to give several citations for contempt
let me be clear any further attempts to administratively obstruct justice in
these proceedings will result in prison and disbarment have i understood yes your honor
yes your honor good because of the media attention surrounding these events it has been necessary to
sequester our new jury for several months however we are now prepared to proceed the prosecution
has called the vice president of ferrios capital management to testify average head phd just gave
50 community subs holy shit thanks for the 50 subs sub city that's right thanks a lot that's
a lot of money thank you your honor community subs as the defendant you've been called to testify
a result of the overwhelming evidence against you over the past several months you've made
substantial use of a dark web communication tool known as geiss net isn't where i do like the like
move my arms around like put my eyes rolling back my head i don't know what what is that for
this tool you were able to gain access to privileged information that enabled you to
act on a legal foreknowledge of the movement of several markets do you admit to it
your honor that sounds like a mega man that sounds like a map in mega man
this tool you're able to gain access privileged information that you know
no of course i don't admit it no i mean i mean maybe once i saw i looked over the shoulder of
somebody that was doing it no i have no idea what you're talking about because of a use of
insider information fair competition in the coffee market was destabilized do you understand
you were responsible for this air competition in the coffee market i was not responsible for
this what are you talking about you callously reaped tremendous profits from the crash of the
global gas and electric market a crash that left thousands of people in developing countries that
produced it unable to care for their families do you deny this i know i didn't do this wait no wait
i don't want to answer this wrong do you deny this i invoke my right to not respond on the
advice of counsel that i may incriminate myself but that means that means i did it i deny this
yes leading the fifth just means yes i did it in a different sentence most significantly the cascade
of all these actions resulted in nothing less than a civil war within the democratic republic
of balcador do you realize that you did this for your own personal gain is this the part of the
movie where i go yes yes it was yeah and i felt like my head starts spinning around i did it
and i could have gotten away with it too but this little legal council had and i have a
fucking big black cape on like a big top hat like no i'm gonna deny it you did you really do you
realize that you did all this for your own personal gain and nothing else no objection your honor none
of us are here to moralize on the social outcome of a free market these events could have taken
place regardless of whether or not they invested on behalf of the firm as they did the objection is
sustained council will limit themselves to matters concerning the specific little realities which
occurred with pleasure your honor as i mentioned we have overwhelming evidence of insider trading
through geist net i mentioned the implications only to demonstrate a complete lack of remorse
on the part of the defendant objection the evidence proves nothing about their state of mind
his employee was offered the opportunity to cooperate with the government to make amends
for their crimes and refused this person is a financial professional performing a task on
behalf of an employer no more responsible or directly connected to the state of the world
than the rest of us enough i will not have this trial devolve into the kind of circus that led
up to it again this court will limit itself to the rule of law the impact can be considered if and
when the client has been found guilty well they won't be the verdict you've been found guilty
of all charges please know that the jury wait did he just turn and say that to me please know
that the jury required 15 minutes to reach this verdict however given the scope of restitution
that could be made this court is determined you will be punished via financial penalty rather
than incarceration i hereby impose a fine of one million dollars payable immediately
holy shit that's awesome i have 10 million dollars in the bank your honor i wish to have it noted
that a penalty of this amount implies the expectation that ferrios will accept liability
on behalf of the employee and due to substantial liquidity problems at the moment i'm afraid that
ferrios will not be able to undertake this responsibility the employee will be forced
to pay the full amount from their personal account is that is that it can i go can i get back to the
desk your honor according to our evidence the defendant is perfectly capable of making this
payment from their personal account but your honor think of how little this will leave them
to begin the long and hard process of rehabilitating their character unfortunately it seems that a
substantial portion of the funds are overseas held in shell companies are otherwise difficult
to access fine i will put the matter to the defendant directly are you prepared to cooperate
with this court to retrieve the payment required i would say no nope i am not i am not prepared
yes take the take the million the matter is settled then the client will pay the amount
ordered and be released presently this court is dismissed i'm good i have like 4.8 million dollars
in my account you're still a millionaire they cracked you good huh you just lost more money
than most people will ever imagine well you know what they say easy come easy go with everything
you've done i'm sure you can get back there the worst is past us what do you say you want to come
back to ferrios tomorrow's a new day no time like the present yes i want to stay at ferrios
and i'm coming for you motherfucker oh you thought this big song and dance here you thought you could
gonna get me thought you were gonna get rid of me as i remember i was up four million dollars to
your measly one hundred and seventy thousand dollars and look where i am now and i'll be back
to the fucking office tomorrow and your ass is gone you hear me you'll never get rid of me
it doesn't matter what you do i will always win goodbye see you tomorrow you think it was
gonna take this you think this they think i was this was gonna shut me down see you tomorrow
yeah we'll see you there what happened on behalf of the company i want to thank you for doing the
right thing the amount of scrutiny that ferrios is presently under we are unable to render any
kind of payment which might be misinterpreted as compensating you for paying the fine however
please know that your loyalty and discretion in this matter has not gone unnoticed or unappreciated
when time is right you'll be rewarded handsomely for what you've done on a completely unrelated
unrelated note please send me a list of jurisdictions outside of the free state of
york dominion where you think you might enjoy permanent residency most of them really aren't
that bad not if you have the requisite amount of armed security servants and whatnot if you think
about it things here will probably be equally bad before too much longer and they've got better
beaches anyways give it some thought goodbye back in that fucking office i look sad today but don't
worry i'm through the worst of it i'm just thinking about how much suffering there is in the world
like have you ever heard about the stuff going on the box wait i already
i'm ready to do this we don't have an open trade in the coffee company
okay what we got what do i got i guess 7.4 million dollars they're lost 7.5 million let's go let's
go let's go back in the saddle back in it back in it back into smartphones are on the rise
smartphones lobby just do the lobbies again i forgot to buy i forgot to buy i forgot to buy
i forgot to buy i forgot to buy it's been i've been out of the office for too long
four same mistakes all right that's half a million oh shit let's go uno eats
oh my god this is going to be the first million dollar trade keep going go go go go go go go go go
go go go big money big money sell it charbucks going up smartphones down short them thrust them
thrust them thrust them thrust them thrust them thrust them thrust them my chest he's going back
to jail the next day the actual psycho prison speed run oh okay i gotta relax does it feel good
no it feels awful oh come on look it's still going i gotta trade on a catalyst the next catalyst
i'm going all in looks like it's it's smartphones took a dive smart they bounced back immediately
though i'll get tea no i don't eat tea the lobbying is not illegal using the this the this geist net
is all right next catalyst let's go it should be hey what a fucking weird ass world we live in
wait fsu soda mobile mobile mobile mobiles mobile phones let's go mobile phones let's go
keep going one million in one million it's going to go up to two million one point three million
one point four million one point five million one point one with six come on two million
that's good enough for me coal going down it's already down too much
lobbying is just is the weirdest thing to me why do we want outside companies to be able to go in
and like be like weird like snakes in our representative's ears ah yes you see you see
into the coal coal you need to get involved with coal pass the legislation for coal what did that
say danger zone oh all right i got one more trade to make it's gonna go down a little bit more we
can you know make lobbyists go take go go go take care of that give me the bonus i want that daily
challenge coffee coffee going up i think i got the i think i'm gonna win i'm gonna become the
president of the company now even though i got the neutral ending or whatever the hell that was
oh that's going crazy somebody said smooth cigarettes smooth cigarettes are you talking
about whoa that why oh this is going down down down down down close this trade out for the day
i'll take 10 million in cash do a cigar in one drag i don't even cough all right did i win i got
the daily challenge oh my god it's been seven hours all right i'm done that's fun i got really
sucked into this game this is a lot of fun i'm so glad somebody made a game like this
even though it's like you know it's a little wacky right i'm not buying anything else i'm
done for the day like this this is cool this is exactly what i wanted this is what i wanted for a
video game like i why can't a company like this get like 50 million dollars to make a full game
about this rather than like a two to three hour experience i want like a i i want like a full
market and i yeah i could just make like a paper trading account but it's more fun when it's just
fake video game shit i just took a screenshot please don't stop being fucked up out there
i have no idea how i'm gonna hit okay i only need three and a half million more dollars to
win the game i get i've no i get no money they took it all from me they literally took all my
assets all right one more trading day and i'm done i'm not done yet i got i can make three
million dollars tomorrow read is good read is good have a bonus leave the scene that person
made yesterday afternoon when they got let go people act like their job is their whole life
you're so unhappy with things why don't find a new hobby love yourself first
t i'm making the the i'm making the most omega trade it's time for an omega trade
i have 10 million dollars we're gonna go to what's what's a beaten down stock hello it's
quinn miller oh another thing i forgot to say can you believe how bad we got hacked
whole system is all messed up and i i leave me alone all right we're going for an omega trade
whatever is going to whatever skyrocketing let's you know what i'm drinking this the other tea
because whatever is get skyrocketing i'm gonna throw lobbies at and put all my money in it
okay here we go what whatever happens here i'm doing 10 million bucks get it ready we're gonna
look for something horrible like a huge spike and i'm gonna jump on it i'm gonna dump
every cent into it like for instance launches a new advertising campaign
ah ah that's not a big deal i'm looking for the red one i need to make three to four million
dollars today and i get the next ending is this just free play um it i still had that screen
showing me that helped my progress to being the ceo okay here we go new safety standards
for munitions industry workers escalate prices no no it's not really a big deal
innovation breakthrough in construction product carrier loses surge in demand
what do you think by going on this one and then just going crazy with lobbying
start of war no no nobody cares about this public finance crisis casts fear
ah we're gonna short taboola beef this is it this is the big one this is the big one here this is it
five seven hundred thousand this is big problem here come on one million i need to get like a two
to three million dollar trade lobbying i just did i already did sounds like half of the place is in
oh get out buy me state subsidies will be granted in the meat business i was gonna say these people
in the background sound like the resident evil four villagers okay that was a 1.2 million i need
like another big million plus dollar trade i'm gonna settle need a big catalyst come on i just
want to get to the ceo position i'll be done and one of them goes i don't even know what it
says i don't know what they say but it's something like that it's not i love it i love it instruction
come on give me another catalyst i want to make another million just sell more money i need to get
another 1.5 million something else has to happen all right i'm drinking coffee fuck it let's go
i'm not in a trade am i i hope not sienna sienna oh i can't i can't i can't yes i can
keep going up no shit too fast produce produce beverages produce go lobby produce
meat oh that's gonna be that's a sympathy play that's a produce is a sympathy play to me
i went i'm the new ceo i am now the new ceo that was a pretty good old mega trade yeah now short
meat not a bad idea imagine the lobbyists go in and lobby for everyone to care about the meat
industry and then they come in like a few days later or the same day and they say no no no fuck
meat you don't want that shit we should get rid of all meat no i got out too quickly meat industry
embarrassed by canceled camera video of management meeting what i didn't orchestrate this i'll take
it though 369 391 oh i'm dead there's no way i'm not the ceo of the company half a million i win
yeah there's no way balkador anything balkador go meat oh my god meat what the hell yeah should
i jump back on meat 4.5 million all right i have that's four and a half million triple a games
oh i'm stepping away get away get away i'm done i win i win i i'm the ceo of the company now
means i can do stuff like this smash smash smash smash i didn't mean to throw that at you
hang on here what the fuck is this there's how many that's illegal they got that's not fair you
have like five people trading at the same time but that's why you thought you're gonna be ceo
that's illegal that's an illegal move peak trading she no no no yeah she's just trading super fast
where's the bill oh okay okay it's over high frequency trading all right let's go
i'll take it thank you very much oh shit i need more money i'm going to jail see you later
i'm fine i'm all right i just need four million more dollars shit yeah yeah it must be nice yeah
i'm sure you'll have far more enjoyable night than the crisis communications team we had to
pull the deal with all the negative public attention your work continues to gather
also without saying that nobody cares about the happiness of pr people but these firms are
outrageously expensive smarten up this is the last time i'm gonna be polite about this all right i
got one more chance i'm gonna be his boss tomorrow anyways who cares it just keeps increasing germa
you can't win wait is that for real everybody the way what are you talking about that's not
true is it you serious leave me alone it's not true wait i'm confused i'm just i'm waiting for
the bill what five million more dollars no one has played this game don't listen to them
oh i'm gonna do this one more day and if it increases again then all right
cold oh electronics we're going in i went all in on electronics fsu how can fsu be going up and
down at the same time if it ends right no shit how can fsu be going up and down at the same time
electronics i can't do it oh fuck electronics come on i can't lobby i don't have no money
i'm down a million dollars so far it's okay electronics are going up electronics let's go
what is this bullshit this is bullshit come on fsu oh boy oh this is it this is it this is the end
here oh yeah this is it fsu and electronics both going up the same time this is five million
dollars trade let's go they stay in or should i get out i'm staying in five million five point
two oh electro gear oh boy this is the if i don't get ceo from this one i don't know what will
six point four million six point seven million seven million dollars let's go boys and girls get
it to ten holy shit it was like sometimes like the games was real life this would be cool this
would be awesome and i'd thank nine million dollars this is that would be fucking awesome
like why can this be real let's make it real like this is real right that's a 10 million dollar
trade i win you almost got arrested video games just went up this is sympathy play watch this
electronics are gonna see sympathy from video games going up this is more than my entire
fucking net worth here what do i have oh no it's not 27 million can i do more than my whole net
worth what was it 12 13 what was it 15 all right i'm out it's a 14 all right walk indoors going
down that means the free state union goes up 15 million come on and i'm just gonna go pound
coffee to the end of the day let's see 15 now no that's it get out the 14 million dollars
trade i'll see you later oil going up food stuff now we're gonna play we're gonna play nice
potato pc cafe get a little bit why not that didn't work out so good sorry public opinion
it's fine i only did lobbying once so it's not going to go down to zero
let's just pound some coffee and get the fuck out of here i only lobbied one time
and i only sent two people not four i've been staring at the coffee machine for like 45 minutes
floor is closing all right i'm ceo i win oh come on yeah it's it's the never-ending
it's never-ending all right br i think uh it's never-ending all right fine i got the bad ending
i got my 15 million dollar trade they can't catch me if i leave out the back door oh get up before
the boss sees me oh i didn't say go home but boss look at how much money i made us i brought in 25
million dollars you have your pr team working on it i brought in the firm 25 million dollars
the dick i tried to throw paint on me after i pepper sprayed the fuck out of him the cops told me he
was motivated by some viral internet post about some stock you picked now it fucked something up
somewhere i did the post and it had been made by some uh uh okay who writes young adult novels
it had been shared like 500 000 times she's getting a talk show this is what our lives have
to come to being in the crosshairs of the ugly and unemployed because of you because you can't
keep public opinion about us or out of the toilet a word of warning the more philosophical corbin
gets above this kind of shit the closer you are to getting up you're in trouble past a certain
point away and we can save you i still win remember why did you write this all right that's it that's
it it's just it's just free play i got my ending and now it's free play it's not yes it is it keeps
going up that was that looked like rip taylor just drank coffee for four days well i'm gonna
do a 25 million dollar trade i'm gonna try to get 30 million dollars on one trade i need tea
no i don't me a catalyst come on i'm ready to go all in at 25 million i'm not going to lobby
this time i promise i'm gonna do it legit come on catalyst catalyst catalyst let's go
already 10 30 what's going on any company in sienna right now sienna company come on come on
down down down down down no lobbying i don't need to lobby see look at that i got 25 million in
this right here i'm not gonna lobby why would i do that now i need food stuffs to take a shit
uno eats needs to have a huge scandal i needed to take a dump nope nope okay
okay okay that was very bad okay he's shorting your viewership he's thinking
i don't i don't care all right what was your aqua firma let's go meat short meat everything
everything how high is this guy i don't know not high no i gotta find the right one to go into
security security going down security new regulations are holding the security business
back come on how am i gonna get my multi-million dollar trade you already had a multi-million dollar
trade i know but i want a multi multi-million dollar trade meat oh that would have been awesome
if i had a short on meat sound stop the sound from playing quiet oh i gotta get up in the dust
greed is good no it's not manpower what should i do manpower you got it let's go 25 million
gone all the way to four bucks fsu oh shit nope eight hours incoming no i'm done after this i'm
out i'm done sure you're so close am i though oh you gotta go past four days all right fine i'm
just gonna pound coffee for four days after this you are raising the bar for the girl every day
it's not your goal the competition ends in three days oh okay i've been doing too well
well then i'm just gonna go drink coffee now yeah fuck it whatever i'm just gonna drink
coffee for like five days invest in coffee first whoa what do you mean oh shit she's
she's gaining on me i can't just take a drink drink coffee all day shit i can't drink coffee all day
she's halfway there is it because there's four of her it might be because there's four of her
they just tallied up three times of what she was doing over the course of the day
i've just got started skipping everything she says all right here we go i gotta i have to keep
trading i'm almost done i'm gonna be i'm gonna do a huge trade and then quit what are we going in
livestock no wood wood is way you got a hint about a danger zone during a party
you can click on the what i don't know i don't know walking are going down
smartphones oh shit i just bought the top get out wait is it is am i in coffee time right now
all right livestock i can do a little bit of lobbying here all right we're going to go into
a business that's pretty dead coffee yeah look at this we're going all in on coffee and i'm
going to lobby it i'm going 30 million dollars into coffee um what's going on what's this doing
what's happening i'm all in on coffee here we go i'm only going to do this once wish that was coffee
okay coffee just a little bit just a little bit of lobbying not a whole ton not crazy
just enough for me to beat her why am i losing money what's going on the price is going up it's
short oh my fucking god buy back what's happening what do you mean buy back uh what happened
i'm what why buy it back what's going on what's happening cancel no buy back i don't know what's
going on i'm down money what's happening what happened it's like the game is like lagging
the game like where are my positions i best you i just made it all back fuck this let's go i don't
even care if i go to jail you can fire me if you want fuck you what's happening pull them back pull
them back pull them back pull them back pull them back get out get out get out pull them back
i just snapped 135 000 dollars what the hell it's too slow
all right i'm done i can't do this anymore i'm out of this i'm done it's too much i'm done i'm done
it's over it's over it's over it's over i i don't care if i lose i just i why do i have to do this
short on it i lost a million dollars on that stupid trade bingo that's another million i'll
take it you're gonna regret this if you don't finish i wish i could just keep it on 25 million
all right another catalyst plastics down get out plastics going up public finance crisis in the
balkador come on oil we need oil to go down this game lagging yeah it's this awful money sound
because it's in slow motion i need gas to go down oil and gas down it's gonna double whammy
come on public opinion is not good i might get fired gas go down this is a big trade this will
keep me ahead of her i need gas to go down though like but the whole industry needs to go down
all right get up all right drink coffee that's it that's enough
oh no don't do that it's i'm at times 10 speed okay how insane i felt this whole stream since
we went to this game can you imagine if you did this every day if you were like a day trader and
this is what you did your hair would fall out you would not have hair left you'd have like bags
under your eyes and shit this would be horrible oh shit i'm almost there i didn't leave anyone i
didn't leave a million more dollars all right only two more days did i say go home i buy house
sell this condo all right i'm good i live in this house i have two more days until this is over so
again we're gonna we're gonna do one big like two to three million dollar trade and then i'm
gonna drink coffee all day eight hours yeah i know but i've told you this before if i'm gonna
stream once a week then i can sit here for i can be here for eight hours it's fine i don't i don't
have a problem with this all right i'm ready big trade i don't need tea for this one all right
where am i going what's the play wood i didn't i didn't believe that i thought this was from
yesterday does the public sentiment look like i can't do any lobbying today come on give me
something i can lobby tomorrow look how much she has um we're gonna do that don't lobby tomorrow
either she's gonna lose money today i'm not concerned when he said the reason why i keep
getting called by quinn is because these are up on the screen i missed out and i and i missed out
on this looking at my goddamn screen up top she probably caught that trade wonderful big missiles
come on what is this bullshit up come on come on come on i don't like those dumps what is that what
is that what is that excuse me excuse me excuse me i just got fucking what the fuck i just got
dumped they just swept me shit god damn it construction i didn't even i didn't even
fucking see it i'm just gonna go drink coffee fuck this lady i don't even care i got it in a
it's a lock i don't care there's no way she's gonna make 10 million dollars in one day where's
her desk didn't she sit right here throw stuff at her mess her up there's no way that she beats me
it would take it was taking a christmas miracle yeah she's at night i win this game over i win
she's at 19 million i'm at 28 million goodbye i win see you later competition ends tomorrow no
way she makes 10 million dollars in one day go home goodbye what does i what i just do i just
leased my own house we'll get a condo and live there we're just gonna drink coffee and celebrate
in the room until she locks herself in puts on her headphones puts like drake on and just like
gets in the zone and beats me i'm gonna be walking around the office like oh shit i'm gonna be the
ceo all right shaking hands they have like a big party hat on all right there's no way she gets
10 i just can't lose 10 million dollars that's it we're going in on balkador we're going down
a short on balkador right when we get okay coffee no what should i short balkador the drilling
company no that's already way too far down balkador gas company i don't want to long it i want to
short it you fucking idiot misclick oops fuck oh my god i'm so annoyed right now i'm just
fuck her i'm just drinking coffee i don't care
imagine going to work and you just you sit down you press one button two buttons you down 500 grand
you just get up and drink coffee and leave it's um well i don't care i win she needs eight million
dollars it's not gonna fucking happen she's not gonna make eight or nine million dollars today
it's not happening it's almost as hard as streaming i don't know man looking at this screen like this
and then putting your money in it and watching it go up and down and fucking drop and shit and
like losing and gaining this would be fucking terrifying to do this every day i don't like
look i i've trade i've traded i've invested plenty of times i i trust me but i could not do it every
single day i could not every day for like 10 years straight do this i don't i couldn't do it
oh puke it's like investing in companies right oh i think this company might do well i think this
company might do well yeah i'm willing i'm willing to buy those shares and like hold it for a while
or maybe trade whatever like holy fuck just like okay okay short bye bye i just like eight grand
right now whatever um i'm up fourteen thousand dollars on this trade here i couldn't do it no
fucking way no way doing that every day oh i got if you can do that and you can do it well oh my
goodness good for you i you i cannot day trade no fucking way not a million years if trading
bots will do it automatically i win oh it just ends in 10 days what the fuck are you talking
about why am i still here what happened undefined street underground street fighting thing what is
happening later trader what guys get to 30 million it's not going to do anything no that's not it's
that's it it's not gonna never ends that's it i'll see you guys next week we're gonna play
resident evil village next week saturday and sunday i'm assuming it'll be four or five hours
on saturday four or five hours on sunday we're gonna do it should be fun i've heard very good
things about it thanks for watching the stream i like this game a lot i've been looking for a
game like this it's good by the way nothing in this stream was financial advice you gotta
make that very clear nothing i said in the stream was advice on any securities trading
okay good here come the subs thanks the subs everybody that was fun barn finders was fun but
i like this was i had much more fun in this game i think it just kind of speaks to me a little more
i think time to day trade and lose millions no no i don't want i would never want to day trade on
stream because oh i'm gonna put a certain amount of money into an account and just like broadcast
it and look at look at me doing trades every day i don't want to if because let's be honest
if i were to do that and i you saw me buy something or you saw me sell something and
people would kind of do the same thing oh let's jump in on this i don't want that to ever be a
possibility i don't think that i don't like that at all i don't like the idea of like oh he bought
it so then i bought it and it actually like actually went down and we actually fucking lost
money that i don't want that's not going to happen no way yeah i wouldn't want to do that
market manipulation yeah i am not no no thank you no thanks don't want to do that don't want
to get involved with that you're an influencer i'm not doing it this is not me announcing that
stream uh thanks for watching that was a lot of fun see you next week for resident evil
as an evil uh village take care of yourselves good night as always have a great week we'll
see you for a full weekend good night everybody take care of yourselves