Zeus, Odin, Agni. Oh, it's gonna be hard. I'm so bad with Agni. I am terrible with Agni.
All right, boo. How do you play Agni? Tell me in like five steps or less. Oh shit, okay.
You stun by putting your one down and then putting any of your fire abilities on top of it.
And then your two is a short-range damage ability. Your three is a dash. Your four is your meter.
Oh dear.
All random, all middle.
Star's gonna be spying on us. What is with this item menu? How do I just find items?
Alright, I'm just gonna get boots, I think. I don't know. I've never played Agni, ever.
Anybody but Agni. I wouldn't say, I wouldn't say, get anyone out of y'all guys, but.
Remember. Yeah, I've seen you play Hevo before.
Consumable.
Well, I actually spec'd the first one, right? Okay. Alright, so what should I get? My two first, two late. I already did it.
Yeah.
Look at this. Look at this map. This map is insane. Yeah, it's cool.
I wonder how much gold you get a second. So you cannot recall. I have no idea what I'm buying. I'm just gonna buy stuff.
Oh, but you got Ares. It's not too terrible.
Yeah, he's okay. I would have preferred, uh, I would have had Agni any day.
I know. Can we like change characters? Like I would be more comfortable with him. Oh god, the confusion sets in.
Anybody but Agni. You know what? I'm just going in. You want to go in?
I'm scared. I can't find this book. I'm following this build guide and I can't find this book. Who's Poseidon?
No, Gavin's Poseidon. No, I wish I had. God. Gavin, you better carry.
Magical power, maybe. So wait, Gavin. Alright, here we go. There we go. I found. Okay. Do we get lanes? Yeah, we get lanes. Okay.
I have to read up on my build. I've never played Hevo before.
Basically, yeah. Yeah, really really squishy. That's what I know. Star has Agni too. Level up to 3 and you won.
Yeah, okay. Your 3 is the safest move. Yeah, I expect that first.
Alright, let me get a nice. Oh my god. Oh god. Star, are you still on the call? Star's taking a beating.
Oh, did Star drop out of the call to like not hear our strats? Oh, that monkey. I think he's here. He's just like spying on us.
Okay, everybody move in now. Uh oh. No, not moving. What do you mean moving now?
I was trying to trick Star.
So do you have to die? Like you have to die, right? Yeah.
God, I don't. How the hell do you play Agni?
That monkey, bro. Yeah, that monkey is strong. Save your monkey for when the minions are dead.
Because then you can get. That's what I've been doing, yeah.
Look at these minions. These minions are crazy looking. They're like demons. Look at this guy. Yeah, they're demons. They're god damn demons.
Here comes an Agni, rogue Agni, dashing through. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, get punished him. Punish him. Punish him. Yeah, Gavin. Yeah, high res Gavin. Go on, Gavin.
Clean it up. Ow.
So we gotta get both towers and then, okay. Oh my god, they go to Zeus.
This is gonna take a while, I feel like. This is gonna be like an hour long game.
Dancing around so much. Here comes Cage.
No.
Oh god, that was horrible. Get that, son of a bitch.
Get that Ramana.
Jesus. Oh, yeah. Oh.
I got a kill.
Yay.
I got someone. There you go. There you go.
Get him. Get him. Good job, boo. Looking good. Looking good. Looking good.
Oh god. Oh, that Zeus is just doing so much damage.
It hurts.
All right, so get. We gotta get two towers.
Holy. Oh my god. We gotta get high enough level where they're dead. Yeah. For a long time.
Holy sheep shit. This is gonna be tough.
We got this. I need more mana. Right. Is it just Zeus? Is it just Zeus?
Boo's running. He's gonna try to suicide, but Zeus is chasing him.
Get that. Get that, son of a. Get him. Boo, turn around.
Boo, turn around. Hit him once. Oh, I got him. I got him. I got him.
Boo's just like running into the tower.
I was wondering what you were doing.
I mean, if you feed the kill to the tower, then they don't get any XP or gold for it.
Are you sure? But he wasn't hitting me. I'm too tanky.
It's like four towers.
We should all build stone of Gaia so we just have permanent health regen.
Oh, I'll get bracer replenishment. There we go. That'll be good. That's perfect for me.
You should probably buy. Oh, going in on the Agni. Going in on the Agni.
Nice.
No, I'm in the cage.
He'll die fast. What? Can't believe I got him. Can we get him? Nice.
He jumped out. Oh, that was pretty good. Oh, I'm going down. See you later.
Oh boy, whole team.
This is gonna get really interesting really quickly here. We gotta go magical. Where is this the hootie?
There you are. We got magic.
Yeah, that's that Zeus is doing a lot of damage. I'm following this one guy that may just be crap, but
it's better than nothing.
Uh-oh, they're on the tower.
I'll make it happen, boo. Make it happen. I'm on the move. Make it happen. Back to the action, baby.
Uh-oh, boo. Be careful. Get that kill on him.
Yes.
Good job, boo. All right, we're up. We're up. You're going big.
Oh, we got it. We got it. That Harry's bro. Damn.
Get a move on. I don't want to. All right, it's Kelly.
All right, we oh boy. There it goes.
That was my bad.
Get out of here.
Uh-oh, big baby.
How did I not? Oh, she ages. I'm so bad.
Oh, no. Oh, I'm dead.
It hurts. Get that Agni. Just hit him.
Oh, come on. Nice job.
Ah, he can't go back. Yeah, we got to attack that tower now. Yeah, they get three down.
I wish one of us had a damn heal.
Yeah, I'm getting bracelet replenishment. I should have got that earlier. I didn't think regen would be as important as it would be.
Stone a guy it would be. Oh god.
Are we going to get the tower? Ah, it hurts. It hurts. Get that tower, Talix.
I'm tanking it. I can't tank it.
It's almost down. It's almost down. Meditation would be okay in this mode.
Yeah. Let's go with some defense.
I got some medias.
That Kali is going to eat media. That Kali keeps killing me.
Well, we're going to have five down here. I got that.
How did I miss? Oh,
come on.
I'm trying. It's just me and her.
It's just me and the Kali.
Yeah, say goodbye to your lane, bro.
Not sure if this is the best call, but I'll try it. That's right. Damn it.
Void stone.
I'm coming back. I'm pushing her up, pushing her up. Here comes Vamana.
What if there was a fire giant?
Jerm, I'm coming. Help me.
Kali's almost dead.
Her heal is pretty damn good, though.
I need to wait for these things to charge up.
All right, coming back.
I'm going to try and hit Kali.
We're going to put some damage on this tower. We're going to punish.
Mayjack's Blessing is expensive.
Ah, it hurts. It hurts.
Oh, Lord.
It hurts when I pee.
Oh, Gavin.
Gavin.
You three dudes, I'm coming.
Okay, listen.
Damn, I got her. Nice.
Get me the hell out of there.
Oh, God. I may.
No.
Fancy footwork. Fancy footwork.
Got the stun. I got the stun.
Get the Odin first.
Oh, nice wave.
Let's go with the Rod.
And Krone spin it.
One more. One more.
Kill this Agni, and then we'll push tower.
Oh, you guys are going to get it? You guys are going to get that tower?
Damn it. I missed.
Get start.
Why are we pushing?
Oh, that's a DSI. That's a DSI. Get the tower.
Go, go, go, go, go.
There's blue. I need my heals.
Oh, there's so much time.
There's so much time right now.
Oh, God. But I'm dead, though.
You guys are all so dead.
Look at that wave.
Lovely region.
Boo, you have to, right?
Yep.
Just do it. You have to, right? Even if you die.
Even if you guys die, this tower should go down.
Oh, Callie's up.
I'll retreat.
No.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't.
Get down.
Good job. Good job.
Beautiful.
I think we can kill him.
Now run.
I'm up.
Let's jump.
Oh, good job.
Good job, guys.
There we go.
Big plays.
Oh, yeah.
Here comes Zeus.
He's real angry. He wants a double.
Yeah, it's pretty much it's all about the just going in.
Even if you die from the tower, it's still it's it's worth it because
you have to get the towers down.
All right. We just don't want to all wipe and give them full free reign to do the same thing back to us.
So we got to try to stay alive.
Oh, get tripled.
That's me.
All right, guys.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
I came out and Insta died.
I did get I did help, though.
I'm killing.
That's what I'm doing.
I think Boo's killing.
Oh, Boo.
I'm here to fight it.
Well, that was unnecessary.
Oh, come on.
One hit.
Got her.
I need to buy an Aegis.
All right.
I'm going to regenerate it.
You're there.
All right.
The Odin's pretty low.
Ah, missed.
If I if I chain him, he'll die.
Oh, nice.
He's done.
I've got to make this happen.
Can't you use the portal in this one?
That's what I was wondering if you could use a portal somehow to get back.
You probably can.
If I can just catch this guy.
They got three down.
Three down.
Agnestead.
Yep.
Oh, we got to get them all here.
Got to get them all here.
Nice.
Now we push.
That's it.
We're going to get it.
We're going to get Phoenix.
Somebody's got to come up a few seconds.
We got Zeus in six seconds.
Zeus in six seconds.
Zeus will die.
We'll just we'll just smash Zeus.
All right.
Let's go.
Come on minions.
I'm on the move.
Get to Phoenix.
I got I got a minions.
I got a minions.
Here comes Zeus.
Oh, that hurt.
I'm on the move.
Now it's just the Minotaur.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Ow.
He's detonating.
Waiting first.
Was he got a bunch of cooldown reduction?
No, he's just detonating before his.
Should we dive the Minotaur?
What do you think?
Do we just dive the Minotaur?
I don't know.
Boo's pretty weak.
Jerma's pretty weak.
I know.
But I mean, I'm going to drop some medias on him.
We're going to have fire minions soon, too.
Guys, I'm coming in hot.
Oh, jeez.
Plus the Minotaur's not too right now.
Oh, boo.
I almost killed him.
Did you get anyone?
I almost got the Zeus.
They can't regen, though.
They can't regen.
So that's fine.
Oh, boy.
Bang.
I'm already in one.
Good job.
Oh, I'm caged.
I'm caged.
Just run around.
Don't run away.
Just fight him.
I can't.
All right, go for the Zeus.
He's more dangerous.
I mean, you don't have to.
We're about to die.
Actually, just fall back here.
Yeah, I'm falling back.
Run.
Damn it.
I got my charge.
All right, you want to go in on the Zeus?
Oh, wait.
No, crap.
I just don't want to get caged.
Oh, the Zeus.
I'm going on the Zeus.
I'm going to kill the Zeus.
There's an Odin coming behind you.
Well, there's Ulster.
One more.
Did I get him?
Got him.
There you go.
Yep.
Oh, boy.
You're dead.
No, I'm not.
Don't say it.
I'll just kite around.
Kite around.
Go, go, go, go, go.
All three.
He's going to die.
Get that kill.
Oh, my God.
There you go.
All right.
I need to, what do I need?
I have shits on a gold.
I know, me too.
You get full gold a second.
All right.
Let's go with Sprint.
So we both have what, one down?
They got two down.
Me and Gavin versus all three of these guys
ain't going to fly.
I got no health.
Yeah, that's the idea.
That's kind of the thing.
I'm just dropping medias around.
I'm dropping medias around the corner.
I just did so much damage.
I just did so much damage to like two or three of them.
Get a stun.
Oh, no.
You just run away from me.
Yeah, I'm going to die.
Oh, we're in trouble.
We're in a lot of trouble here.
I just got back.
Let's use.
Ah, he hurts.
No, he doesn't.
Never mind.
Damn it.
I'm trying to wait for the opportunity for my ulti.
I don't.
You just got to go right through somebody.
Nice one.
Nice cracking.
Get him.
Star's the only one left.
He could pull off something crazy.
Get the kill.
They just flame lift.
There we go.
He's dead.
All right, let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
This is our moment, guys.
We have so far to go.
You know that you walk faster on my water, right?
Yep.
Now we do, yeah.
Don't worry, guys.
I'll be there momentarily.
There we go.
We got two seconds on Kali being up.
This is going to be so difficult.
Oh, Phoenix is...
Where's our Phoenix?
We haven't had a Phoenix regen the whole game.
Oh, my God.
She's solo.
I almost killed her with that.
I got her with the tick.
Sick.
All right, we got a key.
They're all about two more about to come back up.
The mana and Odin.
This is it.
It's going down.
Let's get it.
Do everything.
Oh, baby.
Did we kill her?
Yay.
Good job, guys.
Seriously.
It's intense.