Good afternoon. Hello, everybody. It is me, Jettemy. Good to see you again.
Whoa, what was that? I went like, whoa. All right, the chair is on a weird spot because of the Wii U.
What the fuck? Did I just break it? Did I? What? No, we're good. What the hell?
Yeah, sorry I'm a little late. I was ready to go at two, but the lights were flickering.
It looked like a power outage was coming. We're getting some high winds.
So the lights were going like, and I didn't want to turn the stream on to have the power just turn
off in 20 minutes. So it seems like it's fine. I think it's good. Just wanted to make sure we
weren't going to get interrupted. Now, wouldn't it be funny if I waited, you know, 45 extra minutes
to stream and it just does it anyways in like 20 minutes from now? So we'll see. I don't know.
I think we're going to be fine. Well, that will be wicked funny.
You're jinxing it. I know this is not like an elaborate routine.
I promise this is not an elaborate routine. So today we're going to play Slime Rancher.
It's a game that came out a long time ago, but I didn't care because it was it was not on Steam.
Right. So and now that it is like a year or two ago or something, it was on Steam.
Like I'm talking a long time ago when it first came out, it was on Steam.
Yeah, no, it wasn't on Steam like a long time ago when it first came out, literally five years ago.
Was it on Steam when it came out? What game am I thinking of? Is there another game that's
like this that came out on like the Epic Game Store first? It's like a completely different game.
Outer Wilds? Is every like is every game that comes out? Maybe.
But what does that have anything to do with Slime Rancher?
Was it maybe it was a crime rancher?
Gooblets? Maybe. I don't know. I must be thinking of a different game.
I didn't play this when it came out for some reason. I don't know why.
I thought it was because it wasn't on Steam and I was too lazy to get the other platform.
Anywho, Slime Rancher today, I will tell you since our last meeting that I have started the
process of potentially doing a GTA RP. Something and maybe talking to some people, getting that
going. But that will probably maybe the next few weeks or something, try to get involved,
have some fun, make a couple characters, or just one character that I play for literally two or
three days. And then they get run over by a train. I don't know. I'm hoping, the goal is
to have a character that eventually just gets run over by a train. Then I just don't ever play
it again. Oh, Freddy subs. Freddy dread subs. It's the 20 subs. Too many subs. Too many. Thank you
though. That's a ton of subs. And thanks. No, I'm not gonna say that because I don't want people
to do that. The pre-streamers will know I was about to do like, hey, thanks for the...
But I'm not going to address that. Not enough subs.
But all right, let's play. Let's see how Slime Rancher is. I have no idea.
Create a new game. Okay. We're going to go with a... We're going to go with a Jettami. Adventure
sounds good. Choose a save icon. Does this matter? I feel like I'm in a weird seat right now. I'm
leaning forward. Let me get a little closer. Yeah, I feel like I'm hunching forward to read
this. Why? It's better, right? Yeah. Choose the Catboy? No. Jerma Sun? Jerma Cinnabon?
Jerma Water Droplet? Jerma Sly Cooper? Jerma Golden Pea? Jerma Carrot? I like Jerma...
Jerma Isaac Bomb? Which one speaks to me right now?
Water Balloon? This doesn't matter. Who cares? I'm gonna pick this one. I'm gonna pick the most
scrumptious cake. I feel like this guy right now. Oh, stop! Somebody help me! Where... I...
The Neelix scrumptious cake clip. I need it. I need to see it. Somebody... Does somebody have it?
There's been nowhere like a timestamp of him doing that. I need it. A thousand light years away from
Earth on a planet known as the Far Far Range, Bellatrix Lestrange began her journey. Okay.
Whatever that was. You made it up. No, I didn't. I didn't make... I... Somebody... I... There was...
That's on the second channel. On the second Jerma channel, somebody found the clip that I was...
I've been referencing for years. Somebody found it. One of the editors and put it in the beginning
of a video. And Neelix comes over with the cake and he's like, here is a delicious scrumptious
cake. It's the one I... It's not a mandala... No, it's not a mandala effect. It's not. It exists.
It is real. W A S D is move. Cool. Spacebar jump hold is sprint. Oh, cool. That's a really fast sprint.
You shoot these? Your vac pack can vac things up and store them in the vac tank. Your vac pack
can vac things up, store them in the vac tank. Your vac pack can vac things up and store them
in the vac tank. Your vac pack can vac things up and store them in the vac tank. Cool.
Look at Kirby. I almost said Kirby the hedgehog. Your vac pack can vac things up and store them
in the vac tank. Slimes are key to your success. Shoot slimes through a coral barrier into the
coral on the ranch. Okay. Select vac tank and then shoot. So you suck them up and you put them in the
little area. You vac'd a slime. Cool. Very cool. Slimes are key. Shoot slimes through a coral
barrier into the coral on the ranch. That's what I'm supposed to do. Do I have to hit the star?
Did it, right? Looking for a coral reef. Okay. So that you suck up slimes. You can only have one
spot. One slime per spot. Okay. You got it. You got it. You got it. You got it. You got it. You got
it. You got it. Do you got it? Thank God somebody's got it. I need to hear this. Yes. Okay. I need to
watch this right now. You guys, everyone thought I was fucking crazy. Everyone thought I was crazy.
I am not crazy. I need to see it. I have to get it on here. Where is it? Where is it?
Where was it? No, that's not. Where was it? We can use a tractor beam. Nobody use that.
Nobody use that. You'll be in big trouble. Do I click on it? Let's just watch this.
Or do you cheer? Open the clip again. Which one? I feel like you try because you don't want to boo
because they're doing the song there. You're there. You're a big fan of the band.
This guy's ruining everything. I feel like it'd be like, I don't know, every like four or five
months. I have to tell you how much Streamlabs OBS sucks. I feel like it'd be like, yeah.
Let's do that here. Cake anyone? Yes. I made the most scrumptious cake. Yes.
I just had the most scrumptious cake. Yes. That's you. No. Yeah. That was me when he
comes in and he goes, cake anyone? I've made a scrumptious cake. That was me doing an impression
of him coming in with the cake, but he did that all the time. He did that shit all the fucking time.
You don't understand. Neelix did that shit every other episode. He'd be like, Captain,
you must try this delicious coffee. It's better than coffee and it's scrumptious.
He would do it every other episode. I swear to God, every other episode.
Oh, what's this? You acquired a slime plort. When slimes eat, they make plorts. Head over
to the plort market to cash in your plort. What? Plort market. When they eat, they make plorts.
I got an email. Plort market gives you new bucks for your hard-earned plorts. Shoot a
plort into the plort market and earn some cash. Think plort. 13 plorts. Oh, that's what they have.
It's the stock market in this game. This is fucking awesome. All right, cool. I already love it.
Captain. Okay, so I need... What's currently valuable right now? All right, the blue spiky
plorts went down. We want the orange plorts. Oh, this is cool. This dude just plorted it out of
his mind. Okay, so catch slimes. Feed slimes. Sell plorts. Got it. Press E to activate.
Empty ranch plot. A garden. A corral. Why can I not say this? Coral. Happy slime makes for a
happy rancher. A garden. Nothing beats the taste of food. Oh, this is food. So, should I make this?
Make a garden so I can eat? A co-op. Keeping chickens in their place prevents the uprising.
A silo. You can't take it with you when you go, so put it in storage. Incinerator. Don't need to
burn it. All right, cool. I think this game seems like it's gonna be really fun. So, do I just go?
Is this... Do I just... Am I... Did I do the tutorial? Do I know what I'm doing?
The grotto. Oh, it's... It's... Otto's grotto. I like grotto. I call Otto grotto all the time.
A dark and gloomy cavern above the sea. It costs money to go over there?
Okay, what about this? What's this? Press E. Backpack upgrades. This upgrades in the game.
This is gonna be my favorite game ever made. Do you clean shit in this game too? I hope so.
All right, yeah. Hearts. Power core. All right, cool. So, should I... I need to go to an area...
What's this 52? What's that 52? Why is it 45? What's it doing?
Plort market. The plort market is a network of buyers and sellers of plorts across the galaxy.
Yeah, okay. I got it. It fluctuates, of course. You need to clean up your act.
The overgrowth. I need 2,000 to go here. Go over here. What's this thing?
Range exchange offline. Stop saying plort. Why? How many slimes can you fit in one
cage? Briar reef. A coral crusted ocean floor that now baths under a golden sun.
Wait, I gotta sell this plort. God, this thing fucking broke his neck.
All right, plort. How many stacks of plorts can you have? How many plort boxes can fit?
This is my house? Oh, shit. Secret style at Starmill.
I. B. What's it like to sleep for a whole year? Did you dream? I can't imagine what that's like.
7ZEE puts you in a pod and then lights up for all that time. Wow. What's the far, far range
like? If you started exploring, is the air as clear as they say? I bet it's really beautiful.
I'm probably asking too many questions. I bet you have a lot of work to do.
I still can't believe it's yours now. I guess I better leave you to it and just keep it short.
Good luck, B. If anyone can make it out there, it's you. Thank you, Stardew Mom.
The 7ZEE Corporation is LeBeau. What if we told you... What if I told you that the 7ZEE
Corporation has developed its secret styles and allows slimes to express themselves and show off
their... I bought the DLC, yes. If you answered that question, please know that we cannot hear
you as you are reading Starmill in a visual display unit. He's a cool boss, apparently.
We got a cool boss here. He's really funny. What's happened here? You are excited. Unfortunately,
cargo ship containing these secret styles exploded for completely unknown reasons
and left them all over the far, far range. Please stay excited. Welcome to the far range.
Who else will read this shit? We would like... Yeah, someone else will read this.
Exercise caution in your first few days in the range until you get more familiar with
your surroundings. Okay. Don't travel at night. Should you require any additional tools for your
backpack or items? Make slime ranch experiences. Yeah, yeah, someone else will read this. Sleep
until morning. Okay. What about secret styles? Early cosmetic won't change a slime's diet. Oh,
they have a diet? Holy shit, this is cool. All right, go back to the... Cool. This is... I love
it. All right, I'm ready. What do I do? Devin Chat. What's up, Devin? So we're sure to go...
Is this the only place I can go? Oh my god, there's so many over there. It's a help marker. I know
because it says H. Oh, hello, Beatrix. The name's Hobson Twilgers, rancher,
explorer, and the former owner of this here ranch you now call your own. Please
to make your acquaintance. I was a rancher here for years that I can... Hey, hey, Peter. Sorry.
I felt there was one last adventure left for me, so I've set off to find just that. Before I go,
I'm taking one last tour around this here land I love to keep your peepers peeled for notes like
these. You want to hear what an old cute has to say every now and again. Be talking to you.
H. You are now understanding the reason why Dark Souls did not let people type their own messages.
These would be everywhere. And like the ASCII art of like Mario shitting. How many can I have in
one stack? More than one? Oh my god, this dude suck them all up. Food. This guy got fruits.
Foods like fruits, veggies, or chickens are used to feed slimes. Try shooting food at a pink slime.
They'll eat anything. No, not yet. I need to collect as many as I can. They can't breathe. Yes,
they can. There's a breathing mechanism in here. Am I going to hold the butt up to 20? What's that?
What about these? Oh my god. Apogryph. The most common fruit found in the range. In some states,
the most delicious. It's like... Okay. Oh my god. Oh my god. This is Luigi's Mansion,
but the whole point is to suck everything up and not like actually play the game.
Oh my god. That's everything I wanted. I can't play Luigi's Mansion because I suck everything
up in the whole room. I tried to play Luigi's Mansion 3. I couldn't. It took me three hours
because of the first two parts of the mansion because I kept sucking everything.
Yes. Oh my god. I love it. How many can you hold? Oh, wait. I don't have enough room.
Can I fit you in a different slot? No, I can't fit you in a different slot. Eat this carrot.
It gave me a flirt. Okay. How many times can it eat? You've learned the fundamentals. Now
it's time to get out there and explore. Remember, the best way to become a pro
rancher is to experiment. What is that? Wait. That's a bird. This is like a bird.
How do I pick up the bird? I want the bird. I want this bird. Can I feed the bird a carrot?
Oops. Oops. Sorry.
Just give me more things. I want some max stacks. All right. You guys hungry?
All right. What about the Pog fruit? Do you like those? You don't like Pog fruit?
This is kind of loud. Let me turn this down. It's like very loud, isn't it?
Okay. There we go. Was it fine? I don't want to be too loud. That seems like a good level
right there. Okay. Can I tell if they've eaten? All right. Pink slimes don't like Pog fruits.
They like carrots, though. I want plorts. This is so cool. Cool. All right. I think I want to get...
Can I just max out the plorts? I want to eat up. He's ignoring us. Turn it up. Turn up the
volume. No, it's a good place. Turn it up. It's in a good place. It's in a good spot.
That's in a good place. What happens at night? Who else hasn't eaten? All right. I think I have to
leave. 120 hertz, Andy. All right. I am going to tell you something that I'm going to make a
lot of people probably really angry when I say this, but it's what I believe. I know that like
a hundred years from now, someone's going to look back at a clip of me saying this and they're going
to say, wow, what an idiot. I can't believe you thought that like the human eye can only see 24
FPS, right? I really believe that after you cross like 144 hertz, you can't tell the difference
anymore. Like 240 hertz is... I can't even see the difference. I can't see it. With 60 frames a
second, which is how most things are built to run, the brain can't process like 500 hertz and like
300 frames a second. Wait, should I put these in the same cage? How many can fit in here?
Should I be doing this? Oh, whoa. Give me that money.
20 pink plorts. What happened? Oh, I thought they died. I thought I killed them. Anybody else not
eating? Keep eating and keep giving me money. Okay. I got to sell this stuff. This game is awesome.
This is the... I can't believe it took me like four years to play this. It felt so good.
More. I need more money. More money. So you just suck them up? Is there a way like I can only suck
up the money? Is it like a money gun that I get eventually? That's an upgrade. Oh, okay.
Just stand far enough away. Oh, that makes sense. I'm sorry. I like love that. I love standing really
far away from shit and getting like a slam dunk. I have 692 bucks. Let me go to the market. Should
I upgrade something? Water tank. Adds a specialized vac tank that allows you to store fresh water.
Cool. Keep your head in the clouds with this amazing personal jet pack. Cool. Get 150 health.
Cool. Energy boost. Upgrade coral. Whoa. High walls. Even the bounciest slimes have difficulty
escaping. Music box plays a soothing tune that gently reduces slime agitation. A plort collector.
A plort collector will vacuum up two types of plorts in a coral at regular intervals,
depositing them into a storage tank so as long as space is available. Okay, that sounds pretty good.
An auto feeder. Whoa. High walls? How about high walls? They can't get up. Or a music box?
Let's do the walls first. I'll do plort. No, I'm doing plort collectors first.
That's probably stupid. Oh, wait. Did that? Somebody has one? Oh, and then it comes out here?
What about this chicken? A hearty chicken bred to be twice as tasty as its cousin. Do we eat this?
What happens if I do this? Oh, shit. You ate him. Oh, okay. All right. I'm gonna go to bed.
This game is so cool. I like this. This is really cool. I didn't know this is what this game was.
I did not know this is what the game was. I don't know why, but I thought this game was Pokemon.
Like it was here. It's a Pokemon game. You catch slimes and you battle them.
No, you didn't. Nobody told me this was like a stock market income simulator where you just
collect stuff. You didn't say the word stock market. Somebody escaped? All right. I just
gave that guy like negative 20 Gs. He ain't going. He's not going to leave again. Oh,
how come my automatic thing didn't work? I need higher walls. Yes. How do I collect it?
How do I take it out of here? They're starving. Get back in there. Get back in there. I'll be back
with food. Get out of here. Stop climbing over each other. This ain't bubble bobble. Cut it out.
They're starving. I will get them food. All right. I'm getting the food. I'll be back.
I need carrots. Do the carrots, the stuff regrow? I'll let you get over here.
Eat everything. Eat everything. Eat everything. Okay. I need carrots. Can I make carrots? Can
I grow carrots? Where do I get carrots? Holy shit. That's a huge guy over there. All right. Hold on.
I need food. What the fuck are these things? All right. Hold on. Oh my God. There's so many
different types. I need that. What? Holy shit. Large Joe slimes are large slime hybrids form when
they slime eats a port unlike its own. Act to keep them on your nozzle to shoot them to send
them flying. Okay. Hold on. Just give me these. Can I plant this somewhere? Like animal crossing?
I need money, man. Bad. Wait. Can I plant it like in the ground? Shit. Come here. Hey,
somebody punched me. What was that? Come with me. I'm putting you in that cage. He's so cute.
Cutest face ever. Doesn't seem to be concerned about this at all. I need another one. All right.
All right. What if I put you in here? Where? All right. Can I feed them? Here. Do I get more money?
Holy shit. You dropped another gem. A tabby port. Eat again. All right. No, you can get out of here.
Get out of here. Chicken. He's so hungry. Well, eat him if you're so hungry. No, shit. Hold on.
I need those. Look, I got food right here. How much money do I have? Garden. Taste of your own
grown food. All right. All right. Let's go. I'm going to deposit this shit. Okay. I'd like more
money. How do I take the money out? There's eight in there. How do I get them? Suck it out. How do
I get it? Oh, you suck it. Okay. All right. Be right back. I don't know why I feel like playing
Overwatch when that happens. This reminds me of an Overwatch gun. It shoots out single crystals.
And if you hold the button down, the last five pellets will do 10% more damage. Did I sell the
tabby port? Wait. Yeah, I'm looking at it too. People still play Overwatch. Okay. I'm going to
feed the tabby port to somebody. I got 372. All right. Come here. You want this? Try this.
Oh, I just made another cat. Wait. Now you eat one of these and then shit out some more stuff.
Yes. Get out of the way. This is everywhere. I have too many cats in my house. I probably
shouldn't have had this many. All right. Garden. Pog fruit. It's now growing pog fruit. Cool. Whoa.
Is it ready? Yeah. Can I only have one at a time? Oh, don't eat that. Get away from that.
I need higher walls. I think I need more than one garden. There's just money everywhere.
I don't even know, man. Like, what the hell? I need more plots. Remember, I want to gamble on
something. Well, just hold on. I sell it. How much does the tabby port go for? I don't know
the market. Is that a tabby port right there? 24. That's expensive. It looks gray on the bottom
right part of the screen. All right, cool. Everyone's having a good time. How long does
it take to grow? Nutrient soil. Oh, yeah. I'm definitely going to do this. Makes crops always
yield the maximum harvest. Crops are always water, making them grow twice as I want that one. I need
500 bucks. Get the walls. I'm trying to push out my walls. 350. All right. What's all over this?
Did you slime this thing? Get away from that. Get the walls. All right. I'll get the walls.
I need more pog fruit. Hey, I'll just watch them eat that. All right. I got to feed them. I need
what? Can I get it from here? If I get it from here, it's a billion off the debt. Oh, here we go.
There's carrot. I want to plant carrots too. So they do regrow. Cool. All right. That's cool. Good
to know. No, don't add it, Bill. That's not what I said. Did I get the turkey? All right. I'm going
to take a roostro. Trust the stuff like he's the king of the coup. Hen hen and a roostro.
Just looking for some more food and stuff. Just initially. I want that soil. I'm going to feed a
chicken to somebody. That sounds like a good idea. All right. If I feed a chicken to you with
a spiky hair, I got holy shit. I got a rock floor. All right. Feed a roostro to somebody. Okay. Give
me that rock floor and get out of the way. Wait, get out of the way. Out, out, out, out. Stop,
stop, stop. I'm just trying to help. All right. I got a rock floor. Just make their favorite food
for better efficiency. They like everything. Get the fuck out of here. Here. Eat a carrot.
Give me that. Stop. Eat that carrot. No, I want one carrot. I want at least one carrot. Okay. I got
it. Because I want to grow it. What is this? Map of the far, far range. This place is huge.
This is actually gigantic. Discover data nodes across the range to uncover more of your map.
Oh, that's cool. Nice. All right. I'm going to head back. I think I have enough to
at least eat them. Good. Now shit out. Good. Okay. All right. I'm going back. Wait, what's in here?
This entire cave system was sealed off from a cave-in when I first discovered it. Maybe that's why
the fellows up ahead are so grumpy. I haven't had a bite in a long time. In any case, don't let that
long-awaited bite come from your own rump. Bring some food to calm them down. You killed that guy?
Okay, so something is coming to kill me. It rolls into a Sonic the Hedgehog ball, looks at me directly
in the eyes, gets mad eyes, and rolls into me, stabbing me through the chest as hard as it can.
And I'm bleeding. Blood's everywhere. I have an opportunity to push, to throw them into the water.
I have to save myself.
He wasn't running away. No, he looked me in the eye. He turned into Sonic the Hedgehog ball,
and he stabbed me as hard as he could through the heart. All right, everybody. I'm here with delicious
foods like paw fruit. Let's get some higher walls. That sucked up. Very good. How much are the high
walls? 350. How's this doing? Growing right now? We need that. It has to go faster. That's too slow.
How much do the blue plorts go for? 21. All right.
All right, I'm going to save a rock plort because I'm going to feed a rock plort to somebody.
Whoever gets this just has to have a pool. Oh shit, he's dead. Oh my god. That was horrible.
Oh, he doesn't. OK, you can't kill the other ones, right? If he rolls up into a Sonic the Hedgehog ball,
is he going to just wipe out this whole colony? Why are they coming after me? He can't be in there.
I think he's killing things. He's killing things. All right, I need high walls. Wait, get out of the
way. Over here. Music box? OK, this is high walls. They can no longer jump out. Now you're stuck in
here. Everybody get back in. Come on. Get in there. One, two, three, four, five, six. OK.
Should I feed them? I'm just going to be a feeding frenzy. I need the plorts.
Well, this is automatically going to grow, right?
All right, well, hell yeah. Here we go. We're going to get a ton of food.
Are they getting bigger? I think they're growing in size. 20, 26, 27, 28, 29. Give me that.
Oh, shit. There's a maximum I can have. Get back in there.
No, no, no, no, no, no. This is so much money on the ground. I'll be back.
Cool. All right. Good. Anybody else take a shit? What do I need to upgrade this?
I want the spring gunny 500. Shit, this is a good price. It's going down.
Port letter. Headler. What? Load. All right. I got I got I'm going to keep one carrot flooding
the market. Is that what's going on? I was supposed to hold on to a carrot, wasn't I? Fuck. How do you
get out? OK, pull that out. So am I actually flooding the market with pink plorts? I need
another one. I need I need another I need another corral, another corral or another feeding station
because they're getting cramped in there. They're getting cramped up in here. All right.
Give me the give me the pets. All. No, shit. No, they'll give me the little ones.
Big ones have to stay in here here. All right. I'm talking about little guys.
Watch out. No, I just want the little ones. Quit crashing into me. Get out of the way.
OK, watch out. All right. Good. Now, I need to be able to keep track of who's even in here.
Feed them. I will. Where's he going? You keep getting out. So they're going,
I got out. You had to stay in. OK, let's feed. Damn it. Come here. OK, we have they've been
separated. Little pink slimes are in this one. Big ones are in here. Now I need to feed them.
Let's feed them. I don't know. What do I feed them? Make the big one out.
That's worth a shitload of money. I have to sleep when the range exchange.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Sleep after the ranch. So I need food. Bad.
I need a second food growing station. That's going to be different. Another garden.
Maybe you keep chickens silo. I only have four plots. Help me out here and I'll make sure you
get what's owed. Holy shit. You're going to be seven hundred and fifty dollars. All right. You
want four flying buzzies, five strawberry delicious strawberry cakes and one loaded hamster.
Got it. I have 30 minutes to do this. Where do I get strawberry cake? Oh, my God. I have to.
Where do I get this stuff? Strawberry cake, four flying guys, five strawberry cakes and one hamster.
OK, let's go. Go, go, go, go. It's seven hundred fifty dollars. It's a ton of money.
Whoa. Whoa. All right. Found one. Is that correct? No, who cares? Go, go, go, go.
Where do I get the cheesecake? Where do I get strawberry cake? Strawberry cake, a big rooster
and then what's that? Oh, my God. Oh, my God. It's a golden one. How do I pick it up?
Gold slime. What? I have a golden chicken. Feed it. Feed it. Oh, um, um, um. Where'd he go?
Go on. I didn't have anything to feed it with. I didn't have anything to feed.
Are these golden chickens? Oh, no. These are just regular chickens. They're just regular
fucking chickens. I thought they were gold. I thought he was shitting out like a golden
goose with golden eggs or something. I don't know. All right. I got 30 minutes to get a cheesecake.
Look at these crystals. Holy shit. What's that? Pod? Whoa. What is that? Visit the ranch house
to manage a secret style. It's free. Okay. What do I need? I need, uh, five cheesecakes
and what's that? Break the box. Break the box. A heartbeat. What else fell out?
Something else fell out. I don't want these fucking chickens. I don't want any chickens.
I don't want chickens. I don't want these chickens. Dash boots. What is that? What is this? A giant
clam. Is it evil? I think it's evil. These awful ravenous rainbows. Oh,
I'm so overwhelmed right now. This game's too interesting. All right. I need cheese. There it
is. Um, I need five of these. Cubary. It looks like they hang on like little cube trees. Cool.
All right. I have a heartbeat too. Come on. Any more of those? Oh, lock treasure pod. Fuck. Plant
the beat. I know, but I need, um, this is so overwhelming. Yes. All right. I got five cubaries.
All right. No, sorry. Let me say that better. I have five cubaries. I have five cubaries. No,
cubaries. Cubaries. Cubaries. There we go. Flip that one. That's one you could use in your project.
All right. Now I need a rooster. Is there like a quest log or something? Because I have five of
those. I needed, what else did I need? A rooster. Open the box. Did I open that box? Did I miss the
box? I don't have any room for it. I'm not getting rid of my gold plort. No, no, no. I gotta get,
I gotta bring this shit back. Go back and sell. Yeah, I'm going back and selling. I haven't
gone the right way. Um, I think so. You're playing Pikmin 1. It's harder than Pikmin 2. No.
I'm not gonna play Pikmin 1. Sorry. Mushroom. I really enjoyed Pikmin. I thought it was a really
cool franchise. I've watched the cartoon. A liar. I didn't watch the YouTube cartoon.
Just told you I was going to. Okay, so I gotta get this right. How much does, I don't have time
to just fuck around. Okay, I need four of those. Where do I even find those flying guys? I'll be
out here. Okay. So how do I deposit this? Five? Wow, it's not, 23 minutes. I need five, four of
these in one giant thing. All right. A gold plort is worth a lot of money. This shit's worth 281
bucks. But if I feed a gold plort to one of these little slimes, I will have a golden slime.
And that would get never ending golden shits. No, don't. Don't do it. Doesn't work.
Lead it to a big one. So if I feed a golden plort to one of these big cats,
it's not going to give me a big golden big cat. Stop. What? Well, first of all,
let's feed people chickens. They eat chicken? You guys don't eat chicken?
They can't eat children. They can. I guess not. All right. I want to plant this heartbeat.
Can I change the fruit that's on here? Remove crops. Okay. I want to plant the heartbeat.
10 cents. Okay. Heartbeat. Now growing heartbeats. Yeah, they're probably just way better. Cool.
Now I need a chicken coop. I only have 22 minutes to get. Okay, I got to find one of these big
chickens. What do I do with the chickens? I'm just going to put them in the cage. Whatever.
I think they're not going to go anywhere. All right. Hurry. Four flying purples and one hamster.
Can I store this in like a storage unit? Sell the gold. Sell the gold. No, I'm keeping it. I
don't want to sell it. I'm going to turn it into a golden rooster or whatever. I don't know.
I got an email. I don't care. All right. I need the flying things wherever they are.
I'm going to just explore. I have 20 minutes to get it. Look for flying shit.
Now what about over here? What can I find a flying guy? They only come out at night.
They're flying. They look mad. Only at night? What time is it right now? Am I not going to be able
to complete this quest or in caves? Caves, caves, caves, caves, caves, caves, caves, caves, caves,
caves. You can find it in that cave. Where can I get it? A cave over here. Cave? Nope. There's a
big boy. Cave? I need a cave. No cave. I see a cave over there. I almost walked off the edge.
This is pretty. And the chicken too. Yeah, this is locked. I can't go in there.
I don't see, there's no animals or anything over here. Oh, a box. Drop gold plort in C.
Dude, does it turn the whole sea gold? Does the whole ocean turn to gold and I can suck up the
gold? You're so fucking cool. I found a bird. That was really loud. All right. I know I need,
I want a carrot. Get rid of this pog fruit. Dude, it's going to turn the whole ocean into
pog ocean. Okay. Now I need those flying insects. Where are they? You dead? It was a very graceful
end. Dead. I didn't kill him. He's shit. Where are these flying insect things?
And I'm running out of time. Sorry. I almost just jumped over the edge.
He chose to fall. Yeah, he didn't have to do that. Oh man. I need, I need these.
I have to start making money. That was a good block.
Cave. I would consider this to be nighttime. They're not flying around. Shit. Come on.
Need to wait a little longer. I'm waiting. Don't swear. This is a kid's game.
Whatever you say. Just truck you. He's really hungry. Feed you here. Come here. You're really
hungry. What do you want? Out of here. Later. It's definitely nighttime. Where are they?
Go home. Home, home, home, home, home, home, home. Why do I have to go home?
You're full. Go home. What do I get out of these? Don't eat them. No.
Got it. Crazy. What's going on? Every time I have, I'm going to do it every time I have
an opportunity. I love that. There you go. Here's your hen. Give me my dog. I am invincible. I am
invincible. Don't eat that. Don't eat that. This is mine. Don't eat that. Don't eat. How are they
getting out? Don't eat the chicken. They're starving. Did he eat it? I probably needed
one of those. Is it rare? How are you guys getting out? Food. There's food over there.
Just make a giant wall. Some of us will get to eat at least. Send the children out.
I'm sorry. I'm working on it. I have five of these. Here. Look. I'm a good guy. I'm a good guy.
See? I'm a good guy. No, I don't want to pick up the money. See? I'm a good guy.
Okay. Trying to get away. This one is being carried. This one is so injured or something
that he's carrying him back to the house where they used to live. This is sad. I'm sorry. I'll
feed you guys. All right. I have $1,000. What if I feed you a beet? What do you do? What happened?
What happened? What's going on? What? Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. What
happened? Oh, my God. Get these guys out of here. What's going on? What's going on? What's going on?
What's going on? What's going on? What's going on? What's going on? It's a massacre. It's a
fucking massacre. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Do I go to sleep? Get out. Oh, my God. Go to
sleep. Go to sleep. Go to sleep. Okay. It's like Minecraft. So, it's like Minecraft. At night,
when it gets to be nighttime, those things spawn and start killing people.
So, now that I'm awake, they're gone. Okay. So, don't stay up so late next time.
We have to get back to what we were doing. Everybody relax. Press F1.
The only way to stop a tar outside of incinerating it or throwing it into the
slime sea is with fresh water. One splash will stop a tar from spawning new tar.
A repeated splash will destroy it entirely. Alternatively, many ranchers recommend running
away with their arms waving and screaming. Okay. Remember, ranching largeos may be highly
profitable, but one stray plort and you could wind up with a devastating tar outbreak. So,
let me get that correct again. If a pink plort, if a pink bunny rabbit thing, cat, eats a,
if a pink plort based slime eats a, oh, my God. I almost knocked my coffee over. Why is it so
hard for me to do? When a pink slime eats a blue plort, it turns into this. Yes. No.
A largeo eats a plort unlike the ones it produces. So, okay. When we feed something,
when it shits out two plorts, if it doesn't shit out like a blue plort, if it eats a blue
prismatic plort thing, then that's fine. You have to feed it whatever it shits out. I get it.
If you feed it something that it does not shit out, it's going to turn into one of those.
Did they eat the tree? They ate the tree. Oh, no, no. Okay. All right. I see. I see.
Okay. I'm good. I'm understanding. I'm understanding. I'm going to just pick up
the stray plorts. I need to put, you go back in here. I get it. I understand the game.
Get in there. Motherfucker. Feed them, you monster. I'm trying to get that first of all.
Just wait. I need to. God damn it. All right. Hold on. $307. Oh, my God. I don't care.
That's so much money. I don't even care. Come here, guys. Come here. Collect everybody back.
You literally can't do anything else with gold plorts at all. They're all coming back in. Wait,
the food's in the cage now. You could hold it. Yeah, I could. Increase in value. Yeah.
Okay. Come here. This game is really cool. I really like this. I bet I got everybody killed.
Stop farming just pink. I know, but my tiny brain is still trying to comprehend the game.
It's going to be pink for a little bit longer. Okay. So these are almost done. I want to buy
the watering thing. Pulse wave. Cool. Push the slimes away. That's an upgrade. All right. I want
the sprinkler. Always water, making them grow twice as fast. I want that. X crops always yield the
maximum harvest. Yup. A scare slime is a stuffed tar model designed to keep wandering slimes away
from your crops. Simple but terrifying. So the wall's higher. That's right. The wall's higher on
this one. It's an air net. Okay. Cool. Much better. I'll have much more food. One of them survived.
I love it. Come here. I'll feed you in a second. So what do you guys poop out? You guys poop out.
You guys don't eat those? What do you guys eat? What are they? Oh yeah. So you poop out
tabby plort and pink plorts. They eat everything. Okay. So how come you didn't eat the
feed? So if I feed you a tabby plort, you're going to be very happy about it.
If I feed him a rock plort, he'll turn into one of those scary things.
Because it says if you feed them a plort that's not theirs, they turn into a tar thing, right?
I don't want to do that. I could feed a rock plort to one of these and they'll turn into
aha. Cool. And then I bring you over here. Now I've got you guys over here
and then I could do tabby plort who wants to turn into a tabby. Okay. We've got kitties.
And then these guys have more yield. You have to be careful. We've got kitties. All right. I get it.
Very, very cool. I make a bunch of cats. I make a bunch of big ones. Just put them all in here.
Okay. Stay in. Yes. Okay. Because eventually these guys are going to turn into other ones.
I'm going to stop. What? He can't. He's not learning. What do you mean?
Eventually I'm going to have a place for the cats, a place for the rocks, a place. Yeah.
Separate the rocks. Don't. Get the rocks out. Get the rocks out. Get the rocks. All right. Because
I get it. I get it. I understand. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it.
You're right. Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay. I understand. Because if they poop out something, it's one of
them going to eat it. The same problem is going to happen again. Okay. I get it. Right. Right.
Because they poop out the rock thing and one of these guys will eat the rock thing and then
they'll turn into one of those things and the whole thing happens all over again. Right. Okay.
Stay away from these. We're good. I've got 250 bucks. Are these ready to be harvested?
They are. I'm going to make two gardens, I think. Is that stupid?
It's two garden plots. Oh, good idea. Garden. I'm doing beets. I'm a beet. I'm a beet grower.
Who's hungry? This dude's a beet freak. Nice. All right. Now activate my sucker.
Sucker didn't get it all. Sucker. Now I can sell all this.
Okay. So this is a tabby. So I could make some more tabbies. I could make tabbies and put a bunch
of tabbies in here. But eventually aren't they going to start getting out? Yeah. They'll bounce.
Right. Okay. So we're going to leave it as is now. I'm going to sell these tabby plots.
How much are you going to get for this? Ooh. 27 bucks a pop. 400 bucks. Cool.
Anybody have another quest? If possible, please acquire the following for a future study. My thanks.
Oh, that's not very much money. It's not a whole lot. It's not very much money at all.
Nine chickens though. It'll be a good starter for a coop. Yeah, that's a bad deal. It's not a hard
quest. No, I mean it's not. Should I just do it? I guess let's do it. Here you go. What do I give it
to you? How do I deliver you? Oh, they need to be little. They need to be little. You don't want
adults? I thought maybe I could do adults. I don't know. Wait, the color matters? Oh.
Wait, does that mean I can do this? It has to be the baby version. All right. So I have to get the
little baby. All right. I can do that. Let's do it right now. Let's go. If this sinks in right now,
it's a billion off the debt. If it doesn't sink in, then I will whistle. I'll take it. I'll fucking
I'll do it. I'll take it. Thank you. No deal. Who wants to beat? Come on, eat it. Okay. I need to
go get eight regular bunnies and eight regular rock monsters. Go. Eight little bunnies and eight
big cats. I don't know. They look like they could be anything. Oh, shit. There we go.
You know, it's it's the carrots. I keep seeing the carrots and then eating the carrots.
No, don't eat that. Five. No. Okay. Tabby. Plorts. Who cares about plorts? Wait, I do.
I don't want the fucking carrot. I want the plorts. Get away from me or I'm gonna start swinging.
I smell the plort. You're clogging my plort gun up. Okay, I need more Tabby plorts. Damn,
this game is fun. Oh, should I? No. It's eight. Oh, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight. Those things
are cool, but I don't want them. All right. I just need Tabby's. I can also take them, right?
I need more bunnies. They're not. I just I keep thinking they're eating carrots.
Get the chickens. No, they all eat carrots. It doesn't matter. Okay, think about this. In my
brain, cat does not eat carrot. Like a kitty cat does not eat a carrot. It's his tiny brain.
I need more of this brain. Cats don't eat carrots. They eat cat food and like fish.
Where? I need more of these. Cats eat carrots. You pothead cats do not eat carrots. I need more
carrots. Cats eat carrots. No, they don't. They do not eat carrots. Cats eat like gazelles. They
don't eat carrots. Can I multiply these? How do I multiply a Tabby? Can I somehow do something
to multiply them? You can't. Who cares, Jerma? It's a game. I can't even read the chat. Is that
going a million miles per hour? I cannot. Okay. Well, I need more of them then. Okay. What if
I give you extra? Did I not put these guys in here? What are they bad? That was like a get me out of
here. Okay. Very good. Cool. We'll do some feeding. We'll do some cultivating. Are these ready?
No. Let's do some feeding. All right. Time for food. Excellent. Now I'm going to come suck it up.
Eat big rocks. Yes. That's too many, I think. Too many. Too many. Too many. Too many. Too many rocks.
Too many. Too many. Way too many. Way too many rocks. I think that's way too many. Is it going
to get out? Maybe not. I need one of those. All right. I need one of those devices on here.
What do they cost? 500 bucks. Take some of the pinks out. Yeah. Yeah. Get out of here.
Give me the little ones. I'm taking some out. I don't know. What do I do with them though?
I just throw them back into the wild? All right. I'm going to put them back in the wild.
Okay. I think we're good. Very nice. I'm going to sell this stuff.
What are we doing on the market? Rock plots went up about 20%. 700 bucks.
Okay. Cool. Wait. How much time do I have left on this? 12 minutes. If I sleep,
is this going to fuck it up? It will. Yeah. I have to do this now? All right. Shit. Okay.
I need to get some more bunnies. They're not bunnies. I can't help it. I'm sorry. They eat
carrots. Whatever. Cats. I don't see any. God damn it. I need...
Now, is there a problem with staying out late at night? Okay. What happened to you?
I don't see any cats. Yeah. I need four more. Four more. I got a roostro. These are cool.
If I have paint, might as well just get them all. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Cool. All right. I need another tabby. They seem like they're not spawning as much as the rock
guys are. Go to the next location. Like through here? Right there. Wait. Did I miss one? All
right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Whoa. They're angry. Run. Oh my God. They're
killing each other. Requires a slime key. I can't go to a new area. Eat these guys? Hungry?
They were hungry. All right. Fuck off. Fuck off. Fuck off. I kind of want whatever this is.
Oh, it's a phosphor. Definitely taking that. Whatever these are. Any more phosphors?
Four phosphor. Hi, phosphor. Cool. The roostro died. Well, I wanted to... I want these phosphor
plarts. Okay. Get me back out of here. Oh. I kind of watched. There's nothing I could do.
There's nothing I could do about this. I have to leave. What happened over here? Did I? No.
What do I do? I need more cats. There's so much money here too. Find a cat. I can't.
I'm trying. I have eight minutes. Tank booster. Allows your vac tanks to hold 30 units of whatever
you can back up. Energy boost. Water tank. Store fresh water. Get pack dash boots. Pulse wave.
I think I want the booster. And then the water tank. A blast of fresh water will calm down any
slime for a short while or dissolve those terrible tar slimes. A water garden's crops also grow
faster. Oh, shit. Can I just sit here and hold this up? I need to put this into water.
Take a splash. Okay, cool. What are these worth? 26. I'm gonna hold on to them. All right. I have
seven minutes to get a couple of cats. Fill this shit up. I can hold 30 of everything now.
Which is like, that's insane. You know what I mean? That's insanity. That's insane, dude.
I can hold 30 stacks up to 30. That's insane. Re-ranging. Cool. Okay. Where are these cats?
Oh, he's dead. All right. Well, whatever. I need cat. Cat. Cat. Can't suck up the water.
Go to where the big cat was. Where was he? Over here, right? Where's that big cat?
Hmm. You stayed up all night. Oh, these are the cats. Cats. Cats. Cats. Cats.
Don't touch them. Don't touch them. Don't touch them. Don't touch them. You fucker.
Stop eating. Stop. Give me the cats. Get out of here. Okay. I need two more. I need one more.
One more cat. I'm good. Right next to me. I don't see a cat. Was there a cat?
See one? Don't eat that. Cool. You have any cats? Trying to shoot it down his mouth.
Feed it. What do I feed it? It wants meat. Meat. Like, I need a chicken. All right. Chicken.
Hi. There's a chicken. Fuck. Well, I'll come back tomorrow. I need one more bunny. One
will spawn on the way back. Quest failed. Not yet. End of the stream voice. Got it. Go.
Stop fucking with me. Stop fucking with me. Guys, I want you to stop fucking with me.
Come on. Stop fucking with me. Hey, Jimmy. I'd like it if you would stop fucking with me.
All right. Give me the quest. Ding. Oops. Don't eat that. You weren't supposed to eat that.
Okay. We're good. Looking good. Looking good. Cool. I got eight hen hens. Now I got to make a
chicken coop. Keep the chickens in their place preventing the uprising. Yes. Come on in there.
They just fly out. Why are they not flying out? Feed big cat. All right. Yeah. Hold on.
I need to say I haven't slept in like three days. Give me one minute.
Chickens can't fly, silly. No, but they can go.
Um, I'm just going to... What happened? Did it get bigger?
Activate. Stop it. Stop it. I want these. Stop it. God damn it. There's too many in here.
There's too many in there. Whatever. I need to... Oh, that felt so good.
Okay. Oh my God. $334 more gold. Activate. And now I want to get in here and I want to suck this
shit up. Come here. Fuck out of the way. Can I die in here? I'm going to die in here. Give me that.
Give me that. Rock Lords. Cool. And nine. Get back in there. Get in there.
Okay. Cool. I got a pog fruit. Let's just feed it to somebody. Upgrade your suck. Yeah, I will.
Pull these out. Make some money. All right. I got a lot to sell. Let's go make some money
and I'll come back and I'll be able to have some more food.
I've got a thousand bucks. I'm going to hold on to these. How much are they worth?
Now I'll get rid of like... I need to make another cage to have these guys.
You little shit. You little fuck. You little dickhead. No.
Just eat one of those and get over here. Get in this new cage I'm going to make.
Fuck. I didn't... You ate all the chickens. You jumped over the fence and ate them all.
You little bastard. I had like 10 in here. You ate 10 chickens. You had 10 chickens. 10. 10.
10. He's dead. He's dead. He exploded. That's what happens when you eat too much.
You ate. He's dead. That fucking guy died. Cool. Whatever. What? Why? Get...
Where's my mallets? Why can I just squish them? I want to just like...
Like Galaga used to do with fucking watermelons. Get rid of this thing. I don't want it here.
I'll be so sad when I do that. I was so sad. I feel so bad about that and he didn't even
do anything. It was like his friend. I'm sorry. Very cool. I love it. All right.
Okay. I got 30 foods. Even more, but I can't hold them. All right. I want... I just got all
those fucking chickens. I'm so annoyed by that. I just got 10 of them. He ate 10 chickens and
fucking exploded. All right. Silo. You can't take it with you when you go. So put it... So this is
storage. I think I need this. Let's put some of the food in here. Okay. I got 30 of these.
Let's say you switch... That's actually really important. Eye walls for the chickens. God damn
it. Spring grass attracts scuttle bugs that chickens just love to eat and will produce
eggs. You guys make eggs? Well, you would have if you'd all had to get eaten alive.
I'm going to store these too. Okay. This is awesome. I love this game. Okay.
365 bucks. What can I... Can I upgrade my body? Dash boots, power core. I can upgrade myself.
Get pack. Okay. How do I use it? You just float around if you hold the space. Okay. Cool.
Still harvest here that I need to get. One. Somebody eat that. Good. Okay. Now wait. Hold on.
One. Looks good so far. Suck that up. Tell this stuff one more time. I'm going to get another
quest. I like doing the quests. I'm working on a new recipe. Help me out. 14 pogfruits for
strawberries. That's not a bad deal. I got 20 minutes. I have to pee really badly. I'll be
right back. First break. What the hell was that? I think it's unplugged. All right. Well, I'll be
back. Oh, look. It's Otto. Otto. Psychostreamer zirks off. Okay. I don't know why. I thought that
was me zirking off. I was like, Oh God, what am I looking at? EP. All right. Let's get back to it.
Oh, I hated that game. I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I liked it. We'll catch that. Oh,
there we go. He admits it. No, I'm kidding. It was a cute. I love Pikmin. You said you were
going to stop doing that. I know I can't help it. I'm just fucking psycho. I will catch this one
next time or we'll just catch it right now. Remember the DMT robot. Very, very cool. That's
trippy too. It's that when we get back. Don't ever stop doing that. It's funny. Yeah. It's funny for
like the it's funny for us, but it's not funny for somebody that comes in and it's just like,
that's mean. I like Pikmin. Whatever. I ain't going to stop. Sorry. All right. So what was I
doing? I was. What was I doing? Let's look at how many I was going to say. I gotta give those a
better name. All right. I need 14 Pogfruits and four strawberry cheesecakes. I think I can handle
that. Hens are doing all right. Got. All right. Let's go read the email. Oops. Let me come in a
little closer. Hiya. Somebody else to fucking read this. Okay. Okay. Carrots improve your night
vision. Yeah. A lot of interest in the huge emails was the TLDR. TLDR fruits and vegetables
give you plus 10% extra health. I pet cactus. You know, I kill every plant I touch, but I promise
you this one will last. I mean, if it can't keep the cactus alive, then clearly something's wrong.
When I look at it, I think of you out there on the range doing your thing. Hope you're okay.
I'm seeing the time to just switch on permanent DND. I'm asleep. All right. I'm on my way. I need
Pogfruits and strawberry cheesecakes. I see Pogfruit. I'll get the carrots too because I like
them. Pogfruits. Nope. I was supposed to bring a chicken, right? To feed the big guy. Pogfruit tree.
Nope. Nothing on there. Nothing on here. Yeah. Is there anything left? No. Thank you. All right.
We're going to feed the big guy a, just a hen hen. Why the fuck is this game in the Grand Canyon?
Why not? That's kind of cool. No, I don't want anything. All right. Here he is. Hen hen. Just
ricocheted down his throat when he was asleep. Okay. You want more than what I just gave you.
Okay. Well, here we go. I want to test this. Anyone want hen hens? Oh shit. Here they come.
I want to eat that. I heard it. What the fuck? I'm trying to get rid of all these guys.
I need chickens. Leave me alone. Wait. I'm going to put the babies in my den. He needs even more.
All right. Well, I would have been able to do this too. That's annoying.
There's one. Strawberry cheesecake. I need a few more of these, don't I? Shit. I need these.
I'm the pink Gordo. I kind of want to go see what that thing is. Give me some of Pogfords.
Nine. I need, I'm going to plant the Qberry. I'm planting a Qberry. I think that's the play.
That's the pink Gordo. Oh, these things feel like I can only get a handful of them. All right. I'm
going to just deposit the Pogfords. These are just, I can get these anywhere.
N in here. And the little chickens. There we go. See? We're replenishing that. All right.
Harvest this. Change it to Qberry. Okay. Change crop. Remove crops. And turn it into a Qberry tree.
This is still fine. Hell yeah. How much time do I have? 13 minutes. That's not enough time. I need
a rooster. That's right. I do need a rooster, don't I? Is he ready? No, not yet. All right.
Let's do some feeding and some selling and some, let's do some selling. Here we go. 500k is
literally a drop in the bucket. Fuck off. You know what? Is it a deal? I ain't doing, yeah.
How did you get out? Come over here. Let him, you know what? Let him be free. He wants to be free.
Let him be it. Go on. Bounce your heart's desire. Whatever. You too. Bounce as much as you want.
I know you guys are hungry. Puzzle piece. What the hell is puzzle piece?
I might not be able to do this one. I'm probably going to fail it.
Eat up. How many are in here? I think that's a good thing to know.
Is everybody eating? Is everybody eating? What about you guys?
The virus. I don't know. I don't know what it is. I'm not going to get.
This is just too many. There's too many in here.
It was good. All right. Hold on. Give me a second. Let me sell my inventory.
Look at how much money I'm going to make from these rock boys. They're going to be sick.
I need to put one of those collecting things here. All right. We're good.
Excellent. Knock it out. That link is loud. Is it loud?
Okay. Let me do it. I got a lot of money. Hold on. This is going to be big, big, big, big payday.
25. All right. Here we go. Check this out. All this shit is down. I'm holding it till tomorrow.
Click the link. All right. This is loud. I'm going to be fucking furious.
Puzzle piece. Whatever. Hold on. It is loud. It's very loud. Turn your volume down.
Don't do it. Turn the volume down. It's loud as fuck. Okay. It's loud as fuck. It's super loud.
Oh my God. What are you doing? I didn't even click it. My bot just destroyed it, I think.
There it is. I'm clicking it. Let's see what it does. Clicked it. Did I? What the hell is this?
Click me. Are you serious? Three months ago. That fucking was so loud. I thought it wasn't
that loud. My desktop audio is turned almost to zero. I'm telling you right now, my desktop
audio was almost zero. Imagine if I had not turned it all the way down. Wait, show this? Hold on.
Hold on a second. That hurt. It did. It hurt me. Where is it? Hold on. Hold on. Let's see what
Jigsaw has to say. I'm trying to get all the fucking way down. What even is this shit?
What does Jigsaw have to say to us? 500k is a drop in the bucket. Is that what it is? It's a deal.
All right, here we go. I don't have a Rubik's Cube.
Hey, Saw. Saw, you forgot to leave a Rubik's Cube in the room. There's no Rubik's Cube in here.
No, there's no Rubik's Cube in the room. Are you sure? No, I don't see one anywhere, man.
I'm certain there's a Rubik's Cube in this somewhere. Maybe it fell under the chair.
It's not under the fucking chair. There's nothing. I'm standing.
There's a chair in there. There's a chair in there. I have no idea where it is.
His voice changer is so fucked up. He's sitting there going like this. Can I leave the room?
It's tricky. My voice changer gets fucked up all the time. Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
I can hear you. Well, that means that you know very well that gas, well that gas,
that gas, gas is filling the room. You've done that bit like a thousand times by now.
And I read Saw 2's script and it sucked. I mean, it sucked. Saw 2 is by far the best in the series.
There's no Rubik's Cube there. What's the question? My stomach. If you get my favorite foods wrong,
gas is going to fill the room. Make your choice. Please say pizza.
Well, pizza's not really that good for you. How about tacos?
Saw doesn't like tacos. They're messy. You can't eat them in the car.
You're eating food in the car? Yes. I eat food in the car.
That doesn't sound like a safe thing to do. Pizza's really easy to eat in the car.
You have pizza in the car? Am I going to get any of this money,
by the way, because of the Rubik's Cube? Nah, just forget about all that. This is the end.
This is just to scare the shit out of people. So they do my fucked up tasks.
Nobody actually has to do any of this stuff. The door is open. Leads out to the outside.
You can actually walk out right now. See the exit sign over there?
Yeah, I do. You can just walk out if you want.
When this goes to zero, nothing happens. So I can just leave?
Yeah. All right. Well, I'm just going to leave.
That was kind of fun. I guess you kidnapped me and took me.
Yeah, I did. I'm in jail for all that because I just keep kidnapping people and putting them
in these chairs. But you still didn't say what I was going to eat.
I'm going to say, you know what, I'm going to say pizza.
Pizza, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, gas, gas, gas.
You really like saying that, don't you?
No saying that word. It's my favorite.
One of the people, there's a guy with a big spider web.
Giant spider. It was really insurance for all that she had or something.
Okay. Well, I'll talk to you later. I'm going to get up and leave.
See you later. It's good to see you again.
This door, that door back there?
Yeah, down behind.
All right. See you later. This door is locked.
That one's locked?
Yeah, this one's locked. I can't get out of that one.
Well, they're all supposed to be unlocked. I'm sorry. I don't know what happened.
You didn't code that. You didn't code this correctly, I don't think.
Yeah, yeah. All I know how to do is have a number to stop.
Bill Gates figured out Y2K because then we would have gone back in time
like minus 50,000 years if he didn't figure that out.
So are you saying that if I let this run, then this is debt that is removed?
Because I'm removing debt now.
Well, you know-
Is debt being added? Right. Okay. That makes complete sense.
Thank you, Saw. This was a lot of fun.
What's happening?
Why is it taking up? I kind of want to leave this.
What happens when it gets to like a hundred million?
Is my computer going to crash?
Just put it in the corner.
All right. I was going to put this in the corner, but I'm going to put the music.
I can't just have the music going.
I have to mute the website.
Gash, we'll fill the room.
Let me mute this.
Okay. I'm curious to see what happens to this.
All right. Hold on. Let me make sure I could-
Okay. This is good.
I'm not going to turn this off.
I'm not turning this off, by the way, until the stream turns off.
Just to make sure everybody knows that.
Although maybe I should just-
Maybe we'll check on it every-
I don't want that just to be counting the whole time.
We're going to check on this every so often.
We'll give it a good look every so often. Okay?
Yeah. We'll give it a look.
I can just open it like that. Yeah. We're good.
Keep it there.
No, I don't want to like ruin-
I don't want to ruin the entire like VOD or the editing that the editors-
No. That can't just sit there the whole time.
You know how many people are going to ask a question about that on this stream?
Hey, why does this dude have just a negative counter going?
And we have to explain it to them every time.
All right. I'm going to leave it there until a million.
We'll see what happens at one million.
There it is. Why does this dude have a negative counter?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
All right. Let's go.
Gash, we'll fill the room. Gash.
All right. Now I'm going to go to bed so I can get up in the morning and-
Whoa. Good.
Stop doing that. Stop doing that. Stop doing that.
I'm 35. You can't act like that.
Okay. Your volume.
Ooh. Here we go.
Okay. I'm going to go to sleep.
The best part about that- I love this clip that like- not clip, this site.
Because it was- whoever made that, you are the- I love you.
You are fucking incredible.
Because you just assumed that I had a Rubik's Cube on my desk.
That's so funny.
The counter just starts going.
Let me tell you right now, I would not have been able to do it in that amount of time.
It would probably take me a few days to do a Rubik's Cube.
And that's really embarrassing to say, but it's the truth.
I would do it a little bit, get frustrated, and then stop.
And then a day later, pick it up.
That's a potential week or two long project.
All right. Let's do the stock market.
It went down even more.
I need money. I don't care.
I need the money. I need the upgrade.
Hold it. Hold. No.
I'm not going to hold it.
Oh, what am I doing? Just hit button.
Oh, strawberries. Nice.
I might actually be able to do this right now.
I got five. I can do it.
Holy shit. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Get this right.
This is so many cubits. This is insane.
15 cubits. Nice.
All right. Hold on.
Four. I need a little bit.
Oh, that's good. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I need some more bugs.
Cool. Nice.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Store these.
All the chickens are doing.
Oh, they grew up. Nice.
All right. I need a rooster and a couple more fruits.
So we're going to rooster run.
All right. I got four minutes to do this.
I just need some bugs.
This tree up here, I know for a fact has them.
I know for a fact.
Chickens. Cool. Cool.
Another chicken. Cool. Chicken. Cool.
Hey, Lenny the person.
Thanks for the 20 community subs.
Right there. There we are.
Fly up there.
I'm running out.
Check in. Give me these.
Touch these. Get away from this.
That should be enough.
All right. Get out. Coffee.
Oh, coffee. Coffee. Coffee.
I'll do it. I'll do the line.
Fine. I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll do it.
Coffee, Cheetos, and chicken.
There you go. He did it.
I'll do it again. I'll do it authentic.
Coffee, Cheetos, and chicken.
There you go.
That's exactly how everybody wanted me to say that.
I get a rooster for this.
I didn't do it right. I didn't do it right.
There you go.
I'll get a rooster in there.
Now we're going to have eggs.
Very nice.
Oh, was that an egg?
No. Awesome.
Now I have plenty of chickens.
I'll upgrade this a little more.
I got 1,200 bucks.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Everybody's hungry.
All right. I'm going to relax.
Settle down.
Feed.
Let's feed them.
Nope. We got much better than PogFruit.
Whatever.
I'll just use it.
Now we're cooking Pogash.
Suck it up.
I need a sucker on here.
I'm getting real sick of having to do that.
Even if it's 500 bucks, I don't care.
I want a sucker on this one.
What do we got?
Four and six.
Do it again.
Suck it up.
Hey, eat one of these.
Doi, doi, doi, doi, doi, doi, doi, doi.
Thanks for the doi.
All right.
Prices are still down.
I'm for upgrades.
Upgrade.
304.
I sort of held on to the gold.
It's a million.
Oh, yeah.
That's still there.
Okay.
Let me take out.
No, I'll leave that in.
What can I do here for the chickens?
Spring grass.
Vitamizer.
Vitamizer bathes the chickens in vital rays,
allowing them to grow into healthy hens and roosters twice as fast.
Spring grass attracts scuttle bugs that they eat.
They'll produce eggs twice as fast.
So we want the grass.
Get them both.
Let's go.
Okay.
So now, this is a pretty good, this is going pretty good.
Now I'm going to take like seven of them to feed to the big cat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Grass, grass.
When did this game come out?
What year?
What year did this game come out?
2000, 2017.
Okay.
2017.
What was my game of the year in 2017?
Can I amend it?
What was my game of the year 2017?
Anyone know?
2016.
Well, what was my game of the year 2016?
I don't know.
It was Sorcery.
It was The Witcher 3.
Oh, yeah.
Was that 2015?
No, that's 2015.
All out for Omega Low.
Now, that's a huge Omega Low.
That's like a mega Omega Low.
That's the biggest Omega Low I've ever heard in my life.
All right.
I'm taking some of you.
I'm going to, I'm taking this big supply.
We're going to go feed the big guy.
And I'm going to get a quashed.
I need these plorts, post-haste, whatever that means.
Oh, oh, that's, holy shit.
This is a rip off for you.
This is the, what a rip off.
This is the easy.
Oh, my God.
That's the simplest thing ever.
Okay.
What about, how many do I need?
I need just pink and I have those already.
Let's scam this person.
Okay.
Now, let's get pink plorts back in there.
I have enough.
That was the easiest.
A huge amount of money.
It was very simple.
I didn't have to do anything.
Perfect.
Plorts, plorts.
Okay.
And what do I get for this?
All right.
I got to clear my inventory.
Eat some of these beats.
Just leave them in there.
You guys will be hungry eventually.
Okay.
Give me these.
Cool.
Sell a bunch of shit.
Prices, still bad.
Give it to me.
Oh, I love just vacuuming everything.
This is the best game ever.
This might be the best game ever.
I know that a lot of you have, you know,
like Mario Galaxy is like your number one game ever made.
No, not it.
No, it's not.
It's this one.
This is the one.
It's this game.
Okay.
Now, I look at all these pens.
Wow.
Perfect.
Sell the rest of these.
Get another quest too.
Why not?
Henry, I think you like this game too much.
All right.
That's good.
Sell the plorts.
Fuck Mario and his dumb mustache.
I didn't say that.
That's me.
Feed the big guy.
I don't think he has a dumb mustache.
I think Mario looks good.
Wait.
Upgrade.
Dash boots.
Power core or no, something else.
What can I do with this?
Solar shield.
Auto feeder.
Music box.
Air net.
Or a new area.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll save it for the new area.
Yeah, I'm going to hold it.
All right.
I'm going to go feed the big guy.
I turn off this 1.7 million.
We'll check back on it later.
It's distracting.
I can't believe I found a golden at the very beginning.
Oh, I just fed them.
Oh, a cat.
All right.
And over here.
So what does this do for me?
Here we go.
Ready.
Feed.
Feed him.
You want more?
More than seven?
Jesus.
You did like 30.
30?
Well, I guess I can't do it.
Save this.
Yeah, I was going to bring the stony back.
And I'm going to take another quest.
Yeah, try that again.
See what happens.
Sell, sell, sell, sell.
Money, money, money, money.
Money.
I'll take money.
Thanks for the money.
This dude is so greedy.
Yes, I am.
Get over it.
Come on.
I want more.
I'm not satisfied with the amount of money that I'm going to bring back.
All right.
Fine.
Goodbye.
The greedy grinner.
Anything else?
See ya.
I'll take it.
Okay.
You unhinged?
Are you asking me or did you say I was?
Hey, dude, you unhinged?
Yeah, I think so.
Hello.
Press Q.
He didn't do anything.
We just crossed two million, by the way.
Negative two million.
There are a lot of people in here now.
It's clucking away.
No more quests.
Time to sell.
Actually, I'm going to sleep.
Maybe the market will be better in the morning.
I'm going to wake up to a better market.
That's as much as I can get it.
Well, it seems like another wannabe rancher
has signed up for a lonely existence on a faraway space route.
Congrats, Beatrix.
I'm Mochi Miles.
That's Miles as in Tatsuya Miles, the billionaire.
I'm going to do important business for my dad,
but that doesn't mean I won't make all the rest of these backwater types out here
look bad in the process.
No one conquers the plort market like I do day in and day out.
My dad gives me the inside track,
so I look forward to my requesting plorts
that I know will make me huge profits later on.
So I wish you the best of luck, Beatrix,
and maybe you'll even reach second place one day.
At the very least, you can tell your friends
that you helped out the great Mochi Miles
in her conquest of the far, far range.
Later, Tater.
Mochi Miles, top rancher.
No, go to sleep.
Hank Booster MK2.
Ooh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Market done.
You keep selling.
Yeah, because it's fucking money.
I need some more chickens to feed to the big guy,
not the snowy one, because that's a rare one.
I want that one.
Are we supposed to wipe out this entire group?
I have 14.
All right, 15 hens.
Is that not going to be enough?
Oh, they're really hungry.
All right, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're good, you're good, you're good, you're good.
Stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay.
Get back in there.
Hey!
All right, I'm going to feed them Qberries.
That's a high quality food, right?
All right, you guys want Qberries?
We love Qberries.
Eat up.
Ooh, the Qberries are a pretty good food, aren't they?
Poison the water.
I'm going to relax, dude.
I'm going to have to put a ceiling on.
Ow, hey.
I'm about to throw them over the edge.
Nice.
Look at all that.
So much money.
A roof on the corral.
Yeah, I'm going to.
Roof going on.
I want an air net.
Now you can't get out.
Stay in there.
Oh, come on, really?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Come here.
Then kill them.
Come over there.
Put his head in there.
I said, then kill him.
What's that from?
Take over there.
Punch him in the face and then kill him.
What's it from?
What is that from?
Um, no, that's uh, that's Who Framed Roger Rabbit.
That's the judge.
He says like, something, something, something.
Take over there and then kill him.
If you say so.
No, I know so.
I want to sell these when the rock plots are higher, but whatever.
Want to upgrade now.
Put them in the dip.
Not the dip.
We can't go into that dip.
No.
Take him over to the dip.
Jump his head in and dunk his head over there and kill him.
Yeah.
No, dammit.
If you get out, you're dead.
He got out.
He's dead.
Just kidding.
Everyone's eating.
Give me that cubert.
Let's just suck up one more time.
Make sure we didn't leave anything.
Cool.
Put the kiwberries away.
I hope German doesn't actually buy stocks.
He would actually be a million in debt.
You don't know anything about me.
How many can I store?
You don't make a low.
Take him over there.
Stick a shoe on his head and then kill him.
I'm thinking good.
Yeah, let's go feed the big guy.
No, no, I'm not talking about that part.
I'm talking, I'm just like, I'm doing it.
It's in my head right now.
That was a weird transition, but no, that's not what I was trying to say.
Chicken.
Press Q, please.
What does Q do?
Chicken.
Oh, you just, I just got, I just booped.
He went like boop.
My god, I got booped.
Boop.
I have 21 chickens.
This isn't going to work.
If you need to eat more than 30 chickens, then that's kind of ridiculous.
Oh, I want you.
Ooh, multiple stony hens.
Cool.
We're safe.
Shut the fuck up.
Oh my god, you absolute unit.
What?
Cat puke.
It was.
It was a cat puke.
Get away from me.
I can't believe I have to keep, why?
What the fuck?
Stop turning into these guys.
We're being overrun.
We're overrun.
Oh, it's a stony chick.
FPS shooter voice.
Watch your tail.
Being overrun over here.
What was that?
Oh, and that's the division voice.
The division.
All right.
Stony hens, stony hens, stony chick, chick, chick, chick, stony chick.
Why are they still going down on value?
Am I actually flooding the market?
All right, I'm back.
I'm here and I've got a thing for you guys.
How did you get out?
I need to put a roof on that one too.
Oh, I got you.
I got you.
Don't worry.
You're okay.
Okay, now none of you are getting out again.
Am I like suffocating that one?
I need music.
I'll get it when I'm ready.
Chickens.
What?
What about the chickens?
What happened?
You little shit.
No, you're not going over there.
Stay in here.
He's just looking at me.
I'm going to get those chickens.
I'm going to eat all those chickens.
You're not touching those chickens.
You're going to be in big trouble.
You should be much more prepared at this point in the game.
You suck.
Open up the fucking slime rancher Wikipedia page.
All right, it's okay.
Let me go.
How do I put it in?
Minimum, minimum, maximum of the game.
Okay, first three hours I've ever played.
What?
What should I not do?
I'm not doing that ever.
Okay, I'm going to have two of the screens.
Have that open into furniture and windows.
What's the maximum thing I gave for that price?
Do that only.
Okay, don't do anything else.
Like, this ain't Dark Souls.
It's Slime Rancher.
All right, feed.
Read the wiki.
I'm just having fun.
Like, come on.
No fun allowed.
No, don't have any fun.
Fun?
This is a lifestyle.
Yeah, this game's fucking awesome.
I love it.
It's so good.
If I'm not playing, if I'm not doing the best possible route and I'm taking it slow,
I want to do that.
I want to just do dumb things like this.
Because guess what?
In like six months when I'm the number one slime rancher player on the leaderboards,
I would like you to come back and then we'll grade your performance in the video game.
By the way, probably not going to play this for a place like another couple of days ever.
Hello, Bob.
Hello.
Chickens.
P.S.
Chicken.
The Z rewards club is that easy.
Premium price.
Each rank grants you a new club title.
Can I sleep?
Yeah.
Yep.
Someone from the chat wrote the chicken email.
All right, I'm going to go.
I want to save up for the new area, so I'm going to do a quest.
I really want to get that just so you can see.
When it hits a billion, I wonder what's going to happen.
All right.
That's fine.
Everyone's been fed.
These are just worthless.
Whatever.
OK, cool.
I need what is it?
1700 to go to the next area.
This is ranch expansion.
The grotto is 1795.
What's the other one?
I need to go to the grotto or the overgrowth.
Which one was better?
I'm sure they're both fun.
Which one's more grotto?
Those are extra areas for farming.
That's cool.
I personally like the grotto more.
OK.
Overgrowth gives food.
We'll go to grotto.
Grotto sounds like fun.
I don't need to do any of that.
This is all good to go.
We'll do a feeding.
We'll do a collection.
We'll do a selling.
And then I'm going to go do a quest.
Chicken.
Chickens.
Oh, fuck.
It was that guy.
OK.
Oh, wrong.
I'm going to do I need eight chickens and one rooster.
Am I going to just wipe out this population?
There's no more red chickens.
I'm going to sneeze it.
I can't.
OK, I got it.
That came out of nowhere.
I'm wiping out this whole population.
No, I need to grow.
Have people grow up first.
You guys just keep having chickens.
Go on.
OK, here we go.
Let's feed.
Collect.
Sell.
And then I'm going to go find some chickens.
I'm feeding you.
I got you.
I know it's clogged.
Get in there.
I guess I guess good.
Who's eating?
Eat.
You'll eat.
Keep eating.
Gone.
Eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
If you have too many chickens in the pen, they won't have Zex.
OK, is that a real thing?
Because that's good to know.
OK, we just have stony hens left, but whatever.
I can replenish that population.
Nice.
It's a lot of money.
And a lot of pod fruit, too.
All right, I'm going to store the pod fruit
because somebody usually randomly just wants it.
Hmm, sell these.
What's it got in here?
Sell this shit, too.
I'm not going to make.
I'm just not going to make them.
Maybe I will eventually, but not right now.
That shit up.
I have enough.
All right, cool.
I can buy the new.
I'm going to buy grotto.
No, wrong.
I need to buy a couple more plots, too.
Got it.
A grotto.
Oh, I'm so excited.
So what's over here?
Before I left the ranch, I found myself sleeping most nights in here.
In this here grotto.
I fill it full of phosphor slimes and watch them dance in the dark.
Drifting off, I pretend I was drifting in a sea of stars across the limitless black of space.
It's funny how when you dream, you should become a sucker for the impossible.
Every time I woke to find myself back in the grotto, I'd feel a little sadness.
But then it was back to work.
It was always something that needed doing.
Oh, it's just extra space.
All right, I get it.
Oh, shit.
OK, there's just a bunch of more plots.
I get it.
OK, that was funny.
I wasn't trying to be funny.
What did you do?
Well, let's just make a...
OK, I got one of these.
So there are certain slimes that only want to be at night, right?
So let's put the night slimes in there.
Pond.
They make a pond?
Fresh water on the ranch.
Oh, little slime.
Eh.
How do I go back?
How do I get out of here?
Oh, OK.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Oh, that's right.
It is Valentine's Day like soon, isn't it?
Was it tomorrow?
It is tomorrow.
Hey, happy Valentine's Day tomorrow.
Am I streaming tomorrow?
No, I'm not.
What's this?
Not streaming on Valentine's Day.
Happy Valentine's Day, though.
If you have a significant other, then very cool.
If not, then it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Who do I want to talk to?
Who paid me more money?
Is there a raid coming in?
We do have a raid coming in.
It's a raid from Limealicious.
Thanks to the raid, Limealicious.
Welcome, everybody.
Hi.
How you guys doing?
It's me, Jeremy, singing a raid song.
No, we don't do raid songs.
I don't do a raid song here.
What we do is we show you a counter on the screen
of how much money is being deducted
from my pretend joke, laugh out loud, yellow bell bank account.
Hope you had a good stream, Limealicious.
Thanks for the raid.
Welcome, guys.
Let's talk to Victor.
If possible, please acquire the following for a future study.
Thanks.
I always have such a pain in the ass to get these.
How many do I need?
Six, six, nine.
I just suck up a bunch of people.
I got it.
Got it.
All right.
Get it.
Peter Griffin.
All 300 people that just came and just left immediately.
I need nine of these.
All right.
That's fine.
Who wants a carrot?
One, two.
All right.
Now I need...
I almost just said bunnies again.
They're not bunnies.
They're cats.
Germa is an acquired taste.
What?
I'm like a whiskey or something?
I'm a very expensive, gross, acidic, painful liquid.
And if you have it enough times, it makes you feel really, really good.
No.
No, you're a shitty vodka.
Whatever.
What are these?
Little nuts.
Shitty vodka.
So what?
You're saying that...
Let's go the other way.
So I'm cheap.
I taste terrible.
And it feels nice for like a half an hour.
And then you puke for the rest of the evening.
Is that what I am?
I keep eating the things and turning them into...
Whatever.
No, you're a good kush.
It feels terrible.
And I know it does.
But I can't stop doing it.
What the fuck?
Come here.
God.
Multiple chickens.
Brock's lime.
I almost just called that a tater tot.
Okay.
Here we go.
Feed.
Again.
Here's 10 more.
How could you eat this much food?
Looks like it's gonna explode.
Is he all right?
I need more cats.
What's the new area?
Oh, there's a new area.
Guys, new area.
Oh, I need a key.
Oh, he just fell.
Careful.
Careful of the bridge.
Don't fall over.
No, you're gonna fall.
Oh no.
Okay, I'm fucking out of here.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
That was just a stinky monkey guy.
No, I wanted that.
Just load up on little chickens.
Oh, big chickens over there.
Regenerate.
I've seen the world record-breaking speedrun.
This is not even anything like your playthrough.
Are you even trying?
Get out of here.
I'm gonna deposit these guys.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Still need a few more rocks.
Stinky.
Sorry.
I don't even think that's funny.
But I do now.
I don't know why.
Chickens, get in there.
And three.
Need three more rocks.
Okay, do I have?
I could turn these into the other guys, right?
Do I have any of the other stones?
I don't think I have the other stones.
Yes.
Yes, I'll get the stones.
I'll go after those stones.
Yes, of course, I'll get the stones.
Three more.
What are you talking about?
Some of you know, and I don't care.
There's a 12,000 people here.
Even 10 of you knew what I was just doing.
Oh, because you just screamed at the TV.
I saw that movie.
Okay, I need to upgrade.
Solar Shield.
A solar shield in case of coral and dim shade,
protecting slimes to sensitive to light.
Okay.
How about a music box?
I think I want to turn these guys into someone else.
Now are we on each other's TVs?
You got, you're right.
Wow, it's been a while since I've done that.
Fuck.
Oh my God, I forgot about that.
I love that.
I don't watch movies.
That's not a movie.
That's like a Facebook ad.
I got a lot of these.
It's time to sell them.
And I'm going to start expanding how many people I have.
Are we on each other's TV?
Okay.
Market, go up.
This market sucks.
Initiate.
Rooster Weather Vane.
What is that?
New Bucks.
I get this.
All right, come on.
Market.
Whatever.
Just sell.
What are you talking about?
Search what?
Searching anything.
All right.
Everybody's good.
Look at all these new chickens.
This is maxed out.
I'm going to go on an expedition here
and I'm going to go get a bunch of new slimes
and they're going to go up here.
Take a look at this.
Bang.
And boom.
And boink.
I want a new slime in here.
Let's go get one.
I need the rock slimes.
You're right.
I'll get those too.
This time I'm going to go get rocks.
See if we can make like blue or something.
I'll definitely take these chickens.
Why the hell not?
You can use a jetpack to get to the do-
I want to-
I'm going over here.
What is this place?
It's a big guy.
What does he want?
He wants mushrooms.
Oh, what's this again?
There's a shitload of chickens in there.
All right, cool.
Do you want chickens?
You eat chickens.
Just like the other one.
Oh, shit.
What is this?
It's Blarkey.
Visit the ranch house to manage secret styles.
Cool.
He eats anything.
All right, so I'm just going to load him up
with cheap fruits.
He should have had some of his own slime,
to be honest.
Not that if he has anything else to do.
All right, I think I don't-
Do I want a cat?
What about a rock cat?
Would that be cool?
It would be a blue rock cat, right?
Come here.
That would be epic.
I'll try it.
What if I do a flying cat?
We're going to experiment.
I'm going to do an experimentation.
It happened.
No, wait, don't die.
What did it-
There's presents in here.
Hold on.
Whoa, what's in here?
Fruits and stuff?
Holy shit, what's that?
What is that?
Cloudy ornament?
Okay.
Fucking goddamn epic game store.
Game event.
Fortnite.
The Flash.
Striking the island with lightning speed.
The fastest man alive is join the hunt.
Catch the Flash set in the item shop
and it won't go away.
Do I even have that open?
Is this a teleporter?
Oh my god, hell yeah.
Wait, where am I?
The docks.
5,000.
Where am I?
Wait, where am I?
What's going on?
What?
How do I get out of here?
This is a new area?
You haven't unlocked that area.
I can teleport into it, but I can't.
Okay, whatever.
All right, all right.
I fed that guy.
He's done.
How much money do I get for that?
I got-
It's sequence broke.
Oh well.
I have a bunch of cats.
I want to go back and do some experimentation.
I don't need this.
Get rid of it.
All right, so that's what that does.
Now if-
I could do rock cats.
Blue rock cats.
I could have two different kinds of cats.
You already have rocks and cats.
Yes, but I don't have rock cats.
I have cats.
I have rocks.
I don't have rock cats.
Cool.
He likes veggies and meat.
Make flying cats.
Fly cat is more useful.
This was checking.
I think I sold all the flying ones.
Did I sell all the flying ones?
I think I did.
How do you want-
What does this do?
How do I use it?
The decoration?
Just put it down?
Oh.
Oh, got a call.
Bob wants chickens.
Chickens, chickens, chickens, chickens, chickens.
Yep.
I got-
I got them, Bob.
I got plenty of them.
Ooh.
And I get those and I can make cats.
You want a rooster?
All right, wait, how many-
This one's different.
What is that one?
Elder hen.
An old bird whose egg laying days are over.
How many does he want?
All right, he needs four more of those.
One, two.
Shit.
Wait, what?
Why?
When you feed the-
That's the cycle, right?
I respect that hen very much.
It did a lot of good work and was a wonderful, wonderful bird.
But they eat them.
What the hell was that?
That was like a three-year-old explaining to you why they ate crayons.
Himi, did you-
Did you eat the box of crayons?
Yes, but that's a cycle.
I like blue.
So I eat them.
I ran out of pink.
So I eat blue.
Okay.
I like eating blue crayon.
That's why I do it.
That's the cycle of life.
I got you, I got you, I got you.
Fill up.
Hello.
What do you eat?
I think you like-
Scrumptious games.
Here, have some.
What do you poop on?
I don't think I've ever seen you poop before.
Let's stare at it.
Captain.
You poop-
Wow, that's a lot.
That's actually a lot.
That's kind of gross.
Captain.
I'm sorry.
How many more do you want?
You need a few more of these.
Two more.
Two more just regular hens.
I'll go grab them.
Make an auto feeder.
I will.
I need-
What the hell?
What am I looking for?
What am I doing out here?
Oh, chickens.
Give chicken.
You dickhead.
You're a dickhead.
Chicken.
No, that's a stony chicken.
Yep.
Here we go.
All right, I got some phosphor slimes.
That's what I wanted.
I want to make cat phosphors.
Or phosphor rock.
Easy.
I don't need that.
Yeah, I'm going to put them in the cave.
Phosphor rock.
Make sure you put them in the grotto.
Yeah, because it's nighttime, right?
I think I'm going to do phosphor.
What's the most expensive?
Someone said geode.
And speaking of geodes,
make sure you join us on the German 985 YouTube channel.
No, wrong.
Twitch channel.
Make sure you join.
Let me start over.
And speaking of geodes,
make sure you check us out
on the German 985 twitch.tv channel.
On March 6th at 1 p.m. Pacific time
for an archaeology geology stream.
All kinds of wild things are going to happen.
Who knows what you can see?
Join us.
All right, I was going to say,
can I store animals?
But you can't.
I need to pick this shit up.
I need...
Somebody eat this.
I don't want them.
Okay, cool.
I'm ready.
We're going to go into the cave.
Go in the grotto.
Where's the grotto over here?
I need to experiment.
So I need a lid.
I need to just fly out.
Okay, so rock.
Should I do rock?
Flying bug or cat?
Flying cat.
That hurt.
Cat, flying cat.
I'll do fly...
I'll try flying cat.
Cool.
Eat that.
Now, what do you guys eat?
Fruit and meat.
Come on, eat.
When do you guys eat it?
There we go.
Eat this one.
I've been watching from the beginning
and I still don't know what you're doing in the game.
You're just making money.
Just make money.
Eat it.
Eat that.
You will eventually.
All right, what can I do?
I want to do solar shield?
No.
So you guys eat root and meat.
All right, I'm going to feed them.
I don't want to do too many.
Not too many.
I don't want to be crowded in here.
That's fine.
That's enough.
Cool.
All right, I need to make this bigger.
It's getting cramped in there.
Sell, sell, sell, sell, sell, sell.
Pea berries.
I know.
You're getting hungry.
I'm coming.
Eat up.
Looking good.
How's the market looking?
Is the market still dog shit?
Who are you in here?
You're a rock cat?
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
Oh, we have rock cats in here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Why are you doing that automatically?
Eat, eat.
Good.
All cats all the time.
That's a cool one.
I need a lid.
Tuck that up.
We're going to make a big sell here.
Oops.
All cats.
Yeah.
Well, I do.
Whatever.
I like cats.
And then we're going to go.
We're going to take a bunch of fruits and vegetables and shit.
We're going to go feed the hell out of that guy.
Big guy.
I'm going to sell.
Lots of rocks.
Good.
Have you guys gone to the bathroom yet?
You will.
I need to feed you guys because you need to go to the bathroom.
I need to put these guys in.
Yes.
This way.
Now, wait.
What do I do with the phosphorus limes?
Give them a new.
Give them a different pen.
Why is this market is going way down?
I'm getting such bad returns from this.
He's still in the first four plots.
Omega lul.
No, one, two, three, four, five and about to be a sixth for the phosphorus limes.
So excuse me.
You had it wrong.
I'm so sorry.
I don't even care.
I'm going to go feed the absolute hell of a hell out of that guy.
We're going to wipe out the entire harvest.
I have almost this guy's going to eat really well.
I could feed them a tabby.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
All right, we're going to get a tab.
We're going to get three tabbies.
Let's feed the tabbies.
Guys, hello.
Let's make this bigger.
There we go.
OK, now it's not so cramped in here.
OK, I want you guys to please eat up and give me some of those delicious gems.
Thank you.
OK, so now, yeah, I want you to over here in this.
No, no, no, no.
Come here.
Here we go.
This is what I want you to do.
Eat that.
Eat this.
Take a bite out of that.
Nice.
All right, now get back in there.
All right, I need this again.
What do you mean 1080?
What's wrong?
FPS?
Is it going bad?
Why?
What?
FPS?
I don't know.
It's not happening to me.
Maybe a little.
Why don't you eat this?
Eat that.
You didn't even miss.
How did you miss biting that?
The other one just jumped off the cliff.
You're OK.
Come here.
Go for it.
Yes.
All right.
We are now ready to feed them.
Here's some Hubert fruit.
Look at all those gems.
Hell yeah.
So many gems.
There's so many.
Now we need a collector.
I'm pleased my eyes are burning.
Take a Tylenol.
I don't know.
What do you want to do?
OK.
I need to come back here with money.
Be right back.
I'll be right back.
I'll come back with money.
Tank booster three.
Holy shit.
Nice.
You guys want food?
You hungry?
All right.
Shit.
Fuck.
I need to go back to the store.
I'm not ready yet.
I need to go with the storage.
Go feed the big slime.
Hold on.
I'm almost done with this.
Let me get some money.
Give me a second.
Hold on.
One sec.
Just one sec.
OK.
Now I'm...
I need to make enough money
where I can have the auto feeder thingy.
OK.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Debt check.
What do you mean debt check?
Good.
OK.
I can afford it.
Saw debt.
Oh, shit.
OK.
Right.
Is it 8.2 million?
Or is it 8 billion?
8 million.
Jesus.
Now I can afford this.
And now check this out.
Suck it up.
Yes.
Money, money, money, money, money, money, money.
Oh, yes.
These are worth money.
These are worth a lot.
Waiting for a couple more people to eat.
Delicious.
Still haven't fed the gray cats.
What?
I haven't?
They don't eat beets.
Fruit and meat.
Oh, beet is not fruit.
Isn't it, though?
You might get tomato.
Tomatoes are technically fruit.
I mean, they're sweet as a fruit.
There's some sweetness.
There's sweet as a fruit.
How the chicken's doing?
I think there are too many roosters.
Do I have way too many roosters?
Hi, guys.
Veggies and meat.
Now give me a harvest.
Delicious.
Crunchies.
I mean.
Or I love when the gems pop up.
What about how can I not get golden anymore?
Okay.
Fruits.
Golden is just RNG.
Okay.
I'm going to get a huge, huge fucking harvest from this.
Look at this.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Look at that.
Oh, yeah.
Keep it coming.
I have 22 phosphorus to sell.
Unbelievable.
I don't want that.
That's like the scary number.
I mean, one more.
Oh, whatever.
Go Biden raid.
Wouldn't that be something?
All right.
$22 per phosphorus.
Yes.
Go for it.
Give me money.
Hell, yeah.
$1,100 now.
Sell the water?
Sounds like you can.
This looks good.
Now I'm going to go feed that guy.
Take all of my fruits and vegetables.
I'm going to feed the hell out of them.
I'm going to feed them some roosters too.
We have way too many of these.
We kind of have to thin this down a little.
And some of the stony hens.
Okay.
That's a little thinned out.
There we go.
Let's go feed that guy.
Pick up fruits and shit on the way.
I can get it.
Mine as well.
I'll take another rooster.
Fine.
Sure.
And another hen.
Oh, I can't.
Whatever.
I come bearing gifts.
Don't do the buck.
That's not very good, but I did it anyways.
Here we go.
This is the real one.
This is the one that takes a lot of...
Here we go.
It's getting bigger.
There it is.
Ooh, a key.
Don't fall into the ocean.
What's that?
I don't need these guys.
Slime key.
An ancient key for an ancient lock.
And another...
Ooh, a decoration.
Do I have a key now?
What?
Murderer.
Guys, they're just little fruit snacks.
Golden!
What do I do?
Feed it.
Give me that.
Don't touch that.
Everyone get the fuck away from that.
Don't eat that.
Got it.
Nice.
I got a gold floor.
I'm going to store it.
I'm not selling it.
I'm just going to hold it for a long time.
What am I going to do with all these hens?
Okay, now I can use that key.
Where should I use the key?
Where should I use the key in that cave?
Go this way.
Here.
Over here.
A few berries.
Okay, I have a key now.
I can use it on this door.
Isn't there more than one of these present right here?
Another one.
Ooh, air drive.
Oh, cool.
Well, it's not going to despawn.
Moss blanket.
Cool.
This area is awesome.
Whoa, wait.
If I go down there, I'm going to go back.
Go back.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
New slimes are here.
Wait, hold on.
I don't think I can get out of here.
What's in there?
Is it a separate exit?
Hold on.
Damn it.
I need to pick an inventory.
It's right to the right of the entrance.
Other way.
Or is it?
Try the path instead.
Is there a path?
That way.
Can I go this way?
Is this right?
Wait, give me this.
I got arcane.
All right.
This path right here.
But I can't go up there.
How do I get up there?
I'm going to jump around a bit.
Slime under feet and then jump on them.
That's a jet pack?
Yeah, the jet pack sucks.
You just float in the air.
You don't actually fly up.
Watch.
I have like a level one jet pack.
I think I can do it from here.
I got it.
Okay.
God damn it.
I should have carried it with me.
Wait, I'm carrying it with me.
Under the bridge, you go up.
I don't have an inventory space.
I can't do anything.
I have to go back.
Why is everyone so angry?
Get out of here.
The water germ with the water.
What?
I need to go home.
I have to go home and sell this shit.
Is there an inventory upgrade?
I hope there is.
Water is its own slot.
Yeah.
What are you guys on about?
Yeah, water is its own slot in the inventory.
That's why it's a circle and not a cube.
Chat's wicked zonked.
Heal brain chat.
Oh, God.
Okay, where?
Store the gold.
I'm going to wait till it's like $5,000.
I need to feed people these hens back.
They don't need them right now.
Does anybody have a quest?
There is a call.
All right.
What is it?
No, not not tomorrow morning.
Let's feed everybody.
No, we're not.
I'm going to bed.
We're going to feed everybody tomorrow morning.
Are you having fun?
Yeah, this is amazing.
Not quite ready yet.
All right.
We'll see tomorrow morning.
Airdrive.
Enhanced jetpack.
I mean, that's what I want.
That's what I was complaining about.
Tank booster.
50 units.
Power core.
Get the inventory.
I don't know.
It's not available.
I'm going to go to sleep.
I have a new day.
Time to get more food.
Let's feed everybody.
I'm ready.
Some of these aren't ready.
Okay.
You guys like everything.
So I'm going to give you the cheap stuff.
Whatever I can find that's cheap.
Love you guys.
Veggies and meat.
Thank you.
You guys eat everything.
Everything and everything.
Let's go take care of the guys in the cave.
Because I think it's only it's fruits, right?
How many are there in here?
I feel like I'm doing the jelly bean game.
We have to count how many are in here and guess.
One, two, one, two, three, four.
I don't know.
Buy an auto feeder.
Once I make some money from this, we'll take care of that.
That's a pretty big payday from that.
That's 36 of these.
Hell yeah.
And 36 of these too.
Nice.
I will take my fruits back and no one's eating them.
Other people got to eat.
Very cool.
It's been sucked up.
Good.
We're going to make another pen.
Or how about like an incinerator?
No, I don't think I can just throw people into the ocean.
The garden?
Coop?
The incinerator feels like it doesn't.
It's not necessary.
Pond.
I can make a pond.
Water is an incinerator.
Ready?
Oh, come on.
They're definitely ready.
All right, you guys.
We could feed the rest of you.
Whatever.
Eat up.
Ocean is slime, not water.
Read the Slimeopedia.
They love it.
That's actually pretty interesting.
I have to be really honest with you guys.
You guys know me, right?
Game's holding my interest.
It's very difficult.
Um, this is, um, I love this.
It's like my favorite thing ever.
I'm going to play the fuck out of this game on stream.
I just want to make sure everyone's aware of that.
Give me these.
More.
I feel like it's kind of like a Stardew Valley that I get to play and experience again.
Ooh, those are going up.
All right.
I'm 15.
They were 20 like two days ago.
Whatever.
1,500.
Nice.
Don't sell the gold.
You need to diversify your portfolio.
What?
You don't mean all, all entire everything into Blue Rock?
B-L-R-K.
I don't even know if that's like an actual thing.
Oh my God.
Portfolio.
Plortfolio.
I just put all my money into Tabby Plort.
Cool.
All right.
So now I can do some upgrades.
I don't know what you guys are doing in here, but I have nothing to do with this.
All right.
What's this call?
Let's do Mochi.
Last thing I want to do is make you look bad.
What do you want?
You got a fire crystal.
I don't, I've never even seen one of those.
I can get three of those and three of those easily, but I need one of these.
Is that probably a new area?
All right.
Everyone's been fed.
Everyone's good to go.
We're good.
I'm just going to, what should I do?
What should I upgrade?
Upgrade this.
Nutrients store.
Yeah, we're going to get this going.
And then auto feeders.
Yes.
Auto feeders for these guys.
They eat anything.
Auto feeder.
There it is.
I have to put food into it.
So there's 15 in there.
Activate it.
What is this?
Slow?
Medium?
I wish I could act.
Does this activate automatically?
Okay.
So now I can go to the new area.
Let me store this though.
One, two, three, four.
Excuse me.
Oh, fuck.
I have to pee again.
I can 100% guarantee you that
we're playing this the next time
I stream to get anything.
This is what we're doing.
I'm literally playing this.
Four.
Pink is worthless now.
Okay.
I got an auto feeder set up.
I'm going to go to the new area.
First, I'm going to pee.
I'll be right back.
Keep going.
Back to debt.
Sure.
And 10 billion?
10 million?
I'll be right back.
I'm eating.
I'm just sitting here eating.
Somebody just wrote.
He's definitely here playing with his wiener.
He's...
Oh, my God.
That's so ridiculous.
I'm just looking at some of the art.
Eating like a couple pieces of beef jerky.
You guys are fucked.
All right.
Let's keep going.
Good stuff as always.
Okay.
So I was going to go to the new area.
I was.
Yes.
New area.
And I need one of these like sauron eyes.
The rest of that stuff is easy to get.
I need one sauron eye.
Okay.
We're good.
Is there a fast way I can get there?
Can I teleport or something?
What's the best way to get there?
Do I have to walk?
Or can I get there from...
Bring back the sus.
You'll see it when it's at the break again.
Just whistle for your horse.
Walk nerd.
I didn't know if that was like a fast travel.
Whoa.
Whoops.
Dude, that was a wicked baste.
Oh, suck up that water.
Okay.
The first thing that I see in chat
is what I'm going to have for dinner.
No.
I saw pizza.
Thankfully, I can pick this up.
Thankfully.
I don't even want it.
I did see pizza.
But what kind of pizza?
Poop on pizza.
Poop and penis.
Cock on pizza.
Right.
Okay.
But give me a real one.
I want new slimes.
New slime.
They're little like sun hats.
A puddle slime.
I want a pond.
That's priority.
This is puddle slime.
Puddle plort.
Give me.
I'm going to make a bunch of puddle cats.
Mushrooms.
I mean, you got timed out
because you're just doing absolute all capitals.
But like you said mushrooms in one pile of puddle plorts.
Just look at how cute this is.
It's just like I have my delicious berry.
Whoa.
What are these things?
What the hell are these?
What is that?
What do they eat?
This exploded.
What did he turn into?
Margarita pizza chef's kiss.
Eat him a puddle port.
Feed him a puddle.
No, he's going to turn.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I need food.
What does he eat?
He eats everything.
Pink boom Largo.
Huh?
And there it is.
There's the thing I need.
Oh, there it is.
Yes.
Cool.
All right.
I need to.
I'm going to.
Oh, man.
There's another.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I need to go back.
I need a bunch more of these though.
I need to.
You stay.
Um, stay here.
What the fuck is that?
It's an ice cream cat.
What is that?
How do I?
What do I do?
No, don't eat that.
What do I do with this thing?
What do I do with the ice cream cat?
What does it want?
Eat meat.
Oh, needed meat.
I don't know how I didn't have any meat.
What happened to my boom?
What are the boom lords?
What happened to them?
I had two.
Such a.
I feel like goddamn the little mermaid.
I just came to a new place.
I want to be where the people are.
Up there where they have the fucking ice cream cats.
I've never part of this world.
This is all so new to me.
Does it follow yarn?
What the fuck is that?
And it doesn't she collect forks and shit?
So yeah, I feel that the exact same way right now.
Does it have like a human collection?
Hey, kid.
Okay.
Human skin.
No, not a human skin.
Oh my God.
That's a dark fucking Disney movie.
I want to be where the people are.
Up there where they're running around and shining.
Like Buffalo Bill.
It's got like human body parts down there.
Give that to me.
I just lost my entire way.
Wait, I made it up.
Okay.
Hey, what's that?
Just at some one point she starts like dancing around with a skeleton.
Part of your world.
All right.
Give me out of here.
Oh, definitely watched the little mermaid like yesterday.
I know I didn't.
I can't believe I didn't get a chance to take the ice cream cat.
I'm so mad.
So what should I do with this yarn?
Give it to one of the cats.
Yes.
Why are you doing that?
Why are you guys doing that?
All right.
I have now some very interesting things going on.
First of all, put this down.
I'm going to get seven chickens, six melon drinks.
I'm going to get a lot of stuff here.
Hold on.
Let's deposit this little plorts.
The room will fail with yes.
You dick.
Who's eating?
Are you guys getting auto fed?
Only three left.
All right.
Well, here you guys just eat these.
Okay.
Now.
Yep.
Okay.
Cool.
You need rocks and light bulbs.
I thought he was talking to chat.
This dude is crazy.
Was he talking to chat or was he talking to himself?
Is this guy nuts?
No, I don't have enough room.
Let's put these.
I need to put a couple in here.
Shit.
What do I do?
Say I sell them.
Shit.
Wait, do I want a rock puddle?
I might want a rock puddle.
Oh, that's dumb.
What happened?
Puddle cat.
Could it be a puddle cat?
Puddle slimes can't mix.
Boom puddle or riot.
Puddle cat is a great username.
Boom puddle.
But you can't mix.
You can't?
Boom puddle.
All right.
I'll do boom puddle.
But first, I've got to...
All right.
I'm getting overwhelmed.
Put this in the cat.
Give this to the cat.
Give the cats this.
They're going to love this.
All right.
Don't all...
You attack it at once.
All right.
I need a puddle.
Puddle is what?
500?
I think it's 500.
How many chickens do I have?
Way too many.
There's only one rooster.
What happened?
This one rooster is doing all this?
Damn.
Okay.
I need just three of the...
Let's go.
You eat veggies and meat.
You don't eat berries.
God damn it.
Let's give it back.
Give it back.
I want to stop hurting each other.
Give me back those berries.
I need some supplies.
Fruits and meat.
All right.
I want to get them from here.
Tuck it up.
Berries or...
Berries.
They're the same thing.
That's a big harvest.
Cool.
So, pond.
Pond.
What are you going to do with this?
Let's find out.
Activate it.
All right.
So, puddle slime.
They eat water.
Are these guys shitting anything out?
They actually...
Can I get anything from them?
They're so happy.
They love the puddle slime.
I don't know.
I feel like this is like an exhibit at an art studio
or a mall or something.
There's a bunch of people that just want to come in and see so badly this.
It's like a zoo.
We're not open yet.
Are they hungry?
They want to eat this?
Do the Meatwad voice.
Okay.
What are you talking about, Silk?
I don't even want to do that, Silk.
Meatwad, I think that sometimes an idiot like you
needs to be slapped in the face.
So, I'm going to.
Go down here.
Now, Frylock.
I can't do Frylock.
What's going on in here?
I did the same fucking joke.
Like six months ago.
I did this six months ago.
Stop pulling it back.
I did this already.
This exact same thing.
I did the what's going on in here.
Shoot the water?
They don't like that.
Does he like that?
Okay.
Well, we got that.
Cool.
Are you guys having fun over here?
You guys having fun?
Okay.
Let's go get our haul.
Save the earth.
Recycle jokes.
It's true.
All right.
I have enough space for this.
We're just going to go one, two, three.
Bingo.
So, what are these like fruits?
These new fruits?
I've never seen these before.
What's in there?
What are these?
Mint mangoes.
Interesting.
Intensely sweet with a cool minty finish.
Who eats these?
Cool.
I have a thousand bucks.
Can I upgrade this thing?
Additional storage.
Up to four ports.
I want it.
I do.
Okay.
So, what do I do?
Can I do?
Hmm.
I cannot give this to a slime.
Well, I mean a slime as in the puddle slime.
Can I not give this to a puddle?
I kind of want to try it.
Oh, what's the point of these guys?
I just spent...
Oh, oops.
Get in the water.
Get in the...
No, I want...
Where'd that go?
Where did it go?
Did it fall through the crack?
No, thank God.
I was going to say that would be so annoying.
Okay.
So, I get it.
They produce puddle ports.
I want to make boom something.
All right.
What else do I want down here?
I'm going to make another one.
Make a boom cat.
All right.
I'm going to make a boom cat in here.
You don't want it?
Cool.
Likes meat.
Okay.
I want to keep you in here.
I don't want you to fly out.
You're not going to fly out, right?
You eat meat.
Okay.
What is meat in this game?
I feel like I've seen fruits, vegetables.
Is there like a meat?
Like you have like chickens, right?
Is there something else besides chicken or rooster?
No.
I want to test it.
Here you go.
Eat that and let me give it some boom.
You all right?
Eat this guy.
He's scrumptious.
There you go.
And...
That's too...
And we can just keep making them.
I need to...
Wait.
Jeez, let's get the shit out of me.
I don't know why.
Re-boom cats.
Now we're going to...
I need a ceiling.
Yeah, I know.
I need a ceiling right now.
I need to...
Stay there.
I got...
I'm working on it.
I need...
How much of the puddles go for?
57.
I'm working on it.
Okay.
Auto feeder is empty.
Fill it with heartbeats.
Okay.
Here.
Fruits.
You guys like fruit?
Oh, fuck you.
I want...
Go in.
I'm trying to get money.
How did you get out?
You don't eat fruits.
The thriller.
I can't take a phone call right now.
I need more chickens.
Okay.
Collect it.
Sell everything.
How did you get out?
Where are you even from?
How did you get out of here?
You came all the way over here.
I need to put a goddamn lid on this place.
No.
I...
But these guys are less valuable.
I don't care.
All right.
I got...
Hold on.
I...
Eat these.
Thank you.
Eat.
I need you to eat those.
Come on, Tabby.
Eat.
You don't...
You...
There's so much opportunity for you.
Thank you.
You're long enough.
One more.
Where are they?
All right.
We're good.
Excellent.
Boom, cats.
Good?
Looks good.
Awesome.
Put some chickens in here.
I'm gonna sell these.
Yeah, this ain't worth a lot of money.
One of them escaped.
Where?
Nobody escaped.
The Tabby flew away?
What?
I saw it too.
Really?
Okay.
I can't quite get that now.
Cool.
Let's come back with some chickens.
And then I'm gonna sell these
and get a lot of money for the boom plorts.
How much do they go for?
58 a pop.
Cool.
All right.
Let's go.
And here we go.
Throw them in here.
Eat up.
I want more of those boom plorts.
How much is it for an auto...
Air net.
That's what I want.
Eat up.
Any more?
Good.
Slimes are so cute.
They really are.
Hey, this game's awesome.
I had no idea this was a gem collecting stock market game.
I honestly thought this was Pokemon.
I thought it was a Pokemon game.
Okay, we're good.
Everyone's locked in.
They've been fed.
I got a lot of boom plorts to sell.
Let's go.
I actually might make enough money to come put a net on.
I think we're doing that.
I'm coming to put a net on.
That is wrong.
I love this game.
These slimes are so cute.
Wait, what?
Sell the bloom.
Boom plorts.
Make some money.
1,400 bucks.
I think it's time to upgrade my body.
Tank booster.
50.
Yep.
Dash boots.
Let's get them.
Did I get raided?
I did.
I don't see a raid.
I missed a raid.
I don't see it on any dashboard or anything.
I missed it.
What was it?
Who was it?
I got two dashboards open.
I don't see anything.
Bob is all I...
Bob chickens.
Two and then one.
Easy.
He wants an old one?
He wants two elder roosters?
Oh, no.
What does he want?
That's different.
What is that one?
I don't think I have any of those.
The briar hen.
Oh, shit.
I don't have one.
Okay, well.
Oh, whatever.
I think I'm ready to go back and explore that area.
I have two briar.
So it's the red hens.
It's red?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got to...
Hold on.
There's so much to do.
There's too much stuff to do.
Put glasses on.
Somebody escaped?
All right.
These are puddle.
Gold.
I'm gonna put the mangoes in here
because I don't really know what to do with them.
It's just a good...
Like a better food.
And we'll feed...
We'll put the heartbeats in the heartbeat container.
But okay.
Cool.
Time to...
Wait.
They don't like fruits.
Don't give them fruits.
I'm gonna read chatter for your record.
I just did.
Thank you.
All right.
Go.
I need a briar hen.
What's my favorite fruit?
Banana or pineapple?
Pick one.
So, did I go...
Wait.
Excuse me.
Whoa.
Any briar hens?
No.
13 days straight.
Briar hens?
Probably in the other area.
A lot of shit over here.
Banana is a bewy.
Why did I say it like that?
Here.
Get out of here.
I said it like some half-assed dude.
Banana is a bewy.
Power core.
MK2.
Cool.
All right.
That's a...
It's decorating this entrance.
All right.
This is a big zone.
Let's just go across.
Okay.
Itchy eyes.
I'm looking for that ice cream cat again.
Ooh.
Here we go.
Yep.
Briar hens.
Cool.
Got it.
If I see an ice cream cat, scream.
I like the puddle slam.
I'm gonna take another one.
Is this briar?
Briar?
Briar hen?
No.
Okay.
Keep going.
What's over here?
Moss blanket may seem like an ancient jungle of sorts,
but the fact is that much of what you see here
wasn't even around when I first began exploring this land.
Whatever.
Cats.
Pink slimes.
I see that's a...
I see orange.
I see orange slimes.
What are you?
I'll take it.
Just a boom slime.
What are you?
You're a honey slime.
What the fuck?
Come here.
A honey slime.
Oh, give me these.
Is this a super honey slime?
Is this a honey...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't shoot them out.
I want those.
Why?
Fuck me.
Where are those honey slimes?
It's a big cat honey.
There you are.
All right.
I want these things.
And I also...
Give her the puddle slime.
I don't want to put...
Puddle slimes are cool, but I want the...
There's another...
Hi.
I've got globules?
Globs?
What are they called?
Glob go gab galabs?
I'm the glob go gab galab.
I love butch.
This place is a treasure trove.
I am the glob go gab galab.
The shwabble dabble flabble fabble fabble flabble flab.
I am the yeast of thoughts and mind.
I had to go all out for that one.
I like the honey slimes.
You really didn't?
Yes, I did.
What do you mean?
No, I didn't have to go all out for that.
What are you talking about?
Give me that back.
That back.
Puddle.
You're a psycho ooey gooey one.
If the stream was not on right now, I would be...
Wait.
Okay.
I would be doing the thing that he does over and over again until...
Like my throat got tired.
Oh, what's that?
Hey.
Wait.
Oh, man.
There's one of these things.
I...
Sly cooper.
Shit.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What are these fruits?
These are new fruits?
I have to go back.
I need to make a new...
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
I'm overwhelmed.
I'm going to slow down.
I'm going to work on honey and boom.
I got the last 10 that I wanted.
Drop the plorts.
Why?
Finish the quest.
Yeah.
I want to bring the honey stuff back.
I need to feed these guys.
Get the sly cooper.
Hold on.
Jesus.
All right.
I'm going to take the sly cooper.
What just happened?
I'm going to get rid of the honey.
Come here.
Hunter slime.
Give me a few more of these.
I want to make a couple of new cages.
I want a few more honey slimes
and a few more hunter slimes.
Your pod is locked.
What?
Why?
Schwabble, dabble, dabble,
flabble, dabble, flub, flub.
Schwibble, schwabble, schwibble,
flabble, flabble, flub, flub.
Oh, come on.
It's an old ass meme.
It really is very old.
I mean, by the internet standards,
two or three years,
that might as well be 100.
Oh, good.
Here.
I want to get a good 10 to 20 of these.
New carrots.
Come here.
Honey slime.
I hear somebody freaking out.
Who turned?
Me.
I am.
Very, very tricky to do the first part of that.
I am the...
Got to get it right.
Oh, look, a decoration.
Cool.
Something's glowing over here.
What?
Shit.
I don't even know what I did,
but I wanted to...
Whatever.
Give me these.
Two more briar hens.
Oh, hunter slime.
Got it.
Cool.
Boom blocks.
Go home, poo poo brain streamer.
Come back and get the stuff.
Remember to sleep.
Okay.
Where does this take me?
Royal jelly.
I use that to go back?
Wait, it's not a return portal?
Are you kidding me?
Oh, well.
All right.
So what do I get for this?
Money and...
Yeah, fine.
Here you go.
Fill up this hen house.
Briar hens.
I probably should make another pen,
shouldn't I?
Why are these honey slimes purple?
Get the elder chicken out.
Hold on.
Play boom blocks or the debt will increase
with interest, whatever.
Okay.
Um, I want to...
Still loading up this one.
I'm gonna just wait until this is at like 100.
Let's keep the fruit in here.
This is a fruit.
So who likes fruits?
Who likes fruits?
We do.
A lot of debt.
There's your debt counter.
Okay.
Pog fruit.
Not bad.
Let's get rid of them.
I don't want to use them anymore.
We'll suck up all these radishes.
Oops.
We need a new place for honey slimes.
And for hunter slimes.
I need two more dens.
Come back and take care of this.
How are you guys doing?
We're hungry.
Get that in.
I'm gonna have a big payday here in a second.
All right.
You guys want something.
Hello.
Okay.
I'll take the boom boards.
All right.
New den.
Burgess.
Another one.
All right.
Hunters are going in here.
Honey's are going in here.
Cool.
Increase that wall, please.
Where are they?
Oh.
All right.
Just don't jump out.
The honey's purple.
I have like the DLC.
Purchase skin thing.
I don't know.
I'm gonna come back in here with some fruits.
I'll take this bounty from the puddles.
Thank you.
You too.
You've done a great job.
Look.
I will.
What happened to him?
Stay in here.
Okay.
Everyone hang out in here for a few minutes.
I'll be right back.
We need vegetables to go up there.
Tuck these up.
Veggies.
I just love a big, a nice crunchy radish.
I have radishes too.
I can't wait to eat them.
I'm gonna have pizza and radishes tonight.
That sounds awesome to me.
Separately, by the way.
Separately.
Not together on the same thing.
An hour apart.
Pizza for dinner.
And then have radishes later.
Separately.
I didn't say at the same time.
I mean these are almost ready.
Might as well.
Wait.
All right.
You guys like veggies.
There you go.
Now it's time to do a massive collection.
You'll see.
I'm gonna.
All right.
Prediction.
I will have two to three thousand dollars in my bank account.
When this is over.
Find out.
Dummy.
Gold.
What's he got?
Nothing, nothing, nothing.
How's the auto feeder?
Fill it back up.
Good.
I knew it was all gonna fall.
I told you.
Good to go.
Suck everything up.
Suck it.
Up.
Suck it up.
I mean.
Go for it.
Very cool.
Here.
And then here.
We.
I didn't finish it.
My new people are gonna be mad.
Have these.
Oh, these have increased in value.
How about a phosphorus hunter.
Honey.
Boom.
Spider.
Put those back.
Oh, here we go.
Watch this.
The punch through the monitor.
And the only reason you're reading this is because you're so long.
As I don't move my arm, the computer stays alive.
But you punched into the monitor like your hand went into the monitor.
What are you doing that for?
You gotta relax, dude.
Gamer rage.
Look at this selling.
Oh, fun sorting algorithm.
All right, I'm gonna hold on to the booms for now.
I think I'm gonna sell the puddles because do I really?
Lots of chickens.
All right, we gotta feed.
What happened to the rooster?
Oh, they think they ate the rooster.
Is it dead?
The rooster's dead.
All right, the rooster died.
I need a new rooster.
Hi, guys.
Give me my boom blocks.
You good?
This is a huge payday.
This is 21 of these damn things.
Boom blocks.
I have boom blocks.
I have it for the way the disc is right behind me.
I'll play it one day.
Oh, these guys are cool.
They're royal jellies.
Okay, so should I do royal jelly boom?
Royal jelly honey.
They are honey.
Boom honey.
Boom honey hunter.
Royal jelly hunter.
Boom hunter.
Puddle hunter.
Hunter hunter.
Honey hunter.
Boom hunter.
X hunter.
Honey hunter.
Okay, so here we go.
Somebody, I need to feed one of these guys.
So I need to feed one of them honey
and then feed one of them hunter.
Okay, I think I got it.
So feed them.
I don't have any honey.
I have to have honey.
I have to have a honey glob go gabby lab
before I can do this next part of that.
All right, I got what I wanted.
Feed them.
Oh, wait, it doesn't have to be.
Right.
Okay, I get it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They eat meat.
Here, eat one of these.
Oh, eat that.
Hurry.
Come on.
What's that from?
Resident Evil 5.
Got it.
Thank you.
Come on.
Holy shit.
How'd you get that?
Sheva.
You need to be careful.
Holy shit.
That was burned in my mind.
You need to be careful.
It happened every time.
She always get like this shit kicked out of her.
I would actually, I would shoot her accidentally in the back every time.
I would respond.
Sheva.
Jessie.
You need to be careful.
I was bad at that game.
Focus.
Right, right, right.
Yeah, okay.
What am I doing?
All right, we're giving a hunter to the honey.
Sheva.
Sheva like spray painting me with the spray heel
while the chainsaw guy was right behind her.
And then just...
Here we go.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
Action.
Whoa.
Now, what do you eat?
Hey, why is he angry?
What's he angry for?
Stop being so angry.
Don't be so fucking angry.
Everybody eat up.
We need you to turn into hunters.
They're so fucking mad right now.
Why?
I need a music box.
There, relax.
More hunters.
Stop.
Why are they...
Who's exploding?
Jesus.
Jessie, be happy for God's sakes.
We need more hunters.
Oh my God, you're killing them.
Stop.
Stop it.
Why are they so mad?
Little assholes.
We need...
I don't think I was suppose to do that.
Get the fuck over here.
You little cuber.
Fuck.
i'm gonna be so angry will you guys why are they doing this what is your problem they're attacking
you well why relax what's the problem stay in here at least i have one left all right so this
is a wait what happened to the i have a regular hunter in here feed them they eat fruit and meat
i'll be back with fruit okay i still have one hunter give them meat hold on i can't just give
um i'll be right back what are they i get it all right bye incoming call jigsaw go to answering
machine royal hunters are a royal pain in the ass they kind of are all right we're gonna feed
chickens in there first of all let's make some money how much is honey worth a shitload i told
you at least three thousand dollars after that sorry sorry hold on we gotta see this let's take
a look so this says sorry this has just been playing the whole time the entire stream it's
been playing the entire stream at like zero percent volume let's see let's get the apology
let's get the apology very sorry about the last trap so low
oh
wait it works wait what how do i get it how do i get it to work are you shitting me
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait i gotta i gotta i gotta try
fuck i gotta get one side correct i gotta get one side i don't guys i have no fucking idea how
to do a rubik's cube i have absolutely no idea i've i've only picked them up and just mushed
them around in my hands for two minutes i don't even know how it works i don't understand how it
works you have to get the colors on the right side but i don't know i don't know how to do that
i don't even i don't know the mechanics i think i got it hold on i always got orange
wait hold on clock is ticking i know i'm trying to get this done where's orange orange is here okay
i gotta try to get what has the most what has the most things on the side
what has the most what has the most things on the side what has the i don't know what
side has the most color on it i'm not gonna be able to do this shit hold on where's white wait
hold on a second god damn it hold on wait wait wait wait wait why is it nice music
why is this like an acoustic guitar i feel like i'm someone's i'm in a college
dorm room and someone's about to start singing oh here it goes it's slime rancher
wait i can turn the cube too holy shit this is amazing wait um isn't it there's like extra
colors holy fuck i'm almost getting there don't get it i never did i should have paid attention
to school that's something i did i shouldn't pay attention to school i didn't pay any attention
to school and then um rubik's cube you have like seven hours to do this i have such a long time
i have an insanely long time wait but what over here
fuck i don't know what to do i i don't even if i look it up jigsaw is very patient yeah apparently
you gotta get each hold on a minute i know how to do it now i know what to do i know exactly what
to do i know what to do jigsaw you're fucked i'm coming out i'm getting out of this alive
i know i know what to do you have to get a solid white on each row don't try to get it all in one
go you try to get it okay i get it i know what to do i have no idea what to do i have no idea
what's going on hold on wait wait wait wait wait jigsaw am i allowed to use my phone
i'm sorry how to suffer you can have whatever i'm on my phone he didn't take my phone he's
an idiot he didn't take my phone away when i got into the front door this video is removed from
youtube why so if you've never solved the cube before it may seem impossibly hard but today i'll
be teaching you a method that i used to teach many people did not believe they could ever be
able to solve the cube anything along the way becomes unfamiliar and you need more examples
thank you that being said it's time for you to solve your first cube yep so the first thing you
do is find the white center piece and then hold that on top what you do is solve the white cross
what what like a white piece on the bottom layer um what's bottom there's no bottom there is no
top there is no left and right always because he has a different cube
he has a different cube he has one that has like an actual centerpiece oh this person's so
intelligent they're way too intelligent for me but that's the person's way too smart for me all right
hold on i'm gonna do it my way remove the stickers just remove just pull the stickers off
remove the stickers i have to just if you get one side no these are not even possible is it weird
that i feel like if you can do a rubik's cube and like just by looking at it that you are on like
another plane of intelligence or existence or something like you can just look at it and do it
like guys i have trouble with you know when you have looking at a telephone and it has the number
the letters and the numbers corresponding to each one i still i have trouble like spelling a word
still i'm not gonna do a rubik's cube some people can just like
it's like you're you're an alien you're an alien person you are an alien and you have like a hyper
alien intelligence not me i can't even figure out a fucking telephone you can do it i can't do it
fuck i can't do it it's too hard i don't i don't understand it it's too many it's too much you can't
give up i i'm gonna give up i'm gonna give up in about five seconds wait hold on and then and then
i don't want to hear the saw theme song again i don't want to hear it again imagine he's playing
this through the speakers in the room he loves this shit he's he's just repeating this into the
megaphone i'm never gonna be able to figure this out ever this is so funny though i love this
i can't how did you even do this dude so how do i give up do i just like inhale the gas call
someone for help who's who's no one's gonna help me right now i know i'm gonna have no one to help
me you can't phone a friend in the jigsaw room and by the way i have to phone a friend and i have to
get the one specific guy that knew anything anything at all about like the ink and empire
right like this is a very specific question it's not like just oh hey by the way uh what's two plus
two google of rubik's cube solver call jigsaw no one can help me i no one can help me
i i can't call it no i'm not gonna bother somebody uh hey yeah i totally you know i'm
in a room full of gas right now actually that is like a good like time to call somebody
hey do you know how to do a rubik's cube i'm in a room that's about a gas is gonna like start
filling the room and i'm gonna make 488 million dollars i feel like that would not bother me if
you woke me up at fucking four o'clock in the morning hey dude uh you don't make them you do
a rubik's cube uh even getting five percent of this pot is life-changing money um we can do it
for you i don't think you could solve the white side yeah okay i'm gonna go i'm gonna i'm gonna
do it let me go fuck this here we go i'm ready i'm gonna take my time no no no no no no no god
damn it all right how you doing not good not good i barely even have the white side done
well i'll check back in on you in another few hours see how you're doing okay thanks
like can i eat something can i have some food or something i'm gonna be for like six hours
trying to do this i could order a piece of just slide it under the door or something i don't know
you sick fuck whatever i might i you bastard well i don't know i'm just fucking hungry
i might get it eventually there's only one more okay there's a white there wait hold on
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait where's the other white where god i feel like i'm so close
but so far away from even getting this white side do the edges first then the corners what do you
mean what everything's a corner edges first what do you mean edges first what does that mean
you've ruined it what make a plus sign make a plus sign make a plus sign all right
i'm gonna try to make a plus sign i don't i don't get it okay hold on wait what plus sign
is this anyone in the middle i can't do it okay i can't i've never had i don't i'm such bad
spatial awareness and shit like it's never going to happen it will never happen i'm dead in this
scenario i'm going to die in this scenario you give me a week i'm i'll die in this scenario
you could give me the you could feed me you can give me all kinds of delicious food
you could you could come in and like give me like a back massage you could tell me how to do it
somebody can step by step sit there and go okay jereby bottom row spin horizontal once and i go
what'd you say like no there's no way not gonna happen use the force brain no i can't i'm not
it's impossible you could let me sleep you could be like jereby it's time for you to go to bed now
have you eaten all of your snake potatoes green beans and salmon yeah it was delicious i'm very
full and i'm very satisfied good you see that bed over there that's a california king and it's got
silk sheets on it wow is that for me yes and the room will be kept at exactly 70 degrees
fahrenheit with a 35 humidity i will dim the lights and i will play slight white noise
that sounds really relaxing it is and by the way on the device next to the bed there is the entire
first five seasons of spongebob and it's at 100 battery on the ipad holy shit i love that that's
amazing i can just rest and go to bed and just relax and watch spongebob yes i'll see you in the
morning and i wake up the next morning and like a tray of bacon eggs and fucking sausages and
toast and shit with like beans rolls in underneath and it's fresh it's hot and he just made it
it was your breakfast jereby go for it i know you can do it it would take i would take me a month and
i would just live there for a month and i wouldn't solve this i'm doing it every day i would not be
able to do it ever it would never you could hook me up to a machine that kept me alive forever
you could inject like ivs into both arms and give me drugs drugs that kept me alive for
a hundred thousand years and i would not do it it still wouldn't happen so it would be a rotting
fucking skeleton in this weird basement by the time that i even got close wait wait wait wait
wait wait what's this what's this please click this please click this hold on hold on no three
by three solutions solve you can do the cube you can do the cube.com why is this
is this like a motivational video you can do the cube.com hold on can i do the cube.com
Jesus can't you can do the cube.com solution rubik's cube 2020 solution guide uses the
layered method top layer get to know your rubik's cube that one create a daisy holding your rubik's
cube okay hold on begin by holding your rubik's cube with the yellow centerpiece in the up
guys this is a scam cube this is a scam cube there is no center up piece this is scam cube
where's this where's the center up piece with the yellow centerpiece on the up face
where's the centerpiece what the fuck are you talking about this i'm reading the guide
you're a fucking idiot what so this this okay look at the up face look at the top layer to
locate the edge pieces that have a white tile leave them where they are what the thing in the
center the yellow piece in the middle this one but i've moved it around center of the nine by nine
yes yeah i but look at the top layer to locate the edge pieces that have a white
tile leave them where they are what doesn't matter it's the example to the right notice
that this stage is okay that if it's okay if the white tile is not touching the yellow centerpiece
we have no white touching the centerpiece okay we're good look at the middle layer move edge
pieces that have a white tile from the middle layer onto the top layer i'm just killing saw
just throw the grenade just throw a grenade in the room and then just donate all this money like
just throw the throw roll the grenade in the room and just donate them just donate the money
i don't want it boom i don't care look at the middle and have moved edge pieces that have a
white tile from the middle layer under the top layer like this i don't know be careful not to
bump out the white edges already in the daisy rotate the up face to move a white edge out of
the way before moving into the white edge into the daisy throw the grenade words
haha word salad i'm trying to have the fucking end of the movie in my head
rotate the up face to move a white edge out of the way before moving another white edge into the daisy
put the yellow on top wait you look at the bottom layer move edge pieces that have a
white tile from the bottom layer onto the top layer and flip it or sometimes when you place
the edge in the top layer the white tile is not on the up face and it needs to be flipped
to flip the edge so the white tile is on the up face hold your rubik's cubes the edge
that needs to be flipped is on the right our face follow the algorithm what algorithm
it's not a math problem what do we follow the algorithm there is no algorithm follow the
algorithm he's the adh just saw saw hello saw yes where is it uh i've been here for a very long
time a very long time i am ready for you to throw the grenade down to like the tube that's where i
know where you're sitting you have like big like pvc pipe tube just drop it down there please
just throw the grenade at me please just throw the grenade could you i mean you do have you do
have at least two or three more months of living here just completely rent free you don't have to
pay anything to resolve this enough means an investment group that exists no um just throw
the grenade down i'm done i would like to leave oh i'll be sure and make you a bit of choice
making my choice please throw the grenade into the pvc pipe really okay all right well then good luck
thanks uh sorry i couldn't get it done i would have loved to have tried and done it
but now he's playing why are you playing this music so
are you okay are you okay so you held it for way too long you held the grenade but i'm like how do
i get out of here i have to get out of this room i'm stuck here for two months
he has a robot to live oh my god no i'm gonna die down here well i was i was supposed to die
down here but he didn't let me he fucking held it for too long oh fuck guys i hit my head against
the wall like a hundred times so i need to get out of here i have to get the fuck out of here
oh the music is still playing for two months
oh i'm done i'm out of here i'm done i'm done streams over streams over
i need to make the daisy i don't know if that means i have to pick a flower or something so
so i can't do it i don't know how to do rubik's cubes they're so difficult
and i know some of you guys probably are like oh this is really easy dude you just have to like
pay attention and like relax i can't oh well i mean i i've got to tell you i've got to say
this is very important um i this is guaranteed best one guy moment of the year like it has to be
i can i just can i can we just give the award to this guy now
i mean this person is just can we just give them like a golden one i think this person deserves
like like a platinum one and then we can vote on the others i don't know that i that might be
better ones who knows but holy shit dude whoever whoever made this wherever you are like this is
fucking hilarious i'm gonna close it out because i can't do it i lose oh my goodness that was
fucking hilarious give us the link sorry link it's so funny that he made a sorry unbelievable
all right i'm gonna get going i'll see you guys in a few days let's see what's today saturday one
two three i'll see you guys on wednesday we'll do wednesday thursday i'm gonna play more slime
rancher and um the week after that maybe i'm trying to get into gta rp and more work is
going to be done on the archaeology stream too which that's going to be a lot of fun march 6th
if you listen to my voice i was just dying march 6th is the archaeology stream bring your shovel
1 pm pacific i mean honestly like i don't think i could i don't think i could go back to play
slime rancher after that i will see you guys on wednesday wednesday at two o'clock pacific thanks
for joining me this game is by the way like one of my favorites of the year it came up five years
ago but whatever oh oh you wanted the link right right right here here's the sorry link good night
everybody we'll see you wednesday thanks for watching as always of course here come the credits all the
subs gifted subs resubs long-term subs new subs thank you appreciate it thanks guys this music
is still playing from fucking saw man oh right yeah let's um let's raid let's raid kiwo go say
hello to kiwo uh she's currently doing gta rp cool and i had to brush up on uh on how this works
maybe i don't know kiwo she's fucking hilarious go give her a follow stick around oh my god my
stomach hurts go raid jigsaw oh yeah we'll see we'll see you wednesday good night guys jigsaw
yeah and that she is doing rp so you know she's probably rp'ing don't don't she doesn't have to
she doesn't have to sing a fucking raid song okay she's rp'ing you understand behave uh have a great
night guys we'll see you later goodbye good night take care of yourselves my throat is like gone
see you wednesday bye