Father? Father? When can I go and play with the puppies, daddy? I'm Lucius. I'm Lucius. I'm such a bad boy, such a bad bad boy. I'm Lucius. I'm Lucius. I'm gonna kill you.
What? What?
Please let that be in the video.
What? Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's wrong with this guy?
This guy was just trying to get me, and yell at me and stuff, and now he's just marveling at the sink.
So we're gonna try this. Hello?
That's it. I'm taking you to the authorities.
Yes, please. Take me to the authorities.
You would seriously think that after doing this like 15 to 16 times, this guy would look down and be like, I shouldn't walk on the green shit.
No. Of course not.
What the hell?
I'm Lucius. I'm Lucius. Hello, nurse. Hey, what's going on, guy? I'm Lucius. I'm Lucius. I'm gonna take over your fucking mind. I'm Lucius. I'm Lucius. I'm gonna go walk into a...
I'm scared.
What am I seeing?
Dude, I'm like a supernatural psycho dragging her on a bookshelf. Like, what do you mean, what am I seeing?
What the fuck is...
Pick up those shaggy butts. Pick up those shaggy butts.
Oh, she actually did.
She just took them. What? You stole those cigarettes?
I clearly threw those on the ground.
So now, I'm gonna fucking can ya.
You wanna get canned?
You ever been to Kansas? I'm gonna fucking can ya.
This lady keeps ducking.
What are you eating? Invisible food?
I love invisible food. What about the guy on the left? What's he doing here? Just wearing that nice shirt.
Fucking naked guy. Just walking through.
This guy's not gonna have... He's gonna have a lot of trouble.
What the fuck?
You dropped it.
You didn't even do anything. You dropped it, dude.
This... Without context, this is really strange.
What's this guy's story? I wanna know his full story.
Yeah, your arm's gonna be fine. Don't worry.
I mean, we're in a hospital right now. You're probably here for surgery or something.
Let me get you to your emergency room, surgery room.
Geez.
So on the right here, as you can see, I'm gonna give you a little quick tour before we go to your room.
That's gonna be the operating room, but I wanna introduce you to one of my favorite doctors.
Over here is Dr. Dean Dingleman.
Dean Dingleman, here's the patient you'll be operating on.
His name is Kryden, Kaden, whatever his name is.
I just wanted to give you a close interaction with the doctor before you go and prep for surgery.
Just take you up a floor or two. That's all we gotta do here. Just don't mind me.
I mean, this thing's always broken.
Gotta throw a can of dog food at it to make sure we can get it open.
But yeah, I mean, can you believe that weather?
I mean, we had like a foot of snow today. I mean, can't you believe...
No.
You're not gonna let me push him out the elevator?
Let me push a guy out a fucking elevator.
Fucking high C ectocoola. Let's see how you deal with this one.
All right, sir, so go ahead and... I knew it.
They always slip. It doesn't matter if they're sitting, if they're on a fucking workout bench.
It doesn't matter. It does not matter.
I didn't even... I didn't do that.
Everybody just saw that I came back from...
I loaded into the game, and this happened.
I don't know what happened here. I had nothing to do with this.
Absolutely nothing to do with it.
Who's gonna get the sandwich first?
Everybody wanted the sandwich.
What?
I didn't poison that sandwich.
I did not poison that sandwich.
That guy just died.
Because he ate a dirty sandwich.
Just a second here.
So you two, that's normal.
You should be doing that.
There's no reason why two people can't be sitting in the same spot at the same time.
I mean, why...
What are you doing?
Hey guys, welcome to my new hit series called...
What would happen if this would happen?
So today, in this new episode of...
What would happen if this was gonna happen?
We have a thing of donuts here.
And we've got these pills. We're gonna combine them.
And we're gonna see, you know...
What would happen if this was gonna happen?
See, the doctor here, he doesn't even know there's donuts behind him.
He's gonna pick up those donuts.
Oh man, I mean, what's gonna happen here?
He's gonna eat these donuts. He loves donuts.
With a giant pill box on them.
So, next episode on...
What would happen if this was gonna happen?