Uh, so I have no idea how this game works. We're gonna give it a try. See if it's any good.
Hard Space Ship Breaker. Okay, I did already make an account in this game because I knew we were
probably gonna pivot because... I don't know. I had it just in case. We needed to do it, right?
Turn this shit on so you can hear it. And we add it. Looking for a... There you are.
This is Hard Space Ship Breaker. This for cleanup detail in space is what I've been told. We're ready
for Evolvo. Okay, anybody that says anything that says Evolvo in it and please play it,
I want you to ban them for at least four hours. At least. That's like 240,000 minutes.
Don't want that one. All right, let's go. This is me, Jerry. Career. Please, please. How do you...
How does this game work? I guess it's gonna tell me, right? Wait, was I supposed to jump?
I can't even hear his audio. Okay, shh. Let's get to work. All right, how do I do this? Open
the work order. Thrust forward. Thrust backward. Descend. Ascend. Break. Roll. Oh, boy. Thrust
backwards. Now, uh, descend for three seconds. I want to change that though. I don't like to see
his descend. Descend for three seconds. Controls break. I'm so glad there's a break that's a hard
break. Grapple. It rolls. Yeah, roll left for two seconds. Depute game. That's all right. I've been
known to at least get an hour into puke games. Grapple. Grapple. Hold. Push an object when
grappled is F. Some objects can be detached with your grapple. Look for the detach prompt. Whoa,
wait a minute. That's a push? So F pushes. I want it to descend. Can you not move when you're in
the... Okay, maybe you can't move. All right, salvage the antenna. How do you salvage something?
Grapple. And then I drag it over here. Green arrows. Yeah, but how do I pull it over there?
Use the grapple to attach an antenna. Push when... Push. No, that's not an antenna.
Oh, where the... Where the fuck is an antenna? Wait, that's the antenna. This doesn't look like
an antenna. I thought it wanted me to grapple with weird things. I don't know. It didn't... Okay.
Grapple the antenna. Hit the brakes. Breaks. Breaks. Break. Oh, this is not going to work well.
This is going to be bad. This is going to be bad. This is going to be very bad. I'm not going to be
able to do this. Attach an antenna. This is going to be really tricky. Okay, grab and detach.
Shoot the antenna. Didn't I just do that? All right, then throw it in there.
Physics gun. The whole game is physics. No. Scanner. Cut points. Oh, cut points. I see some.
Are they yellow? Okay, so you need to cut this shit. Cut level two. Execute the cut. Grapple.
Equip the cutter. Z. It's two. Could it be Z? Okay, let me see it. I'm trying to do the cut.
Okay, I just pressed two. I pressed it like five times. Descend! It's C. Oh my god, it's not
control. You were grappling. Amazon keyboard. No, no, I wouldn't... I don't even know what direction
we've been looking at this fucking thing. All right, scan it. Right there. All right, stop moving.
Cut that. Cutting it. Can I do it? Cut point. Right there, right? Does it have to go through it?
Isn't the cut point right here? Salvage it. Yeah, but do I have to pull it off? I don't understand.
Do I have to be like looking? I thought it was x-ray vision, guys. I thought it was x-ray vision.
I thought that was inside of this thing. Is it because I'm too far away? What the fuck is going
on? Am I not cutting it? Okay, so you have to be right next to it. Okay, what? There's another one
right here. There it goes. All right, cool. I get it. Can I spin this thing around? Wrong timing,
though. The floating around. You guys watch me play Outer Wilds. This is like extra controls.
I want space to be down. Space should be down. And I want... What the hell do I want? Like one
of the mouse buttons. Okay, so that's that side done. Cut this thing right here. I don't think
you have to actually cut it. I think you just have to let it heat it up till it disappears.
I'm going to salvage this thing somehow. So can I... Do I have to go around it?
This thing actually cut through walls. Okay, so I'm done cutting. Am I? So it cuts through walls.
Is there face damage? Is it like into the screen damage? I'm just gonna hold the break the whole
time. I had it right. Go closer. Go closer. What the fuck? What? I don't... What am I doing wrong?
The arrows. What? I'm not supposed to cut all this shit? Or... We just pick it up? All right,
where's that salvage thing? All right, there it is. All right, throwing. Is that gonna get in there
or is that not gonna make it? It's not gonna make it. Space. Yeah, isn't it? It's supposed to be.
Not flat earth. You don't have to grapple to push. Oh, all right. Okay, I get it. Cool.
Don't have to cut all the yellow. Just the ones that they point at. Cool. Certification. 16 out of
16. I got it. I'm good. I have a hot trillion dollars. Why am I working here? Oh, that's my
debt. That's how much I owe. Oh, okay. Probably bull shit. Go home. Trillion dollar debt. Yeah,
that's weird. That seems like a lot. All right, I got it. I went home. Get in the habitat. He did
it. Whoa, yay. Rank two. You've achieved the prestigious rank of basic certification. You
unlocked modular laser cutter upgrades and ship class. Yeah, complete the shift. Minimum payments
are due? Whoa. What's this? Laser cutter. Okay. So, this is split saw license? Cutting head fires
a splitting beam for speedier and more capable ship disassembly. Yeah, that sounds cool. Start
shift. That's too many things. I don't understand all these things. Thank you. Can you tell if
everybody can chat that, please? I can't run until I know how to walk. Establish maximum amount of
value. Split saw. I can swap the head. Okay. Rotate the cut angle. All right, let's go.
Work order? All right, salvage the soft crate, the aluminum, and the nano carbon. All right,
where's the aluminum? All right. Processor. We're going to the processor. This one here.
What do we got? There's nothing in there. Where's the aluminum? Oh, that's where I was about to go
into it. I was about to trash myself into the furnace. I thought these were like Mario paintings.
I was going to go in them and say, oh, here, this is this area. All right. Is this thing right here?
Oh, this panel's aluminum. Oh, sick. Why can't I pull it off? All right, this is cutting angle.
Got to go right here. Ready? That was pretty cool. Did it do anything? Oh, fuck. I just didn't
mean to do that. Wait, I took it off. Am I supposed to do that? Wait, like this, right? Wow. I got it.
It's aluminum. Okay, I like this game. This game's cool. Let's go. I need one that can carry heavy
objects into the processor, right? The processor wants aluminum? Processor aluminum. Doesn't want
aluminum. No. Oh, there's a processor in here. Hold on. This computer's in here. Is this somebody's
computer? Is there a flashlight? Wait, where's the processor? I just saw it. Is that it? Is that a
processor? Is there a flashlight? There's not. All right, that's a... I can't just pick it up.
Oh, shit. Okay, this processor. Be careful with this thing. All right, get it in there.
It's like Paperboy. It's not a processor. This is a barge. Furnace. Processor. Is the processor in
here? Wow, this computer sucks. I can't take... I can't pick it up. I have to cut it out with this,
don't I? Oh! Pretending. What are you talking about? That processor's right there. I'm trying to pull
it out. I can't pull it out. For the processor. Furnace. Barge. Well, we don't... Oh. I don't have
a barge. So what the fuck am I supposed to do with this? That's why it's freaking me out.
All right, cut this shit up. It's not a computer. This is still connected. Hold on. What else is
there? It's still connected. Fuck you. All right, everything's... Nope. Down here. Disconnect this,
too. All right, everything's been disconnected. Cut this. They didn't say it had to be pretty.
Come on, get up. This is supposed to go to the barge, but I don't have a barge.
All right, don't mess it up. Hit the brakes. Wow! It'll get in. It's that thing below you.
Oh, okay. Where's that thing that I threw? What's that for? Barge? All right, I got a barge. It's
down here. Don't please get in the corner. Okay, good. Shit, I didn't do it though. I threw... All
right, I get it now. I understand it now. Processor. Furnace, I mean. Okay. Aluminum has been salvaged.
That wasn't... Wait, what's going on? Why does this say processor now? What? This is a different
material? The other one... The front panel was furnace. Handle. Nanocarbon. Processor. Okay.
Maybe play a game that you can handle. Ban that guy for now. Do I have to cut anything on this?
All this is going to the processor, so just punch it. I could cut it into smaller pieces. I could,
but I could just dump it in here, couldn't I? This whole thing. Processor. Yeah, the whole thing.
Processor. Processor. Processor. Get it in there. Why cut them into small pieces? Do you take the
whole thing? Okay, this is all processor. Processor. Processor. All right, get it in there.
Eventually, it's probably gonna be too heavy to do that, but it's fine. So this whole... This needs
to go into the furnace. That's the barge. Let's get it. All right, now I just need to do the
aluminum. I gotta cut this though, don't I? I can't take the whole thing. Can I cut this in half?
Does that not work? Holy shit, that's awesome. Wait, this is actually how I cut up an apple.
That's so cool. I just needed to see it for myself. Okay, processor. Get it in there.
Furnace. Furnace. This is awesome. This is awesome. I love this. Okay, processor.
You got it. Okay. Furnace. What is this? Let's go down. I gotta cut this up a little more.
Okay, this is the furnace. We got like one crumb. I'm not doing that right. No, no, no, no, no. Give
me, give me, give me. I don't know why I get what you're saying, but I get what you're saying.
I get it. I don't know how it makes sense, but it does. Somebody said this is like trying to stuff
an entire steak in your mouth. Yeah, it kind of is. It's that same energy. It's got that same vibe to
it. Okay, get this thing up. I gotta cut. Can I not cut through this shit? All right, into the
furnace. This is taking me so long to do this. This is gonna get like studied. There's gonna be
a room full of guys in suits studying this with lab coats on. I have to detach it from here.
Feels so good to do that though. I don't even care if it looks like shit. It feels good.
Okay, don't let it fly away. Furnace. It'll get there. How many more do I need? 200 kilograms?
Please. He's cutting the crust off his sandwiches.
Cut.
Go to a processor. What the fuck are you talking about? No, no, no. Only one of those goes into the
processor. Stay right here. Which one of those goes in the processor? The thing on top? I need
to swim over here. All right, stop, stop, stop, stop. I have to cut this out. This is furnace.
This is processor. I can't remove this. Oh, oh, wow. This is fun. Sick. This game's awesome.
I love this game. Okay, I need one more for the furnace. That's a tuber voice. No, it's not. I
did it. I got extra money. I did it. Keep going. That's such a mess. I'd rather start new now that
I get it. I truly get it now. So that's things over there. It's just an absolute train wreck.
Oh, I unlocked grapple upgrade. Destroyed. I didn't lose any money though, right? All right,
that's fine. New equipment. Grapple. Peather. Peathers can be deployed to establish two
electromagnetic anchors that pull objects along a field medium. All right, that's huge.
That's actually huge. Use ship catalog? What is this thing? What is that? Current ship.
Claiming a new ship will clear the salvage bay of your existing ship.
What? Who cares? Yes, this is technically another cleaning game. Man. Wow. Okay,
I gotta be careful. Cutter temporarily disabled to prevent unnecessary destruction to company
equipped by inexperienced cutters. It's tether? All right, cancel tethers. Tether multiple objects
together or stack multiple on a single object for even greater strength. Sick. All right,
I got it. I did tethers. What's pulling them in? Should it be doing that? Okay, now what?
Cutter is disabled. Why is the cutter disabled? What is this? Can I pull this stuff off?
Tether to the barge. New work order. Salvage the nassil. Okay, where's my cutter? Why is it
my cutter's disabled? How do I delete the cutter? I need to put this in the barge.
Throw the thrusters into the barge. No, why did I want me to tether these? You're gonna pull it?
Okay, cancel tether. What? That's like 600 light years away. I did not know the range was that
extreme. Okay, my cutter only goes like four feet. My tethers go across the entire Atlantic Ocean.
Use more tethers? Oh, shit. Okay, compression points? Okay, I see a lot of green. What's the
green mean? Okay, airlock. Enter through the airlock. I have to go in? What the fuck? What the hell?
Wait, I'm in another game. This is freaking me out. Pressurize. That's it? For the atmosphere
regulator? It has a nuke sign on it. Engine. Cabin. Cabin. Airlock. Cabin. Cabin. Cabin. Cabin.
Cabin. Engine. Engine. Cabin. What are the arrows? Where are the arrows? What do you mean? Oh, fuck.
Use it. Cut the reactor. Look at the reactor. It gets out. Okay.
I can do that right through here. I'm just gonna cut this whole thing down.
Okay, so just open up the side and take it right off the fucking exit you make for yourself. Done.
Okay, cool. Done. It's gonna come out here. Wait, there's another one. Where am I? I can't cut
through this. Why? What are these? Like batteries in here? It's the hull of this ship. Wait, I have
to... I need like a good spot to go. I'll just go... Oh, just go through the door.
Just take it through here. Who cares? Don't put it over there. Put it over here.
I got it. Into the barge. All right, salvage the nanocarbon. Easy. Can I not open... I can't
cut through the hull. I can cut through this. It's just the controls. I just broke the controller.
No, no, no. Get it in the furnace. Get it in the furnace at least. Where did it go?
Whatever. Cut the yellow? I can't cut any of this. I can't cut it. Let's go back in here.
Can't cut through nanocarbon. Oh, that's stupid. All right, what do we got in here?
Oh, look at this. Was this aluminum? Oh, I love aluminum. Let's cut this first. Oh, fuck. Oh,
fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
Oh, okay. That goes in the furnace. Does it all go in the furnace? I hope so. Oh, this goes in the
processor. Hold on. I can take care of this. How'd it happen? No, shit. No, no, no, no, no. Get back
here. Get back here. Get back here. Okay. Back, back, back, back. I need that processor part.
I'm going into the fire. I'm going into the fire. All right. I'm going. I'm going to the fire. I
can't. It's pulling me in. There's a current. Just whatever. So, how do I get the nanocarbon to be?
I need to... Oh, I have to get it off. Okay. I have to remove it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get
it. I get it. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Go, go, go, go. All right. Check this
out. Not that. This. I'm going to get up there. I've got to be ready. I've got to cut this piece
off of the nanocarbon. Dude. Chuck E. Cheese is here. How do I get this piece out? This goes in
the processor. They both go in the processor? Okay. Process it, right? Can I just drag it? Okay.
Tether into here. Can it work? I hope so. Nice. Chuck E. Cheese. Good luck to Chuck.
How do I pull this off? Oh, shit. Hold on. I'm just going to take the whole thing apart. Who cares?
Whatever. Let's just go. Just rip it apart. It doesn't matter. Isn't that a Dane Cook movie?
I have no idea. Nesquik is here. Dude, they're all here. Hold on. This one's floating up. Tether it.
I don't know. How much more do I need? This is really cool though. I really like this.
All right. Hold up. Do I salvage everything? Do I salvage everything?
I'm getting too excited. Okay. Hold on. Stop. Really? What? People happy. Corporate. People
happy. Corporate. Can I get through here? This is on there pretty tight. No, I can't. Wait.
Holy shit. What is all this stuff? Cut this off. Taking the whole hull off. Tried to tell you.
It did. But I didn't listen. Okay. One more. This whole thing's going to fall off.
This all goes to the processor. Wait. This goes to the barge. Get this shit off. Leave this stuff
over here. Can I pull shit towards me? What is this? Why is this in here? Get out of here.
Bank of America. Dude. Bank of America in chat. It's gone. Whatever. Fuck it. This is attached
by so many things. I hope I can really push this. Chuck E. Cheese just raided the channel.
Actual Chuck E. Cheese raid. Entertainment is my middle name. No, it's not. It's Edward and we all
know it. Thanks for the raid. Welcome everybody from Chuck E. Cheese. We're playing. This is a
salvage game. We salvage materials from a spacecraft and you have to make money and you
get to carve stuff and slice through the hull. This is it, right? Is it going to happen?
All right. I kind of, how do I get it up? Can you salvage this stream?
Quiet, quiet, quiet down. Quiet. Quiet. I'm not going to hear that. I'm not going to hear that
right now. This whole thing's going to come apart. Are you really going to say that to me in front of
Charles Entertainment Cheese? How could you? It's still holding this on. It wants to game. New
streamer friend. It's Chuck E. Cheese. All right. How do I, can I move this? What the fuck is this
year? I, that's a great question. What do you want to play? Does he talk? Does Chuck E. Cheese talk
in this universe? You're swearing. Oh, that's, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, plays guitar. No, no. I mean,
but like it, does he talk on his stream or is it a silent stream? It's important to know. No,
I don't want to play fall guys. All right. Well, Chuck E. Cheese, well, Chuck E. Cheese play
like a horror game, a horrible one where like zombies are like attacking us and Chuck E. Cheese
is like bury an ax in a zombie's head. I haven't gotten my mic set up. What? I'm just asking a
question. That's all goes processor, right? He said, no, he's a family friendly mascot.
No, we're just buddies though, right now. You know what I mean? Like, okay, guys, I'm sorry to tell
you when Chuck E. Cheese takes the mask off, he, he might say the, he might say shit sometimes,
mask. I'm just saying like a theoretical, like a, like a metaphorical mask. Don't say that. I
imagine like, I imagine a lot of like, like the Chuck E. Cheese, like eye ups right now going,
all right, hold on a second. Who, who, who is this guy that we just rated? Okay. What does he,
what does he do? What does he do? Does he, any family? Does he, does he, does he, does he,
can he talk about cartoons? Can he talk? What's he saying? Oh shit. What have we done? Why is he
why does he talk about, why does he talk about his ass? He's talking about eating ass. We have to
get out of here. Charles, go find a Fortnite streamer quick. No, seriously, thanks. I used to
love Chuck E. Cheese when I was a kid. My favorite place ever. You know, I can't, I can't think of a
bad memory I had of Chuck E. Cheese. I really can't. I'd love to tell you that that's fake.
Always have just good memories from Chuck E. Cheese. Please don't miss. Chuck E. Cheese puke
story. There's no Chuck E. Cheese puke story. Why would I puke there? They have some of the
finest cheeses. They have some of the most delicious red sauce on their pizza. What are
you on about? True. All right. I have to, I, did I do it? What's the hab? Did I get some more? I feel
like I want more. Not, I don't want, I want one more. Which way is the right way of the ship?
Yeah, I want a little bit more. What are these attached to? A bunch of nothing. Still in chat.
Yeah, that's good. Oh, all right. Over here. You think I'm really going to turn down a new
streamer best friend? That's Chuck E. Cheese. That hurt. I'm sorry. I mean, sorry, kids.
I'm sorry, kids. More in there. I can't help it. What if Chuck E. Cheese became my best friend?
Then I would definitely be in a cartoon universe. What is it still attached to?
I want to just take the whole hole. Yeah. Okay. Now what? A few more over here. I feel like that's
a conversation I would have with my mother over the phone and she would start to get worried
and ask me like if everything was like, okay. Hey mom, you wouldn't believe it. My new best
friend is Chuck E. Cheese. You know, the rat from Chuck E. Cheese. He's coming over tomorrow.
Okay. Jeremy, how do you feel? How are you feeling right now? That's a like, how are you doing
conversation that my mother would have? CBD is taking over. There we go. Look at this. I guess.
Look at all this money. All this money. I'm going to get that tethered together. Let's do a double
tether right now. Everyone's going to be like, Holy shit. I didn't even think of that. There you go.
Check it out. Look at that. Tether that too. Tether this too. Take the whole thing. Nice. It'll get
there. Don't worry. Being friends with Chuck E. Cheese is like a throwaway family guy bit. Yeah,
but this is real. Oh, no furnace, right? Yeah. Can I take this whole thing now? Yes. Make a giant
train. Need a little bit more tension over here. How's it breaking? Hold it. Shit. Did I lose it?
There goes the broom. Whatever. I'm being hosted by Chuck E. Cheese. It just feels so weird to me.
Does this feel so surreal? This is like some type of weird comedy validation that I'm getting right
now. Dude, I'm being hosted by Chuck E. Cheese. Man. Nice. It's real. I know. I keep, I see the
raid. It's ridiculous. Just give me the damn thing. Whatever. All right. I need some tethers,
tethers, tethers, tethers, tethers, tethers, tethers, tethers, tethers, tethers, tethers, tethers.
I don't know what I'm doing. Freeze, freeze, freeze, freeze the game. Pause. Fuck. It's time
to wake up, Jeremy. I need to carve this off and not be an idiot. First of all, second of all,
carve this. Easy. What the? What is it being held on by? Nothing left. There's nothing,
it's not attached to anything. It's not attached to anything. Oh, gonna work. Carve this shit
while it's being pulled. Wow. That probably would have killed me if I didn't get out of the way.
It doesn't mean I get to be in like a Chuck E. Cheese commercial. You know what I mean?
All right. Can I just, I don't want to do anything. Look, I'll do this for free. I don't even care.
Can I be the guy that they paint, like there's a lot of quick cuts and it cuts to, like it cuts to
a guy like me and I've got a bunch of tickets in my hands. There's two pizzas in front of me.
And there's like three or four other like family members and I've got a bunch of tickets
and I'm like, like that with like two fistfuls of tickets and there's three
untouched pizzas in front of me. That's a one, like a two second cut. Can I be, can I go like this?
Like, can I be like, like looking around for new games? Like it just make, put me somewhere.
Look, I'll even just give it to you right now. Like you can just use this. Like ready? Like,
oh, there's new games at Chuck E. Cheese. I'll be like, like I don't use it. I don't care.
You can literally put it where I do it. You can use it wherever you want.
Just do it on a green screen. No, it has to be like there, like in my, on my camera.
Nice and hairy armpits. Somebody, I didn't, I manscaped really recently. So wrong. Use RTX.
Not the brand. No, the, like the, the term, just because somebody made a product that is called
manscape, that's the term that existed. Prove it. Show a receipt. A receipt for what?
What have I done? I'm talking about my, my, by the way, no dust. I'm talking about like,
I don't, okay. Should I just go to just chatting and just who fucking cares anymore?
I feel like Chuck E. Cheese has turned this stream like it's not, it's not who cares about
this video game. Chuck E. Cheese is my best friend now. Like who cares about the game I'm playing.
Fuck it. Okay. All right. Hold on. I'll be back. Let me just put on, let me just put on underwear.