What is sicko mode? What is that? I just keep seeing it. I don't know what it is. Is it a
Spongebob reference? I see it on Spongebob videos. Yes. Yeah, it's a rap song from Spongebob.
You are sick, so you are in the sick mode. Yeah, I'm sick in a couple of strange ways.
Somebody just fall up! Yeah, we gotta fall up! I can't be loud. I'll explain what's going on
to everybody that's out of the loop. Like, where the fuck has he been for three days?
Yeah, just wait. We'll just let some people trickle in and we'll discuss all these things, okay?
See you in just a second. Hey, so I'm seeing some people say it was the seaman mic and I hate to
think that that's even remotely possible. No, I don't think it was. This is uh, that would be
horrible. I would not sleep for the rest of my life if I knew that that's what it was. If I
actually shoved the butthole mic up the ass in the mouth, I would have been really bad. This is not
even an M rated stream. I gotta, what am I doing? You know, this is not a, I'm not one of those like
18 plus streams. I better, I better cut it out. We said the F word, which is, was that 18? No,
no, no, no, no, no. They said, they said fucking venom. PG-13 is now allowed like two or three
fucks and shits, right? Why is there not another rating? You know, there should be two more ratings.
One like 30 plus and have it be movies like the notebook. You can't go to that movie unless you're
30. There should be another one. Okay, so PG-13 and then you get all the way to 18. No, this should
be like a, this should be like a, I don't know. I don't know. How do you fix that? I used all my
swears from today. It's called NC-17. NC-17 doesn't exist. That Peggy 16. There it is. The Europeans
know what they're doing. They got it right. You understand, Peggy 16. Why do we have Peggy's 13?
I don't understand. The America's got to get with the times, man.
Yeah, Peggy 33. You see like a Peggy 16. That is a god of war.
The next trailer that you get at E3, Peggy 33. Hidden object game. Look, I see it over there.
Do you see it? Anyways, let's go over a couple things before we get started with Hypno Space
Enforcer. I've been gone for a few days, not because I wanted to be gone, because I had
some medical problems. Those of you that know that I have migraines and sometimes they're okay,
sometimes they're bad, sometimes they're not so bad. Usually if I have one maybe every couple
months and what it does is it kind of puts me out of commission for six to eight hours or so. I'll
be okay and then I can get back to normal. I had a migraine two days ago, two or three,
whatever it was. It was the day after the sea man stream and it was the worst migraine I've had in
probably three or four years. It was horrible. I feel like I was in the exorcist. I believe in
exorcism now because it happened to me. A demon fucking came out of my body. There's no way it
didn't. They must have been a priest. They must have been doing an exorcism two doors down and
it didn't work. The priest is sitting there going, I don't understand why this is not working. This
child is obviously possessed. He ends up leaving. They have like tea and shit and I'm just sitting
there in my bed like. So a priest, if you're watching, it worked. It worked on me, but it
shut me off for two days and then for some reason all of my digestive problems came back
the next day. So I've been kind of working at like 60% the last day or two. That's why I didn't want
to stream because I didn't want to have some like sick shitty stream or I'm just like turning it on
like, okay guys, here we go. Hey guys, so we're gonna play. No. So what I'm gonna do is I still feel
kind of sloppy. So I don't know how long this stream is going to be. We're just going to kind
of play it by ear. I do plan on streaming tomorrow and maybe the next day depends,
but I'm gonna take another few days off. I have a couple of friends coming in, like my mother's
coming in soon over the next 30 days here. My friend's coming in like next week. I have to be
healthy. So I'm gonna have to take another couple days off, probably three or four days off,
because I want to go to the doctor and just see what the fuck's going on. Because this,
it was the worst migraine I've had in years, like I said. So pardon my absence over the next,
probably as of stream today, stream tomorrow, maybe stream the next day, and then I'm probably
going to be gone for like three, four days. Can we meet your mom? Maybe. If she's comfortable
doing that, maybe. I mean, you've already met her, but anyways, let's get started. So pardon my
potential. Is he off today? He seems off today. I am. So just want to get that out of the way.
I get to have a, that's just great. I get to have a blanket statement. Oh, you know, guys,
the stream like not going to be good today. Perfect. That means you have such a low expectation.
I'm going to pull the rug up from underneath you. Let's get this off. And here we are. So what I
know about this game, there's only a few things that I know, is that actually, I don't know
anything at all. I know this is a game where you pretend to go on the internet in the 90s,
and I figured it was in slightly relaxing kind of hangout stream, and maybe it's not.
Maybe I'm going to trigger a new migraine. We'll find out. But if you weren't alive,
if you're not a 90s kid, then you're not going to know what this is like. Just read the title.
Okay. So I know that you're an enforcer and you have to scour the internet for bad pages.
I don't know. Okay. Enter your name. Custom pronunciation. What the hell does that mean?
Should it be like that? Custom pronunciation? Is that better? No, this is fine.
How? What does this mean? Custom pronunciation. German.
That? German. Okay. Should I have the custom pronunciation be the 985?
German 985. No, no, no. It's not 85. German 985. There it is. 85. No, I don't want to say that.
Just German is fine. Hypno OS version 1.04 November 5, 1999. Double click the question
mark to begin. It is 1999. This is 1105. This is November 5th. Or no, it's not. This is the day.
I have no idea. Is this British? Is this a British game? All right. Here's the settings.
This is the fitness tab. Here's the app menu. Okay. Let's double click here.
The future is you. Turn it up a little. Your passion, your imagination.
I love the compressed video. Your hard work. We're used to seeing this shit.
And now, with the help of hypnospace, you have the tools. Remember that. Tense already. Remember
that clock. To make it a reality. Witness the dawning of a new world where sleep time is no
longer downtime. You turn into a... It's where the future is built. You turn into like a serial
commercial advertising. A future built by you. Hypnospace. You turn into a gushers commercial
advertisement. Welcome to hypnospace patrol department enforcer training. Okay. Enforcer
training. I like this is going to be fun. Is it? Okay. Begin training. Hello, German.
There he is. Thank you for volunteering to help keep our wonderful community of hypnospace
citizens safe. Hypno-S enforcer edition is different from the standard version of Hypno-S
in several key areas. Okay. This tutorial will guide you through everything you need to know
to best serve your fellow hypnospace citizens. What's with the WarioWare guy here? What's with
the WarioWare face? Let's do this. Why does everybody have like a WarioWare avatar? Okay.
Using hypnos. Direct your attention to the top of your desktop and you'll notice the
hypnos info bar. From left to right, this handy toolkit features quick access to...
You're old. To the settings menu. What? The quick switcher.
The application menu. I love this. The current date and time. Your hypno coin balance. Hypno coin?
The restart and log off buttons. Where do I get those? Make sure to click the log off button to save
your progress and safely exit Hypno-S. The info bar may be repositioned anywhere along the top
or bottom of your desktop. Okay. You can move it around. The settings menu you can do. I'll
probably just open that now. How are we doing on volume? Probably fine. Sound effects, sound effects,
special effects, key special effects, mouse special effects, caption, all hype speech,
uh, autoplay, rage music, page music, voice speed. Hypno space is great.
Okay, that's fine. Turn it up a little. Robot language only. That's just fine. Pizza? Display.
What wallpaper should we have? These ones are gonna hurt my head. In fact, all of these are
gonna hurt my head. Which one is gonna hurt the least? Probably this one. Oops. Now that one's
fine. Theme. Olivine alloy eggplant. Screen saver. Oozle drip. That's probably the one. Yep. Wow,
this is really scratching the 90s computer itch. No, I don't want that one. That one's cool.
Wow, computers really did suck. Kids make this shit in Roblox now. Humans are progressing too
fast. Somebody set up Minecraft electricity blocks and probably made this. This has been
10 to 15 years. Why are we going so fast? What's gonna happen in like another 20 years?
It's called redstone. Yeah, whatever. That's, I know. All right. Pizazz. Mouse trail. Uh,
that shit's fucking annoying. Is that, doesn't this mean less mouse trail?
No, there we go. Yeah, I don't want the, like, I'm on mushroom's mouse.
12 hour time. That's good. Double click icons. Okay. All right. Sounds good. Nice smooth mouse
experience. The streamers on mushrooms. Set captions. Yeah, I probably should do that too,
shouldn't I? Caption all high piece speech. Okay, let's go. Did I do the pizza menu? I did. Yeah,
I just want to make sure. Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep. All right. Next. I can move this around too.
It's fine up there. Hippie, also known as the hypnospace intelligent intermediary, is your
digital helper. He'll notify you when you receive important messages and even alert you to new
hypno-ass system updates. Hippie is always happy to help. Here's a useful tip. Right click any text
in hypnospace and Hippie will read it out loud. Whether you're new to hypnospace or a veteran
citizen, you've come to the right place. It's like the manager's talking in the background.
Okay, so you can right click any text and he'll read it out loud. Okay. Enable
caption in settings for additional captions. Digital helper. Yep. So let's see.
Thank you for volunteering to help keep our wonderful community of hypnospace citizens safe.
Hypno-s enforcer edition is different from the standard version of hypno-s in several key areas.
This tutorial will guide you through everything you need to know to best serve your fellow
hypnospace citizens. I'm getting some real 3D movie maker vibes. Let's do this. All right,
select a topic. Let's see. We've got chime laws, HSPD inbox, HSPD cases, investigating citizens
enforcement tools. What about the, let's go laws. Chime is an easy way to remember the five types
of violations that we'd like enforcers to keep an eye out for. C stands for content infringement.
H is for harassment. I for illegal activity. M for malicious software. And E is for extralegal
commerce. Find more information in the HSPD handbook. Extralegal? Does that mean that
a lawyer is there every time you make a transaction? He just sits there and watches
you transact the money. How about it's extralegal? Beyond legal. Outside of the law. Why would it just
be illegal? Sue, that's so legal. I've got a notary, a lawyer, and a doctor there watching
me transact my muffin business. All right, so content infringement. We're going to like content
ID claim, harassment, illegal content, malicious software. All right, let's say click the video to
pause and resume. Okay, so we chime. Let me see. I got to remember that. Chime, content infringement.
I'm not looking at the screen. H, harassment. I, infection of software. No, illegal content. Okay.
I is illegal. M is for malicious software. E is extralegal. So why is there an I and an E?
Illegal content and extralegal content. Okay, but this is commerce. So this is okay. All right.
You don't need to memorize this. Oh, all right. There we go.
Thank you for volunteering to help keep our wonderful community of hypno space citizens safe.
Hypno S enforcer edition is different from the standard version of Hypno S in several key areas.
This tutorial will guide you through everything you need to know to best serve your fellow hypnos.
The HSPD enforcer dashboard is a special secure program that only our volunteer
enforcers have access to. Nice. The inbox allows you to receive messages from merchant soft,
hypno space, or HSPD dispatch agents. You may also receive automated communications from
some messages come with files attached. Attached files will appear at the top of the
message and look like this. Attached files will be downloaded to your Hypno S download manager.
But then what am I supposed to do? Read messages sent from the dispatch to or automated
communications from hypnos space pages. Some messages contain file attachments which are stored
in the download manager. So what if somebody sends me illegal content? What am I supposed to
do? Report them? Is there a report button? The cases tab opens as a database of all cases
you've accepted. Most of your time will be spent on cases assigned to you by an HSPD dispatch agent.
Cases are generated in response to complaints from hypno space citizens or leads from the
hypno space security team. Once a violation has been found, the offending citizen's name will be
listed here. Click to jump to the page to the where the violation was removed from.
Once all reported violations have been found in a case, you may close it by clicking the close
case button. Upon closing a case, you will earn a bonus payout of five hypno coin per violation reported.
Bitco coins, bitco coins, all right. So this is the main important portion of the okay let's think
about this. You get cases, you gotta investigate, you gotta get evidence, and then you get Bicno coins.
Got it. So let's look at the end box cases. We did this already. Investigating citizens. Here we go.
The version of hypno space explorer you'll be using has been modified with an expanded search feature
enabling you to find unlisted pages by searching for the tags that they contain.
Search illegal. Good time scam watch. Bad citizen McGee's page. Bad citizens. Yeah I'm bad. So
don't you know anything about being illegal? Why would you put illegal content in the
metadata tags of your website? View the stamped page list to revisit your stamped pages.
Okay. So you can search. You can find unlisted pages by searching for the tags that they contain.
Use the stamp system to keep track of which pages you visited. So that's the stamp right there.
Like stamp it. To view the stamp page let's click view list or control L. Okay control L is probably
a little easier. Or maybe not. View list. Hypno space's citizens place the pages they've built
in our themed zone communities. You will be given search and browsing access to zones only
if you've been assigned them by a dispatch agent. I can't just go rob us the internet? Your assigned
zones will be listed in the HSPD zone access hub. To return to the zone access hub at any time,
click this icon or use this keyboard shortcut. I'm bad so what? Okay so you'll be given search
and browsing access to zones only if you've been assigned them. Your assigned zones will be listed
in the HSPD zone access hub. Access hub right. Click the home icon and press control H. The
citizen data dialogue will show a citizen's name, age, place of residence, as well as the unique
number for the hypno space headband unit they're using. This information is only visible to HSPD
enforcers or hypno space security team members and may not be shared. Access the citizen data
dialogue by clicking this button in hypno space explorer. That's weird. This button next to the
message sender in your inbox or here in the file manager. Okay there's a lot of info. Citizen data
dialogue will show a citizen's name, age, place of residence, as well as a unique ID number for
the hypno space headband unit they're using. So this is virtual reality? Back in the 90s?
Don't be loud. I'm gonna hurt myself. Access the citizen data dialogue. Okay listen listen.
All right I had a migraine a couple days ago and it's fucking with me. So there you go. All right
access the citizen data dialogue by clicking the button to your upper right in the hypno space
explorer next to the from name in your inbox or the bottom of the file manager. Okay I'm gonna say
enforcement tools. Here we go version of hypno space explorer has also been modified to include
an enforcement tool. If you spot text or images that appear to be in violation of time, first
click on the enforcement tool. Once the toolbar appears select which time law has been violated.
Okay you may also press the numbers one through five on your keyboard to quickly select a law.
Okay after that click on the offending content to report it. If the citizen's content is found
to be in violation they will accrue violation points and you'll be rewarded with hypno coin.
Secret coins. What do you do with the coins? There were plenty of VR stuff they tried before
2000s. The virtual boy doesn't count as VR. Virtual boy was an eye microwaving device.
It wasn't VR. Okay that looks good. If a citizen has accrued four or more violation points their
account will become flaggable. Click the flag button at the top of any of the citizen's pages
to alert merchant soft security team and they'll promptly review the case to determine if further
disciplinary action is necessary. I can flag them. Click the flag button at the top of the citizen's
page to alert merchant soft security team will review the case to determine if this really is
just 90s internet papers please. Not virtual but I don't I'm just kidding around. Because you may be
asked to report citizens engaged in harmful malicious or illegal activity your account will
be temporarily deactivated. You may not send messages or other outgoing communications to
hypno-s citizens for the duration of your volunteer service. Please browse the HSPD
headquarters zone for more in-depth information on using hypno-s enforcer edition. So I can't
I can't talk to anybody. All right I think I got a general idea of what's going on. You guys are
gonna have to help me out. Thank you for volunteering to help keep our wonderful community of hypnospace
citizens safe. Welcome to hypnospace patrol department enforcer training. We think we're good.
Let's go ahead and exit this. Important message received from merchant soft. Important message
received is the dashboard. Welcome to enforcer life. I forgot I put that in.
Message received from dispatch. All right I forgot I put that in and I was just like where are they
pulling that from? Hello Jerma welcome to the hypnospace patrol department. Adrian and Dylan
Merchant here. Co-creators of hypnospace and founders of merchant soft. We would like to
personally thank you for volunteering to help us keep hypnospace safe. You will be assigned cases
automatically based on reports by hypnospace citizens or activity. We've noticed here at the
hypnospace security center. Look forward to receiving your first one shortly. Please remember
that while you're enlisted all outbound communication is prohibited. Have fun the merchant brothers.
Can I delete emails? Welcome to enforcer life Jerma. Okay this is a new case content infringement.
Uh hello Jerma this is a content infringement notice regarding any content that copies or bears
the likeness of 1962 cartoon character gumshoe gooper. Look through your assigned zones for at
least three possible violations and utilize your enforcement tool to check them. An image 1962
cartoon character gumshoe gooper is attached to this message. Okay let's what is downloading
gooper screen? What does gumshoe gooper look like? Downloading gooper screen. Okay so no no shit I
had just I just I only need one. Okay so we have to go to the zone we've defined. I'm gonna sneeze
and it's gonna give me a headache. This is bad. How do I not sneeze? Tell me I just not
sneeze. Is there a way to not sneeze? This is the ultimate way to like get make your headache worse.
Okay I think I'm okay. Anybody that's ever had a migraine before a sneeze is like lighting a fuse
that explodes in your head. So let's drop this back. Uh I got my download. Let's look at gumshoe
gumshoe gooper. That's what gumshoe gooper looks like. So we have to find the cases of that
character and infringe them. All right yeah I know what it looks like. All right here we go.
Let's do it. Hypnospace explorer. Zone access hub listed zones assigned to germa. Welcome to hypnospace
rated best sleep time social network by arm arc mag need help come here. What if we're doing
copyright infringement? Whether you're new to hypnospace or a veteran citizen you've come to
the right place. Clip the image to the left to access our getting started section. Oh yeah you
can hover over things. After that check the global newsroom our virtual newspaper and then read
hypnospace guides for exclusive material from the celebs you love. Wherever you are your home in
hypnospace. How many people visit the hypnospace global newsroom daily for all the latest national
global headlines? All right uh who cares? Guides lost. Verified experts. Merchant soft. Find out
more about merchant soft. Complete our brief survey and we'll send you 11 oh fuck yeah 11 coins
immediately. Are you the kind of person who enjoys giving your opinion? Would you like easy
hypno coin? Great click the following link to enroll in our citizen feedback club and receive
11 coins instantly. I actually uh knew somebody that was thinking about doing online surveys for
money. They never did it but it was always the argument of if I just take like 500 of them and
never do it again you're on like 500 selling lists for the rest of your life. Okay so 11 coins. By
clicking the above link you agree to allow hypnospace merchant soft and hypnospace partner
brands to use and distribute all further submitted data in any way we deem appropriate. Your data
will remain private. Yeah fucking right. Yeah your data will remain private when we have private
conversations in private meetings discussing how we're going to use your data. I want that money.
You now enrolled. You'll receive a message shortly. Please close this page. You've got no mail. Okay
here we go. Feedback tv spot preview. Welcome to the citizen feedback club. We hope you're enjoying
your 11 coins. We've attached a link to download a new tv spot called easy that we plan on broadcasting
nationwide this summer. Please click the above link to download the spot and open it from your
hypno file manager. After viewing please complete this short survey. Okay downloading easy underscore
this is easy. How much is 11 coins worth? Is that like four cents? All right easy spot. With hypnospace
the easiest sleep time social network just keeps getting easier. Even my grandpa uses it. It's easy
as pie. My kids got me into it. With our new hypnospace guides you can navigate hypnospace
with the direction of top experts. It's a real game changer for movies games and music to cars
and sports. We've got it all. Hypnospace is awesome. We've spent over one billion dollars making sure
hypnospace citizens wake up fully refreshed. I wake up feeling great. Why waste your sleep time
merely sleeping? Going to bed just became a whole lot of fun. Fiber actors. For a busy parent
hypnospace is amazing. Take advantage of our 30-day no risk trial and leave your dream
right in hypnospace. With hypnospace the easiest sleep time social network just keeps getting
easier. It's the word my grandpa uses. It's easy as pie. My kids got me into it. Oh this is just
replying. All right so I got it. Let's take the survey. All right police dinner return when you
finish to have. Is your combined annual household income over or equal to 24,000 us dollars?
Let's say yes. Yes. Are you the financial decision maker in your household?
Yes because I am only my household. Would you say you generally like the easy spot hypnospace ad?
Yeah I thought it was pretty good. I thought it was good. Would you say that your opinion of
hypnospace's ease of use and user friendliness changed for the better after viewing the hypnospace
easy spot ad? Yeah I think so. Would you say that your opinion of hypnospace's value for the money
changed for the better after viewing the hypnospace easy spot ad?
Uh I don't really know what I did. No don't think so because that ad didn't really tell us.
Would you say that your opinion of hypnospace's status as a cutting-edge high-tech product
changed for the better after viewing the hypnospace easy spot ad? Yeah they said they spent a billion
dollars. So would you check your mail? Uh in your opinion would the people featured in the easy spot
hypnospace ad relatable pleasant attractive and appealing? Yeah. Please choose the face that
represents how physically agreeable you found this spokesperson. It might I need to all right I need
to match their face. This one's does that means like fine right? Please choose the face that
represents how hard working and down-to-earth you found this spokesperson. Well this is uh I think
they are. I don't think they are. And then what is this cool one? Hmm this is tough. Click on him.
No that guy's not extra cool. Please choose the face that represents how well-behaved all-american
kid you found this spokesperson. That was a pretty well-behaved. Thank you for your time. We will
notify you future citizen feedback department surveys as they occur. Please choose close this
page. Okay cool. All right so okay infringement. I'm going to find the infringement for
uh muddy mudskipper. So let's go. What is this thing? Tune box. Sticky note.
All right oh shit I have to go back. No shit. How do I go back? No no no malicious software.
Content infringement. No no no. Oh there it is. Okay so we've got let's look at the cases here.
Got to find gumshoe gooper infringement. So this is the cafe. Don't know where to start your
hypnospace journey. The cafe. Good time valley. Remember the good old days. The great music,
home cooked food, and respectable youth. We're gonna live it all here. All right where's the
you definitely have this is the tutorial level. So you obviously have good time valley. For those
who remember the way things used to be. Ever wonder what happened to home cooked meals, good
music, and putting in a hard day's work. In good time valley you remember the way things used to be.
Okay and how is that? There's no links. Oh okay. Abby's world. Welcome to Abby's world. I am a
first grade teacher at an elementary school and I love to write. Wait what are these all just pages
to that link to here? Oh okay let's go to Abby's world. Abigail Warren status. It's been 10 years
but sometimes I can't help but cry and think of her. No violation points. Model citizen.
Looking for gumshoe gooper grouper. Gooper stories. Wait hold on you've got gooper here?
Welcome to my hypnospace page. I am new to this so pardon my dust as I learn the ropes here.
I'm a first grade teacher and love my kids. They are my world. We got some fucking rub
rats music playing in the background. You hear this? Uh oh. Gumshoe gooper art from my first
grade class. Art and stories from Mrs. Bowerson's first grade students. There it is. Gumshoe gooper.
Look at that. You're under arrest. My first grade students made this artwork after watching a gumshoe
gooper feature about being safety minded in all kinds of different situations. It's old but such
a cute little cartoon. Gumshoe gooper is the police. He catches the pig robber and puts him in handcuffs.
Fucking violation kid. Gumshoe gooper and his friends in court. Everyone cheers for
gumshoe gooper. You're going to jail. Oh no watch out for gumshoe. You made this?
That's pretty impressive for a six-year-old. Help. The boy in the building is stuck and gumshoe gooper
hears him yell help and calls 911. Gumshoe gooper does not try to play with a dog all by himself
even if it is nice. Is this real artwork you think? Gumshoe gooper finds a bag with bad stuff.
He tells a grown-up and they throw the bad stuff in the trash can. The end.
With a carrot? The end. Gumshoe gooper 3d animation is donated by noble warlock designs.
Really? Interesting. Noble warlock designs. Well now you're fucked because I'm gonna find that.
Where's my sticky note? Hold on sticky notes. Uh what was it called? Warlock
designs? Noble warlock designs. Noble warlock design. Okay then move that over here.
Good. Blind. Don't even blind. Just click on it?
What are you talking about? Mechanical click. Hammer on the top left. No I know I'm just
I'm writing down noble warlock designs. Oh
yeah look at this font though I did it's that could be like globular
that's a lowercase n look I'm just trying to do it correct okay
first of all I thought I was gonna have to go searching for it listen all right we got
content id content infringement content infringement there it is
bang uh I jermos submit this evidence has proved that citizen abby rights 58 has violated content
infringement investigation well done enforcer get paid oh they take it off okay wait does this
is this fair use is that fair use this is okay draw a depiction of a character is it fair use
if I draw a picture a terrible photo of sonic the hedgehog and I have him have handcuffs in his hand
I'm not selling it though nobody hold on this is all bullshit this website doesn't cost any money
I don't think that's infringement this yeah I'm shut it down this this kid didn't even
has violated well done it's infringement shit it is this is unbelievable
oh did I really just dmca claim a six-year-old shit I'm getting lots of money here take it all
down this is not even I don't like this this is fair use they're not doing this because is that
all right this could be an ice cream I don't think this one counts that doesn't even look
remotely like gumshoe gooper I mean it says the words gumshoe gooper but I don't think this is
infringement I see I told you damn it I shouldn't I should have listened I that didn't look okay
hold on but is it legal to write the word gumshoe gooper I got mail uh-oh uh-oh okay now I know what
is and what isn't illegal this is illegal I knew it too yeah okay the end here we go all right so
I got important message received from hold on let me go see the mail wait a minute oh shit okay
hold on I'm going to inbox you solved new case harassment for germo what you've solved your first
case great job germo to close the case to earn your bonus after you found all reported violations
remember to close the case finding more than the minimum number of violations will result in a
higher bonus cases may stay open for as long as you'd like we will assign you new cases as they
come in regardless the case closure bonus exists solely to encourage more thorough investigations
all right well first of all I'll close let's I'm closing this no I'm not no I'm not no
look what about the warlock I want to be thorough here we go I'm just Alan Reynolds status I'm just
trying to add something good to the world and what do I get I get made fun of and stepped on
some things don't change welcome to noble warlock design studio and corporate I am here to
fulfill all of your ethno space page design needs I do 3d graphics design as well as page layouts
do you need your business to have a beautiful page then I'm your man message me for a quote
oh it's jewel wizardry fight Diablo tooth palette acceptor more about me if you're
wondering about the Celtic graphics on my page that's because I am actually of Celtic descent
my Celtic culture was not celebrated by my family but I recently uncovered evidence that I am indeed
related to the ancient Celts who would have thunk it more about me I made a self-portrait
3d version of myself well I did use a little artistic license is that copyright hold on
our land for obey means noble warlock in Celtic download my
Erethra ethereal if Erethra real wallpapers for free by clicking here Celtic morning and Celtic
evening let's download those Celtic morning Celtic evening check out my first hypnospace clients
rr's leather cowboy waist satchels page this is too much here hs downloads it just creativity I have
72 pals on chit chat more 3d graphics and information coming soon all right hold on
this is a new client oh god damn it no no no no we're going to go back to noble warlock
can I sail the products and services through unauthorized payments processing systems
participation in multi-level marketing schemes are paid is this what it is
this is illegal commerce right no there's no link more about me you can lay there and stay down
and let them win or you can stand up and give them hell ah hello arlen here if you recognize
this quote it's because you have excellent taste in movies you may not be aware of this but I am
sometimes suspicious that born hunter 4 was actually inspired by yours truly me oh boy the
director came into my shop well not my shop but I am top salesman to buy a couch we must have talked
for an hour if you ever meet me you may be surprised to learn that I am actually in a
wheelchair a car accident left me without the use of my legs at the young age of 22 years old
well that's life as they say what jesus what about hs downloads well design alan this is
boppos fine meats about me what is all this we're going down like we're going through the
rabbit hole i can't look i'm gonna close wait a minute how much is this meat saver screen saver
custom visual theme okay if i buy is this illegal if i buy this i have 77 bucks
virtual hypnosis partner brands food fanatics downloads this is this is cool all right
always delicious downloading i want them all i want the screen saver i want the visual theme
and i want stick back boppos
extra thick chips look for boppos extra thick chips coming to your lunch counter this whole
we love hypnosis all right i gotta i gotta go back i gotta close this
model citizen no violations okay i'm gonna look for tags what about gooper i don't see a gooper here
graphics i don't see i don't see gooper oh they're page sensitive okay anything else here
i think i have to just go back where where am i design rocks noble warlock design studio
for our wait my way hold on wait wait wait wait wait isn't
shit search for gooper okay how do you can i can search for tags was it gooper gooper
so i can't send him a message because he made that fish 3d for for arlen right there it is
no no no no sandy for leader is this sandy for community leader i don't know about you but i
think sandy has been more of a community leader than our current leader has ever been please
contact merches up and hit those based by phone and mail and let them know we need a change around
here got you feel free to share this beautiful banner credit to alan for obi if you stand with
sandy she looks like a cookie endorsed by gumshoe gooper himself here he is playing us at sandy's
future inauguration now you fucked we got go back sandy's humor page the dumpster is full of smelly
trash just like the name says you reap what you sow welcome to my humor page get ready to bwl
burst with laughter first up gumshoe gooper and his grumpy partner detective frank up to their
old antics again enjoy abby i hear you detective frank a little bit of sarcasm for your day
don't you just love monday's it's garfield and finally some wisdom for the kids kid there's no
such thing as a grumpy old man when you get over there you stop being polite and start being
honest sorry but this is all this whole thing is violation nice all right all right let's go
close that case i have what about 21 downloads what the fuck are all these what is this oh cool
okay let's keep going uh yeah uh yeah i gotta get my money's worth uh
in the corner here well you don't make hot dogs like this that looks cool okay i don't know what
that is i don't want that uh is this supposed to i don't want that either it's like silly string
i don't want this string is it cheese wait hold on wait wait wait is this supposed to be like
mustard or something no papa sticker no that's patties let's chug it is sliced cheese uh no
no you can build your own hamburger but i don't want to do that i'd rather have the hot dogs
and stop whoa oh it's a wallpaper just cover the screen in cheese we want cheese well you're
gonna have to wait you that's that looks like mold where's the cheese which one of these is the
cheese there it is there you guys happy yeah you can sleep easy tonight see now we're happy all
right so we got celtic evening these are new backgrounds this is cool size it to the whole
screen no that's i don't want to do that falling meat flying meat is screensavers
oh this is a neat little game i'll tell you we'll pick the good one what a bwl moment
all right looks fine now let's go let's go do it so now we go up here pizzazz no no uh display
theme screensaver so we've got falling meat what's wrong with me my desktop background is hot dogs
and cheese my screensavers hot dogs and meat what why am i so obsessed with meat flying me let's
see this one this is way better i i love this one but the other one might be better all right
space meat hmm yeah that's gonna have to be space me all right what about my wallpaper
was a grill is the celtic one right let's just do the grill
oh that's so cool i could have the cheese on it i'm grilling cheese
how do i make this how do i get rid of that dude i am bw battling so hard right now
all right let's close that case how do i get the screen saver to come on just don't move
i'm gonna do this to my desktop tonight let's close that case you've solved the case let's go
to the cases we've got additional stuff close it wow germa great job removing that content
thanks a lot case closed case two teen topia harassment let's read about it hello germa citizen
zane rocks 14 has been reported for harassment in the zone teen topia please look for possible
violations and utilize your enforcement tool to report and remove them if zane rocks 14 is
found in violation and you deem it necessary please flag their account so the hspd security
team can look into the issue further remember that pages containing the harassment violation
may be unlisted but can still be accessed through search tags if related violations are found by
citizens who are not zane rocks 14 please report them also all right so teen topia i'm gonna find
four violations in teen topia let's go back home here all right teen topia a fun safe place in
hypnospace for kids and i've got a pee and i want to drink water too i'll be right back i gotta keep
hydrated tonight i'll be back in 20 seconds that's no no that's way too little like two minutes
oh leave on the desktop you're right here just so people know well this actually worked all right
i'll be right back we sorry i ruined it yeah i'm gonna be taking a couple more breaks
this stream just because if you don't know i talked about it in the very beginning i had
one of the worst migraines i've had in years a couple days ago and it like
fucked me all up so i'm gonna stay hydrated and let's go back to the case and what was it
oh uh harassment right okay teen topia a fucking brb fun safe place in hypnospace for kids and
teens to relax and be who they are the kids aged 13 to 18 elevator they come out oh no it's a
school locker i get it all right no adults allowed teen topia is a safe totally awesome
hangout for teenagers all right we're looking for harassment from what was his name zane
zane rocks 14 i'm awesome this is harassment no adults allowed that's harassment
that's not harassment you guys don't you can't take liberties here all right zane rocks let's
see it's me zane the undisputed king of teen topia this is zane my name on here is zane rock
but now i'm 15 excuse me what's with the gun here um that's a violation
putting up a firearm is it
oh
well i thought it's an illegal or profane activity
illegal it's including weapon assembly drugs oh never mind it's just a clip art of the gun
guns aren't even legal yeah but all right i run a secret page in teen topia it isn't in the
listing so you can only get through if you get the link if you're lame don't even think about
okay sea bitch is the best band in the flipping world they're incredible
guarantee you it is a secret secret page i make awesome comics big z studios layers x comic number
one i have a girlfriend named jessica sorry ladies check back here later in case i'm single but i
don't plan on
get stacked like the well this is c this is i thought we said c topia this is c
pitch 15 10th grade seafood hurdles psycho syndicate favorite movies the techno wizard
cataclysm squisher relationship taken but i'd like to make friends still
hobbies making hypnosis pages gaming drawing comic books doing programming hacking making
out with my girlfriend riding my moat head
i won this award second annual dumpies chaos award
that's like if that's an explosion no no stop
the dumpster is the most hilarious page on hypnospace
so this is kind of a big deal it's an underground comedy page the dumpies are their awards guess
i'm hilarious oh wait i knew that the dumpster taking out hypnospace is trash so you don't have
to i have 16 cows on chit chat do you send messages exchange files features chat with
friends and family find old friends and make new ones participate in group chats with the 24
it would be on chit chat right install chit chat now not available for hypno ois enforcer edition
or hypnospace enforcers okay so wouldn't there be would wouldn't zane be on chit chat talking
shit and harassing people well it's definitely a seepage page i've got there's no way to go
let's go to okay what about the comic big studio slayer comics model citizen
today big z studio slayer x issue one
killing demons get up and go to school dude why do you sound like my mom oh well this sucks
mom comes in 10 minutes later family apartments i must kill zane before he taps into his secret
powers next time on slayers x those dreams you had they're all real the demons the green energy
your secret powers and double pistols all of it is real we need your help zane
wait why is this right wait wait wait wait right to left this kid live in japan right to left
no what are you talking about why why would you even say that all right where's issue two
there's no there's no issue too one dollar well i didn't say all right let's look for uh
uh secret right it's fine to see okay i love zane rocks zane rocks got game i love zane
did zane get a sub burn or is he always this hot i love zane he's so fine he's so cool
this is the home page of jessica white zane's girlfriend he's the most incredible boyfriend
he knows how to treat a girl right and i'm a huge fan of his comic books he draws his comics have
the best characters and they're really bloody and gory same ip headband id who great i'm glad
it's who who 114708 same person yep zane has a page where he pretends to have a girlfriend
he's got id that's not illegal that's just sad all right we're gonna find the secret page
page right like that's his favorite band seepage review wait a minute scanning new music reviews
any page designers out there that can advise me i'm not used to using this page builder
is he going to be seen talking shit like freaking out in the comment section
seepage review heavy brooding hybrid rock rap for the teenage set scrape records it's easy to
immediately dismiss bands that have such a blatantly manufactured facade but to do
this with seepage would be a mistake the group's image may not age well i believe that their music
will be remembered as something special seepage's debut self-titled record packed with
inventive production inspired fusion of heavy riffs and hip-hop beats okay the lyrics are
not technically impressive we're looking for a name of a record or a name of a song
they always have scrape records are angling for angst-ridden teenagers
see if you've recorded something tight fresh and enjoyable
did you search for secret no yeah there's definitely i would say like the comment section
of this guy because he's probably gonna be like fuck you it's my favorite band house of sound
seepage please note under heavy construction i'm working this is the seepage review but is there a
comment section here scrape records bill aldrich out there sound cosmic rock i'm looking for him
to like scream at this guy for making a bad review let me go back to his page seepage review
is jessica's wife zane rocks 14 big z slayers x zane rocks got game or way lame got it got it
secret page got game or way lame wow it is truly honored to have mikey psyche the lead singer of
the amazing band seepage here with us today let us say that got game or of their way lame seepage
hi mikey thanks for coming on the show even though you are so famous and friggin awesome
no problem zane this is the kind of sarcastic humor that me and the band love
we just eat this shit up motherfucker haha i had a feeling this was the case to be honest this is
not even fair i don't think there is a chance in hell you are lame any last words before the
verdict let's rock this shit you heard the man let's hear the results drum roll and the voters
decided seepage has got game no real surprise grins to the main got game or way lame episode
selection page this is a secret page do not link in normal hypnospace seepage if you see this page
send me a message don't you know the rules about scrolling down here pinches your arm so hard it
bleeds oops unless you're a quarry and it's not an accident ladies and gentlemen internet meme
video we're gonna find quarry by the way uh copywritten material
what what are you talking about unless you're quarry then it's not an accident idiot is that
a threat this is a threat right harassment yes all right this is the first threat we need a few
more so we'll look for quarry he doesn't like quarry to the main got game away lame episode
selection page this is the hypnospace page that dares to ask the question are you way lame or
got game choose your episode episode two quarry we got him this month on got game away lame that
brassy kid aka quarry got the username that brassy kid his name used to be give me pizza too because
he's quite the big boy and has uncontrolled food urges we caught up with him for an interview all
right so we got two usernames here eric hartman hi quarry as you know this is a game show where
we see if you are lame or not how's it going i don't know i'm just being fat and popping my
pimples on girls why don't they like me what uh dude that's gross look at me i can play saxophone
and eat a hot dog at the same time so hungry oh no i spilled ketchup on my stretched out shirt
seriously i think i'm going to hurl good think there is a toilet here hurls into the toilet
no why are you puking in my mom that toilet full of diarrhea is my mom that's why i smell like it
uh well people i think we have our final results in let's see if quarry has got game or is way lame
and the vote have decided that the brass kid is way lame i guess we now know why he can't get a
it's got to be somewhere down here yeah thought i warned you about scrolling down my page
asshole kicks you in the nards especially if you are quarry it's all it takes man
little do you know that your secret one sentence on the bottom of your pages well
didn't this consider harassment but is this harassment it is right this is harassment right
here the entire page i can't count can i do that i have to pick uh i can't just pick the whole page
can i yeah i can't pick the whole page it's got to be certain material one by one all right how
about this one this is that's harassing right it's just introducing it being hey this this kid
sucks right yeah a couple more my quarries you know this is a game show i mean this is the picture
is that every picture of quarry is harassment i need four all right well that case is pretty
much closed all the words of quarry brassy kid brassy kid and what was the other one
oh shit what was the kid's name brassy kid and give me pizza i gotta remember those hi quarry
you know this is a game show where we okay that's not harassing he's introducing himself and we're
just gonna see if you're lame or not oh fuck wrong violation uh just being fat and popping
pimples on girls this is harassment is it all harassment and i have to flag the page look at me
i play saxophone eat at the same time just flag everything can you l okay ella flag flag citizen
for investigation citizen zane rocks has been flagged important message received from dispatch
the hspd security team will be verifying all related violations and review zane rocks 14's
activity to decide a further action is necessary if this flagging relates to one of your assigned
cases you may now close it so that's we're good i don't have to do any more right could get money
too that's pretty sick still need to look up this dude's name okay uh i think we have for let's see
if quarry but is more money way lame i am making a lot of money that's not harassment this is just
a diarrhea toilet with peel over it the dev is in the chat and trying to give you tips
this is pretty cool game okay uh way lame is that harassment is way lame harassment
of course it is yeah it is all right i'm gonna hurl yeah but this could be a completely out of
context we flag the page i can close the case let me look this up read top text got game aware
top what do you mean top text were you talking about oh i thought okay whoever ratted out my
secret page watch out i know who you are and i'm flipping out right now oh do you i can't report
that why can i not report this oh there he's going to jill i want to look up uh what was it
pizza i love pizza pizza pizza lover two what was it called give me pizza give me pizza pizza fan
give me pizza too no results what was the other one brass the brassy kid no results
or is it that brassy kid we go quarry's house that brat quarry paul anderson status hey guys
tell me what's what's my problem is pull up a chair you're at quarry's house welcome to the
page of that brassy kid i'm a junior in high school and play tuba and saxophone if it wasn't
obvious i used to be called give me pizza but that name is so stupid and idiotic ah check out
my joke page everyone has a joke page pizza dance is hilarious everyone put this in your page
what's that lizard dance with frog dance thing i don't know what it's called but that's what
what's it called no dancing baby no the lizard baby dancing gif baby all right let's go to the
joke page jesper laughs the humor of quarry paul i just found the funniest thing this sound
effects theme by steve guy is hilarious install it and it makes your hip noise sound very interesting
this is a virus downloading sound effects what do you call a pepperoni pizza with only one slice in
it a pepperoni pizza what do you call a really horrible illness that gets you excused from school
for two weeks because you used damien's tuba in band practice because you accidentally left yours
at home tuba-licious what's a vacuum called if you play it like a musical instrument a saxophone
freak what to want to see what i look like i like this pic because i made this face when my friend
derrick hit a wrong note and it looks so goofy someday i need to get my own digital camera so
i can get a different pickup look pretty funny though right oh it's wonderful i have a girlfriend
but what's your criteria for your boyfriend girlfriend put anything music taste looks
religion whatever if you must you can even message me something like his name would have to be zane
shrug oh can i put something here my girlfriend oh we're doing this in the wrong order
just letting everyone know i am now taken by a wonderful girl named jennifer
we met at a movie theater when i spilled some popcorn she helped pick it up
we were going to see the same movie we were going to see the same movie and we sat next to each
other and both felt a connection she has a page on hypnospace two go visit it jennifer not enough
info survey super bored after moving to the middle of nowhere so i spent an hour or so filling this
out i've kissed someone x equals yes on the cheek on the lips on their hands or fingers
in my room in their room uh i have not yeah actually that's not true uh younger than me
i can see yeah kim's younger than me older than me uh yeah maybe like a few years with black hair
uh yeah i've kissed a male before you know like a wedding somebody came up to me was like oh you
know you're like you're the best like thanks for being around and like you like right on the cheek
right that's the godfather does that what are you talking about what do you mean that doesn't count
well there's just there's no context here well you know you don't have like a good friend that
you've like kissed on the cheek and a very like an emotional moment you're like yeah like i love
you man what come on get over it all right uh yeah uh black hair let me see i don't know
probably yeah blonde hair and green eyes that's a tricky one i have no idea
red hair right here smaller or shorter than me yep bigger or taller than me
ha ha ha that's everyone right guys let me click that one a hundred times
with a lip ring i don't think so okay i lied maybe that wasn't so time consuming oh that's
that's kind of sad triple decker the pizza dream i love pizza too germ is so short yeah i know the
official zane sucks wait a minute we've got some reverse harassment here this is like violence
the official zane sucks club badge oh boy this is by paul henderson corey paul henderson
it goes deeper than we thought zane sucks let's face it zane sucks he's probably ugly in real
life so he has to go online and be an asshole to everyone his mom probably drives him to school
what a mother-flipping little moron share this badge on your page if you agree you're both going
to jail right up here yeah we're gonna have evidence to look at all of them zane sucks
harassment free zane zane is innocent another zane sucks anymore there's like three of these
this is just free money both guilty yet two wrongs don't make it right all right yeah it's time we
got an investigation here yeah i'm gonna have to flag you corey paul check the girlfriend's page
oh you better believe it activity decide further actions necessary i'm gonna go back he also got
one down here i'm making some money i don't condone zane is an idiot zane's an idiot but
you're not allowed to call somebody idiot you can't call okay so all you guys are going to jail
you know any times i've seen idiot in this chat you better watch out somebody's got like a gavel
hovering over your fucking text box all right all right all right jennifer do we have a lead on
jennifer jennifer no link there's tags jennifer no username nothing full name i don't think we
have enough to go on here hs ronnie's club what is this ashley's spinning planets
randy's dino world squish world corey's house monarch
there's harassment on the joke page where there's no where's the harassment on the joke page
the chit chat friends i don't think i can do that i think it just i have nine pals on chit
chat see it's just an ad i can't see his friends it's just an advertisement for chit chat all right
let's close this one we got we have way more than we need close it up we got tons of violations here
install chit chat no i can't i'm not gonna install it way to deal with that harassment
you're a real hero germa hey thanks all right so we've got the new case content infringement for
all enforcers we got it that's the gooper one citizen feedback we got that one that's the case
solved new case harassment we've done it extra legal commerce for all enforcers here we go new
case you told those teenagers yeah i sure did go flag chit chat no i chit chat's not illegal it's
just illegal for me to use it all right this is a notice that the kappa that was a lot of money
downloading frody and weapon just gave 5 000 bits 50 bucks thank you so much frody and weapon for
the 50 dollars in bits huge money thank you and they say glad to hear you're feeling a bit better
i originally was going to say use some of these bits for drinks on saint patty's day but since
you're sick maybe invest in some water in saltines yeah well soon thank you appreciate the
concern and yeah when is saint patrick's day did it already happen i don't even know sunday
damn okay i'm not gonna be drinking i'm too fucked up for that so i'll be just like hanging out on
saint patrick's day watching tv or something but we're good i'm probably gonna be streaming actually
oh what's today's date no i won't be streaming all right let's do this but thank you so much
frody and weapon it's a lot of money thanks for the 50 goddamn dollars all right this is a notice
that the kappa cash payment system is considered extra legal please look through all assigned
zones for at least four possibly more possible violations and utilize your enforcement to remove
and report them an image depicting the kappa cash payment system is attached to this message
we've added open-eyed to your assigned zones list okay we're looking for whatever that we need to
find money for instance here uh magellan thanks for the community subs five community subs from
magellan okay so this is what it looks like buy now with kappa cash they're in violation
that's what that looks like let's take a look on the world wide web okay so we have open-eyed
force them to use bald coin oh the funny sound effects that's right it's a big install how big
is this so now was it a theme where is it audio sound effects team
okay now not looking for jennifer anymore we're looking for
that's cool all right it's sands
no it's a different character it's not sands so we need to go to if you're pissed off you're
not paying attention free thinkers only keep an open mind open eyes it's the thing from pans
labyrinth interested in esoteric spirituality alternative medicine and deep fruits open-eyed
is for you this is a non-judgmental zone for all free thinkers a lot of pages that i keep passing by
the wide is the gate and broad is the way that leadeth to destruction and many there be which
go in rare red matthew 713 the word shall not return void look out ministries be sober be
vigilant because your adversary the devil as a roaring lion walketh about seeking whom he may
devour 150 000 people die every day one day it will be you do you know where you will end up
what page cannot be found go back it's a dead link notice lookout ministries did not choose to
be a part of the open-eyed zone and has kindly requested that our page be relocated to good time
valley i will not remake the whole thing we do not agree with the things that they
allow in here this is how to be saved the squisher's deception about lookout ministries
look up ministries as a bible believing non-denominational ministry led by the
holy spirit it was formed by evangelist teacher and prophet todd who received the holy spirit
at the age of 17 after being miraculously delivered from the brink of death after a drug
overdose dr hall knows what it's like to serve the father of lies and it ain't pretty
past todd this is wait this is todd this is the guy who owns the website angels in the bible do
not look like cute angels in the bible do not look like cute little girls with little instruments
and flowers this is a lie from what is it from whom was the fire is this is is this bad
from you know who okay this is kind of uh the violation
gladly share my testimony all right let's take a look at some of the stuff here how to be saved
how do you say would you like to be saved close your eyes and pray this to the lord mean what you
say lord jesus i know that i am an imperfect sinner and unless you save me i am lost forever
i thank you for dying for me on the cross i come to you now lord the best way i know how
and ask you to save me i now receive you as my savior i'm read by the way i'm reading this
just somebody's gonna like clip this and put me on the in front of a church or something
in your name jesus i pray amen i'm reading it sarcastically no i'm not i'm just reading it
i'm not reading it sarcastically don't say it like a spell no i was just reading
how shall we escape if we neglect so great salvation that was hebrews 2 3 you accepted
jesus into your heart please scroll down congratulations you are now a part of the
family of god you are brothers with christ and a true child of the most high god welcome jesus
loves you no nothing illegal here the words shall not return boy nothing illegal
chat you've all been saved but it's not choose to be part there's nothing here that's this is
fine so hs christians there's got to be something fucked up here i don't know i don't think there
is i don't think the squisher is deception uh-oh well her princess in the midst thereof are like
wolves ravening the prey to shed blood and destroy souls to dishonest gain ezekiel
the wolf of squisher z the bible warns about woes many times it's a streamer
that's a twitch name that hat that's that's like a top 500 fortnight player has to be
and he laid hold on the dragon that old serpent which is the devil and satan and bound him a
thousand years revelation all right that thing's zooming how much more convincing do you need a
serpent for kids to play with if you need more evidence let's look at his eyes for a moment
what is this i don't understand what this is a picture of a squisher z's it's like a cartoon
or something the snake's eye very clearly drawn to look like the egyptian third eye
the eye of chorus this eye supposedly grants its viewer sight that transcends good and evil
meaning the snake is teaching our kids that good and evil do not exist who else tried to erase
good and evil i'll give you a hint satan did in the garden in his serpent form then the serpent
said to the woman you will not surely die for god knows that in the day you eat of it your eyes will
be opened and you'll be like god knowing good and evil that's from genesis three four six and
we're not through yet let's take a closer look at this popular giraffe squisher there's no way
this funny looking creature can carry a hidden message can it i'll let you see for yourselves
not so cute anymore is it nope it is not
jesus paid it i can't take it anymore that's right pentagramic markings right on your kid's
toys how did this happen when a generation grows up without the lord what do you expect
we were so busy having nice little pageants and school plays that we forgot god now this rebellious
generation is in charge and we're reaping what we have sown these people make the popular cartoons
and movies and design the toys for our children and grandchildren if you think these people have
your kids best interest at heart think again at best they are unwitting servants of satan
at worst they are card carrying members of the cult there's a lot more where this came from we're
just getting started okay well you kind of go squisher z we're gonna have to remember that
look that up how to be saved we got that copyrighted images hold on are these copyrighted
that's a copyrighted image
we got trouble what these how's that not copyright it has to have to be part of the case
well all right you're a little weird let's go back so nothing else here seems to be out of the
ordinary though just somebody with a highly religious webpage that thinks the squisher z's
are satanic don't see much else glitch peace devil demon squisher z squisher z world squisher z
squisher z okay squisher z world welcome to squisher z world i love squishers i collect
all squishers but not for sparkly sparklies are hard to get because
they almost never in squisher packs if you have a sparkly send me a message and i trade with you
squisher's champion badge game let's see game champ this hypnosis citizen is still on their
free trial period game champ the game champ the games you love anywhere you want them
game champ portable the power of the game champ on the go now you can tap into the raw power of
the monarch game champ system anywhere life takes you get into the game official hypnosis partnership
brand what's this we're downloading squishers 18 that's okay i didn't want to download
squisher's quest brought to you by merchant soft in collaboration with monarch entertainment
squisher's quest help 10 squishers have become lost in teen topia click them to rescue them and
bring them back into the real world rescue them all for an awesome word can you collect them all
when you find a squisher they will appear here stamp this page and return to check your progress
oh i stamped it you stand okay squisher quest stamped so they're in teen topia the more
squishers you find the more awesome squisher stuff you can get after you find one you get uh
chowder man find one squisher creature for a download of the squisher z theme song by chowder
man level two find five squisher creatures for a download of the official sound effect and visual
theme pack if you find after finding 10 turn find 10 squisher's creatures for a download of
the official squishers rap music video by up-and-coming rapper mc ooze man property of monarch
entertainment all right well i i saved it in case i find some more that's cool let's go back so this
was the okay go back weirdo oh i get this is a mini version of that song we're looking for
ruth ruth really really ruthen another squisher's theme song this is so cool
rebby ruth an account i found them right i'm finally on here this is so amazing can you
believe we are talking to people all over the world during our sleep it's so futuristic so
everyone's asleep i'm rebby ruth my real name is rebecca though i'm 16 in the 10th grade
and i'm a pastor's kid if you couldn't tell by the way that no but that means bursting with
laughter and hypnosis speak most of the time if you're doing homework playing squisher z
or playing piano with the youth praise band our band name is called called out see you're
wrong not allowed to message or use chit chat here so if you want to talk to me you can't
and that's me has this on a shirt babble wow i bet bursting with laughter praise peak worship
company gotta praise him right okay someone heard rumors about squishers being satanic i hope not
because it's my favorite game and i'd be so bored without it hobbies include hypnosis i've seen
hypnosis on tv for like a year and i'm so glad my dad finally let me get on here now it's so cool
my dad got me a program to draw on the computer last year so i've been practicing that a lot
but i mostly only used to do church flyer art working on some of my own art soon squisher z
this game is so cute mushy is the best squisher z my cousin he lives in the next town over it
is also a pastor's kid didn't want his game champ anymore so they gave it to us my brother thinks
it's for geeks but i've been having so much fun with it mushy isn't method favorite praise song
is lord your name is lifted also like all the hymns like peace peace peace i played piano usually
but not very good but getting better anything else here praise peak worship company who else
we got squisher z squisher z what is this one you gotta collect them all there's so many squishers
ads the squisher story after an intergalactic war in a distant galaxy the squisherians
preserved the wildlife on their now destroyed planet by sending it to earth in squish capsules
it's now the job of a special group of heroic earth teens to collect and preserve these rare
powerful creatures are you up for the task real squisher whiz kid plug into the high hypnosis
space and participate in the new technology squisher quest game got it already various pages
got it downloading squishers well sorry squisher z quest players the squisher quest above would be
too easy squishes above this line are not part of the quest got two all right nice
what else we got monarch i think we were here already official partnership lookup ministries
squisher deception yeah we've been to both of these yeah we were here already
these don't count as squishers no these don't count because this is not on the team page right
all right let's go back let's go back to here as we went there we go look up ministries all right
magic orb knows all ask the magic orb a question and it will reveal your fate
i the magic orb do not concern myself with such trifles all right ask the orb
uh will i ever will i ever travel the world uh please phrase your query with eloquence please
am i turning the stream off right now are they turning the stream off right now
the opposite is true yes you're staying you're not gonna you're not leaving um will i ever travel
the world ask the opposite question will i never travel the world the opposite is true will i never
travel the world no you will cool all right will i ever have a million dollars in my checking account
no will i ever have five hundred thousand dollars in my checking account
no uh will i ever have two hundred thousand dollars in my checking account
will i ever have a hundred and fifty thousand dollars in my checking account
what will i ever have five will ever have fifty thousand dollars in my savings account
will what will i ever have am i never going to have fifty thousand dollars in my savings account
oh am i gonna be broke in the next five years okay everything's gonna be just fine
stop tempting for six years will i be broke in six years false will i be
will i be broke no i don't want to answer these questions is there anything on this page
is does red bull cause migraines fuck off actually that's like a big blanket like slanderous statement
does germa 985 eat ass uh six us's temple of serenity i'm hydrating i'm good
all right so wait hold on magic there's gotta be something else here
right it's gonna be a hidden page or scroll down or magic orb magic orb magic shapes illusion
scroll down and stare at this image for at least 10 seconds well all right i'm gonna give warning
here all right don't look at that all right don't look at this uh warning it's probably
gonna hurt your eyes but it might cause a problem so warning i'm gonna be fucked up image on the
screen for about 15 seconds uh it's giving me a headache already i don't want it all right magic
orb the orb keeper this is it nothing else here oh my god i'm shitting shitting why are you
spelling it like that all right uh back it up who's the fraudster gustus temple of serenity
enter my temple and stay a while won't you please do not dwell in the past do not dream
with the future concentrate the mind in a present moment gustus temple of serenity
serenity tower bizarre visitor center welcome to the temple of serenity i'm gusts the temple
offers people of all faiths and creeds a virtual place of their own to experience true peace
come and meditate with us or just enjoy the wondrous sights and sounds before you
serenity tower is the main attraction go there to visit one of our many meditation rooms
the bizarre is where one purchase my handcrafted digital goods the visits center
offers information about me and the history of the temple we might have some fraud here
free background of the month eternal dawn of prayer by gus downloading this wall what i'll have
okay so the bizarre is where you may purchase stuff let's go let's hold on let's not let's enjoy
their website before they put them in jail serenity tower the doors serenity tower do not
lead to damp rooms in an old temple they are portals that transport to realms beyond the
imagination detected only by the spirit realm of planes portal cosmic healing prayer chamber portal
for sherry under construction mystery portal under construction all right let's go uh the realm of
planes we are all on a journey there is no destination only a beginning a beginning you
choose start your journey through the serenity temple or simply feel free to gather strength
from the positive energy here by this mailbox it's a mailbox meditate and rest you're a okay
click the arrows to turn to the left and right it's like a little mist game the gazebo hosts
a number of glorious creations dancing silver bunnies and fawns of blue rubies rimmed with
green transcendental masters with wisdom from days gone past a tree of marmalade and peanut
butter you can take a picnic here or just watch the stars beneath the gazebo's canopy go by this
spot is great for meditation too it's all okay with me i'm just glad you're here i was gonna do
it again sit this tree with me here peanut butter anything we're looking for the illegal shit here
the garden's got a band sherubs of stone inlet with marble veins play all the latest hits
and neat music and even that oldies too for folks that enjoy that your journey is endless so it
helps to carry that music with you in your spirit and your ears chit chat me and let me know how
it's going i'm so glad you're joining me today what is this dark souls boss the golden gargantuan
the first and greatest of the old souls see i told you he watches over the temple guiding and
keeping the many friends inside safe friends like you ben franklin it's buddha that's not buddha
that's the golden gargantuan we'll return home we got what we wanted buddha franklin all right the
visitor's center hi i'm gus if you're new to the temple of serenity you've come to the right place
here you can learn more about me what i do in ways you can get in touch with me i am a single dad
with two beautiful children but where are they it looks like you're pretending they're there and
you're going to photoshop them in later a single and looking likes spirituality meditation good
conversation romance healing techniques computerized artwork and world music
omnisom all religions are beautiful in their own ways all right let's set him to prison buy
where's lonely traveler purchase my premium wallpaper the celestial duality of music
oh shit you aren't illegal here sure i'll buy downloading celestial duality you got no illegal
wait hypno coin merchant bizarre that one's fine sherry heals proven healing techniques from world
renowned spiritual guru sherry claire sherry heals welcome to sherry's healing page sherry
has had over 30 years of spiritual and physical healing experience and has consulted with world
leaders celebrities and everyday people like you all over the globe glover healing and love spells
demon and ghost exorcism she takes an open non-judgmental approach to serving her clients
if you are in need of healing don't wait read exorcism client testimony here my name is gus
parker and i want to testify how amazing sherry's services are i had a problem with the demon knocking
on my door at 2 a.m every night our whole family was terrified sherry helped both us and the spirit
find peace here's a picture my daughter drew of the spirit it's just is it pumpkin that somebody
cut the head of a doll off and taped it on we had a seance through chit chat
and it immediately made contact with sherry it identified itself as smolder boulder the demon no
i will not go not until you contact me 25 more times it said so we had 24 more seances in the
cup this lady's full of shit finally the spirit left not only does sherry know how to get demons
to leave your house but she's great to talk to i would like to say that we are pretty good friends
i'm so glad we met gus parker all right so she comes and knocks on her door at 2 a.m every night
then run okay what else you got on here consult sherry now let's just see the story why do you
not have a real photo what are you a painting of yourself welcome i started my career as a
psychic and healer 30 years ago but i've been developing my ability since the young age of
eight one day on a visit to a department store with my mother i fell from a balcony and became
unconscious in my dream i saw a bright light and heard an angelic voice and immediately upon
waking up i knew it was i was different need answers if so then it's time to get the accurate
answers you deserve the truth from a god-gifted master psychic i've been solving impossible cases
and have been performing miracles throughout the world for 30 plus years honest and accurate and
have yet to fail a case where's your okay here comes what if you'd like a consultation please
make a small deposit of 33 coins and i'll message you a link to my services page this is not a scam
this is just a safety measure due to hypnospace making unfair rules about taking money that isn't
their fake hypno coin this is extra legal commerce right here thank you for your deposit with a 100
success rate you are sure to find the peace you're seeking after investing in my services hope to
communicate with you soon jump to sherry's got you i have multiple plans available for you to
choose from if you don't see what you like send me messages 20 minute healing session over chit
chat 20 dollars buy now with kappa cash buy now with kappa cash with custom love spell candle lit
for you or a loved one sorry i do not accept hypno coin at this time because it cannot be exchanged
for real money we got trouble oh i can't buy the love spell all right here it is extra legal
commerce you're in trouble sorry sherry we got trouble in fact we can just report your page too
you got trouble i never would have found this page if i didn't spend 33 bucks
oh there's so much here this is all free money
you got trouble this is it too right this whole page is
hmm you got trouble no that's not a violation what i do not accept hypno coins isn't that saying
that that's admitting unlawful behavior all the text is against the law too right
you got trouble no what okay well isn't this sale of products and services through unauthorized
payment processing systems promotions so it is just the hyperlink so i i thought it was
something along the lines of all the evidence that is here has to be a link okay all right uh
you are eligible for flagging so i'm gonna flag you you got trouble no more links here
that was a big room that just came through yeah all right sorry sherry you're going to jail
for the rest of your entire life that's it for here let's keep going we need a few more don't we
do go to cases this one yeah i need another piece of evidence we need to find another one
let's go back uh we got through sherry's page i got emails too hold on
you missed one or more maybe also hi i'm dylan what hi dylan here i noticed that dispatch sent
you the kappa cache thing you've already found a few but we're detecting kappa cache you still
and don't really know where it's coming from i mean i could go digging and probably find it myself
really quick but that's why you're here right i mean not being lazy either it's just i'm working
hard on a few sweet new features for the new year and blow your socks off ps me and an intern
our security team are the only people running the hspd dispatch stuff right now so expect to
hear from me every now and then okay squisher oh we've got the okay is this the the tune that's
cool music file added to tune box library tune box all right i don't want this to play the whole
time play this on an endless loop i don't think so all right what is this cool uh yeah super cool
uh i'm gonna keep the grill okay that looks fine
do you ever think that somebody is really just a gta 5 npc see sometimes i think about this and
i'm like that that person is on an ai path that that person is just artificial intelligence that
just did just do that we live in a simulation no i've just been like why every single day
like three four five times a day and it's the same guy we've confirmed it's a glitch in the
matrix i'm telling you man sometimes you got to think about like what the what the heck's going
on here all right he has a job well it's his job delivering goods on the same street is this guy
responsible for like pizza deliveries on the same road only does he ride a bike no do you
hear that shit's on a bike is he on a bike he's just making that sound with his mouth
that's pretty talented electric bike with a tuba yeah he just pedals by and he puts his mouth on
it just blows as hard as he can bike like motorcycle no that's not a motorcycle motorcycle
and sound motorcycles point deep motorcycle is like
that's like
they're different sounds he's right i know i know i know this haha loud car joke is not funny
oh i know it's not okay back to it but there's still more to do professor helper for hypno os
your friendly computer expert now for hypno os need help try professor helper
now baldies basics for learning i've never played that game but your friendly computer expert now
for hypno os fast easy convenient and completely free i'm not going to play that game when it came
to hypno os and hypno space i was so far behind the times i thought i'd never learn sound familiar
do you have trouble getting around in the digital world if you've been putting off learning how to
use hypno os and hypno space now is your chance for a limited time we're offering our award-winning
professor helper software for free click here to download and install professor helper for hypno os
oh my god use of this software constitutes an agreement to the helpful enterprise terms of
service this finance helpful enterprise full license to collect and share anonymized information
with authorized partners this data includes but is not limited to use of hardware software browsing
data page creation deleted files marital status marital doubts preferred cleaning products this
data to be shared with government entities in relevant situations this data be used to suggest
commercial products relevant to the user instead of be used to refine optional recommendations
system inputs may be used to improve professional helper services inputs may also be used to create
future programs services and subscriptions relevant to the health of enterprise users
please note that a full uninstallation of professional helper is only possible upon paying
an uninstallation assistance fee of 33 coins helpful enterprises is not affiliated with
kappa cash and should not be treated as such with legal context this is ransomware yeah okay
so they they said the word kappa cash downloading professor helper it is but it's not free
are any links where's your kappa cash is kappa cash like in the link
you can't uninstall without paying yeah but do i have to pay through kappa cash
okay i see you're installing something can i help out yes great you are a winner
you win katie's cuddly cat corner your cat love it you've seen it on tv now order it on hypnospace
professor helper here allow me to introduce you to a friend i think they can help
clip here to meet professor helper's other helpful friends got you had to install the virus
professor helping here ready to go no i see you're playing hypnospace mind if i offer my services yes
you are a winner it's bonzy buddy your 2000 survival kit don't wait until it's too late
everything you need to keep you your property and your family safe
hold on a minute just i gotta get these i gotta arrest these people
you're out okay what does it say kappa cash sleepy time shopping network
cat not included why would it be all right here we go another one
year 2000 survival kit don't wait till it's too late the year 2000 survival kit includes one
week supply of canned food military flashlight pocket new testament king james a pocket bible
no it's another one i already have i'm already there she's out of here 90 page year 2000
survival kit manual order today and receive free military grade multi-tool what was the link there
was a little hyperlink here what was it you saw that right everything you need to know
to keep you your family and your property safe reverend harry pence no mail oh
fuck what dylan we need to get rid of a kappa cash but professor helper is okay to stay we are
talking to their people to make a deal and get them to break away from their kappa cash partnership
i'll update you all soon i think this could be good for our partner brands
like i said get all the kappa cash off there it's not good but the professor helper he's okay
message received from hs underscore is an underscore zero zero six eight three twenty five b so don't
professor helper here need some help no no no no i see i see you're using the hypnos based
patrol department suite can i help great you are a winner you want money from the top down what if
everything you have ever known is a lie wait what about the other one go back wait wait wait wait
back hold on kappa cash you got trouble all right you're in trouble message received you got trouble
don't click that link what link if you get a link to true tranquility important message
ah do not open it auto installs a virus it's coming from an account with no headband id
so we can't track it if you did install it use hypno cure to clean it out the virus itself won't
hurt your system it's just gross it's also replaced by hypno space page with a weird gory picture
hopefully no one saw that while it was up we're getting the virus page taken down as soon as
possible but you enforcers might have to hunt down the nasty pics if this was sent to normal
citizens and not just merchant staff i may have something neat for you enforcers soon if any of
you are interested in a few testing features wow this is so relaxing jump to the true tranquility
installation page forwarded messages from citizen you get my cap but professor helper is okay to
stay we are talking to their people to make a deal and get them to break away from their kappa cash
who is this hello there i'm professor helper using citizen data
you are a winner all right i gotta go you are a winner just wait wait wait wait wait
you are a winner click here to oh this was the link they got me click here for personal helpers
you are a winner sign up for your free credit report by click the buy now button you already
came from fire don't you got trouble okay hold on wait wait wait i gotta go back
we got this one what's the other one professor helper here need some help
ah yes i need help where's the other one don't flag professor helper
that was bullshit though that was all right here we go free blood money there it is
lovely to introduce you to a friend i think can help blood money welcome i am
don't i need the fucking virus thing
illegal shock images no no no don't you must see this don't click that link why do i get hypno cure
mustn't have to hunt down the nasty picks of a sense of normal citizens
it's coming with no headband id if you use hypno cure to clean it up
i gotta clear the rest of this shit hold on
okay i got the virus twice 1995 limited time offer kappa cash get rid of it
you got trouble is this a shocking image it might be if you get the virus twice they eat each other
um
protect yourself and your files viruses are no joke okay what
this is i only 400 bucks automatic virus detection easy cure me one press button
auto cure virus quarantine remove viruses from quarantine
safe mode browsing tool remove i don't i can't i don't know how to have money
hello there i'm professor helper professor helper is always here for you merchants hold on
um go pirate it i can't how am i gonna do that auto cue i just need to get rid of this
hello dear sir madam please help my green warmest greetings to you germa from when i was a young
from when i was a young child i have always dreamed of becoming a treasure hunter and explorer of the
seas unfortunately my parents fell ill when i was but a child and i was sent to a foster home i did
not receive the education needed to pilot a ship or submarine so i have worked as a ladder store
clerk for my whole life till next time i am not one to beg but an opportunity from a wealthy stranger
has presented itself to me if i am able to raise 10 000 hypno point the stranger will fully fund
me and a team to go out on a submarine expedition this december please respond by november 27th by
donating to my cause or my dream will be dashed you know how this is not uh capa cash
if you collect the 10,000 click the button below to donate and help us achieve our goal
thank you and god bless amount donated amount needed 200 when we prepare for this trip i will
post many updates on this page it's not capa cash so it's okay you gotta help him fulfill his dream
do not donate what you don't have a heart it's either this or antivirus professor helper here
need some help you don't have a brain i know this is bullshit but does it unlock something
that's my point if i pay this will something interesting happen you know i know this is
bullshit what do you think i'm doing oh yeah i'm gonna help this person in their dream of being a
bulk salesman i don't even know what the hell it was why would it unlock something i don't know
because that's gonna update the page what if i come back here it is is a uh is a crypto kitty
whatever the hell they are
it's something's gonna happen something cool is gonna happen and i'm you guys gonna be like oh
shit i didn't even know that was possible i skipped that i'm professor helper
okay all right let's give me this one auto cure
it's auto cure functionality okay hold on
hypno cure plus coming in virus detected for your safety please open hypno cure and click cure me now
hello there i'm professor helper
please open yeah i could use some help here you gotta remove it get out of here well cure me
we got trouble detected and clean the following viruses from your system wave hello
what do you mean wave hello infection alerts are active we got trouble how do i get rid of this
professor helper hello there i'm professor helper here try this no how do i uninstall
a professor helper we got trouble you professor helper here application icons can only be
the professor helper is always using their official uninstaller if available you will be
able to download the uninstaller in hypno space i have to go buy the uninstaller
good time scam watch professor helper uninstall this helper is sad to see you go we hope you've
learned a lot once the press helper if such a deed is truly rain please pay a small uninstalling
assistance fee of 33 points here the helping hand will be helping hands well fine then
i need 33 bucks i don't have it just wait until we get an email from that boy's dream of being
a salesman and i mean s a i l not s a l e for all of you people here wondering flag them
they told me not to flag professor helper here but that was a fake email though guys
right look wowie wow wow wow wow jerma thank you and god bless to you to the maximum it is
possible in this world i will surely share the treasure when we find it kindest regards and god
bless demetri jackson i bet you in another couple hours here need some help professor helper is
always here for you i bet you i'm gonna get an email with like 500 bucks in it and everyone's
gonna be like what oh those things were always a scam and i'm the guy that clicked it okay we
got illegal shock images don't click that link shocking image example downloading shock image
example what's the example they give us here do not visit my page right now a virus we're gonna
strip adding a gross image to good news is that the virus is simple and harmless adding it to
hype hypno cure now a bit blurred so as not to scar everyone who opens this
i don't know what that is but it's blurred so is it like a bug
you must see this jump to the true tranquility installation page
professor helper here the helping hand with the helping hand well
at least i got hypno cure your safety please open hypno cure and click cure me now
do
did i get a report this imagery detected your safety illegal image no cure and malicious software
malicious software i can't even click it what
where is it we're fine we got trouble open hypno cure and click cure me now fat
festering orifice has been cleaned we got trouble fine you gotta have antivirus
i gotta get rid of this fucking annoying guy i don't know in my brain for a second i don't know
why but i was like oh i'll just sell the cheese and stuff i thought i could just sell it i don't
know why where that came from all right this is a bad website how do i um flag this website
you tell me i cannot flag this website by running this program you accept the true terms related
terms and conditions in mere moments you will experience the security and peace that only true
tranquility can offer see the unseen and hear the unheard well bye then yeah malicious software
right this is not malicious software you got trouble no violation how is that not a violation
okay look i gotta delete some of these fucking emails welcome to a force of life how do i remove
emails how do i remove emails where's the delete all right hold on wait wait wait wait just take
the case hold on hold on i know i know i know i just need to is there any way i can remove emails
all right new case i still have the old one open though i think we're good to close this
there's no more cap of cash well they're not that might not be true okay this is an illegal
content notice regarding disturbing images that may be in any zone please look for violations and
utilize your enforcement tool hey dylan here it looks like a few citizen pages were hacked
by that same true tranquility guy while you can come through every single page to check for the
images you might want to start by investigating the hacker first hackers like this are always
bragging or posting serial killerish cat and mouse games with hints i would love to go hunting
for nasty shock images but i have a lot of programming to finish today plus that's why
we pay you sort of haha the image isn't quite illegal but we're going to categorize it as such
for the case i've attached a blurry screenshot of what the thing looked like on my page
professor and add a cool punk paradise to your assigned zones this case has been
manually assigned to all enforcers click the cases tab to view your progress just flag them already
all right hold on let me take that case i'm closing this one
this one's good to go i mean i can just keep it open right so shocking or violating images
disturbing on violent and pornographic images the illegal content notice so i'm already on his
webpage let's see this is hs citizen zeros or six a325b type something here to update your
fellow syndicated it's just a default page can i like search for this zero years old undefined
i need to help well bye oh 14 topia
no no no no no trouble okay so teen topia four oh 14 topia professor helper here the helping
man really helping hand well bye then it is another one they added a new place but i thought i'm like
i'm skipping too fast do you got trouble wait wait wait is that okay wait whoa that takes his
page does that take his page down how do i get there it's gonna take his page down and i'm not
gonna be able to uninstall this um how do i make money right now i'm gonna close that case right
now and get the money and pay for this right now
wow that's that's it
mostly removed from your system what does that mean okay well at least not gonna be annoying
anymore all right we're gonna go so let's just take a moment just calm down do i have anything
in my inbox no my dream has helped the legal content disturbing images we already saw what
it looks like and we're looking for this in pretty much anywhere but the cool punk paradise is where
we're gonna go but i like um we only checked how many sides do we check here see like secrets
uncovered stevie guys free sounds look at all the stuff we didn't see what did you do excuse me it
never ceases to amaze me how dumb some of you can be i told dylan that getting random users to do
hs pd would be like hurting cats and i was right i said not to report professor helpers
ps if it was just a mistake i apologize yeah but look at look at how this is worded what we need
to get rid of kappa cash but professor helper is okay to stay we are talking to their people to
make a deal and get them to break away from their kappa cash partnership i'll update you all soon
this is a hacked email account yeah this is a that's a hacked email let's go back here
here people used to type like that back in the day i mean if you're ceo of a respected company
clean up your emails all right secrets uncovered do not scroll down my page unless you are ready
to read classified info i want to do this we can't just skip everything i hate that song
all right uncovered secrets stop do not scroll down the page unless you are ready to read the
universe's biggest secrets there's no going back if you think you are ready to find out for
yourself keep right on scrolling just a little farther do you guys remember the people that had
the websites where they were never ending scrollers where if you held down uh the scroll button it
would play like a cool animation with text it'd be like a would come up it'd be like a
baby do we get to see one of those i hope so uh do not do not pass this point unless you know
you are 100 ready to see this i hope it's the illegal image what is it going to be
secrets coming soon if anyone knows how to put pictures from your computer on hypnospace let
me know i need to put my photos on my site uh that's funny nice job kid who has a scanner
i probably should have caught that what else we got here free sound effects cool check what just
happened we got trouble how do i not have a virus you saw that see you guys free sound effects
refresh the page see what's wrong this page cannot be found my computer is gonna break
none of these work what are these no none of them work net seller net settler what the hell stevie
tall green factor fiction everything you thought you knew about tall green is wrong
myth legend or fact that's kind of scary whether you're a skeptic or a believer you can't deny
that there's something people have witnessed and yes even video recorded near lake rosalie
to say they're lying would be to throw out years of evidence testimony and true encounters read
on if you are ready video recorded citing 1989 louisiana look very closely
did you catch that look closer here maybe this will help any questions didn't think so didn't
think so just a guy walking you see it do you can you see it up here yeah actually that was hard to
see for a second that's awesome anything else here yeah i don't want to move on that quickly
we're missing all these great websites i seen them marvin michernries watch those videos
all right almost done with this place the truth about trentis all about the original trentis that
the sports leagues don't want you to know about in the brilliant mind behind it trentis is a lie
do you know who this man is of course you don't but you should this man harry whisker stone
is my great great great great great great uncle and the real inventor of the game as we know as
trentis the famous trentis court design that everyone knows is a stolen bastardization of
a design whisker has made way back in the late 1800s a group of investors saw potential in my
uncle's brilliant game after watching he and his friends play on a court he made with his own two
hands leaving a broken heart empty wallet read on to learn about the original trentis the real
trentis this is trentis wasn't even called trentis at all it was called tennis it was also informally
called stickle for a short time and rather than being played in a circular court with three
participants it was played in a much more sensible rectangle with two participants what pictured as
a commissioned artist rendering of the real tennis court who knows what could have been if the real
original game tennis was allowed to flourish if you'd like to invest in restoring my uncle's
brilliant game to its rightful place in culture please contact me we are currently interviewing
industry investors thank you to gearhead greg for helping me to locate the trentis song
and casper air graphics for giving permission to use it there's no i don't have a place to invest
a scam zarid celestial reflection why does it have to be the uninstallation fee for professor
helper whatever his name was the latest record from zarid pronounced zaried the award-winning
composer and earth haze pioneer is now available in stores now this is too bad
six selections from the full album and a hypno os background
can't afford it that's the best song in the game that is pretty great all right p break i'm gonna
get some more water i need to fill up my glass we'll let the screensaver take over i'll be right
back how long does that take to happen did that just start why did you report me i thought we had
a deal like 45 seconds interesting yeah i got another full glass of water trying to keep my
fluids up i've been all fucked up the last couple of days so sorry for my frequent breaks
but we're good let's go screen all right we're going to where are we going cool punk paradise
we're home our home now that's cool cool paradise is the new official sleep time hangout for cool
punks now this is a good song all right we'll look at very legal content specifically uh images of
somebody's asshole something like that art by me don't steal it snow joke collective
why does everybody have jokes it is so chill of graze peak cola to actually listen to us i am
done with cyber worlds if you're not into the culture of cool punk you might be skeptical but
to me the cool fest 99 announcement says it all graze peak gets it graze peak may be a big company
but is run by people whoever those people are they obviously get what cool punk is about
what is what is cool not only that but they helped get freezer signed to estonic a respected
independent record label or even setting him up for his own concert and helped him release a single
like cool punk is on the radio it's a fan a group freezer verified by hypnosis community leader
i've been chosen as the cool punk community leader i can now report problems to the hypnosis
police people if you have any issues let me know there we go what is cool punk what is cool punk
anyway it all started around christmas of 1998 jan wolf was on break from school for the holidays
and was very very bored he found an old acapella tape recording of the graze peak cola theme song
as a joke he decided to mix it into his music much to his surprise it sounded very cool
in december of 1998 he released a seven minute song featuring this new cool punk music he invented
called colder than the rest it was an underground hit especially in hypnospace where it had the most
fans even though the first release was popular and made cool punk an underground sensation
freezer was unhappy he felt the true message of the music was lost so he decided to stop making
these songs for a while it's not a bad song the cool punk community continued to grow and grow
over 20 cool punk albums have been made over the last year all right and like lightning freezer
returned this time he partnered with mark elo and estonic records to make new music that would reach
even bigger audiences so what exactly is cool punk that my friends for us to know and for you
to find out helps fan diary let's see this is cool punk look at the fucked up images right
uh hands beats just gave 10 community subs thank you hands hands beats oh hans beats thank you so
much never lucky congrats on the uh on the sub recipient all right this is just like a diary
that's fine we're looking for hacked websites all right we'll see okay freezer this is freezer's page
snow joke collective specializing in cool punk remember the chill drink it right gotta gotta work
through sunrise longing for that feeling at first discovering cool punk what is this drink it right
downloading snow is it's under right what's the album
tricky tricky right now what about gotta gotta downloading snow is it's work through sunrise
get them all downloading snow is it's work through sunrise there's the season this one doesn't have
any joe man sorry people it's very cool punk though downloading i see underscore november's belly
okay downloading snap these are a work in progress but they're mostly done
you don't like it you don't know what's cool for us let's put one on
oh i feel like i have to install them all right um music file added to the box library
so these have been added right putting them all in okay so which one no not this one
this one the xmas medley we'll try this
that's santa all right fan page this is my freezer fan page it has album reviews lyrics
and everything about jan wolf's music chill it right song and lyrics icy girl song and lyrics
i cbi freezer is back and he revealed his identity i just knew he was going to be cutie
i'm obsessed if you like freezer and graze peak cola too add me on chitchat let's talk those eyes
rating five stars out of five stars two tracks
graze peak cola we hear you cool punks loud and clear which is why snow cap chill soda drink
is coming back look for your local cool punk friendly grocer this spring oh while you're
uh i thought it was a virus and while you're enjoying the cool icy flavor of graze peak snow
cap chill soda drink remember the eternal words of snowman joeman chill it right the 80s may be
over but old joeman is just getting started capiche graze peak joeman street team fan page
so that's joeman okay street team well so this is all desktop background proud to be cool punk
which one do i want it's time to change it up graze peak underscore cold punk
the grill is i'm not feeling it anymore leadership brand
okay this is freezer link to the freezer fan page what else is in here
this is the graze peak soda no legal imagery freezer just released a new single it's totally
stuck in my head check it out as soon as possible who's gonna have the disturbing image on there
website long time fanning students and group that is cool punks send me your song and i will review
them what's wrong with the song wait was that the song okay i thought i thought they were playing
on top of each other all right cold snap reviews which artists are real cool punk if you're not
well you might end up on the other page quick bottle to hear my original music is all 100
real cool time turn this off downloading cold snap underscore smas midly didn't we already have
this downloading cold snap underscore smas we already have those don't we music file added to
toolbox library put it back it's back don't worry yeah we got these we have to remember belly gotta
gotta yeah chit chat me or message me feels like christmas yeah
cool fest sponsored by graze peak cola cool fest 99 chowder man and freezer
king amphibator one king foods way in san francisco doors open at 7 p.m
chill right don't miss free graze peak cola merchandise guess who's back cruncher
what's going on why is it reloading the page
come on shut this up where's the jukebox all right quiet
that's that's illegal that's an illegal image turn this up
uh illegal imagery where is it this one
you got trouble well done the chowder man presents cruncher history of chowder man
merch shop and music okay how many points do i forget ask the chowder man
cruncher is chowder man on guitar and vocals kenny masters on lead guitar terry rabid on bass
johnson on drum this is a call to all the muscle boys and freak sheeps out there
chowder man is back with his new kick-ass band cruncher don't miss cruncher cool fest 99
chowder man's chowder copter three winners will receive an all-time pay trip to cool fest 99 where
the rides will take place i want to sign up sign up for the chowder man hypnospace newsletter
how do i do that merchant music ask the chowder man
are you really bringing the chowder copter to cool fest i thought you had to give up after you
were bankrupt after a few years ago hey pete yes i did get rid of it but the chowder man needs his
copter so i got it back and yes you'll be able to ride with me on it when you win this week day
are you just dumb or do you think cool punks are actually fans they're making fun of you dude
now that's not what it says in my fan mail chowder man's music is for everyone
that's why i'm doing songs for big huge companies they know that the people want more chowder
get off my page if you don't like it do you still have a drinking problem
it's been so for six months now though i do cheat every once in a while
ah that's not how it works is it really you running the page this is awesome
it's all chowder man baby coming at you live in hypnospace chowder man's hotel room his hotel room
music file added to a box library
oh
broke just wait till i get that email you'll see all right let's see what the
chowder man's hotel room this is chowder man
yeah see chowder man i am the chowder man oh so he did the squishers thing that's pretty famous
three why is this one so cheap it's a life philosophy skipping the good ones
1954 birth of chowder man chowder man's parents helped him start chowder entertainment his own
personal record label super an asshole image i think that's it for chowder man but let's
make sure this is because it showed up here it was injected into this flash video
does this have a song no it's just an image it's just a gif all right we have to hit the
chowder man hotel where the hell were we we're back here right all right back back back here
we go freezer we already did this bio i think we found the image on this page already
yeah we got that's just on a record be who you want to be for dates artists boy releases we are
freezing
we can't hear you over the music probably for the best
like i all you can hear is that i'm sitting here trying to do a murder mystery to find the
hidden asshole images that looks good how about the story mark alev again recording
off the wall synthesizer music under the name are kello remember that turn down this hamburger
music what is what does hamburger music mean hamburger music
okay for some reason i know what you mean is it weird that i know exactly what you're referencing
this is typical fourth of july american backyard barbecue music cool fest 99 yeah we already got
this artist's home okay anything else i think we're good here don't need to find the hacker
they only have like two more places to go okay hold on we got all the fungus fungus scene
anyone know whatever happened to i you're right i cannot handle this hamburger music anymore
let's try this one
all right anyone know whatever happened to didge exchange i had a bunch of my freezer
and basita stuff on there but it just disappeared didge exchange remember that it's probably hacked
fungus scene a new movement coming soon check back in a few days seriously check back in a few days
fungus scene didge exchange
didge exchange was didge exchange hacked rip didge exchange more tips coming soon need help with
using hypno s chit chat with me i'd be happy to help out also check out my wytw page by searching
wytw now there's no music on this page oh what a teen topia look at that all right didge exchange
is dead it shouldn't be a surprise that big record labels are contemptuous of real music fans but it
still stings search flst for greener pastures all right wytw and flst let's go with flst
flst access portal welcome to and flist enjoy your stay flist is invite only if you have a
password to be able to search for flist pages please enter it below there are no easy steps
to being invited you must ask someone with a flist account do not share your password
click here to access flist after logging in once the system will remember you enjoy the files
so you need to be invited so i need to find somebody with a flisk account
the password well let's take a look access portal are you sad sad that didge exchange
closed down and none of your friends are on flist and you're missing out on all the good tunes
can't figure out how to get a password well my friend today's your lucky day you can use mine
for the low price of 99 coins click the purchase button to buy my flist password it works purchase
after you pay me and get the password search flist and find the access page god damn it
do i have any emails no shit what with this person can i give this person's password
what in the world a directory of interesting tidbits chit chat is a back and forth chat
program originally released in 1998 flaming os the hypno os version came out in late 98
users are able to add their friends to pals list and then engage in private or group chats with
them hypno os communicates often communities often have large groups to talk about their
particular interests like the popular cyber cog and cool punk groups was also instrumental
in helping the music sharing didge exchange and flist groups become organized right the chit chat
for hypno hypno os pals system is presently broken meaning that members who aren't technically your
pals may send you messages no word back on when a fix is coming okay fuck i can't use chit chat
hold on a minute here okay no space sleep time servers publishing pages of error messages
you sure you can't no i definitely can't install it enforcers are not allowed to have it
you can't send messages through it bttv is back good all right so these are error codes
your hypno headspace headband hardware has been damaged application incompatible with os enforcer
edition right i don't think he's meaning anything right now linked to my sandwich encryption info
page which files do you need protected unofficial sandwich encryption hypnosis info page
what is sandwich encryption ever see a file that looks like this that's a sandwiched file
sandwich encryption is a file encryption and compression tool made by sam parker
and roddy wall in 1995 for flaming os why sandwich a file protects files from the mindless
masses so it's encryption there may be a way to decrypt lock sandwich files you'll have to
chit chat me for more information i'm gonna put a stamp on this page i feel like i'm gonna need
that i'm gonna i need to know what that is gearhead greg okay read the dylan email
read the dylan email uh if you got a link to true tranquility don't open it it auto installs a virus
the one for the case looks like a few citizen pages citizen pages are hacked by that same
true tranquility guy you might want to start by investigating the hacker first hackers like this
are always bragging or posting serial killers cat and mouse games with hints okay so i'm going to
go back to the true tranquility page i'm good i'm good i got this info for later though
oh dear well choose your parasite choose a car to see life through the eyes of one of these
digital parasites as they encounter true tranquility if you've encountered true
tranquility you are truly blessed don't fight it let it guide you let it open your eyes
dear the rock star the furniture salesman the lonely shaman that was chowder man the biker
all right i'm gonna click chowder man your songs topped the charts in the 1980s you've rocked
stages from los angeles to new york they loved you or at least you thought they did because now
15 years later things are different now you're a punch line your music is remembered as a fad
people can't even recall your name anymore only how lame and annoying that one of your songs was
oh you take another swig of whiskey and sit down to check your email it contains a link to something
called true tranquility sounds like another rehab program no thanks you move your cursor to the
delete button but you stop something above the subject line draws you in you click the link
hold on would you like to experience true adoration true worship hello pig i see you
this is from t1 mageddon your computer headband id who 00928a 014 topia installing
this is fucking crazy all right do i report this before you're able to take another breath
10 drills emerge from your monitor everything turns to black at long last you have found what
you were looking for choose a different card special thanks tiff true tranquility is not a
virus malicious software thanks a lot tiff choose another card no this is not there's no malicious
software here that's not really in that's not an illegal image the salesman no this is not the
virus i see you status okay the image was that weird blurry one graphic designs hello i'm
ann lee and i make high quality graphic designs and 3d graphics and make web pages
if you need a web page just let me know this is a 3d model of me i'm a wizard who knows karate so
we have to go to these different pages and find the clues he knows what you've been doing you haven't
had it easy a car accident lets you paralyze from the waist down at age 22 after years of deep
depression you found work as a furniture salesman you've been there for the last 40 years you're
good at it but you suspect it's because your customers feel sorry for you the internet has
allowed you to escape to a new reality you can be anyone there you're not andy on the internet
no no you're ann lee people like ann lee there and you like them you spent most of your free time
this year on the computer you've learned how to design web pages and make all sorts of digital
art it's never too late to pick up a new skill your online friends really seem to enjoy what you
make you log into your email there's one new message with the link inside you click it
tendrils emerge everything thanks
i think i have to go to these people's pages let me see see what happens is this a bad image
got trouble no it's not it's not illegal to have like a dumb web page save the wizard
rock star so this is the designer's page this is chowder man this is the
gargantuan golden gargantuan have we seen the biker oh this is that guy the spiritual guy
okay your kids hate those weekend trips to the flea market they're sick of sitting in a fold-up
chair for six hours while you peddle your dream catchers and crystals and cycle that cycle of
t-shirts it's the only time you're with them but you have to pay rent somehow you tell people that
your divorce was the best thing to ever happen to you it wasn't you're alone you're refreshing
your email inbox waiting anxiously for her next message when you two started talking it was
business she's a psychic and you needed guidance it's something different now there's a deeper
connection your spirits are intertwined you still pay her fees but you do it because you care for
her a new message appears it's not her it's from an unknown sender and contains a link to something
called true tranquility let's see what's it like to be loved go to pornhub that doesn't exist
you found what you were looking for all right so hold on let me we're gonna follow this little
the trail here so i go to hold on ann lee no matches for ann lee
yeah what was it t1 mcgeddon t1 mcgeddon beyond twilight t you've reached tim i am tim you
stop you've reached him leave a message god damn it can i report this person stop it
i thought yeah that that could have been a dick you're right click the link you've reached him
leave a message i can't get whoa no i got it okay there's his other website hacker dick
all right there's another beyond twilight school sucks they should just stop it at the eighth
grade because do any of the kids actually try to learn new things after that are we asleep or awake
how can we really ever know and these mystical tombs are tales i have penned some nice and so
who the fuck is this tiffany wright and my story is nothing is sure wait was that a knock on your
door i'm so proud of my friend tim who just finished his first interactive scary it's inspired by
cyber cog and horror films he did the art and music and writing and i tried to help out a little
by giving him feedback but seriously how talented is this dude read it below okay interactive scary
one by tim mcgeddon digital parasitic reborn okay so this comes to here we've already seen that
a scary set on the internet not hypnospace in which different kinds of people have sent a
mysterious link this is mostly tim mcgeddon's but i gave feedback mostly to make it less mean
warning disturbing imagery come on where's the disturbing imagery your beloved wife passed away
weeks ago but the memories of your years together are already fading fast you're not young anymore
you sold your motorcycle because you can't see well enough to ride it you no longer desire to
have a mark on things and you know you couldn't if you tried and your desire is now rest you've
never been fond of computers and learning to use the internet has always been hellish ordeal but
it's worth it the new email notification appears from your daughter contains a link to a website
with the only accompanying text reading wow this is so relaxing an odd choice for your daughter
who normally communicates via thick wordy grammatically pristine paragraphs so we did
them all we did them all we're gonna have to go on some kind of hunt here don't accept it this time
okay hold on let's go i do not accept it error page not error page not found home you got
trouble where is home really you got trouble fresh the page you got trouble uh this is just
a game this button is fake you dummy you got forward please don't click these fake buttons
stupid so i know who these people are at least except most of them this is chowder man this is
the um designer this is the gargantuan buddha guy shaman guy i don't know who this is though
before you're able to take another breath tendrils stuff
all right let's go to the noble warlock see if anything that's going on there uh got it
you got trouble so now we're gonna go to chowder man chowder man no results for chowder man what
cruncher right i already got chowder man right didn't i yeah i did okay so now we're gonna go
to the gargantuan golden gargantuan probably just golden right uh what was this what was that guy's
name what's that dude's name i forget open-eyed what's going on with this website lookout
ministries is it look on this no where was it gusley's there it is
got it so this last one i don't know what the last one is
you got trouble okay i need to like get the hacker don't i let me just take a look at the case here
this cap of cash i need one more put the music back on uh why is this muted
shouldn't be muted cafe i don't get out of here use the search what search for like biker
i mean yeah so this case is now closed but it's not that's too easy to do that i'm going to find
it organic uh burning rubber born to ride live riding or die trying you've reached the hypno
space page of carl p if you are from the class of 50 get a hold of me i'm looking to be reconnecting
with a roger robinson if you know roger get a hold of me please spread this everyone needs to
know radiation from hypno space headband causes beef brain in kids and elderly roger we're looking
for roger robinson let's just find it tech giants confident important message received from dylan
oh god hold on dylan what do you want take some time off and test new hypno os game hey the germa
enforcers today is your lucky day we're testing out an early version of our new game and you're
in on it no this stuff is top secret and sharing info or screenshots is very very prohibited
you can face some hairy legal trouble if you leak information put that out of the way i'd like you
to announce a new hypno space original game outlaw you'll be playing an early offline version
but the final release on schedule for our year 2000 update will be 100 online
no need to send us feedback either the game will automatically report data to me
visit this page to download it and have fun i will resume sending you cases after you test
uh hi i made hypno space as in i'm the guy who dreamt it up and programmed it i'm also a game
designer composer and sound experimentation aficionado confidential a multiplayer online
gaming experience hypno os out in january we picked you to test the new secret project working
on called outlaw i do not share information on this game anywhere this is top secret
just play the game adjust the controls in the hypno os settings menu if you wish data will be
sent back to the developers as you play there's no way to win in this version because this is
a test just play it for three to five minutes don't share it temporary art please remember
that this is an early pre-alpha version of outlaw it is not finished can you send it to me yeah
what's your email don't put your email in this chat i'm kind of scared to open this we got trouble
early alpha software may cause hypno os to become unstable are you sure you want to begin testing
not yet hold on uh wait i need to scan it for viruses we got trouble it's my boss sent me this
program i mean this case is closed but i there's additional violations i could find close the case
but but i don't i want to do more i want to get close the case
close it you're done close it close it but what about additional violation
there could be more on violation okay no more cases we're all done
and the other case these are all closed what are you talking about i closed these all already all
right i'm gonna play it because i'm here the other one we got trouble press any key to start
what do i loading and connected citizen germa connected to outlaw all connected citizens loaded
to fall outlaw slush mouth is on the loose since how do i how do i play okay this game just sucks
how do i get the am i getting points what do i have to do i'm losing money anti-government
page germa's found the outlaw give chase where i don't think i can do anything i think the game
is broken hardware damage concept contact merchant software repair replacement i just got damaged
bio settings oh what did i die why do i have 53 dollars three weeks later interesting i think
i might have died important message received from dispatch important message received from dispatch
oh god important message received from hold on we have some important message received from dylan
all right flag germa it's been 21 days since you last logged on i got the beef brain where have you
been all right let's see security team has freed your flag zane rocks 14 will receive a warning
thank you for remaining vigilant important message received from dispatch hold on looks like he was
just playing around sent a warning if he does it again we may ban that brassy kid will receive
three day detainment thank you for remaining vigilant so corey was a real bad egg here
the decapitation was a little extreme keep an eye on this one seems like a loner type detainment
is just a word meaning that users can't post for a while and their page becomes unlisted we aren't
actually detaining people oh uh sherry heels will receive three day detainment psychics are weird if
she does it again flag and will ban her detainment just a word meaning that users can't post doesn't
mean we actually are detaining them all right sorry about frying your headbands
hi enforcers it's nice to have you back i'd like to apologize on behalf of our shipping department
interns that we couldn't get those repaired headbands to you sooner thankfully most of the
components were unharmed so all of your settings should be preserved might have another outlaw
test for you later this time one that won't destroy your hardware it's been a crazy few
weeks around here the few enforcers who didn't get their headbands fried have been pretty slack
on the job so there's a lot to clean up i won't be handling the hspd enforcer cases from here on out
too much coding to do instead one of our new hires and some interns or someone will handle this stuff
so expect a message from them soon see you okay mass clean up hello enforcers samantha here
dylan asked me to do the hspd stuff for today because only two enforcers had been working
headbands over the last two weeks hypnospace is a complete mess oh god we need you to go out there
and clean up anything you can find we won't be sending cases or reports in advance because we're
completely swamped if you find multiple infractions of a certain type i'll create a case for it but
only after you report the violations i will be assigning each of you cases individually after we
clean up but sifting through the individual reports from the last two weeks is going to take me some
time this has been a message for all enforcers from ms samantha okay i know you have a lot of
bugs to squash but it's chaos out there just send the enforcers out to hammer violations without
making cases first thanks m'lady okay no cases here it's just a mess how much of a mess we will
find out okay let's check out uh let's check out good time valley how's good time valley doing
look of a violation stand with gooper if freedom of speech is taken away then dumb and silent we
may be led like sheep to the slaughter said abraham lincoln this is not about a cartoon
it's about resisting the erasure of the work of a patriotic hero a man who was willing to
sacrifice everything for his country we brings we honor his memory and we honor america by standing
with gooper add this badge to your page to stand in agreement go ahead enforcers do your worst
yep shut it down we got trouble
we got trouble all right we're gonna stand with gooper how many pages do we have here
oh jesus rr ranch i stand with gooper a blatant attack on free speech and american values been
carried out by the elites at merchant soft and their mob cronies the hspd add this club best
to your page to let merchant soft know you are not putting up with it it's the teacher
okay disclaimer not me i just like this photo
oh my god i'm i did i just did one thing case added gumshoe gooper content this whole zone
has been a problem for the last two weeks but none of us want to ban anyone over a silly goldfish
cartoon hopefully they retreat soon added a new gumshoe gooper case so you can cash in on today's
violations all right all right he got two of them uh let me see if there's any more
i stand with gooper abby's world i stand with does that count close the case don't be evil
i need the money i blew all my money giving it to some random person got trouble
i don't think that counts as an image the dumpster the dumpster needs to be shut down
i don't know why hypnosis tolerates them insulting everyone who just comes on here to drive a good
time and no it being unlisted is not an excuse a little kid could type that in the search bar
and see all that horrible horrible trash all right who else has the gooper image
uh right here warlock noble warlock supports the stand with gooper movement my brother is a
lawyer and he said that there is no reason these people can't show pictures of the gooper cartoon
so stop picking on my friends
you got trouble message received from this hold on there's a badge let me try the badge
we got trouble nice okay page by page it really is easy money you can call me a terrible person
all you want it's like 15 bucks every time let's see eight it's like 11 dollars every time
worth it barkley adams are the only bikes okay oh you got a lot wow i'm gonna flag you too
you are fucked you went overboard with this one i stand with gooper it's like five people
no one's gonna use this service
is
who else was standing with gooper you were and there's yours
you got trouble okay i think that's it right no just this one flag them
should i flag them all you got trouble no they told they even did no no i'm not gonna do that
they even told me this is just a harmless dumb thing if they keep at it ban them
i was told in the email that this was harmless let's close that case look at all these extra ones
all right we got some just good job out there germa but there's more to clean up
i'm arranging a few normal cases for you right now but in the meantime see if you can find a few
more violations on your own easy look at the violations go to the home page all right
let's go back to good time valley i feel like there's a lot of uh granny's cream granny cream's
hot butter ice cream tasty and healthy too we call it heat and sip oh that's to fred the
winner of this year's granny stash competition oh that's fucking disgusting children being
served hot butter ice cream the real granny cream made her first batch of delicious hot
butter ice cream all the way back in 1937 after serving generous batches to the less fortunate
kids in her neighborhood lucille's husband encouraged her to package and sell her creation
she initially employed local butter boys to serve her hot butter ice cream at sports games
her delicious hot butter ice cream achieved global fame after green devil pitcher filbert smith
with the ice cream that's chowder man again chowder man you are everywhere the world series
would download chowder man's creative rap take on the classic granny cream jingle downloading granny
cream official hypnospace partner brand all right there's nothing else here can i flag a website
for being this is just disgusting and pornographic in nature that's fucked up uh hypnospace heaven
it's like i'm being attacked by snobby 20 year old sitting in a cushy office building somewhere
get a life welcome to heaven this is a page for sacred space where the members of those who have
passed on may live namaste bill bowerson be the best friend husband god gave me to sue my beanie
girl you shine so brightly wherever you went to and everyone could see these people these people
that died lisa i wish you were still here with me they took my bike license i can't see no more
so don't worry about me i won't be getting into no accidents i wish we could have ridden together
one last time can't wait to see you it's the biker that's that's gooper that's gooper you're
in trouble we got trouble everybody uses the gooper image is it any other cartoon characters
wait make sure you get those we got oh damn she has helped so many with her love and support
now the time for action we need a leader with the courage to stand against the attack on her faith
and values and southern gent rr is that person southern gent rr i can't even read this endorsed
by gumshoe gooper himself here he is walking at reginald's future inauguration parade you stand
with gooper too don't you you got trouble you got trouble okay anything else here 25 violations i
mean come on abby writes you've got way too many you got trouble what do you mean wow dude
you have 25 violations a lot of these people have like two three nine okay looking for
stuff besides gooper scotty's page if you got gooper i swear to god please stop putting the
gumshoe gooper cartoon on your pages thanks scotty hi i'm mr old-fashioned i'm happy to be the
community leader for good time valley even though i don't know why they picked me i think it's
because i have good behavior but that's because i don't ever use hypnospace other than for listening
to songs haha if you are having trouble you can contact me but i am sometimes busy and i'm also
not on hypnospace every night well bye okay good citizen this is mavis's page i've updated my page
welcome this is so ugly the citizens free trial is ended this page will be deleted in 30 days
unless their subscriber option is renewed they're gonna be a goober down here oh i can't even i
can't even still look i can't look at that pete's love poems here are my poems let's see pete
everybody has these free trials i can't even read this i'll miss you all thanks for hearing my poems
may be i will get another free trial probably not this guy got beef-brained yeah reginald for
leader look here if you support reginals and want her to be on the community leader we saw this
already looking for other violations sandy's empty nest my kids are grown and i'm just enjoying life
to its fullest with my husband this is sandy okay sandy gumshoe gooper statement why are they all
obsessed with the gooper thing hello my loves please don't take this as me being against you all
but i think we should not be putting the gumshoe gooper cartoons on our page it
if we brig's estate doesn't want us to it doesn't seem like merchant soft are lying about this one
beef brain is a hoax click here to go to my humor picture gallery yeah we already saw these gumshoe
gooper was on here anymore beef brain is a hoax stop falling for these obvious tricks hello friends
i understand that some of you are concerned that hypnospace can hurt your brain and who knows maybe
it can but i have to say that this beef brain thing is very suspicious if you look at the bottom
of the beef brain main page it says something about minks if i remember right these are the
same hooligans who pulled the explosive headband prank and then half of you put that horrible
horrible song on your page in order to prevent your head from blowing up if the hypnospace
headband is unhealthy it's probably just because it makes you tired and not some crazy brain
love sandy okay sandy the dumpster the dumpster page should be shut down i don't know how they
get away with tearing people down all the time arlen your artwork is awesome don't listen to
these spoiled punks who wouldn't know good art if it bit them in the behind if they were any good
they wouldn't hide their page like slimy cowards we're going the dumpster taking out hypnospace's
trash so you don't have to previous dumpings i went to cool fest 99 this event was incredible
cool punk is finally dead folks and cool fest killed it from the moment i stepped out of my
car onto the ironically scorching pavement of the king amphitheater parking lot i knew this was
going to be special germa lied about minecraft vr thanks to five community subs again your
username is going to be pretty pretty irrelevant in like a week when i play minecraft vr but thank
you so much for your five subs okay hold on sandwich between two enormous ads for extra
thick chips was the cool fest ticket window waiting patiently in front of where 200 people
not quite the 5 000 person turnout the cool fest plan as we're hoping for here's a highly
scientific pie chart of the attendee types confused 45 year old chowder man fans 15
year old cool punk kids and parents of 15 year old cool punk kids is this a fire festival
jab here after grabbing our tickets a venue attendant had us from another line at the
opposite end of the venue for our promised joeman merch only the cool punk kids and parents hit
this line with the chowder man people heading inside to get good seats for his opening act
after waiting for nearly an hour for the merch to show up the sound of tires screeching called
our attention to a truck speeding towards us knocking a few trash cans over on the way
some sweaty guy emerged with a single box of joeman keychains no shirts and no free grace
as promised people were pissed and the keychains were used as projectiles throughout the rest of
the evening chowder man had already launched into the chowder man's hotel room let's get some
what did i download where's uh where's chowder man there we go found it to be appropriate
chowder man had already launched into the chowder man's hotel room when me and the
gaggle of cool punk kids and parents arrived at the stage he followed it up with some eight
minute song about shaving a couple of newer rap rock songs with his new band cruncher
and an encore of an extended version of the greys peak jingle no one really cared or seemed
particularly into the stuff until the greys peak thing then it happened a helicopter landed on a
platform in the middle of the crowd and the band ate and a few the band and a few fans from that
stage hopped aboard i was surprised that the thing even made it safely with all the wires hanging
around as i'm sure you all know chowder man crashed his copter old chowder's leg had to be
amputated and their drummer died i can't bring myself to be awful about this because it was
harrowing to watch do you think they'd call it a night after a helicopter crash but no cool fest
continued an old guy from greys peak a guy in a joeman costume and a few merchant saw people
came up and gave a speech about how amazing and dedicated cool punk fans are and threw a
few shirts into the crowd it would have been weird anyway but the crash just made it completely
surreal to watch freezer hit the stage next and played for only 15 minutes before it became clear
that he was lip syncing the cool punk kids started yelling mild swear words and started throwing
their joeman key change on stage an old guy came out and told everyone that cool fest was over
and that was it needless to say the event exceeded my expectations
well that was fucking rude that was very well written too that's a very good comedy write-up
right there all right so the dumpster i want to cool fester it is too popular now currently
filling the void the ditch exchange left behind after merchants off banned it until recently
people were only using it to post rips of the bad obscure music they listen to but now the hypnospace
ravel is sharing passwords i guess and it's getting really really bizarre oh like do these
people get that it's private here are a bunch of interesting poems this is a password these are
passwords drawings of cars with human heads even chowder man himself is using it and well just see
for yourself this is a password we should probably revoke all flissed passwords and start again at
least they don't know about the net settler safe mode thing yet nobody tell them please
safe mode net settler safe do i have net settler what is this now that's hypno cure
all right so f 00088 d somebody write that down right everybody somebody everybody write these
down the free lands are amazing taking out hypnospace is trash okay this group of geeks
staged an insurrection after merchants off deleted their favorite zones and i legitimately
like what they're done it's dumb as hell but i love it instead of a list of pages you have
to navigate their zone by clicking arrows on a giant multi-page map and click on landmarks to
visit their pages it takes ages to find what you're looking for i have sticky notes maybe
you guys already wrote down look the only thing i have my only sticky note is from the first 10
minutes of the game all right what are they you guys are gonna fuck with me here so i'm just
gonna get it myself all right f1 f10427a f10427a f10427a f15997a fuck no f15 what was it oh god
dammit control i'll delete f1 f10427a f10427a f15997a f15997a and f 00088 d f 00 f 00088 d
got it cool copy and paste i can't see no no stop stop stop is currently filling the void that dg
exchange stopped talking behind after merchants soft bandit stop talking recently people were
only using it to post rips of the bad obscure music they were just gonna wait till he's done
but now the hypnospace ravel are sharing passwords i guess and it's getting really
here's a twitch tts donation do these people okay complaining about zones that a merchant
soft employee is partially responsible for its existence he disabled the page owner field on
the freelance page so technically anyone who knows about it can get in and make changes
really he just disabled the page owner field i did a little tinkering yeah added a dong shape
but my edits were changed back minutes later so there must be some nerd out there keeping a really
close eye on this stuff let me don oh he put a dick on it okay i get it all right so the home
page can be edited and then visit the archive 1999 halloween and hypnospace world's worst hsm
shutdown designed by non-musicians to save bandwidth by triggering samples that come
pre-installed with hypno os hsms can only be made using hypnospace tune sequencer a free software
package for flaming os the accessibility of the software has resulted in a plague of unlistenable
trash music from amateur composers the world over please put your ears together for the world's
worst hsm showdown this is pizza dance pizza dance so this is the pizza dance song we already have
this we've done a little it's like five times underscores massively kill cybercog circus
kill cybercog circus result of a give a monkey hypnospace tune sequencer experiment
now let's see how bad they are pizza dance
sounds like pretty good sega genesis music i've downloaded this four times why is this one bad i
actually like this one no not chowder man get i'm gonna keep this one on
all right so he says these songs suck especially archive halloween and hypnospace
nothing illegal here nothing just put this keep the song on all night
uh they've decked their pages up with broad assortment of horrifying images of the skeleton
playing guitar skeleton laughing riding a motorcycle standing there hand pointing
tipping a cowboy hat
can i get this as a standout can i get the 3d printed six and a half feet tall let's have a
look at the fellow on the right he's on the left what why do i exist there's a bunch of
gaia dear readers is a halloween offering from good time valley's own celtic warlock arlen fur
obi while not torturing his neighbors with marathon bagpipe practice sessions arlen creates
3d art oh chowder man please we consider that admirable if he wasn't also inflicting irreversible
psychological trauma in the process arlen found our article ow had a personal meltdown and removed
his halloween page don't take these things so hard arlen we're just pulling your hairy celtic leg
arlen's halloween i need this that's the dumpster uh these are the dumpies
and the award for most heinous abuse of a hypnospace template goes to
your bud reggie 55 of the cafe his website sucks the bubble gum template reggie live
with us man what were you thinking here at least bump that placeholder graphic down a few pixels
so your three visitors can actually read about your wife
that's pretty good the chaos award goes to zane zane rocks 14
zane is only 15 years old but we've made an exception to our usual over 18 rule
because this page got game or way lame is an exceptionally juvenile cruel testosterone
fueled work of art like the pic to visit we already shut them down
okay yeah the dumpies page of the year goes to gray's peak coca-cola
they're unironically thrilled about gray peek's horrible tasting drink coming back the three weed
smoking 19 year olds who actually believe this was a meaningful anti-capitalist art movement
have got to be pissed right now go check their pages let's go see with it let's go check up on
them you still seen if you're a little lame episode 2 deleted the news is true i dumped my
girlfriend it just did not work out also i don't like squishers anymore it's for kids i like gory
movies a lot new comic up my best one yet i gotta go back to his uh where's his webpage
to the main god game away lame selection page how do i get to his website zane i guess i just type it
in zane i'm gonna report this kid again okay new updates i used to run a cool hilarious page here
but it got shut down because hypnosis couldn't handle the jokes too sensitive like seven year
olds all right big z studio slayers episode 2 jessica's no longer my girlfriend all right
let's see this is episode 2 all right let's turn this let's mute this so we can get the full
experience okay hey numb nuts over here don't scream yes i am powerful but i am a good guy
come outside zane now voila i am mikey psyche we have been watching you zane come into my energy
portal only if you can handle it let's go a few minutes later they go into the portal practice
stage training zone elite training only game zone this place is freaking huge yes it's the
biggest secret base in the galaxy welcome to the steel sewer we have every single gun machine gun
machine gun sword an rpg in the world we have every instrument and every video game and movie
there's even a soda machine but for now we must talk those dreams you had they're all real the
demons the green energy your secret powers and double pistols all of it's real we need your help
zane there is an evil force at stake in this world most people are blind to its power but we have
been fighting it for 20 years for some reason zane it is scared of you it knows you have a secret
power and if you train and unlock the power it knows that you can kill it sorry i didn't unmute
the music catch up and read issue one not your daddy's comics all right zane good work all right
we were back here what was i doing no we were in the dumpster i'm still looking for a random
illegal do i have any emails i don't think i have any new cases or anything no i gotta find illegal
content let's go back cafe i'm gonna say we should go to teen topia oh check the password
it's a good idea i have there's a lot of pages i have not been to jennifer jennifer's page here
we go i got broken up with unfortunately i have some very bad news corey paul has dumped me he
says he has met someone else who is very special on here so i totally get it i wish we could be
together forever but alas it was not to be farewell corey paul reading writing graphic
design athletic teams at school doing hair and makeup girl stuff oh no me and corey are no
longer together as a couple she took that very well yeah she took it way very well it was not
meant to be goodbye what was going on with his web wait wait wait did you hear that what did say
what's and what's going on here he's still handsome and smart but don't like him anymore
i've broken up with zane he just broke up tonight he's awesome and his comics are incredible
just didn't work out it's because i'm too scared at horror movies and he likes to watch those all
the time yeah it's he's making these websites zane is making multiple websites pretending
all right here's pizza boogie downloading the doctor pizza pizza dance song it's free
i already have it you guys remember hamster dance does that still exist that website
still launches you did it on beat saber no no no that was the crazy frog song the one that goes
that hurt i can't do it mention the pizza dance song in your next doctor pizza visit to get a
free ice cream treat offer valid until 131 2000 one ice cream sundae per child 11 100 per visit
doctor pizza that's squishing number three never do that again why would i ever do that again
can you come up with a reason why i would ever try to do the hamster dance song again
this is the only context where it makes any sense a 1990s internet simulator why did i do it once
because we're in a 1990s internet simulator and i had to show you guys okay we got the uh
squisher i'm still looking for violations randy's dino world okay happy thanksgiving
randy's dino world and more i'm eight years old in third grade this is the fastest dinosaur in
the whole world what are you asking santa for for christmas i'm asking for a dinosaur that really
walks triceratops t-rex that one doesn't work stegosaurus broken triceratops broken
pyridactyl broken spinosaurus broken and many more broken take this website down
randy's other page see listen why is it doing that why is it slowing down like that this is
about me i am on hypnosis every night i am so sleepy so i go to bed early so i can go on
hypnosis more and more i love hypnosis my birthday is january 10th i like drawing ice cream and
dinosaurs i like mr peters he's so funny i like taurus x i love squisher z i love my mom and dad
and little sister it's pizza dance what's taurus x no nothing what no i'm not gonna ban the little
kid he's not breaking any laws he's not look there's nothing here we still tim again we still
have this fucked up website no violations here sure i'm gonna try this passwords all right what
was that wasn't even that thing what the hell was that website flst right access portal passwords
here uh the price went up to 200 bucks wasn't this 99 this was so much cheaper before oh fuck
off okay let's try it f-104-27a f-104-27a get trouble does not match any fuck f-15-997a
you got trouble you know f-00088d
f-00088d you got trouble what the fuck those aren't passwords you need to tilde
tilde tilde at the beginning i can't do tilde it doesn't do anything
tilde doesn't do anything those are error codes you got trouble uh do i actually have to buy it
check the scam see if the sub boy updated with treasure
there is nothing there i got scammed and what if i just search for a password is it that broken
is this internet that bad password pick a secure password i get almost every day is how to
best go about making up a password that online criminals won't be able to guess here's a good
method use personal information that only you know my favorite method a great example might be the
city you live plus your favorite hobby plus your birth year uh hold on can i can i hack this guy
wait denver computers 1970 so if you live in denver you're 29 and your favorite hobby is
computers wow mine too your password would look like this good luck cracking this password hackers
denver computers 1970 if this works
to get trouble fuck no damn it i thought that could have been somebody's go back well what's
his ad what's his i need his info i had his info all right he's from lexington if you live in
denver and you're 29 so it will be lexington computers 49
did you forget your password you're close not i get wait i get a 1940 why would it say that
lexington computers 1949 to get trouble what 1950 got him
pages must be hit wait wait wait welcome to flist enjoy your stay rules flist pages must be hidden
no zone listing if we see pages listed here we will delete no linking id sharing without
permission ah dmghg welcome germa that's not who i am how to find flist file directories new users
you are now able to see flist directories by searching for flist ids oh i got three of those
flist ids are formatted as follows the last six characters of a headband id
we have chowder man's id do not share flist directories with other other than your own
without permission keep flist music and software related no porn be aware that merchant soft
developers and enforcers can see your headband ids for your citizen data so there's a chance
they could find your flist if they gain access oh boy no porn flist page style guide hypno font
regular or bold preferred transparent background please follow the style guide as it makes flist
directories look un-uniformly computery and official okay how to find flist file directories
so i just need to search just have to search for their ids is there a portal or do i have to just do
just do it from the search page here who do we got first let's do uh chowder head whatever
his name is chowder man this background sucks hold on let me redo my background this is bad
okay theme eggplant space meat no keep that that one's kind of cool where's the one with the soda
there's a soda drinking one right get this like cheese out of here
no don't delete the cheese oh my god idiot why here i made one big one for you no here it is
that's the one i want why is this broken no this looks like shit that's better
all right let's go search let's search uh f 000 88 d real chowder man cuff my man my best friend
i have let you down for the last time please forgive me fans and friends i am deeply sorry
for this tragedy i beg you to have mercy on directory file list the chowder man private
files one legged man for the chowder man eyes only do not look if you do not belong here then
do the right thing and go downloading one legged man what is this
oh there's a song you crashed and you burned your time has run out the chowder man must ask
himself who am i now where will you run with only one leg you can barely hop and now you must beg
come back oh come back oh don't let it end forgive me and hold me signed one legged friend
may i maybe i can be like the mighty men of old the pirates with one leg they got so much gold
that's private file right there all right well that's his private data all right what about
violations i feel like i'm missing something here hold on wait wait wait now leak it we have to find
another violation list master directory we can just look up everybody's fucked up shit huh
all right what about the cafe we've got i this first time i've ever even been here
this is the hypno space dev dm tune box secret project secret project we have an opportunity
to create an interactive gaming experience like anything the world has seen using hypno us and
the hypno space network the tranquility guy has a list yeah we'll we'll get to it so this is the
game he was talking about right cool thing by dylan plus business stuff by adrienne equals tons
of cash okay for the creative team they're gonna be there's not gonna be any violations here
hazel pedia beauty emotion experimentation
oh 885 d let's just collect fucking a bunch of data is that actually supposed to be boobs
i think it is all right let's go back barnaby's chair american alternative rock band listen now
band bio e scrotum records e scrote east satanic records and we already were here
click the monkey to hear satellite orchestra now oh it's instrumental intro okay disturbing
imagery that's not a that's a it's a monkey band bio we need disturbing imagery we need like
drugs or there's no drugs here don't bother there's nothing on this page this is the dumpster
told you why don't just remove it then if no os tech tips by gearhead greg again my desktop
doesn't usually have this many stickers on it just a fun example of what stickers can do
so greg has yeah greg greg's the moment you get the the cheats joe's software reviews
instead of taking a break but i can't stay away from this place still really tired but it's
worth it to be with you all the janitor game i think it might be illegal hold on it does allow
you to score easy hypno coin but i deleted it because i don't want to implicate myself in crimes
janitor the janitor game got it type something here to update your fellow citizens here we go
let's get the id that's 00928a janitor i gotta start labeling these what was this one no i can't
click again it'll delete them welcome to your job janitor wants to earn hypno coin are you a qualified
accounting professional over the age of 18 good become an independent contractor accountant for
royden capital today by clicking below by installing the janitor accounting software
you agree to the terms at the bottom of the page how to do the job to make hypno coins
make piles of five documents by dragging documents over one another put completed
pile in incinerator to make coins put infected files and incinerator immediately what downloading
janitor does it work make piles of five documents
okay accounting software janitor welcome to your job
does it work you lost a note oh okay let's go again
okay what what's wrong do these not count no those are infected oops so what i do have to put
different categories why do i only have one dollar these have to go directly in why do i only have
one coin you delete what do you mean i'm deleting what wait wait wait wait my passwords receipts
can't say that they're already jokes these aren't real you can't say these aren't real these how
these what i don't own these popular free quass quass word puzzles these aren't even real songs
gum shoe gooper season two episode five
oops no no this shit's even real you guys are just freaking me out yeah this is all right let me
level up we get to level three get in there come on yeah this is like invoice it's not real
why is your hard drive space increasing my hard drive space is not increasing you can't even see
that info that doesn't even make sense give me some more i'm making money this is good shit
365 look at that see i burn these books oh three that's not anything on my computer i'm getting
16 coins for a pop per pile i'm gonna be here for the next two hours and then i'm gonna sue them
i mean i'm starting to understand there probably is a catch though is there a catch because this
seems way too easy to do but none of these what what the hell was that i picked it up i just
picked it up what cash it out no i did what i that was stupid just start over each incineration makes
you a millimeter shorter that was pretty good all right level up i'm gonna get to the last level
to slow it down documents on the right multimedia on the left stop going over there fun and
interesting gameplay i'm trying to make money okay i'm trying to make money how am i ever gonna make
it this is so boring just let me get over 500 bucks or like a thousand bucks just let me get up
no i'm done i'm done fuck come on i'm just if i i'm not i'm sitting like defending why i'm
playing the game just all right you know now i'm gonna play it again just despite everybody
get in there what happened last time all right i'm at 501 that's what i wanted
i will finish this last one though all right close it get it out stop making two piles well
here's why wait what hold on a second wasn't the last time i put a multimedia file in with
documents it fucked it up it blew up what no that happened that happened last time it did
that happened no that wasn't a joke play the beginning what it was a virus i thought i did
like a multimedia image all right well now i'm gonna sit here for another few minutes no that
wasn't a joke i thought i couldn't combine them i thought i could only combine documents
everyone's probably fucking freaking out right now please beloved god anything but this
the rich get richer what's the highest level well we'll see it don't worry we'll still see we'll get
it all right almost there why was there i was there i was there i'm close somebody said there
has to be severe consequences for doing this i agree you're right there has to be i think you
guys are right when i exit out of here all my files are gonna be gone uh i might as well go the whole
mile then i said a thousand dollars right i'll get there i'll get there really quick you said
50 yeah but look at how close i am 300 more dollars and then that's it and i could buy
whatever i want who cares if we don't get to hear the same song that we heard five times already
this is so much money you know how hard it was doing my job was less money than this don't you
guys realize that working was giving me less money than dragging files 800 how do i get to level how
do i get higher up is there only three levels probably all right we're gonna get to that look
at how close it is now you guys were concerned before an hour almost there 900 917 945 almost
done i promise and i will collect a thousand bucks what happened what happened what's going on what
happened what happened i don't understand i didn't touch anything sexy farts sound collection what
i don't understand what if you leave it i missed a virus it looked like it looked like it just like
sat over here for a second and then disappeared i don't know they were time sensitive the virus
wiggles so it's all right we're almost done all right would you rather be played this for another
another 15 minutes or would you rather me do a 10 hour picross stream starting now wow really
really i don't buy that for a second all right we're at a thousand that's it how do i get up
it's that easy everything's still here it's not a scam
you got trouble how is this not illegal
you got trouble what malicious software it's not malicious i mean is it this is it's not malicious
software
you got trouble i guess i guess it's malicious software or unauthorized software okay i guess
well let's get this guy's id 00928a i think i got it already yep okay goodbye i already got it
so welcome to your new job as a janitor received from dispatch there we go i think we think we
triggered it case added janitor found by germa whoa so this janitor program surprised it hasn't
been passed around more seeing as it's a source of endless hypno coin seems like a pretty poorly
thought out scheme all around good find this case has been manually signed to germa by miss samantha
click the cases tab to view your progress all right i got it important message received from
dispatch you found these violations before being assigned this case i'm a narc good job no more
free money case closed great job removing that malicious or unauthorized software speed booster
malicious software type of violation malicious this is a malicious software notice regarding
another another that does he reported at starport castle dream station please utilize your
enforcement tool to report and remove it as soon as possible starport castle dream station
okay speed boosting report to starport castle utilize your law enforcement tool you got it
note one of our servers is severely overloaded and keeps crashing as a result this normally
only happens at this rate if someone is using a download accelerator or speed booster to get
around merchant soft's bandwidth capping measures this case has been manually signed to germa
let's go find the malicious software starport castle dream station a new zone for all you geeks
nerds and other citizens with niche interests starport welcome to starport castle dream station
a message from hypno space ceo adrian merchant a new zone where fans of fantasy science fiction
and other niche interests may converge if your listed pages appears if your listed pages
appeared in one of the following zones they may have now been relocated here home shop gamers only
okay new email alert change your password now what it seems that passwords of multiple
merchant soft personnel have been recently compromised change your password immediately
if you have access to code base how do i do that
how do i change my password
restart should i restart the computer
we got trouble your launcher tutorial download man i don't have any what is this thing
we got trouble i got no viruses i'm good i'm getting the big one virus quarantine
remove viruses safe mode browsing tool install that shit right now all right wave virus quarantine is
what does wave hello oh right right okay does the professional version have anything
okay pro versions running all right we're good
so let's go back to where we were castle dreams station so we have sovereign alliance of
imagine wait i'm gonna go to the bios does the game just save if i log off all right i'm gonna
restart the hipto station bios right fuck i gotta actually log off i don't know oh fuck it i have
the best antivirus in the world here we go welcome to the bowl ring unofficial taris fan resource
taris x right sad that has come to this i support my employers but i also support my friends so i
have joined the freelance 0021 d did you not have the 0002 three zeros
uh taurus guy taurus whatever log off on the bottom right what are you talking about
log off then check bottom right what are you talking what do you look
log off and check bottom right uh yeah but there's nothing here the path i've had the
path i don't have a password i figured that out once i didn't have a place to do it yeah that's
it i got nothing i got no reason to be here change the voice this is a test of the hypno s voice
synthesis bot hippie this is a test of the hypno s voice synthesis bot there's only two this is a
test of the hypno s voice custom voice custom voice this is a test of the hypno s voice
i probably have to add that hippie all right that's fine full screen scaling this is like
an interesting little menu here though i'm not going to reset the bios no probably going to
reset all my save data that would be terrible all right let's go back to what we were doing which
is we need to find the speed hacker we're here the bull ring i still have the merchant brothers
and i believe in merchants off this company i feel it is only right to stand with my friends
in these trying times and move to a new company so they have moved to the psi freelance they are
no longer on this console interesting stuff all right linda has moved to psi everyone's moving
to psi cooking up a few new scarries for you all making a big one with the dark twilight tiff
linda's library of weird is now located in the psi freelance click here for more info
sovereign alliance of imagination because merchant soft has seen fit to merge our zones no warning
and severely limit our download speeds the remaining members of the five deleted zones
have come together to form a sovereign alliance of imagination we have decided in unison to
delist our pages and form our own zone free from the control of merchant soft well she probably
shouldn't have said that everyone's welcome contact gil s creates for an information on how
to join and how i secure how to secure a place in the freelance all right visit the freelance
quick to read the psi freelance credits we got trouble gil sanders and sarah sanders
we got some names here chowder man's back rotty wall for special things we got gil sanders sarah
sanders ready to shave by the chowder man let's go up trial of acceleration
secret stash is hidden in the freelance you shall unlock it to east of roddy's bowl ring that's me
one north of casper's rocket only one path leads to this place look closely at the border hold on
once you find it come back here in this trial you will rock it to set again two left and boring
a secret stash is hidden in the freelance you shall unlock it to east of roddy's bowl ring
one north of casper's rocket only one path leads to this place look closely at the border
once you find it come back here in this trial you will rock it the secret stash is hidden in
the freelance you shall unlock it to east of roddy's bowl ring to east of roddy one north
of casper's rocket only one path leads to this place look closely at the border once you find it
come back here in this trial you will rock it all right thanks a lot kid
so we got the ball ring all right here's the ball ring
to east of ball ring is the ball ring right here to east i mean that's north
north starport castle there's a library of weird signify starport gamers only
just go back down somebody said flags to east one north you think it would be this one then right
no that's not right maybe you have to physically be on the website to east from bowl ring check
the borders i would think like back here who is tourist comprehensive history me i'm your that's
me about roddy me your friendly ringleader programmer merchants off working on hypnosis
dream job none yet hobbies living in california it's on the map yeah but there's no it was
two east of of roddy one no wait a minute yeah of the bowl ring one north of casper's rocket
it let me just check over here just want to look this casper's rocket north of casper's rocket
check borders this is casper's rocket right there one north from casper's rocket up here
wait wait wait wait yeah i probably have to go around then it's probably like up here
go up and around i i know i know i know my goodness yeah then it's down it's down here
going down again court this is it is the treasure in the castle welcome to my court
i can adopt a dragon secret path oh there it is click to open the stash of the acceleration
only if worthy am i worthy it's another video another clue i should have wanted to adopt a
dragon let's see where do you want me to go now the father of the cybercaugian name
the mother of the freelance what she shoots in her game uh the amount of zones that merchant
soft sent to an early grave as five now return to the freelance south of the coliseum wait an input
this code you figured out for your final test i really hope to see you the father of the father
it's roti cybercaugian name the mother of the freelance what she shoots in her game she shoots
the amount of five that merchant soft sent to an okay so we needed the names the names and what
they do
okay it's the ball it's the guy the ball guy and what about linda linda's world famous library
weird cybercaugian name mother of the freelance what did she shoot the amount of zones that
merchant soft sent to an early grave now return to the freelance south of the coliseum
it's not linda figured out for your final test i really hope to see you ring ring well you're
gonna get that all right hold on this guy's still talking linda stevens prank call 1999
can i download these you like classic schlock low budget movies gore and guts with wild biker women
child there's so much content in this game i'm actually surprised with just how much there is
horror movie page does it but there's linda the mother does she i mean she oh she shoots movies
right i'm not the right lady though yeah one two three four five these are the five places that
were now defunct gary's control room welcome to gary's control if you've been to a cybercaug event
we've probably met i've attended over 20 events all over the country over the last
three years new interactive story let's go back the bull ring guy did not make the place i thought
he did hold on a second the ringleader about roddy me your friendly ringleader i'm roddy let's see i
dropped out of high school then i became famous in the world of computing after releasing sandwich
encryption with sam parker now i work at hypnospace programming some of dylan's creations
so this is this is the ringleader but it's not the father wouldn't that make sense
gil sanders and sarah sanders map art by gil sanders so gil sarah's gil and sarah sanders
no for all you smart alex out there the page is gil s it is not gil secretes thank you
with that out of the way welcome to gil s creates okay the ready to shave analysis page
so what does it want me to do it was the the father and what cybercog circus downloading
gil cybercog circus sanderverse custom campaign for quest of six mountains rule set
oh there's a bow and arrow sarahina is a character me and my wife sarah made up based on
many of sarah's real life quirks master archer and can use telepathy to communicate with almost
any being in the sanderverse this drawing is my own artistic interpretation of sarina
sarania quick link to see my wife's drawing she uses in game that's bone arrow so it's sarah
an arrow power telepathy 26 so she shoots arrows she uses a bow gil and i are proud to announce
that sigh freelance are now open let's show merchant soft how to really run a zone
okay so bow what about his character let me listen to that video again
no that's not i wanted the video his handle is signal okay it's played by me okay signal
how do i delete this fucking song get rid of this song this one is killing me
me all right so signal bow five got it oh let me get his like personal information too while i'm
at it gil sanders okay 104 25a skill okay i need another note here because i'm gonna run out of
space so the last part of that was it was hidden down somewhere right on the map play for me one
more time she shoots away she shoots arrows we need that information the father of the
freelance all right where is it iberkogian name the mother of the freelance what she shoots in
her game uh-huh the amount of zones that merchants five sent to an early grave now return to the
free return to the freelance south of the coliseum self of the coliseum put this code you figured out
for your final test so it's self of the coliseum
you got trouble some of the coliseum where the fuck is the coliseum
save a signal arrow five you got trouble
oh
speed booster found and unlocked get the fuck out of here free download and loading speed boost for
hypno ls are you worthy of acceleration acceleration is only for members of the
sovereign alliance of imagination to prove that you're a member of the psi and gain access to
accelerator please answer the following six questions oh shit what is the name of the
size special custom made zone it's the freelance if you fail you have to start over from the
beginning hahaha okay that's fine freelance what did casper air graphics do before he made
amazing fantasy sci-fi artwork well fuck me played guitar in a cosmic rock band played synthesizer
in a cool punk band played saxophone played bass played tuba in the swedish national orchestra
wasn't it's guitar right tuba is the tuba are you sure i thought it was a guitar in a cosmic rock
band yeah i got it what are short scary stories involving everyday objects called hint they were
invented by the citizens of the comic shop scaries which popular dragon adoptee is an impish prankster
in goofball hint this dragon was famous in the dream castle i have no idea we didn't adopt one
this is just a 20 chance to get this right that's mozzarella i don't think that's correct
all right 25 chance to get this right that sounds too cartoonish 33 chance to get this right i can't
believe you guys just made me do that told you it wasn't mozzarella why would it be mozzarella
freelance cosmic rock scaries no it's not giraffe oh we can do it as much as we want
cosmic rock scaries snoggle off my god scary there it is all right what are torus and muletta
aside from being the best comic book heroes in the world it's a bull a psychic bull and a magic
carpet a mutant ox okay it's a humanoid bull and a sentient camp a psychic bull and a magic carpet
done what highly valuable cyber cog items grant human superpowers after they are decrypted in
special computer terminals cog cog disks data cogs cog works data cogs well pog works i'm not sure
i'm going to say data cogs case closed you are worthy download and loading speed booster for
hypno os click here to download while accelerator is free a small hypno coin donation to one of the
following people the organizations would go a long way to making their lives a little better
donate to one or all of these great people if you want to be added to the donation zone just ask me
all right roddy i got you 00021 d well let's get it let's download it
i got it downloaded right let's go test it out to make sure it works
all right let's try it accelerator
it's on all right this is do i get broadband capable speeds
you got trouble say hello page text removed due to violation of their hypno space law
what about these two i'm above the law sad that it has come to this i support my employees but i
also message received from dispatch new case pirated music this is a content infringement
notice regarding multiple instances of unauthorized music distribution reported an unknown zone
please utilize your enforcement to the report and remove them as soon as possible
i'm gonna piss my pants i'll be right back i'm gonna get some water see you in a second
this is a really cool game it's fun just to chill and play it i recommend okay so
finally close this one it's a music one here's this one great job removing that malicious or
unauthorized software so uh notice that we had a ton of backed up music piracy reports from the
last few weeks that were never assigned to an enforcer i've attached to reports text files
please do these as soon as possible as it sounds very serious good luck
and thanks we have to find copyright
he's still pinging no i'm back so can i just keep this on i'm not gonna get in trouble for that
right oh geez okay uh your hypno space service has been used to access download or distribute
our copyrighted works without authorization please remove the musical compositions listed
below from hypno space to avoid legal complications artist glamocaster album glamoplasm
okay let's go remove glamoplasm
glamoplasm this is a review it's not on here right
hazepedia i already donated it what i already did this all right forget it what is haze
okay hold on popular artists earth haze listen to haze i'm working on getting a public page
you're free to download haze songs up not so easy to copyright restrictions
chit chat it's not on the site right now it just plays on their site can i just like
what's this reload in safe mode uh copyright infringement
that's that'll do it right we got trouble no really could listen to haze's i can click this
and then 808 5d
oh you're fucked okay buddy well uh this is the whole album here glamocaster glamoplasm
i'll see you in jail download it first you know that's a good idea downloading 12 files
downloading four files downloading six files okay good no linking or i'll ban you
oh you got you got way more problems going on here man did i get them
zary the zareed glam yeah i got it what's going on music file added to tunebox does my d drive
have enough space get trouble right who's the other one uh glamocaster glamoplasm yep
now should i do every single one of these all the links to get trouble oh yeah here we go
it's gonna be a while
slam the ball oh god shake my mouse you got trouble i need a new sound pack
i've been using this one for a long time this is good money i got mail
hold on i'm busy listening i'll see you in court i wonder how close i am to the credits of the game
are there even credits in this game or is it just sort of an experience where you
just can keep doing it forever important message received hold on
you've been what wait wait wait wait wait where's my email what happened what email email email
what happened you've been ha ha ha you're hilarious did you seriously just report me dude what when
who did i report i didn't report dylan when did i do that i had to wait was that was that him
sharing the music it's been 35 days since you last logged on that page was his
i'm sitting there just like crunching on a butterfinger why is it a butterfinger i don't
know i have nothing else after that i don't know why it was a butterfinger and it fucked up my
whole statement most stable secure release yet no crashes okay i don't know where that even came
from restart okay oh this is sleek you are now on active duty important message received from
all right let me see what the hell is going on here change your password okay pirated music
this is from dylan did you seriously just report me dude uh did you think i wouldn't notice i don't
know if this was you being funny or what because everyone shares music nowadays but the fact of
the matter is that our whole team knows about my flist page now if any of our interns are snitches
you could really cause a problem for me and the entire company we're doing some amazing things
over here and i'll be damned if some little idiot is going to bring it crashing down because they
wanted to be funny i'm taking you off duty you're lucky i'm not banning you i was just listening to
this whole playlist and reporting every line of text that was my boss's webpage okay you've been
removed from active enforcement no you will not receive cases or hs pd communications until you
replace back on active duty thank you this has been an automated alert sent to germa enforcer
punishment i don't get it uh you're now on active enforcement this is an art of interventions you're
back on active enforcement okay oops i'm so sorry hi germa so i don't know if it was me or the system
or whatever it looks like you were removed from the active enforcer list which means you've
probably been really bored over the last few weeks this very well could have been my mistake and i'm
so so sorry not an excuse but i don't think i've ever been this exhausted at a job our interns are
off for the holidays so dylan has some of us pulling double duty with hs pd stuff and our normal
tasks i've just added you back as an active enforcer you received cases after the year 2000
update finishes installing see you in the new millennium sorry again okay so we so dylan
removed us and then she put us back on so does she not know that we're on the team again someone
has hacked into the teen topia main page and are threatening some sort of attack i'm not sure what
you enforcers can do about this but if i don't assign the case i'll never hear the end of it from
my bosses since the violations are on official merchant soft pages the system will reject any
quick checks you do it would be an easy fix if everyone with administrative access wasn't out
of the office still look into it if you think you can find a way to stop it okay so the violations
are on official merchant soft pages the system will reject any quick checks you do this is a
malicious software notice regarding an admitted year 2000 hacker in teen topia please figure out
how to disable or prevent the attack i wish we didn't have to do this important things in
caps thing because it's a pain to keep it consistent yeah this operating system sucks all right so
malicious software we're gonna find it gotta track it down in teen topia yeah there sure is
something going on in teen topia right now uh it's the same guy it's tim the y2000 mine
crash cometh the digital parasites you love so much are in danger only one can stop it
if only you'd make peace with your blessed imparted name mother of son of mother of son
of tim dearest chosen one then you could save them time until mine crash to what accept thy
name and input it here i don't i don't know what it is back good thing i got that accelerator
installed okay uh citizen pages april the angelic hamster this is not gonna be professor again is it
okay health happiness buy food how much is food how do we get rid of the shit trash okay rename
no i don't want to keep it be sure to pet feed and clean up after her click here for virtual pet tips
it's monitoring health drag their poop to the recycling bin if your pet's poop is not disposed
of your pet's health will decline do not wave your pet's excrement in their face it's not fun
for them it shouldn't be fun for you i kind of already did that okay unfed and ignore their
happiness would decrease don't feed it feeding your pet icons and files that aren't pet food is
not advised okay c man 2.0 all right all hell's breaking loose here i got what i got safe mode
what about my safe mode doesn't even work okay ashley's planets go back and get the squisher
all right all right i'll get this go i'll get the squisher where is it got it can i have two i'm in
the third grade i found these planets on hypnospace these planets are made up they're
not real ones in outer space i like them because they are fun to imagine about two new planets
crazy planet it's can't make up its mind that this planet will just waste your time and it
can't choose so everyone yells at it hurry up hurry up girl and boy planets mom told me about
these new planets the boy one is blue and the girl one is pink they can make a little baby planet
the boy planet is not allowed to play with my toys so i am happy uh new planets tiny planet
this planet is so small it is swimming ants living on it is the mustard planet quick quick quick i
gotta get the first one got it yes thank god i got the first one this planet is mustard instead of
water like normal it is where the mustard comes from they have mustard spaceships that go get it
and bring it to the king foods on earth i can read this this is a big one this planet is made
out of lines and water splashes only fish lives in the water splashes rebecca the planet i name
this planet rebecca rebecca is my sister all kinds of shapes on this one josh the planet this planet
gets mad all the time for no good reason that's why i call it josh jesus the planet this planet
is pretty like god that's why i call it jesus moon planet this is moon this is different than
the normal moon it has waterfalls on it and a secret rainforest on the inside of it me my
friends were digging here and that's when we discovered the rainforest with monkeys
moon to the planet this is the moon planet too it is not the normal moon it is the foe
of water like a water balloon do not poke it this brain protected by beef brain beef brain shield
no to other parents and kids hello this is ashley's mother once again i can't understand why none of
you care about your children but since it is obvious that you don't i don't want her learning
things from your bad eggs ashley is forbidden to talk to any of the other kids in teen topia
and her chit chat what the fuck was that has been deleted do not send her messages i will be
watching what was it why did that happen wait wait wait wait wait wait all right ashley rolls
oh aldrin 16882a 16882a where's 16882a no what was that one no fuck no oh come on
that was roddy's i don't know the fuck it was my god this operating system is gonna make me die
16882a was her name ashley excuse me uh the planet no that's too okay just ashley she's a
planet girl why do i need everybody's id i don't know that's rebecca aldrin's sister from earlier
yeah that's interesting it's all connected what's the what's what was roddy's somebody know just
like rewind the stream just tell me what it was just just 000211d because before i leave i want
to snoop on everybody in the world okay counselor ronnie's place ask ronnie play hi teen topians
click the play learner ask ronnie buttons to to navigate my awesome pages made just for you
squisher's art contest got him art contest winner grand prize
ribby i got mail way to go here's your first squisher quest reward
oh downloading squisher finally we can change the sound effects downloading squisher perfect
oh it's the it's the hamster okay squisher's um cool so where that was the i got a theme too
dude i didn't even finish the last case what the hell is it called stop god damn it no no no no no
what is it called squisher z sound effects theme downloading squisher z one downloading squisher
okay there it is is it down is it installing both of them oh that's nicer okay squisher's
fly did i get a squisher's theme why is it just not at the bottom
ah just sort by date yeah that's true squisher's theme nice all right what about wallpaper
i don't have a squisher's wallpaper that's kind of annoying i'll keep this one
uh that's a lot of money who just gave that uh colonel zero just gave it fifty dollars
five thousand bits from colonel zero thank you colonel zero on roll uh counselor no what am i
doing i gotta read your message hey jeremy can you tell my boyfriend i said good night yeah
good night good night colonel zero's boyfriend have a great night if you're going to bed see
you tomorrow if you come tomorrow thank you so much for the 50 bucks seriously all right we need
to find that's a shitload of money really jojo reference where here this is this is a jojo
reference one of these all right in addition to helping you guys with issues that new kids
often face i'm also keeping a watchful eye on what goes on in teen topia this is the hacker
this guy's info 00185 d and this is counselor 00185 d counselor i know it's spelled wrong don't
matter 00185 d okay play play with ronnie check out squisher's quest to win special prizes
yeah i already got this let's check back though how many do i have missing like five six hamster
hamster hamster hamster oh i think i have i held my hand out and let him shit in my hand
i have a donut how much food do i this is so expensive there's no point to have this
it doesn't grow up it doesn't do anything you don't get anything for it i can't just delete
whatever all right ask ronnie coming soon check out the learn page okay grayson's page all right
where fear me tim again it's this guy again all right it's time to go and get on your account
all right how about stick breed construction toy with attitude
strict stick bricks is thrilled to be a hypnosis partner brand our full stick bricks catalog is
coming soon get the stick bricks brick placer for hypnosis and play with stick bricks on it
yeah let's get it stick bricks okay who owns this not registered all right it's legos except
it's painful yeah i can see that i don't get it oh i get it that's like a two out of ten for fun
i made that oh you did sorry all right that's it for that all right squish champ
this page was deleted please remove this page like the name of page squishy champ 500 in the
zone good time please call who what something hidden here nothing hidden interesting yeah how
is zane doing let's find out or corey let's let's do zane this is zane my name on here is zane rocks
but now i'm 15 my mom gets shoes at the dollar store new updates i'm on free lunch because my
mom works at a gas station and barely even keeps that job going my most boyfriend pays for hypno
space so i don't hear them going wild all night in her room what the fuck is going on here
about saying 11 age 11 uh 15 why are you 11 great farts music girl music not seepage because they
suck you got hacked favorite movies nude dudes too naked crimes favorite games anything where
you pet horses yeah he got hacked i'm with corey now big secret probably eating free lunch pretending
to not suck stalking girls on chit chat jennifer's the hacker jennifer's behind the whole y2k incident
what else you got here what about the comics page no that's with any new comics i got speed
what's with this okay what about corey okay here's corey pull up a chair you're at attention teen
topia this is corey again after having a big talk with my parents i have decided that i must come
clean with you all i did not really have a girlfriend the page i made was fake i'm very
sorry for being deceptive and i hope that you will forgive me the reason i made this page is
because i was embarrassed that everyone else on here had a girlfriend but i did not i thought it
would make me look cool well as you can see now i was wrong about that i promised never to lie again
on here my parents have agreed to allow me one more chance to straighten out so it's back to good
old classic corey with the jokes and the pizza i'm sorry i tried to change where i really am
sincerely corey so what so what's going on with zane's page let me see this zane zane lofton 1147
11478 no this is different person corey paul henderson which is jennifer's page still up
all right squish request squishers rave rave raves roots pin jessica's page have broken up
with hello this is tiffany the reason i broke this is a real person no it's not so this is zane
he uses way too much cheap cologne he's lame also seepage sucks all right pizza boogie have
your parents take you to dr pizza we've seen this right all right we gotta we're gonna get
this hacker it's time to go into gas files hacked the fake uh grayson they have not been here this
is the most popular hypno space page i can draw every car or motorcycle for one dollar if you go
to lake wales high school and can give me a dollar i will draw you a car or motorcycle for you i can
draw also a few characters from cartoons thanks it helps a lot i'm 14 years old my favorite subject
is art uh all right all right all right hold on extra legal commerce no it's just a kid
all right what's this dude what's this dude's fucking page 00928a you got anything on here
butt's disease true okay hold on a minute mine crash got him virus ideas marshmallow i got you
downloading my downloading my crash those butt disease
downloading true tranquility downloading virus ideas downloading three y three
marshmallow pick downloading marshmallow so this is it right this is i i got you
this is malicious software right here let's just make sure my var i'll get out of the way
okay let's see let's sort by date three oh it's an encrypted file this is encrypted
marshmallow picks i'm gonna hold on to this i don't i need it virus ideas finished
butt's disease make all windows say butts fart noises recursor make like a hundred images that
look just like the cursor appears so it's hard to know where to click boy we're laughing a lot
okay robin h minx will like this steal from the rich and give to the poor kind of thing robin dot
h nude professor help or something with pets nude what's robin h all right we we don't we
we can come back here robin h will you fucking stop robin nothing they're not here they don't
exist okay recursor okay so let's see what butts what butts does butts disease i have an antivirus
i'll be fine does it work how do i get this to run all right he just ate butts disease
so it doesn't work okay well that was fun i'm not missing something here right true tranquility
this doesn't work either what if we get this is it my antivirus disable antivirus okay
turn off no i think it's just placeholder just kind of to be there look like it
all right turn that back turn it on turn it on all right here's mine crash hey marshmallow uh what is
this okay hey marshmallow or i mean tiff it's me tim i'm sorry if this comes off as weird but i
didn't know how else to get you to hear me out just want to say i'm sorry for whatever i did
to hurt or offend you and i hope we get to talk soon i really miss our conversations you are really
important to me and i don't want to throw away what we had too soft maybe take this out before
posting there's no mine crash it's just a silly thing i did to get you to read this page
chit chat me and let's work on something together you can write the whole thing
and i'll just do the art and music it'll be all yours love tim ps i was using that chit chat
spying program to watch merchant soft's internal conversations and i think you were totally right
about hypnospace causing your migraines they seem like they know it's bad for people but
don't care want to move to cyber worlds maybe notice elf have teentopia reset to normal after
she sees this tiff now okay encrypted file i know how to deal with an encrypted file
which files do you need protected what is sandwich encryption hmm while sandwich isn't officially
supported by a hypno os there may be a way to decrypt locked sandwich files you'll have to
chit chat me for more information roddy wall as mentioned above he helped invent sam which
may also be able to help he's currently working on hypnospace's virtual pets game and has a page in
hypnospace that's huh really now wouldn't that be interesting do it yes yes i didn't even i didn't
even think about it i was perfect perfect install way i don't know what this is should i install it
don't do it yet how do i go back and get that again i still own it right no it's in it i can
just go over on his website i can get it that was such an over the top reaction i thought that was
it downloading relax but okay hold on this is it i got it come on that was funny all right here we
go installing all seeing i you have been blessed with second sight have i sees all sees all
interesting i probably have to put something up here like icon or a webpage maybe oh well there
you go okay sees all sees all we'll put it over here for now but first i need to uh i need to
i mean i mean you're you're you're going to fucking jail like just like let's be honest here what
about what about tim's actual webpage the one with all the shit all over it uh teen topia okay this is
alcohol let's see i told you it was the guidance counselor no never mind it's tim's website it has
to be look at the what it say look at the one you've reached what does it say no stop stop stop
with the deleted page come on stop that shit it's not here come on i'll find it did i just
catch something shit what about tiffany's where does tiffany have a website who you probably
don't belong here if you are in need of entertainment check out dork twilight tiff got it and now i know
who you are she isn't a hacker but her stories are amazing who will watch the watchman only those
with true site may enter we don't meet with the uiv oh here we go enter the fleshy domain of
tim mageddon enter the fleshy domain of tim mageddon butthole testing testing this is cool oh no i
can't see what i'm typing click to enter okay hold on uh dark twilight tiff i feel like i should do
that first beyond twilight give me that info got you 17105a are we asleep or awake how can
we really ever know in these mystical tomes are tales i've penned oh i already been here
some nice and sweet some dark and grim in my stories nothing is sure what was that a knock
on your door yeah we've already been here i'm a 16 year old girl from a small town in the midwest
pretty boring humdrum life before hypnospace nothing else interesting to say i like black
licorice like a freak i'm not dating i have epilepsy but have haven't had any seizures in
many years okay my picks my friend linda has been making amazing scarries all right linda all words
by tiffany if you want to use or repost art you have to use tim mageddon we no longer associate
so talk to him yourself if you want permission yeah we've been here too okay all right are you
i'm going into tim's domain here tim mageddon the only good community in hypnospace if you know how
to read it minks tim mageddon is proud to present the year 2000 mind crash can she save us aka
marshmallow we work all right any any any discernible thing i didn't know here okay we got
that's a machete she's holding machete in her hand covering her face what is this is that
snowboard skis is it a crowbar oh right just fucking here just fucking eat i'm busy okay
you're good there's no like hidden message here save that poop for later i don't know why that's
making me laugh okay we're we're getting there haven't heard from her in a few days if you know
tiff let me know if she's okay good file sharing zone lots of free music whereas cracks etc
oh so you found our humble home it is i son of tim tim is out planning the apocalypse at the
moment but if you'd leave your name number and a brief message he'd gladly return your call
in hell mr potato head with a mustache and a pig nose making a lot of laughing sounds
anything else here that's kind of scary looking can i click this no all right i think we're going
to go in can she save us no no wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what wait wait hey no no no
no go back wait i have to get the password right it's like probably tippany or something
the code what's the code what was the code it was it's only one goes up if only you'd make
peace with your blessed and pardoned name mother of son of tim dearest chosen one oh okay it's
marshmallow yep why am i shouting because actually it's kind of loud here we go thank you thank you
thank you hey marshmallow i mean tiff it's me tim i'm sorry that this is another one of my weird
things but i didn't know well how else to get you to hear me out i just want to say sorry for
whatever i did to hurt or offend you and i hope we get to talk soon i really miss our conversations
you're really important to me and i don't want to throw what we had away there is no minecraft
just a silly thing to get you to read this page chit chat me and let's work something out
we already read this love tim ps want to move to cyber worlds maybe a hacker good i'm friends
a hacker good i'm friends with found some evidence that hypnosis is really dangerous to your health
so i'm probably going to get off here as long as you come with me dr boulder misses you too
my what's with the weird thing that was knocking on the guy's door okay so i stopped it if you
minks chit chat me disable scary stuff uh well not yet minks go away if you can't figure out
how to access this login link below you definitely don't belong here if you want an account talk to
one of us all decisions are made by committee troubleshooting god damn you guys have long
pages wow wow minks looks all messed up i can't read it don't worry about it you'll never afford
the software anyways jokes on you i got myself a copy all right here we go enter here enter minks
here enter your password i don't i don't know what the fucking password is what's the password
marshmallow no that's not it the password is not going to be one two three four guys i don't have
this password i don't have this all right let's go back and turn off the scary stuff marshmallow
there we go caps lock on all right hey marshmallow disable scary stuff and just
should i report this first well done disabled hypnosis 2.0 okay i did it can i get rid of this
thing though important message received from uh you stopped the mine crash important message
received from dispatch wow germa good job we saw this page but couldn't figure out what the password
sam oh i did it what how do i get installing outlaw package one of two
at least just give me give me my money at least first great job removing that malicious or
unauthorized software it's the anti-virus this is not a virus yeah i can't get out of here
it's taken over my computer delete outlaw oh i don't i died i don't have it where is it
i can't uninstall it yep what do you need no not my pet oh shit he's dying quick buy food for the
hamster quick before he dies i i can't power anything off jesus remove from quarantine all
right i got a virus so am i dead if i die in the game i die in real life am i in the real world
i got beef brain
what happened to late night live commentary what happened to stir
it really is a fire actor so the little teen hacker is going to jail he was hit by multiple
trucks and died okay so the virus killed six people uh years later it was a setup it wasn't
a mine crash virus yeah so what hello german i'm alive left me unplugged for like 20 years
what is wrong with you um keep all new content here do not create new content or manipulate
old hypnosis captures be nice it's an archival project get to know your fellow archival project
team members all about the mine crash and what happened at the end of it all looking back the
end of sleep time the y2000 mine crash was the year 2000 event without it our biggest y2k
problems would have been two malfunctioning bus ticket validation machines in australia
and a couple dozen disappointed end times preachers what's the date oh shit it's today
it's a tent this is actually right now that's pretty cool the mine crash wasn't the fault of
a computer programming oversight or date related bug its cause was an out of control joke virus
created by a teenager in an attempt to impress an exclusive underground hacker group teen hacker
okay creator of mine crash timothy randall stevens the california teen hacker responsible for the
year 2000 mine crash virus that left at least six hypnosis users dead has become the first juvenile
charged in federal court with manslaughter by way of computer hacking stevens who went by the
hypnosis space handled tim mcgeddon will serve up to six years in federal prison for the crime on
december 31st stevens good tim served six years in prison and emerged a changed person he reached
out to me last year about helping with the h.a.p and we're happy to have him he's currently working
on a program to help preserve data from special enforcer headband units huh in tim's words hi
all tim stevens here i hope that after two decades you'll be able to forgive me and understand that
i'm not the person i wasn't he's still alive okay good to know after 20 years uh okay hold on my
actions back then were driven by juvenile insecurities i've had a long time to grapple
with the pain i caused people and make amends with the surviving family members of those who
passed things were difficult after i left prison but i'm happy to say that i've since been blessed
for the wife and a little girl i'm open to talk if anyone has questions the victims oh shit zane's
dead twice tiff tiffany's dead i don't know who the hell this is this person is just a random person
i don't think we even came across this person same with this person i don't think we know any
of these people zane's dead oh may this was the old lady burn rubber 50 carl parker dead
ringleader roddy roddy is dead too oh come on zane was my favorite character what about corey corey
is alive well okay here's the product of recall hold on please discontinue usage of the hypnospace
headband immediately this product carries serious risks and may result in injury or fatality
merchant soft is offering refunds of the product in cooperation with the cpsc product codes the
hypnospace headband manufacturing dates 1998 to 1999 devices recalled in the u.s 64,424
nations oh my fucking god just delete them i don't want you anymore how do i get rid of you you're
ruining every moment that happens on this screen every single one there is no delete tool you just
you just shit and fart and make noises uh the hypnospace headband and accompanying hypnospace
software contain exploits that allow users to manipulate the quality and duration of sleep for
other users five fatalities and 340 injuries have been reported after an incident on the morning of
january first 2000 that's kind of insane tim mcgitton i got this one in tim words
i'll go back here this is everything here who is this t frost here yes the same t frost who
wrote between the angry spaces who the hell are you tomorrow frost you don't have an id this is
the hypnospace archival project profile page of tomorrow frost it is not an original archived
hypnospace page hello everyone i'm uh tomorrow perhaps better known as t frost when chelsea
reached out to me about supporting the h.a.p i literally jumped for joy there was something
special about hypnospace it felt like a livid in place that folks out there trying to preserve its
history inspires me greatly sorry about the old picture did you use a hypnospace in 98.99 it sure
did if so did you do anything embarrassing i'm not so sure it's been ages from my age at the time it
was highly probable young tamara didn't know where to take her life she was an autumn leaf blown
every which way by people in social movements and her own creative whims what are you up to now
i'm a poet for children i wrote a few anthologies that kids your kids have probably seen at their
school library between the angry spaces and river river river river how's chowder man doing okay
interesting uh okay let's see i have tim's page tim stevens profile there he is it is not an
original archive okay thanks for all the warm welcome please read my page before sending me
any messages directly thank you i'm just gonna let it die i'm sorry feels a little strange using
this page builder so many years later but yes hi i'm tim yep the same thing you probably heard
about back in 2000 yes i went to prison and yes i spent the whole six years there i'm much different
now as anyone is after adolescence i did use hyper hypno space in 98 you do anything embarrassing
i'm not really sure how to answer this one embarrassing is not the right word for what i
caused i still think about it every day and i'm deeply deeply sorry for it i was a kid missing
around with tech that i knew almost nothing about my entire world revolved around wooing a girl
i was infatuated with and getting into a hacker group and i would have done anything to impress
either of them i had no idea that i'd even be capable of harming people with the software i'd
made it was all so so stupid i now work in computer security and live a contended contented life with
my wife and daughter okay uh we have chelsea chelsea's page i'm chelsea the h.a.p. co-lead along
with tomorrow sorry about the lack of picture i'll have to get a suitable one uploaded soon i'm chelsea
it's unlikely that anyone remembers me since i never made my own hypnosis page i used chit chat
but hypnosis was a very important part of my life uh this whole project was my idea thankfully
tomorrow was interested enough to help foot the bill i did use it do anything embarrassing nope
if i ever got around to making a page i wouldn't have plenty i'd have plenty to share okay not a
whole lot really just working a boring office job and reminiscing about hypnosis in my off time
can't wait to see what we're able to dig up only a couple more arty arty dispenses profile time
flow flow time steaming gone gone gone gone okay did you use hypno space hypno space did we really
use it or did it use us if so did you do anything embarrassing embarrassment is shame humiliation
is hurt embarrassment is not me not us what are you up to now lover designer giver reader of hope
agent of peace wonderfield spirit is me copy and paste that and put that on your tinder profile
because that's where it belongs okay and a lot this is where we post requests for things
that we're trying to find in the old hypno space backups help us locate them you've laughed at every
fart i have not laughed at every single part absolutely not i got no way can you mute your
mic i have not laughed at every single one you bring me documented proof i did not i i know i
did not bullshit i don't believe it here's where we'll list the things that we believe may exist
only in hypno space and would otherwise be lost to time all you need to do is view the page that
these things exist on and they'll be sent to us and archived okay please do your best to find them
germa as your headband backups may be our last hope okay look the chowder man song okay found
one adrian wanted to know if you dig up a song that the chowder man wrote about his helicopter
accident i got that one yeah this is something i'm missing close friend of mine and famous rap star
remembers putting his music on hypno space when he was in his early 20s but never really getting
any attention all he remembers is that some guy deleted him from a listing saying that his music
wasn't real music because it was flip-flop and that he should do something more imaginative
i found him this would be a huge deal uh roddy's early test pet i'm almost certain that roddy made
an odd looking test pet early in november that looked like that comic book floating eye he
always talked about would love to play with it again weird secret eye cult all kinds of
pages with a strange encryption eye on them if my memory serves i'm pretty sure even adrian
merchant had that symbol somewhere can you find out what that's all about missing person demetri
jackson the daughter and ex-wife of a demetri jackson have contacted us requesting any information
we can find what may have happened to cause his disappearance in 1999 no i'm laughing now because
i'm trying not to laugh because i know that people think i'm laughing at it
all they know is that he was using hypno space frequently at the time and was communicating
frequently with a rich guy who was going to help him fund some sort of sea voyage
what that's me i killed him i what no i didn't i caused him to die no let me check my emails
you found the chowder of antoine yep welcome to the archive project i knew there had to be
someone out there with a working enforce it there is no mail can i just so yeah this is the
i mean if you form a hypno space users formed a ragtag group to preserve content from the
services late 1990 period just before the crash we've been unable to find anyone involved with
merchant soft outside of arty which is a story in itself and we're pretty certain that the backup
servers are long gone after merchant soft got raided you represent the first major breakthrough
we've had towards preserving a piece of history that would otherwise be lost please check out
the lost and found page on our intranet and help us track down a few of those things there
enforcer headband units had an entire gigabyte of internal disk space our best guess is that
enforcer units doubled as many backup servers which conveniently wasn't told to the unpaid
moderators who might have scrapped them for parts we coded a little program to help you
help us extract the data accessible in your headband and upload it to us
download and install the attached program to get started we're all really excited to see what you
dig back up check out the zone we set up if you want to learn about your fellow hp members
okay so here's the program downloading half install
god damn it i'm not i'm gonna make sure i don't laugh again
it's stupid yeah well this is still on the desktop hover over an archive page for details
what in the name of god is this important message received from half underscore tomorrow
team strategy email first of all i wish to warm welcome to our newest members
gerba we couldn't be happier to have you hypnosis archive needs more outside attention if it's
going to survive to put it painfully we need to attract donors my own social reach can only go so
far the kids who read my books don't remember forums let alone hypnospace found the music is
actually one of the strongest stimulators of both memory and emotion today then our goal for the
time being is to track down a few of the music related things on our lost and found page
okay open yeah this is a really neat epilogue service what okay so we got
hypnospace oh that's what is this one thank you for your time we will notify your future hypnospace
citizen feedback department surveys as they occur please close this page
hypnospace guides error okay go back go back to the go back to half no no i don't mind
username jas wilson lopez zone the cafe come to jas's software be for high quality reviews of all
the show the janitor one remember this next oh you just go king oh okay so what are we looking
for i didn't even get an opportunity to not laugh at the last poop all right we need i need to i
really give up the lost and found how the fuck do i even get there archive public unarchived
to like decrypt this shit i want to look at the how do i get back to that page the lost and found
the intranet yeah but how the fuck do i go jump is shift lasso space bar double tap left hour and
right arrow go faster i'm supposed to kill these guys report this game for infringement
let me get this one it's not the right one can i turn the car around no it's not the right one
not the right one will i get data for doing this it says adrian right clear that's not it
that's not it either that's not it different arrow on top see i told you there it is yeah the arrow
was different that's the one do i get data for this i just got them wrong guy what that's the
wanted outlaw wasn't it what was different about that one that's it that's it right there it has
to be yeah i got you what was that see the image oh for the love of god if that wasn't it come on
how many one two that's not right one two splits is that correct got it that's not it
oh how do i get out of this program i gotta get out of it because that's it look at that
what's the difference there is no difference i got the dev all right how is he that bad
i won't go back and you clip that and you tell me that that wasn't the exact image that was just
the top of my screen you tell me that that's not the exact same car you look at it tell me you
tell me all right so uh let's open up the magic eye here let's see curious about something
no don't get this out of here you can take this picture off the desktop fine
the last car you got was red i ain't gonna take that bait i'm not taking the bait okay so
looking for i still have all this shit so am i did i complete the game is this just the epilogue
oh need to preserve not delete
all right let's go clean this up okay here's the network load new capture we only have these
ones so let me just see how long this will take start up here 35 archived so archived
unlisted unarchived archived public these are unlisted pages let's just scroll through
it can't be opened that's fine this one can't be opened and it's broken here
nice chowder man we already have his shit though six to eight hour game yeah we're at seven hours so
it's probably not that much left i just like i'm kind of not understanding exactly what it wants
me to do just go page by page i know it wants me to find that stuff but how do i get to that
the archive project like where is that where's the actual like lost and found i just want to see it
it's in you have to go to the emails downloading half install it's the half install
i already have this don't i yeah but that's this oh all right well that's no that's not it
important message received from half underscore demira there's the internet i got okay strategy
email lost and found page all right come on open it up what you gave me a broken link wrong date
wait hold on a second wrong date
go to today it is what do you mean go to today click 20 xx so okay i'm here now okay i understand
i thought it was like a separate app or something so with i'm i can see this and i can see everything
else in the helmet okay so let's go see what they want how am i gonna first of all this is me don't
i have this email it's not me yeah what if i just open that email uh what did you do you must see
this you missed that one consultation with sherry you solved your first case do i not have it anymore
there it is okay this is what's his name deep into the deep what's the date on this email
this is 1999 1105 uh let's see 1999 see we got a date here this is never this is 1126
so let's see number of fifth 26th quickly changed it yeah i can't go to no look at
so if i start here what date is this 31st okay let's go back what am i a fucking beef brain or
what i'm okay i'm here i'm just why is it november 26th now november 5th here we are okay this is
november 5th this is the capture from november 5th how what how do i do this it doesn't make any
sense which one of these is what date is this what stop opening the map it's the timeline for the
home page press next and previous on the home pages on the pages so let's see okay so here we go
so oh my god i'm so fucking stupid i can't do this
i'm so confused this is november 5th 1999 this is to go to november 26th god okay i'm here i made
it i actually am beef brain well it's guys i think i've opened the way back machine like
three times in my entire life now go forward in time so you're talking about if i press next
right here is what you're talking about this button right here that's not what i'm gonna press
click this button so you go into a page and then you get the capture so it's it's every website
has a snapshot i never i don't i've never used something like this i know what the way back
machine is i've never opened it it wasn't even a scam i win okay anyways let me just take my
brain out and put it in a fucking blender for 30 minutes and put it back in and then piss on it
all right here we go let's go all right expedition is underway thanks to germa you guys thought it
was bullshit i'm in the planning stage of the expedition i found a submarine on acution auction
and i will use the funds from the rich benefactor to secure and repair it here's an image of the
submarine i cannot afford a crew at this time so i'll have to go on this expedition all alone
i'm charting maps and looking for the most likely place of hiding treasures
if i find the treasures i'll bring a crew back to retrieve them and share it with my generous
donators well he didn't make it uh treasure found going back tomorrow i have found treasure i went
on my first trip but could not get my camera to function so no one will believe me and help me
get it i'm gonna go out again tomorrow on a boat and dive for it myself i will post an update soon
i'm so close here is the coordinates in case something happens to me uh it can i like hello
it wasn't a scam it's a 40 point so i have i think i got it right let me write these down
should i just write the coordinates down or does that just now i see them let's see anything else
nothing else the coordinates well that that's it right because i should be able to uh
go to those in real life yeah check the lost and found i'm assuming that it'll be
back to normal there let's go back up oops
okay that's not it the daughter and ex-wife of a demetri jacket of contact is requested any
information we could find on what may have happened to his son is there a done i wonder if there's
a way i can like click on it or something upload it i maybe hold on
use the map i have to upload that to the archive page all right well let me go back to that
let's go to his email so this is this is the december 31st snapshot
so december 31st 1999 open the map and it is which one of these is it this page sucks
there it is help us fund our submarine expedition search tag submarine trip
okay so there it is load new capture no it's just the one right here click it i just did
i mean is there a way i can pull this right click it or something now this is this is just the new
snapshot um is there a way i can like take a picture of this or something
um click it or okay report it we'll go back to the lost and found okay not still there
maybe the coordinates have to be used for something last seen mid-december 1999 that's
this snapshot here no that's it there's no way i can punch in coordinates somewhere right
i'm gonna map or something like that uh let's see lost and found okay all you need to do is
view the page that these things exist on and they'll be sent to us in archive so
i think there's something wrong here refresh the page review it in a different year
maybe there are more pages to find yeah i'll check his uh his other account all right let's
go back to his email all right what about here 202 202 a okay let's try that what about like here
different snapshot there's a button behind the robot now let's just reload and save mode
you have to have the f i didn't have to put it on before no you don't have to put the f on
um maybe you have to do them in order i'll try that
all right i'm gonna turn i gotta turn this off who cares about the super speed get it out of here
disable it get out of here leave me alone so look for lost early song demo of now famous rapper
kev jay a close friend of mine remembers putting his music on hypnospace when he was in his early
20s kev jay some guy deleted him from a listing saying that his music wasn't real music
okay so kev jay somebody deleted his listing so look at the kev jay didn't use any search tags
let's just see what we can find no search but maybe his name anything about kev jay no didn't
use any search tags yeah where were the music reviews there were music reviews on the dumpster
there are music reviews on that that somebody had an entire website about music reviews
the dumpster okay let's go to november 5th okay world's worst showdown the dumpies hold on let's
see here worst website right zane had this chaos awards the dumpies page of the year coca cola
no not this one what about uh world's worst showdown all right here we go hsm is merchant
soft's proprietary sample-based music format hey hold on wait wait kev jay did he make the pizza
song no nothing about kev jay there is there a goal to decay i already sort of did the goal
we're just kind of cleaning up now okay let's check this next day here uh this list is too
popular the freeland they're amazing i went to cool fest i could use the term flip-flop too
here we go slushmouth god kevin jay flip-flop found it
okay
four three people say i'm short but that don't stop me gonna hop on the table gonna move
all right we got this one i'm rosa lita and it's nice to meet you let me tell you about my very
best feature master flip-flop i drop the mic on okay let's go back see if that did it right
do i have to do anything with these music file library
that should be it right
wonderland it's the best of time with the important message yeah i've got you gotta do
them in a row until the very next day got dogs and buds and friends around and gonna rock this
house gonna pound this no way he found kev jay's old song you got it gonna hop on this table gonna
move surround gonna drink this for adorable especially the buffet one i'm rosa lita and
it's nice to meet you let me tell you about my very best feature master flip-flop it's too late
for that it's too late for that all right this next one is uh roddy's early test pet
roddy made an odd looking test pet early in november okay so november 5th that looked
like that comic book floating eye received from ms underscore samantha what is going on here
private i need your help my name is samantha but you know me as chelsea here wait a few seconds
i'll show you you've got him no mail okay see switching back over to the samantha account
i have something very important to tell you please wait for me in the meantime do more archiving or
something i have a lot to say this is the one the lady that sent us cases so let's all right
sounds good so now we're gonna get the test pet early november that looked like the comic book
floating eye he was always talking about so what's the name of this stupid thing important message
received from ms underscore samantha dude what do you want i still need your help what do you
think i'm doing you died it's been 10 seconds once upon a time i was an overworked employee
at merchant soft you can still see my picture on the team page while we scrambled to put together
the hypno os year 2000 update dylan merchant worked on whatever he pleased flissed some weird
big game project i also caught him hanging around in some hacker group a few hours before we went
live with the update a giant software package was uploaded from somewhere else in the building
while everyone was gearing up for the merchant soft new year's party i believe this was a
software patch added to the year 2000 update message received from ms underscore samantha
you are just firing away at the keyboard inserting last minute changes that ultimately caused the y2k
mine crash i believe dylan merchant is responsible for the resulting deaths i believe dylan
knowingly allowed tim a fellow team member you know him as tim mcgeddon to be framed for this
disaster and spend six years of his young life in prison i need your help to prove it details in
coming i need you to find and access files that prove merchant soft knew the year 2000 update
wasn't ready or hypno space knew that their technology could have harmful effects on its
users i do remember dylan having an anxiety attack over a security breach right before y2k
so maybe look underground attached to this email is an installer that will add a submit to sam
button on your hspd enforcement toolbar using the sam hammer will send whatever you select
directly to me without alerting the rest of the hp team if you find this information do you have
any idea what will happen if you find this we can see justice done all without telling a single
you ready let's do this downloading sam hammer so we need to find out that merchant soft knew
the year 2000 update wasn't ready or that knew that their technology could have harmful effects
on its users we're gonna go to tim's website let's install this right now sam hammer all right we've
got tim's uh we got i don't have like files on tim already virus details
no where is it minecraft sure it is there's no minecraft just silly thing i did blah blah
there we go i was using that chit chat spying program to watch merchant soft's internal
conversations i think you were totally right about hypnosis causing your migraines they seem like
they know it's bad for people but don't care all right well let me send this to you uh where's
that program and i just important message received from lord or arty arty uh a suspicious
addition an auspicious i cannot overstate how proud i am to introduce my good friend and former
full-time employer tablo role please dylan merchant is joining our team i'm sure you'll
find him as valuable a source of information an intriguing conversation as i have over the past
two decades uh-oh well hello dylan welcome well we're gonna get you is there a send to sam
button message received from god ah thanks for that warm welcome arty if any of you come across
something that seems like it came from inside merchant soft documents images wip fragments
please contact me before going to the rest of the group i can verify stuff provide context i'm an
open book with a lot of offer what's a lot to offer excited to join this passionate team and
make sure the full legacy of hypnosis is preserved properly sent from my d phone
all right let me i need to sip this water all right so he did it did i not install this shit
because i don't see a thing to upload to sam trash half this garbage on my desktop just getting in
the way you've got him no mail oh my god do they can i please just go what the fuck oh no nothing
like that just checking how things are supposed to work for people like that internally and going
forward from chelsea everybody's fucking emails i have to go okay so let's let's go here i spelled
that so wrong it's okay how am i spelling this it's like it's tim t i t 1 read the rest of the
email you don't have to worry about my authority being leapfrogged already cleared it with me
before bringing dylan on board actually am i speaking to dylan about germa joining and our
new potential to access the merchant soft intranet seem to play a major part in this coming
board that's it if there's any issue at all with anything say a new recruit please let me know
direct messages smoke signals anyone is free to talk to me through whatever they're comfortable
with at any time it's my job to ensure everyone here is safe and comfortable not just funded
okay but i realize already did this somewhat independently can we just bring folks into the
core team anytime we want going forward okay the email before that one look it's just gonna be a
bunch of fucking company to company bullshit all right we already did this one yeah i read that
already yeah we've already seen all this it's getting late it's very late but i'm probably i'm
so close to the end that's gonna scan a couple of fucking pictures and then we'll be done
wait what is happening continue what do you mean continue oh i thought you talked about the emails
it's been a long day i tell you time while i hit the continue button in the email all right we're
gonna go to tim's first ever website i'm just gonna type in tim remove search terms tim what
i think you can just sam hammer the mind whatever 2000 on tim's yeah i thought you could nothing
from tim mcgeddon here nothing was it scrubbed or something i don't think i don't think i have
tim's id i have tiffany's id maybe you should look at that dylan deleted it all what about let
me check let's go to a seven one seven one zero five a anything from okay here's scary
smolder boulder digital parasites my name is tiffany downloading my name is tiffany
downloading okay let's see what these are
oh shit this is fucking chat logs hey hi hey marshmallow everything good
i'm working on something new i just found out how to edit hypnospace zone pages it's so easy
even my grandpa could do it i'm not kidding i took what you said seriously and i'm making something
positive will you help people i mean it still has my signature style and everything but it isn't bad
i think you'll really like it i don't care about getting into minks anymore by the way they're
annoying cool okay so get this what if there is like a year 2000 crash ah everything's on fire
but then you get to be the hero of it and stop it we could even pretend you hacked me or something
to stop it i mean i'm already the villain right and you don't want people to think you're involved
in illegal stuff this way you can be the hero also i promise i won't use any more bright flashing
colors because i know you have epilepsy issues anyway let me know what you think uh well just
don't go overboard i cbi you're cool with it yes our son says mama i'm so glad you've come around
he he he he just kidding okay what the hell all right why would you save this okay i just
made it for proof here's my name is tiffany you explore a virtual mall by clicking spots on a
bird's eye view map you can encounter scaries randomly by clicking on the very section
now you probably see this this is just going to be a scary between me and linda sorry also i will
absolutely not answer any more messages if you call me that name i've told you i don't like it already
okay interesting so tiffany just only has chat logs there the question is i need the teen site
back fuck i gotta go back to like teen topia whatever the hell it's called there's no way she
has anything here still no uh can i report uh maybe that's probably a good idea let's just go
back to her little site here does that give you any info it's about tim mcgeddon wrong
oh fuck i did all right tim mcgeddon beyond twilight tim mcgeddon now this is just his
website i mean i could go to his weird website oh can i no this is just her website i could get his
id 00928a 00928a let's get it all right this is the mother load here
butt disease virus idea marshmallow pick no i already own all these though yeah i have all
these already what's the other thing that's added here nine crash three i3 what's missing
all right here it is let's try this
that's not it doesn't do shit apparently not tim mentioned reading the chat logs and hearing
about how hypno is bad maybe start there uh yeah that was where did i get those chat isn't that
this is it right isn't mine crash dot ht isn't that this is i was hey it's spying on people and
it's causing people that it's bad for people right where's the one where they're talking
about migraines uh can you please do something about these guys they've been messaging me
non-stop i tried sending a message to counselor ronnie and hspd a few days ago but i haven't had
a reply chit chat doesn't reply to me either i'm cori nice to meet you how are you hey tiff what
hobbies do you like it looks like you're busy that's okay we can talk some other time hey i
was working on something nice to meet you glad you're back so we're you were working on something
with tim he does art right very impressive a little crazy sometimes do you mean that tim is
crazy in the way of being dangerous or just crazy in a zany funny way he could be dangerous
just in a funny way okay good will you can never be too safe these days which is why i've been
doing karate every day with a master karate expert you and tim going out hello bwl no sorry about
that tiff so how are you doing must be busy again so let you know people are chit chatting
know if you want to stop a conversation so they don't have to wait for a reply and be bored
sorry if that sounded mean i'm just bored hi tiff i mean this will all do respect but did
your parents teach you manners i'm not being mean just curious jesus is this zane hey hi hello hi
what's up cool hi are you a virgin hello i bet you are i know you're thinking about me excuse me
i'm naked are you what's up never mind you're ugly suck it what the fuck
okay um fuck what do i have dylan's code i'm getting from his website right eight thousand eight
five d okay dm noise pusher oh this is all his bullshit all the music anything else here
no no just report him again
just his music files i can't even do anything i can't even report
headache migraine i spelled migraine right maybe minx let's try it we never got the password for
this shit enter minx here i don't know the password is beef brain um so the minx website
let me just hold on a second here just change it all over the years no and doesn't have i need
that website that tim made what was that website damn it he had a couple of those websites no what
the hell was it zone here it is okay here we go digital parasites read the sad tales all right
enter the mind of tim mageddon here it is the only good community in hypnospace
okay true tranquility let's wait for now in hell egg pull this up let's try the next date
thanksgiving password feast what else thanksgiving password feast downloading thanksgiving
underscore f3 ast cracked programs hacks art viruses in a sort of mischief a hacker group
who should let old tim hang out with them before more of their passwords get leaked
it's probably on here here we go son of tim here my father spent two weeks collecting these passwords
for you ungrateful imbeciles be thankful ps my dad's also preparing a little christmas surprise
underground hacker board dear minx let me post and i won't leak your passwords again
formatting note username password they will change these quickly try them all
there we go so this is how am i going to do this page two chit chat for a hypno os
zane all their passwords mousy man dink dinkerson real chowder man adrian merchant adrian merchant
really pin this window let's try it i can go get chit chat now can i because i'm not an employee
anymore that's probably gonna be the smoking gun all right let's close this this window is pinned
get this back up here let's try these passwords all right let's go with dumpy
be that's not the first one we're gonna go right in the middle jez zero don't care abc
one two three got it i think that i'm in right
what the fuck is all this safe mode activated okay here we go tim and minx i kind of like the guy
like safe mode activated he's got style he can code he's sick of merchant soft's utter
incompetence let's give the guy a chance i mean dylan is here so why not also i'm sick of having
to remind her when to reset their passwords hell no he's like 13 he has skills for a teenager
there he is but i wouldn't trust him not to share too much we wouldn't last another week
if our lame interns found out seriously there's no we
you're the one who shouldn't be here rich boy go back to working on your bad car game
we're gonna get it shit safe mode activated shit was in december too safe mode activated
no it wasn't all right so go back go back back back back back back back back back back back
there's more here safe mode activated there's no we go play your stupid car game and then
safe mode activated he's he's obviously a big fan of your stuff but he's just doing it for attention
there's no meaning almost all of his junk is to show off for that tiff chick it's a high school
mentality half of his greasy pimple friends would be in minx in no time if you invite him so no
no meaning is an interesting critique from the dude who runs the dumpster oh so did you see what
he did to those guys in teen topia that's just as if i've ever seen it small scale sure but
effective okay you guys were right tim just launched a year 2000 mine crash attack code
more gain than an attack really on hypnospace tonight and it's entirely meaningless it's
completely overshadowing my leak and people really need to see this i wish he'd stop it
with the theatrics because this could hurt people if anything happens to my leak i'm putting a backup
on my island in scdfl scdfl that's freelance so that's reckoning inc with a backup in freelance
scd hold on no we're not leaving yet not yet because there's more there's a couple other
threads here safe mode activated stop using hypnospace right now look inside safe mode activated
here we go oh here we go don't use cyber worlds either i won't post it here since the chances are
too high that dylan can find a way to see this but if you have second site search this tag
revelation putting a backup copy on my island same one as the dream tools in gil's dumb area
no one goes there anymore because merchant soft deleted half of their stuff by accident
won't be using my headband again you know where to find me outside of here
ps dylan is out of minks again as of right now some of these screens are very incriminating and
i can't risk him knowing what we know i think this is uh what the hell i can't do the hammer
why safe mode safe mode activated all right so we gotta go get the the leak we're almost there
we're so close you can't ban the past so if you have second site search greater than revelation
okay putting a backup copy on the island same one of the dream tools so we gotta go to
freelance all right so let's first three first thing first let me go back safe mode activated
where is dylan guys please give us a break on new year's eve hold on let's go there's so much data
activated safe mode activated beef brain work you're welcome what's next for what safe mode
activated all right here we go beef brain worked you're welcome what's next for jezzo i've still
got some fresh counselor ronnie stuff coming but that's getting old and i think going too
far with that may be getting into some trouble open eye to spun because we blend in so well there
any ideas maybe something with bible guy or psychedelic hippie drug guy counselor ronnie oh
god i didn't even catch on to that well whatever just don't get too wild beef brain has already
been expensive what with our health experts and all still it makes me laugh knowing how much adrienne
would hate this okay safe mode activated hey ladies new outlaw testing safe mode activated
how about it i've got a new alpha really more verbato with some sweet new stuff and it's still
playing with bots but i'm getting online going in the next week i'm interested if only to see how
unfathomably terrible your code is otherwise i'd like to keep my headband from exploding thanks i
can't like click on that safe mode activated new dumpster trash i hate hypnospace but
safe mode activated sometimes it is great cool fest 99 was better than any of us could have
hoped chowder man losing a leg in a helicopter crash you can't make this stuff up also watching
cool punk implode because of lip syncing has been great so dylan official statement yeah this was
a mess the whole cool punk thing was stupid and we're about to do away with it adrian saw
potential because the gray's peak connection but nah there's no real movement except a few kids
being weird online and gray's peak are done with us here we go he's like the master the master
debater here it's interesting the cool punk is dead guy and father fungus have matching headband
ids same person as far as i can tell he worked with freezer at some point or did music for him
his fungus style music sounds similar also dylan i thought you were the creature brother who didn't
care about money what changed all right here we go i think we got all the info we need safe mode
activated very cool all right here we go get revelation like that right net settler loyalist
saunt hacker resistance leader projects leaky piping crow h stool kit now in freelance okay
where's that site open this thing up
does this mean anything second site three by three hex what else is in here here we go
oh fuck he didn't change it leaky piping hs dream tools now in freelance and then second site three
by three he only put the ability to it's all here leaky piping let's see what that does
and then go to the freelance leaky piping merchant soft's leaky piping oh dear interesting
leaky piping 001 the mystery of the deleted zones oh dear okay here comes the whole thing
this edition of leaky piping merchant soft deletes five thriving hypnospace communities because they're
geeks and losers jump to file downloads oh boy this is it this is the we got it this is the end
leaky piping one the mystery of the deleted zones this is dylan and adrian merchant can we do
something about the geeks you have been putting it off adrian the geeks make up a third of our
citizens and half of the zones and hypnospace city menu we can't just delete their pages what
do you want me to do they are still everywhere when new people come the thing is it's a geek
club the hypnospace is different because it's for mom and dad and grandma and kids not for computer
geeks what the fuck is wrong with this person so that email that i got was real we have five
zones for geek losers and not even one zone for sports it's ridiculous dylan tell me something
today hello i'm back one intern ralph some arcade said to condense the geek zones into one big sci-fi
cybercog comic gaming zone but make it seem like an exciting event probably not a good idea because
of inevitable backlash can you move all their files to the clunker so we can put the stadium
on speedy one so it run fast for the big y2k event oh oh you're gonna have to come you're gonna have
to look at this you're gonna have to look at this oh yeah hey dylan did you have anything to do with
this starport castle dreamville thing this is from roddy oh no roddy i'm so sorry we had a team of
interns trying to solve a problem for us and they chose to put a few zones together on their own
server and i totally forgot your pages were there i should have watched them it's okay but it would
have been nice to know ahead of time is it just my connection or is my page loading slower probably
just hasn't page yeah yeah yeah mirrored text transcripts god damn peeping made possible by
the spy tool jump to file down okay download chat log screenshots downloading leaky piping i zero
one leaky you should take these zero two leaky piping i zero three okay you should take it all
mirror to hone what what are these mirror downloading leaky one one leaky piping i zero two
one leaky piping i zero three one and transcripts downloading lp1 okay yeah fucking take it all
okay got that one take this take them all just read them all
all right so that's leaky piping one let's go back we still have other dates to look at too
mystery deleted zones dylan's bad car game in this edition of leaky piping dylan merchants bad car
game hey i'm working on knocking out bugs now just wanted to let you know that i'm testing outlaw
with a few enforcers tonight i'd really like to get it in by the y2k update okay if you think
you have time not being rude here but i don't think we have time we really need to address
the bugs and only the bugs hmm come on dylan you know we can't finish that thing in time it's
cool but it's not time yet samantha mind your manners dylan is a whiz kid i could finish it
it would be nice if more than one person at this damn company actually understood how huge this
could be i'll finish it myself if i have to do your boring daily grind drone work and i'll do
this myself because i'm apparently the only person with creative vision here wow i'm sorry for
exploding it's just that this has to happen outlaw will outlaw will be released for the new
year's day update it's the only way cyber worlds won't crush us yes it's ambitious but i'm really
just trying to keep us having a job here cyber worlds has good graphics and games it's true
samantha we need to get this on the balls fucking take it all get into all this shit take two of
give me one of these two downloading give me both of them downloading leaky piping
all right leaky piping two done piping two dash zero two leaky dash zero three so that's it here
let's check out the other dates i remember fifth that's okay safe mode safe mode activated
mysteriously this is like a long time ago area what about december december is there a third
one there is there's more shit leaky piping three numb this sounds bad okay hey santa's here
my incredible helper reckoning sent me these new year's eve promises to be very interesting
for merchant soft this sounds bad we should probably stop using hypnosis now here we go
i'm not a medical expert but if i'm reading it right they're basically telling us that
people aren't getting decent sleep while using hypnospace where's three three oh all right
and listen additionally a brief exchange between adrian and arty arty i need help namaste nam to
you too i feel torn apart graze p colico is such a big client but i think they're getting cold feet
any guidance to bring them back cool punk is a big big mess ah peace and be still dear adrian for i
already knew that this pain has been plaguing you you filled your eyes as you spoke at the
investor meeting this very morning you're not centered adrian you're adrian are you still with
me is your quiet corner ready yes i'm at the quiet corner in my mind that i'm in my comfy giraffe
chair very good now chance slowly as we practiced on gum gunna part i a nama i'm gum gumbly numb
yum gumly gumbly nam you know adrian we should do this all right this is who cares about this
just give just take the take the fucking screenshots yeah why would you type that i want
this too downloading leaky piping three take the fucking transcripts i want you to have everything
take the fucking take this too send to the mirrors people made fun of me for that
yes 300 emails all right is the final leak and this is going to be the real evidence to put this
guy away for 100 fucking thousand life sentences no get out of here this sounds bad here we go here
comes the whole thing here comes the big one here we go i'm not a medical expert but people are not
getting decent sleep while using hypnospace lazy bums who stay up late watching tv don't get good
sleep so what's your damn point in hypnospace they can talk to people and learn which helps brains a
lot not my point the doc said that look don't worry about it if people are tired after sleep time
just get on fewer nights per week people are responsible for their own choices too much ice
cream will kill you but no one does studies on that yeah hypnospace is like ice cream it's good
it's we who don't get sleep with these long streams this i know we're late we're late again
very late at night i mean he's beef braining us along with himself it's all right yeah hypnospace
is like ice cream it's good it's fine also it's our study it was privately commissioned by us so
it can just stay private the new pr guy suggested it as a way to deal with the beef brain rumors
we'll find some other way not a big deal good uh the report said that beef brain is fake right
that would be bad for pr if it was real and people's brains did that yuck not good for the evening
news i'm reading the afscar it's lots of big words i'm guessing you're still trying to get
outlaw out in the 2000 update i don't mind this hspd stuff but it wasn't the job i was hired to do
as a matter of fact we're uploading a press preview demo now as long as the team puts in the hours
it'll be there by 2000 for sure surprised yes but more skeptical than surprised dylan i'm begging
you please pause the game right now and get more people on stability i just ran the update last
week and it gave me the worst headache of my life literally this can seriously hurt people
send it all now you're fucked now you're fucked now you're fucked now you're fucked piping four
dash zero now you're fucked leaky piping all right zero two now we're gonna go find the last thing
that's all the leaks wait wait wait wait wait there's another thing here hold on hs toolkit
now in freelance and then second site three by three that was the program so the toolkit is in
freelance so let's go to the freelance what do you say important message received from ms underscore
samantha oh dear god dear god germa you just found the jackpot these conversations are painful to
relive thank the stars we never followed through i'm banning tim oh i'm banning tim if you can
find anything else especially concrete medical evidence send it to me there has to be something
floating around out there in the meantime i'm going to start putting this information together
for the authorities all right let's go get the last piece of the puzzle i can go to bed you can
go to bed too so we're looking for the freelance freelance five e now what the heck did that thing
say some place where they said they didn't go some dump somewhere something like shit something
shitty where important message received from hey there germa i noticed you were racking up violations
on some user you do know there are other ways to get a hypno coin right anyway just thought it was
amusing it's funny that our violation reporting system works without our servers online but hey
just goes to show how good i am at coding also your name sounds so familiar did we use to chit chat
wait a minute samantha is doing the same fucking person i'm sending all the evidence to samantha
and then he's gonna know where it is and he's gonna get rid of it look at this picture okay
i'm going castle is it the castle where was i supposed to go island an island
how many drugs are you on very creative you need to remove the animation of yourself from this plot
also please remake your page because netzilla isn't exposure to this anymore
do you think this is a joke you have one last change to remake your wait a minute
okay kevin the freelance work because people play by the rules
no is this we're never gonna finish the song
what does it say welcome to accelerator island merchant soft clinical leak backup bingo excuse me
this changes everything the final reckoning act one merchant soft commissions hypno space headband
clinical study to silence beef brain rumors merchant soft isn't happy with the findings
and buries them instead commissioning paid tests by independent experts reckoning releases copies
of the damning documents bringing an end to hypno space and merchant soft good riddance click
to download unreleased hypno space clinical study abstract and sleep study samples share
far and wide downloading s zero two two five psg hypno space one s zero two two five psg hypno
space two hypno space clinical abstract i want to see this shit recently a little research has
been conducted on this new range of products the study aims to examine yeah yeah yeah
medical mumbo jumbo the meantime spent in rem sleep during the nights without the hypno space
headband was 22.9 plus or minus five percent similar to data found in literature during the
nights when the patients use the hypno space headband time spent in our m sleep increased
significantly to 49 indicating poor sleep quality in those nights almost all patients experienced
an increase in rem sleep when using the hypno space headband 16 significantly so subjects
reported average to good sleep quality during the nights without the hypno space headband
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah night time use of hypno space increases rem sleep and
decreases both objective and subjective quality of sleep daytime fatigue increased after using
the hypno space headbands in most patients long-term protective studies are necessary
to further determine effects of continued hypno space use until then we recommend discontinuing
or severely limiting the use of this product and this conflict of study was funded by merchants
soft incorporated brain activity look at this look at all these seismographs look at how fucked up
you are when you do this let's check this one this is like a triple earthquake here game over
let's send it and watch the fireworks here you go this is the real one i don't need this anymore
is there anything else external mirror download yeah downloading s zero two two five psg hypno
space one one s zero two two five psg hypno space two one hypno space clinical abstract one all
right waiting for that email important message message look down what do you mean look down
there's nothing here down here we scroll down this as far as i can go what are you talking
about it's eight and a half hours of this you're gonna debate me at the final screen
there we go you got it you are beautiful just a drop dead gorgeous hunk of investigating prowess
did you know that these reports have horrifying implications it seems that people in sleep time
weren't really sleeping much at all surprised more people weren't hurt together with these
chit chat logs you found we have enough to put away dylan merchant for a long time stay tuned
who knows you might hear your name on the news up here soon important message received from dylan
hello samantha what hello samantha switch to the hap intranet capture before viewing this
pretty soon you'll figure out like i did that chelsea is actually samantha former
employee of merchant soft working with germa she's attempting to compile evidence that proves that
merchant soft is guilty of several crimes one of which is knowledge of the inherent dangers
associated with sleep time computing whether she found and submitted these files or not the truth
of this allegation is simple i am responsible for the y2k mine crash attached you'll find a
link to a confession of sorts sorry if this letter sounds a bit formal i've been waiting to write
one like it for a while dreading it actually however i'm not scared anymore i know several
incredible people that i previously did not i finally experienced hypnospace and the beauty
its citizens brought me into the world for myself i'm so so sorry to you tim more than almost more
than anyone send this to whoever you need to or want to i'll be waiting sent from my d phone
i don't know you're gonna the first thing you send me is a virus link
are you serious that's how you open i'm not gonna click that hey open this link i know you got me
oh you dastardly you're very good at what you do it samantha click the link though guy that's hooked
up to the machine that i'm gonna hack give me a fucking break get out of here i'm logging the
fuck off i have anti-virus that's not gonna do shit scan it with my anti-virus that is not a
function island why is everybody saying island island island what the fuck is this should i click
this i don't know what this is i don't want to click this there's nothing here dream tools safe
mode activated downloading hypno s underscore oh fuck here here here take what does that do
do dream tools what does this do these tools are built on merchant soft's internal debug tools
some function identically to their original design some have had a little fun with
deep message me clear debug debug i'm not liable for any unintended consequences of using these
tools do not message me if you encounter issues do not contact merchants off both these tools
for any reason blah blah blah i'm sure you've downloaded hacker apps in the past
get files downloading debug what does a debug do if you can see this file your downloads appear
to be functioning normally if your file manager shows this file it is functional if your hypno
text viewer can open this file it is working if your recycle bin is not full and accepts this
file it's fine if your launcher is not full and accepts this file it's a good boy what the fuck
are you talking about chapter one looming's call me ishmael some years ago nevermind he's
gonna read an entire book having little or no money in my purse and nothing particular to interest
me unsure i thought i would sail about a little and see the watery part of the world it is a way
i have of driving off the spleen and regulating the circulation downloading silence downloading
silence music file added to tune box library
i'm not we're not gonna listen to the whole moby dick thing i can hack help
i'm bringing him back there he is everybody sticker hacks sticker hacks nice cool
desktop oh oh pac-man okay tunes low pitch let's get this let's get some songs on here
what is the song is this playing
this is too slow let's keep it there for the finale all right that was fun
debug installer all right stop this is really important i have to wait for something to happen
here stop what are you doing what the fuck is this doing get out of the way i this is important
i feel like i'm installing roller coaster tycoon 2 again important didn't laugh told you how do i
could get this off stop the recursive installer yeah that's programmer humor in there right kiss
me debug nelson puns go here your launcher is hungry drag some icons into it what oh
here's everything all right just i'm done i'm done where's the final sequence
poo interval i can't do one it's the brown note
okay do i have to click on dylan's email how do i even get back to my email
get how do i go back to where this was desktop no desktop icons right this one okay
shit just log off don't log off click email try logging off finish the lost and fun
no i've done i'm done i can just get out of here right i don't have any more emails
i win okay well dylan merchant san francisco oh switch to the h.a.p. internet capture before
viewing he shit himself to death wonderful wonderful he's not dead he's alive so let's
open up let's go to the intranet thing h.a.p. intranet there we are and we're good to go
okay okay okay all right i'm doing it let's go see you later hi i made hypnosis and i'm the guy who
dreamt it up and program i'm also a game designer composer and sound outlaw jerma samantha and rest
of the hypnosis space carver project team i finished my game click here to install outlaw 1.0
move along the hypnosis highway until you spot an outlaw then apprehend them by positioning
your vehicle behind them and using the laso long be enough to apprehend them you may fly
for a limited time it's not it um i think we just died just send her a virus we're just going to
take the virus and installation complete debug it debug it with it's right because i have this
tool how do i debug installer loading debug two
what are we talking about trying to give you fucking all my money what is this like the
credit sequence pizza bad end who's this who did i get got you who is it zane file trees
zane rocks has ascended oh these are the citizens that died what do you mean they ascended i'm going
to sneeze i'm sorry why are you keeping them here that just gave me a fucking headache again
god damn it no so is this a way of him saying i'm sorry so what is it dark twilight tiff is now
ascend so she said game sucks no it doesn't that's uh rods anti-government yeah these are
these are this is like one or two more people burn rubber has ascended and uh ringleader roddy has
ascended he spent 20 years making this yes he did come here don't kill me what is this is that
dylan dylan has ascended or maybe it's me was i dead i died right that's it okay i get it i
know has let me explain so i died but i died inside of the program and those people were
able to contact me my code brain inside of the program and after the they got what they wanted
they were going to release me close the program no if i close the program it's going to have to
i'm going to redo the whole thing downloading seven files hey look we did it it took us about
nine hours what about in the other time periods oh you did the music too that's cool hey good job
jake seven new files i'll take a look at them read the file reading this was really impressive
yeah it was this is this is really just this you know i would describe this game as neat
just really neat it's excellent work this is a kickstarter game wow that's really neat if it's
a kickstarter game now that's a round of applause because honest to god i don't know if any of the
developers are still here but uh this is one of like six kickstarter games out of four thousand
that either released or were actually fun though i mean that's a pretty big deal there's been like
probably maybe like 12 kickstarter games yeah that's my there you go there's my rating one out
of one out of six out of four thousand oh jeremy that's me no i'm kidding holy shit this is a lot
of people first impressions all right so i think i've had a little bit of time in the game so far
look at all the people that worked on this no never mind these are kickstarter backers
for okay i thought they had more developers than anthem for a second these are all kickstarter
contributors that's a lot of backers no it was good huge game yeah we had 1500 developers
there's a real chowder man music video i'm sure there is well thank you to everybody that stuck
around i know we got late and we moved deep into the night here all right we got a couple
of files to look at i'm just curious what they are i'm gonna read the i'm gonna read i'm gonna
read the files i'm gonna read the files you think i'm just gonna not do it i'm gonna read the files
i'm gonna read those files don't worry come on this is important we had to show the kickstarter
backers and the credits you know where these are these are the people that made the game
i didn't make this oh i did no i did right yeah okay here we are and you can finish up this stuff
if you really wanted to there is still a handful of little things to do i said i'm still not sure
what happened here vinny is playing this right now i think vinny was playing it a couple days
ago wasn't he i'm not sure he finished it maybe he's finishing it tonight all right here we go
download manager new files sit okay here we go navis i'm sorry rodney your family came after
us hard after the crash they disgusted me they smelled like body odor their clothes were stained
stretched out and dirty they wore flip-flops they came all the way to san francisco to our offices
and we sent them away i want you to know that if they're still around i'm going to make it right
i'm sorry this is from ringleader roddy roddy you might not buy this but i considered you my
best friend at the end there who is this who's making these my work consumed me and became me
people who weren't helping me build my masterpiece were invisible through all of it you were always
willing to come back and put up with my garbage and god i wish you hadn't i'm sorry this is dylan
i hope you're with your wife now carl i'm sorry dark twilight tiff tiffany i took your future away
from you your little world's delighted others mine destroyed them i'm sorry and this next one's gonna
i think gonna cause a little bit of a tear up action here i think this next one is gonna start
the waterworks for a lot of us zane you could have become someone your mother was proud of
i'm sorry zane that was a backhanded compliment it's like i got one dollar what am i gonna spend
it on it turns out i didn't even like need these now but even after you're done there's still a
bunch of pages that i didn't really see that i skipped skim through you could probably spend
another there's at least probably another two or three hours of time at least to go through bwl
burst out laughing right play janitor for the next six hours no no no no uh that was a lot of
fun thanks for joining me i'll see you guys tomorrow tomorrow there's one of two options here
either we're gonna do space channel five or or uh then get a new game that came out on steam
that's co-op it's like a co-op story shooter called like was it rico i think it's called
space channel five is only like a couple hours long so i probably i need to put that somewhere
where that is the beginning or the end of the stream i'm actually really happy that i was able
to stay on for this long because before i turned the stream on i was sitting here thinking maybe
i'm not gonna peel the stream from within a couple hours but i feel okay so late tonight i know
thanks there was still a shit little people here all the way into like two three a.m eastern so
appreciate it i'm not gonna do vr for a little while until i'm not sure if anybody
how many of you guys were here at the beginning of the stream but i had a a massive catastrophic
exorcist like migraine there a few days ago and it shut me off for two straight days it fucked me
up bad so i'm kind of taking it easy i'm just happy i was didn't have a problem streaming today
so that means i'll probably be fine tomorrow actual beef brain yeah imagine getting irl beef
brain and then playing this game on accident what did i say blend up my brain and like piss on it
or something something like that well i'll see you tomorrow if you're coming we're going to do the
bits and the credits right at the end here i got a stamp of approval on this game this game was a
lot of fun and they were developers here and that's that's really cool you made an interesting uh
piece here so nice work let's see log off how much in-game time was it uh zero 21a
oh no that's a.m let's close that out and hey what do you know here comes the outro
i don't think we have two this bits aren't gonna take too long i don't think no this should be
maybe like 30 40 minutes all right let's start thank you to bake me home for the 250 get some
rest you little man i will i'll be good to go for tomorrow whatever it may be the space channel or
co-op lazy look thanks for the 250 by reading this message your body agrees to be perfectly
healthy for the next 300 years doctors hate me i wish it were that easy i wish it were that easy
but thank you uh foury thank you foury for the three bucks hey germa i was wondering if you
could do a movie night like star where you watched old videos with chat and gave behind the scenes
perspectives this stream is very relaxed trip down memory lane we've done some stuff like that before
before we sat there and watched random videos not as an entire stream though um
probably not maybe maybe maybe not for an entire stream i could do that for like an hour or so
just old videos that i maybe i'd want to re-watch or haven't seen in a long time
it's an interesting idea though you get carried away yeah you sit there for like six hours
star actually made a new video if you don't know star made a new basically video
just three years later it's just like bang here's another one uh it's pretty funny it's pretty fun
you'd probably like it imagine not uploading the same year as stars i don't have any plans
for any videos it was good but thank you for even three bucks and not immediately hey trust
no one thanks for the 250 hey germa good uh good you're in a better state now but during my long
ride through your archive streams i stumbled upon several occasions of you saying something
particular but most of it turned out to be something different later to be more precise
lies lots of lies i've collected some examples just to reveal the truth to chat i have to bring
this message to the people they must know justice must be served please don't be mad god damn it
you're gonna pull out everything i've ever said that wasn't true this is gonna be embarrassing
let me preface this video just by saying a couple things okay
so i just rifle off shit right and i try i'm trying my best sometimes it's hard to remember
conversations you had six years ago remember i've been i've been broadcasting for three straight
years i had the youtube channel for six years i've made i've been on camera fucking thousands of
times i've talked i've said i've said probably hundreds of millions of sentences i expose me
let's see it i'm ready it's so embarrassing you can talk about you can talk about the book
i know it book is gonna be the first thing weird flex no i'm just saying like it's hard to keep
track sometimes of all the fucking things you say it's gonna be about the book yep what an
embarrassment uh here we go it's germa from germa 95 you watch him oh god i'm a bad boy guys
can i play stardew valley again yeah i when multiplayer comes up with that game i'm going
to fucking play it am i gonna play smash with vinnie fuck yeah if he wants to
when smash comes out i'll play it with anybody actually i am gonna do an asmr stream i'm buying
one of those mr magoo ear headset thing you just wait god this is happening probably sooner than
you think don't you wait you just wait that shit's still my first stream from las vegas
oh it's gonna be fun i'm gonna like pop open champagne and just drink it pop the bottles
we're in vegas i came in on a goddamn hot air balloon promises guys you will ever take my shirt
off champagne than travel in a fucking balloon i'm a local streamer who has gone insane and
left his own stream oh i gotta show this on camera too oh you got me i don't do drugs i am blood
turning a different color i don't know what this one is tastes like trash wow holy shit germa's
tiny oh germa's so small well yeah let's see it let's see you want to go get the tape measure
and show you guys how fucking tall i really am no we're not doing that i'm not big i'm like
fairly small actually please give me more money i'm gonna do all these sponsorships and i'm gonna
shout out all these companies fake news i don't want to be some like fucking poster boy i don't
want to be that guy jet blue what a great airline that is huh where's the best place to get an ice
coffee i happen to think that the jet blue cart service has a fresh brewed coffee uh system in the
back i would put it up there with some of the best i've ever had that's such bullshit that's
that's that's a personal endorsement that's not a sponsorship i didn't get paid to say it
it all wait wait wait wait wait wait i don't want to say this again
as a fresh brewed coffee uh system in the back i would put it up there with some of the best i've
ever had yeah the camera fell over shit based on this dream not a huge hockey fan and not really
a huge american football fan but but what but i was gonna just absolutely i'm not like that
i don't understand what was it
so
what do you think i'm insane you think i'm something really think there's something wrong with me
good let's just help you see to the truth let's see what the auto on its trust
let's see what it is certified judge joe brown gets cussed out guys okay let me be very very clear
here no listen to me listen to me that algorithm makes no sense that is not pulling from my youtube
account as you see looking here i'm not even signed in this is just wherever youtube decides
to take you didn't even mention the book oh my god it's a joke i know cookies oh that was
fucking brilliant that was just that was fucking fantastic thank you for that video trust no one
it was great tell it to the judge thank you again trust no one let's make sure we get a link here
because wow that was good shit that was trust no one again with another fantastic video
moving on here we got slice for five dollars german 9.85 the boomer scout hope you're feeling
better i'm doing okay i'm doing okay peek the mic for old time's sake no keep in mind those
mics were all dog shit that was like a blue snowball microphone that i bought specifically
for that stream i've not done that ever to this microphone i never will and i turned the volume
down it's all right i don't even have to explain myself i'm not a liar uh tar alacran thanks for
the two bucks hey germa speaking of uh uh harassment why do you go into streamers chats
when they are offline and spam germa old don't try to deny it we know it was you what are you
actually talking about these are my most used emotes as you can see the first four are real
and the fifth one germa old i've seen a total of seven times in my chat but for some reason it's
fifteen thousand eight or six hundred eighty seven times where weird for some reason feels
birthday man has been used six thousand nine hundred times pepe d has been used eleven thousand
i know that's big how has that email been used that many times top twitch what website even is
this here here look look and use like germa spam conspiracy no that emote is used almost as often
as lul are you kidding me i don't know if i even believe that i really don't does that happen
that happens that often people do that shit here so often what about other channels that's
like somebody's fucking game in the system here i don't know how that's possible
okay let's have a one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirty four
all right so it just happened 16 times so okay is there a way to pull from this stream
you see the vinnies chat a lot too well number one emote on twitch make a global twitch
you need to go to the stream elements website ah 15 000 times is that per day
oh fucking that's real and fucking cool one of my emails is top five bottom top one thousand
streamer top five emote i'll take it thank you thanks a lot appreciate it oh it's only on that
stream oh never mind so so one of you assholes is like spamming that chat is what i'm taking
taken from us wasn't me well it didn't don't do that it was me well cut it out it's like get
i was like i'm gonna start getting phone calls from the school oh he was spamming the emote
in my classroom and it's like ah god damn it oh what did he do let me see yeah you can do
whatever you want but the emotes that you have paid for but that's kind of fucking hilarious
i thought that was global i was gonna say how is it possible
but somebody just being uh crazy but i thanks for letting me know that that happened i guess
interesting weird but interesting it was a single insane spike yeah but let me just be
clear about something i don't don't like spam somebody's channel you know if you're gonna put
an emote 15 000 times on somebody's channel just being specifically to annoy the streamer i mean
like just just just come on think about it you know i need a global boomer emote i don't think
that's what happened i don't i'm not saying it is but all i need is like somebody coming being like
hey dude like what the fuck are you what what's with you a fucking community what the fuck
and i have to be like i mean i mean uh i mean it's i mean i'm such a millennial holy shit that's
first time i've ever seen that word in this chat but thank you tar olycron thank you future gaming
for the 250 there's a guy who did a challenge to wear a vr headset for an entire week streamed
for 165 hours yeah we we already we saw it we talked about it i cannot believe somebody could
be in there for that long that's just i hope he has a good eye doctor because holy shit that's a
long time i can't imagine sitting in 165 straight hours i mean what that's got to be some guinness
book of world record shit there has to be congratulations but thank you future gamer we
we did talk about it before uh c4g thanks to the 257 germa said gay rights i did yeah well
what's wrong with that when did i say that did i somebody's holding the horn down oh was we
talking about when i was like kissing somebody kissing a male come on yeah you guys just come on
kissing your dad because when you said you kissed a guy yeah i did you you could i told you like
don corleone i talked about it already who don the don what do you know don corleone
let me look it up and make sure i know who i'm talking about don corleone there he is veto corleone
now i'm not going to do it again we're going to move on but thank you to frody weapon 50
dollars from frody and thank you so much thank you that's a lot of money a lot of support oh
casey thanks with 250 space channel 5 vr trailer really oh we're watching this right now on the
internet on your screen right now i gotta see this shit i'm a space channel 5 streamer now
don't you know i'm gonna do them all let's see pegi 16
better not be people to dance i got a funky feeling about this
uh here come the aliens it's time to dance this out here we go
uh oh more aliens
we sure dance circles around the big one close left down here we go dance
cheer cheer thank you lola we did it space channel 5 vr kind of funky news flash okay
okay hold on a second that looks they didn't show any vr space channel 5 vr what platforms is it on
no space channel 5 vr prepares to broadcast onto playstation vr the dancing looks exhausting
okay a little bit i don't what the what platform you just stand in the room where the dancing is
happening and can look around what you're not playing as lola you just understand that sounds
a little stupid i'm not gonna laugh okay that has five good well uh mj won't be back um no
michael michael jackson is probably not back because michael jackson is dead i don't think
that he would have recorded like did he does he did what is he in it he would have had to record
lines before 2009 he's been dead for 12 years yeah i don't think michael jackson's gonna be in this
one i'm very quiet yeah i turned my mic down sorry but anyways uh if it comes out and i'm
gonna play it i'm playing the other one i played the other two well technically uh breeze thanks
for the four dollars breeze hey germa recently my two best friends left and your streams have
helped me cope with the lack of friendship thank you germa fireman germa heart thank you thank you
for the four dollars and i'm really sorry to hear about that two best friends left well don't worry
you'll make new friends you're gonna make some new friends thank you for the four dollars still
going at it no we're just closing up we're just closing up shop here uh hold on let me move this
okay there we go but thank you breeze for the four dollars we also had freudian weapon came in with
two dollars and fifty cents sniper elite vr announcement well that's amazing i can't wait
to play that this game is making me seriously nostalgic of the old days of the internet
when all i was worrying about was message boards for my favorite cartoons the good old days germa
hold yeah good old days of the internet and you would spend 64 minutes downloading a stone cold
stunner compilation that was a minute and 45 seconds long i remember those days i used to
queue up like 10 to 15 wrestling video downloads overnight and wake up in the morning and before
school open them oh yeah i remember when he did the tombstone cool click that one x that one out
oh mankind did the the soccer move nice it took like six to 12 hours to download like 20 to 30
videos now you can just stream netflix you guys don't know how you got it for me to watch like
20 minutes of content it took like a week god but now for real thank you for adding weapon and then
now that was a very good rendition of old websites hey wild fox thanks for the three bucks long time
no bits old man i've said about a thousand times but i really enjoy the fact that you regularly
stream for something like six hours or more and on that note do you ever get sick of streaming
or feel like you just don't want to play anything would you feel like playing a certain game that
you already streamed and don't because of it um no you gotta remember i i don't stream like a lot
of other people stream i stream four days a week sometime you know three or four days a week
i don't go hard every day i don't have the kind of the same game or the same content that i like
to do so i have time to not be streaming you know and have a life outside of streaming and
do other things and see other things and try to work on myself in the quotes right but i
don't ever feel like ah god here we go just gotta get your face on
huh huh huh fuck i don't want to fucking be here hey guys what's up man uh here we go it is time
for stream welcome everybody it's saturday because whenever i stream it's when i want to
and that goes with why did you get rid of the schedule because that's able to happen but i
i had the same exact mindset when i did youtube was i'm gonna do it when i know i want to and
when i know i can when i know that i want to put myself forward and have a level of energy and
know that i want to do something have something i would like to do and if i don't know what i'm
gonna do for a couple days in a row and i spend some time trying to figure that out then i'm not
gonna stream it's been like that since youtube i sometimes i didn't make a video for like five
or six straight days because it was like ah whatever let me figure out what i want to do
and i am forever grateful that there are a shitload of people on the internet that are that are okay
with that and think that that's interesting and like the stuff that's here you know i take that
incredibly seriously i take it very seriously so that long-windedly maybe opened um not opened
maybe that closed that question for you maybe but long story short when you see a stream turn on
it's because i wanted to turn it on and if a stream does not turn on it's because i didn't want to do
it for some reason either i wanted to break i wanted a day off i had something i wanted to do
i had the other year in real life shit i wanted to do so every time you see the stream turn on i
want to fucking be here it's part of the design so thank you so much for the incredibly
uh wonderful continued support and thanks with three bucks thank you fraudy and weapon for the
250 professor helper here need some help germa iq what about the mario tennis stream well the mario
listen i didn't start with mario tennis i started with that shooter we transitioned to mario tennis
because you know i wanted to be there initially for the first like six you know four to six hours
then we had to move on to mario tennis which he didn't like that one so there's your answer
so what you're saying is every stream you start that you want to be here but maybe halfway through
you say i don't want to fucking be here no no it's just it's happened like twice mario tennis
and skate three there's the only two times i've ever been like i i got i want to get out of here
that's it i've streamed i've turned this stream on like 767 times two out of 767
that is very pretty that's pretty good what about evil within two three times okay three three times
out of 767 times that happened so all right you got your third what about carers in you got okay
four yes that's true four out of 767 look i'm just going to round up for you let's just say it was
10 times 767 out of 10 i don't even know what percent i can't even do that math because it's
so small you know you guys understand you got it but thank you i got a clutch for the 20 bucks
i got a clutch appreciate it please watch this video it's like 13 seconds you're going to hate
it because this i don't click links what i don't know what this is somebody kills a soldier i don't
i don't know if i want to click that this might this might be like a monkey s scenario but thank
you thank you for the 20 30 dollars appreciate it thank you thank you mandum requiem for the 25
dollars no message that's it thank you appreciate it 25 bucks from mandum requiem also zaka reito
zaka reito thanks for the 250 professor help are here ready to help what does monka s and sour
please look like see i was just like you i didn't know i had no idea what it looked like and then i
finally downloaded bttv now i can see them all i can see monka s i can see sour please and they're
glorious and he's regretted it ever since no that's not true flank tank thanks for the three
dollars who is your favorite mario party character um i'll probably koopa troopa thank you thank you
alf aleph the librarian thanks for the 250 i'm the librarian what book do you want comics magazines
or books i'm your bookkeeper i'll take the winds of winter by george rr martin please
you can get that to me that would be amazing but thank you also the cremator thanks for the 250
cremator say hey germa so i made so i made a flamethrower with a spray and lighter and
there's something i want to do with it uh well first of all this is uh it's a little extreme
i say don't do any of that shit i would not uh i would not play around with a spray and a lighter
you're gonna get fucking hurt don't do it it's not fun it's not cool don't play around with a
lighter and a spray can that is 100% advice you can take that advice thank you flamethrower by
elon musk those things real thank you dork cube for the 250 uh sorry nia is the girl of my dreams
oh that was the archer right germa lied about minecraft vr five dollars thank you hey good stream
germa hard the only thing it's missing is a good old-fashioned funny scream no i can't scream i'll
give myself a fucking migraine that's how you get a migraine i don't want to see minecraft vr why
not store up power minecraft vr is beef brain god i think i'll be fine though i need to think about
what i'm gonna do with i'm trying to think of like a schedule here because the vr is gonna be let me
see the vr is gonna be interesting because i need to block out because i need to block out the whole
room i want to do like three or four more games let's see when can i actually do this reliably
i'm gonna probably play something else tomorrow or today technically saturday it's probably not
gonna happen till next the end of next week i'll do like another two or three days in a row of vr
this time next week we're gonna beef brain ourselves but thank you germa lied about
minecraft vr i'll be there also thank you unkind for the 10 bucks uh prayers to those that lost
their lives in the mass shooting at the mosques in new zealand it's incredibly upsetting to see
people being brought into mindsets where they think that violence is the only way goes show
there are plenty of crazy way what happened jesus christ oh that's not that's terrible
what oh man 40 people dead holy shit that's fucking horrible
did this just just happen this just happened well that's not good yeah i'm i can't even
i can't even fucking look at this right now it's terrible that's fucking sad and horrible but um
um stay safe everybody stay safe out there that must have just probably just happened so
yeah i'm not even gonna address it but thank you for the 10 bucks unkind
and they say stay safe as well yeah thank you we're gonna move on from that one
i'm gonna move on to e dragon thanks for three bucks i might regret finishing the
stream in the morning but i had a great time hope your migraine doesn't come back i know
painful they can be yeah they can be such a pain it's been seriously so long since i've had one
that was that bad as a couple nights ago kim was lying down next to me and it's i was seriously
like rolling around being like i was like open the window open the window we need to get some air in
here and she's like okay okay okay she opens the window and i'll be okay all right yeah all right
now close the window it's a little too hot in here she's like okay okay and she closes the window
it's very bad she took really good care of me though she's great but thank you e dragon and let's
uh let's grab the credits while we're at it here there were a lot of subs tonight i haven't been
around in a few days looks like a lot of people queued up their subs so thank you everybody for
sharing those let's get them rolling hey look at that here they come all the new subs all the
subs thanks a lot everybody we only have a couple more bits to do uh this is from the jewish bro
for two dollars and 85 cents you should go to the doctor and get a cat scan also can you play
gravity bone in 40 flights of 11 they're fun little short games um i think i've heard gravity
have i heard those words before i feel like i have but i have had a cat scan before i've had a scan
of my brain this was a long time ago but i still had it when i had my first i had a migraine like
10 or 11 years ago that put me in the er and i had a scan it came back negative so maybe i should do
it again i was given an uh imitrex was the prescription i was put on when i needed to use
it but i didn't like using it because i didn't like how it made me feel so i kind of just take
a couple advil when i get a migraine and just power through it but i plan on i have a colonoscopy
coming up because i've had like digestive issues back again too recently so i have a full colonoscopy
plan i'm probably gonna do a full scan of my brain i gotta make you know i'm 30 i pushed over 30
it's time to i gotta be a regular about getting you know appointments and scans and keeping up with
my illnesses and shit recommend you do the same take care of yourselves guys really
you get one body take care of it i'm going down the path of give me a full colonoscopy let's get
it done i get two no you don't but thank you uh dearest bro i have had it before uh hallelu thanks
for the 250 appreciate it hey germa i heard that you weren't feeling well and i drew a little get
well card of sorts hope you get back to feeling 100 soon and enjoy your time off with family
thanks for all the laughs enjoy even on tough days thank you that's incredibly nice thank you
uh hallelu and some art let's see no this is just this is so this is wonderful thank you
take a look get well soon there's shito there's the j this is great so many people are so talented
here just look at the videos and the artwork and the it's is remarkable i'm spoiled by all of you
thank you shito looks adorable yes shito does but thank you hallelu again uh thank you snoozing
copter for the 250 hey germa kind of nice you're still streaming it's 9 a.m here and i gotta go
somewhere to sign stuff for my first job i'm kind of nervous not gonna lie i barely slept
something about the commitment that gives me worries any stories from your first job
here's the best thing about first jobs gives you a lot of good experience when you go to work for
the first time but first of all yeah congratulations hell yeah glad you got a first job that's good
you learn a lot and you'll take that wherever you go so the story of my first job ever um i
don't know if i was particularly nervous as much as i was i wanted to i wanted to do as good as a
job as i possibly could as long as you like you don't want to overwork yourself though
but just you know try to care about what you do people see it people can tell and if you don't
if you don't like what you do and if you're not enjoying it anymore if it's something like you
go to work you don't like it then try to transition to something else deep lore and it can be tough
i worked in i did a lot of substitute teaching i did a lot i know people again i think that's a
meme and it's a joke that was i think that's the only time i was really ever nervous
because i was responsible but on all the jobs i ever had i was never responsible for other people
and then when i started substitute teaching it was like okay now i'm responsible for other people
were you the cool not i was not the cool teacher i've talked about a couple of stories
when i used to sub need more stories about being a teacher i don't really have any
i was just handing out worksheets and making sure nobody did anything bad and you know answering
questions it really wasn't like oh i got some school of rock oh i turned into jack black and
i got a guitar no i i just kind of sat around and made sure people did their work and making the
teacher noise sometimes yeah but congratulations on your job snoozing copter happy to hear it
you get done where you're gonna be just fine you're gonna knock it out of the park
and then finally we had 250 from lazy luke and then 250 from a honey chain
the thought of you in pain makes me sad hope everything works out for you
also i changed my mind i do want to see minecraft vr is germa way lame confirmed um i don't know i
don't think so i mean if you think i'm lame then that's what you think i can't tell you that i
i cannot i can't tell you that i don't agree with you i actually know i don't agree with you
but i can't tell you that what you're saying to me you know just ban them
no i'm kidding don't actually do that that's it i'll see you guys tomorrow
we'll figure something out take care of yourselves uh thought of you in pain makes me sad
look we all go through shit you know don't worry i'm gonna be i'm just fine just the shit that i
am having problems with right now and that's it you just gotta deal with them and try to figure
out how to get through so thank you all so much see you tomorrow see you soon good night and goodbye