Hey, what's going on, everybody? Jerema here with a Shoot Mania Storm gameplay commentary.
If you don't know what Shoot Mania Storm is, this is going to be sort of an introduction to this game.
I'm not going to break this game down to a science, really.
I'm just gonna tell you why it's fun, why I'm having fun with it, why you should potentially check it out, and that sort of thing.
There's a lot to this game, even though it has sort of a disguise of being a very, very simple game, which it is.
This game is one of the easiest games I've probably played in the last couple years, where you just get in, you pick up, you play it, and you know pretty much exactly what's going on.
We'll dive into that, and we'll talk about some other things, but first, I want to apologize if you guys can hear any loud noises in the background during the course of this commentary,
because I'm having tree work done in the right side of my yard, and literally it's happening like right there.
So if you hear like a chainsaw, it's not like Jason coming to get me. It's just like we're having tree work done, and I apologize.
So what is Shoot Mania Storm? Well, first of all, it is a first-person shooter, as you can probably tell.
No view models, though. This game does not have any view models, which is kind of a jarring thing when you first get into it.
I don't know about you guys, but when I play a game, a first-person shooter, having the view model there adds to the realism for me,
able to see the gun animations moving, the traction of the bullets coming out.
I like to have view models, but they are not really required for me to have a good time playing a game.
And I mentioned that this game is incredibly easy to pick up and play, and that's because there's only three weapons in this entire game.
The one you're going to be using the most is sort of this flare gun plasma cannon thing that has four shots and recharges over time.
That's your main weapon you're going to be using. So everybody's on the same playing field.
Not one person has, oh my god, what gun does he have? What weapon does he have?
Does he have like the super strong one that's quick and does more damage, or does he have this like unlockable?
It's none of that. It's just very, very simple, very basic. I shoot you, or you shoot me.
And this very simplistic design philosophy works really, really well.
And it has this Tron-type futuristic laser tag experience, not like any other game I've ever played.
And probably the coolest thing about Shoot Mania is not the different game types, it's not the gameplay, although those things are very cool in itself.
It's the map-making tools. What Nadeo, I think it's Nadeo how it's pronounced, the guys that developed this game,
they're the ones that made Track Mania, and they really want to focus on community involvement in this game.
So all the map-making, all the mod-making tools are built into the engine.
So you can play around and make your own maps and your own mods and stuff very, very easily,
which is a huge two thumbs up to the guys at Nadeo and Ubisoft that are responsible for this game.
One more interesting thing to note about Shoot Mania Storm is the fact that they're trying really, really hard to make this an e-sport.
It's built from the ground up to utilize e-sports, to utilize casting, to have a great spectator mode.
They really want this game to go places in the FPS e-sport community.
And I think it has all the right formula there. I think it's ready to do that,
but it just needs the right amount of people playing and the right support from the community.
Is that going to happen? I don't know.
I don't know if the community is going to take this game in and really want to see it flourish,
or if it's just going to be kind of the flavor of the month for a while.
But hopefully not, because like I've said previously, this game is very fun.
It's an awesome game just to jump in and play with your friends.
Try to cap some flags, try to do the various game modes.
There's the real competitive one.
I'm sure a lot of you guys saw me play the competitive mode.
It's called Elite. At E3, me, Star, and MLC Stealth,
we essentially got in second place to go to E3 and play this game when it was back in Alpha.
And that will go down in history for me as one of the coolest experiences of my entire life.
And that was all thanks to the guys at Nadeo in Ubisoft.
So they get two thumbs up from me. This game is really fun.
If you have the extra cash lying around, it's $20 on the Steam store,
and I highly recommend you check it out.
And if you guys want to see more Shoot Mania content,
whether it be live commentaries of me and friends,
or just another post-com talking about how I'm playing a certain thing,
then please let me know, because I am not against making this a series to play this game.
It just really depends on how you guys judge this content.
Let me know in a comment or a like or whatever you guys want to let me know,
and I'll see you guys all next time.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
Shoot Mania Storm, guys. Go check it out.
Take care, everybody.