All right, I'm not here yet. I'm not I am but uh, you know starting soon screen, you know, the I'm a streamer
But somebody said it was funny somebody said
Omega lull losing viewers
On an offline screen
That's pretty funny
Stream's not even on. Oh, man. Look at those views go down
It's ruined. Yeah, uh, we're gonna do keep talking and nobody explodes
I'm gonna be the diffuser this time
Joel
Like a couple weeks ago two three weeks ago. I was the one reading the manual
Now we're gonna flip it around
Do this for a little bit. See how it takes us
and then
I don't know maybe
What's what else I could be? I have to doing this for a little while. I what else is possible?
Oh like fuck like what else could we do?
I'm gonna have I have a hardcore still alive necromancer. I mean I
I don't know I could be anything
If it's diablo 2 I will puke
Well, I haven't said that yet
We'll see how long this goes
Dead for a year anniversary
Oh, that's right. Yeah, I did die last year at this exact time. Oh, no, no, no, no, no
In like three hours
Three hours from now
Is my one year dead anniversary?
That's weird to say
That's very strange
How does it feel? Um
I don't know. That's interesting
Yeah, i'm going to be the diffuser this time
This is going to go very well
It's this is going to go
Uh people haven't really showed up yet
Caught the stream yet
I feel like this is going to be uh
interesting
Interesting. I miss jermis so much. I'm here for his anniversary
I can still hear you. What? Oh
Super bruce 10 community subs. Thanks bruce
Appreciate it. Thanks for the 10 community subs
10 just dropped right now
Apologize for being late
Sorry, all right
It's not okay
It's all right. It's okay
I think jill should be live now
It's okay. We forgive you
Can you introduce yourself? Hi. I'm jeremy jermo
We also have to do the squad stream so you can see both screens because he's gonna have the manual
Did I invite
Did
Kind of squad up do a q and a all right, let's go q and a right now
I will answer questions until jill comes in the call
All right, let's go. What is it?
Fun and ask me anyway
Why am I streaming because uh, it's fun
Am I gonna play halo over again? Uh, I don't know
When are you going to play tribes ascend? That's a great question
Do I like shrek? Yeah
How many teeth do I have?
30 teeth
What else?
Have I eaten a vegetable today? No, I haven't
You know do diablo 2 later
I don't think so
My I might I don't know. It depends how long this goes
favorite video game song
Beware the forest mushrooms
You have too many teeth
I feel like what is it 30 32? Whatever it is 31. What does kim do for work? Uh, she's a butcher
Do I have extra teeth?
That's sick
All right. Let's see if he's around
You're good. Hopefully he can still see the screen
I'm gonna come calling him right now
See if he picks up
Let's see if he picks up the phone
Hello
Is anybody there?
You've been earning your germa coins. Well, the webcam will be on for a lot of the stream. So i'll be able to wink at you
He ignored the questions about nancy drew
Well, what do you what do you want me to say?
What yes, I will go back to nancy drew eventually
It's probably not today
Same shirt as yesterday. That's the shirt yesterday was green. This this is blue
This is a blue shirt
I don't I don't think the yesterday's shirt was green
Somebody's linked that person to clip please
Hey
That just actually scared the shit out of me. Hey
It was just like how you doing?
i'm doing good you're ready to uh
Ready to defuse some bombs i'm ready to defuse some bombs
Okay, so I was just I was just giving the uh the intro spiel here at the start, but I said this before
um
Uh, you know last time we did this
it was uh, it was a bit of a bit of a challenge because uh, we never played this game before and uh,
Uh, we quickly realized that reading instructions while also timed on it and having people uh,
You know tell you what to do. Uh
It can be quite quite the challenge. It's tricky. It's tricky. Yeah, absolutely
Did you squad up I sent you? Oh, I gotta squad up. Hang on. Hang on
I'm gonna squad up people can see both screens
There we go. All right. So um, big big question before we do this before we do this. All right first bomb. Let's go
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I'm just kidding. Um
I was gonna say um, this is more from my chat really, but would you guys prefer that? Um
I put up the I put up the the manual on screen or uh,
Just again, because I I i'm gonna be reading the manual on my phone. Yes
Oh, you're gonna wait you're reading on your you're reading it on your phone
Yeah, because I I thought like well, I don't really have a piece of paper. This is the closest thing
You know who reads these days. That's gonna be so small. You're gonna be like scrolling through you're gonna do a microscope
We got one white wire two white wires. Let's listen big letters scare me. All right
Um, so the finer the better, you know, um, that's you're gonna have trouble reading that shit
I'm gonna it's gonna be no, I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna pull up a pdf. I
You um, do you want what do you want? Do you want to start easy? Because this is the first time you've read right?
Uh, this is the first time i've read. Yes. Okay, so we'll start easy. We'll start easy. All right, really easy
Yeah, so let me let me know when you're ready because i'll have i'll have an easy one ready for you
Okay, uh, I swear to god if you pull up some like gigantic bomb
With like every model on the planet. No, no i'm gonna make it very easy for you
Because let me know when you're ready to have a fairly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Are you ready something?
No, not yet. Not yet. I'm trying to like, uh, trying to see what I can do here
So you know on your stream to like make sure?
Yeah, i'll tell you i'll tell you man. I'll tell you don't look at my stream. That's cheating
I'm not doing that. I'm getting the fucking manual up man. Don't chill out chill out, man
Okay, uh
Well, i'll tell you what i'll tell you what um, i'm just gonna
game capture your screen
Oh and uh for their enjoyment
Because i'm gonna be reading this on my phone. I know that's not the best way of doing this
You're gonna turn you're gonna turn around
Honesty policy don't you know if you have an honesty policy on halloween if you have like the treats and the honesty policy
Bucket people just take the whole thing
You you you bostonians man, what the fuck on halloween if you have like a hair
Please take one and it's a bit thick full of candy that thing's gone in 10 minutes
Well well
Can we trust you so so?
Yeah, you can trust me man. I can trust you
All right. Yeah, okay. Um
Let's see here
I think
i'm almost ready here and uh
na manners
What what's like what's like boston famous for it's like rocky or whatever the
the founding of the country
the founding of the united states of america
Yeah, but like you know important things like, you know hot dog inventions. Oh, well fucking pizza, you know
The north has got the best pizza in the country number seven
What is your favorite topping? Sorry. I'm just making small talk while i'm trying to get this fucking manual up
pepperoni
americans
You guys I heard that you guys don't do ham on pizza. Yeah. Yes, we do
You do? Okay, because they've been telling me otherwise man
No, no this ham on pizza
Pineapple and ham is like one of the most popular pizzas in the country
Is pineapple popular for you germa?
Don't bring fucking we can't talk about this
Okay, good because I was gonna end the fucking call. Anyway, uh
so, uh
I think I think i'm pretty much ready, man. All right. All right, cool. So um
So you got the manual ready? It's being it's we got all right. I'll start one
Just click the button there to get started
Okay. All right. So screens black we've uh, what screens black?
Uh the game capture thing you're wait, you can't see anything
Well, you shouldn't be able to see anything
All right, so we got uh, I i'm not saying i'm looking at the fucking screen. Hey, hey, hey, hey
Don't don't make this a bad thing. I'm saying if this was actually a bomb to defuse and this was the conversation happening
Hey, so what what kind of what pizza toppings do you like?
Okay. Okay. Listen, listen, whatever. Well the point here. Let's stop jerking around
On screen i'm saying I have the game capture your thing for their enjoyment. I'm not saying
All right. So so can you can you can you all right? Can you see the screen like just you?
Uh, can you see it? I I can I can see the mouse moving around but I cannot see anything
You can't see anything. It's just what's this black screen for you. Yes. Yes, but I see the mouse
I tried
I tried with the info that I had
So you wait, you can't so you can't see anything
No, no, no, no. No, if you check my stream, you'll see what my problem is. Let me see
Let me see what your problem is. Let me see what it is
Let me see what's going on people are people are talking about squad streaming here and it's not working out. I think hold on
Squad stream did that work?
We should be it should be working. Uh
No, it's still still uh, it says we're in it. It says in a squad with barg skelethor
Oh, that is working on twitch. Oh my god. This is like more more hard and actual disusing a bomb. Uh
Okay, all right, yes that all that was working but the the screen that i'm looking at right now
I only see a mouse and nothing else really
Yeah, can you do window capture? Uh, no, no, no, no like, um, I see like the overlay of steam and everything
But there's like nothing on the screen. Tell what do you want to like just um
What do you call it? Um, re-invite me to a new game perhaps. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, let's try that
Okay
Oh, I see I see what you're talking about. Yeah, that's fucked up. All right. Let me re-invite you. Yeah
And you thought you thought I was doing some sort of joke, huh?
No, I thought I thought you I thought you were memeing on me
No, what I thought you were memeing on me
Well, I never do that
What did you did you leave that uh that little group there?
Uh, yeah, yeah, you re-invite me
You should get the now
Yes, now we're talking. All right. Can we see now? It's starting up
Starting up
Yep. Let's see here. Let's just pre-position this window because it's so ginormous on my end. I mean
okay, so so
Make sure to disable the uh
Uh my mouse interaction so it doesn't fuck up. Yeah. Yeah, I got it. I disabled you
Okay
And I think that's a bit you guys see this everything fine
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Are we good? So we've just had to refresh it
All right at the same time we're gonna say fuck yeah, and that means like that like we're ready to go ready
Uh, yep. One two three
Fuck. Yeah. Fuck. Yeah. Nice
All right. We go. We're ready. We're ready for the first bomb. We'll do the first bomb
Okay
Do you have your manual? Are you ready to give me instructions?
Uh, I I have i'm out of the only problem now is that I don't think I can hear the fucking my god. Hang on
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. This is totally on me
I don't know why all these technical issues crop up when I'm where we want to play a game and I fall
Don't worry. Don't worry. We just fixed it. We just fixed it. I've brought a gift sire
For the king. It's this key. Are you good? Yeah, I gotta ask you when you do that voice
Why did you play lord of the rings for like 16 hours?
Because I had to beat it. I had to beat it
All right, you ready? What's chat? What's what's do chat doing a challenge or whatever? Yeah. Yeah
All right
No, I had I had to beat it because I had to do the gamer challenge you to beat the lord of the rings two towers in
One go. All right. Are you i'm ready? All right. Are you ready? Yes. Yes, i'm ready here
Okay
It's three modules
Oh, it's okay. I gotta remember I gotta okay
Uh, oh we've got wires. There are one there are okay. There are six wires
There are six wires. Is there any yellow wires? Yes, there are two yellow wires two yellow wires
Three red wires and one white wire
If there are no yellow wires in the last date of the serial numbers odd
They are yellow wires. Otherwise, if there's exactly one yellow wire, no, that's not true either
Are there any red wires? Yes, there are three red wires cut the fourth wire fourth wire
Yes, incorrect
Oh, no, it wasn't
Uh, all right. Yeah. No, no, we're good moving on to symbols. Okay, let's move on. Let's move on. All right
symbols the the symbols with like the
Omega symbol thing that I couldn't do. Okay. Okay. Okay. Just just just tell me how they mirrored k mirrored k. Okay
Uh three that somebody fell asleep in the middle of doing like a three that they they fucked up at the end
Okay, um a
uh
a um
the a big a bum a big a bum with like a
comma at the top
Does it look like a like a bum scrote?
Yes. Okay a ball sack
Okay, i'm on board now
Okay, uh, and then the last one is is a uh looks almost like the like a currency symbol
It's like a uh, it's like a uh, it's it's like a currency symbol
It's like a upside down v
It's like a
It's got like a line at the top
It's like a triangle triangle triangle with like a little thing on top
Triangle with a little okay. Okay
It looks like a we like a currency
It's a triangle. It's got like a little tail through on the right side. It's like a triangle without a bottom
It's just like upside down. It's like upside down v
Are you talking about the lambda symbol?
Yes
All right. Um
Well, uh, you will be going, uh
ball sack
Good weird x
Okay, he fell asleep on the three
Okay
And dumb fuck has never played half life. All right. Yeah dumb. Fuck. Oh my god. It's the half life symbol
Okay, we got a button. So we have a button. I just it's a it is a blue button
Are you sure there's nothing on the back there? Okay, there's nothing on the back, but there is a there's a serial number here
Okay, let's not worry about that. Let's let's let's get to the point here. Okay. What color is the button?
The button is blue and it says press
That's a blue button that says press
How many batteries do we have? We have any batteries?
There are no there are one battery
There's one battery. There's one battery
There are three batteries
The three. Okay
And the bottom said set abort
Uh, the button says press
Okay, uh
Three batteries the button says press and it is blue. Does it say frk somewhere on the bomb?
Uh, does it say it says there's frq on the bottom
There is no it says frk. No, there's no frk
Just just hold down the button. Just hold on the button for me. Hold the button down. Okay
What button what color it's just blue and there's a thing on the right that's blinking just blue blink
Okay, release it when it says four four in any position we did
There was a four at the beginning
All right, good. I can't believe I didn't do the half-life thing. I can't believe it. I sat there for so long
I cannot fucking believe it. See it's it's it's we learn we learn through
Uh, we're learning we're learning about things, you know, i'm learning about
Bostonians and you're learning about half-life. I can't believe it. That's worse than omega
I just don't I just get locked out. I get locked out of my own brain. All right
All right, we're doing we're doing it. We'll keep we'll go we'll go from here. We're gonna do w money
All right this left. Okay. Mm-hmm. Okay, that sounds good half-life symbol. What an embarrassment
All right, double your money. You're ready to go. Just keep it rolling. I'm ready to go man. I'm ready to go
All right, i'm gonna be ready this time. No, i'm not gonna i'm gonna do this lightning in
all right
You can do this, man
You have to we have to trust each other and we i'm i'm not gonna do any
Bullshit because that leaves explosions. We have to do this. Here we go three wires
There is three wires. All right, one yellow one blue one red yellow blue red. That's it
So the the we do have a red buyer. Uh, there's one red is the last wire white
The last wire is red cut the last wire good symbols
Omega symbol looking at omega symbol ae. Yes. Okay
Uh, somebody had stitches everybody had stitches and they have a cut. It's like a frankenstein stitches and then a um
Like a h but the line is going from top right to bottom left. It's like it's like an h
Gotcha. Gotcha. Uh, we will be looking at uh stitches ae weird as h omega
Okay, now we have we have two buttons. There are two blue buttons. They both are the same exact button
It's a blue button that says press both of them are the same two blue buttons that say press
Gotcha. Gotcha
There's going to be some things that factor into this though
So we've got to be careful, but i'm gonna look through the manual here and see what we can deduct from this
um
How many batteries do we have on this bomb? There are
One there is one battery on this bomb only one only one bomb
Okay
Um, and the it said press on it. Yeah, both buttons say press. They're both blue. Okay
Okay, here we go. We're gonna be holding this down. Okay, hold the button down. Mm-hmm. Okay. I have a red
Blink it's blinking red. It's one in any position one in any position one in any position. Okay, you got it
Yes, I have to wait because I have to wait until it gets to a one. Okay. What about the second button?
If this yeah, it doesn't completely duplicate do the same procedure. Okay red again
Is this one in any position one in any position? Okay. All right, wait 10 seconds. I hope I hope I did this right
What's your favorite piece?
All right now
We have there. Okay. We got we got more symbols
Okay, okay. That's fine. That's fine. We can do symbols. Okay, we've got uh backwards p smiley face of the tongue sticking out
Uh upside the t the t up tb thing and then a trident. Okay
Uh tv thing tv thing smiley face trident tb and backwards tb, okay in that order
No, no, no, no, no. No. Okay. Uh, the order will be
Uh trident. Yep. Mr. Smiley. Yep
Uh weird tb weird tb got it. Yes, and then yes the last one. Okay, cool final module. We have plenty of time
So don't worry. Just relax. Okay. Okay. It's another wire module
We have one two, three four. There are five wires
Two of those wires are yellow
Two of those wires are red. One of them is white two yellow
Two red one white there are five of them
Um, is there any black wires here? There are no black wires and we have a total of five here
There are five wires two yellow two red one white cut the first wire
That was incorrect. Um, we're even them real quick again. I got really stressed. I'm sorry. All right, two yellow two red
One white there are five two yellow wires there are two red wires one white wire
That's it cut the second wire my bad my bad. We got it. Look at that
I I started freaking out like here come here comes the
The the the bomb demons in my head like come on dude. Just tell them anyway. I'm like no we have to commit to this
All right. I I think we're doing all right. We're doing all right. We're doing all right
But that's because I disciplined myself before the stream and I said, okay, maybe maybe I shouldn't be devolving the streaming too. It's like, uh,
Making fun of uh, jerma's lack of Greek symbols for like three hours. So
Well, we didn't know what we were doing last time. All right last you gotta give us some credit
The last time we played this that was the first time we've ever even seen the manual
And the first we didn't know how the game even worked. We had two
Be honest, we probably put both the stream for 10 fucking years now. Do we know what we're doing still? No next level
All right, this one how did it take us this long to do this last time?
Here we go. I think it was because I was screaming and uh, we had some issues
But anyway, um, let's go man. This one we gotta be careful. This one is three minutes
All right, but that that as long as we coordinated and we're not
Screaming. All right, relax. Just relax. We're just having a good time here. Relax. Relax. It's just a bomb
And you know 3 000 people screaming at you. It's okay. It's fine. Are you ready? I'm ready
We have
Uh, I believe this is simon says with colors. Okay, that's fine. That's fun. We have red it blinked red
Okay, read me the whatever. Let's let's do simon says first. All right, i've never
Okay, so, um, what are we looking at here? We're looking at it's uh, it's red
Red is the first one it blinked red before we do this. We need to check if there's a vowel on the bomb
Okay vowel on the bomb you got it. Uh, there is not wait vowel on the serial number or just on the bomb in general
Uh the the serial yes
Okay, there is not a vowel on this bomb. Let's go back to simon says, okay. Okay red, uh
You're gonna go blue red
Green blue green red green green blue green green
Red green green red blue green green red. Sorry. Sorry blue green green blue. Sorry. Jesus. Okay
Red green green red blue blue green green
Blue yellow, was it red green green red blue red green green red blue
So red green green red blue then you'd be looking at no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I was I was like reading that
Okay, let's stop freaking out. Okay. Hang on. You'll be looking at blue green green blue yellow that solution. What's happening?
blue
Oh my god, germa. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I just realized something if we get a strike on the simon
That means the equation is totally different so
I'm sorry. This is the first time i'm fucking reading. Okay
We're going we're going we're going we're going
Okay, look learning process learning process. My bad. That was totally on me. It gets tricky. It gets hard. Okay
Here we go. Ready? Okay. This time it's it's a little different this time. We have okay
A okay, it's the number four. It's the screen with it's a screen of the number and then four numbers underneath
Okay, so uh
Okay, it's the it's basically memory essentially, yeah, yes, it's a memory game and then you have to do this five times
I remember this one
All right. So when I did this I had a lot of problem. Yeah, it's your turn now. Ready?
All right inside the screen is the number four press the button in the fourth position
The number is now one press the button labeled for labeled for
One again press the button with the same label is just pressed in stage two the same label in stage two
Mm-hmm that was same label instead same label. Okay, that was four
Now the number is three press the button in the same position as it pressed in stage two
four, okay
finally four
Press the button with the same label as it pressed in stage three. It was also four
Done. Good. Okay. Awesome. Now we've got we have got a it's the word
It's there's a word in the box and then the six other words. So the word is red
Okay, hang on this car contraption is something like out of a sketch comedy routine
I'll tell them about it, which might be funny if you weren't connected to a bomb
I'll keep this brief
Okay
So read the display in a step one to determine which button label to read using the button label you step you step two
Determine which button to push repeat until the model has been disarmed. Okay, so what?
Word do we have in the thing? The word is
red
Inside of the box the word it's the word reading what is on in the middle button to the right middle to the right
The word is right. Okay, right. Let me see here. Uh, uh
Okay, i'm gonna spout i'm gonna spout these out and you just until you see some okay. So here we go. Yes
Nothing ready press
I see ready ready is on here. It's the bottom right slot first one ready. Okay, Joel
I don't want to alarm you but all right, uh, the word is no. Okay. What does it say?
Uh, you are next uh, uh sure done hold no, no, no, no, give me the word. Give me the word
Word is no the word is no
Okay, uh
Blank, uh three letters, uh
Wait, uh, uh, what this word y'all get down fuck that
Okay. Well, uh now we deducted how we should do simon sess and we do that quickly
We're quickly learning now that uh, you know with this reading thing. Don't worry. Don't worry. These are growing steps
We did great at the first tier. Let's just let's just keep going and hammer this in and eventually we'll be
Experts, but i'm just telling you something it's gonna be next bomb. We're gonna actually be treating as we'll die. Yes
Next one is so serious. Yeah, we will actually be dying. Okay, i'm gonna take this as if we were gonna die
We are going to die in there. Okay
All right
Like your life we are going to die
Okay
Okay, let's go
Here we go for treat this like it was real
Yes
Okay. Okay. Um
Uh yellow yellow on the Simon says thing. We're three minutes. No, no, no. Okay. Simon says
Okay. Okay. Hang on. So uh yellow yellow yellow yellow
Do cost call please call somebody
Call somebody
Yellow, okay. Let's let's not go. Okay. Whatever. Whatever. Just read me the fucking serial on the thing. Uh,
Do we have a vowel on the serial? Okay. Do we have a vowel?
There is there
Yes, there is a vowel
Okay, uh
Tell me what the first flash is yellow
Green good yellow yellow green green. Tell me tell me what it's flashing
yellow yellow red
green green blue
yellow yellow red blue
Green green blue red
one more
yellow yellow red blue yellow
green green blue red green
Okay, uh, it's uh, we have three wires
Okay, we have three wires. We have three wires. It's two yellow one blue the two yellow wires are on top of the blue wire
Which is below
Cut the second wire
Okay
All right. Now we just have one more thing to do. It is the box with the word in it
It says hold on. What does it say?
Okay, uh
Okay, read me read me
The bottom right bottom right middle blank ready blank is here. My blank is here. Okay. Okay blank next one
The next word is lead read me bottom right
Uh-huh. Um
Uh-huh. Your as in possessive your is on this list top left. Okay
Wait, wait, you are you are like you are possessive possessive as in like your pizza your pizza
I pressed it. Oh
Uh, next one was it you are pizza. All right, you're you're you are you're you're you're you are you are you are you are you are
You are top top left top left what?
No, no, no, no, you have to read me that. Oh my god. We're dead. We're dead
Mom, I was gonna say I was I was I was
Honestly, don't don't worry about it because now
That simon says thing was fine
we're quickly learning that the uh
The it's called who's on first that one is a little difficult for us
It is because we have to be very specific because i'm noticing a lot like here's the thing
That's very important about this some of these you are there's three variations on you are there's you are without you space are
You know, whatever, uh
There's possessive
Like your pizza. Yeah, why oh you are right? Why oh you are and then there's there then there is
You are a pizza as in you apostrophe re, you know
Oh shit
Okay
All right. So i'm gonna start saying apostrophe i'm gonna say possessive apostrophe or space on the you and there's also this different variations on
Right. There's not just uh, there's uh, yeah and okay h h h so there's gonna be a lot of
Specifics here and we have to be super fucking like talking about this
So, uh, this is this is very bad for me because not i'm not an english speaker. You know, I don't speak english
Yeah
Neither do I so uh
well
We're just gonna have to do the best. All right, but here's the thing. Here's the thing
coordination
Let's not screw it any every second special for us is vital. So now
The problem was and all right
I burnt like 20 seconds during the simon says because I tried to do it too fast
You can't do okay
For instance, it was like it was like green red red and you were like, oh blue like yellow yellow
And I did blue yellow yellow, but it doesn't register. You have to go slow. Okay. Okay. No, I get it
It's stressful. It's stressful. But but uh, we can do this. We can do this. Okay. I'm ready
You ready? Okay. Here we go. Yes. I'm ready
free wires
Blue red three wires blue red blue in that order
uh the
Okay, hang on. Uh
Uh, there's three wires, uh blue red blue in that order. Is there more than one two?
Okay, so uh, cut the last cut the last blue wire
Okay
Uh, it's the word game thing again the word it's lead l e e d
Bring me the bottom left one. The bottom left word is ready
Okay, i'm gonna spout the words. Yes
Okay, four letters what?
Middle what is on here? What is on the bottom right press that one press that one
Okay, next word coming up. The next word is
I don't there's no word. There's nothing there's no word
Okay, uh, read me the bottom left one
Your y-o-u-r as in
Your friend your friend. Okay, your friend germa
Okay, okay
Uh-huh four letters as in uh-uh with a space. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. You are with a space. Yes
Okay, there is uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh. Go go go. Yes. Go with that. I'm gonna have one
Coming up next we have
Your like you are
Your middle right middle right middle right first
Left. Okay, four letter four letters. Yes middle. No middle right
Yes, press that one done one more of these the word is lead again l e e d
Bottom left. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh space, huh?
Uh-huh. Okay. Uh, okay got it
Same word. Uh-huh. Your as in possessive with just one or you just like like you like your friend germa
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I pressed it. Oh, I fucked up. Sorry. Just keep on keep on going. Okay. Hold on. The word is hold on
Okay, uh
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Okay bottom right bottom right. Sure
S u r e i'm sure of it you are as in a space you are like you are yes, that's here top right. Yes
No, no, no. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes
Okay, next word coming up
Next word is you space are you are
Bottom right bottom right done. That's what we'll be soon like, uh, sure. Uh-huh with a space in between
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay last word. We have 10 seconds. Okay. Last word is okay
Okay, ay spell the whole thing up, uh top right top right. No
Was that the word or was that you screaming in fear that was the word no
I thought it was like, huh?
Can't we save this or is jerma shitting his pantalonies? Oh
We this game's fun. This is fun. We we what we managed to do though. Simon says is on the lockdown right?
Okay, and we're getting better at
who's on first, but the thing is
That time is really really like close
Uh, so I think if we're not getting fucked up by uh, two of those I think we can do this
But it's a little bit the random chance of yeah, but I think we're doing great. I mean, yes
We are dying here, but honestly
Let's be honest here. I think we're doing just a little bit better than last time. Yeah, we are
All right. Well, uh try this one more time. This is fucking wild. All right. I'm ready. You ready?
Yes, here we go. Uh Simon says it Simon says okay. Hang on. Okay. So check the serial
Do we have a vowel or do we do not have a vowel? There is
There's a vowel on the serial number. We have a vowel. Oh, okay. We have a vowel
All right. So what's the spotting our color blue red blue green?
Red yellow blue green red
Red yellow blue blue green red yellow red yellow blue green
Okay, we have a word game the word is display
Like a display like your monitor like a display like it'll put me when I fuck this up on anyway, so bottom right
Nothing. Okay. Uh, we got uh, three h's
Right. That's here. Okay. Okay. Yes three h's. Okay. What up next? The word is first spelled out completely
F-i-r-s-t top right top read me top right right
Yes
Nothing. Yes is on here ready. Press that final word coming up. The word is you
Y-o-u like you did that middle right what with a with a question mark what?
Okay, um, okay. Okay. Here we go. Uh, you ready? Uh,
As in three h's uh h h h what left?
Nothing ready. What what is on here? But it's what with a with a question mark? Uh, say them all again. Okay, uh,
Okay, uh god
Three h's what left nothing ready
Blank middle no
Okay
So it has to be what it's it's what is it is it what first one first one? No, that's not right
I we have uh, we have another one. Don't worry. What is red? Okay red
Okay, uh middle right middle right middle right word is okay spelled out completely. Okay. Ay, okay
Middle no
First yes. Yes is on here. Okay. We got one more yellow button. It just says press on it yellow button press
Just hold it down. Just hold it down. Okay, it's flashing yellow five and in position. We did it. We did it
We did it. That was good. My soul escaped my butthole. I was my heart was fucking beating on my chest
So what what happened to chimo man? Oh nice bomb defusing 101. We we passed the tutorial
All right, well that proves that we can do this. I think honestly this sounds ironic, but I think me being an idiot
I'm actually reading better than actually playing
I think we found our groove
Yeah, I think so which will shake up later on the string mind you so
That's gonna be fun
Okay
This one. Okay. Now they're getting harder
Okay, this one is called a hidden message
Oh, yeah, this is now moderate difficulty
Okay, we do have five minutes
Information can be obscured in ways that are time consuming to decode in the world of bomb defusing. That's a bad thing
Information can possibly mean it's weird with five minutes
Okay, but that's fine. Listen, the last one was so hard because we were at like two minutes. I think yeah, that was three minutes
Yeah, that's a little all right. Okay. Well, that's fine. Let's just try it out
Let's try it out and see what we got. Let's give it up. Let's give it a whirl. Let's go. I'm so fucking nervous
I know
I think there's only three modules though
All right, you ready?
Yep, do a hard blink. Here we go
Uh, we have a new module here. It is a game boy looking thing that has five letters on it
It's a five letters. Okay, five letters looks like a game boy and there's arrows on the top and bottom
I can switch I can change the letters. It's five. Okay. Well, here's what i'm gonna i'm gonna start writing down
I think I yeah, I see this module
This is gonna be impossible because i'm gonna have to deduct a word from this. All right
So just give me the first letters. Okay
The letter is a
Okay, a
oh
Okay. No, no, no, no
so so so
I'm not saying what's on screen. I'm saying cycle through them. Oh, okay. The first letter has potential to be a
okay
Oh, yeah h or v or j x o
A x o h v j
Okay
second ones
o i b m
R q so we're looking o i m q almost the two letter ones. Oh, oh
Oh
Oh then oh then oh then what?
What do you want the third one?
Cycle through the the the second one. Okay, the second one has o i
b
m
r and q okay. Here we go. Um, read me the third ones k
n
y o
s m
k n y
o s m
Okay. Now I accept now I accept to deduct this. Okay, uh, let's see here. Uh, geez, uh, a a a a
Um, can you spell about about a b? Yes
o
You yep. Yes, go with that one. Got it. Okay. Uh, we have a wire module wire module. Okay. Hang on
I got this for you. Don't don't worry. Don't don't fret. Don't don't stop this. Oh fuck. Oh my god
That's dark. I can't see anything. Uh, it was
It was too much like okay flashlight. No, no, no, that's not in this game. It was okay four wires
Thank god you turned lights back on okay
Two black two yellow in a row so black black yellow yellow four wires black black yellow yellow
Cut the first wire. Okay, we're good
Uh word game. Okay. Okay. We're game. We're game. What's the first one c as in I can see you s ee
Ironically, okay. Uh bottom right. Okay spelled out. Okay. Why so four letters?
Middle no
First yes. Yes. No is no is on here. No no is on here. Press that one. Okay
Says s a y s like they says
Somebody says this they says okay bottom right
No, okay, uh
blank, uh
three-letter h s
wait
first what
Ready, right. Yes, right nothing. Okay, press that one final word
is
Your like is an you are coming to dinner tonight. You're coming. You are apostrophe. Yes, you're
Middle right middle right nothing
Uh with three h s right
Okay
Middle yes, okay. Okay. Hey, why okay? Hey, why letters four letters?
I'm scared too. So again, I kind of still go over to dinner for it with you
Yeah, we're having pizza ham then it'll be no pineapple man. It's ham there
Yeah, all right. Did you just like eat you ever bought ham from the store in a package and you just don't even make a sandwich
You just like eat it out of the right thing ham. Is it cooked?
Yeah, it's you know, like, you know, it's not raw. I mean it's like you're like, you know, she's like shit like that bag
Yeah
You don't do this
Um, I I used to eat bagged chicken. I used to eat chicken out of a bag
That that's fucking weird. Well, you mean like deli ham like sliced deli ham
Yes, like oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Okay
I thought you meant like you went to the store and you bought like a full ham in a bag and it was
I don't know. So you're saying like I i'm not saying german. Do you eat raw pig like no?
I don't know. Let's just go ahead. All right, so let's go something's different
Okay, um, what does it say five minutes
Okay, three modules
And it says do these wires look different to you? Does this bomb look exploded to you?
Great. All right. Well, let's uh
Well, see bar you've got a good ham here
Okay, let's go i'm fucking nervous
We're gonna die german. Oh, I need a second. I just like farmed a bad joke for fun
All right. We got a simon says
Okay. First of all, do we have a vowel or do we not have a vowel?
there is
No vowel on this
There's no vowel. Okay
Uh, so what what is the color sim blue?
yellow
Okay, blue green
yellow green
blue green blue
yellow green yellow
blue green blue red
yellow green yellow blue
final one
blue green blue red red
You're gonna make fun of this. But uh, do they have a
What's my trade of thought? What what what happened? Hold on. Wait, what are you waiting for a vowel?
What did we have a vowel? Yes or no, sorry. No, no
Hold on. Okay. Okay. It's making sure. Okay, so read me them again. Sorry, but it's quick. Um, it was
blue green blue red red
Yellow green yellow blue and the last one was red. Yes
Yeah, hold on. Let's just refresh
Okay
Yes
blue green blue red red
yellow green yellow blue
No, no, no, sorry my bad. No, no, that's green. That's yellow
Did we do it? What it was red red? What what i have a suggestion
All right, we clock out of this one now and repeat it immediately. There's no need for this time waste
Let's just let's just redo this one. Let's just leave the room back out of the situation and redo this mission
All right, because I lost my track just walk away
Walk away walk away from this one
You don't have to kill us
Go out of the fucking room. You have to like blow me off. It was quicker to do that
I was quicker to do it that way. All right, let's
It's sorry that was totally on me. Do you see how easy it is to just throw
It's so easy to throw everything off because it was like, okay blue green blue blue
Do we have a serial number? Do we have to do a vowel? It's like, hey
It's super embarrassing but the problem the problem with that is like it's like riding a bike
Like, you know how to do it, but somebody just like throws a stick in the wheel and you're like, okay
Yeah, like all right. Let's just cut our shit. Yeah, was there no there was no vowel. I don't remember
Okay. Okay. Don't worry about this. We can do this. Here we go
All right. I'm going to talk very clearly and very slowly
Okay. All right. We're going to do this wires here. We have six wires
And they're in this order four blue two red blue blue blue red red
Last digit of the serial number is odd
Is the last digit of the serial number odd it is even? Okay
Uh, it's exactly one yellow wire. There is it's only blue and red four blue two red
If there are no red wires cut the last wire, but you do have red bars
Yeah
Two red wires the last wire is red two red wires the fourth wire cut the fourth wire wire done. Okay. Okay, we have
Um some different looking wires. These are strange looking wires. They go they go they're they're they're different. They're vertical not horizontal
Are they are are they? Uh
Do they have a star and a light on them? Um
Yes, they they did they did for a second
But we're gonna go to go with simon says because the lights just turned off simon says, okay
Simon says holy shit. Okay. Yes
Uh, yeah, I know
Okay
No, I just I I still on that page
So so read me this serial, um serial number. No, no, no serious. No, no, no. There's a vowel. Okay. So, uh,
Here we go. Okay. Let's go first flash blue red
blue yellow
red green
good
blue yellow blue
Red green red
Uh, hold on shut up. Not you. All right back to the wires. That was it. We're done
We have uh, five wires
Well, that was almost this we're done with it. Yeah, that's it. That's it. It's green light
Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. So relax. We have three full minutes to figure this out. So just okay. Okay, here we go
we're gonna be looking at something called uh, uh, it's saying the
These wires are not like the others some have stripes this makes them completely different
The good news is that we found a concise set of instructions
so this is what it's referred as a
M diagram, okay. Oh, I just gotta align this. Okay. So what is the first one?
Okay, so from left to right it is white. Yes
Okay. Um, no, no, no, no, okay
That doesn't matter the instructions said that doesn't matter. Okay. It's like I line these so we have does it have a star?
Yeah, okay. There are three stars on the bottom
Okay, the first second and third wire are on a star. Okay. Uh, okay that won't matter then. Okay, so
You would need to uh
Let me let me read you the wires. Let me cut the first one cut the first wire first
Like all like like left the leftmost wire. Yes. Okay. Uh, there's more to do. Yes
So, uh, what's the what's the what's the second one? So these wires are red
And then blue and red striped that's the two different that's it
So there's two blue and red striped and then there's two red
Does it have a light? Does it have a light the blue and red stripe has a light and it's on a star?
Okay, that's a star. Uh, don't cut that one. Next one
The next one is a red wire on a star with no light red wire with a star. No light
Cut that one. Yes, there's more to do. Okay. Yeah, keep going. Keep going
The next wire is no star with a light and it is a red and blue striped wire
So just the light on this no, no, no, no star light. Just the light no star
It's the last serial number even is the serial number even? Uh, yeah, the number is is even cut it cut that wire
Okay, there are two wires that remain the last wire is they have a star the last wire does not have a star
Okay, so that's nothing on it. Not just red. Let's have a star. Nothing. Nothing. Just red. It's the last even it
It was even right? It was even it was even last year lumber cut it
Somebody said hello cut it. Hello. Just cut it. Hello. What do you mean? I don't want to fuck it up
Okay, so do you know what a venn diagram is? I'm gonna pretend to yes. Uh, okay, so it's like a giant
um
It's like a bunch of circles circles with different colors essentially inside of each circle. Yes. Yes. I know that spells the solution. Yes
Except these are colorless in the manual
So you're gonna have to really like squint your fucking eyes. The only way of reading this is if the colors spell out
Uh, if they're striped or dotted it's bullshit, but don't worry about it. I feel like you're doing a lot of good work here
NA education, um, well here's the thing about my NA education. Uh, Joel, I gotta ask you this
Uh people people like oh, I can't believe you didn't know you didn't know what what that symbol was
You didn't know what that math problem was
When was the last time you sat in a math class?
Like what's the time you were sitting in a math class in a chair in a math class
I feel like i'm in a math class every fucking stream with these people
Uh 100 years. I don't know. Uh, it's been a while. So it's been 20 years since i've been in a math class
So yeah, I don't know what the omega symbol is. You're 60
No, i'm I turned I turned 25 next week
This one's gonna be hard
Okay, uh, this one is four modules
And it says 60 percent of the time this bomb explodes every time
Okay, I don't know what that's supposed to mean
Does this mean that we have a 60 percent chance to lose? It means nothing good. It means nothing good
All right, let's just are you good. I'm ready to rock and roll man. All right. I'm ready. I'm feeling 100 about this
Did you take a hundred percent? I'm sure that is I took a multivitamin last time it helped
It helped
Yeah, yeah, but I don't need performance enhancing drugs to do this all I need is the the skill of a gamer. All right
Yeah, if uh, all those guys that got in trouble when they did took vitamin b12
All those athletes
Yeah
It's about honor. It's about honor. Yeah, I i'm low on vitamin d. I'm not gonna i'm not gonna like drink any milk
All right, you good
I'm good
Here we go. We have a different module this module
Uh has a megahertz on it and it's a blinking light with with almost like a radio, uh dial
I can change the the amount of megahertz and there's a button that says tx
We have a blinking light up top and then we have something with megahertz. It's it's drama 3.5
Is this morse code?
I mean morse code. I don't hear anything
Is there a light going beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep if it was morse code?
It's wouldn't be able to hear it
No, it's a visual because that's how people communicate with flashlights in like world wars. Okay. All right. Yes, there is a light up here
And I uh, okay. Uh, yeah, do you know how to read morse code jerma? No, absolutely not zero knowledge. I know that like I know
What's that that's that's sos right that's sos
jerma
You can't read morse code
Why the fuck do I know why would I know morse code?
That's basic school knowledge. No, it's not what is this 1910?
What do you mean basic school knowledge? This is like 1840. All right, ready
Jerma, I can't read morse code either. I'm fucked too. Oh god. Okay. So here we go
this
All right. Listen, listen, we wasted a lot of time on this. Can you hear my screen?
I can okay, you ready listen to my stream for just i'm gonna be quiet
No, hold on let me hold on. Okay, jerma. I have a better solution to this
Is that helping a better solution to this? No, absolutely not
This is going to practice right? It doesn't matter if this explodes or not this we have to hammer this in
Uh, we I have to teach you morse code
or rather
I gotta complain about something. It's dots and dashes. I know I know the basics is dots and dashes
I just gotta complain with something chat
Yeah, yeah, let me let me just explain something to both chats here. So
Two weeks ago
I read the manual and it said
morse code
And i've been telling chat for two weeks that
Chat i'm going to learn morse code off stream so they can snitch on me and tell jerma beforehand
Joel has been practicing off stream in reality
I did not practice at all because I wanted you guys to just see how much of a snitch you guys were to jerma
Um, so I didn't practice at all. So you guys that have been going around talking to jerma saying hey, by the way
Joel's been cheating
You guys fucked up, I know who you guys are
I'm gonna tell you on sos and fucking morse codes because i'm coming over there and i'm gonna tell you something snitches get stitches
All right, so fuck you. All right. Anyway, but that doesn't deduct from the problem here. We have to learn this
So I propose this morse code is relatively simple. It's a it's a matter of taking it slow and easy
So what I propose here, you're going to be reading me again
I know that there's a clock here, but don't worry about it exploding. We have to learn this so again
I have a diagram
Okay, so here's what i'm saying. This is going to be a repeating pattern essentially, right? Yes
And we're not going to be we don't need to read the full letter
So for example, uh, if the word will be shell there will be a frequency at 3505 do that
That's a test just ask anyway press tx
Okay, I just want to make a make a see if it worked anyway, but that doesn't matter
Uh, so here's what we're gonna do again. I know that the clock is ticking, but this is just a practice round
Um, so, um, let me read this. Here we go. Okay
interpret the signal from the flashing light using the morse code chart to spell one of the words in the table the signal will loop with a
Long gap between repetitions once the word is identified set the corresponding frequency and press the transmit tx button
so
Essentially what we're going to be looking at here is um
It's it's going to be actually quite simple. Um, it's it's it's a you are going to be rating me
Yeah, yeah, you're gonna be reading you're gonna say dot dash, right? Yeah to spell out something
Yes, and there's going to be a space in between these when the spaces happen
I propose that you say dot dash comma dot dot dash comma
Yes
And that's going to spell out a word for me to like deduct and then we take that word and then we transpose that into a frequency
so, uh
German did that and any of that register? I was repeating the last three words you were saying and nodding my head. Uh,
No, no, I get it. I get it. Yeah, it's dot dot dash
dots and dashes and then in between
Like for instance like dot dot dash if it was dot dot dash
That's a letter so dot dot dash that will actually let me see if that actually means something
Dot dot dash would be you as in the letter you yes, and after you say that
Make sure you say comma so you don't say dot dot dash dash dot dot like that would fuck me up
Yeah, add a little comment between this. I know where to separate the letters. I think we're good to go
I think I get it
Okay, uh, but keep in mind if there's misspellings here
We're gonna have to do this all over again and this could lead to a lot of fucking problems
But i'm gonna be very look. I promise i'm known for my noises, right?
Like I mean that's good. I'm known to be able to get correct noises. If there's one thing i'm confident
It's making noise. Okay, i'm ready
I'm known for like literally if you type in german on h5 into google
The first thing that pops up is probably like the mini century noise so like i'm good
Uh, we don't have to do that this one. All right, we got the um, we got the
We have a new module. It is three wires
On horizontal and there's one two, three abc. It's a new module. Oh, we're looking at a wire sequence here
We're looking at a wire. Yeah, it's a wire sequence
The wires are horizontal and they and there are there's one two three abc on the left and right
Let me let me read this see what the fuck this is within this model. There are several panels with okay
So basically this can also be a practice round because this is also going to be something completely fucking
Within this module there are several panels with wires with them
But only one panel is visible at a time switch to the next panel by using the down button and the previous panel
By using the up button. Okay
Jerma, okay, press the down button to go to a new panel and it said
Don't don't don't touch no touch
Do not switch to the next panel until you're sure that you have cut all the necessary wires on the current panel
Jerma, anyway cut the wires as directed by the following table wire occurrences are cumulatively all over the panels within the module and
Okay. So the first one here you have to tell me
One goes to what and what color? Okay. So one for instance one is black and it goes one to a
One to a okay cut it. Okay. The next wire is blue and it goes two to b
Do not cut that one. Oh, actually does it go to b? Yes
Sorry cut that one
That was my mistake. I'm so sorry. I'm so glad that there's like a lot of audio in the background
Because that was like a bullfrog noise that I made
All right, so then three goes to c and that's the last one to cut anyways, so I cut it. Yes
Yes, and then go down. Okay. I see. All right. I get you. All right, so we got four five six
There is no wire on four. We have a black wire five b
Uh skip to the next one
Black wire six c. Yeah. Yeah, just skip the next one. I I think this will work. Okay
Uh, it's seven eight nine and then a b c eight. Okay, so uh, eight goes to c blue wire
Cut cut cut the blue one. Okay, nine now goes to c black wire and then we'll take it will be
in terms of like
Occurrences like how many blacks this will be only black wire will be
So this will be the second right? Oh, we have to keep track of how many wires there were
Okay, and then we'll be so the sec this will be the second one go up go up go up. Oh you can go up
Okay, so wait, then now is okay. So this there are two
Black wires here on this one and then on the one before that there's one black wire on the one before that
So we're looking at four four in total now. So this is the fourth black wire. Okay. Uh, does it go to c? Yes
Cut it. That's it. Next one is
Uh 10 11 12 a b c 10 is a blue wire 10 b
So the blue one will be in terms of occurrence. We've been looking at the this would be
One this would be this would be the third blue wire. Does it go to a?
Uh, it does not it goes to b
Uh, don't okay. So second one second one is a red wire 11 c
Okay, and that will be I think the second one
Yeah
um, I don't know
Yeah, probably
Just go next. Just go next. You can't say probably
Yeah, probably. I don't know. Oh my god
Listen, it's a completely new fucking log to me and I I don't I don't it's hard to like decipher
What the fuck these mean, but whatever whatever listen if we refresh now and we get a morse code one
I I think I think we're we're good. All right, we've learned we've learned these two
We've learned these two now maybe the bomb. Okay, let's just let's just get some ass in absolutes if you're a bomb diffuser
Okay, okay. No, you got it. You got it. You got it man. You got it. Here we go. Ready? Yes. Yes restart in go
Simon says okay, but are you sure it's just simon says though?
What do uh, no, I mean the Simon says that we have morse code on this one and one of the new wire ones
but there's
Simon says how about how about this another practice round it here?
Because here's what I want to do
I want to get this morse code shit down here so we can do this in the future, right?
You got it. All right
So, uh, you remember what I said about saying like comas and all that shit. Yep
I I got you. I got you. All right, so let me let me wait till let's wait till we get a big break here
Okay, hold on. Mm-hmm dot dot dot dot that's h
Okay, so we have dot dot dot germa. I already know the answer. It's three five. Oh five dot three five
Oh five three five. Oh five is a solution. No, it's not three five. Oh five three five
three point five oh three point five oh five
three five
One five three five one five
That's correct, sorry my bad
All right. Now we've got the wires
I'll tell you i'll tell the solution for this and this is going to be a strategy for us
All right, I know we probably can't do this. It's another practice round here do this quick
Okay, so basically I have all these words that correspond to the letter
And basically if the letter or there's words there's words
There's all of these words
But this one was unique because it was the only one that started with an h
That means I can deduct and immediately know the answer beforehand so I can immediately spit out the code at you. So
That's
All right. All right. We got we got the the wire when we practiced last time here it comes
All right. We have okay two red wires
one two three a b c
One b red. Okay, you're gonna have to repeat that because I got lost in the manual here. I'm so sorry
We have this now now now
Okay, so we have two red wires. That's correct
Okay, so uh the first one
uh does it go to
C now you said a right one goes from one to b red wire
Okay, do not cut that one. The second one goes to to a two to a red wire
Skip all of these just go to the next one. The next one we have four five six a b c
The first wire is a black wire four to b second wire is a blue wire
Okay, the next wire is a blue wire five to c
Skip to the next
This next one is seven eight nine a b c
The two wires that are present on this module are red and do we have
Okay, if there's a red wire
Cut it right now
Okay
The next one is a black wire nine a
Okay, and this would be the the third black wire. Yeah, that's okay. This would be the one
This would be the second black wire
Okay, and that goes to a a you said
uh cut it
Got it. Okay last one. We have three wires. It's 10 11 12 a b c
This is a black wires the first one it goes to b
Cut that cut the black wire
Okay. Now we have two red wires
11 b
okay, and in terms of occurrences this this one will be the
Third or fourth one. Yeah, this would be the one two
three
This would be the fourth red wire
that is dust dust
Does the fourth one here go to a?
It goes to b
Okay, do not cut that one and the last one was a red wire as well. It's 12 a
Skip to the next one done. Okay. Oh, we have symbols you ready?
Uh, yeah, uh ae trident stitches h or n
uh
Batman symbol batman symbol
What batman I heard the fucking music. I know we would be fucked. There's no fucking way. I could spit out that much shit
Maybe aquaman
All right, we got we got we're getting that done. So we got to keep tracking the amount. Okay. I got it
Mm-hmm. I got it. All right, so more morse code is not a problem for us now
I I think I think we got that down and the occurrence wires
I think we got two the thing we've got to be watching out watching out for though is we got those complicated wires
But I think I got that down with the venn diagram. So, all right, I I think we're we're we're these new
Complicated wires that have been you know
Generated for it. I think we're good. So next one. Here we go. I think we can do this
I think we're good. I think we got it this time. Yeah, I think we're so yeah. Yeah, absolutely
All right. Are you guys ready?
Are you ready? Are you ready? I'm ready, man. I'm ready, man. All right game boy with a word to spell
Okay, we're gonna be spelling out a word here. So we're gonna looking at the
This is called a uh, this is called the subject of password
So i'm gonna be writing down all the first ones in the first column, right? So get ready
I okay, here we go. Ready first first letter in the first column b
j b c
t
e d
So we're looking at bj ted
Yes, yes bj ted, correct. Okay bj ted second row
So c e h n w s that's correct. Okay, so and the third ones are s
l n b
i
K. Okay. So the first one let's see here. Uh c b t ted
Uh t is anyone start with t
The word is think. Mm-hmm. I think so would make sense. Wouldn't it? No
Yes, it is. Nope work. It could be thing with the word is thing. The word is thing
All right, we got okay. What's code? Okay, we got morse code. All right, you ready now now keep in mind
I want you to like remember these so like and say comma in between so here we go
So we got a v yeah, yeah
Try putting in
3595 as a solution three five nine five. Okay
Uh, now we have the word game where like the there you uh, what? Huh? Okay. We I got that
So are you prepared? Huh? Okay. The first word is there
It is there like as in like
Okay, so middle right middle right
What with a question mark what what would the question work? Uh, so we got uh with three h's we got what four letters
left
Nothing ready. What is on here? But it's what I just asked. It's what I just said to you though
What with a question mark? Oh, yeah. No, no, no. What what is the word here? Okay. Oh, no, no, no
Okay, I got okay. Uh
Wait, okay. The word is there their pizza in the middle right sex spot is what you
Hold your with an apostrophe like what kind of single you or you you like you a person
Uh us in like three letters. Yes. Okay. It's there. Okay next next word. Okay, we have you it is y-o-u
You as a person you
Okay, uh, let's see here you are looking at uh, you
Middle right middle right no
blank
Uh three h's wait
First got it final final word is you again y-o-u you so we're looking at middle right again
You y-o-u the person you sure you are with a space in between
You're possessive you're with an apostrophe next. Okay. Yeah, we got it. All right. We got
Uh, we got one more and it's just it's the symbols like the half-life symbol thing right half-life symbol
All right, we have half-life symbol mirrored k
Sleepy three and a not filled in star. Okay, uh the x looking weird thing
we're looking at the uh
The three half-life and the weird star
sleepy three sleepy three
Yeah, it's like somebody just like was doing three and then they just fell asleep when they got to the end
We had a minute left to go that's about our best time by the way, that's good
You know, you know what though I think the morse code is really easy the problem with the morse code though is
Sometimes I can't do that logical
What is it called when you elimination where you're like, you know
Basically, the word was vector right? There's only one word like that. That's one v in it
So why I chose to do was just go v and then it's got to be vectors
I correspond with the frequency on it
But there might be several ones that start with t for example
That means I have to also get the second letter so I can't do up
I think it's process of elimination. I think it's called so uh, it's it's gonna the channels will ramp up
But don't don't worry. I think we got this this next one is called fair game
It's called no more hand holding remember everything you've learned because anything can appear on the bump. This is a big one
This is the uh, this is the gear check. This is five modules. It's five minutes. This is the this is the dps check
Dude, let me tell you i've been so nervous. I've been holding in this p I I
Now that I can relax like the the the the pp instincts are kicking. I gotta I gotta go i'm i'm sorry
You want to take p? All right. All right. We'll take it. Yes
Wait, are you are you like sprinting to go p or is this like let's take a break for two minutes?
Yes, which one? Yeah, you you are you you're or you're yes or yeah, which one i'm fucking pissing head on
Go pee with them now. No, i'm i'm i'm gonna take a long it's gonna take a lot longer for me guys
I take my time when I pee I I like arch my back. I like crack the neck
I like roll my shoulders a little bit. I look directly into the bowl for a full
10 seconds and I go. All right
That's that's where it's going right there
And then they're okay. I take my time. I don't I don't rush pee
Where else is it going?
Where else is it gonna go? You know what today?
Today I think i'm going right at the back wall. I think that's where i'm going today
No one wanted to know that this is how germa paints his house
Do the sentry noise?
I don't need to do the sentry noise right now. It's not necessary
This was like when you when you go somewhere with somebody and you don't have to pee but they do
And you just want to get to where you're going?
and
It's like hey man, let's get to go pee. You're like, all right
Whoa?
Why did it take you that long?
Why did it take you that long to start?
What are you doing? All right. All right. There we go. There we go. Did you pee into the corner?
Wait, did you did you go like a snack and then pee in the corner of your room?
No, I I didn't go I didn't go right. No, I didn't go pee. Anyway, uh, let's uh
Let us uh
Let's let's play some games. Uh
All right. Well now I uh now I gotta go pee
No, no, you don't
Let's go. This one's gonna be hard focus
Use everything you've learned. Um, I am yes you are you got it. You are
So smart and you've been a big my reading beast
Here we go
Uh, we're gonna do we have uh, what's the word game boy edition?
All right. What's the word? Here we go. We're gonna start kicking ass here. So tell me what uh, what is the first letter?
x
u w
y s i
Okay, let's see here. Um, second row v b
o
q y f
Okay, let's see here. Uh
See if anyone at starboard s
Okay, uh, does the third row have a u in it the third row?
Does not have a u in it
shit, okay, uh shit
Did the second row have a p in it second row?
No, i'm not making a joke
What the second row does not have those?
Okay, it does not have a p. Uh
Shit, this is gonna be really hard one
Uh, there's no t's either. Uh, does anyone start with w?
Yes. Yes, it's true. That could be could be that
I got it. I'll be you the word was world. Okay. Uh, Simon says what the fuck? Okay, Simon says
Uh ready Simon says, okay, whatever. I have to deduct that later on whatever. Yeah, so serial serial serial number is
Serial number is uh
What are you looking for a vowel?
Yes, no vowels
No vowel. Okay. So well what the color sequence is
green
That's the solution. Sorry what?
Oh, that's the solution
Okay, green green green green green green green green green green
What the fuck's going on? Okay done
Now we got okay, uh
We got the wire scenario. No, no, no
We've got the the the box with the number in it with the sequence you gotta remember the sequences
Okay, that that shit's easy because you you you're like an elephant. You remember everything anyway, uh, sorry
I want to say that but whatever let's just do occurrences or whatever. It's called right the complicated wires
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
We're doing this is just the number with the the sequence the number in the in the box
You want to do the complicated wires? Yes, because that's hard one
Okay
Tell me which ones do we have?
we have
Uh, it's one two three a b c
And okay black red
Cut it
What cut it?
Cut the black wire. Okay, what else?
Red what else do we have red two c?
Cut that one, too
Next we have one black wire four to b four five six a b c four to b black wire skip skip skip
Next we have seven eight nine a b c blue red black
Blue seven goes to a this is the first this is the first blue one first blue wire of the game
Okay, skip that one. Don't skip the full thing. Don't skip that one
Like did you skip the thing? I did not skip it. I I I clicked it. It was a strike
Okay, shit now, okay
Okay, so when I say skip it, I didn't mean like skip the full whatever
So that was the blue one, right? Okay. So that this is the second red one second red one, right? No
Yep, second red wire second red wire and it's from a to eight to a
Okay, don't cut that one sen and then it will be the
Third black wire the second one. Sorry black third
It's the last wire is a black wire and it is the third black wire of the video game
Okay, what does that go to b?
Good that it
Final one is 10 11 12 a b c two blue wires one red blue blue red 10 a 11 b 12 b
But in terms of occurrences the blue one, this will be the third one
This would no this be the yes, this would be one two three
No
This would be the third two and three of blue wires. Yes
Okay, so uh third one. It doesn't go to b
It goes to a
Okay, don't cut that one
I we had three seconds. I had them. I we had three seconds. I was trying to guess
No guessing
How the fuck did you deduct that that member? Uh, what do you call it?
I just saw how do you just how I just saw w and just went with it
There was like there was like four fucking different ones
You had a 25 chance of winning and you you won. I think it was just on oh
I saw like the or and then I saw there was a w so I was like it's world
I guess man
Okay, i'm just telling you that's my don't do a cowboy move like that again. We we don't know what's gonna happen
Oh my god. All right. I won't do it again
Okay
So this one we're starting with we've got a new module, but it's remember we pick it up
Uh, it's the pac-man module thing with the with the red triangle and the lights
Okay, I remember when we did this last time. Okay, so we're gonna be referring to this as a b c d e f g
Right. Do you understand what I mean there? So when i'm saying numbers here
Uh, i'm saying like the the uh, the vertical ones i'm saying like alpha one you'll be in the first position if i'm saying
b2 that will be uh
Like yeah, like one over and down like one over and down. Yeah one over and down
So where did you spawn here? I spawned in alpha two
alpha two, okay, um
Okay, uh, and then um, we have two dots here. We have two dots here
Yes, where are they located? The two circles are located in
um
beta one
and beta six
Okay, beta one and beta six and you spawn in a two a two
Okay, and the light the light is in a b c is in
There was a delta delta six
Okay, then go down one
Uh, did it work? What's going on? I just went down. Why am I not moving? Did I go I did down twice?
What's going on? Why is it not moving?
Did you do this correctly?
You didn't you didn't confuse the red and white did you? I did
Oh, so we're
drama restarted I I didn't know I thought I thought that was us because it's everything every video game that's ever existed
You are the fucking triangle pointing in every single game. You're the triangle that's pointing. You're the triangle on the minimap every time
All right, just scratch it just go
Scratch it
You ready scratch it new. Let's kick ass. Let's kick ass. Let's kick its ass
We have a blue button that button says detonate on it
It says detonate. All right, so let's see here
uh
How many batteries do we have on this one? The amount of batteries are
We have one
battery one battery
And it says detonate detonate blue
Okay, but the problem is there is not more than one. There's just one not more than one
There is only one button here. It's a blue button that says detonate
It's a lit indicator on this one. There is it's on the right
Okay, does it say frk?
No, it says trn
Okay
Well, we're gonna be holding down this button. Okay yellow flashing light
Well five in any position. Okay, good. Very good five in any position. Let it go
Okay. Now we have a game boy find the word
Word scrambler. All right. Here we go
So i'm gonna be starting writing this down. So here we go
Okay
next one p u
y t
m i
Okay, before we do that one, let's see here. Um
V v v v it's not a v words. No s s s s
Uh, bring me the third ones bring me the third ones
The word is study
Done. Okay. We have uh, we have we have symbols the the weird symbols with like the the t b and the k and the
Okay. Okay. Yeah, we we go. I got it. I gotta go for you. All right. Holy shit. You're really good at this
Okay, uh
So, uh, what are we looking at here? We're looking at the uh, the mirrored k
Uh the backwards p
Um, it's dark mirrored k backwards. What is dark?
uh, the lights turn off mirrored k backwards p t b and then um
An octopus holding a okay. I I I got I got I got you the what the fuck. Okay
Uh, do the backwards p do t b. Yep weird x
No, that's reverse and then that will be a spider with spear and then okay. Sorry. Okay. Okay. Okay
We got we got plenty of time
Uh, it's the it's the number with the thing in the middle the number of the big box with the number
Okay. Okay. No, no, no, no problem. No problem. The number is
four
fourth position
Okay
The number is two press the button the same position as pressing stage one same position same position
uh
Fuck I think it was four
I think yep. Okay. All right. Next number you're making me nervous is one. All right
Same label it same label as the president stage two same label as there's a stage two got it. Okay
The number is one again
Press the button the same position as the president stage one
Same position or the same position position position as state one. Yes, uh final number is one
Press the same button with the same label as the president stage one same label
Okay, we got one more module. This is the complicated wire is going to go horizontal one two three abc
Okay, okay. Let me let me talk into this one. Here we go. Here we go. All right, so we we got what?
black wire
only from two to see
Good. Okay next
We've got uh, this would be the second and third black wire
So we have two black wires one red four five six abc
Where's the second one go to the second black wire is going to a the second wire is going to be and it's red
So the first okay, so don't cut the first wire. Do not cut the first wire
Okay
The okay, so give me the give me the there was another second black one, right?
It's the second black wire is going to a it's in the third. It's it's it's six to eight
Skip that skip skip that one skip this whole thing and then we got what?
Okay. Now we have one red wire two blues red blue blue
And the current in current this will be uh, the the second would be this would be the second red wire
Does that go to a or c this one goes to a?
Cut it
That's not correct. Um, that's okay
We have two blue wires. Oh
Just getting hard now son. Oh, that was it too
That was close
Okay
Well, i'll tell you what man the word scrambler thing
I you're a fucking genius at it. Like unironically you are amazing at this. I I don't I I think I think i think i'm
I think i'm just a little strange
You know, you know, you got that one thing that you can do
I'm writing this down like, okay, let's see here. Uh w like and you're fucking
Like
Going through it. I don't know if I could do that every time look you're amazing, man
I think I think it's just a little strange
Dude, i'll tell you what man. I'll tell you what if if nasa needs like a word scrambling man
This streaming shit
Ben, all right, you're going to space buddy
Thanks
Wow
Word scrambler. Don't worry. I'll take care of this
If you actually do this
Tell me i'm not gonna help you this time because you are so good at this friend. You're so good at this
Isn't he amazing guys?
It's probably fucking solving it in any fucking second. What watch this five
four
three
two
one
germa
Here we go. Five four
three
Two one germa moss moss
God, this is one like the guinness book world record shows up at your house and you can't do it
You're you're the master at this and everyone realizes that he wasn't real
No, you can do this you're really good at this
Germa, what are you doing? Keep from uh
time
Oh good. Uh, I I it was like a full minute and a half that we just threw away
All right, let's do it again again again again
Okay
That was not very good. No, it wasn't. Yes. I'm ready. It wasn't very good. Okay
Okay, we've got double pac-man double pac-man game with the thing
Give me two dots. Give me two dots the two. All right, we've got two circles are in a two
and then
F3
Okay, gotcha. Okay. Where do you spawn? I spawned in
D6
And the light okay, and the goal is the goal is in e1
So you spawned in did you spawn in d6? I spawned in d6
D6, okay, correct. So you want to go up? Yep
And you want to go, uh
Up. Yep. Nope. We spawned in d6
a b c d
1 2 3 4 5 6 d6
I mean i'm i'm at d5 right now
a 2
and f3 for the circles
and
E1 for the goal something's wrong here. What's wrong? Something is wrong here. Uh,
E1 is the goal
A2 okay, uh bottom bottom bottom. Tell fucking redo this redo this one redo this one. Okay
Totally on my fault totally on my fault
Okay, that was totally my mistake totally my fucking mistake that is totally on me. It's all right full responsibility
Look, I had I had the whole guinness book world records team watching that was that was my fault. I am sorry, man
They were here
they were just the guy was sitting there like with a pen in his mouth just like
You won't be part of the academy and they left
Well, you're going to space with your fucking
Password solving skills, man. I hope so one day
Okay, here we go
We have a pat was pac-man game. Let's get this right
Okay. Okay, let's go. So what do we have the dots on are these little like green?
little green circles, okay, we have d4
Mm-hmm and f4 d4. Okay f4
Gotcha and you are spawning in I am an a6
a6 okay, and you want to go to the goal at the goal that I would like to go to is an e1
Okay, so you want to go right right right
Yep, go as long as bottom as you can. Okay, go right
Okay
All the way up
You want to go left?
Okay. Next we have a
Guinness book of world records puzzle. Are you sure you want to do this yourself? No, just like just i'll help you here
g, okay, um
g
so g w r
f
i v
Okay, uh, let's see here and the second rows are
r
i x h
c s
Okay, let's see here. Uh
Let's see. Uh g g g over there. Let's start with g. There's no sort of g. Do we have w's? Yes, we do
uh
Do we have any i's in the third row? Yes, we do
Right the word is right
As not right as inside but as in like as you know, you use a pen to write something it's not the direction, right?
Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Okay. The next one is a uh number inside of the box numbers on the box
Okay, but the sequence number is two. Fuck. Okay. Hang on. Uh, the number is two you said
Yep, press the button in the second position
Next number number is
Four press the button in the same position as you press the stage one same position
The number is the start number number is one press the button in the second position
Number is two
Press the button the same position as you press in stage one
Number is four press the button labeled four the next but the next number is four
Press the button the same position as you press in stage two
Okay, the final number is
one
Press the button with the same label as you press on stage one
All right, we have
uh
The candy cane wires the vertical wires with the stars and lights and the
Okay, not not a problem man. Not a problem here. Uh
Let's see here. So we're looking at uh
There's six wires shit. Okay. Let me let me read this. We have time
We have time. You know what? No, no, that's it. Let's you know what this is. There's a button
It's there's a button. Let's do this first because we have time. Oh
The button is yellow. It's abort yellow abort. We have a we have a strike. We have a strike
Yes, there's one strike and it is abort yellow
Okay, let's see abort
Uh blue no, uh, one of the others do we have how many batteries there are one?
Three batteries yellow abort three batteries. It's a lit indicator. There is on this so say frk
Frk is on the side. Yes
Um, it's not let me release the button immediately release the button press and immediately press immediately release
No, it's not lit up. Frk is not lit up. Oh, it wasn't lit up. No. Oh shit
Hold it down. Hold it down. Hold it down. Okay yellow blinking five and in position
I can't time that okay wires. We have 25 seconds. Uh, uh, I don't know the third one the third one
We're doing so good
Shit, I i'm sorry. I should have asked if this thing was light
I uh, no, I I saw that I saw that and I was like maybe no is that frk? Whatever?
Oh, fuck. I'm sorry. I should have asked if there's a light about the light. That's my fault
I should have brought it up. I saw but I didn't know I I take responses about my bad my bad
Okay. Oh, I did ask you did. Oh I did
So who who was in the wrong?
Then I was like I was like super on my mistake
Is it my fault
It no, I no stop stop attacking germa. I I will be the christ on the cross on this one attack my flesh
All right
I will take the explosion into my body. All right, that was me
Now don't don't don't well, even if you look off at germa if you stood in front of me
It would just it would just liquidate the both of us. So it's not like it's gonna stop anything
Do anyone
Here we go. This is the totally this is the gear check. This is the wall
All right, we have
Uh the regular wires just standard wires
Standard wires. How many do we have? We have five
And there's a lot of colors, but the first wire is white and in a row. It's white red
Yellow blue red two red wires on any no black wires. There are no black wires
Cut the second wire
Okay, we have a button here. The button is white and it says hold on it white
Hold, let's see. Uh, wait, wait, wait
Is there a lit indicator with the label car?
No, there is not
Are there more than two batteries? There are no batteries
No, there are two batteries. There are two batteries
Is there a lit indicator with frk on it? There is not okay. There are two batteries
The button is not yellow was white. You said white and it says hold
Okay, uh
Hold it down
Blue flashing light one one in any oh, no, no, sorry. Sorry four in any position four four in any position or any position good
Uh, we have the uh, the word like you or your your uh, uh, uh, uh, okay gotcha gotcha
Let me just read read this read this read this read this. Uh, the word is first. Okay, uh, uh, I fucked up here
Okay, wait, okay. Now. Okay. We're kicking ass now now. So the word is
First bring me top right bring me top right. All right, i'll reach top right. It's hold hold
Hold hold hold you are with a space in between the letter. There it is done
Okay, next word the next word is
Blank b-l-a-n-k blank so blank. Okay, here we go. Uh, where is this one?
Okay, we're look middle right middle right read me the letter u just the letter u
Uh-huh. Yeah on space, huh on space, huh? Yes. Yes. Yes
Okay, now we have the it's read like you're reading a book r-e-a-d read, okay, uh read read
Okay, middle right middle right blank. Okay blank blank blank. Here we go
Wait, right
Okay, four letters got a metal
Okay, gotcha got it. Next we have uh, the sequence of of the annoying wires the horizontal ones the ones are like, oh black
Red, okay. So first one first red one first red one. So red is going to see cut it
Okay, second wire is red also going to be cut it
The last wire is a black wire going to c cut it
Okay
Next we have a black wire going to a and a blue wire going to c
Four to a the black wire cut the black wire. Okay blue wire is going to c six c
It's the third slot and that is the first one we've seen that's the first blue wire
And do not cut that one skip to the next round next round
We have two blue wires going from seven to c and then nine to a two blues
The first cut the uh, wait, this is the this is the first blue wire. Yes
No, this would be these these would be the second third blue wire second. This would be the second, right?
This one here would be the second blue wire. Okay. Does that go to c? Yes cut that one
Next is the third blue wire and it's going it's going to a skip that one
Okay, finally, we have a fourth blue wire going to b
And then we have fourth occurrence blue wire fourth occurrence blue wire. Does that go to b? Yes cut it
At this incorrect, okay
So we have a black and red wire next both going to c black c so the black wire
Occurrence for black wire would be that would be the
Sec the third black wire
Does that go to b does that go to b that third black wire goes to c?
Let's get that one and the red one will be what occurrence the red wire is also going to c
And it would be
The third occurrence of red skip that one skip that one skip it all. Okay, that should be it. Yes, it's done
Okay. Now we just have we just have a word a word jumbler. You do it. You are the master
You are the master jerma go activate go. That's not goofy. The word's not goofy. I thought it was goofy
No, I had it. It's not goofy
Oh, come on
jerma, please joker
You know, maybe I I know you guys like
Jerma you fuck up. I should have said
Joker's not a word in here
Joker's not a word go goofy. It was goofy
Oh, I had it it was goofy
Come on, it was goofy
I feel this is poetic in a way, you know
Oh, come on. I thought it was gonna be bang. We had it garsh. What was it supposed to be? How is goofy?
Not a word
It's the perfect
Let me let me double check if there is a word. Hang on. It's joker word joker or goofy are not words in this
Dude we could have had that if if
Okay, so now we just know for reference. They will never be goofy some stream
No goofy jokers. All right
God damn it. I'm so sad
Joke goofy. It was correct. We had it
Here's what I propose. Let's not do any more cowboy moves on this one
Let's be slow and just you know
All right
Here we go
Morse code we got a morse code. All right, let me let me get in position for this one. All right. All right, so
Uh, we are going to do some morse coding. All right, so here we go. Uh, you're ready to read
Don't no, no, no, no you you you say dosh and death
I have to wait
Holy shit, what happened? I uh, I dropped it. I dropped the bomb on the ground
You dropped the bomb
Yeah, I literally dropped it on the ground. Did goofy steal it again landed on the on the down the explode button
All right, ready three two one and scene. Here we go
Simon says oh Simon says okay. Here we go. And do we have uh any any vowels?
No
We do not have vowels. Okay. So what are we looking at?
We're looking at red
blue
We have we have we have vowels as an eye
Okay, okay said it was red you said yes vowels red I thought it was I thought it was a blue blue
Okay, I thought that was a one. No, no
red red
blue blue
Red red yellow
blue blue green
Red red yellow blue
Blue blue green red
yellow
Uh red blue blue red yellow blue yellow
Stop talking like that. You fuck them up. I'm trying to give you that again
Red red yellow blue yellow
So blue blue green red green
blue blue red
That wasn't red
Okay. Now I have a strike fine. Fuck whatever. Okay, so now we're looking at
red red yellow blue yellow
yellow yellow red green red
Got it. Okay coming up next. We've got uh the word thing like see who what don't uh-huh
Uh-huh. We're good. Okay. So first one is see two e's I see you. Okay, so uh bottom right
Uh-huh with a space on space, huh?
Uh-huh. Okay, so we're looking at uh, oh actually I gotta ask you
Uh, it's the uh-huh with h u h or just uh, uh space h u h. Uh-huh
Okay, so we're looking at uh-huh as in the word. Uh, huh
Your possessive you are with a space in between okay
Are you way on the right page here?
Wait, like your or with a space possessive as in like your
Like you are if you're asking that many questions, it can't be it
Okay, so uh-huh you you are do you have you are with a space in between no, okay
Uh, do you have you no done hold?
Uh, uh, no do it start over once. Uh, we have two strikes by the way. Oh god
There's no we're not doing this. We're not doing this one. Whatever
Where's nothing two strikes worth nothing. Yeah, middle left middle left done. Uh
Done done done. Uh, shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Okay. Sure. Uh-huh
Next what your possessive you're as in you are
There as in they are there, okay, but it's with the apostrophe left left left bottom left next
Uh, shit, what with a question mark? Uh-huh
Uh, uh your possessive hold sure final word coming up is yes
Yes, okay. Uh, we're looking at how many seconds we have left. Um
Plenty you sure might as well. Uh restart it. Well, no, no, no, we can do this. Yeah. The word is yes
Yes, the word is is dead dead. I pressed it. Shit. This is the wall. We got we got this wall here
We'll get it. You know what with five modules in five minutes, we've got to be doing one module per minute
We gotta get bang bang bang. We just have to be tight man. We have to be tight about this
We gotta be tighter than dick skin on this one. Ew. Okay. Here we go. Ready?
Morse code, okay
Morse code. All right. Here we go
Uh, so what are we looking at here? We are looking at first first letter just be like dot dot dash dash dot dot like in comma
Remember the commas
dot dot dot
so s
What's the second? What's the second letter? The second letter is okay. So we have
We have
so
Dash
It's dash
Yes, the dash. Okay, so st
Yeah, it's uh
Fuck we need a third letter. Fuck. We need a third letter. We need to check third letter. We have to check third letter
Okay. All right. All right
Hold on. Just a dot. It's dot
three five eight two
Three five eight. Yep. All right. All right. All right, right
Okay, uh, we have just the symbols like omega symbol a and all that shit. Okay, so we got let's kick some ass
Let's kick some ass. All right. Here we go. So, uh, read them real quick. We have a e stitches trident upside down nine
Upside down. Okay, so we're gonna go upside down nine
And then you're gonna go stitches
Okay, uh, do we have a vowel uh, we do
We have a vowel. Yes
We have a vowel. Okay, uh, so uh remedies green
yellow
Green yellow
Yellow green green yellow green
yellow green yellow
green yellow green green
Yellow green yellow green
That's not correct. I got it. Okay. Oh green. Okay green yellow green green green
So, uh yellow green
Yellow it's just in the reverse order. It's yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we got it. We got it. We're good. We're good. We're good
Okay now now we need we have uh, the number of bucks box and the number in it
The number is four sequence thing press the first in the fourth position fourth position. Okay in the fourth position
Mm-hmm three, uh press the button in the first position
One press the button with the same label as the person stage two
Okay
Four press the button in the same position as the person stage two same position and stage two same position in stage two
I think it was the second. I think it was second or third second or first, please don't mess this up
It was the first
Got it. Okay. I don't know. Yep. It was first three
Press the press the same press the button with the same label as the person stage four stage four same label same label three
It was no it was three. It was three
Okay, finally finally horizontal wires with the abc one two three. Okay. Okay. Hang on. I'm almost ready. I'm almost ready
Okay, so, uh, what are we looking at red blue black red goes to c
Okay, cut cut cut red blue goes to c
Skip that one black goes to b
Okay, cut that next. Yes. Okay. We have uh red black black red goes to a uh
Uh, does the second one go to b? Yes
Uh skip that one and uh the third one
Skip this one skip the one go to the next one. Okay, we have two black wires
Okay, uh, first one goes to c
Okay, uh the third go to a no third one goes to b two black wires third one goes to b skip that
Okay, it's a fourth fourth one goes that's go to c. It's all three
Okay, skip this one. Skip this one. Fuck it. Last one is to c black wire in the middle to c
How many seconds we're left point two eight. Oh god
I don't know if I fucking nerves can take this point point two eight, uh, three tenths of a second
Holy shit
That was um, that was a
That was tricky, you know, you know what you just fucking did
Jerma wild guest until I got it, right you you you made a hollywood move like you did some sort of like
Hollywood shit where you're like you're sweating sweat coming on your face. You're like what fucking wire is it?
Just fucking rip them all out, you know
Oh
That was wild. Hey, we beat we beat the gear check though
No, that's true
So what are we looking at now? Uh, that's why that's that's why that's the gear check because the next one
Uh is also five modules, but here's the difference
It's two minutes and 30 seconds instead of five minutes
uh, so the exact same thing we just did but
we have
50 we have a full 50 percent less time
I wonder how the modules i'll tell you i'll tell you what though
Before we do that one
Can we do another practice round by ie instead of doing the mission here?
How about we do a free play and we clock up the time a little bit or something like that not a bad idea
Because I feel like if we're gonna tackle a challenge like that. We need a little bit
You know extra
That's too much. Um, what do these mean? Well people saying it's easier. Let me see. Um, oh, it's easier modules
It's not hard modules. Apparently apparently it's like a bunch of really easy ones
Yeah, they say it's not it's not hard ones. It's easy modules
Okay, well I think we can do that one I think we can do that one see if it just simon says shit fine
But when it comes down to like the wire ones the horizontal wires the occurrences fuck me up
the occurrences fuck me up because uh
Basically, i'm unsure of myself because I have to do
Definitive answers. I can't just say eh and I have to be like, okay
What was it what was it and I have to just like manually think you know
So actually hilarious that it took us about an hour and a half to do the first two or three missions in the game
And it's been two hours
and we have done
What like eight missions? Well, uh, you know, I think we found what I really
Uh, yeah, I think I think me being the the reading man
Are you being the fucking cowboy here with the bruce willis the bomb defusal shit? Yes
I think I think it works. All right, you ready to try this one five modules two minutes 30 seconds. All right
I'm ready. Okay. Hopefully they're easy. Okay
Regular wires there are six regular wires. How many do we have? It's six wires six wires. It's sick
It's mcdonald's so it's four red two yellow
Yellow is in the first slot red is in the last one. How many yellow do we have?
We have two yellows. The first wire is yellow. The last wire is red four red two yellow
So we have okay, uh
Otherwise, if there are no red wire cut the fourth wire fourth wire
Okay, uh, we got pac-man pac-man. All right. So what are we looking at?
Uh these the two circles circle one is a five
Circle two is c2
I have spawned in c4
And the goal is in a3 right right like oh go like go right. Okay. I thought you were like right
Okay, so I went right once I went right once
Okay up
Right. Yep. Up up left left left. Yep down down. Yep left
Uh symbol omega ball sack, you know the three. Okay. Yeah, I got it. Okay. So what we're looking at ball sack sleepy three
Unfilled star and us and a swoosh. Hey, if you mean swoosh do you mean infogrames? I don't know. Yes
That's a swoosh. Okay. Uh, it's like a it's like a swoosh. Yep. Yeah. I got it ball sack swoosh. Yep
uh
Sleepy three
Okay, uh, we now have two buttons and that's it one. They're both blue
One button says hold one button says press both blue buttons. Okay. Do we have any batteries? Yes
There are three batteries. Okay. Uh
None of this is fuck. We're just gonna do a cowboy shit on this one. Just hold it down
Okay, we have blue blinking four in a position
Fuck, okay blue button again. Okay. Hold on. Okay blue blue blue blinking
We're in the position four in the position four in the position
We did it. I was trying to save us like two seconds
What the fuck you can't do that
I was trying to save us a second and catch it on the tenth of a second like you almost saved us save our skeletons out
of our fucking
Skin, I was trying to do like the f1.4. That would have been so cool
People would have thought I was awesome. People would have thought I was awesome if I did
Yeah, we got a first try
jerma, have you ever drank mug before
mug
It's a root beer mug root beer. Yeah, I've had I've had what do you think of it?
I think it's the best root beer, but you can't find it anywhere. They don't sell it anywhere
Really? Yeah, I love serious. I love mug root beer. They don't sell it anywhere
oh because a lot of people say that mug is a really bad tasting root beer compared to like uh
Berries or no, it's like some other like franks barks barks barks barks. Yes barks is good, too
I love okay, but but bark is better barks is better than mug, but I like mug
But I can't buy it anywhere because they don't sell it anymore
how about this jerma at some point in the future, would you like a
Culinary snack exchange because I would die for some mug
Don't ask me why but if I send you weird swedish weird shit brands that you cannot get in america
Yeah, would I be able to get bostonian root beer? Um, yeah if you knew somebody that currently lived in boston
Oh, yeah, you you want to be living like you want anything from las vegas?
Uh, what do you have in las vegas? They have like elvis cola or something like that elvis cola. Yeah copyright elvis cola
I don't know. I fucking don't live there elvis elvis cola
Um, yeah, I can send you some sprite. Do you like sprite? You have sprite over there?
bitch
I've never drank that one before do you have sprite in sweden?
Yes, jerma. We have sprite here. All right. What about uh, what do you guys have?
You guys got arby's you got arby's in sweden
Arby, no, no, well, I'll send you a double meat turkey sandwich. I'll send you a double meat turkey sandwich extra mayo
How about how about this? Um
You send me that I will eat it on stream in for one. Okay, well on one condition, right?
I'll do it but on one condition I get to send you
Swedish fish
Yeah, I don't I can't get those if you know if you know anything about arby's every sandwich i've ever had from arby's
I've only had a few it's like somebody while the sandwich is in the wrapper
Put as much meat as much condiments on it as possible and then rolled it out with a fucking rolling pin
Jerma, can you explain hooters to me?
um
You don't have those
No
Uh, it's a restaurant where it's it's a it's a restaurant that's based around can you say yes or no to this?
Hooters is a strip club that serves you spaghetti. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No
So what is the restaurant that okay? It's it's known for
They're and they're by the way, they're changing their name and their whole approach
They're changing it to like hoots now
Uh, it's now gonna be hoots
I've from what i've been told and they're going to change it
It's not they're not gonna have like the girls in the in like the hooters out like shirts and like sneakers and stuff
Okay
Uh, who told you this?
it's i'm just curious because uh
You know, I I see these american brands and i'm thinking what do americans think?
Okay, now that we played american football my good friend
Let us hit up hooters and eat some chicken wings with buffalo sauce my good friend
Well, I mean that's that's kind of like a cartoon way to look at an american
uh, but no, no, no
We roll our sandwiches out with rolling pins and um, and then we eat them covered in mayonnaise. So it's not wrong
It's that's wrong
That is wrong. I I
Uh, I don't go to hooters. In fact, they're closing them. No, they're closing them all down
Okay. Well, what is what is your favorite? Uh chain restaurant in america? I'm asking this for for cultural
Culinary knowledge exchange. That's not that's not funny in america best fast food in america. Uh, I don't know
I I love mcdonald's I really do
I actually really love mcdonald's. What's what's your favorite thing at mcdonald's? Uh, that's simple mcchicken
Just a plain just a plain mcchicken
Or hot or mcdoubles the mcdoubles is the fuck. How do you how do you feel? How do you feel about those sesame seed?
Uh regular cheeseburgers the small ones for like a dollar sure. Yeah
Okay, here's the thing. Those are less than a dollar sometimes when I buy games on steam on stream stuff like that
And it's a waste. It's a waste time and whatever I equate my losses in what how many cheeseburgers could have gotten at mcdonald's
Versus buying this game. So standard mcdonald's cheeseburger is like probably the best one. Yeah for sure
Well, why the fuck are we talking about? We should be solving. Sorry. Well, it's a nice little segue mcdonald's is I guess but it's good
But i'll tell you what i'll tell you what, um, what is the worst place to go if you're hungry on a fast food situation
Burger king is terrible. Really burger king is dog shit like taco bell. Somebody said taco bell
Taco bell is like one of my favorite places but burger king sucks
Doesn't burger king have that like, you know, they had a commercial with return of the mac, you know burger king mac and cheetos
Whatever. Um, yeah, but you eat one and then you go
That was kind of good and you eat a second one and you go
I don't want these ever again and you don't order them ever again burger king has this thing where they make a menu item
That you will order once and never fucking order ever again. It's half their menu
I got like the chicken cheetos
The chicken fries the cheetos fries the cheese the mac and cheese bombs you eat it once and you never fucking order it again
Half the menu goes uneaten germa germa. I just thought of something amazing
I've been talking about something on stream for years hard attack grill. You live in vegas now
Yes, do you know about this do you weigh over 350 pounds do I sound like I do I don't know
No, if you eat if you weigh over 350 pounds
You eat everything for free at the hard attack grill in las vegas
It is free germa your meal is have you ever been there? Have you ever been there?
I have never been to I have walked by it many times, but I have never been inside the restaurant
I'll tell you what i'll tell you what
Uh, this is this is a question you come to vegas you want you want to get weighed and go to the hard attack grill
No, no, this is a question more for germa's chat right now. I i'm out i'm reading my chat right now
But i'll ask you guys a question
Would it not be the best thing ever to see germa?
Just go and eat at a hard attack grill put him in one of those like surgical dresses and just like
Eat onion rings until he has a coma, you know, I can eat I can eat a lot though
That's the thing people get surprised whenever they whenever I eat food around people. Okay, mr
Big shove i'll tell you what let's put your your your your money where your mouth is
Let's head down to hard attack grill and let's obliterate
15 plates of fries and let's see who truly is a gamer you ready?
Maybe not now, but I at some point I can eat a lot of food. I can eat a lot of food
I told you my order everybody everybody in my chat knows the order
They know my order and they think it's a joke and i've told it's
A big mac number one like two mcchickens and two double cheeseburgers and I eat it every time in a large fry and a large soda
And the large soda. Yes an extra dip extra dip. Anyway
Don't worry about it. Anyway, my point being i'll tell you what do you want to do?
Uh a wager here. Do you want to do a little bet? You don't want to do this?
I'm telling you i'm just trying to be honest with you. Don't want to do this. You really don't know
Germa germa, how about this here's a proposal you made the friends of mine call me friends of mine call me the bird
Because they can't understand how I eat like six times my body weight
They're like you fucking bird and I i'm like what are you talking about?
I I I just pictured you like vomiting into your friend's mouth after you've been eating so much
I don't know why the fuck whatever the point being I have a bet for you. I have a bet for you
Okay, uh, i'll hear it and you may decline and there's nothing nothing bad about it
That if we can solve the next bomb even though we've been challenged at this
You will at some point as a joke or whatever it is go to heart attack grill
You don't have to overeat just go there and be like
Just be a patron of the heart attack grill just show them the world
Do I have to stream going to the heart attack grill?
No, you can film it or do whatever you want just just to be like I have the privilege of living in in elvist town
And now i'm having an elvis burger, you know, what would you like to do this?
Here's the thing though his thing if we fuck up, there's no need to do this
But if we win, but if we take his ass and eat if we win or how about this?
This sounds like a losing scenario. Like if you lose you have to do this. Okay. Well, okay
But here's the thing we are guaranteed to lose i'm saying if by some chance we and we have to play
Okay, but if we win you have to just eat an elvis burger
All right, if we win i'm gonna try as hard as I can. I'm not I will actually okay
If we win, okay
I will go to the heart attack grill and I will I will have a photo of me taken in this restaurant with a hamburger in my face
And i'll it'll be like here. I'm eating a hamburger. It's here. I'm eating a hamburger at a restaurant
Okay, we have to we have to do it first
Okay, but uh, what patient are we on? We are on no room for error. We have one strike and it's over. All right
So if we so I get it if we lose it's over
We win oh mama if we win I go I take a photo of eating the hamburger. Whoa, what do you do?
There you go. You ready? Mm-hmm. We have regular wires. There's six regular wires. How many how many how many six wires?
Two white two red
It's the serial number odd. It's the serial number odd
It's the serial number odd the serial number is even the lat you talk about talking about the last number, right?
Mm-hmm. Yes, it's even okay. It's even so is there except no there was no yellow wires
You said no yellow wires. The two white wires are in the top and bottom position. Okay, uh,
Oh, they're no red. But okay
There are two reds fourth wire fourth wire cut the four wire
Okay, another same thing another just regular wires three of them white blue and red in that order. Okay, uh,
cut the last wire we have uh symbols just you know, like the
Omega ball sack whatever it was. All right. Okay. Okay. We um, i'm ball second. Okay upside down
So what what what what upside down nine a e
The h that looks kind of like an n and a trident. It's a ball
We have we don't know. There's no no omega ball sack in this one. It's just okay
Upside down nine a e trident upside down nine upside down nine. Yeah, and then you want to go, uh,
uh
ae
Yeah trident. Okay. Uh, okay, uh there it's the word with the u. Uh, huh
Oh what huh gotcha gotcha word is we're going to go there. We're gonna go there like a place
Okay. Oh, I see. Okay bottom right read me bottom right is what?
What with a question mark you hold like why oh you okay?
Yes, you why oh you you you did this? Okay. Hey middle, right?
Like I like this that's a lie. Well, I mean I maybe you know anyway, uh like let me see here like like
You're with an apostrophe next like like like what like you are like you are going. Yes with an apostrophe. Yes
last word is
c
ce
Not se ce
Got it bottom right one first left. Okay. Yes
middle no
right
Nothing, uh h h h
Okay, we have one more it's it's the the number sequence thing with the the you know
There's a thing in the box the numbers and we'll see once we got it
We got the number is two press the button in the second position. Okay reverse two
Press the button in the same position as you press in stage one. Okay. The number is one
Press the button with the same label as you pressed in stage two
Okay numbers two press the button in the first position number is four
Press the button with the same label you pressed in stage three
Same label that's pressed in stage three
Fucking lights were off
Press the button with the same label that's pressed in stage three
Lights were off. I didn't see it lights were off. You didn't lose some purpose. Did you? No, I didn't I actually really didn't
I when you said first the first position and the lights were off and I just pressed it
Why three you want to double down this? Oh, all right. Fine. Let's double down
If we get it right this time
Then I will not only will I eat the cheeseburger, but I'll have to be I'll be smiling in the photo
Okay, that sounds great
wires
Okay, what are we looking at?
Six wires. We have uh, two blue two black a yellow and a red no white wires six of them
We have one yellow wire said there's only one yellow wire. It's the first wire
Uh, do we have any white wires? No
Cut the fourth wire on this one
Okay, uh omega symbol stuff
All right. What are we looking at trident?
upside down tb
a
backwards p and then a
c with a dot in the middle
Okay, we're gonna be looking at uh
trident
Okay tb
Yeah c
Okay backwards p
All right, uh wires again. This is regular wires. Okay, three wires. All right
we have
Uh blue white and black in that order three wires. No yellow wires. Just three wires. There are no red wires
There are no red no red no yellow the second wire cut the second wire. Okay you you're sure. Uh-huh
You got it. There is no word
bottom left
Uh-huh. Uh space, huh? Uh space, huh?
Uh-huh
That was not okay
Same word as an uh-huh, but you don't have that do you? No
Okay, so
Uh-huh. So the the words would be
Uh huh your with an r as in you're like possessive
Uh, I did y-o-u y-o-u-r
It was y-o-u-r, right?
Like your it was u h h u h
U h space h u h and then you said the word what you said one of the words was y-o-u-r is your
All right, triple down
I'll eat the burger. I'll smile and i'll fucking be winking too
All right, but no more than that if we fuck this up
boom
Nothing remains
We have a a red button that says press
Red button that says press
Uh, let's see here. Uh
There are no batteries on this bomb red
Press no batteries
hold down
Okay white flashing light
One in any position one in any position
Okay
Uh you your nothing blank middle ready. No
first word no
Bring me bottom right
Right as in i'm gonna take a right
Okay
We will be looking at
Yes
Nothing ready got nothing press
No, okay. Good. Very good. Excellent work. Next one is c e e c c e e
Read me bottom right
old
You are spacing between there. Okay. Got it
The last word is spelled out. Okay. Okay a y letters. Yep four letters
Read me top right
The top right is also okay four letters
middle
No
First yes
Uh three h's okay. We've uh, we've got some we have a number sequence here
The thing with the oh it is four and then we're so let me let me
Okay, here we go. First first one is four
Press the button in the fourth position
four again
Press the button the same position as it pressed in stage one. Okay
two
Press the button with the same label you press in stage one
Okay three
Press the button in the same position as it pressed in stage two
I'm so bad with those ones
I'm so bad with like the position and the label and remembering like three times ago
Jerma, here's the thing and I know I said the last one but this is poetic
This is poetic. You know why?
Because at the heart attack rail, there's something called the quadruple bypass
This will be the fourth one
The number is one. Okay. The number is one
Uh press the button in the second position
four
Press the button the same position as a person stage one
One press the button with the same label you pressed in stage two
One don't fuck up. It was one gotcha four
Press the button in the same position as you pressed in stage two
It's fucking the ding ding the ding ding the ding ding the ding ding the ding ding the ding ding ding ding
It's this one
Don't fuck up. I can't I can't I hate that. I can't
I can't do that one
No, do it again. I'll leave four quadruple bypass surgeries
Okay, okay, it's your death four
Press the button the fourth position
Four press the button the same position as you press on stage one
Two press the button with the same label you pressed in stage one the same label in stage one
I was remembering though. I was remembering the last number I was remembering the last number
I can't I know I can i'm gonna be all right
two
Press the button in the first position
Four press the button with the same label as you press the stage three here that was
It was three or one. It was three or one
Three. Yep. Good. Good. Good. Good. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Uh, it's uh, say the word it's words you there. Wait first, huh? Who?
Okay, hang on. I'm getting ready. I'm getting ready. All right. So what we're looking at?
L-e-e-d lead l-e-e-d bottom left bottom left right i'm taking a right in the car
R
Yes, nothing ready. Nothing press
No, oh, yep. That's the one half
Lead again, but this is l-e-a-d
Or lead lead lead. Okay bottom right read me bottom, right?
Uh your like as in that's gonna be yours your it's your thing
u-h-u-h
u space r
u-h space h-u-h got it. Okay
Final word is l-e-d an l-e-d light
Lead l-e-d middle left middle left is your thing yours your
Okay, it's a possessive. Yes
u-h-u-h
y-o-u space
r
u-h space h-u-h
Got it y-o-u-r
That one's done. Okay. Now we just have uh, we have a blue button that says detonate on it blue button detonate
Watch that. Hang on and there are three batteries on this
So one of one battery and the bottom says it says detonate. Yes, it says detonate. It is blue
Okay, and there's more than one battery. Yep. There are three batteries
Pressing immediately at least the bottom
Okay, we got wires regular wires. All right. Okay these wires there are five of them
And they go as follows. There are two white
one red
One yellow and one blue
Okay, uh
There are no black wires. No, there are not
Cut the first wire
Well, we exploded
What happened?
That was my fault. That was my fault. Listen
That was my fault
Tell you what tell you what tell you what tell you what
I will up the stakes on this one, too. Oh, no, we'll still eat a quadruple burger
But do I have to keep eating four of those? I can't eat four of those that I just said that out of anger
Well, okay. How about this? How about this? I have a proposal you go to heart attack real
Those are 3500 calories each
No, no, no, you don't have to eat that because there's blood on my hands now. Here's what I propose, right? Hear me out
You go to heart attack grill you order whatever you want
But you take a photo and you give a thumbs up or whatever
Preferably from the onion ring in your mouth or some stupid shit like that. Sure. Like I
I'm funny. I will eat I
I will eat a raw egg on string. No, that's bad for you. Don't do that
No, no, it's fine. It's fine. People do that shit all the time
Raw egg on stream. No, you don't eat raw eggs. You don't eat it. Don't eat a raw egg
Okay, good that you agree on this jerma now. Let's do the next level and do this. Let's go eat one full cooked egg
Okay, jerma, I agree on that
Is he gonna eat a raw egg on stream if I do this you do? Wait, are you even on stream?
Okay, jerma, let's play the level. Why am I getting a recording? I've called within business hours
Okay, we have
uh wires
Okay, there are four wires
Okay, uh
Two more than one red wire. It's the more than one. Yes. There is two red one black the last
serial number odd
Yes
Cut the last red wire the last red wire. Okay. We have another set of wires. Just regular wires. There are six
Okay
six
Okay, are there any yellow wires? There are two yellow wires
Okay, there are also two blue wires
One red and one black
Are there no red wires? There is one red wire
Cut the fourth wire
We have a number sequence here of my favorite
The number is three
Press the button in the third position
two
Press the button in the same position as you press the stage one
three
Press the button in the third position
Press the button in the same position as you pressed in stage two
and finally four
Press the button with the same label you pressed in stage three
Now i'm gonna ask you chat
Was was that on me?
Was it on germa? No, I I there were all three
What when did I press something? It was three. It was three like three times
Okay, I i've deducted something
Our weakness and strength we are you are
platinum
at the password
But the memory thing it's not even memory. It's remembering
So it's four numbers that you have to remember out of order and then like the position in the labels
I can't do it
I ate captain crunch every day when I was like from eight to fucking 14
So like I don't have the capability to remember that shit germa. What what did you just say?
It's not memory. It's
It's what?
Quote say that again
No, I I can remember lots of things. I remember I could I remember
You said you said
It's not memory. It's remembering
No, it's not memory dot dot dot dot end quote new quote new quote
new quote
It's about remembering the seek that's remembering. Whatever. Let's go. Let's let's do i'll eat fucking two eggs
Let's go i'll shove a hamburger into my underwear. All right, fuck it. Here we go
wires
Okay, here we go. Uh six wires
Okay, here we go. Let's do this one
All right, here we go. All right, so we read wires his head six wires three red wires
It's the last day to the serial number odd
Uh
No, it's even
It's an even number six wires even number. Are you sure it's an even number?
Look
Look look look two. Oh, yes. Okay. I just wanted to make sure okay
There are no yellow wires and the last date of the serial number is odd to cut the third wire
Which you're not going to do. No, there are six wires and there's one white three red. Exactly. There's no yellow wires
Okay
uh
The cut the fourth wire number sequence. Oh boy
I did these so good the first like hour we played. I don't know. I lost getting tired
I need to eat a fucking ball with captain crunch numbers. Well, are we doing three four two?
What what are we looking at? The number is three
Press the button in the third position
Third position is the number one third. Okay one
three
Press the button in the first position
Would it help if you wrote this down? Maybe I don't know one. I can't write shit down
The number is the button with the same label you press in stage two the same label and press the stage two
I'm already gone. I already don't know because we started I said something
Ask chat ask chat. Hey guys
Did you see me holding the finger out? All right, the number is four
If the display is four press the button the same position is appraised in stage two and that would be position number
Two make a mistake here now
Don't listen. Listen, it's very vital mod has to tell that mod has helped me
Um, I can't do i'm i'm i'm checked out for some reason my brain can't do it as one
Listen clear thoughts. It's easy. Okay. All right, relax. I know it's hard
Last number is two
You have I look at your chat same label you press
Press the button with the same label you press in stage two and that would be the stage was stage two was was here
That that's another that's one. That's one. That's one. I know that I know that one already. Okay, i'm good
I'm good. Somebody said great value brand memory
And i'm upset with that person but i'm and that was they were from your chat. So you got to get on that
All right symbols symbols symbols like the omega balls
Okay, here we go. Uh mirrored k
Octopus with a spear smiley face with a tongue ring and upside down nine
do
let's see here, uh
six
What do you know? I stopped paying what i spot spider with spear?
Yep
Uh weird x
Okay, smiley we have uh a there you your huh? Uh-huh
Okay, here we go. It's there yours like because like yours possessive like there like there read me middle right like
Okay, sorry. I'm wasting time here. But uh
Your s n with an apostrophe u apostrophe r next letter u
next yet next
Okay. Yes next. Okay
Red red
Okay, here we go. Uh
Middle right. Okay with four letters spelled out. Okay
Okay, uh middle no first. Yes
I thought it exploded my heart just exploded
All right. Uh, last is the last one is the letter c just the letter c top right read me top right
Yo, you you you are you you did it. No, no, no, no, no. Why are you just just you you?
Okay, sure u space r
Why oh you are?
Okay, like just what like why oh you are like your
Yes
Okay, good
Okay, we have six we have six wires
Six wires regular wires. Okay, two red
Two red two yellow two blue no white no black
two
Yellow cut the fourth wire cut the fourth wire
I'm eating too big. I have to shove a hamburger in my underwear
You know what? The worst thing is that was like the easiest one, but just because the stakes were so fucking high
It was the worst one like my my heart did not skip up like it was just like
And then it just stopped and now it can like pump blood again
You're maligned about a hamburger in underwear
I'm glad you're already writing that
Because it's definitely not gonna happen
You know the worst thing about um, so I had a physics when I was doing the password thing. I wrote these down
Somebody's gonna like find me one of these days. I go through my notes and be like my god. He was insane
There's nothing makes sense. There's like spiders with spears and there's ball sacks and it's
F you you you you you you pp pp pp q q q q like
Yeah
Thomas
jerma
Holy shit. I'm just gonna ask you something but
I am really drained after all that
Would you like to take a small break? You want to take a pee break?
Yeah, all right
I I need uh
We do have one more, this is like the boss coming up here.
Okay, let's clear for the night.
But first of all, I need to take this like damn burst, right?
Yeah, let's take like a few minute break.
We'll come back and we'll beat the boss.
Okay.
All right.
I'm back.
Oh wow, perfect timing.
That was, we must've been completely on cue.
Our PP is in sync.
That was kind of strange actually.
Odd.
Anyway, let us do this last one, man.
Let's see if we can do it.
This one's the big one.
This is the big one.
All right.
This is eight minutes.
We have eight modules and it's gonna take eight minutes.
It says, take your time, relax.
Then it says, don't relax.
If we can do this in one minute each, no problem.
The bomb tend to stream.
There's no stakes here.
It's just a matter of,
can we clear this monstrosity, you know?
All right, if we beat this,
if we beat this first try,
then all we have to do is when you visit Las Vegas,
we have to take a picture
in front of like the Bellagio fountain.
You're cutting out what?
I said, okay, if we do this one first try,
then when you come to Vegas,
all we have to do is take a picture
in front of the Bellagio fountain.
The Bellagio fountain, what?
Yeah, it's like a tourist place.
There's a big, big, big connotation here.
When I come?
Yeah.
You don't wanna come?
I'd love to come.
There he's going.
But, but, but, all right, okay, I was,
okay, yeah, I'll go to the fountain, man.
You gotta beat the first try, though.
All right, yeah, absolutely, absolutely, man.
Yeah, I'm brockin' raw McDonald's.
Eight modules, let's go.
We have Morse code.
Morse code, all right, let's see here.
We gotta quickly do this.
Let's not fuck around for this one.
All right, so the first letter is,
let me, you know, the usual shit.
Usual shit, okay.
And he's like dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, dash.
So dot, dot, dot, dot, dash.
So the first one, dot, dot, dot, comma, dot, dash.
No, it can't be that.
Then it would be sa, sa.
I don't have any sas, do I?
No, that can't be right, man.
Is that a correct call?
No.
Dot, dot, dot, dot, dash, dot, dot, okay.
Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, dash, dot, dot.
So dot, dot, dot, comma, dot, dash, dot, dot.
Dot, dot, dot, comma, dot, dash, dot, dot.
It's three, five, two, two.
All right, we have the horizontal cut the wires thing.
We're gonna do this twice in a row.
Complicated bullshit.
Complicated bullshit, we have plenty of time to do this,
but we're gonna do this two of them.
Okay, let's go, here we go.
So what are we lookin' at?
Two blue wires, blue, blue, both going into A.
Those two go to A.
Yes.
Cut that one.
Cut it?
Next one.
Okay, we have another blue wire.
This one is going to A in the third slot.
Okay, is there any more wires on this one?
It's only blue.
Skip to the next round.
Okay, so this would be the fourth and fifth blue wire here,
so blue, blue, red.
So what current is on the red wire here, sorry.
The red wire is, yeah, this red is first,
and it goes to C.
Cut that one.
Okay, we also have the fourth and fifth blue wires,
both are going to A.
So fourth is going to A.
Yes.
Cut that one.
Okay.
And this is the fifth one, and it's going to where?
A.
Next round.
So we have a sixth blue wire here, it's the last one,
but we also have a black and red wire.
Black is first, it's going to C.
Cut the blue wire.
Is that it?
What occurrence is the red wire at?
The red wire is second, and it is going to A.
Okay, don't bother with it.
And the black one is at?
It's going to C.
First spot.
Okay, and the current is first ever.
That's the first ever black wire, yes.
Cut the black wire.
Done?
Next one, next one.
Okay, that's it.
All right, next one.
Same deal, we're gonna start it over.
Completely fresh, same module.
Whenever you see the first ever,
just cut the black one.
Okay, so we have black, black, blue.
Yep, cut that one, cut the first one.
Cut the first black wire?
Okay, now we have a black wire going from two to B.
Don't bother with that.
Blue?
Blue, yes, going to A.
Don't cut that one, next one.
This is the third and fourth black wire.
Only black wires, there's two of them.
One is going to C, one's going to B.
Skip the first one,
and this will be the fourth one, right?
This would be the fourth one going to B.
Okay, skip that one too.
Okay, only one wire on this one.
It is red, it's going to A.
And that will be our first one too.
That will be, that's the first red wire.
Yes, that's correct.
Okay, and that's going to?
A.
Okay, the last panel here is the fifth and sixth black wire
and then a blue wire.
So it's black, black, blue, fifth and sixth black wire.
Blue is going to B.
Is sixth going to B?
The last black, yes, it's going to B.
Cut that one.
Okay.
And the blue one was the first one we had.
The blue one is, the first wire here is black going to A.
The blue wire here is the third one going to B.
Okay, and it's going to B.
Yes, and this is, by the way,
this is the second blue wire.
So the last one is blue, cut that one.
Last one is blue.
That was incorrect, but it's okay.
Just go, just go, man.
That's it, all right, all right, Simon says.
Okay, Simon says, all right, here we go.
We have one strike, we have one strike.
One strike, vowel.
And there is a vowel.
We have a vowel and one strike.
Okay, colors.
What the fuck, I thought I wasn't even clicking on the,
you have two strikes now, sir.
I didn't know I was in the module.
Two strikes.
Whatever.
Yellow.
Let's go, blue.
Yellow, blue.
Red.
Yellow, blue, red.
That will be blue, red, green.
Yellow, blue, red, red.
Blue, red, green, green.
Okay, next one.
Now we've got a, we just got regular wires.
There are three wires.
Okay.
Two white, one yellow, that's it, three wires.
Are there no red wires?
No red wires.
Cut the second wire.
Okay, we have a white detonate button.
Okay, hang on, hang on.
There are more, there are two batteries.
Press and immediately release the bomb.
Press and immediately release.
Okay, we have Pac-Man.
Pac-Man, the circles, by the way, are A2 and F3.
And then we start in A2, and we are going to B5.
Okay, go up, right, right.
Yep.
Down.
Left, down.
Yep.
Right.
Down.
Yep.
Right.
Oh shit, I'm sorry.
Left, up, left.
Left, up.
Yep.
Up, right.
Up.
Left, left, left.
All the way to the bottom.
Okay, we got up.
Oh.
How many models do we have left?
One after that, and it was the symbols.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I was supposed to go guess.
It could have been good.
Oh, that was close.
That was so close.
I got confused there for a second.
No, I fucking, no, it was because when I clicked,
I thought I wasn't clicked in a module,
and I made it speed up faster.
I was like trying to click into the module,
and I thought I was already in there.
All right, let's go, let's go, we got it.
That was, you know, possibilities are there, you know.
We're good, we almost had it, first try.
Too bad you're not coming to make it.
Okay, we got a word, just a jumbler thing.
Okay, first one, what do we have?
B-R-G-C-I-E.
B-R-J-C.
C-I-G.
Okay, second ones.
Yeah, B-R-G-C-I-E.
Second one is V-U-P-K-M-I-V.
Let's see, I got it, that's right.
Okay, Pac-Man, Pac-Man.
Okay, we got Pac-Man, Pac-Man, let's all fuck this up.
Okay, so what do we got?
The circles are in A-2 and F-3.
Starting position is F-2.
The goal is A-5.
Okay, so down, left, left, down, left,
left, right, all the way left, spam down.
Okay, U, okay, blank, first, uh-huh, there.
Okay, so what word is it?
The word is read, R-E-E-D, two E's, read.
Bottom left, read me that one.
Right, R-I-G-H-T, like taking a right.
Yes, nothing, ready, press, no.
You're gonna have to say this again,
you're gonna have to say it again
because the lights turned off.
Okay, yes, nothing, ready, press, no.
No, okay. Wait.
Wait, that's not right, that's not right.
Okay, no, okay, restart, we have one strike, restart.
Says?
The word is says, S-A-Y-S, S-A-Y-S, says.
Bottom right, bottom right, bottom right.
What?
With a question mark or regular one.
Like what, what with a question mark?
You hold your apostrophe.
Like you are, like your apostrophe, like your.
Let me see here, just to double check, it's you,
yeah, it's apostrophe.
Okay, good, next word we've got is display,
like a monitor, display.
Bottom right.
Hold.
Hold, we are looking at you are with a space in between.
Letter U.
Last letter, last word is with spaces, they space R,
they are with a space, they space R.
Middle left.
Is uh with three H's, uh.
Ready, nothing, left, what, okay.
What with a, just no question mark, just what?
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, okay, we have Morse code.
Okay, here we go.
Dot, dot, dot, comma, dash, comma, dot, okay.
Repeat, second one, second one.
Dot, dot, dot, dot, comma, then dash.
Okay, the word is, I need a third one,
I need a third one, I need a third one.
Okay, hold on, dot, dash, dot.
Dot, dash, dot, three, it's three.
It's three, five, four, five.
Okay, symbols, omega, copyright, okay.
Okay, copyright, omega.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, reset.
We have copyright, we have copyright,
sleepy three, star that doesn't have a failed end
and mirrored K.
Stop, what are you eating, what are you eating?
Sorry, it's developed.
Copyright, sleepy three, star with no filling
and mirrored K.
Copyright, then we'll be looking at the weird X.
Sleepy three.
Okay, we have a red button that says abort.
Okay, hang on, hang on.
By the way, there are three batteries.
Red button, abort.
Lit indicator with FRK?
Lit indicator with FRK on it.
There is no lit indicator with FRK on it.
Hold it down, hold it down, hold it down.
Holding it down, we have white flashes.
One in any position, one in any position.
Okay, we have regular wires here, regular wires.
We have five, two red, one white, blue and black.
Five wires.
No black wires?
There's one black wire, it's the last one.
But the first wire.
But the first wire, that's not correct.
Shit.
We have five wires, two red, one white,
one blue, one black.
Cut the third wire.
The third wire, look at that.
Fuck, I took a chance.
I took a chance, I don't wanna speak.
Basically, I had a chance there to go, oh my God.
Shit, that was close.
I did such a bad mistake there.
Was it what we did, serial numbers?
Totally on me, the stress got to me.
Gambling with your life.
God, I'm sorry, I'm super sorry.
Hey, hey, it's all right, it's all right.
That was an easy mistake to make, it was.
It's hard.
This game's not easy.
All right, this game is boss.
Here we go.
All right, here we go.
Let's kick some ass.
We'll go quick on this one.
Bang, bang it out.
Look out, we got, Simon says.
Simon says, Simon says, here we go.
By the way, there is a vowel.
Simon says with a vowel.
Okay, so, and we got no strikes, obviously.
What color do we have?
Green.
Yellow.
Green, red.
Yellow, red.
We have one strike.
Fuck, I'm sorry, we have a strike now.
Fuck, whatever.
Restore, restore.
You all did it for the absolute, ah, fuck it, fuck it.
Smash it.
Toy on the lives, man.
All right, here we go.
That was quick.
When you're exhausted, and if you're doing this
for a couple hours, you start to do really stupid mistakes.
Did you see what I was doing
with the number sequence bullshit?
Okay, here we go.
Force code, dot, dot, dot, dot.
Okay, dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, dot.
Dot, dot, dot, dot.
Four, three.
Three, four, three?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How many more are there?
Four.
Four, okay, so we're gonna, H, H.
See, it's a two and eight.
We are looking at three, five, oh, five.
Three, five, oh, five.
Got it?
Three, five, no!
Got it, yes, yes, yes.
Got it, Pac-Man.
Okay, we are looking at, what are we looking at?
What are we looking at?
We are looking at, you've got C, four,
is one of the circles, and D, one is the other circle.
The starting position is D, four,
is my starting position, and we're trying to go to F, two.
I start in D, four, we're going to F, two.
Oh, okay, okay, right, right?
Yep.
Up, up.
Done, okay.
All the way up.
Yep, we got, all right, so we got you, your, uh, uh-huh.
Okay, okay, gotcha, gotcha, let me just.
Okay, so we go, what word is it, what word is it?
The word is blank, like a blank space.
Read me, read me middle right.
Middle right is,
your, you are, just your, you are.
And then two letters.
Just two letters, just you are, your.
Done, the letter U, you are.
Got it, next word is, U, space, R.
U, space, R.
Bottom right, read me bottom right.
Is what without a question mark, just what.
Without a question mark.
No question mark.
U, H, H, H, what, letters, left, nothing, ready.
Hey, nothing?
What, that wasn't correct?
The fuck?
Whatever.
So, read me this new one.
Your, it's an apostrophe, like you are, your,
an apostrophe, like you are.
Read me, read me middle right.
Middle right is right, R-I-G-T-H, R-I-G-H-T.
Okay, uh, yes, nothing.
Got it, done?
Ready, okay, gotcha.
Again, you are, your, with an apostrophe, your.
Okay, read me middle right.
Like, L-I-K-E.
Your, with an apostrophe.
Next, the letter U, two letters, U-R.
You, so U, like you are, letters?
Yes, yes.
Got it, okay, done?
Moving on.
We have symbols, like omega, half-life, okay.
So, okay, reset, here we go.
Half-life symbol, lightning bolt, curse of H,
and a backwards C with a dot in the middle.
Okay, half-life?
Yep.
Lightning.
Got it, done.
Copyright.
We have a second Pac-Man.
Okay, second Pac-Man, okay.
What are we starting at?
So we have D-four and F-four are the circles,
and we're starting at F-two.
We need to get to D-six.
Spam the bottom, spam to the bottom, spam to the bottom.
Done.
Left?
Yep.
Up, up, up, left?
All the way down.
Done.
We have a red button that says hold,
red button that says hold.
By the way, there are two batteries.
Okay, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Red button that says hold.
Two batteries.
Okay, hang on, there are two more batteries
and there's a little kid.
If the button's red and the button says hold, right?
Mm-hmm, yes.
Press immediately release.
Good, over.
Regular wires.
Yeah.
Six wires.
Two white.
One blue.
It's exactly one yellow wire
and there's more than one.
So there is one yellow wire
and there are two white wires.
And that's the only thing that has,
white's the only thing that has more than one.
Exactly one yellow wire
and there are more than one white wire.
Yes.
Cut the fourth wire.
Done.
Okay, now we've got a complicated one.
It's the sidewards horizontal complex wires one.
Okay, let's kick some ass at this one.
Let's kick some ass.
Here we go.
All right, so red, red, first one is going to.
Red, red is the first wire, it's going to C.
Cut it.
Blue is the second wire, it's going to B.
It's in the third slot, so three to B.
Cut it.
No, no, no, no, no.
I just, I did, I cut it.
Okay, sorry.
Good, go.
Next one, next one, next one.
Okay, next one.
We have our second red wire and second blue wire
but our first black wire here.
So the first red wire is going to C.
Cut the black wire.
Cut the black wire, okay.
The blue one, the blue one is the second one, right?
Or the first one, first one, right?
The blue one is the second wire.
No, no, no, the blue one.
The blue one is the third wire, I believe,
of this sequence here.
Okay, is it the first occurrence we see in blue?
It's the first blue we see.
No, this is the second time we've seen a blue wire.
It's going from five to C.
Is it going to C?
Yes, it is.
Cut it.
Yes.
Keep going?
Okay, here we have our third blue wire and two black wires.
Is it going to B or A?
It's going to C, the blue wire is going to C.
Third time we see.
Ignore that, ignore that one, ignore that one.
Two black wires, one going to B, one going to C.
And this will be the second black wire, right?
This would be the, let's see.
This is the second and third black wire here.
Okay, so the first-
One's going to C, one's going to B.
The first one's going to C.
Cut the one that goes to C.
Okay.
And does the third one go to B?
Yes, it does.
Okay, cut that one too.
Okay.
Last one, we have a black wire and a blue wire.
11 to C, both going to C.
11 and 12, both going to C.
Blue wire and black wire.
Blue wire will be what in terms of occurrence?
So this would be the one, two, three, fourth blue wire.
Does it go to A?
Goes to C.
Skip it.
Nope.
Oh, cut the black wire, cut the black wire.
Done?
Yes.
Woo, we did it.
Oh, we have plenty of time, we have plenty of time.
42 seconds.
We have plenty of time?
Yeah, we have the 42 seconds.
That felt like fucking 25 minutes.
Yeah, I thought we had like 10 seconds left.
Jesus.
Oh my God.
Nice work.
That was good.
Dude, I'm fucking exhausted.
That was fucking wild.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
I can't imagine how much more difficult this game gets.
Dude, I tell you one thing.
We sure got way better at this in the fucking first stream.
Yes.
My God.
Wow.
That was fucking-
Dude, I'm like, it feels like I'm running a marathon.
Like, I'm physically exhausted.
I've been sitting down, but it's been like a,
I've actually been nervous this time.
Like, holy shit, man.
Yeah, I'm like sweating.
Somebody said this would be funny.
Do you want to preview the next one?
Just to see what the fuck is ahead of us.
Yeah, what is needy?
This is like a, this is a new mechanic.
Something is different about this bomb
and it demands attention.
Plus, yeah, apparently this bomb is needy.
Somebody said we should hook ourselves
up to small electric devices that give us small shocks
if we blow it.
That would be like death penalty.
That's electrical chair, man.
That's like TOS.
You ever seen the green mile?
Yes, I have.
All right, what's this?
Okay, so what the fuck are we looking at?
Okay, so apparently there's a new module here
that has like a bop it.
There's like a pull it, twist it, measure it.
Okay.
It says discharge the capacitor before it overloads
by holding down the lever.
So if I hold this down, okay.
I don't know what any of this means.
I think, and the word is needy, right?
I mean, needy is just the name of the bomb.
No, it's like the type of bomb it is.
I think this means that when we were gonna do this
next string question mark, I don't fucking know.
I think this is gonna build up a danger factor
and we have to like keep on being like,
no, go down, go done, you know?
We can't.
I think we have to like discharge it or something.
Oh, okay.
Well, I'll tell you what, I'll tell you what.
I think, how long have we been streaming?
Just curious.
Like three hours, 15 minutes.
I am fine with that.
I think we can call it here.
Okay.
Any more than this and I would have been like,
dude, just blow it up, we're fucked.
But here's-
Oh, is this not, oh, actually that's how.
Let me see what you're doing on screen, hang on.
Okay, you ready?
Can you imagine doing this?
Start, press start, press start.
Oh, would you, is this even possible?
Let's find out.
All right, let's go.
Quick, three, five, nine, five.
Three, five, nine, five on the Morse.
The word is,
th, th,
see,
sex.
Sex.
No, no, no, back, back, back, back.
It's sex.
No, no, no, sex.
Sex queue.
Winsage.
Sorry, I lost you there.
Thicc.
Let's try that,
insane mode one more time.
Wait, we can't, we can't do that.
I know, but let's see if we can solve one
completely randomly.
Do you want to just try to solve one?
All right, let's try to solve.
If we solve one, then I'll eat for,
I'll eat something.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen, we have enough Salmonella for a lifetime.
All right, here we go.
Ready?
Okay, symbols.
Just look at the very first symbol.
Omega.
Oh shit.
Okay, hang on.
Omega.
Hang on.
Trident.
AE.
And then Microsoft staple mascot.
Okay, you want to go,
you want to go staple mascot.
Yep.
AE.
Trident.
Omega.
Got it, got it.
Okay.
All right, we solved one.
I was just trying to guess.
We got it.
Holy shit.
How would anybody,
there are probably speed runners that can do this shit
in five, 10 seconds.
Dude, imagine getting so fucking good at this.
You don't even depend on somebody.
You just remember from just like,
You just do it.
Algorithmic, like, you know.
Somebody, oh, by the way,
I forgot about this.
Somebody emailed me,
there is a mod for this game called Speed.
Speed?
It's a multiplayer mod.
You've seen the movie Speed?
Uh-huh.
Somebody modded in that someone,
you have to drive the bus with A and D
and always go around 80 miles per hour
or else it explodes.
Why didn't we do this?
Why didn't we do this one?
This looks awesome.
I'll tell you what.
Next one.
Next time.
And I'll tell you what.
Let's get a bunch of mods next time.
Let's download a, you know.
You want to fuck it up the whole,
you want to fuck the whole thing up?
A bunch of crap.
Well, I'll tell you what, man.
This was a lot of fun.
And I think the stream went way better
now that we're like sitting down
and we're like, let's be very serious.
But this was a lot of fun, man.
This was a very fun stream
and I can breathe now,
but a lot of fun, man.
A lot of fun.
Yeah.
Well, we'll probably see you again soon.
Thanks for hanging out, Joel.
We're squad stream so people can just look to the right
and see your channel, so.
Absolutely.
Always give Joel a follow.
He's a fucking great dude.
And we'll see you again.
Whenever.
Yeah, absolutely.
Whenever you want to do this again.
Hit me up and I'll wake up at 3 a.m.
and have sand in my ass and be like,
knocking over cans.
Like, I got a diffuse mumps.
You got cans in your room too?
Wow.
Look at how similar we are, guys.
Look at us.
But what are you saying?
What are you guys saying?
Except one of us is funny.
But that's not me, by the way.
But which one?
No, you are.
Okay, listen.
No.
Anyway, my point being,
my point being,
I had a blast
and now that we know how all these modules work.
Now we can drive a car.
And yeah, the only thing we have to be a little better at
is we have to,
I have, well, you don't need any practice
on the password module, but I'll say this.
The memory shit is really difficult.
And I suggest maybe next stream,
get like a note thing or something to just be like,
yeah, that's not cheating.
Cause it's, you know, fucking,
when I do math in real life, I'm like, I had to write shit.
You know what, I'm going to get the thing.
I have this thing where I can draw on my screen.
I'm just going to get that.
Me too.
Hang on, hang on.
Check this bad boy out.
Hang on.
You got one?
Yeah, they're pretty, they're awesome.
I've used them before.
A pencil.
No, no, no, no, no.
Like the pen that you can just draw on the screen.
So I can be like, okay, one and then two, three, four.
You should race desert bus with Joel.
Oh, that's, how do you race desert bus?
When you just go the same speed on the same road.
It's a race.
It's like my stream, man.
Oh, let me see.
Let me see what you're doing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can draw kind of well.
You know how to draw.
It's a photo, dude.
You didn't just draw that?
I'll see you next week.
Hopefully whenever we, whenever we,
whenever we cross paths again,
but once again, thank you for having me on the stream.
I hope, I hope that, or us playing this a little bit better
add a little more quality to the stream, but you know.
Hey, the last one was quality too.
We were learning.
The last one was quality, but with 15 quotation marks.
But now we're in a little different league, I think.
But regardless, thank you so much for having me, man.
And you know, I hope next time we can,
we can breeze through it even more in an accelerated pace.
So.
That was a lot of fun.
Absolutely.
Yeah, absolutely.
We'll see you later, dude.
See you later and.
Have a good sleep.
Well, actually, you know, you just woke up, didn't you?
Yeah, but you know, I'll probably eat two raw eggs later on
and I'll fucking have salmonella on my clock out for a week.
But anyway, yeah, speaking about that,
you, listen, that's not my prerogative anymore.
You check out whenever you are gonna go
on a heart attack grill and eat onion rings
that will give you like.
I'm looking forward to it.
Biblical, biblical diarrhea.
So, you know.
I don't know, I, yeah, probably.
But regardless, thank you for having me, man.
And.
You as well.
Thanks for having me too.
Thanks for you having me, having you having me.
Right?
Yeah, absolutely.
Thank you, Jerma.
And thank you, Jerma Chat for calling me a turnip.
I'll see you.
All right, get deleted.
Yeah, get deleted.
See ya.
All right.
All right, guys.
What we're gonna do is
I, I am going to be,
I just was talking to Kim.
And I think we're gonna go to dinner.
We're gonna go out to dinner.
It's Diablo and you know it.
It's not.
Oh, I see how it is.
You hate us.
A three and a half hour stream.
Get it.
We're going to the heart attack grill.
No, that's probably a good place.
I don't, I don't wanna,
I don't wanna know Diablo II tonight.
No Diablo II tonight.
It's time for the water filter stream and you know it.
Now, I'm gonna give you guys kind of how the,
the way that the streams are gonna work for a while.
I have a very, very, very busy, busy February.
Real wink.
Well, all right, well fucking let's go to the wink.
So how, let me, let's go.
This actually will take like probably a few minutes
to go over.
Let's go over this.
Let's go.
I'm gonna just give you a bunch of money.
Dry Ski just gave 5,000 bits.
Thank you, Dry Ski.
50 fucking dollars.
Yeah, no, we're still gonna do the end of the stream.
We're still gonna hang out.
5,000 bits.
Let me just pull up my bit device here.
Here it is.
It's Dry Ski.
They say, hey, Jerma, it's my birthday today.
Wanna say you've made it so much better
with the laughs tonight.
Love the idea of you, buddy.
Have a great time.
Thank you, Dry Ski.
Happy birthday.
Not sure where you are in the world,
but hopefully it stays your birthday
for a little while longer.
The idea of you.
Taking ice cream was on its way, yeah.
Thank you.
Have a great birthday.
Phil's birthday, man.
Jerma induced a heart attack.
I love the idea of Jerma,
but the execution is just, you know,
it gets lacking sometimes.
It's lacking.
No, thanks a lot, man.
But let's go over.
Let's go.
Let's put the cam on for this.
Just so, cause, you know, obviously
not really playing the exploding game anymore,
but I'll just go right in the middle.
So there you go.
You guys are right here.
So over the course of the next couple of weeks,
I have some doctor's appointments
and I also have some old friends,
some hometown friends that are coming up to visit Vegas
and they're going to spend some time here.
So we're going to do a few kind of one day off,
one day on, two day, but here's, hear me out on this one.
So I will be back on Sunday.
I will be back on Sunday.
We're going to stream on Sunday.
So that's the 26th.
And then I'm going to be off on the 20th.
What just happened?
Oh, okay.
I'm going to be off on the 27th.
And then we are going to go five days in a row.
We are going to do Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday, Saturday.
We're doing five days in a row
because the week after that, the next week,
that first, second week of February,
I'm not going to be live for more
than probably once, twice a week.
So we are going to do five days in a row
as of this coming Tuesday.
But again, you'll see me again on Sunday,
nothing on Monday, and then five days in a row
until I take some time off.
It's not going to be Diablo.
No, we have a lot of games to play.
It's not going to be fucking Diablo.
What's wrong with my hair?
It's painted on.
I mean, it's a little bit of this, yeah.
When's community content night part two?
That's actually a really, really great question.
That's a great question.
That's going to happen on probably Sunday
because that's when I said I was going to have
this coming weekend, right?
So we'll do that on Sunday.
That'll be part two of community content night.
That will be a quick one.
So we'll do something else.
We'll do community content night
and then we'll bleed into something else.
But that's the schedule for the next couple of weeks
because I'm taking a lot of time off
that first week of February.
Don't point at me.
I told you I'm like a fucking,
I like cast spells when I talk.
That's it for tonight.
See you guys in a couple of days on Sunday.
And that's it.
Shorter stream tonight, I know,
but my brain is a little,
I mean, he was right when he said that after doing that,
it's almost like I need to go eat
and just relax for a while.
Signing off.
I'll see you guys on Sunday.
But let's do the end of the stream.
Let's hang out for a little bit, as always.
I'm not just going to leave.
When's the rumble?
Yes, there's going to be a charity rumble.
I haven't talked that much about it,
but I've talked enough about it for you guys to know.
The next rumble is going to be a charity rumble.
It's going to be to sponsor one of my closest friends,
Boston Marathon Run.
All the money that comes in during that stream,
there's going to be a special link to donate
to raise the money to sponsor his run.
That should be really fun.
And that's probably going to happen
somewhere in February into March.
That's when it's planned, at least.
Because obviously the marathon is in April,
so we kind of have to do it before then,
because obviously he needs to be sponsored before then.
Yo Joel, why you eating chips?
Why though?
Why what?
Why do a charity stream?
I don't know, I don't follow you.
But why though?
Hey, but why though?
But yeah, now that's the plan.
Let's rewind the clock a little bit.
Let's do the bits.
Thank you to E-WordTorteyWordTort for the 250.
It's been a while since I've said that name out loud,
one of my favorite names.
I love saying it, E-WordTorteyWordTort.
It's 250.
We had 10 community subs from SuperBruce.
I caught it, but again, thank you, Bruce.
Much love to you.
Again, E-WordTorteyWordTort gave 250 bits.
Remember, please play Halo M when it comes out on PC,
or I'll fly to America and sign a petition to ban you.
Why do you have to fly to America to ban me?
There's a clip here.
I know what this clip says, but I did it.
And it...
E-WordTorteyWordTort, thanks for the $5.
Jerma, play Halo on PC, please, thank you.
Probably.
I did.
I don't see why not, probably.
Not the next day, probably not.
On legendary mode.
I did that too.
Delete that.
Demons V, thanks for the...
I did that too.
You call what you did playing.
Yes, I had, I controlled the character and moved around.
Fucking Halo.
That's so funny to me.
It's all good though, whatever.
All right, he's gonna ban you in real life.
You know, how do you get banned in real life?
Thank you, E-WordTorteyWordTort, appreciate it.
Oh my God, how did I miss $100 from Freddy Dredd?
How did I miss this?
This is like the most important message ever.
Freddy Dredd gave 10,000 bits earlier,
and they said, I'm at Hash House right now.
I'm gonna order.
That was like three hours ago.
God damn it.
I need to know, I have to know.
You got the blue cheeseburger?
He's waiting for you.
He's been waiting for you for three hours.
You were supposed to go to dinner.
That's the most important because of the money?
No, it's the most important because
they went to Hash House or GoGo at the link.
That's why.
Literally there, they kicked him out.
Freddy, if you're still here
or if you check back in again,
thanks so much for the fucking $1,100, $1,200 now.
Over two days.
Hope you liked it.
It's one of my favorite places.
He wouldn't notice, Freddy,
if he just typed in chat normally.
But thanks, Freddy.
Thank you so much.
Seriously, I hope you liked it.
I'm gonna, I'm so sad.
I'm kind of nervous.
What if he comes back and he's like,
dude, that was like a six out of 10 at best.
In fact, like two of my friends are sick.
I'm gonna be like, oh shit.
No, impossible.
Not possible if you go to Hash House or GoGo at the link.
Not possible.
It's just a fact, but thanks a lot.
Thank you.
I'd ever agree.
Thanks to Five Dolls.
Jerma, so me and my friends
were doing a hunger game simulator.
We added you in as a joke,
but unfortunately you ended up killing everyone
and you won the hunger games.
Is this my, the winner is Jerma from District 10.
People add me as a joke to things and I just win.
Is the image, apparently.
Well, Adam is a joke.
Well, you know, now you guys know,
I take shit dead seriously.
I'm not, I don't fuck around.
You add me to something like that.
I'm gonna go for it.
I'm saying.
I can't just be jokey, add it in
and not win the whole thing.
But thanks.
I'm honored to have won.
Hey, Noodle is bad at gaming.
Thanks to the five for the bits.
Hey, Jerma, I made a funny video.
Why is there, oh, sorry.
Someone's talking.
That was like a poker tournament going on
on the front page of Twitch repair.
I don't know.
I just like, I hit the back button
and I'm on my Twitch homepage.
Sorry about that.
That's not the funny video, I guess.
There's another one.
It says here comes another bad Jerma video.
Last one is to see.
Black wire in the middle to see.
What number, what number?
Which time was left?
You don't wanna know.
That's a halo spoiler.
Okay, this is, I'm gonna,
here comes a halo spoiler.
Those of you that have ever seen halo,
here comes a spoiler.
Last one is to see.
Black wire in the middle to see.
What number, what number?
How much time was left?
You don't wanna know.
That's the first level in Halo 2.
I've never seen Halo 2
before you spoiled the whole game.
I can't even play it now.
Autumn Dragons, thanks for the 250
and they say, this is Morse code.
Let me just like put this
into like a Morse code translator.
Make sure this is not something
that I was gonna say something fucked up.
Okay, this is what they wrote.
I can't even write this.
Why?
So that's Morse code for Jerma sucks.
Cool, thanks.
Hey, appreciate that.
Hey, Meaty Patty, thanks for the 500 bits.
Thanks a lot.
Agent Dark Booty, thanks for the 500 bits.
Jerma, I've only been watching you since 2017
but you're giving me more wheezy laughs
than any other E-clown.
Thanks.
They say, I hope you don't take chat
ribbing you seriously.
We all love you and it's all in good fun.
Yeah, I hope you don't take some of the things
that I say seriously either.
I'm not talking about putting a hamburger
down my underwear.
You know what I mean?
That's not real.
We both say things, we're just kidding around.
Also, I have ADHD and have trouble
with motivation sometimes.
Do you experience this
or have you had any tips regarding it?
Keep it up, dude.
Yeah, all the time.
The thing that helps for me the most
is trying just to focus on one thing at a time
because I can get so spread out
and have so many things that I care about
that I care about, I have 100% of my brain that cares
and if there's 10 things that I wanna do,
each one of those things will get 10% of my brain
which just, that sucks.
It fucks everything up.
You gotta do one thing at a time, 100% of your brain power.
It's easy to be like, well, this, that, that, that, that
and then you spread yourself out so much
that you're all over the place.
So I've tried to, at least recently,
in the last probably three, four plus years,
is just to do one thing at a time
and just get it done and do that first
because there are, especially if we're talking about
just even for streaming, the stuff that I wanna do,
I have things that I'm starting to want to plan out
that are gonna be three, four, five plus months
from now in 2020,
but there's other stuff that takes precedence first
that's happening now or sooner
and you gotta do it one step at a time.
It's really easy to get overwhelmed
when you overwhelm yourself, one at a time.
But thanks a lot.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
Xwar2, thanks for the 300 bits.
Enjoy the dinner date with Kim Germa.
This is like my third ever Twitch stream of yours.
Also, it's pronounced Xwar2.
All right, but I think I said Xwar2, Xwar2.
Thank you.
Welcome, hope you like it.
This is the third time you've ever seen a stream.
I'm not sure if you've ever seen anything else,
but what's going on?
Thanks for stopping by.
We'll see you again.
Beck Ali, thank Beck Ali or Beck Ali for the 400 bits.
Thanks a lot.
They say, hey Germa, watching your videos
really helps with my depression and shit.
I wanna say thank you.
Also, I used to have pet rats
and they're amazing like little dogs.
Yeah, and they're insanely smart too.
They're very, very smart animals.
But whatever you're going through,
I'm sorry to hear that.
Hopefully you can go day by day
and start feeling a little better.
Rats are fucking awesome.
Year of the rat too.
Year of the rat, pet rats.
Gotta get two though.
Otto is a rat terrier.
That's also not, that's not, I didn't make that up.
He's rat terrier.
He's 40% dachshund, 40% rat terrier,
10% Shetland sheepdog and 10% Chihuahua.
We got the real data.
He's an actual rat.
But thank you, Beck Ali.
Appreciate it.
We also have 300 bits from Gray the Color.
Thank you, Gray.
Great stream tonight.
Would like to see more co-op with you and Joel.
A lot of people recommended it,
but will you be playing SWAT 4 anytime in the future?
Also, do you ever finish that petition
to get Burger Boy to permanently wear a bib?
Permanently.
Oh, that's so fucking stupid.
Yeah, this bit, there's so many games
that I just wanna play co-op or not.
They just go in a line and then you do one
and then one gets put behind you,
you see it, you wanna do it.
Well, I'll give you just a perfect example of this.
The SWAT series.
Me and Star were going to play SWAT,
like SWAT 3, SWAT 4.
There's no online anymore.
We were going to do this like five years ago.
We just, it was just too much for pain in the ass.
We've been talking about that for like fucking every year.
Star and I are just like, oh yeah, we'll do it.
It was always just a pain in the ass to do.
But that was a conversation that we would have
over almost a half decade.
SWAT 4 multiplayer still works.
You just have to get it from GOG.
Is that for real?
I always thought you had to get in a server
and you had to make a server or something.
I'll have to look into that.
He doesn't know.
No, I don't know.
It's super easy.
All right, I'll figure it out.
All right, well, add it to the list
after beautiful Joe one and two.
So many games I want to play now.
Oh, too many games.
But thank you, Gray the Cutler.
Thanks for the 300 bits.
Stephunky Chicken, thanks for the 400 bits.
The best root beer is mug.
That's a weird way to say A and W.
Well, I didn't say it was the best.
I just said it was the one, I said it was really good.
Did I say it was the best?
I didn't say it was the best, did I?
I did.
Oh, well, I probably shouldn't have said that.
I misspoke.
But thank you, Stephunky Chicken.
Mehdi Marin, thanks for the 500 bits.
Hey, Germo.
Yeah.
Were you ever considering returning the games
in the Monster Hunter series?
The Switch has a couple games in world recently
got the Iceborne expansion.
And was there any reason you never returned?
I just think that after a while,
it's almost like streaming an MMO in a way.
You know the thing that you're going to do.
You're gonna go do the same thing at least.
Well, we're gonna kill this monster
like three or four times.
I think I got most of what I wanted out of it on stream.
Grind, not necessarily like the grind,
but when I turn on a stream, I'd rather do that off stream.
Not that I don't think the game would be,
I think it's boring, that's not the right word.
But it just takes a long time to do stuff in Monster Hunter.
There's a lot of setup and then there's a lot,
oh, you're just kind of going for that one weapon.
I need that tail.
I got the tail.
I need that claw.
I need that tail.
I need that tooth.
And it ends up going something like this.
I need that claw.
I need that tooth.
I need that tail.
I need that claw.
And then I kind of just give up.
Sans, hold on.
I didn't know I could even do that.
I need that claw.
I didn't even know I could do that shit.
Wow, that's kind of fun.
Cool assisted improv.
I didn't know I could even do that.
Now I'm quieter?
There we go, there we go.
But probably the answer is no.
I don't have a reason to release stream it.
Lost 100 to me is more fun
if I can just sit with my mouth open
and I need that tail for like four hours straight.
Thank you though.
Let's get the credits on screen.
Credits, credits, credits, credits, credits, credits,
credits, credits, credits, credits, credits.
Are they actually gonna show up?
I hope so.
These are all the subs and all the bits.
No, they're not all the subs.
There's no bit credits.
Play Mortal Kombat 11 on stream, shaking my head.
But why would I play Mortal Kombat 11
if I can get diarrhea'd on by people that know how to play?
Thank you for the subscription guys.
Have a fantastic rest of your night.
Thanks for subbing all of you.
Please do the Kylo Ren voice.
I can't do the fucking Kylo Ren voice.
I.
That's the thing.
Sometimes you have to do what you're saying to do.
I know I can feel it.
That's just Bugleberry with a megaphone on.
That's a warehouse announcer voice?
Wait, wait, wait.
100 spaces down.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's full glass of salsa.
That was shattered in aisle number four.
Jerry, if you could.
I can do this.
Check this out, ready?
I.
Hold on.
Wait.
I.
Do you know, oh, oh.
Wait, why is it not working?
Oh, it's not even on.
I.
Oh, it's so much fun to sing.
This exists too.
Why would there be a button for this?
Why would there be a, I'm sorry, guys.
I'm so nervous.
I didn't think I was gonna get,
I didn't think I was gonna have to come up on stage
and tell you guys anything.
But seriously, I am so excited for this,
winning this award.
And thank you, everybody.
Thank you for all the support and everything.
Good night.
Bye.
All right, I gotta go.
I gotta go.
I gotta get out of here.
We're gonna raid Box Box tonight.
Box Box did a double raid over the last few days.
It was, I think there was a coordinated raid.
It was two people.
Go say hello to Box Box.
I missed a donation.
What the fuck did he do?
I did, I missed two.
Thanks, 300 Bits for Wilcorn.
Thank you, Wilcorn.
This is my first donation to anyone.
I've seen your streams for a while,
and I've wanted to say thanks for the laughs and good feels.
That thanks for even considering giving me money.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks for being here.
And then finally, it was one more thousand bit donation
from Xwar2, thanks to 10 bucks.
Say, I feel like I'm really bad at Twitch messages.
I've been enjoying your VODs from Twitch,
randomly started watching you
after the first don't talking or you'll explode stream
because of Twitter.
I don't really watch Twitch,
but I've really been enjoying your content.
You're obviously an inspired and passionate guy,
and I dig that.
The bits are for conquering my childhood game,
Simpsons Hit and Run.
I'll definitely be sticking around.
Possibly any more Mountain Blade.
If I were to go back to Mountain Blade,
it would have to be with this shitload of VODs.
Just like a total joke stream.
But thanks.
Yeah, Simpsons Hit and Run is a wild experience.
Play the new one.
Yeah, Bannerlord's coming out.
But hasn't Bannerlord been coming out
for like four years?
Is it, is that actually gonna come out?
Sadly, it has.
Hasn't it been in development for like five plus years?
Or is it 10 years actually?
Okay, it's been 10 years.
Now, but now it has a steam page.
Really? Okay.
Now you got me interested.
See, now I'm interested.
Yeah, we're gonna go send some love to Boxbox.
Got a lot of raids from Boxbox recently, like I said.
Continues to show tons of love to the stream.
Go say hello.
See you guys on Sunday.
Have a good couple nights.
That was the wrong button.
That was the right button.
See you guys Sunday.
Goodbye.
Let's raid.
I will not be participating in the raid.
I'm going to go out to dinner.
Give my best.