Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a gameplay commentary on Team Fortress
2. Gonna be playing with the Soldier, the Scout, and the Engineer in this gameplay,
and before I get into anything, take a look at the screen, holy crap. This is on a 100%
crit low-gravity server, and before anybody freaks out, let me give you a little bit of
a reason why I'm doing this. So I know we had that talk the other day. The Team Fortress
2 is dying talk. Had a lot of good responses, you guys had a lot of good discussion from
that, and a lot of it got me thinking. I think it's time to try some custom maps, some custom
mods, some interesting game modes, that type of thing, and that's why I'm doing this.
This is a real, incredibly, radically different experience than playing normal Team Fortress
2. If you've never done something like this before, absolutely go try it. It is some of
the most fun I've had in this game in a very, very long time. Now, not only did this
server have low-gravity and 100% crits, it also had a dice mod on it, and that adds another
layer of insanity on top of this cake of craziness we're making here. And just in the beginning
for the first couple minutes, I wanted to show you some crazy one-lives or crazy situations
I got myself into, Scout and Soldier, the next thing after this Scout run I have right
here, which is ridiculous, I kill a bunch of people, but the gameplay after this, the
engineer, it's a full gameplay. I'm going to commentate over it, tell you some things,
but holy crap, words can't even describe what you're going to see. So if you happen
upon one of these servers at some point in the near future, which class should you play?
Now that's a good question, and the easiest answer is definitely the Scout. The Scout
can move around so fast and double-jumping, you can pretty much fly around the map like
a flying squirrel, it's ridiculous. And if you're going to use Scout, oh my god, the
hitscan weapons, not just for Scout, if you use a hitscan class and you're good, you will
dominate an entire server, especially with the Scout. If you can jump around and land
your shots really well, get some good meat shots on people, you'll kill everybody. So
here is the end of the Scout run, I get this last Soldier, and then we're going to transition
into the engineer gameplay. Starts from the beginning, and oh my god, use the Widowmaker.
If you get into a game that's a server like this, oh my god, use the Widowmaker. That's
the only thing I can say. Cause watch this guys, with the Widowmaker on a 100% crit server,
you will have infinite ammo, cause when you shoot somebody, you get almost all of your
Once you hit one person, you'll get at least, at least double or triple what you put in.
So as you can imagine, you can stand in a corner like this, or get in a long corridor,
and just fire away and just smoke everybody that walks down a hallway. And as for the
mini century, I think I only place maybe two, maybe three in the entire gameplay, and they
don't kill one person. I kill every single person in this gameplay with the Widowmaker,
and it gets to a point where I stop placing it, because it's wasting my metal to shoot
people. I go, you know, I could place a mini century right here, but who cares? I'm not
going to do that. And this part right here is great, look at this. You know the world
is upside down when an engineer kills a heavy from 500 feet away. Just unbelievable. And
you know it's crazy when it happens again, right here. World ending now, 2012. Is it
2012 yet? No it's not, it's okay. Demoman skeet shooting right there, he launched about
5 million feet in the air, and I ended up catching him with a little pellet, and he
died trying to sticky jump, I think he was trying to jump across the map, which is crazy
effective cause one sticky bomb will launch you across the entire map. I was actually
messing around with it before I captured some of this footage. It's kind of like getting
shot out of a cannon. You kind of feel like Evil Knievel when you do it. Oh I almost forgot
to bring this up. Somebody told me about a new winter crate. So I did a little research,
went to the wiki page, went to go find out for myself. Now I am excited for the winter
update cause last year, if you guys were around, last year when they did this whole crate key
winter thing, there were a bunch of new items and new weapons. So hopefully this is part
one of the saga that is the Christmas update. Just wanted to get that out there cause I
know I would have forgotten that, and I would have three days from now would have been like
did I mention the crate key? Oh dammit I didn't, that kind of sounded like grandpa. Oh by the
way speaking of grandpa, I know I'm going off on a wild tangent right here, but this
kind of has to be said, I got a lot of PMs and a lot of comments from people asking me
where's grandpa? Is there any more grandpa videos? What's going on with that? And I got
to, I'm going to say it one more time. Make sure I reiterate this to the new people that
came in. A lot of new guys have come into the channel. So grandpa is going to be every
Sunday 4 PM Pacific time on Machinima Respawn. Grandpa will appear on this channel at some
random times. I'll do random games with him. This is a gameplay commentary channel though.
If you're looking for just straight up craziness, I do other weird characters too. I have a
whole playlist that's dedicated to my real life skits like Burger Boy, the egg and stuff
like that. You guys that have been in the channel for a while know, but if you're new
to the channel, go check out the playlists. A lot of grandpa stuff is there and some other
characters you may not have heard of yet, but that is where the comedy is going to go
in that playlist. That is going to wrap up this commentary on the crazy 100% crit low
gravity server. Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. If you
like this video, go ahead and shoot me a like and I will see you guys all next time. Take
care everybody.