Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with the Team Fortress 2 GAME PLAY commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Spy with the Conivers, Kunai, the Ambassador, and the STRANGE making this part up.
Um, the... Why the hell can I not say the name of this item? The Sapper! God, Jerma, what the hell?
Get eaten by the cot. Or don't get eaten by the cot. It missed ya. Bang. Headshot. Boom.
As you can already tell, this is a coffee commentary of Justice and Doom.
And what that means is I just hit record and I backstab two heavies in a row.
And then I just start talking about anything that could be on the screen. I don't know what's gonna be happening.
It could be something that is not on the screen.
Like, for instance, I could have you direct your attention right now to outside the current window in the room you are in right now.
There is a monster and he's gonna get... No, there's not really a monster out there, although there very well could be.
So, just for me, be careful. Just make sure there's no monster. Are you looking?
Okay, good. There's no monster out there. So, let's move on now. We're gonna talk about the spy.
I'm gonna talk about some spy tactics and some spy strategies.
As you can see right there, I sap that sentry and got the hell out... What? Dude, what? You shot right in the back.
I'm trying to do like a spy strategy and you shoot me right in my freaking back. What a real friggin' embarrassment that was.
Anyways, when you sap a sentry, one of the main important things you want to do is get the hell out of there.
If there is an opportunity for you to stab the engineer and get out, don't dilly-dally around and like look at your watch and...
Well, literally look at your watch, but don't metaphorically look at your watch.
When you sap a sentry, there was a heavy standing right next to that engineer. He actually was shooting at me.
Just run away. Just go away and try to get another kill because you're gonna stand around too much and you're gonna get yourself shot right in the balls.
Kind of like what happened to me about 15 seconds ago.
Another tip right here, if you have the opportunity, shoot the engineer in his face.
Don't wait around for the enemy to get backstabbed. Just shoot him right in his face and you know what?
Shoot this guy in his freaking face too.
I actually get a couple of good ambassador headshots in this gameplay. I think you've already seen the good ones.
I could be completely wrong, but let's start shoutcasting now. We do that sometimes in these coffee commentary.
He's getting that backstab on that heavy who was trying to get the car to be suppressed.
Coming around the ramp here, Jerma is gonna come up and hide because he doesn't want to be seen by the heavy, especially the guy in the top left here.
So he backs up. Demoman is unfortunately enough jumping into it in front of the knife and he gets backstabbed right there.
Going for a headshot. Maybe Jerma decides to back off there, but he gets it.
One headshot does not pull off the second one, unfortunately.
If he had only had one more second time, he probably would have had that shot.
Now he is being very cautious because he doesn't want to go up here by himself.
Wants at least two or three people to maybe distract somebody.
A heavy sees him, gets a couple of shots on him, but Jerma does not back down that easily, it seems.
He's still gonna hide here. Not sure why he's doing this. Maybe that heavy does not think he's still here.
Disguising himself as a pyro to try and throw the heavy off.
Maybe he's not gonna be in there anymore. Maybe he's gonna decide to go for this.
He's gonna go for the sentry gun. Engineer going back into spawn for some more metal.
He gets the sapper down. Medic coming out with the ubersaw.
He gets a couple of hits on him. Does not kill Jerma.
He's gonna find his way down here to hide back in the original spot.
It's just unbelievable. Can't believe he got away with that one, ladies and gentlemen.
The sapper was removed, unfortunately, and looks like he's gonna try for some crazy.
He gets the stab on that heavy. Oh my goodness gracious, that guy is probably rage-witting right now.
But let's take a break here for a moment, folks. I'm gonna talk about our sponsor for a second.
Crispy cream ice cream cones. Make sure you get one. They're delicious. Crispy creams.
Now let's get back into the action here. Jerma is gonna disguise as a heavy.
This is a pretty risky move, ladies and gentlemen.
Jerma does not understand that he moves a lot slower as a heavy.
But I don't think he realizes this because he's an idiot and sometimes he does not think logically.
But he's coming back up here trying to find his way back up top.
What a beautiful stab by that spycicle. And a pyro shows up.
But he doesn't do anything, so Jerma is gonna be fine.
But just in case he drops down, does not want to be in that situation.
Sees the knife, raise nose. This is a spy. We got spy on spy action here.
Goes in front of him. He gets a whirlwind stab.
I've never seen anything like that, folks. A whirlwind stab.
In all my years of casting Team Fortress 2, which is actually like 15 minutes that I've been doing this,
I have never seen anything like that before.
And he's gonna get another stab on this guy. No, he's not.
No, run. Just get out of there. Oh. Shoot him. Get him. Please. Oh.
Did I really just spend the last like half of this video doing a shellcast?
Is that like what just happened?
Am I gonna have to title this video? It's a shellcast, even though it's a coffee commentary?
You know what? It's gonna be coffee commentary slash.
Oh. My elbow. Oh, damn it.
Okay. Anyways, before the video is over, I'm gonna stop shellcasting now.
I do want to bring this up. I want to mention something.
If you watch American football, the Patriots just won.
They're going to the AFC Championship game now.
If you're not big into sports, neither am I.
But it's still pretty interesting to see that and to know that.
So if you guys are football fans, let me know the teams that you're rooting for that are currently, I guess, still in it.
With that being with the Patriots or the Atlanta Falcons or something.
And if you're from a different country, then you can just disregard this statement.
That was pretty sick right there, by the way, that stab.
That guy was invisible. And that guy is dead now.
But yeah, I just want to get your guys' opinion on the football playoffs.
Because it's something I'm currently watching right now.
And now I'm on fire. And I die right up here.
I remember dying from this because there was like five million pyros or like two or three or something.
But that's going to pretty much conclude the video.
We actually pull off the victory right here.
Thank you all so, so much for watching.
I really do appreciate this coffee commentary shoutcast thing.
Whatever you want to call it.
But yeah, I do really do appreciate it, guys.
Let me know what you think.
And I'll see you all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
Coffee commentary, baby.
Let's drink some more like tea.
Is this tea? I don't know.
Yeah, it's tea.