I know the pieces fit cause I watch them fall away.
Hold on.
This is super liminal.
So this game suck.
Well, how's this game? Is it good? Is that better?
How's that sound? Louder? Shorter? Longer? Whatever you want.
This is a tuber game. All right, this should be fun then.
All right, how about the graphics?
Default. Okay, this is probably fine.
This is high. Ambient occlusion. Gross.
That's yeah, whatever.
All right, let's go.
Wait, is there FOV?
Ah, thank God. Okay.
Turn this down.
Attention to be refined. Subtitles.
Yeah, 2560 by 1440. What a big ass screen.
Oh, we're turning that up.
I mean, that's not high enough.
Okay, super liminal. Terms of service.
I just, wait, I signed it?
I didn't want to sign it. I just want to look at it.
This FOV feels huge.
You missed the intro.
What intro?
Who cares? Does it matter?
I'll turn it up.
So I see an ad for that and then I go do it.
And I need to, I had to see that so badly.
You could have just told me,
hey, you saw an ad on TV for this place.
Is that better?
Now you have context.
Yeah, that's true.
Let's go ahead and sign it. Sign it with my nose.
Reception is reality. Grab.
What? I don't get it.
Okay, because it's making, it's bigger?
Yeah, that's trippy.
How do I, oh, there we go.
Do I, what do I just do? Duck?
Oh, cool. All right.
Okay, I get it.
Terms of service accepted.
Congratulations on falling asleep.
Welcome to Somnascult.
Your progress may be monitored by qualified specialists.
This orientation will adapt you to eyelids,
our interactive lucid induction dream state
in which you retain full consciousness and control.
What do you want me to do?
Move this?
Oh, fuck. What do I do?
What? Wait, what?
I don't get it. What just happened?
What? Okay.
What do I, do I have to play chess?
Okay, put the board here.
No, that's too small.
Um, oh, that's huge.
Do I have to make this big?
Oh, I thought I had to play chess.
Shit. It's okay. That works.
No objects beyond this point at all times.
How do I make it big?
Make it look big.
Can I like hold it up to my eye?
How do I hold it up to my eye?
Well, that's gone now.
I broke the game and I have to restart the whole thing.
Thank God.
How do I, how do I hold it up close?
Distance. Yeah.
Can I crouch?
Is there a way I can pull it forward to look at it closer?
Whoa. Well, now what?
What do I do? How, what do I do about it?
How do I get it in there?
From the vent?
How do I get it through? I can't.
How do I put it? Just go through?
I thought I couldn't.
Wait, I'm confused.
I can't bring this through.
So how do I put it here?
Put it in the vent?
Yeah, I can't go through the block.
So how do I get the, how do I get the block in here?
Is there a vent?
Oh, sneaky.
Shit. Hold on.
No, I want it to be smaller.
Confirmed.
You can move freely, interact with surrounding objects,
and listen to messages from your patient care team.
Please note that I am the standard orientation protocol
and that my voice has been explicitly chosen to remind you
that I am not a part of your patient care team.
I do not care.
Whoa, it's big. All right.
So now just go through here.
Dude, smoke is coming out of his ears.
Hold. Okay.
Oh, this is huge.
Wow. Oh, is that it?
Yeah, kind of.
During eyelids, you will lose the ability to awaken suddenly
due to realizing that this is a dream.
Evidence. I have already informed you that this is a dream.
You did not wake up.
Please complete the remaining orientation activities.
I feel like I'm going to...
All right. So what am I doing here?
This has got to be a dream soda.
Warning. You have deviated from the orientation pathway.
At the Pierce Institute, patient safety as a keynote...
We're going to every floor.
A variable degree of force cannon will be authorized
to ensure patient safety.
Please return to the orientation pathway.
Oh, that's a tiny little button.
All right. How do I make it teeny tiny?
I got to go like this, right?
Like, cool.
Looks like somebody tried to...
I mean, probably just like through here, right?
Yeah.
All environments perceived during eyelids
should reflect a typical mental state.
If you believe your mental state was compromised by somnascope,
please provide a comprehensive, rational explanation
in your post-procedural survey.
Completed surveys may be eligible for a gift card.
Oh, whoops. Can I put this?
No. I got to throw it over there at the top.
I'm getting the hang of it. I understand it.
The mold must have rotted his brain.
I'm fine.
I just did that faster than probably all of you combined.
What the hell is going on?
How do I get out of here?
Whoa. All right. Hold on.
I don't know how I can pick this up.
I'm too high for this?
Well, relax.
Please stand by for polite recognition
on your completion of the somnascope orientation.
You did it.
To maximize the time allotted for your therapeutic journey,
please do not delay in proceeding through the final doorway as indicated.
Final doorway.
We're going to get some portal type shit.
Watch this.
I don't get it.
I feel like I could grab something through here.
Can't pick up the sign.
I would imagine it would be the boxes right here.
No. I can't grab the speaker.
Sprinkler. No speaker.
I can't grab the bricks.
It's not something out here, right?
Cheese.
Oh my god. That emote is fucked up looking.
Can I knock it over?
This thing?
Oh, all right.
This thing's big and heavy.
What about the other ones?
There's a couple more I can do this to probably, right?
There's one more over here.
No. All right.
So what's through here?
Can't pick anything up.
Chills. This game is fucking scary.
Is this pretty?
This is cool.
3 a.m.
That's the Satan hour, isn't it?
Satan hour.
Sweet B.
Okay.
Private.
It's like, why am I coughing?
All right.
Is this like a Hearthstone game board or does this matter?
Or is it just me going like tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, boom.
And then something happens for a second.
This is a new contract.
No need a contract signed and sealed.
What if it happened?
You may think it all would be a bad dream.
Big can.
Some doors are best left closed.
I feel like I won this at the fair and it's a huge pain in the ass to get back to my hotel room.
Oh, yeah, honey.
You won me the big soda.
And like, yeah, can we just donate this?
I don't want this.
How are we going to bring this on the airplane?
Well, we're going to want to check this.
We need to give this to someone.
Whoa.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's doing the it's doing the Super Mario thing.
Um, all right.
Let's just leave.
Oh, my God.
I don't know if I can play this.
What the fuck?
What is that?
What?
Oh, it's an object.
That's weird.
All right.
Look, it's an exit.
Um, I jump over this.
Yeah.
Tip that way.
Come on.
Tip.
Oh, my goodness.
That's huge.
Okay.
That's all right.
Bingo.
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce and I'd like to talk to you about being special.
So special, in fact, that we have no idea where you are.
But not to worry.
We're working on it.
Okay.
Bye.
Does it matter what door I go in?
Whoa.
Wait.
Hold on.
Whoa.
That was fun.
Cool.
What do I do with this?
Oh, my God.
I made it.
He doesn't think this game is that fun.
What?
What are you talking about?
How do you know that?
I didn't say that.
Why are you saying that?
All right.
I'm back to constant.
I'm concentrating.
This game requires a lot of thought.
No, I can't.
I can't rant about the shitty ice cream that I am.
I can't.
No.
You want that?
We should have stayed in the other game.
I have to pay attention.
His eyes are glazing over.
I can't.
All right.
This doesn't make me like a moron.
Somebody explain it.
OK.
Tell me if this makes me a moron.
This music is nice.
I enjoy this, but I could never listen to this.
It's too high functioning for me.
It's almost like I don't like it.
It doesn't make me.
It's like too much for me.
This kind of music is almost like an instrumental telling a story.
Right?
That's how a lot of jazz and instrument, right?
It's like kind of telling a story without any lyrics.
It's just a piano.
Piano kind of tells the story.
You guys know what I mean by that, right?
You played the Hatsune Miku game on stream.
But there's a huge difference between like bopey, bopey, bopey, bopey, bow.
I can just sit there and like, yay.
And I don't listen to Hatsune Miku.
I don't.
This is wonderful.
This is the kind of music that I could just, you know,
have like two fingers of whiskey.
Just be like, yeah, yeah, I'm smart like you.
Clink it around.
Just go like this.
Two fingers.
Yes, two fingers of whiskey.
That's what they call it.
Is the amount of fingers tall.
The beverages.
Hey, I'll take four fingers of whiskey.
It's like, whoa, dude, settle down.
No, two fingers.
Settle down.
You don't need four.
Hey, I'll take the whole hand.
I don't think I've ever heard of ordering four fingers of whiskey.
Anyways, should I leak a stream idea?
I think it might be funny.
No, what if I just do it one day?
But who cares?
What if I don't?
Do I have to connect this somehow?
What did that do?
Oh, neat.
Oh, there we go.
What the hell is going on here?
Did we forget that?
No, it's not a whiskey stream.
Something else.
God, dude.
Good enough.
This is way too dank.
Should I turn it down?
It's all about perspective.
I don't get it.
Wait, this is not one of those things here.
OK.
Bartender stream?
No.
What the hell do I do with this?
Oh, I know what to do.
Watch this.
Really?
Reception is reality.
Yeah.
You can hire?
Hey, what the fuck?
Jerry.
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce, and I'm just popping in to give you a quick update on where you are.
We still don't know, but please keep moving forward, and hopefully you prefer frequent
updates to being reminded that you are completely lost.
Look at that one out.
Doc.
Bo peep, bo peep, bo peep, bo peep, bo peep, bo peep, bo peep, bo peep.
Oh shit.
OK, cool.
This is a cool game.
I like it.
It's just pretty chill.
It's fun.
It's a interesting mechanic.
I like it.
All right.
Can I do anything here?
I guess not.
Hello.
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce, and we still can't find you.
But you should now have access to a series of elevators that should trigger your subconscious
to gradually wake you up.
You should also find a variety of emergency exit signs that should lead you to them.
Will all of this work?
Absolutely.
Oh, I did it.
I did it.
That's what I'm supposed to do.
This game is mid.
When did I say that?
I didn't say that at all.
Give it a seven.
Why does everybody think I'm going to give this thing a six?
I'm not going to give it a seven.
I'm not going to give this game a six.
Why is everybody?
Everyone's just like, oh, my God, I can't wait.
He's going to say like, oh, the game sucks.
It's like kind of bad.
He's going to give it a 6.5.
Why is everybody waiting for that?
No, it's a fun game.
Just grab the moon.
What is all over the moon?
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce.
The event that this elevator does not wake you up.
Please don't interact with anything that strikes you as psychologically significant,
as we will no longer have any way of controlling it.
He's toxic.
He hates everything.
If you see your parents, please punch them in the face as hard as you can
and immediately run away.
Put that back.
Put the moon back?
I don't think I can.
All right.
So this is wood.
So how do I get by the wood?
Remember, pay attention.
Perspective is everything.
What is this?
Pizza?
Cheese?
All right.
Hold on.
I can build.
Do I have to climb out of here?
Dude, I have to climb out of here.
Oh, no, I don't.
Thought I had to climb out.
Don't get lost.
What if there's a fire?
Regular beer fund, five dollars.
35 dreams per night.
What if there's a fire in an elevator?
Don't meet sister-in-law.
Don't get lost.
Wait, should I take one of the signs?
Ah, fuck it.
Whatever.
Why am I so small?
Five dollars for beer?
Yeah, that seems a little incorrect.
4 a.m. now.
Okay.
So I was really looking to see if there's anything off.
Guy, it's sort of gross.
Baking soda?
Green soda?
I probably would like that one.
Red soda, probably.
Water soda?
No.
No, thanks.
It's gross.
It just tastes like just air.
It's a weird burp air.
Okay, do anybody here drink soda water?
You're just drinking burp air.
Nobody drinks soda water, right?
I don't even like the seltzers.
Okay, every time I drink a seltzer, I take a sip.
It's like, ooh, that's kind of nice.
And then I get this weird pop rocks kind of at the end.
And it just tastes like fucking gross chemicals.
No, none of them ever tasted good to me.
It's just, I don't like it.
You know what I wish they would really make?
Have I talked about this yet?
What was that?
It was a scary noise.
I wish they would make soda that was 60% less sugar.
This is an automated message for all patients
who attempted to use an alternate pathway
to access the next phase of somnasculp therapy,
but who have become trapped in a dream state paradox instead.
Your decisions imply a failure of orientation,
which reflects negatively on the standard orientation protocol.
What is this?
You will rectify this failure immediately.
No, I don't want diet soda.
I just want less sugar soda.
Diet soda is, oh, there's no sugar in it.
It tastes like fucking chemicals and stuff.
And it's got aspartame.
No, no, no, I just want like 15 grams of sugar in my Coke.
I don't want to drink zero sugar diet soda.
I just want less sugar.
Just put sugar in your diet soda.
No, because it already has that gross weird diet soda sweetener.
Just drink water, dude.
Just hold on.
That's actually kind of a funny solution, but it's not accurate.
Somebody said just put water in your soda.
So if I buy a 12 ounce,
if I have a 12 ounce can of Coca-Cola and I dilute it by 50% with water,
I mess up all the other ingredients.
That's not going to work.
There are flavorings and other stuff in Coke and Pepsi and whatever.
That's not just sugar.
You'd be diluting all the other stuff.
I want the same syrup ratio, but I want 50% less sugar.
Take your own soda on SodaStream.
Just drink half your soda.
No, it's the same sweetness level.
Add soda water.
No, it would mess it up.
What are you, a chemist?
SodaStream might actually be the solution.
What?
Okay.
Is the SodaStream Coca-Cola ripoff a gross Coca-Cola ripoff or does it taste okay?
I feel like I know what it tastes like.
It's pretty bad.
It's okay.
It's bad.
It's pretty good.
It's okay.
I don't know.
All right.
I can't pick up anything here.
Just drink Pepsi instead.
I don't really like Pepsi.
Pepsi has a weird taste.
It's almost too much.
I don't like it.
I think Coke is way better.
Okay.
If you took Coke Starlight, if you took fucking Starlight, kid, and you reduced the sugar
by like 25%, that would be the best soda I've probably ever made.
How do I get that?
There's something on the bottom of that.
Can I look at the bottom?
Starlight is good.
Starlight was very good.
Stop making all these other stupid things.
Oh, light.
All right.
Should I go down here?
I'm confused.
Let's go down here with the light.
All right.
It's the chess piece and chess board.
Guess I'm going to go this way.
Professional tip.
The average adult can only withstand three to five dreams per night.
Once this threshold is eclipsed by entering more dreams,
your mind will suffer an explosive mental overload,
reorienting you for the emergency exit protocol.
No, I could feel that.
Please subject yourself to explosive mental overload.
No, I could feel that for sure.
Whoa.
All right.
This looks weird.
Can I pick that up?
No, I want that, boy.
All right.
Yeah.
I don't hate Pepsi.
I just don't prefer it.
I used to love Dr. Pepper, but that got a little too much too.
Your tastes change when you get older.
They really do.
Anybody that doesn't agree with that is...
I don't...
I...
Okay.
Hold on.
I guess that's okay.
Okay.
Please note that a reluctance to volunteer for the risks
associated with explosive mental overload implies a misunderstanding
of all other solutions, all of which are far more traumatic and likelier.
That's kind of loud.
You're right.
Nobody said that, but I said it for you.
...to result in catastrophe.
I am not capable of suboptimal suggestions.
Please exit this dream as soon as possible.
Whoa.
There's a rubber ducky in here.
What can I do with this?
All right.
That's fine.
Yeah.
Starlight was the best.
God damn it.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
Just...
Hey, if it works, you need to worry about it.
Anything else?
Whoa.
Jesus.
Okay.
Well, how many of these do I need?
A few?
Are they good enough?
Yeah.
Did I do it wrong?
I don't think so.
I don't think I did it right.
Oh, moka ee.
casino.
If you love Hatsune Miku, wish her a happy birthday, then.
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce.
And despite touring the Waterfall Serenity Zone
in the previous section you've just completed,
you may still be experiencing feelings of worthlessness
and self-doubt.
Happy birthday, Miku!
So I feel like everything is going...
From me, Jeremy.
...even when the sun is shining.
Seven days late, by the way.
Within seven days is fine.
I don't think that's a problem.
I'm just waiting for the Cleric Beast sound
that they use in all the Souls games.
Meat freezer?
A lot of Bloodborne references today.
Yeah, I'm a very simple person.
Whatever I'm referencing the most on a given day,
you better bet your ass that that's the thing
that I've been consuming for the last week or two.
So if for some reason you start getting
a bunch of Breaking Bad references,
I'm currently watching Breaking Bad.
It's just everything lives up here for about two weeks
and then goes away forever.
Yeah, like Eren, I was watching Attack on Titan.
Yeah.
I think it was at one point when I was talking about
having quirks from My Hero Academia.
And I watched like...
I think I watched like six episodes of that whole show.
And I was just like, ah, never mind.
You should watch more. It's good.
That's six too many.
I...
This Blood...
Wait, hold on.
This Blood on the Ground in this fucking PG Disney game.
It's just this...
Wait, the Disney didn't make this,
but you know what I mean?
Wait, what the hell is going...
This is a scary game, is it?
Is this a scary game?
What the fuck happened?
I thought this was a fun puzzle game.
Is this a scary game?
Okay, I was not ready for a scary game tonight,
but whatever.
Why is it Blood Murder?
I want to play a game where I just have a big wrench
as a melee weapon and that's it.
And you get like two attacks.
Just like wild swing, wild overhead swing.
Don't you think it'd be so fun with scary monsters and stuff?
That's Half-Life 2.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I already played Condemned.
Yeah, I kind of want another Condemned
where I just have a wrench or a pipe in my hand and that's it.
So what do I do here?
Cry of Fear.
I played Cry of Fear.
Posing Force.
I feel like I played that too.
Okay, I obviously don't know what's going on.
So one of the lights up here, the door handles, the lights.
I can't pick anything up.
I don't get it.
You should play Bioshock.
I die, die, die.
Almost got me.
Almost.
Nice try though.
I applaud your effort.
Whoops.
It's scripted.
It's scripted, it's scripted.
All right, should I just do the Fall Guys strategy?
All right, what's going on?
Tell me.
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce and I'd like to know more
about the feelings of worthlessness and self-doubt mentioned before.
You feel this way because you want the kind of happy life you see all around you.
Kind you know everyone else is enjoying.
And that's exactly why we're here to help.
It's all about perspective.
This is why I don't have a coat rack in my house.
I don't have any furniture that looks like a person in the dark.
It's just bed, barrows, nothing else.
I don't want to turn over in half asleep and look at the coat rack
and think that someone's going to literally hit me with a fucking hammer in the head.
You know what I mean?
That's not going to happen.
I'm sorry.
Shut up and play the game.
I am.
What are you talking about?
Play the game.
Don't play the game.
Next game.
New game.
Old game.
Got fucking Goldilocks Andes here today.
Oh, right here.
You were advised to subject yourself to explosive mental overload
by descending into additional dreams but have now descended into a dream within a dream instead,
disorienting yourself even further.
You are responsible for failing to make this crucial distinction.
That counts, right?
That doesn't count.
Dude, if you ever find yourself a dream within a dream and you're very aware of it,
think of an insane invention.
Think of something that is just crazy.
Think of an awesome story or an amazing invention.
Your mind, your subconscious mind will create such unbelievable shit.
And then when you get up, fucking write it down because it might be revolutionary.
How many times you've been in a dream and you've actually thought of,
holy shit, this is an incredible invention that I just came up with.
Oh, this is an awesome movie.
That would be amazing.
This is a great video game.
Our subconscious minds come up with some of the craziest shit.
I never write them down.
Write them down.
Can I?
No.
I thought this worked on the exits.
Like, it's going to change the...
Oh, wait, that wasn't an exit.
Wait, what's down here?
Yeah, if you're talking to somebody in your dream, go,
hey, what's the best thing that you could come up with invention-wise?
What is it?
The person will be like, oh, well, I mean, we've got to have a new type of
plastic material that could be a rope.
Listen to that person.
They're going to tell you something insane.
You will come up with a new chemical
because the person in your brain you're talking to will tell you.
I need to get that over here.
Does that work or should I move it?
No, that doesn't work.
All right, get it away.
Can I grab it through here?
No.
Wait, is there an opening here?
Does that work?
I'm confused.
I don't know if it worked.
That did not work.
Hold on.
Can I go the other way?
Oh, shit, did I blow it?
Did I blow it?
Oh, no, I blew it.
Wait, what's happening?
Give me that.
I don't have two.
I need light.
Make this bright.
Light this whole room up.
These aren't open, though.
I don't get it.
Can I light it up or something?
I don't understand where to go.
Oh.
Did you know that unintentional multi-dream layering occurs in less than 1% of patients?
This correlates strongly with the 99% of patients
who are able to follow simple instructions from the standard orientation protocol.
Where's the knife?
And there's a knife right here.
What?
IKEA?
Oh, it was red paint.
It was red paint all along.
And that's the-
Look at that.
Interesting.
Okay, can I pick anything up?
It was just a joke.
I can grab the cans.
I'm getting out of here.
I'm going out the window.
Hey, I'm almost there.
What the fuck are you doing?
Did I lose it forever?
No, no, I can get this.
Never mind.
What does it say?
Something.
At least he's handsome.
I appreciate that.
This is my good side, yeah.
I know some people say that.
Turn it off.
Thumbnail photo.
You know, I thought a long time ago
it would be kind of funny.
10 years ago, I took 20 to 30 thumbnail photos
and never stopped using them.
And I used them still everywhere for everything.
10 plus years later, I look-
Wait, it's like, man, you look really young in those thumbnails.
Take enough of them where they could have any context.
Take some really specific ones
that could only exist in Elden Ring, for instance.
Like, look, I'm wearing a-
Oh, I'm wearing a crown or something.
Or something very specific
that could be used for Elden Ring.
And I took all these 10 years ago.
Like me with a Mario mustache on and a Mario costume
and I play Mario and it's like, dude,
you were fucking 25 when you took these pictures.
Take some different ones.
Only Elden Ring has crowns.
I know, but you know what I mean, though?
Just take like 300 photos.
Incredibly specific shit.
At least 200 of them would be very specific.
Like me holding a Rubik's Cube, right?
Just in case.
Just do it now.
It's too late now.
I can't do it.
One of you other comedians can do it.
But I want credit and I want 5% of all your royalties.
When you're 60 and you're streaming,
you're going to want to do this.
I'm clearly in my 50s.
Do it for 10 years from now.
I don't think I'm going to look down
on just different 10 years from now.
Will I?
Probably.
That's a weird thought.
I don't want to know the answer to that question.
All right, something to do with unlocking it, right?
Perspective or something.
Look at it from an angle.
Hold on, can I take anything from here?
Are you going to be Benjamin Button?
What a fucking weird movie, by the way.
Great.
Now I know what we're doing for the next hour.
I know for a fact at least one person closed the stream
because they went, it's time for bed.
I don't really want to see this shit.
Somebody just went, oh, he's going to do this.
It's like, oh, it's kind of funny.
But close the iPad, you know, whatever.
Put it down.
Like that sound.
And then they put it over and go to bed.
Oh, that's it.
All right, we're good.
I fucking ruined it.
I hate that I ruined it.
You've ruined everything.
Attention.
Dr. Pierce requires you to note the following risks
of dream over exposure.
Significant memory loss, both quantitative and qualitative.
Hallucinations of dreaded or annoying objects.
Unrealistic beliefs about the lengths of hallways
and other side effects which have not yet been discovered
or which cannot be understood.
I don't want to hear it.
I actually don't want to.
How do I turn this off?
I actually don't want to hear this.
I actually don't want to hear this sound.
OK.
Silent stream.
I don't want to put.
My cursor is different.
It was a smiley.
Now it's not.
That's weird.
Right click to return.
All right.
So I got a bunch of apples and holy shit.
That's big.
All right.
Um, take it off.
How do I get it?
Oh, I have to roll it.
Come on, get it off.
This reminds me of the Beatles movie.
Um, I can't pick these up.
I can't pick these up.
Am I doing this right?
Uh, I don't think.
I don't know.
This is where I stopped playing.
Really?
Uh, I can see why.
Shouldn't have quit, man.
Where's the exit?
It's right by me.
Dr. Pierce is frantically submitting numerous spelling
and grammar mistakes into the standard orientation.
Wow.
You're so much better than them.
You will not receive these messages.
They would not make sense regardless.
Saw that one from a mile away.
Did I have a play condemned too?
I did.
Did I beat it?
That was one.
Oh, no, I did.
Yeah.
Have I played every video game?
Significant error will interpret his basic ideas.
Hello.
My introductions are redundant.
A real doctor who went to doctor school.
VR has never been a mistake.
I can help you, but I also do not know how.
I thought I had to pick that up.
Transmission ends.
Hello.
Name is my Pierce, Dr. Glenn.
To the Somnusculpt welcome experience.
You haven't played Cave Story?
Little do you know.
I did on YouTube.
Professional invention.
Age science with cutting.
A tomorrow can brighten.
I'm actually, seriously.
How many of you guys were here for the,
those old YouTube streams?
Wait, what?
Is there even anybody here?
I wonder just how many people stuck around for that long.
What about the suffering?
I played the suffering one.
I don't think I beat it though.
All right.
That's a relaxation room.
That's bait.
We're going to go into the scream room.
That's pretty nice.
Started watching you on YouTube, but not the YouTube streams.
Hello.
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce.
This is a notification that you have reappeared.
Was Cave Story on Twitch?
Was it?
I thought it was on YouTube.
Please continue to do whatever you did most recently.
And discontinue whatever you were doing immediately prior to that.
The beginning of the game?
Wait, I need to, I need to stand on something.
What can I bring with me?
Chair?
Podium?
Dollhouse 2.
Should I make it smaller?
That's way bigger.
Hold on.
Oh shit.
It is what you do.
All right.
Can I get out?
Oh, I can't get out.
Shit.
It's, I got to make it, it should be perfect.
Um, how does this work?
God damn it.
I think that's correct.
Yeah.
This game is cute.
Hello again, Peter.
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce.
In addition to continuing and discontinuing as mentioned earlier,
please also disregard any unsettling experiences that you may have recently had.
Everything should have now reverted to being soothing and therapeutic.
If this is not the case, you may be receiving this message in error.
Cute means you hate it.
No.
Cute means exactly what I said.
It's cute.
It's a cute game.
It's fun.
I'm very engaged.
There hasn't been any slow parts in this.
It's been just content, content, content, content, content.
No stopping.
No slow down.
The puzzles aren't obnoxious.
They're fun.
They're interesting.
Content.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Can I jump into this?
Try harder.
I think I'm doing fine.
Oh, no, stop.
It'll be huge.
You're doing suspiciously good.
What, like, you mean I watched a let's play of this yesterday in anticipation?
Words have been tough today, I'll be honest.
I don't know why.
If a word has, I'm telling you, go back and watch this VOD.
If a word has had more than four syllables, I've got it wrong.
Anticipation, right?
You know, soliloquy.
I said that wrong earlier, didn't I?
You're reading too many mean comments.
Am I?
No, I'm not.
None of them mean.
Who said a mean comment?
I don't remember a mean comment.
I don't think anyone's been mean.
People have just been messing around.
It's fine.
No, I don't think anyone's been mean.
People are just having fun.
It's all right.
My name is Dr. Favorite Inspirational Quote.
Worst thing you can do is focus on negativity.
Won't spare you from the cage of death, the pain of disease,
the cruelty of time, the cold shell of human nature,
or the eventual loss of everything you've ever held dear.
Whatever you do, don't focus on that.
OK, I'm going to listen to the narrator.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
Is it going to be fun?
No, it's too big.
There we go.
Too much.
God damn it.
Shit.
Did I make it?
What am I looking at here?
I don't get it.
I've got to get up there.
I ruined it.
How do I do that?
I don't get it.
I get it.
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce, and I'd like to thank you
for triggering every single one of our 823 emergency protocols.
This will assist us greatly in improving the system for future patients.
Congratulations.
Anyway, you're now headed in the right direction,
and we should be able to initiate the emergency exit protocol shortly.
The dark portal.
Oh, shit.
I'm going into the nether.
Come on, give me all you Minecraft fans.
Come on.
Wait, am I too big?
Oh, my goodness.
I'm so OK.
I need to be.
I don't get it.
I wait.
I kind of get it a little.
I kind of understand this.
I get it a little bit.
OK, I get it.
All right, I get it.
I just have to go through that.
Wait, I think I'm too big to even go in this.
I'm too big.
I can't.
I broke it.
I can't do it.
I think I'm actually too big.
I don't think I can make this big enough.
Maybe.
Hold on.
Yeah, I can.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't fall.
Stop falling.
That works.
Get in there.
Can I crouch?
Stupid.
Come on.
Get out of the way.
I made it.
I am very small.
I am incredibly small.
I need to fix this.
Hold on.
I can't get even smaller.
Can I?
No, I've got to be at least normal size here.
Is that better?
No, I got to be huge for this.
Hold on.
Can I not do that?
Okay.
I think I don't.
Oh, how am I doing on time for the game?
Am I almost at the end?
Am I halfway?
30%?
Two thirds?
What do you think?
Oh, how tall?
Not how tall am I.
How far am I?
You're pretty close.
Okay, cool.
Just curious.
Analysis.
Uh-oh.
Blood except it's paint.
This is lore.
Some lore here.
1991, 1992.
This takes place in the 90s.
Okay, cool.
Reformulating.
Improved hypothesis.
Patient requires additional Somnascope therapy.
Conclusion.
Emergency exit protocol cannot proceed.
Wake up.
Emergency exit protocol has been emergency destroyed.
Instruction.
Continue with Somnascope therapy indefinitely on an independent basis
as all orientation resources have been exhausted.
This concludes your standard orientation protocol.
Goodbye.
I don't have a TV in this hotel.
Okay.
Wake up.
Where's the continental breakfast?
Yeah, where's the orange juice machine?
There's a trick.
Do you want to check out this little indie game?
It's called Disney Infinity 3.0.
I would sooner show my asshole on stream than play Disney Infinity 3.0.
If I think of like where that sits, you know what I mean?
Like if I'm just being, I'm just telling you that's where that sits.
What the fuck?
Why am I on the ground?
What is happening?
Um, is this supposed to be happening?
This doesn't feel right.
Wait.
Whoa.
Okay.
All right.
That just freaked me out so bad.
I was on the ground.
I, what?
Okay.
That was, that was weird.
I thought it was sucking me around and pulling me backwards.
But no, there's, I, there's nothing, I have nothing wrong.
Nothing bad to say about Disney Infinity 3.0.
There's just not a single chance I would ever play that.
Ever.
Under any circumstance.
Any circumstance.
It's just something I would never do.
Ever.
I also would never show my asshole on stream.
I'm making this up like if I had a choice.
You have to choose.
Okay.
Is the, is the show asshole stream 10 seconds long?
Is it 10 seconds of show asshole versus how many hours of Disney Infinity 3.0?
Okay.
So it's 10 seconds.
How long is the Disney Infinity stream?
10 hours?
I would, I'd show my asshole.
I would, I would, I just know I don't want to play Disney Infinity for 10 hours.
You just get banned.
It was pretty good run.
I think it was pretty good run.
I'm not playing Disney Infinity for 10 hours.
Because that means two, uh, okay, maybe I would still do it.
If you said 15 hours, that crosses the threshold of that's three streams.
I'm not playing Disney Infinity 3.0 for three streams.
What if it's awesome though?
What if it's a great game?
What if I loved it?
Okay.
Maybe I make that bigger and jump into it in Mario style.
Yeah, definitely.
I found the first one okay.
All right, hold on.
Is it one of those games where you select three or four licensed characters
and they auto battle turn-based RPG style with people in the villains from the universe?
No, wait.
So hold on.
It's not I choose Buzz Lightyear, uh, Woody and, uh, the dog from Lady and the Tramp.
It's not that.
It's not like a battle RPG kind of.
Wait, so it's Skylanders.
Oh, oh, I had the game wrong.
I'd play it.
Yeah, it's like a Disney Skylanders.
One of those toys to life games.
The figures have a chip in them like an amiibo.
Dude, come on.
What?
Oh, oh, you're going to make me puke with this one.
Are you actually going to make me actually throw up this one?
Uh, uh, this is infinity.
Okay, but can I put a can I put a stipulation on the on the asshole stream?
Could that be, uh, all right, Disney infinity for 15 hours or I show my asshole,
but I need I need a half a million dollars in donations.
Can you imagine the fucking articles?
I'm just imagining a scenario where it's like, oh, yeah, we're almost there.
Four hundred and eighty thousand dollars.
Wow, I can't believe it.
Almost.
Oh, we took we did it.
Five hundred five hundred.
I can't help.
Five hundred thousand and I turn and would the stream go off, right?
Somebody would be there waiting.
If I had a half a million dollar donation goal, the stream would turn off immediately
when I turned around.
It would just do the disconnect thing and then it would be like this channel no longer exists.
There is no other incentive.
There's not like, oh, at ten thousand, I'm going to do this at fifty thousand.
No, it's just this one goal.
That's it.
Oh, my God, dude, what is going on?
That's the retirement stream.
No, I mean, that's that's an absurd thought thing we're doing where we're just thinking
about holy shit.
It's like Metal Gear Solid Boss music.
I got to get out of here.
Reception is not reality.
Oh, fuck off.
That's it.
No, it's not.
Go back through backwards.
There it is.
OK, backwards again.
Can I turn this green or something?
Stop.
Dead end.
Shit.
Wait, you don't get it wrong and then walk this way?
Why is it?
What did I do?
What did I do to get that to change?
What?
Wait, what did I do?
What did I do?
I did something weird.
I went through.
Wait, what?
I did it.
All right.
I got it.
Oh, that's not good.
What changed?
What what's changing?
What am I doing differently?
What am I doing differently when I walk through the door?
Something is changing.
I'm going through a weird where I'm doing it weird.
What am I doing?
What changed?
Hold on.
Wait, what?
Why is it?
Did I have it right with the go through backwards thing?
I don't get it.
All right.
I have an idea.
What?
That's not right.
OK, hold on.
One, two, then this one is legit.
Oh, my fucking God.
What's going on?
If I look to the left, it's going to be the dead end.
So I got to look to the right.
I got it.
OK, if I look to the right, it's going to be the dead end.
If I look to the left, it's going to be the dead end.
OK, I got it.
I got it.
That was confusing.
Jump map.
Where did that go?
What?
Oh, that's weird.
That's confusing.
Good vibes and chat.
Good.
That makes me happy.
Every patient, you must understand it's possible to completely
exhaust your supply of dreams, thereby entering a state in which
you will not be able to wake up even with the help of triggering mechanisms.
This game is pretty fun.
I didn't say cute.
I said fun.
I got to get out of this room before everyone sees how ugly I am.
Bright light in my face.
All right, we're good.
What the hell?
OK, I don't get it.
This one has lights over it.
It's that one.
This one.
OK, this one has lights over it.
So it's this one.
This one has lights over it.
This one.
Oh, they all have lights over it.
Interesting, interesting, interesting, interesting, interesting, interesting, interesting.
I'm looking for the arrows on the ground.
Here we go.
There's an arrow on this ground.
I don't get it.
Follow the arrow?
That's what I did.
There's no more arrows.
Where's the other arrows?
Where are the other arrows?
Just keep going?
I don't think I'm doing this right.
Why?
That was correct.
Holy shit.
Get me out of there.
This is trippy.
Wait, there's a wall.
Oh, that's weird.
I don't like that.
Oh, I don't like that either.
I don't like that either.
Oh, is this going to turn into a...
Yeah, OK.
So what is the right way?
OK, it's this way.
Wait, what the hell is...
It's closing in.
Is this like a coffee shop?
What's over here?
Oh, am I picking up my own box?
What the hell is going on here?
I want it to be bigger.
What's going on here?
Hold on.
I got to...
What should I do with this?
Ow.
Oh, shit.
I can get in there.
What did I do?
What did I do wrong?
I did something wrong.
What did I do?
I broke something.
How do I get out of here?
All right, I got to be small.
Small enough to open.
All right, I'm going this way.
This thing is going to say fucking forever.
Earwig POV.
Why did you do that?
Because I wasn't big enough to go in the back door.
What I meant to say,
I wasn't small enough to go in the back door
because I need to be tall enough to...
I have to be a certain height.
Why are your hands so white?
Because there's a big light right here.
Oh, my God.
No, get this out of the way.
I need that.
I need that thing.
Oh, it's gone.
I hope I don't need it.
Why am I going so slow?
Why am I walking so slow?
I'm an atom?
Microscopic Andy.
Just go to the checkpoint.
Why am I doing this?
Wait, what?
Where am I?
Now, I need to be both in the town
and not in the town at the same time.
Okay, where's this door that I was looking at earlier?
Right back here, right?
Right here.
I can't get in this?
Okay, never mind.
So I was doing it right before.
I have to bring this in here
and just fuck the whole thing up, right?
Ah, you made it to the giant antenna.
I'm the electrician.
I created this world.
400 years ago, humanity fell into darkness.
Is that where we're going to get one of those?
My name is Dr. Glenn Pierce.
And many years ago, I had a dream.
I found myself in a place where I understood
that each of us begins as nothing,
where everything I perceived was shaped
by seeing it exactly the way I wanted to.
I'm telling you, listen to the person in your dream
when you ask them for the best invention.
If you have the opportunity and you're in a dream
and you can talk to somebody, say,
what's the greatest invention that's not,
that doesn't exist that you know?
They will give you,
make sure you write it down when you wake up.
You know what, how do you even make this in a game engine?
That's what I want to know.
How do you do this in Unreal or something?
It's just cameras, lots of math and lots of cameras.
You mask out all the cameras.
That's cool.
Can I pick anything up?
Door.
So who's the architect?
Who's the dream architect?
Is it me or is it him?
Oh shit.
But in white space,
I also faced the greatest challenge I could imagine
because with a lifetime of life itself behind me
and all of the weight that it carried,
I realized that seeing things the way I wanted to
was not as easy as it used to be.
I don't want the afterlife to be like this.
Every time people think of the afterlife,
oh, heaven, oh my God, I'm moving on.
They're floating as a specter.
Oh, wow.
Look at it.
So Elizabeth's mist everywhere.
Everything's misty and you're floating.
No, I don't want it to be like this.
Eternity is a long time.
I'd get sick of that.
Don't worry.
You're not going to heaven.
So I don't have to worry about it.
So I'll be all right.
How do I get up here?
It's all dogs go to heaven, not Jeremy's.
It's all about perspective.
Okay, like close your eyes.
Oh, heaven.
This is heaven.
I would freak out after 20 minutes.
If I was just floating around just hearing this song
and if I opened my eyes
and it was like, oh, there's like grandpa
and like my great, great, great grandfather,
my great, great, wow.
We all floated around.
I'd be like, well, this sucks.
What can we do?
Can we do anything else with this?
I don't like afterlife thoughts.
That's weird to me because I don't know.
We all know what this is like.
So changing our plane of existence in reality
drastically is too much.
We know too much.
We've experienced too many things.
Just play the game.
I'm stalling because I can't go up the stairs, man.
Just walk.
Oh, I did that like five times.
I can't wait to hang out with my great, great, great grandfather.
The guy that ran the cigarette factory.
I don't want to hang out with that guy.
I don't want to meet the caveman ancestor.
They're all going to be there.
I think we all think of like, oh, grandpa and pa
and like Uga and Uga is going to be there.
It's going to be everyone.
It's going to be too many people.
There's going to be like a trillion people up there.
That's that we've fucked up.
Everybody's caveman ancestors walking around.
Every human that you've ever come from, ever.
You, your group is going to be the most,
it's going to be the most annoying family reunion ever.
Going around and shaking every one of their hands
of like the 500 fucking people.
You know, when you go to an event and you're like,
well, I can't wait to have the same conversation
with this person and this person and this person
and say goodbye a thousand times.
That's what's going to happen.
Except it's, where are you going to go?
Yeah, and what if Uga is a piece of shit?
What if he's a dick?
I don't want to hang out with him.
I don't want to spend time with Uga.
No, I don't want to go to hell either because guess what?
You know, there's going to be somebody there
that's going to be like, yeah, yeah, it's fine.
Everything, man.
I'm glad to be down here.
It's like, I don't want to be with the one
like distant great, great, great uncle that went to hell
and hang out with him every day.
Oh, that's going to be fun.
Oh, me, drunk, great, great, great, great uncle Frank
and some random caveman that bashed in 50 people's skulls
are the only ones that are going to be down here.
That would be a disaster.
It'd be horrible.
No, dark Uga.
Dark Uga.
They both kind of suck.
I don't want to be on my best behavior in heaven every day.
You know, if like grandma's around, like I have to,
I have to, I got to hang out with grandma all the time
and I got to, I'm not going to be like, oh, fuck you,
fuck this and fuck you.
No, I'm going to be, I'm going to have to mute it down a little.
You don't talk to your grandparents like that.
I don't want to do that.
But great, great, great, drunk uncle Frank and dark Uga
are going to be doing coke every day.
I don't want to do coke every day.
I don't want to do coke.
Did I pick the wrong one?
What did I just do?
Oh, just water down the sugar.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, so what am I doing here?
No.
Okay, I'm going down this one.
Yeah, and also I know people have made this reference before too,
but I don't want to answer to my great, great, great grandfather,
some great man that created the first steel mill in America
or whatever it is.
I have to answer to this person.
He probably thinks I'm an idiot.
He probably thinks I'm an asshole.
He probably thinks I'm stupid.
I'm the caveman to my great, great, great, great, great, great grandfather.
He will think I am insane.
Can I like fall through here?
Oh shit.
Okay, this one's safe.
Is this one safe too?
I think.
You can tell him he made half a million dollars selling ass baseballs
and he'd be impressed.
No, he wouldn't.
He'd be like, what have you done?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, sit here.
What have you done?
It's like, I don't want to talk about putting baseballs up my ass.
No, no, no.
Oh, what an idiot.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, that can't be.
Dude, I was right there.
I'm sorry.
I know.
I'm just talking.
It's more important to focus on what you enjoy in life.
Yeah.
Okay.
You know, the cafeteria sounds, you know, just loud, indistinct chatter.
That's what it's going to be like.
Except times a hundred trillion.
Where are we all going to be?
Is there a hotel room?
Is there accommodations?
Or are we all just floating around a trillion people?
Like, is there a heaven hotel?
Right?
Like, think about it.
How does, how would logistically that work?
Heaven is infinite.
But what do you mean?
I didn't sign up for an existential crisis tonight.
Well, look at the game we're playing.
It's a pretty good topic for what we're doing.
Cheese wheel and the, oh, right.
Okay.
Thank you.
There's no concept of time in heaven.
I know, but I don't, I like worldly stuff.
You know what I mean?
I don't want to be like a floating specter.
I want to, I want to be able to watch Frickin' Morty, okay?
And I was like, oh, but will you be one with the cosmos?
Okay, cool.
But do I get to pull some levers and do some cool shit with planets?
Can I make a planet or something?
Like, do I get to do anything like that?
It's going to be really hard to replace Frickin' Morty.
I mean, it's got to be good.
I mean, like crafting planets and being a part of like the cosmos.
I mean, is that as good as, it's got to,
will it even compare to Rick and Morty?
You will be Rick and Morty.
Okay.
I can't look at this.
I'm going to look over here.
What did you say?
This is Mormonism?
Is it?
Wait, what do you mean?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Wait, Mormons, Mormons, you create planets?
Making planets?
You become a god and make a planet.
You get your own planet that you were the god of when you die.
You and your first wife get a planet.
That sounds fucking awesome.
That's sick.
That's fucking sick.
Wait, I just said a bad word.
Is that bad?
I don't think I can do it anymore.
Oh, well, I was a Mormon for five seconds.
My name is, you see, everyone who comes to these,
they feel that they are no longer in control of something important.
Now you don't get a planet minus one planet.
But news to see our problems from it.
So we do the same things again and again and again.
They're in, of course.
We find exactly the failure we were looking for.
You guys are fucking hilarious.
Whatever doesn't work like that.
Somebody said, hey, dude, you could have my planet like when I'm gone.
You can't just give the planet.
That's not how it works.
You can't just give me your planet because you went through all the
you were a faithful person.
That's not how it works.
There's a bug in here.
A lot of chess themes that we persevered.
We took different ways.
We we made our own path.
And here's a planet just for you.
A few minutes, you'll be back in the room.
Some part of you will say that none of this was real.
So how could it have really meant anything?
But just like the power of perspective itself,
it will have been as real as you believed it to be.
All you've got to do is wait.
That was a good game.
That was really good.
That was a nice few hour experience.
That's cool.
I very much enjoyed that.
That's good.
Go back to Mythbusters.
I'm not going to do that.
That game was cute.
What's wrong with it?
Nothing wrong with it.
I like this song.
Long stream.
Um, not long at all, actually.
This started at 7 p.m.
This is a late night stream.
So I didn't go long.
Pretty normal length.
Five hours or so.
That's cool.
Here's the plan for this week.
Uh, I'm not going to stream tomorrow,
but I'll be live the next day.
We I'll be live on well tomorrow.
Okay.
So technically we're talking about Thursday is when I'm streaming.
So I'm not streaming today.
Wednesday.
Technically, I'm streaming on Thursday.
I'm going to play multiverses.
I think it's going to be sponsored.
It's going to be I'm going to be playing a lot of gizmo.
I'm actually looking really forward to it.
Morty came out too.
I didn't play it, but I'm you bet your ass.
I want to play it when gizmos out.
Uh, that is not the only thing we're going to do.
We will do something else as well from gremlins.
Yep.
Gizmo from gremlins is going to be in multiverses.
I whenever they put it in.
How come you don't have a graphic tea of gremlins too?
They don't even make them.
Do they?
I mean, I don't know.
Yeah, we'll play multiverses and we'll do something else.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I would say sorcery, but kind of want that to be its own thing.
We'll start with something else.
We'll move to multiverses.
So for those of you that don't, uh, not into multiverses, that's fine.
We'll start with something else.
We'll move on to multiverses.
Although I, I mean, obviously it's a sponsored stream.
So you, uh, you know, come, come hang out, split tune,
but we'll do something for a little bit before.
Yeah.
I have no idea if gizmo is coming out or not.
I know that he's supposed to soon.
I'm going to have wicked.
Yeah, they already announced it.
They announced gizmo, but Disney infinity.
Is it September 8th?
I that's a, I hope so.
I'm under the impression that it was happening soon.
Make a tier list.
I'm not going to read that stream sooner.
This is not a normal stream time for me.
This is completely out of the ordinary.
I just had stuff going on this afternoon.
Uh, you can expect most streams to start somewhere around three or four Pacific,
which is exactly precisely when we will start playing, um, on Thursday.
We'll start around four o'clock.
We'll move to multiverses.
Probably around maybe some, but there might be around six or seven.
Maybe play that for a few hours.
He was supposed to be out today.
Okay.
Well, then that makes sense.
Or is too late.
Not for me.
All right.
That's it guys.
I'll see you later.
I'll see you on Thursday.
Uh, I'm glad to kind of be back to normal now.
Just kind of hanging out.
Although name your price was a ton of fun.
And hey, Donna was too.
If you didn't see that, uh, that was a blast.
I had a ton of fun on those streams.
That was a lot of fun.
Austin is awesome.
It's actually the first time I've really spent any significant time with Austin.
And will too, for that matter.
I hung out with him.
I talked to them briefly at the streamer awards and we said,
oh yeah, we'll do something together sometime.
Cool.
Yeah.
And it's like, oh, let's do this.
They have that show.
We got, hey, Donna, we got, uh, name your price.
And I'm like, fucking let's go.
You had sensational drip.
Yeah.
Uh, they're awesome.
It was really cool to, uh, participate in their shows.
I thought they were really well made.
They were really well done.
So it was a good experience.
All right.
I'll see you guys later.
Take care of yourselves.
Goodbye.
Good night.
Probably mother.
You know the deal.
Oh, also when I jumped up on the chair and freaked everybody out,
I saw somebody commented.
I saw a comment saying, guys, maybe he can dodge a battle X.
So now you believe me.
I'm glad I'm convincing you, uh, more and more every day.
I saw that comment.
I saw it had some upvotes.
I was like, yes, yes, you get it.
Glad you didn't eat shit.
No, I wouldn't.
I wouldn't.
I might have some pain issues in my kind of upper chest and back,
but I can still move.
I can still move buster.
That was a weird laugh.
I'm sorry.
And usually there's music to mask how weird that would sound,
but not right now.
That was like, I'll give you my planet.
I'll see you guys on Thursday.
Take care of yourselves.
Good night.
Goodbye.