Did it work? What the hell was that? I don't know why it reverted back to 720p for no reason.
Output, scaled resolution, 1536x864 selected. Done. No, I had to click on use custom resolution,
put in a custom one, hit apply and then hit done. But there's a drop down menu where I can select
it. I hate this program with a passion. It's like one of three programs that exist to stream on.
You have three choices. Curly, Moe, and Larry. Alright, anyways, hi guys. How's everybody doing?
Which one is this? I don't know. Now you're gonna ask me to go stream on like the NVIDIA
fucking shadowplay. I'm not gonna do that. That's not gonna happen. I was doing fine until I had
to restart my stream fucking and give notifications to people that it just dumped on a bunch of people
and they all saw no stream. Fucking real happy about that. YouTube streamings made- no, no
YouTube streaming. I bet Jaren's playing this on easy baby mode. I'm playing it on- listen to my voice.
I'm cured. Not 900p. You're not actually- you're not supposed to stream at 900p.
Did some research. It's actually kind of- it's actually a little worse.
Something to do with how like the pixels get broadcasted or something. I don't know.
Anyways, why does everything have to start with so- I swear to god. Like everything just starts so
negatively. Why doesn't shit just work? It's 964, not 864. Yeah, well whatever.
Did you remember to get the FOV mod? I didn't get the FOV mod because I've been playing the game
at 81 FOV the whole time and I've gotten used to it already. So I'm just gonna play the way
the developer is intended. The 20- never mind. I don't want to get into this. I don't- no,
we're not starting every stream with like- I'm angry. Okay, that can't happen. But just it
somehow happens that every time I start a stream something annoying happens. Every time. We're
gonna continue. No, don't blame me. Blame our annoying world we live in. It's not me,
it's our annoying world. It's- it's our society. Angry. Angsty. I'm not angsty. I'm fine. I'm like
a can of soda. Don't you understand? Like when you open up a can of soda like- a bunch of fucking
like rage- air comes out of it. And it tastes really really good for like 20 minutes. After
like an hour or two of the soda sitting there, it's gross. Don't shake me up either. Don't shake
me up! Though it does not imply to stop watching the stream after like 30 minutes. Don't do that.
Stay. Next game? What? No. I'm playing Resident Evil Village. See you after 30 minutes.
All right, so what do we leave off? Did I get a beard in one day? I think this was here yesterday,
it was dark. Planned your whole day around this stream? I didn't even tweet this stream was live.
Did I? No, I didn't. Did I? Did I? No, there's no tweet. Hope everyone's doing well. Hope you're
having a good day. I know we went for- I can't- no, I can't do that transition. It doesn't work like
that. Hey, how is everybody doing? Hope you're having a great day. Yeah, good to see you. You
can't start that angry and be like, oh hey, by the way, how's your day? Finishing RE Village.
Somebody said I have really boring tweets. I mean, I don't- I don't even use Twitter. Okay,
there we go. Boring tweets. What else do I have to tell you? So if I'm- okay, if I'm playing
Resident Evil Village today, like I'm playing Resident Evil Village right now, come on over
if you want to, right? Why do I have to have- I'll add like a bunch of like fucking like emojis and
shit. And like- I don't know, like dancing GIFs. Like I don't- that- I'm just- I'm live right now.
Come watch or- or don't. I'm sure- you know what? I'm sure- here, how about this, ready?
Let's do an experiment. Let's see how many more engagements I get. I want someone to clip
this and GIF it. You know what I mean? Like I gotta have like a cool like I'm going live tweet,
right? Like- and then like loop that and I'll use it tomorrow. Oh, not tomorrow, next week.
Going live! You gonna show up? That was terrible. Doesn't have to be good. Lazy comedy? No, it's
just like I- like I just tell you that I'm live. I don't have to do anything else. That's visible
regret. Not really. All right, so where we going? Uh, underwater. Those of you that didn't see the
stream yesterday, we got to a point. We got to, uh, three out of the four pieces of a thing. If
you haven't seen any of the game, this is a spoiler. If you don't want to get spoiled,
the Resident Evil Village and I suggest you close your ears. This is like my daughter's body, okay?
Uh, we need the- I'm on the third piece right now. We got it, but it's not the end. We have to
go through this weird puke guy that falls in the river. Double audio. Might have a- had a- might
have an audio problem? What happened? I don't have any drop frames. Looks good on my end.
Does something happen? I have zero drop frames for now. All right, so, uh, we- this is like the swamp
level. And I got a- I have a code here. This is the code. It's three red, one two three tic tac toe,
and then two blue, and then solid blue top right. So I'll represent- if somebody will screenshot
that and just give it to me later, that's good. You can hear the audio twice? It's echoing. The game
is echoing. The game audio is weird? Is it? The game audio. How would that be happening?
Oh, am I getting trolled? Why are you doing this to me? It's fine. Hold on, let me do a test.
We good? It's not one guy? It's fine. Okay, all right. Mod just said it's fine. I'm going
perfectly fine. It's fine. Okay, all right, all right, all right. Why is- why is everyone doing
this? All right, so I gotta go down. The exit's underwater. I gotta drain the water.
So the question is now go- oh, that way, because the chicken. Yep, okay. All right, all right,
I know what I'm going. I know what I'm doing. We like to do a little bit of trolling here in
this community. It's literally not fine. I cannot think of a reason why this would be happening,
though. It's actually definitely echoing. It's doubled? Hold on. It's not like playing my stream
in the background, right? No. Is your stream muted in the other window? Yeah, yeah, it should be fine.
I don't know why that would- that's really weird. It's the game audio doing it.
Let me see. It's not actually a troll. It sounds like the audio is going through a fan.
It's got a weird echo effect. It only sounds fine because it's a sound effect not spoken.
When Ethan spoke right at the beginning, it was noticeably weird. I'm so confused. Nothing
changed from yesterday besides talk to Duke to confirm it. All right, yeah, this is- that's
really strange. I don't know why this would be happening. Let me go- hold on.
How's that? It's there. It's kind of weird. Let me restart the game and see what happens.
It's like metallic? Yeah, let me just restart because I don't hear that, though.
It sounds normal to me. It sounds like he's talking inside of a pipe.
Oh, let me see. We deleted the links. Yeah, that sounds perfectly normal to me.
Let me just- let me restart the game. Hold on. Give me one sec. Give me one second.
Sounds cool. You should leave. This is very strange. Sounds like it's being piped into OBS
twice. Like we're getting desktop and also a separate input for the game, like a capture card.
Let me listen to it. Hold on. That's really weird.
As you wish.
What the fuck is going on? What? That's so weird. Why is that happening? Yeah, it's- it's playing
twice. The audio is playing twice, right next to each other, but nothing is doing that.
Hold on. Let me see. The only thing pulling audio is the GoXLR and the routing on the GoXLR is-
so now I'm pulling myself in here. Okay, so that shouldn't be happening. This is so weird. Okay,
um, I'm gonna try to pull it through one more time and see if it fixes it because this- I
cannot think of a solution as why this would be happening. Try it again. Hold on. The only thing
that changed is I changed it to- I moved my OBS settings to make it so it would stream at
864 and I made my CPU preset slower so it would look better. That's the only thing I did. Let me-
hold on. Let me just confirm something with you guys right now. I'm gonna like play a sound effect.
Tell me if it sounds weird. Ready? Did that sound weird? Was that echoed at all or anything?
That one sounds fine. So why would- so wouldn't- hold on. Maybe it was just a Resident Evil
problem. Try this again. Oh, I'm sorry. The technical fucking problem's Andy.
Choose a different sound effect. Let's try a different sound effect. Well, that one has
reverb on it. That doesn't help us. That one has reverb. That one has echo. How about just like,
I don't know, like man talking. Okay, how about- or just like punch sound. This would do it, right?
How's that? It auto-played. Hold on. Hold on. Oh shit! All right, I got the problem. I know
the problem is I got it. Problem is done. Problem has been solved. I figured it out. We're okay.
Everybody's fine. We're gonna play Resident Evil Village now. Problem has been figured out.
I got it. I should got it. Let's see. There it is. Okay, we're good.
The problem was for some reason it was pulling my audio twice. I don't know why this shit happens.
I'm so- I'm as confused as you guys are. Trust me. That definitely- that absolutely fixed it.
No way. No chance that it didn't. Let's come back. Hello. Hi. We should be good to go.
I don't think I've ever- have I ever- have I ever had a normal fucking stream? Like, has a stream
ever started normally? Ever. Every stream it's always like something weird happens or like I'm
fucking mad at everything. There's never been a normal start to a stream. I have to get- I have
to get normal. I have to have a normal start to a stream. Like, hi guys. How's everybody doing?
Mm-hmm. Resident Evil Village part two incoming here. Here we are. We were at the gatehouse last
time because you're not normal. Yes, I am. I am. How dare you say that? Did it fix it? We're good,
I think. Yeah. Get to the game already. I'm trying, man. I'm sorry. All right, let's go.
It's been 20 fucking minutes. I hate my streamer ability. All right, let's go. No, wrong way.
He said the exit's under the water. Don't be normal. Well, sometimes I have to be. Like,
for instance, I got a job interview. I just wish that one stream would start where I don't like
curse out a company. I tell- you know what's wicked funny? Last night I was lying in bed
and I said to myself, I said, you know what? I'm from- I'm not gonna like curse any more companies
anymore. I'm just gonna like just, you know, if I'm annoyed, I'll just be annoyed. Cursed out a
company the first fucking five seconds of the stream. I actually cursed a company out and then
turned the stream off and came back. All right, I already have the crank. I think I do, right? Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no. I did not. I did this part after. All right, so I got the crank.
I broke the crank off. I said, well, that's annoying, right? So I had said get to the
second windmill. So we're going to try to get to the second windmill. We're normal. I'm normal
today. Somebody gave 10 community- thanks for the 10 community subs. Appreciate it. That was from
Void. Thanks for the 10 community subs. 10 of them. That's a lot of money. Thank you.
What part am I on? This is uh, I'm just gonna say- I'm gonna say Igor and then maybe you'll know
what that means. I got that and I had to find a way to the second windmill. I'm gonna be normal
today. No like fucking weird movements. No like screaming and shit. No cursing out Fortune 500
companies to take me off the guest list of every fucking exclusive party I could ever be invited
to. No more of that. I'm normal today. I'm gonna try to go inside, right? Go in and then down. All
right. Here we go. I'm normal today. Don't listen to them. Don't listen to all- like thank you Cat
Sum for the five community subs. Here comes a joke. No, I'm gonna be normal. I wanted to so badly do
like a beat to that, but that would not be normal. Now would it? All right, let's- I'm gonna- let's
make a little friendly bet here. Let's see how long I can be normal. Like just like just normal.
I'm gonna say- I'm gonna try to go for 10 minutes of just normal. No, nothing. Just be a normal- just
be a fucking normal person. Just sit here and play a game. 10 minutes starting now. Ooh, cool. Oh,
does it look better? That's another question I have. How much better does the stream look?
Does it look good? Better than yesterday? Looks about the same. Looks a little bit better. A bit
better. Same. Not as good as you. Thanks. Okay, let me keep walking. Ooh, we can break that.
Normal's boring. Let me just see if I- I lost! Holy shit! I died? That was it? I got really scared
and I looked into the camera and I realized that was being weird so I just made it- I- okay. I made
extra weird. I was like- I looked over, I turned, I saw like in the preview over here how weird I
looked, and then I was like I'll add some weirdness to it because I already lost.
Lost to normal wheel. All right, so just don't get eaten. That's easier said than done.
I'll rip and run! All right, is there a place I can hide? I don't know where to go. This way?
Where the- where am I? Where do I go? Ah! What does that do? Oh my god, he's gonna jump and kill me.
Ah! Can I go? Oh my god, what's- is there a ladder? What's happening? I don't understand
what's going on. Where's the ladder? I have to knock it down? Why is this not going down?
On the other side. What other side? Oh, fuck you game. There's 50 subs? I missed 50 subs. Well,
thank you. Tuber voice. No, that was a tuber face. All right, come on, let's go. Oh, I changed to E,
right? All right, get out of the way. Oh shit! I had to go the other way. Just restart. I thought
I could get there fast. I thought I could get there before he did it. Who gave the 50 subs?
I only gave 50 community subs. I need to know who it was. Don't go on the planks.
Okay, wait, he's gonna do a big jump. Okay, now he's gonna come this way and then run around.
What the fuck? Wait, he- I didn't- go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
excuse me excuse me excuse me good i made it i'm good
okay i keep pressing f guys i changed it to e oh god just hide you can't get me through here
how many more i have to do more of those oh my god what do i do down there and then what the
hell is all that oh my god i hate this are you kidding me hey hold on i'm gonna see if i can
get to a safe place all right he's gonna see jumps there and then so if i go that way how am
i gonna walk anywhere is there can i go in oh my god open open what do i do do it thanks this is
so stressful whoa where is he hey don't turn no no turn it back on turn it back on normal
into that hut all right we get out of the way there's another box i have to pull oh my god
i hate this part i hate this thank god i get to start here though all right pull this wait and
then i think i have to bait out a jump right bait a jump out all right go i'm so i don't know where
he is what happened i can fall in the water platforms will yeah i know the platforms drop
but i didn't wait why okay so it's turn on blue one run back to house turn on blue one run back
to house turn on orange one run back to house wait go turn on blue and again run where's this
fucking white one what oh god i'm dead oh my god how am i still alive it was why did i fall through
it's not hard it's not hard it's don't say it i'm not mad today i'm a normal guy do it
don't have to go back the last time i tried just to go forward he killed me instantly
here we go no one's ever died this much at this part i are you sure so you just go so you tell me
just go okay go so you tell me he's not gonna kill me right here i'm just gonna stay alive right
here i can't believe that just happened i can't believe i don't believe you i don't fucking believe
you i thought i he's like jumps up and eats you and shit he jumps up and eats your body and he
eats your brains and shit and he kills you oh my god i have to press them when they go oh my god i
can't do this part i'm fucking so stupid i can't do it i can't i have to get it i have to keep
pressing them i have to keep pressing them as they i can't have to keep pressing them as they
happen i have to keep pressing them as they happen i got it i got it i got it i got it i just was it
what's resident evil about this by the way hey open it where is he no where the fuck am i okay
now what now what now what i hate this part all right so that's one i gotta get that is that going
what i what just happened did i win did i win did i do it i was pretending for content you haven't
been in this channel for very long and you think that's real those are big burps this guy this is
the guy that beat dark souls three on stream yeah dark guys i can play dark souls because dark
souls is just three buttons attack and dodge and like run i can do those very well hey what
this game is three buttons too no it's not it's w it's shift it's a it's space it's right click
it's left click it's two it's three it's left it's right it's up and down there's a mouse there's a
view that's aiming no you're wrong anything i got the crank i got the crank you can't climb up like
this what what happened what's going on what do i do what i have to crank that's cranking well what
did i take the crank out why would you remove the crank no no i why would i remove it come on i got
um what's going what the fuck do i do now what am i what am i missing what's going on
jump why would i jump the rope what i was pressing e i was literally pressing e
all right now crank this fucking thing let's go no crank okay all right i did it i turned all the
windmills on so now the gates open i still he's still alive though i still have to kill that guy
all right nothing else nothing else i can do here no the items nothing
this is just leave the area i believe it is let's go i already did everything over there
it's gonna be some motherfucker right here i swear to god hi welcome what we got here i have 36 000
bucks should i upgrade something or just save it i don't think i need it i'm skilled at all
sorts of weapons i look forward to seeing the fruits of your exploration i have four pipe bombs
i don't think i need anymore i'm good okay so here we go red red okay wait what's 50 community
subs void just gave 50 void 80 just gave 50 community subs is that who gave 50 before
is that 100 community subs from void or is it two different people void what are you doing
50 more community subs from void that's too much money you don't have to don't give me that kind of
money thank you though don't no more don't give me any more of your money that's an insane amount
of money to give somebody thank you all right so what's going on here i'm missing a tile
is it the colors change depending on what's okay hold on i get it oh wait wait wait okay so
how do i change the this one in the middle i can't select the one over here so how do i make is it
just blank so easy it's the paper the paper is the wrong way blue blue where's the other blue
wait that was another 50 subs don't give me any more money don't give me i am demanding i'm
commanding you don't give me any more of your money that's ridiculous that's an absurd amount
of money this is like 150 community subs i command you to stop that's thank you though that's
fucking insane i don't deserve that kind of money thank you no void thank you though seriously
got it looking at r2 d2 npc oh our red dead redemption 2 wait it is r2 d2 isn't it red dead
redemption 2 all right now what so that drains the water now i can head back out there and see
what it does take a look where you're going god damn it oh what's this on a sunny day
it's 200 community subs all right void that's this we're gonna we're gonna have to shut them
down we're gonna have to shut them down that's 200 community subs you've given in the last 10
minutes thank you that's crazy mother miranda brought me five peoples from the village just
like i asked did i made them sleep with some liquid and then i put a dew in their tummies
i'm looking forward to the kudu to grow in their tummies four of the people from the village are
dead this morning one is almost a lichen i sent it to my lab on the mountain i failed again mother
wants strong vessels but i cannot get any i will need more people from the village
oh oh i'm stalling what i'm playing the game what are you talking about this game is fucking
awesome too by the way let's be let's be honest here i'm actually very much enjoying this game
contrary to all the things i've said negatively about it over and over again i want more stuff
though no okay something blinked at me oh i thought it was like a diamond or something
all right well this is where we actually fight this guy kick his ass
mother i didn't do a good job mother
oh got you right in the head didn't i oh explosive oh my god shotgun run oh shit
oh whoa what's he doing it's like acid i gotta get up i have to get up somehow how do i get up
climb can i climb how do i get up can i climb this shit why am i gonna i can't climb it
oh fuck no don't do that shit again what how do i i gotta figure out how to climb the buildings
is there a way i can get on top because he does that like gas shit and i can't get away from it
i have to like hide in a corner oh my god he's close oh god oh what have i done
can't get caught shit i don't understand this part i don't understand this part seriously i
don't get it how do i climb something i'm just like burning health i can't get on top of anything
i gotta get under something oh no i think i died you're not gonna die it's baby mode
disgusting it was acid rain i thought it was gas i thought it was like filling the area with like
gas i didn't know it was coming from above i thought it was like permeating every surface
like a gas all right let's make sure i didn't miss anything i burnt through a lot of health there
so not good but you know whatever fucking god all right i i don't even know what to do this person
keeps giving like fucking hundreds of dollars void that's so much money you gotta stop all right let
me look for items void it's ridiculous i don't know what to say like that's thank you that's crazy
you have given me more money than i would ever expect anyone to give a single solitary person
that's an e-clown on the internet so you don't have to do that i have to like get out of this
why is my steam on hold on why if why am i i'm not even in i'm not even logged into steam
whatever take the money and run oh more yeah i hey i know i i hey i know people okay look just
because they're far more talented than i'll ever be doesn't mean i can't know them all right where's
this key go whoa kadoo is that guys i i i was i've told this story a million times
i know people from like more than a decade ago i used to be on newgrounds all the time you you'd
be surprised at how many people have turned into like wild successes from like this old newgrounds
like board and section and a couple of like voice acting boards and stuff it's it's actually
incredible i know people right now that are like working voice actors in the industry like
cartoons that you see on tv video games it's fucking awesome it's awesome so yeah there's
plenty of people that i've like come across over the last deck two decades like when i say the
industry i mean like the voice acting industry a lot of very talented people we got a famous
guy over here no i'm not the famous guy i know the famous people you know what i mean i'm like
the guy in the entourage that like just knew the guys in this isn't that person in that wait
how many how many people are here am i famous i don't think i'm famous is it a flex no it's not
yes i don't know i'm not famous i'm not famous i'm not you're more famous than most people
i don't think i'm famous you're the sus guy yeah the sus guy is not even me though the sus guy is
just like a face of mine that's not even me top 100 streamer oh no don't tell me that top 100
streaming no don't say that oh it's getting hot in here wow no you guys think i'm like the top
50 top 100 whoo don't do it don't think i am i all right no i don't care about how many people
are here or not i don't care how many fucking brand deals i don't have or do have i don't care
about how i don't care about anything okay all i give a shit about right now is getting angry
at capcom for you to laugh at me about my eyes turning red that's all i care about right now i
don't care about anything famous not famous known unknown i don't care okay i've just i've been
doing this for fucking 10 years he loves the attention yeah i'm i just this is fun for me
okay and i told you guys when it's not fun anymore i'll be done but that hasn't happened yet and
whatever i don't know i'm even talking about this i'm not like accepting a fucking award i just told
you that i i know like some voice actors stop making this about me it's nothing to do with me
it has absolutely nothing to do with me congratulations thank you thanks you mean
that thank you god damn it all this stemmed from you know what let this be a lesson for you
all of you log into an invisible offline mode on steam when you broadcast probably a good idea
mother marana gave me a rose jar no one likes me which is why i thought they would leave me out
again but heisenberg said that was why we each get a rose the ceremony cannot happen without us
all there mother didn't seem to care though we all need a rose we each get a rose mother said
rose is a vessel with a vessel mother can get her real child back even though she has been dead for
a very long time this is going to be a scenario where like i'm like this is mother is just mia
and this is like some weird twisted thing like even though she's been dead for a very long time
but if mother does then what will happen to me i'm not her real child would she abandon me no i
don't want that no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no mother anything on the tv
so can i like take this key combined with the four-winged unborn key you now have a
six-winged unborn key that was just like the highest level upgrade in an ipad game
who's that we just met a while you're the last asshole in my way aren't you you've got fight i'll
give you that even but what's the plan when you have all four flasks what are you trying to get at
i could lend you i'm trying to get on my good side i don't get caught i kill you if you weren't
worth the trouble there's a stronghold not too far outside the village go there and get my flask do
that and you pass first head back to the graveyard self-centered prick that sounds like me no he
doesn't how does that guy sound like me just over here somewhere all right where's this chest though
out this way and around that's exactly like you no it doesn't doesn't sound anything like me
how do you think that sounds like me and i need is there a typewriter in there that i didn't get
treasure i want the treasure chest that's over there and i and i'm gonna get you missed it
i do have an extended mag you're right nice i look at chat like every five seconds and it's
why i get killed every day every stream all right cool back to where we're now did i miss out on that
find out she killed every day can i get this chest from here uh this dude's all the way up here
is it a mermaid ball oh this is a spherical ball oh it's one of these where do i put that ball
i want the money these guys drop really really expensive shit like that crystal wing i'll take
it it's down here wait did i oh no no this is where i just was okay wake up wake up jeremy wake up
huh i wake up in a coma right wake up you're in a coma right you're alive what no don't die up
there i don't think i can reach it wake up jerma wake up oh you've been in a coma for 20 years
wake up boink boink boink boink boink oh i need to make health because i don't have any i have
one health pack like shotgun and i make mines no no i should not oh there's a chest over here
is this it locked from the other side is it right yes i guess i'm saying i missed this
i'm talking about right i hear something mother miranda gave me a mountain now i can do lots of
kudu experiments this is my secret special laboratory i did three kudu experiments today
but they all went pop and made a mess i put in the kudu and then tried putting wolf blood from
a needle into the spine person wriggled a lot and then killed my assistant i could not hold
down so i put it in a cage now i have to feed it that's my favorite gun from this full of frags
i love this thing i mean rearrange i have too much shit in here how much magnum ammo i got
sniper rifle ammo handgun ammo all right we gotta move this shit out of the way
handgun ammo shotgun sniper rifle grenade launcher magnum i'm gonna keep it down here
because it's a rare usage anything that's only used like sporadically goes down here
better i like it good i can make shotgun ammo no i'm gonna save it five shots this is awesome
all right i love magnums in this game doll head that you sold was a combinable i still have it
i didn't sell it i got it magnum always sucks what the magnum is the most fun thing in resident
evil because you save it you you you get like 10 bullets for it and you wait till the final boss
and you shoot the final boss like seven or eight times with the magnum and win
that's the whole point okay let's go now i can get out of here and i killed down what's down here
what's like further down this way wait is that a giant monster guy it is
holy shit it is it's one of the huge things they gave you that weapon for i'm not using that weapon
where'd he go is he on the roof where did he go there he is oh my god what am i doing what did
i do that for i walked into him god stop what am i why is he up here again what he ran that way what
kind of cartoon is this he ran down there nice that's like fifty thousand dollars use the magnum
no i'm gonna save the magnum the magnum is only to be used only back there the final boss oh cool
zip line cool but hold on what else is over here is there anything else cool i can do
well aha i have the webcam on don't flash bangs cool all right
uh
cool all right now we leave this area completely go back to i'm gonna go back to the uh the merchant
what was the point of going on the zipline was there a point of going to the zipline
you unlocked it now this goes just back we have to go i'm assuming we have to go this way like
this way i go up it was for fun yeah i guess it was kind of fun use ball use ball right ball
where do i put the mermaid ball was there a there was like a mermaid uh thing is it in here where
was it all ball yeah but where is it it's in where is it in here i remember there was there was one
in here wasn't there down where do i put the ball on the map is it not in the windmill behind it
yeah i remember looking at it and going what the hell is this for
oh yes i know what that is now yeah it's back here okay so this is the mermaid ball and that
goes down here a puzzle okay this is kind of cool what do i get at the end it's fun it is kind of
fun gray chartreuse skull holy shit that's probably worth a lot of money crystallized human remains
found in the labyrinth by the windmills very valuable not combinable either very very cool
all right nice i got stuff arteries i don't know i don't have i don't know this way what the fuck
i kind of don't want to go this way this way wait they are they helping me they actually telling me
where to go this way papa is it a trap i want to go back to the merchant rose is waiting for you
yeah but hold on i want to go talk to the merchant oh that's rare meat this is rare meat right i just
saw the huge off of these goats of warding to protect the village and its people any who break
them shall feel mother marinda's wrath but i'll not be shooting those no must go on yes it will
but i want to go hold on what's here i need fish i'll be able to get a permanent upgrade with this
all right i should be able to get some upgrades you deserve everything coming to you
i have to kill the i told you yesterday i don't want to kill the animals but i have to
because if you don't kill the animals you don't get the permanent upgrades i gotta go back this
way back to the hub up here right yeah forget about that blue bird yeah that's right there
was like a blue bird in the in that graveyard area hi i tell you guys that i'm um some new stock
i'm talking did i tell you guys that i'm uh growing sunflowers they were planted like two
weeks ago they look really cool we don't care okay holy shit 40 000 40 000 only 20 000 that's it
this is lord morose i suppose it's what they call the beauty of the grotesque i care yeah i know i
do too i got i get four so this is this is hey you want to think of a fun gift here's a gift
make sure the person that you're giving this gift to like actually wants a sunflower
so you grow i got four sunflowers growing in a big pot huge pot it's big enough you space them out
they got to be i believe somewhere around eight inches apart to be able to have a sunflower
little like kind of pot garden and make sure it's deep too it's got this is got to be like a couple
feet deep it's got to be like a two to three foot deep pot um but then as they get to be little
little babies they grow up to be like this tall they get like a couple leaves what you could do
hey i got a sunflower you want a sunflower here's a gift it's a sunflower it's about to be an adult
in like two or three more weeks it grows into a beautiful head it's got the seeds and everything
and it's and it's a great gift because you did all the hard work they just have to put it in the
ground we'll put it in the pot it's very hard gardening stream i wanted i wanted like those
mammoth monster like 15 foot sunflowers i just wanted to have like one just gigantic god
sunflower just sitting but it was just too big the seeds are tasty sunflower seeds are incredible
yeah they call them mammoth sunflowers they're ridiculous their heads are bigger than ours
like a mammoth sunflower's head is probably like as big or a little bit bigger than my
fucking head they're enormous they're really cool though sunflowers like my favorite plant
those of you that didn't know there's more and more things you can know about me
do you have enough firepower i can now offer an expanded weapon modification service
all right this this is for the shotgun this is for the
reco i should just get get the upgrades right because i have yeah get them get the upgrades
upgrade the ship and then i'm gonna buy this i want this to be a two or three shot kill for
the boss this simple modification can be done in just ammo i love a shotgun is my favorite weapon
it's fine all finished food is life and give me one of these two thank you for your purchase
yes and give me a bunch of these two all right we're good now next we meet i also can i store
shit is there with me to put something in the storage so i don't have to because i don't really
want the grenade launcher on me they're like a storage you wish to make a purchase all right
this is it so this is meat it's this one health increases permanently oh i need another fish
damn it damage taken when guarding greatly decree i don't guard i gotta get more fish damn it i just
wait this is gonna waste it oh wait he can just take it and then he keeps it okay i'm working on
that one oh no never mind oh yeah that worked health greatly increases permanently i want that
one movement speed increase yeah let's give him let's do the health thank you open what
what else do i need from meat meat is good meat is good fish all right i'll just whatever
anything else use quality meat no this is the only thing that uses it just take it
now all the meats out of my inventory it's sure to be a good meal sure so now where how do i store
items please come again or should i just sell the grenade launcher i was just thinking of ways to
pass the time can't store things maybe i will want it later okay all right well that freed up some
space do i have anything they can even use this the whole let me see i have two i hold on i have
three how do i change the um the type of um ammo i'm using f how do i change that to
the other ones press f that's weird why is it oh you have to be aiming okay so this is explosive
cool i have mines too all right it needs to be cleaner than that right like it's got i have
an after night i have to have a nice inventory can't live like that 12 shotgun i've got plenty
of health all right i'm ready to keep going everything's loaded up if it's just looking
window shop away it's the duke have a wonderful adventure no all right so we're going back down
they're gonna go he says this way this way this way i'm gonna see if i can get that treasure too
let's do it this game is fucking good it went up to an 8.7 in case anybody was curious it was an 8.6
yesterday okay now i want to go down here this is where i got in trouble last time trying to
figure out how to get around here we go again rtx is not on and the only reason why it's not on
is because one of my fans stopped working in the front of the case and i'm i don't know i'm it's
in the 3090s run real hot i don't want it to run at like 110 celsius like for six hours
this way how do i get over here right like remember this remember this nonsense if i go
straight from here and i'll be able to go this way and then in here rtx will get you more viewers
at the chicken through the chicken pen ice no so what's gonna happen is i will stream
i whatever game comes up i can utilize it i will play games with rtx on and everything
all right where's this chicken i want to get a substantial cooling system for this thing
because this thing seriously runs hot hot hot hot hot like super hot like holy shit hot
i don't i can't get that through here the same problem that i had last time is trying to find
the one specific route to go around like three different circles to find your way around to like
down here so i have to go this way i have to get over here so if i go through here then i can go
straight and then wrap around this way so i need to get over here go through the shortcut window
super super overthinking andy um what do you mean oh there it is okay overthinking andy
locked due to missing homeowner all right let's get the whatever this is in here yeah i also think
i might want a solution for my cpu too because i have uh i have a ryzen 5700 or something it's
one of those eight core like 10 core or something could be and i i don't want like a stock fan on
it i want like something right now there's like one of those h100 whatever they are coolers
i don't know maybe oh oh shit i don't have no i don't have a stock fan on it i say i don't
that's my point the 3090 just has a stock fan system and that's like i don't for 3090
i don't know it's like there's a car in my room i don't i kind of want something better than that
all complete antique doll of a young witch based on a local legend can i put this is it can i put
this down at uh the doll boss's grave will i get the treasure no damn it okay whatever well there's
that got it now we have to go get the actual treasure which is over here the treasure only
it would be a key item okay who may concern due to the luthier's long absence i am keeping
hold of his house key please find me if you'd need it well i found it what do you got in here
is it a enemy machine gun i was either played metal slug anytime we'd be when you pick up a
machine gun they say heavy machine gun but when i was younger i thought they said enemy machine
gun i thought it's an enemy machine gun it was a little bit lower of my 14 year old brain what
do you got in here enemy and it was like enemy machine gun i don't know why i thought those
spelled out like the numbers oh shit i need a code thanks for that this code's probably
written somewhere on like a one of these loots i'll never forget her fifth birthday seven six
three nine seven six three nine three four what was that it's her birthday whose birthday
i'll never forget her fifth birthday yeah that's what that's october eighth so that is
october eighth sixteen hundred two five that's october eighth so that would be ten the one oh
oh eight one oh oh eight what year turn around did you actually see the happy birthday banner
oh shit what what is this fucking leg day why is this circled
1625 2709 17 2709 17 2709 17 steel
whatever i don't know what that is oh f2 rifle f2 rifle do we even have an f2 rifle
high capacity mag let's go don't say that nice okay so that gave me uh what that thing's probably
worth a shit load of money got the treasure chest in here take those chemical fluids oh my arm okay
let's go yeah i don't want to just like do the story i want to like get all the cool stuff at
least some of it that completes that and then i'm just gonna go across and there's a something to
explore this house no and i get in this house i can't even get in that house all right i'm
gonna just now let's head back to the guy sell that shit upgrade one more time and then get out
of here some secret treasure chest yeah that's what i'm saying all right let's go get me out
uh let's get ahead out up i'm gonna go up hey wait hold on can i i get there no i can uh just
head back out he's mispronouncing it on purpose mispronouncing treasure treasure chest on purpose
yes i i think it's fun to say it the other way i think saying treasure chest is like fun it's a
fun word to say all right where's this i got the permanent health upgrade oh yeah what happened to
the normal stream i already lost after like the fish came out of the water and scared me as you
all right juicy game health greatly increases permanently let's go this reminds me of monster
hunter somebody nominated i think such a dish could be had in this winterbound frontier yes
i'm drinking a coconut water relax it's not a big deal it's hydrating i look people gonna be like oh
what a reddit drink whatever what else can i do uh poultry i need one more fish i need a lot more
fish actually whatever i don't need poultry anymore so just just dump it we're gonna water
do be fresh very valuable nice very valuable nice in something special to be fresh what
this is all an investment a good deal if i say so myself don't say do i drink lacroix
no didn't i already tell you that like the did i make this reference
the croix tastes like the air in an airplane right like it's like an airplane air was that
a different drink i don't remember what drink that was all right so we're gonna just go back and
uh you know what i'm you know i'm doing it i'm here no there's no more left in there all right
i'm just gonna go follow the signs whatever let's go i was just waiting for you this way the show
must go on skip all the optional content i mean i i just did i just did optional content for like
the last 30 minutes good luck what was wrong i had to do reverb not echo wait what whoa
i just woke him up holy shit there's a treasure in here can i get across there's no boat
i guess i don't need a boat this is where i'm supposed to go there's like two treads
two i can't even say the word right i've been saying it wrong for so many years
that that sounds backwards to my brain i have to say she has her trust why would i use a shotgun
for this what does that sound that's weird well you're giving me them for a reason i might as
well put it on the bar fresh oh this shit is fresh this is fresh auto come on why he still runs
oh what's he doing oh god he summoned the flying objects get away from me bats
get away from me bats don't trigger that oh my god he's fast oh my god he's fast
do i have any mines do i have any more mines i didn't mean to fall feed auto oh my god this guy
has why does this guy take so many shots he's invincible holy shit he's invincible is this
guy supposed to be this ridiculous why is he having so much health i have to start sniping
him pipe bombs i finally killed the motherfucker oh my god are you kidding me that took every all
my oh i stop stop stop stop stop settle down i did it just relax get out of here stop it
okay that okay that was ridiculous that was ridiculous giant crystal axe i mean that that's
not 50k then i don't know what is a job using all your ammo yeah but i mean come on it's probably
worth it i can always craft my stuff look if i'm not going to use i have don't do not don't fret
remember i have the magnum the whole point of the magnum is to never use it one time until the last
few bosses that are very difficult and then i can kill them very quickly okay there's a still a
chest in here oh whoa anything else that i'd missed in here no all right barbecue i don't want
to eat this fish all right there we go i can complete that if i want to speaking of doing
things um all right but let me reload this just go if i panic use it in the next few chapters i'll
be able to use it okay what got taken oh right yes i'm ready to rock and roll let's go father
cola's angel that's the chest father cola father cola father coca cola
so that was optional see he doesn't optional andy he doesn't do the optional stuff yes he does
what's that for just checking to see if there's any fish or anything is your name actually andy
yes it's andy anderson well now i have to go back and sell this stuff you look like an andy
you gotta i thought the uh filter was still on array health increases permanently make it
health increase permanently and then we have juicy game yum yum yum and what else is here
all that's left to do is i mean there's no more poultry right okay it's just i need one more
poultry i don't really care about this one i never do it so i just need fish and finest fish
all the other stuff that i have so can i just delete the meat what do i even need it for
did i just like throw this away just throw it just discard it right there's no point
doing this oh i can sell it okay feel free to peruse i can sell it you're right giant crystal
axe i wish it was more than that i feel like that fight took fifty thousand dollars of supplies and
i got thirty thousand dollars in return in something special thanks i still don't know
what to do with this all right i got a hundred thousand bucks what should i do yeah put that on
okay what a waste why is it a waste ah it's fine all finished this simple
modification can be done in just a moment good all right i like this gun reload the magnum
i don't this got five minutes get the pipe bomb blueprint uh get they'll get all the
blueprints what's the point of not having them they're cheap yeah was it why would i not get
them thank you for your healing all right let's see i can make pipe bomb let me go with five
health kits i feel like i'm terrible at this game and terrible at video games in general
more shotgun ammo and i'll make another pipe bomb all right there you go i got my shit let's
rearrange it and it better looking good okay perfect looks good your inventory looks so nice
thank you i tried moving on now it's time to go through the main storyline rose is waiting for
you go must go on take a break um not yet i think we'll get a break in soon though is he up on there
where is he that sounded like he was right next to me oh that's where all the wait those are not bad
i thought those were the big um like flying bat bad people things oh my nerve give me the money
scrap scrap scrap all right anybody else hey stay back okay oh don't even you're annoying
i changed my zoom button what i okay control i shot the arrow and his head that should be a clip
why are you giving me this stuff get why are you giving me this you give me this for a reason
anytime you see like a highly explosive device in one of these games something horrible happens
oh you're climbing i'm almost at a handgun bullets i need handgun ammo i should really
craft some i told you i'm a i'm a big handgun guy i love using handguns in games it's what i
use the most the reason why i'm not good at counter-strike or any of those games that require
you to be like good at a video game is because i can't do like the crouch and hit people and
hit no but you give me the deagle and i'll go bump up i'll hit you i can win but like i always get
outplayed by the person that can like crouch shoot you a crowd let's get this door open how
do we do it is that what is back here there's a treasure over here somewhere like right here
doesn't hurt you right standing on top of it is that it right there no wait what there's gotta
be a way i think it's up read the name of the treasure treasure under the stronghold
it's not above me then all right a way up a way up way is shot it was made for those who are dead
this is peter jackson's least favorite part of the movie he wanted to delete this part he was so
desperate to remove this part from the movie because he's despised and he thought it was too
long it's true okay there it is where the shot that why am i streaming at 864p i don't know i
pressed a couple of ran i i fucked it up it's supposed to be 720 i don't know what i did
i miss am i missing something here yeah the stairs it's not a 1080 because my computer will
blow up i don't i mean right now let's see i have to you know this is i want a my hw monitor has
been running for a while i want to ask you guys this but right now my gpu is at 70 degrees the
gpu memory is at 86 degrees celsius is that okay for 3090 it peaked the peak temperature of the
gpu was 75 degrees peak temperature of the memory on the gpu was 90 degrees celsius that seems kind
of high my cpu is 77 right now the maximum that it was during this stream was 84 degrees celsius
that's kind of high for a cpu isn't it vram always runs hot on new cards you know up to 90 is fine
i guess yeah 3090 is like boiling yeah 100 celsius is boiling that's almost 200 degrees
germa yeah i know that's ridiculous 84 is hot yeah i gotta just get like a better like cooling
unit in here you missed the stairs so let me not miss the stairs the stairs that way wait
oh my god there's a fucking camouflaged ladder really capecom here comes the horde
oh you don't think so i thought the lamp post was a bad guy i'm fine this timed or something
all right i gotta go what did i just do i'll blow it up right now i made i just made the angry bird
sound what's the angry bird sound angry birds what what angry birds we all right i gotta have
you played angry birds not really i played crush the castle the actual game that it was that was
came before it fake gamer are you sure about the real gamer because i played crack crushed castle
what else can i make i got plenty health uh more shotguns yes thank you very much let's go only
real gamers played crush the castle that's what i just said i want you to time that person up
for three days don't actually do that i'm kidding i can't make it dude don't i'm kidding don't do
that all right here we go we are in the stronghold now this must be they're dead i feel like i'm
invading mordor right now or i'm playing um might and magic i'm trying to like line them up and
kill too many people in the same time are you serious how did you get me who the fuck what
that why is there so many people about wait i'll time it's a time out come on oh i said
what the fuck did you come from do they just do they not stop this is quite the horde i'm
fighting all right wait wait wait wait wait wait they never stop maybe they don't stop
all right just go go go go go go go wait wait wait wait wait wait wait i guess start throwing
bombs i have like 10 pipe bombs didn't do it geez give me all the stuff is he dead hey oh god
did i drop it i'm just like farming for items oh my god do i get in items give me give me i just
want items and shit all right stop stop i already have enough i have enough i already have enough i
have enough just run i where am i supposed to go come on come on whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa he's
gonna drop an item and i want it okay big guy big guy oh he's still alive there's so much stuff on
the ground just get it all come on come on come on are you happy are you happy are you happy have
the onions are you happy have the onions crispy onions they have to be crispy is everything dead
i'm gonna walk around and collect everything holy shit that was so long there's so much shit
all over the ground and i'm gonna craft all my weapons again minecraft andy i mean come on i
just used so much shit i need to at least see if i anything's still here didn't all disappear right
there's no fall damage in the whole game don't worry maybe i got everything fucking ai director
got angry oh no did i just redo it i didn't just like reactivate the whole encounter by going
downstairs did i no i gotta get out of here what am i doing no i gotta get out how do i leave it's
where is it oh my god what did i do what did i activate oh shit this is the ghost from bubble
bobble i took too much time why did i do that i have 15 rounds left what are you stupid
okay give me a second i need to make ammo for the gun all right there we go it was just one guy
don't you know how powerful one guy can be in this world especially this one one guy could be
potentially the most powerful entity they can change the course of all history you know that
if you've been in this community for long enough what do you mean one guy who is a typewriter
not more of that shit is there what is in the water there was something in the water
i'm gonna break through the wall this is way too close for there not to be something smashed
through this this is like bloodborne my eyes are so watery i don't think i've blinked the king's
orders the kids stop israel free palestine just gave 10 community subs thanks for the community
subs thank you for those subs oh well the king's orders finally arrived withdraw it is most vexing
that we must abandon the border stronghold to those heretics if i had but a little more time i
know i might be able to turn the tides of this battle uh nay i should not put on air as it is
my curiosity that ties me to this place nice accent i'm not putting on an accent everybody
you just got political i know we gotta play resident evil so what rule number two that's
it's not it's just a lot of crazy shit going on in the world right now a lot of crazy shit going
on in the world right now so i don't know about you guys but i use this this place here as i can
escape from myself the world is fucking crazy right now this is my place to have fun and kind
of forget about it if i'm completely honest it's a it's a way to just kind of enjoy what's going
on here right now um and we don't really talk about very many things on this stream and that's
because i don't want to because what i want to do here is take myself away from that kind of stuff
i want to take myself away from it and enjoy this we make little jokes you've heard me do
like fucking trump impressions and we talked about like joe biden is gonna watch bionicle with you
but like i think that's just like little dumb shit that we do sometimes but this place is for
me just to come fuck around and forget about the wild fucking crazy world we actually live in
so if you want opinions of mine on things you're probably not going to get them here
81 fov was way more contentious than to you because that's this place here right now
i use streaming and just fucking around with you guys as a way to just kind of forget about
shit and escape from the goddamn crazy world we're in and i kind of want to keep it that way
so there you go 70 fov is too much with that we're going to continue and play resident evil
you don't got to explain yourself no but i mean so i mean sometimes i do because the world is so
crazy that you know it's it's stuff just shit look at the look at the last year it's hard to
ignore the last year of crazy shit we had like a we had a covet 19 coronavirus that like shut the
whole world down it's hard to like escape from that but you know i try you still owe us a left
for dead stream you lost one k of viewers while saying saying what oh what did i say you can be
emotionally taxing it can and i don't don't get me wrong do not twist the statements i'm gonna
that i've been making here i put a lot of private thought and a lot of personal thought into tons
of stuff going on in the world this is this is like my place to come escape and have fun
that's all i'm gonna say let's continue anyways here we go save the game did i get the fourth one
no you should try taking lsd why would i take lsd i don't you i don't want to take drugs
the way that i like see the world and the way that like my brain works up here
i think i would literally i would probably start to fly like i but maybe i would i would
i don't know i would go crazy i would freak out if i took hard drugs you want a tldr lore statement
here i've never taken hard drugs in my life ever not one time ever i've drank alcohol and i've
smoked weed and didn't consume marijuana products right okay right like your grandmother does that
shit too i've never had hard drugs before in my whole life and they terrify me because i don't
know what i would happen if i took them like if i ever like experimented with like a hard drug
i swear to god i would like i would like end up somewhere like i would end up like on another
planet or something and it would freak me out no way i can't do it all right engage oh it's this
guy from the very beginning of the game all right let's get some wait wait ready any mines all right
pipe bomb let's go holy shit he missed i have no more crutches i have no more crutch weapons
why did i reload after taking one shot oh boy oh shit stop it don't pick shit up yet
run he's blind why what he hit the wall oh take his picture don't quit the game why would you
put photo mode right above quit game this is like a photo sasquatch that focus area does not change
i swear to god i want the focus area to be up here wouldn't you think that this would be like
far away and this is like coming like well how come i can't get it but i'm trying to the other
way make it turn it down i'm trying to make the background blurry in his face it's not even like
a real camera a bloom is turned off like in the settings never mind turn him off i want a different
frame this fucking sasquatch holy shit he ran fast well out of bullets don't you know what do you do
with that what do you do with that what is he doing with that got him or shoot him in the head
i did like a thousand times crystal hammer demon this is a dark souls name a game that's what his
name would be everything in here wait let me make sure uh there's a problem i don't have any more
shotgun shells so we're gonna have to just use the sniper rifle is gonna have to turn into a
makeshift shotgun oh this is pretty ray tracing would look really cool here too bad i don't have
it enabled i'm sorry holy shit it's a ton of crystals like actual crystals everywhere
is there any more of those just free the free money room wow i think that's it right i don't
miss any it's free money rtx on all right what the hell let's try it didn't really do anything
not really all right ray tracing off it's unfortunate oh but let me turn off the i
hate volumetric lighting i think looks awful volumetric lighting to me is it feels like i
just got out of a pool like a chlorinated pool you know what i mean it's just like everything
has like god rays on it i like i hate it i still don't know what you're talking about when you say
that it's just exactly how it sounds chlorinated pool oh i got it the torso it's mia
cool your jets just a little bit more and you're all wrapped up i'll lend you a hand so in exchange
in exchange what within exchange first of all come to me
put all the flasks in the altar and i'm sure you'll figure the rest out see you
god damn it can somebody please edit me like and just i don't know just send a clip no don't do
that that fucking million of you are gonna do what i ask in a second so no none of you do what i'm
about to say what do you mean too late i didn't even tell you what i wanted i said can you edit
me and then i stopped you have no idea what i'm talking about you have no idea what i
want to be edited into is there no typewriter what is this treasure oh google google google
emos google emo google google emos plate google emos plate oh is that the treasure i'm gonna come
out of the water and be very scary i'm just gonna jump out of the water and it's gonna be scary
i know it's gonna scare me yeah please those of you that wonder how i make do that sound
just watch my cheeks babies i would like some babies babies babies babies babies it's just filling
my cheeks with air and then expelling it quickly babies babies i believe this is a shortcut of some
sort so it's cool that there is a shortcut system in this game but what the hell for what what is
this for like for what this doesn't really do anything because i mean i guess i could go sell
and craft again before continuing but do i really care to do that i guess they're gonna give it to
me might as well from here i need to go straight down i can't i missed a shiny you have about
three hours left it's exactly what i thought too where's the shiny it's precisely what i thought
too all right what's the fastest way for me to get i probably need to go this way yeah just go
around that way i'll sell what the hell was that why what was the what was the big t-rex growl for
you know i probably could do a t-rex growl let me try let me see let me see if i can do a t-rex
growl let me see let me see if it can get it to work okay so this is kind of fucked up
you see that's not what it's supposed to sound like hello hello hello hello hello hello hello
i can't do it why is it doing that though it doesn't sound right this one's is yesterday
it was i did this and i did the same knob so i did this same knob yesterday and now it's a
different sound coming out of it i don't know why don't ask me why but the idea was i was gonna go
that's close that's kind of close that's chewy that was not chewy that was the t-rex from
Jurassic Park one stop you're hurting him that was not chewy chewy is like a
yeah
that's chewy don't have any more meat please do take a look at my new stock okay i got four of
these fragments two large crystals yellow quartz damn four crystal skulls a perfect crystal skull
crystal hammer i still have not apparently found what can go in here with two holes
all right magnum no i gotta find some new items or something yeah i'm gonna save the money
142 000 that's fine i'm skilled at all sorts of weapons locations and we'll do them for a small
fee i feel like i should buy some ammo i know that probably sounds crazy to a lot of you but
seriously look at how low i am we're gonna take the first break of the night and potentially the
only break in the night depending on how much longer this goes i'll be right back and we will
we will go from here oh he got up he was lying on his back like this
go over there so they can see you after go over there hey over there i want you to pay on the
camera oh no he doesn't care well he was almost there all right i'll be right back
if you break i'm gonna get another drink maybe another coffee or something
it is uh starting to get some thunder over here it's a one sort of blue moon that happens
864 p omega low it do some research oh my god it's like i just burped and like that was like a puke
burp it was just like i'm look i this is why are you all here why would people watch the stream
why does anybody watch this stream uh by the way same bottle just refilled all right you guys
ready let's go that was fake i did it for like two people to go what the fuck okay as the great
super mario once said what did he say you did all right go back up here view bots are leaving
have view bots you're all real i'm sorry you're all real you're all real uh we go deeper we go
deeper ow my jaw that's a healing potion isn't it no just pills is a photo of a phantom fish
oh wait i want to see what that is i need that photo of a dazzling golden fish where was it taken
where is that it's like a river coming down with a boat it's a little dock wrong way it's the you
need to use the crank to get that boat oh yeah this is empty i forgot about that not anymore
snowy yeah it's a snowy place how do implantation notes all right here comes the big twist
one one male silversmith scars from pneumonia results low affinity kudu failed to grow body
transformation drop in cognition another lichen sent to pasture subject 177 characters is 21 female
no occupation no history of illness results in death 44 alcina d 44 female noble descendant not
from the village hereditary blood disease very high affinity no loss of cognition arbitrarily
able to control body transformation applied cognition control procedures sent for observation
we sneeze oh all right come on dude oh my god awesome stream thanks thank you robot
10011100100100100111 oh um where am i supposed to go did i miss something down there
no i have to go this way what was the point of coming all the way back here
thank you jora's for the five you know what we say all right i'm community stuff thank you
you're going back aren't i going towards his domain no wait what did i kill that guy
oh yeah i have all the okay it's the thing that was i'm confused because i got the four parts
but every time i've picked up one of the parts some it's like oh you thought you could leave
i don't think so and i get laughed oh i'm trapped and i have to do i don't know that's
happened three times if you he just told you that you could all right all right yeah he did but
i thought it was like a big trick or something and i was gonna like walk down to the hallway
and it's gonna be like oh no look out show that face when you make that noise no nope i hate face
cam because lets you see the weird shit that i do i don't want you to see that why would i ever have
that on there's no reason why i would ever want you to see that we say go back to louise's house
for treasure i don't know how to get the veneviento ever back treasure house oh i i'm gonna just get
out of here go to the cemetery no no you wish to make a purchase let's just go ah well i look
forward to seeing the fruits of your exploration well let's do it okay here we go we have one two
three examine the six-winged unborn key a flask of the torso what was that flask of the arm
no content a flask of the leg and of course the flask of the head all that combined captain planet
let's go i don't get it and there's nothing to get the lone road what does he have to say about it
shall i choose something i can choose something for you a bigger shirt at this point you might
as well just wrap a bunch of blankets around you okay i have the the flask the completed crystal
flask is there something here that i could do that i didn't do at the very beginning of the game
president evil does this weird shit where oh yeah you remember this thing that you walked by like
nine and a half hours ago you can open it now told you but what which key goes in here
really what the hell louis louisa house go back to the field for louisa house i need the louisa
house key inspect the louisa necklace and on here under key items oh say sorry to duke he doesn't
have the necklace because he didn't go back to the house what where is the louisa house which one of
these is the louisa house so all right i hold on let me ask a question all of you that have played
this game before how much is left of like the actual game i've got the body thing i've got the
chalice i'm about to go like open the door to like the probably one of the last areas
maybe like two hours three hours all right so well just like this one like major chunk left okay
so i'll go back and get this why not i'll go back to the louisa house and go get all this stuff
scroll down and key items necklace stone inspect it again can i not put this in there
precious stone that fell from louisa's necklace necklace with two holes i can't put anything in
here necklace with key okay like you can blame me all you want but is anybody else getting a little
irritated with the fucking janitor key ring that these games have turned into like i've got i've
had i've had access to like 12 different keys caesar's goblin yeah fuck capcom no that's not
what i said i'm just saying that i give me a key ring like a like 40 things on it and when i get
near an item that can be unlocked with a certain key key have it glow green is that so hard to ask
i walk by a thing and it goes turn where is it where it's bright green like bright fucking green
right there'd be so much better this is something to splurge let's go open the house
that would be so shitty i know i want everything to be lit up i want this to be like an ubi soft
game where i hit m and it shows every single thing on the map every single little location every like
mailbox everything i want to look around and had to be like a blue line going that way a red line
going that way a yellow line going that way a green line going that way and they all lead like
to a certain thing else to like an object i just want to stare at the blue line while i go like
this just don't even look at the video game okay so louise's house is over here we need to go
i can't go straight through because of that thing in the way so i gotta go around here and then
out here i want a game that plays for me thank you some people fucking get it a lot of you
don't what is that what is in here oh my god where is it what is this is it i'm like frozen
in fear hold on i need to just go that way oh my god it's a big guy it's a big guy holy shit
what a mine let's go show yourself i don't i can't even see him i feel like there's a bug in the
room you know there's a bug in one of your rooms like in your house or your apartment or whatever
like all right we gotta go in there and i'm gonna i'm gonna go in there with like pillows all
strapped to my body and like a fucking ski mask on and we'll see if he's in here i don't know i
heard him i heard him hit a wall i don't know what wall he hit though there he is all right let's go
i'm gonna i'm gonna trap him right here perfect thing i'm gonna do check this out ready now i'm
gonna bait him into that i hope i don't wily coyote myself if i do i'm gonna be very sad
get in the house get in the house get in the house get in the house get in the house
no yeah oh my god you little dick where is he hey come over here you big stupid alien
what a mess i fucking missed i hate this am i hitting him am i actually hitting him
just use the magnum no it's called it's called wolf's vein he regenerates all of his hp if you
hide no he doesn't don't say that i'm such a wuss but i don't care i'll win eventually remember
he resets if you hide no he doesn't stop saying that stop it's just a game it's not even fucking
real it's not real why wait crystal ancient beast wait was that the that was the big one
crystal ancient beast i thought that was just one of the wait there's there's different kinds
all right i've got the key can i do anything else i can't go in the house can i wrap around
that was an exploit how was that an excellent i was hiding in the house that was the treasure oh
all right well i'm good what difficulty am i on um the one after hardcore i think it's called satan
all right well i guess i can't i've already explored in here i want to see what this thing's
worth back to the church we go around it's worth 20k i would be surprised if it wasn't at least 30
or 40 you don't get the crystal ancient beast it's worth 80 grand is it actually hmm i mean
that's i'll take 80 000 i need ammo i have so much money i'm gonna buy ammo a good deal
i need ammo i have to buy it if i say so right ah yes save money save money i'm gonna buy an
ammo i'm gonna buy 15 shotgun shots i see anything else i'm gonna buy 15 sniper rifle ammo
i'm gonna buy 15 okay i'm gonna buy two more a wonderful adventure without my shotgun i'm
nothing i'm not walking into like the final act of the game with like 40 handgun bolts no thank
you i got a lot of money all right let's go if you're nothing without your shotgun you shouldn't
have it to begin with what is that a quote from what is that that's from what are the rings oh
frodo if you're nothing without your chain wheels and you shouldn't have it to begin with
is it from gandalf says that's frodo or something gandalf says it to like pippin
i'm nothing without my uh my wand or whatever harry potter gumbledore says it to harry potter
right well if the wizard cannot be without his wand then he shouldn't be a wizard to begin with
and he just forced lightning out spider-man oh yeah it was if you're nothing if you're nothing
without hold on if you're nothing without sooty i can't do fucking robert downey jr whatever i
that was awful it was so bad i was trying to do like the look around i like eyebrows look around
nothing without eyebrows you know nothing you should look around and uh be cool and have
sunglasses have your eyebrows go like that i couldn't do with those too much to do if you're
good at something never do it for free if you're not if you're nothing without your eyebrows then
don't ever do it for free hey wait i wanted to all grave ah it's all right you can't get every
treasure on the first playthrough photoshop his eyebrows yeah photoshop my eyebrows off
let's see what i look like and even give you more like hold on that a good spot yeah don't
worry it'll be fine just get your ass across the bridge um come wait did i miss any secrets
thank you for being funny um no thanks oh this looks good it's running flawlessly
on my gtx oh no it's rtx i keep saying gtx
survive worse back in america i'd like to speak to you about rose amaranth oh come on then don't
worry it's not a trap what are you planning blood's just splattered there and he's like he's falls
into the window got him i don't there's anything i can grab out here probably not
okay oh gunpowder don't go down there yet it's possible there's more shit
even touch this is a weird like invisible wall i don't i dislike this part of the game entirely
but i'll watch you play it oh does that mean you're gonna get a shitload of complaining
am i about to just like talk a ton of shit and be really mad that i'm playing this
links are disappearing yeah they are yeah links are just okay there we go a lot here
yeah that's uh that's horrifying what is my what my eyes look so weird why do my eyes look weird
i don't know why my eyes look so weird but i mean that's fucking clearly gray
that's absolutely gray there's gray in there but who do i look like this is one of those really
easy spot the difference from highlights magazine what do i look like who do i look like wallace
and grommet why do i get that why do i understand what you mean but he who looks like this in wallace
and grommet you look like the joker it's because of clay it's wallace does wallace no wallace
doesn't look like that like deadpool you just need you just need a damaged tattoo on your forehead
yeah somebody somebody put like the hands going like this and add and add like the like smile
that really is the joker all right well in 20 minutes if somebody does that okay are we in a
good spot no i need to be moved a little bit down there eyes you look like gary oldman i don't know
when you take eyebrows off somebody they look crazed eyebrows is one of the things that just
kind of shapes your face and i have big eyebrow bones so i have these huge big like caveman
eyebrow chunks without eyebrows they just they're just there big reveal
take me out like the others and then he gets going save rose right i'm healing my daughter
you got the soul wallace shut your fucking hole sorry why these are so weird take a seat
i don't want to take a seat but you can push me into the dungeon thing you're gonna kick me
and spar to me into the hole you think this is a game i said sit lady supersized bitch
ugly psycho dog an amaranth freak it's a test to see if you're strong enough to be a part of
mirandas family i don't want to be a part of mirandas family neither did i but here we are
and i'm next in line right kill me move up the chain well fuck them i don't give a damn about
your personal issues i just want to fix my daughter so do i if you have any idea how powerful a kid
is even around her scared last time you freak i swear to god glasses off together we go save
roads and we can use her to grind miranda into paste my daughter is not a weapon fuck you
we can conquer the galaxy you and i last chance i saw that i'll take my chances
your future why didn't you take the deal what the hell is this guy oh god oh okay here we go
whoa he can get through crouch what are you doing crouch good trash shoot go and then both of his
hands get cut off we have no hands again a junkyard all right cool gunpowder oh i thought that
was him peeking his head over it was us what's this oh more scrap good okay you would figure
there'd be a shitload of scrap in the scrap yard right i'm gonna just brush my leg there's
something alive in here joy joy something alive in here joy wait was were they even in that part
of the movie i've mixed up that entire movie like all three of those movies are just the same kind
of 13 seconds in my brain now we're gonna have to go in there i got a vr they got vr helmets on
i blocked for the first time in the whole game wow that's useful i need ammo oh yeah they were
playing fortnight vr i hope they had a good victory royale ethan this place is messed up
what is this i gotta get upstairs escape the factory this looks like producing these people
these people are being just produced it's kind of crazy cool all right whatever let's go we got
a huge area right here gonna oh thank goodness i'm glad to see you i'm very glad to see you
oh i got a lot of money little and often fills the purse as they say oh shit inventory increase
nice i'll take one of these oh this is like the this is it this is it this is the final upgrades
new gun what do you mean new gun whoa b61 custom sy g12 shotgun to be alive those and then i'll go
up buy the new one just upgrade yeah well i'm gonna get the money back worry not you can buy
semi-automatic shotgun hell yeah makes itself useful oh look at this thing already at 1160
all right i definitely want full capacity leave this to me i like the handgun
ah it's fine all finished i actually like the handgun better securing goods is more important
than anything anything i don't want this thing buy the new handgun not yet 200 damage yeah i
know but i got 180 i'm good i like this one it's more powerful but i like that one i even buy it
things overpowered but i don't want it i'll get it later it's full auto yeah i don't like full
auto i like to line up i'd buy magnum shotgun and pistol like my favorite weapons because you just
get to go i don't like it's too hard to control selection good day then look at this thing this
thing's sick if i get if i get if i come across some more money i'll come back and i'll do it i
promise but for now i want to upgrade that shotgun okay so this is an elevator i guess i can use the
elevator but what's over here something in here they're like keeping something closed in here
some kind of locking mechanism looks easy to break let's test it out on this guy pretty damn
good if you ask me all right what we got a lot of places to go this can't be opened from here
look there's not enough power okay let's go get power ethan double tap give me ethan
oku goku well that was three thousand bucks that was good all right i'm probably gonna make some
more ammo for the handgun because i really do like it a lot his brain how's the game i have to pee
sure you have a few minutes i would say you have a minute maybe one maybe two okay so something
goes here i'm like square metal object or some mold that is missed three times so what's the
are they making like weird like soldiers or something well i don't understand i've played
almost every single resident evil game and i still i don't understand what the whole point is
all i remember is like ah yes we have this virus it's a virus and that's we need it to have we need
we have a virus and i don't remember like why there was ever a virus
she's like oh we made this virus to make uh the guns a bio weapon right but i mean over like
like 30 straight years bio weapon shit never worked like we've got eight nine ten video
games of them failing to make a bio weapon like can't we just go back to fucking swords
and shit like i don't like we're still looking for a bio weapon
oh yeah see this is this is the j the 5g virus the t virus the b virus the a virus the tyrant
virus like wesker it didn't fucking work it's not it's not working it doesn't work i don't i'm like
we've got how many times we have to do like the make a parasite virus thing oh god what the
fuck is that thing it was not enough power oh i hated the chainsaw guys in four
oh they brought the chainsaw guys back i hate these fucking guys except it's not a chainsaw
guy it's a drill guy really is the mold he's blocking he's blocking he blocks wait for him
to swing and then do it holy shit does he lunge that hurt crystal mechanic heart that was not
that bad it was just a little startling what's this it's fitting the depression oh it's this
thing i get back with my p break and you're already playing no this is just we're just doing
hypothetical stuff i'm gonna reload i was just testing new weapons dude just well i'm we were
testing new weapons relief of a horse seems useful i wonder if that goes here it does
in the sacred passageway but don't go yet because there could be other things here right
no nothing i can't do anything yet all right let's go just testing speed run strats yeah
scary just oh my god fucking blow his head off i need ammo bad what is 864p don't don't click it
dude don't click it don't touch it man i don't i don't know it was there i've that's a to me that
seems like fucking really i'm skeptical of that don't touch that just showed up today i feel like
i might be in my fucking computer like a horse key yeah we need a horse key what's in there
oh there's a weapon cache in there the final weapon of the game it's going to be the lightning
gun i need ammo good i should have just bought a shit load of ammo from that guy you got it
somebody got it this looks like like a little kid got into like the red velvet birthday cake early
and is now trying to figure out he's he's he googled like how to bake a cake
he's so nervous concerned about it i don't know why he doesn't have eyebrows
like mom's coming home in 15 minutes how do i bake a cake raid who came in with a raid
there's a double raid what just happened the raid i'm like get that off the fucking screen right now
get that off the screen turn that off fundy just came in with a 13 000 viewer rate
holy shit thank you fundy welcome everybody hopefully you didn't get here until right now
it was a double joker raid thank you that's fucking insane that's a shitload of viewers so
uh hope you had a good stream fundy thanks for the thanks for the raid sing the raid song
no no that's too many people to embarrass myself in front of but hey what's going on
thanks for watching thanks for coming i am pretty normal guy just hanging out and i just i mean this
is i filled this this is a this is not fiji's this is from yesterday i drank one but then
i filled it three times with regular water i'm talking too much i'm going i'm talking way too
much let's just let's just let's go pretty normal guy that was wrong nothing wrong with me
no but that's a shitload of people thanks a lot man what a fucking awful time to show that image
i'm just a regular on my head i've no i'm trying to get him to hit his fucking head on it
didn't even kill him die can i please make ammo now my goodness no i can't what do i need gun
powder and scrap i have that i need two rusted scrap don't swear all right he'll be taken care
of i'm good to all the new people like how yeah so just give you guys like a little bit of a
i'm on so this is i this is like my my 20 my 26th hour of resident evil village
it's pretty long game there are new people here it's hard this game sucks no it doesn't it's fun
what is that i don't know what i did but i turned something off you're doing good hey thanks open
you spent 20 well i bro i spent like about maybe 12 hours at the first village part this is about
what 29 27 hours of game time i'm a completionist i do like 100 of every game essentially
um i'm kind of like people have called me uh the wizard from the wizard from vegas you know
because like i i get in i figure out everything and i i just figured out all the completion
routes and i try to get everything as fast as i can 100 they call me the game the game wizard
from las vegas is what i've been called before all the new people here oh god like if there's
something to figure out in the game you know i'll find it all right well that's a shortcut back to
there uh can we go can we jot that down for the uh for the vod the time stamp here because i want
to make sure i put that in the video like a thing that i found for the completion of stuff so this
is how you get to the mechanical part cylinder everybody just said shut up on me okay it's taking
a good mental picture of exactly the layout of this map so i can remember it 100 of it i really
don't want to okay here's this part remember this is so obscure everyone's gonna think you're a
fucking weirdo what are you talking about why would you say something so weird you're like scaring
people off fully grown male corpse used remove heart and implanted kadoo muscle stimulation
via electric shock was successful brain dead so no high cognitive ability only moves by destructive
instinct then stops attached headgear to the cranium electrodes confirm stable brain waves
everyone lichen fight was dismantled and eaten within three minutes mechanical soldier soul sold
that replace lower part of the arm with drill not enough output for effective movement need live
bodies perhaps implanted kadoo reactor into the chest output greatly increased lichen fight
destroy three lichens in one minute results with issues with reactive durability may stop
functioning reactors destroyed okay hog mold we have to make it back to the car all right we're
gonna go back to the cog room which that might be really really no how am i hurt i'm like very
injured right now hog mold all right where where was that where is there a mold somewhere casting
okay there's the casting machine and then here's the switch casting machine i'll just gotta go
straight through here comes up here they're gonna all wake up one two three go it's gonna go oh i
told you ah what that didn't hit why they're getting this close to him nice i just mortal
combat default beat that guy cog now where was there a cog is there some other door that i didn't
see there's a cog door somewhere i have no idea where hog door um kind of kind of lost did you
unlock the sigma dick door no not yet is it this thing no objective terminate jeremy who's that
i'm kind of lost i might as well turn these off so i don't have to worry about it let's go the
gaming wizard yeah uh yeah i'm kind of lost those are gaming wizard strats yeah turning off those
things for no reason there's the map there's nothing on the only two things on the map this
is a switch right here and then there's the mold is it this way no i don't know use the mold
what no i already i got the large cog can we can we get a wizard diaper check please
um sure yeah i think it should be okay this is i don't have to take a break yet is it up here
i forget not in here is it where is this place i really don't know it's not this right this is a
switch but should i just go see if i can click a switch that's a reused bad joke that's a reused
really bad joke t on the map lift controls that's b3 mb3 mb4 i just don't know where to go
i don't remember the backup generator yeah but that that could have that honestly that could have
been like three or four years ago generator level okay i need to go b4 so where am i right now
i'm on mb4 i need to go to b4 it's in the dark room the drill guy came from i was just in there
wasn't i not enough power okay is it just like here somewhere dude just play among us down the
stairs in the second drill room is the backup generator next to the drill guys like the time
where they're all on the wall is your brain check the map is this why the person said this place
sucked they said i really hated this place but like i'll watch you play it this is why
where are those you said the guys that are on the wall i don't even care if you backseat
for this part i really don't i don't give you backseat a lot of time actually it's right there
yes probably near where that secret door you blow up with the pipe bomb i don't i don't even i have
no idea adjacent to the mold room i don't even know what that is generator sus guy lost another
concrete building back in the mold room through the door behind the table behind the table behind
the table behind the table engine room this is why like i hate when there's like three four five
levels like up and down it just confuses the absolute hell out of me i don't even like
understand like i did what where i need to go i did like so long ago in my brain i don't even
remember being there blue hallway top of foundry like here okay blue hallway they don't have this
key yeah i just ran past it what the hall with the hang drill guys take a right to the generator
and use the cog okay take a right and use the cog here's the guys with the fucking wall here
like through here cog jeremy the cog the vent left no left i can't go left i can't go left
stop moving for a second okay left at the clown this is your brain on drugs no this is your brain
on let's keep backtracking in all of our games because people remember how much they hated this
shit so let's do it a different way this time no in here in here down here the cog is an admin
i walked by it i'm getting i am getting fucked with even this goddamn factory map stop at the
mold door okay here's the the room you guys telling me to go to stop at the mold door
just before the stairs in the guy divot drill guy down here yeah this place sucks i don't like
this place you move back to like the big swamp where like i could see everything
such a disappointment i thought we could join forces against that
bitch miranda concrete rant yes it is disappointing like every wall looks like
i'm inside of a goddamn motherboard i can't even pay attention
me
i'm half paying attention to our conversation i don't even know what you just said but i'm going
to give some kind of reply to make it seem like you think i was listening wow holy shit
crazy that's crazy
that's crazy man what the fuck all right all right big big i gotta pay attention i don't
want to get attacked wow holy shit dude wow really oh my god they oh my that's a good one oh my god
it's and yes here here i'll give you a good example so if somebody goes
you go oh my fucking oh my god dude what the fuck oh my god is useful when you hear like
a little bit of inflection at the end if there's like a the voice raises a little bit
you say oh my god what else is in here oh i found you he's gonna go through the ground
no they got me in a pickle shit i just got caught in second base i'm still alive right fight each
other oh get out of the way i'm trying to shoot them mines don't hurt you oh that's actually
that would have been really nice to know that stupid jeremy idiot brain
well wow there's a lot of money in there actors come on that would have been cool i'm almost
completely out of ammo i'm gonna have to start sorry hit me with a knife all right i need to make
i need shocking ammo yep and you're not even halfway through the level oh that's not good
that sucks what's this why is this in here that guy's gonna wake up wait can i just shoot him in
the heart right now i don't know why i didn't think he could get through that there was no way
he could get through that in my brain i don't know why i was like i thought it was safe so now
get no ammo i gotta pee again too that's not good anything what's my actual goal right now
i mean like what's what's my goal escape the factory i guess but i guess where does that mean
this vibe okay what's that i go that way you're getting lost again yeah probably
i'm back in this room um i have to open this door by pressing some kind of button
germa germa germa please fart i mean there's definitely something i have to activate over
here i'll take it why did i go backwards i it this is a this is a really confusing area
i'm not trying to go backwards uh just every backwards is forwards in my brain
everything looks exactly the same it's more like the concrete like fucking concrete metal
fucking walls and shit a bunch of like machinery in the middle like every room is machinery in the
middle with concrete and steel all right i remember this did i go this way i mean i killed
everything here i'm gonna go back up the stairs and you notice it's like the spatial shit too
it's like everything's just this this i can't see anything it's just every this somebody said it
everything just looks exactly the same like put some fucking balloons and shit like what i put
some fucking statues or something so i can know oh i have this i remember the balloon room
this guy's got two wait he's not his heart's not showing why it's in his head is it in this
no it's on his back shotgun shells oh thank goodness thank you thank you thank you thank
goodness trusty shotgun power use the map if you're getting lost my problem with the map is just it
it's just like tetris pieces like you know what i mean it's just like oh this is just
i guess that's just a hallway that doesn't show all the machinery and shit there's no balloons
he hates tetris and capcom yeah i'm only playing this game out of spite because every time we turn
the corner we're gonna make fun of it like oh scary this is what we do in this channel we pick
like the fucking games and companies we think is stupid and like oh yeah we were like pretend like
oh look at me i'm playing through this shitty game right it's wicked funny oh look out the guy with
a drill oh wow right guys it's a way i was just pretending to be scared like capcom sucks
when he said what i mean why yeah capcom would be back in the 30s what do you mean the 30s like
technology what the 30s played tetris and hate capcom no i don't hate capcom resident evil 2
is one of my favorite games probably probably the last five years the remake the remake open
it dude okay okay okay okay what's wrong with you what hey i'm fine you're sure to find something
new all right this is really important i have to buy a bunch of ammo apologize for killing
please do take a look at my new stock i killed igor i would do it again if you resurrected igor
right now and put him in front of me i would shoot him and then i would have you bring him
back again and i'd shoot him again okay i can't i can only buy a sniper rifle ammo from you all
right i'm gonna give me the new gun give me the new gun i can afford it now this is my favorite
gun i'm about to delete it okay give me the new one i suppose you'd call this a farewell to our
okay it's got 200 ammo capacity that's gotta get better than that reload speed rate up reload speed
leave this to me thank you for your patronage okay buy ammo if it's just i don't know he doesn't
have any well he has a sniper ammo i can't afford it i'm i'm in trouble so it's taking care is this
thing not good shit wrong gun knows no i need rusted scrap i need more handgun ammo i need more
everything rotate your saves actually i'm in trouble oh i have 15 magnum shots i am perfectly
fine i am going to be 100 fine i'm gonna have 20 magnum shots eventually here nothing will kill me
i will be invincible i got look at explosive rounds yeah i look at this all right that looks
good very good okay etrus inventory yes all right what do i have reloaded every gun
as much as i can i guess all right let's go craft ammo stop telling me to craft ammo i can't
go to upgrade the 1911 into the killer or whatever okay my next goal is to i guess we
go down so i'm gonna go to another floor we're gonna go to wait should i go where are we
press this button isn't i already on b4 i open this door a red panda thanks for the 11 community
subs so i want to be on b3 he's gonna regret selling that gun in 10 minutes am i this thing
just does more damage doesn't it got a long way to go yes it's just better i thought it was just
better gun so while you twerk it's not the song i think at the end of this tunnel oh you don't
even put like a gem or something here like a jewel i'm around her thanks for nothing but children
she doesn't care for us no she's long why aren't we like we should be on the same team
why would i hate this gun this thing's awesome this thing's beautiful
you haven't made a sound since the stream turned on do you know that you're muted
that would be so stupid there's no way that twitch chat would let that go for more than five minutes
we can't hear you man we can't hear you you can hear me just fine just two over here
you know what i meant lockpick you're that was pretending to be scared you know it's funny when
you watch somebody play a game like this or if you want even like a friend of yours you there's
something about watching somebody playing a scary game and startling things versus actually doing
it yourself because like i've watched friends of mine play scary games and they they go they scream
and i'm just like i i'm sitting here watching you they why why are you so scared that wasn't
that scary that's really that was your reaction but when you're actually like locked into the
matrix it it's a lot different when it's you being attacked because this is an extension of me someone
just attacked me i sitting on the couch and watching somebody just get attacked it's not even
it's not me like you are you might have the first person perspective but you are watching me get
attacked you're like from a distance but like pretty much you're like 50 feet away that's why
is that true dude you get really immersed when you play it yourself yes and this is a circle this is
the square this is a rectangle look i mean it's basic all right whatever it's been all right that
was pretty basic but you know what i mean it that's true though yellow quartz large crystal
large crystal oh finally some money so low on ammo it's crazy more explosive rounds more
turn off your light nope more more more my favorite part of all the movies everybody thinks no just
when darth vader and luke like me no mine's more that's my favorite part of every single star wars
movie he goes more he made he does like a more the cap gun this is a cap gun ammo i'm not going
to shoot that last one yet that this is a this is like a fight this is a big fight get everything
first look at this are you kidding me you tell me this is not a fight a big one i'm gonna collect
everything first fuck oh fuck oh my god what do i do oh my god what have i done i'm in trouble
oh my god i'm in deep shit i'm in deep shit now i'm in deep shit what the hell is he doing
oh fuck you that happens to me every time at pub g uh fire dude oh gosh oh gosh oh gosh
oh my god what the hell he's jumping oh lucky break that's what we call a lucky break
this item's down here i think i got it very necessary the gaming wizard from las vegas
yeah uh people are calling him the gaming wizard from las vegas this twitch streamer
made quite a name for himself you see he shit his pants in a diaper on stream and didn't get up to
clean it he was subsequently subsequently banned from the platform sorry the teleprompter was a
little slow sorry didn't that actually happen to stir yes stir and i were playing i believe one of
us was streaming and he shit his pants we were playing a game of overwatch stir shit his pants
sitting there like on stream like we were streaming it and didn't get up and he waited
till the end of the round because it was very important because it was a very important game
so he was just i he yeah that happened and he sat there for like i think like 30 minutes
and they're like oh how funny like you made that up right you guys like make shit up like that no
no no we're not no that really happened that really happened was it a whole shit or just
a wet one i don't i'm not gonna answer that because i don't know and that's a gross thing
to answer i don't know it was a long time ago too oh he is such a funny motherfucker i swear
to god he really is hey look attached to jetpack and head stabilizers to assault that greatly
improves mobility experiments prove limited capabilities attached aluminum alloy shielding
to assault that to protect chest reactor and exposed flesh experimentation whatever we experiment
don't change the subject there is no more subject stir shit his pants live on stream on i don't
remember what stream didn't get up and sat in it for like 25 to 30 minutes i think he actually
left the stream too i think he was like i gotta go it was like all right i think he turned his
stream off that's it that's the whole story there's nothing else for you to know there's nothing else
you need to know for that story it's over the story has ended stop pretending like we haven't
sat in shit before i don't think that's ever happened before to me is the link for it where
is it the mod link me is it actually archived why are you exposing him he told he told this
story on stream this is not like i didn't i'm not exposing stir he like shit his pants
you're really stepping it mate that was a distraction this video has 20 000 views
it's not like oh wow i'm exposing him you're really stepping it mate that was a distraction
you really stepped in it mate this is my stream yeah some dog poop on the ground this is my stream
no is this his stream oh my god i have to do a big poop
and the character's classes it's just easier i don't know classes classes in session
that's how calm i sound i'm so calm what happened to me this is 26 minute long video
go to 807 why did you go on modpocalypse what happened it was all your fault remember that time
you were like in my chat and you like banned everyone as a joke and blamed it all on me
i didn't do that that's a lie i didn't that's a lie other mercy is gonna have
like now oh you enjoy a good story the movie deadpool that's not a story that's a statement
let me tell you a story aka i'm gonna say one statement so you have a statement no it could
be told in three words you're gonna ask questions if i said the three words but yeah just don't
fucking worry about 807 we're getting there so how interested in the story am i gonna be
oh my god are we talking like edge of my seat like leaning forward what or like kind of just
leaning back like eating a bag of chips like i don't all right all right you remember last night
when we were playing overwatch and i like really had to go to the bathroom right i shit my pants
that's that's the story that's the three words i shit my pants
oh wait it doesn't happen on this screen yeah just a little bit just a little
when i was streaming yeah when you were streaming you shit your pants on my stream yeah
and that's why you were gone for like 25 minutes oh yeah oh yeah do we have that stream anywhere
i mean it's like five years ago you just you know you just try and squeak a couple farts out
what did you eat what oh what the fuck oh why would i ask that don't ask that what the hell
don't ask him that what happened i ate like two double bacon cheeseburgers from five guys
in like in a hurry in a fucking hurry hurry yeah let's just say i was i was really hungry
oh my god and what's four words well then take a word out i shit pants i shit my pants holy shit
do you hear that that's a fucking thunderstorm going on over here all right well there you go
that's the beginning video of this frame all right let's get back to this let's go wait wait
what's somebody has the weather what's the weather from vegas what the vegas condition
are clear the temperature the wind is blowing east current humidity is 58 like fucking three
days ago this is raining oh maybe that's what i'm hearing cloudy oh whatever all right let's go
it's time to fight the final demon shoot it shoot it
shit that was close wait there might be some treats there might there is there look at this
some treats and trinkets over here so what are those goats actually doing what is it what am i
actually doing i'm gonna go to the bathroom and take a shit i don't have to go i do here we're
missing here oh it's everything need to do a leap of faith i can i oh shit there's i don't even see
this it was being clouded don't go up there there's probably no nothing germa auto germa auto two
germa auto three germa auto four germa auto five germa auto six germa auto seven germa auto eight
it's an eight part emote of auto space it's in here uh-huh always look around i don't have any
heels i have one first aid that's it i'm in trouble soon she'll start her ceremony with your
if that happens it's all over it'll be fine okay for your kid and for the whole village
but don't worry i'll don't get hit forehead okay i'll use rose to kill merenda
you're the only one who doesn't see your kids power take rose i'd like to see you try
key mold don't tell me i have to go all the way back to that mold place right i don't actually
have to do that do i kidding me oh that sure is dumb i don't want to do that there's more
but oh my god i have to go do the key mold and mold the key go in the horse door and then go in
this horse door wow all right that was on the first that was on beef the first floor before
still have no ammo hi germa i'm going to bed good night as you wish large crystal free
yellow uh yellow quartz is worth a lot got a lot of stuff don't i
as always all right 62 000 don't like i can't buy any ammo
shit all right shot i don't have any money what should i do you can't you make ammo scroll down
to buy ammo no it's all sold out crap the ammo securing goods is more important
i can't a good deal if i say so myself i would rather have health than ammo i'm gonna save money
while you work all right let's go down let's make the mold we have to go all the way down
to b4 right and there's something in there is like a place to go in b4
what is it you can't hide from this question forever where's the grotto beast shit
well you'd be pleased to know that the grotto beast merchandise currently being worked on
right now you will be able to purchase grotto beast cards very soon we don't have a date for
you yet but you will see them i think it's a little more involved than a lot of you guys think
it's fucking awesome more details very soon more details very soon very soon all right i need to go
to inside of not is it here in like the actual factory which is this way right am i in the
right place i hope so oh this is not the right place but okay boundary is it b3
i think it's right i think it's in the right place that's the shit out of me god you okay dude
yeah it's a scary game that's all i am running out of stuff to shoot you with
all right where's that room where is it boundary where is it downstairs okay at least i have i
got four shots make this key where's the keyhole okay there's this one here wait okay make the key
hole go that way all right all right i gotta make them count i have to make this shit count
here it is all right so if i make this here and then i go bang of right and go that way i can
open up that heisenberg door upgrade the capacity so you get a full magazine that's a good call
good call heisenberg's key go let's go somebody in here there are quite actually a few of you in
here uh i got a better idea sit down please thank you more ammo running on empty
jesse you brought the wrong shit oh yes thank goodness mechanical part shaft
all right operating room what is the mechanic what is that oh nice i got his hammer heisenberg's
hammer very cool so i could go down here you know what i need to collect shit this is wait
this is gonna take me down i don't want to go down here can i go anywhere through here i don't think
so god damn right use it oh well it's in the elevator oh well let's go ah missing i'm gonna
miss a secret whatever oh well gonna be another one of these assholes here and know it where is
he oh it's a huge one oh oh oh oh oh oh oh fuck you oh come on how is it not hitting him how much
does it take no no magnum see what a waste of a magnum that would have been perfect crystal
mechanical heart get me the hell out of here i go on the right way i go on the right way no of course
not oh god he's the magnum on this thing i tried to fucking run just run no i want the money
fuck the stupid mechanical bullshit everywhere put a fucking generator in the middle put a
generator on the left side put a jet and stick fucking mechanical generators and
generator put a generator there die motherfucker generator mechanical machine generator stick
give him this much space to walk get it leave oh i'm so glad to see you
gamer grease on your forehead that's not that's just the lighting wish to make a purchase all
right that's 50 grand that was worth it that was actually worth it glad i did it your coin
eisenberg's hammer 45 000 i'll take it all right here we go this is all an investment
so if i increase this capacity i will get 14 shots worth doing ah it's fine all finished
our leave this to me i'm gonna do power to do power on this too for ammo capacity
this simple modification can be done in just a moment good day then
okay 14 all right i'm going to switch this to flash banks and use them
because why not our saves ammo it's better than capacity you know that is actually probably true
all right now we have to go up open that other door and i i'm assuming this is probably one of
the major fights of the whole game or damage you do less ammo you use that's right as long as i hit
my shots well i've got about 13 or 14 magnum shots to make let's hope i make them two heals
i wonder if i'm gonna be able to do this let's find out i'm over the railing holy shit well
that helped a lot thank you one guy that's thanks a lot that actually really helped a lot
how do i get back up oh there's a zipline anything up here oh shit nice okay
the one guy giveth and the one guy if taketh one guy giveth and one guy taketh
i was supposed to do this now i was just thinking of ways to pass the time
ah you'll be slaughtering things in droves securing goods i want it please come again
it's time you really are a tough one i'm tired of chit-chat time to die
final fight of heisenberg
sniper rifle ammo what are they giving me all right first aid ammo ammo ammo
money what's this prototype sturm used a cheap turboprop engine but he's impossible to control
all he does is charge too much power output from the reactor completely invincible head-on
the dumbass managed to chop his own damn arms off on the propeller also issues with overheating
from running for long periods so we need to just avoid him he's invincible from the front
let him run out of gas and then shoot him with a shotgun into his spinal cord got it okay make
sure everything's loaded i have the magnum if i need it i have rockets if i need it i have a
bunch of mines and shit i'm actually going to put mines but isn't he invincible from the front
wouldn't mines be kind of a waste of time here i know i don't have time for this bullshit
i don't wait wait what what the fuck is happening what oh i can get out
ow oh shit i should restart it right restart restart kill me restart restart restart restart
restart oh why can't i die when i want to where do you go okay let's go you really are a tough
one oh we have to do this shit again come on but i'm tired of chinchats time to die
you can hear it can't you someone waiting for you okay so he breaks the wall and then it's just a
case of just let him run out of gas shoot him in the back let's go one two three power power
i don't have time for this bullshit out of my way power power power power okay why is it okay well
whatever he did why is it not broken holy shit he can turn oh my god i'm in trouble i'm in trouble
i'm in a lot of trouble i'm good you all right what's that mean oh he's like just super mode
oh my god what's happening oh oh oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh my god just run out of the way
he's burning he's burning my skin what am i doing what the hell he's pissed again mines use mine
where's the mine did he break the mine did he break the mine is the mine still there it's not
there anymore he broke it stop destroying my minds you fucking asshole ah he's not dead now stay down
take a photo oh you killed my little toy you're next snake that's what he sounds like
sounds like a snake guy i didn't i didn't have to even use a uh revolver that's good cigar brand
it is abominable her deceit knows no bounds for merely a bunch of failed kadu experiments to her
i was just lucky i had more affinity to the stuff than the other poor schmucks in the village so
she still calls me her son what a joke i'll never forgive what she did to me that crazy bitch has
never been right in the head she can't see a difference between experiment and family
Miranda didn't just change my body she took my dignity if i don't kill her then my life will
never be my own still she may be crazy but she's also powerful she can turn into anyone using the
mega me site the trick is that brat rose if i could access her power then maybe speaking of
the kid's dad Ethan has a pretty interesting body himself maybe i could get him to help me out
okay let's see what you got in here something in this room what's in this very room chem fluid
let's see what i can do here i can't do anything right it continues this looks like another
boss what is it like a back-to-back boss fight or something it's not back-to-back fight is it
the boss rush well that sucks anything else over here um not really okay in one of these things
right one of these little let's go all right we got lightning outside nothing in here either
like oh yeah he can like bend metal and stuff right he's got like magneto powers
no not bad you're persistent but i've got a rebellion so stay out of my way i feel like i
did that what the hell
that's a dog from half-life that was cool he used all the junk metal that bastard
why wouldn't you just kill me again like why not just kill me shoot me i'm like getting rid of me
he wants me to join yeah he wants me to join his little group or whatever i don't know what it is
oh i told you to leave it alone you are in the way what do you care chris you killed my
wife you son of a bitch you think i killed me you didn't take the grenade launcher chris wasn't her
it was miranda what she's a bio weapon she changed her appearance and pretended to be mia
seems she also survived new shots so now i'm here to finish the job
bullshit why don't you fucking tell me right away because i knew you would want to be involved
this job is hard enough without civilians getting in the way yeah which will get
chris files will you play like his side of the story what the hell is going on
dlc i guess i owe you an explanation hand me that wrench long story short miranda's fucking insane
this village all these monsters and freaks this is their life's work
some sort of crazy experiment with the mold like louisiana god damn it all this time
i thought i could save my family i can't escape from here i can't do anything that might not be
true take a look at this my men sent those pictures a few minutes ago miranda keep looking
don't go too far though don't go too far oh shit we gotta go relax my men are monitoring the
situation but they have my daughter and it looked good last saturday don't go more than five
that's the most nerve-wracking thing ever when somebody has your phone down here and finish
planting explosives you take that elevator i'll meet you topside when you say hey look at this
picture and they go oh cool yeah and they swipe and they swipe and i don't do that
she's a dead woman that's all i didn't do that's all i wanted to show you just that one that one
photo you don't need to i don't want to show you anything else all right ethan you take this
and do me a favor try to stay under the radar why does he have like a wesker look-alike costume on
owned wolf squad the sweep of the factory is complete no proof of any connection with the
organization guess this was just wasn't our day uh i did manage to get my hands on a number of
documents disclosing some of miranda's experiments which support our previous theories
she seems to have infected herself with the muta mesite which grants her a number of abilities
including mimic mimicry she can control herself and transform herself to look like anyone or
anything so that could have just been her she disguised herself as mia and infiltrated the
winter's home her objective was to kidnap rose maybe she thought she could control rose easier
if she looked like her mom when we attacked it put a little damper on her plan so she
mimicked a corpse but is she the guy that's been lying around remember the guy that i keep saying
like hey this guy's like in every scene why is he lying down on the ground is that her she then
revived herself from the transport truck killed everyone on board and took off with rose things
didn't go the way she had originally planned but in the end she still got what she wanted
till now it's time to rendezvous and blow this place sky high this might turn into a fight with
heisenberg but i think i found something useful he left one of his little toys laying around and
it's even made from a metal polymer composite we can't control time to turn the tables
tank fight got ourselves a tank fight uh this shit in here i don't want to leave without it
maybe this will save me some ammo okay let's go save the game i have to hold this for this long
it was a really long hold metal polymer composite huh time to fight fire with fire
oh my god old ready cannon fire cannon guard do i have ammo i have infinite ammo oops can i die
reloading hurry up come on come on come on all right wait for it to reload i don't want to go
let's go you're like a god damn cockroach oh battle box
i think you can take me on before i kill that bitch let's start
nice run away all right right there i see a weak point mom i see a weak point oh shit that hurt
oh got it other arm
oh
out
funny
i'm a goddamn superhero what do i have to shoot him
what do you have to shoot him whatever to shoot him in the head oh is he is he up there
i can't even tell
what's wrong with the face what happened did i beat him oh chris has one too
what
where should i shoot him what is what's his weak point the head
head
and the eyes only fans what do you mean only what are you saying only fans for where is this body
where do i have to shoot him this is so anime
am i shooting in the head oh my god
oh why shoot the flux capacitor
run away run away get behind that thing get behind that thing get behind it get behind it get behind
behind behind oh my fucking god carry him
die like the world's watching again what am i supposed to do i don't know what i would shoot
him oh fuck so long i've taken my deal after life wait what what the hell how would i have done that
yeah crystal heisenberg my phone is ringing i'm it's mom mom you did it son i saw you beat
heisenberg that was very tricky what the hell happened i dealt with heisenberg now i'm gonna
find miranda and get rose back not without me it's too dangerous rose then respond nia our child
she's so important isn't she she's everything to me and mine to me she's a mimic with heisenberg on
you've lost your lead what are you going to do i don't know but i'm saving rose yes
you'd never know do you even when i took me his place in your home poor ethan who are you
where's rose enough remember evelyn and her power over the mall rose is her successor
no rose is evelyn's true complete form that happened she will grow to fully control the masses
and i must have her fuck you you crazy bitch
oh if that were a magnum i would be scared
but you don't have 15 bullets in that gun do you however she will be reborn as my daughter
she's my child not yours where are you show yourself why did rose come to be was it because
oh there's sort of shock on this lady and you are truly a special case
but i've learned all i can for you you're worth as a lab rat has run out miranda you coward come
on and face me i already have don't worry your death will come you will join the megamycetes records
uh he will join the turbo ice i will make sure to sample your blood for later once dawn breaks
the ceremony will be complete and i will become her true mother bound for eternity blood
but
i've waited so long the dreams really can come true vessel or not i can't wait to see my true child
who's what i just took a picture of her who's who is perspective is this the camera has sent
to you now oh shit i'm just a camera what am i gonna do take pictures captain have confirmed
the death of ethan winters i wasn't able to retrieve the body but i can't is that it share
your screen now and i'll go over this play as chris and you probably fight my team and i were
careless yesterday we took down the transformed miranda but we didn't kill her since miranda
could have infected ethan i forcefully took him and rose with us but the vehicle they were
riding in was attacked when i got to the wreck ethan and rose were gone that's not an ending
the last time i was able to contact ethan that's not the end of the game i heard miranda's voice
she murdered him is he driving not chris eyes on the fucking road when does it end all of it
three years trying to put this thing in the ground three years too long i didn't use the magnum sir
you're pretending to drive a car again like an action movie sequence yeah this is you play as
chris and you've been you i didn't use the magnum i used it once oh my god bsa got here already they
didn't waste any time mission adjustment no it doesn't change anything terminate miranda and
rescue rose that's the mission that failure is not an option can chris at least take his stuff
like old times move out roger k-9 i want to know what the hell bsa is doing here
find out what you can roger then i'm on it in a while since we fought together captain
fuck when was it last the desert doing nothing but recon's gotten me out of shape but thanks
to your recon we know miranda's plan we're not actually gonna do like uh
nothing to sneeze at either spooky you know oh no no i mean they did this in the other
fucking game it's the part that i hated the most and then they change your character and they take
your whole inventory away and they make you do like i had 15 magnum shots to shoot and i don't
get to shoot them now yes i feel like that person could have corrected that take that thing out
at your back boss let's get to work everyone watch for hostile bio weapons
roger hey that's what i'm gonna do to this motherfucker down there
what about you man let's see it made contact with a group of hostile bio
it's god
god
oh yeah oh it doesn't matter to take fucking a million rounds it doesn't matter it's all
go that's probably where miranda is oh shit let's move out oh wait we got a big guy big guy coming in
don't worry i got this
watch your six watch out you got a bogey here
i have to buy one of my supplies what about i have to make sure
i fish it on it's clear keep going uh boss i get a well down here
umber eyes i need some backup no i really i really don't i need backup
oh wait i gotta look crazy here it's 8.7 is falling
what is what am i doing what the fuck is this thing am i like trimming my nose hairs what is that
oh nice dude dude what a kill streak what all right enemy uav is online our uav is airborne
but grab me what whatever reach the target location what about this guy marking the target
roger that guy go uh okay that guy's gone target acquired uh i heard this game uh there's a low
supply is a target locator working shut up i'm getting i'm doing my terrible ending the way
that i want this dude is fucked i go in here just point the laser at the target and leave the rest
to me what the hell what do you want me to do with the laser oh it's the nose hair trimmer
you're good reloading now just a minute there's a swarm headed that way it sure is
is
say good night what happened i beat him okay captain i'm reloading ready when you are hold on
shit no crack can't die this plot armor
shoot the fucking gun what the hell
please don't tell me the locator's busted how many are there when okay
reload the weapon reload the gun christopher
oh who it eat shit oh my whatever did i get them
why am i the only person that has the thing to do this with oh come on go go go go go go
got it
no no no no run run run this way this way this way this way no no that way that way wrong way
wrong way this way that way this way that way where's the dirt is oh come on fucking die
what the fuck aim it right here okay do it here do it right here do it here do it on me do it on me
right there what in the next round just a second who kept me the fuck out of here
just win shoot the tentacle wait what this kill the fucking no don't shoot that
which one which one where which one what do i shoot mega my seat must be below all right let's go
let me through jesus christ that was terrible no it wasn't it was i found a way down
fun i'm going in the rest of you stay back captain i'll compare the mold of the village
with a sample from the bakers and there's no sign of the genome editing we saw in the e-series
the stuff originated here you did everything you weren't supposed to do no that's not even
accurate i did what i was supposed to do it's fine okay let's go got everything going down
you have enough ammo i i guarantee you i do i'd fight this
i got a tough guy here i'm gonna need backup
there's an opening in the roof use it shoot through the roof
ow first legs in the back blow it up get behind him get behind him get behind him
i'll signal with the locator give a good break thought so
get it oh he hit me right in the head watch out
right here right here right here right here get him get him get him get him get him get him get
him right there right there right there right there right there right there right there right there go
i'll keep pointing down so the rest of you flash damage stay above ground
blame team fortress too okay so if miranda was the fake mia where's the real one
i doubt she saw any further use for her don't get any of this how did miranda even know rose exists
a moldy little bird told her maybe we can figure that out later
focus on the plan i found it it's the megamycete
crank turtles i killed this the best tigger impression i've located the megamycete
so now we can end this mess after all about damn time and two explosives armed there's enough
there to blow the whole village sky high let's get out of here and blow the damn place not before i
and miranda i'm not taking any more chances i'm going in captain i have eyes on the ceremony site
keep your distance do not move until i give the order i know it's too late now but we really
should have told ethan the plan there wasn't time we didn't expect miranda to act so soon
even so you should have told him yeah and two explosives i guess it was no time
yeah i think there was time when we were sitting in the garage working as buddies
on a father-son tractor project i feel like you had a little bit of time to tell me oh here we go
the final save point before the final boss i know it you know it we all know it this mermaid
got in it uh subject salvator moro has caused drastic changes to internal organs
transforming them into organs similar to fish like gills and a swim bladder another subject
with a regular cell division caused him to transform into giant fish subject is unable
to control this transformation too many defects an unfit vessel for eva alcenia dimitresu dimitresu
there it is most favorable brain function normal regeneration rate is incredibly fast
subject can heal any external wound within seconds and grow her nails into claws in
mere moments of rapid regeneration also means an increased body size due to hereditary blood
disease the subject must ingest human flesh and blood on a regular basis to maintain regeneration
properties i suspect that if the subject's regeneration is not properly balanced then
she may mutate uncontrollably okay well that's lady dimitresu and then we've got of course
karl heisenberg has electric organs similar to that of an electric ray
ponica these electric organs are connected to the subject's nervous system
oh unfit though try to put the book down and then donna benaviento physically she's no different
from a regular human however she can secrete a signal producing substance which controls
plants infected by the mutants site when humans absorb the pollen from a particular flower she
can cause them to have hallucinations however she is mentally underdeveloped and has had divided
has divided her kudu among her dolls there we go that's an explanation for all the people
this is a kudu a dow using this to control the bioweapon
is that that's miranda that's miranda that's miranda talking to somebody that's heisenberg
heisenberg and friends dear miranda my deepest apologies for not meeting you in person
i would love nothing more than to visit your quaint village once more however i'm incredibly
busy that i can suppose for an immortal woman such as yourself you no longer remember this poor
half-dead medical student in the snow i've always cherished the revelations i came to 15 years ago
when i strayed stayed in your village i was inspired by your research to think one could
transform a human by infecting them with an organism positively visionary i know that with
that knowledge i could achieve my own vision for the next step in human evolution even after the
two world wars and humanity on the cusp of another than my conviction never way i stopped putting
this on i'm like just locked in like a train of thought too much on i realized however through
the many nights of intellectual talks you and i shared that your conviction differed from mine
you hope to bring back a single dead person while i aim to change the world your experiments on the
mold would not have aided me in my endeavor to achieve an exponential infection but a virus
would be more effective this is why my dear i had to leave you still regret never telling you goodbye
my apologies for reminiscing i actually have the news that i thought might please you
i found the key to evolution the progenitor of virus and a virus found in africa i plan
to start a company with friends and colleagues dedicated to the virus research i would call it
umbrella just like the symbol in the cave that we spoke about
i'm one step closer to making my vision a reality i hope you will be able to achieve your goal
someday too taught me so much of that i would be forever in debt sincerely your lifelong student
oswell e spencer wesker so wait this is this takes place before this takes place before like
four five it's not wesker spencer yeah it's his pen name it's like rl stein
the head's kind of distorted what is this the real mia the real mia show me your hands
umbraz this is alpha where is miranda right now
i'm glad you're safe mia why are you here i was caught in houston experiments
wait did you say mia winter's in the flesh what's the situation up there kind of a war
going on nothing we can't handle don't get distracted stick to the mission i'm headed to
the ceremony site wait you can't leave me here lie you promised damn it you said that you would
keep us safe we did everything that you asked we moved over here everything and i didn't care
so long as we were together so you tell me where is my husband where is my daughter
i couldn't save him but i can save rose even though rose is currently in four separate bottles
i have faith in my ability to be able to do that i'm not a scientist
right really are gonna maybe put it back together he's dead i'm sorry mia but we have to leave
we have to destroy this village no you're wrong i tried to keep this a secret but
i'm pregnant you don't understand how special he is oh i thought there was like another like baby
or something that like i'm pregnant with another baby and this baby has like powers too
wait i'm alive i mean i guess we could have figured he was special considering
his arms have been chopped off like five times
is this like supposed to be the afterlife or something did i get my body back
he's special
was it me all along that had like the superpowers or something
uh lot armor you can even have your heart removed and you don't get to die
never mind i can't take that dead i mean miranda she no i still have to save rose
it wasn't miranda you were always dead what are you saying i can still
oh the whole time see miranda didn't kill you you mean you didn't think it was weird
no matter that you got hurt remember three years ago he punched me in the face working hard i died
are you fucking kidding me that's so funny three years ago that's really actually fucking
cool that's funny that's that's impossible he punched me in the face and killed me
that's fucking funny messing with my head you shouldn't be walking screw you he stomped on your
head and that was it i'm just dead
what happens during the game over screen no rose i have to save my daughter
uh
where who where are you where are we where where are you why are you here
you're not paying attention to the story as a job i mean i played resident evil seven
fucking three years ago i i barely remember this guy was a character
asked he awakes i carried you you were having a nightmare duke your battle with heisenberg was
a sight to see but to think miranda would show herself how long have i been out not long till
dawn duke i need a favor take me to miranda i assumed as much and i'm already on the way
we should arrive shortly do you die thank you is this the end of duke we're going to see duke
get like killed are you sure of this your body is well falling apart yes foolish of it as
speaking of foolish questions who what are you even i can't quite answer that we're here
can i buy anything from him i owe you one mr winters i'm afraid you can't return to your old
world any longer are you ready wait so what would it be my old world i have to be i gotta go i
actually really do have to go so we're gonna take a final pee break before i do this i really have
to go to the bathroom i'm very back all right let's uh let's finish this let's get to the end
feel like i'm right there hello uh let's go after i take a sip oh yes i've got it here it is the
magnum let's get it on the bar what shotgun bullets do i have all right two is the rocket
launcher let's actually why would i do flash bangs i have 17 shots i don't need a knife either
okay so let's go with sniper rifle on knife okay let me change this around i want a magnum to be
one i want rocket launcher to be two it is two i want shotgun to be three it is i want sniper
rifle to be four let's do it duke duke oh shit wait i can actually buy stuff from him one more
time duke's emporium has everything you need for your decisive battle jesus just sell everything
i didn't get it yeah sell necklace with two holes i didn't get it sell the cigar sell everything
right just buy a bunch of ammo sell everything yeah oh the assemblage of life and machine
i can feel lord heisenberg's essence through it yeah okay um what are you thinking are you
thinking magnum power i had a hundred thousand i would do it again your journey nears its end
how about some reckless spending to finish it off uh-huh oh give me shotgun ammo that was a
reckless spending all right can i sell anything else okay wait what about um oh shit sell the
handgun let's go sell the fucking handgun i got a hundred thousand dollars i can do yeah let's go
sell the handgun this is the handgun right i'm gonna do more power i'm gonna sell the handgun
i'm gonna sell the handgun i'm gonna why what do you mean no no no why not i'm not gonna use it
i'm not gonna use this okay i'm gonna sell the handgun and i'm gonna sell the fucking sniper
rifle what would i need it for i want full power at the magnum here we go i suppose you'd call this
a farewell to arms all right this thing is insane now shotgun ammo power from the shotgun
it's fine all finished i'm not victoria koram all right let's go please sell all ammo well thanks
naturally that's right sell all the handgun ammo all the sniper rifle ammo okay why are
there all these categories for this sniper rifle ammo get rid of it i'm ready to think i would buy
such things i'm gonna replace it with let's get like a bunch of pipe bombs yeah i'm just
gonna get a bunch of fucking pipe bombs this is a troll this is not a troll mine's too looking
forward to testing it out this may be our last meeting all right just in case this is a total
fuck-up this is going here so i've got i've got 13 shots of like 2500 damage each i've got a i've
got 17 fucking grenades and then i have a massively powered shotgun i also have seven mines i've got
five pipe bombs i'm ready this is i'm this i'm gonna kick the shit out of this lady okay
let's do it let's go shotgun first i'm ready if you were right on this first try i will drink a
gallon of milk don't drink a gallon of milk for any reason wait just run why would i even
shoot anything wait do you have anything on you why do i care it's the end of the game just run
go little ava my beautiful daughter come to me
is that you oh how i've missed you what wrong it's rose when you weren't looking
i put rose's body parts into the machine
is leaving me miranda i don't even have that gun anymore interesting your body certainly is
a normal you've had it like a sock now you will see once i kill you properly everything
i've spent a lifetime creating this moment and you try to take it away from me what is due
my desires will be fulfilled okay magnum
you disposed of my false children and awakened the glorious
now please do not worry for little rose i assure you i'll provide her with truth
yes so now you can die peacefully and you can die
how can you deny me why the hell can't you realize rose is my i'm skipping faces
it granted me this splendid power yeah right all it's done is drive you nuts
feel the dark god's wrath we're missing dialogue i think uh-oh i gotta use spider sense now mr
winter's i think it's time you left things in my house the hell i will i will take back my daughter
if i combine rose with a mega mindset my mega mind what
i've waited a century a century all for this day why do you
i've never seen a human live without his heart
are you sure i do you sure that you have no need now so close today she's my god damn daughter
you psycho oh such life time
oh
yeah i'm saying the same thing this is like a standstill this sucks
those four they could do nothing to assuage my years
i don't even have a knife to ensure i never free loan i got
i did it with only whatever i did it with exact amount of ammo i told you i had it
that guys don't drink a gallon of milk that's actually fucking terrible for you
i swear to god don't do that like you're gonna have two sips of milk that's what we're gonna
compromise here don't do that i'm serious that's actually really bad for you didn't miss one shot
with the magnums it's all right that's why you save every fucking shot from the magnum and the
grenade launcher to the final boss don't drink a gallon of anything yeah don't drink a gallon of
anything ethan ethan come on ethan wake up
we gotta move i thought she was dead keep moving ethan where's do is a bomb in that
thing that'll blow this whole village sky high hey look at me when i hit this trigger we can't
be anywhere near it damn it me is waiting for you she's alive you hear me alive me i'm so sorry
i love you bros safe hey hey hey
wait i'm i'm part of miranda and you tell yourself now come on it's not that much further
watch over her teacher to be strong
it's only goodbye rose had another magnum round right chris
all right let's go i need to look up time for you to say goodbye giant evil plant baby fetus
monster damn it i didn't get it i didn't take a picture right
go take us up now i didn't have to all that chris just like drop the baby oh fuck no oh fuck
oh my god is she all right get moving we have to get clear no we can't go not without my
sit down and strap in not before you tell me where ethan is i know he wouldn't abandon us you had
antlers back there what were those those things were crazy what are those what's going on where
what was that i told you to sit down night vision oh that's cool chris what have you done he's gone
i thought he just output her in the face i tried like like backwards he stayed so we could all
escape i was like why does it make a metal sound i'm sorry captain you need to see this
bsaa didn't send soldiers this is a bio weapon the hell were they thinking orders captain
pick up the rest of the squad plot a course for bsaa europe hq someone's got to pay
and what about what about duke maybe he'll narrate the ending credits
you never find out what duke is maybe after the credits i'll get off cam for this this is like a
very cinematic experience don't eat that don't eat that don't eat that don't eat that uh they
showed this in the beginning i still kind of don't get it i do but i don't why is she eating all
these things it's the buffet which one of these is lady dimitri sue gifts we gave but more you took
she snarled so more in turn is due in a blink the girl was trapped inside a mirror her parents
though had searched all day and at last arrived with rampant rage father fought the witch
while mother's loving touch shattered the dark enchantment but the witch was strong and father
yelled save our daughter so mother bore their child to safety as the forest was consumed
that didn't happen even now the burnt forest is a grim reminder of father's sacrifice
to this day any child who stares too long into the charred wasteland will be haunted by nightmares
of getting lost it's chris the mother no it's chris is not the mother
all right okay let's turn it down i'll give you my assessment i'll give you my assessment okay
uh i'm gonna have to say that was that was a started today is an 8.6 the ending brought it
down to an 8.2 like that just like cod zombies level brought it to like an 8.2 for me i don't i
i don't think i don't think that's cool i don't i never do um and then when i got to actually be
use my magnum the way that i wanted to i brought it up to in uh 8.4 and then this really cool
cinematic in the end kept it at an 8.4 it was that was like a that was great that was a great
game you stay at an 8.7 or an 8.6 for me if there's a fov slider like what the hell is that
it's fucking 2021 it's a pc game releasing in 2021 i understand like no but you'll ruin the
cinematic experience i don't care about that you know what i mean like if the if the zombie that's
gonna be like three or four pixels forward or something but i'm not gonna throw up playing the
game i don't like i don't i it's i just want to play the fucking game and not want to throw up
it was an 8.7 it turned into 8.4 they do that because they they designed the game around
oh you we don't want you to see shit you're not supposed to see and it has the best experience
all the scares all the jump scares i i know but it was in the last fucking game in resident evil
seven though you could it was you could make 90 fov in resident evil seven what happened what's
the difference it's the same it's literally the sequel to the last game where where where
anyways now it was really good it was really really fun i like the kind of like treasures
that they put on the map i thought that was a huge um i thought that was a nice touch it's cool
they're like well wait what's over there i'm gonna go over there i'm gonna get that treasure
i did i missed a bunch of shit was it scary that was very scary i think this was scarier than seven
i buy a lot the first like two hours of seven was really scary really kind of intense but i
thought this one was like i the the weird baby chapter freaked me the fuck out it really did
i would say the first two to three hours of resident evil seven was scarier than a majority
of the shit in this game but i kind of just liked i would play it out in this one a little better
resident evil seven was like actually like a more creepy scary video game
resident evil eight is like just like jumpy very jumpy and i guess depending on how you decide
what you like more as a scary game i guess just more of like a fairy tale yeah i if i would
choose which game i liked more i don't know man like resident evil seven's last like four or five
hours i just it was a slog to me that boat sequence in resident evil seven was the ultimate slog and
it brought the whole fucking game down the whole game came down i did not have i was a little
irritated in some points in the game but no point in this game did i feel like that boat level
were you just like shooting machine guns into enemies i mean except for that chris ending
i think as a whole i think eight's a better game i think seven the first few hours is scarier and
more interesting but i think eight's probably a better game yeah seven's definitely seven setting
was probably a little more interesting i don't know just sound about like a weird scary family
chasing around a house and shit it's like weird and terrifying but then they got rid of that and
then they moved on to like the boat shit bone in or boneless wings well boneless because i'd like
to just dunk them in sauce and just drain them what about the heisenberg parking garage segment
yeah but once i started to feel kind of annoyed and frustrated in that area and how much of that
is my like adhd inability to pay attention to like certain environments um i still don't think i was
i really just thought the boat sequence was just terrible so they're both really good games they're
both like great okay let's see what happens here we have an ending sequence we do do you think the
little boy will be able to touch the moon nobody can touch the moon it's too far away wait what if
he has a rocket ship uh okay then you can touch your butt it'd be very very cool he's going to
Xavier's gifted school for mutants hey dad happy birthday my opinion a grenade launcher
is etched into this last week headstone i have a lot of tests coming up you know how it is
goddamn devil duty calls i love you yeah i found her where else today of all days
this we have a situation you're needed evelyn don't you ever call me that again oh it's just a joke
rose oh what kind of joke is that even chris doesn't know i can do that's like a horrific
part of this person's life why oh stand down that's not a funny thing to joke about
i want you to keep it together rose you're all like him you know i know
i don't know i just thought of like an ice cream video where the girl's like
i'm sorry who's in the road that car the car is going to get stolen or something the car is
going to get flipped over the father's story is now done captain america will return in uh
resident evil 9 i know like almost exactly 10 hours exactly what i thought it was going to be
right uh difficulty level village of shadows added a new difficulty levels available
okay that's the satan mode right following content has been added to the bonus menu
extra content shop challenges three challenges listed in the challenge menu in order to receive
completion points see if he can be exchanged for variety bonuses in the extra content shop
weapons concept art for years yeah yeah village of shadows full version wcx challenge completed
you've completed the following challenges that sucked wait one fish out of water up yours
iron giant down what i just do what i just do what happened i just picked iron giant down
what was that sucked i didn't i thought it was gonna give me a uh like we kind of have to see
bonuses extra content shop extra game the mercenaries of course right special weapon
i mean might as well get this this cool knife don't people pay like 300 on steam for this
challenges world's best dad finish the story on hardcore finish the story on village of shadows
wrapped 150 items in the menu as just yeah cheapens all right so now bonuses
no no no bonuses mercenaries i have to do this at least once get the lightsaber first purchase
any equipment or weapons you need from the shop and when you go up to the field you need
to defeat as many enemies possible in time let it get a good rhythm going to build up combos
once you defeat a certain number of enemies the goal will appear touch the goal to finish
and to move on to the next area there are blue orbs which give you specials okay can i have
for those orbs whatever let's just go i have for weapons 250 shots all right can i without
oh yes um thank you for your purchase give me a shotgun and a pipe bone all right let's go
delighted to all right i just want to see what happens good start blue orb what the wait that
just freaked me out what's going on why do they have health bars why is it playing why is it
playing ipad roll the marble music here's what i'm talking about ipad roll the marble game music
all right let's see if i get a combo all right die die die oh all right blue orb pick it up
it's the ability hp recover slightly when attacking with a gun speed increases long
distance speed let's go these really are dark souls characters oh what's this bonus time
stamina i just what did i pick up speed enemies 15 goal has now spawned this is a goal area
complete this is kind of cool next area i mean i guess i'm gonna go till i can't go anymore
how much money do i have oh good i was just thinking of ways to pass the time delighted to
this is cool yeah this is pretty choose wisely your life may depend on it oh god
oh god come on somebody die keep the combo going
okay cool somebody else somebody else gruesome shot initial attack does more damage when enemies
at full attack increases with speed yeah where is anybody where are the enemies oh god what
you kind of were just sitting around weren't you this is a slow doom yeah there'll be probably a
million videos on youtube of people beating this shit with like 5000 enemies killed right
just keep it going i didn't what i think i didn't whatever you're throwing i mean i'm
sure you're throwing i'm done i don't even care i'm just trying to play this one more guy with an
arrow what all right goal where's the goal oh fuck oh how do i get up there i don't remember this
it's a ladder where's the ladder i'll kill these guys these guys are worth extra
hi there's the goal all right i think i'm done i'm getting i'm leaving i'm out of here
you know what a combo is i do i don't i don't care it's fun all right i'll see you guys next
weekend the plan next weekend is fable 2 i believe we're gonna start fable 2 on saturday there you go
8.4 game was very very very good not fable connect fable 2 have a i'm so hiccupy right now
i think it's like the scares just jostle up my body but have a great night everybody what just
happened oh there we go that was weird he's jostled he's yeah we're gonna let's raid tonight
let me see who do i want to raid do i want to raid let's see he got oh i mean joel is literally
doing this right now where is he what part of what part of the game is yet all right he looks
like he's uh all right so he's like he's like he's kind of where i where i started today
you should play online minecraft sometime you would suck why would you want me to do it then
yeah uh don't be a fucking dick um he obviously is halfway through the game at this point come on
uh yeah that's right joel go say hello see how he fares during the game we will ban you here yes
please do they're watching if somebody goes over there and does that you well you have fair game
to to give them a very very strict ban here go see how he fares i'll see you guys soon let's
get the that raid going i will see you guys next weekend for fable 2 take care of yourselves have
a fantastic rest of your evening we had a huge raid from uh fundy came in which is i'm shocked
that that many people almost 13 to 14 000 people right that's a monster raid thank you for that
fundy if any of you still stuck around uh don't be surprised if i say i can't believe it good night
everybody take care of yourselves go say hi to joel good night goodbye have a great week