What are you, what are you doing?
I was explaining my theories on being a furry.
No, I don't.
And I was, I was just saying out loud that you would not want to hear this.
Just like, okay, if you, listen, if you guys want to, if you guys want to hear
Ster go off on his, on his takes or whatever, or whatever we have to say about whatever.
Yeah, he's, he's got a stream that you can watch like,
when I'm not on it, so I can run the fuck away from him.
Yeah, no, I, I respect your, how, uh, how much of a prude you are,
that you are not evolving with the times that you're stuck back in the 80s.
And, you know, the world is becoming more and more woke.
And you just can't accept that some people have.
He's, oh, he's, well, he's muted again. He's, he's been muted again.
All right, so he's back. So, um.
Yeah, so no, I wasn't reminded. So you were a cat boy.
So I was talking about furries. You were a cat boy.
What are you talking about?
My chat keeps telling me because I, okay, long story.
I'm doing a cosplay trade with another streamer who is a VTuber who is a cat girl.
So I'm going to become a cat girl.
And my chat, every time this gets brought up is like,
oh, he's going to do it before German does it.
But ever since your, your hot tub stream,
they've been saying that you beat me to the punch.
I did.
But you were just denying it.
When I asked you if you were a cat boy, you said no.
I didn't do a hot tub stream.
I see what's happening here.
What are you talking about?
When Bugleberry, did Bugleberry become a cat boy?
Of course, of course I remember that, yeah.
Okay, I see.
You have like such a profound amount of shame within you
that I think one day the cap's going to burst and the pride is just going to fall out.
What are you doing?
He's got to put on a fucking mask of an old guy to get in the hot tub.
Like just live a little, man.
Time for some stretches.
Hey, if you want to be able to do some stretches, you got to start now.
All right.
So can we talk about video game conference stuff?
Absolutely.
If you would like to talk about what you enjoyed from the first day,
because that's the day that we've both seen.
Okay.
Elden Ring.
That would be fine.
I want to hear, I really do want to hear, and I really mean this.
Stop muting him.
I'm not.
So I want to hear what you have to say about Elden Ring,
because you, correct me if I'm wrong, you did not like Sekiro.
I think Sekiro was the worst Souls-like.
Okay.
I don't.
Not by much.
I think it's still a good game, but I think it was the worst in the series of Souls-likes.
Okay.
Which without context, people are mad.
I don't like that they made you have to grind healing potions.
Why?
They did that in Bloodborne.
Bloodborne had that.
Oh, I'm remembering it being a lot worse than Sekiro.
And honestly, it's been so long since I played it.
I don't want to unpack this.
Look, they're all Dark Souls games, and they're all great games.
There's no opinion other than,
I saw Elden Ring.
It looked cool.
I signed me up.
Do you think it's going to be like a Dark Souls game,
or do you think it's going to be more like Sekiro?
Do you think they're going to go back to, it's Dark Souls, but not really?
I think it's going to be just another Dark Souls game,
with the twist that you can get on a horse, so a little bit added to it.
But it's like the same thing.
Oh, Arise, Tarnished.
Oh, you changed the word that you call it.
They're not Hollows.
They're Tarnished now.
It's just Dark Souls.
Yeah, but all right.
People that keep saying that.
They brought on, what's his name?
What's the guy that the Game of Fire and Thrones?
They brought him on, and he just did, what's the hotkey?
In the program I use, it's Ctrl-H for Find and Replace.
And he just did Find, Replace, Hollow, Tarnished.
And he did a whole bunch of words, Replaces.
And then they were like, okay, let's go.
You don't know what the story is yet.
Sure, it could be just, oh, the Tarnished.
But you don't know what's going on yet.
It could be something cool.
I know that the trailer showed like, oh, you're in a hub world.
And here's like the soft-voiced girl with a hood on.
And she's the one that lets you level up.
Yeah, but okay.
I've been willing to give From Software a shitload of leeway.
And tons of room to just, oh, they've done that before.
The Dark Souls and the Souls-like games that they have made
are so fucking fun.
And they're so good that I want like more of that.
I don't want less of that.
I want more of that.
Again, I'm not disagreeing that I expect it to be a very good game
and I'm going to play it and enjoy it a lot.
But you're asking for opinions and saying that it's going to be a great game
is really just a very boring conversation if we keep going back and forth on this.
So let me bring you way back to The Binding of Isaac
when you used to have the joke that you would say all the time,
it's the same game, Ed.
Why don't you say it's the same game, Miyazaki?
Because, well, there's two reasons why.
Because I really wanted...
Well, we'll break this down even further.
So The Binding of Isaac was so unlike anything, right?
And I loved playing it so much.
It was like, I have probably...
I probably have...
He's struggling.
It's quiet.
I'm working on it.
I have probably...
I read a comment that was like, did these guys hate each other?
I don't like having him on.
He challenges me and I don't like it.
Okay, so...
I enjoy a divisive conversation.
That's too challenging.
You got to give me like...
Give me like softball question.
Okay.
Give me softball question.
Do you think that Miyazaki is...
Give me like a what's your favorite fucking like...
What's your favorite drink like whiskey?
You know, that's very easy.
The guy's name that did Death Stranding?
Kojima.
Kojima, yeah.
Kojima had an interview on the first day.
Did you see that?
That's my highlight of E3 is his interview.
The first part that I...
I'm not going to go on about the first part,
but he actually said if aliens came to Earth the way things have been,
you would not be excited by that,
but you will be excited by my next game.
This dude's crazy.
So wait, he's saying that his new game is going to be more interesting
than if aliens invaded Earth.
Yeah, and I don't...
He said he brought up 9-11 for some reason
and the guy threw him the softball questions like,
oh, hey, Kojima, how's it going?
Hope you've been having fun.
He's like, we're in a state of emergency.
It's like 9-11-2 over here.
It was really weird.
Really? I didn't even see it.
And then he said that aliens were less interesting than the games he make.
Anyway, as you were saying,
you were defending your position on the binding of Isaac.
No, okay.
So I didn't see that.
That's weird.
Okay.
I kind of want to rewatch it to make sure I didn't mishear it
and that I'm not misquoting
because these are pretty wild allegations I'm throwing out
for the public statement he made.
Well, anyways, I have probably the same amount of time
in Binding of Isaac that I did in...
It's probably pretty close.
It's probably my second or third most played game on Steam.
It's close to TF2.
It's like, if not more than 500 hours, it's close.
And I have played Binding of Isaac across multiple devices.
We're talking, I've played it probably two or 300 hours on the Switch.
I played it like two or 300 hours on PC.
I played like two or 300 hours on like PlayStation.
I just kept, I kept taking, I kept redoing save files
because I would play it for like 200 hours and I would delete it.
I would just uninstall it from Steam
or uninstall the game from like Switch.
So I would constantly start over
and I have like probably a thousand hours total in the game.
So there was a lot of stuff that I wanted in the game.
And when I kept saying, oh, same game, Ed.
That was just like a joke to say
because there was silence in the chat room
when we would be in like vent.
It didn't even mean anything.
I'm noticing a trend with silence for you.
Dude, you're talking about somebody
that literally walked around saying Thanos lines
into the shower and shit after.
I just say words.
They don't even mean anything.
Okay, does it feel good to get this out?
I'm not getting anything out.
He vented.
You guys don't, people don't even vent.
Is that, are we old?
That's not that old.
That's not that long ago.
So how does this relate to, it was just a joke back then.
And that's why you don't say it's the same game Miyazaki.
That's what we're getting at.
Well, because I like it.
I like, it's the stuff that I like.
And when you get more of the stuff that you like.
Okay, so I have a great direction to take this.
What was your favorite Souls like?
Bloodborne, without a doubt.
Okay, actually that totally, I agree.
That kind of takes away the point I was gonna make.
Because you know what?
Bloodborne, actually like one of the best games ever made.
If Bloodborne was 60 FPS,
it would be the best game that's ever been made.
Second best.
What's better?
I don't know.
Diablo 2?
Um, like a true, okay, if they read kind of,
and I don't even want to use the word remaster, because.
I don't think they're worth comparing, actually.
I just.
Okay, if they, okay, if they was a,
you know how the PS4 Pro came out?
And hold on, like the gas is coming up here
and it's hard to not, okay.
So don't do that shit.
So, because you just freaked me out.
Okay.
So when, you just threw me off.
What was I even saying?
Fuck, it's gone.
It just went, you just, a hole came out of my head.
Well, we were talking about an incident in your childhood.
You said it disturbed you greatly.
So listen.
So when the PS4 Pro came out, I remember being like,
I'm going to get, I'm gonna get a PS4 Pro.
I can't wait because they're definitely going to put
Bloodborne on it and have it be 60 FPS.
I was like, that's the reason why the console is coming out.
And they just, they didn't do it.
So I was like, what?
And then PS5 has like the PS5 mode for a lot of games.
PS4 games, right?
And I'm like, this is it.
They got to do that.
Like, come on.
It's, I don't know if it's so baked into the game's code
or something that they can't do it.
Because remember the Dark Souls shit
where if you made it 60 FPS, like they went like 100% faster.
Just give me that.
Give me like a 60 FPS Bloodborne.
And I would, oh, I would play it again.
I would.
Bloodborne 2 or something.
I don't know that I would really even, it's just a good game.
The atmosphere, everything about that game.
To like the art style, the atmosphere, the story,
the gameplay, the trick weapons.
It's like, I hope.
Look, if Elden Ring even has a 10th of that kind of stuff.
I want just trick weapons.
The trick, no, they need to do that again.
Trick weapons were the coolest thing of any game
that's a single player game that can come out in a long time.
Having the two weapons you can switch between are amazing.
It was so much fun to be able to transition between the two.
You know what I mean?
Like you go like one, two, big load, L1, slash.
And then you had two.
And then there's like two guys coming at you over here.
You slash with the big two-hander.
I loved that.
It was the best thing that I've ever seen in a single player game.
What are trick weapons?
I'm just in agreement.
I don't have a, I don't have a counterpoint.
Bloodborne, when Bloodborne came out, everybody was like,
oh, hold on, there's only like 20 weapons in the game?
What the fuck?
That's, but every weapon is like two weapons.
So each weapon has like a different mode, essentially.
There's two modes for each weapon.
I think when Bloodborne came out for about a full year,
you would just randomly say like quotes from it too.
Like Amigdala, you just say that randomly all the time.
Yeah.
You're really asking the guy why he's going, oh, same game, Ed.
It doesn't mean anything.
I'm just saying words.
Okay.
So how do I know what you're saying now has any meaning?
Because you were quite, there's a lot of conviction in your words.
You should know this more than anybody.
That when 24 hours go by, the last day, I don't remember half the things I've ever said.
People will like bring up stuff like, hey, dude, remember when you said this?
Like, oh, remember on that stream?
I'm like, what the fuck?
What are you talking about?
Why does everybody want me to do Aaron?
Why is everybody saying Aaron?
Aaron, why?
Well, can you do Aaron?
Aaron?
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, have you seen, have you seen, have you seen Snack on Titan?
Yes.
Okay.
Are you ready?
I've not seen the newest season.
Aaron?
Yeah.
Okay, no, Aaron?
Right?
I, are we talking like a dub here?
No, like, you don't, you didn't watch the dub?
No.
Oh, well, then you don't get it.
I'm sorry.
You don't get it.
Okay.
Whatever.
I don't, I'm sorry.
I don't get it.
Well, I tried.
And now I do remember it was been a long time since the early seasons, but I do remember
that girl really did like to say Aaron while crying.
So I, I can piece the things together.
Dura says Jerma is unfunny.
When did he say that?
Did he?
You say that all the time.
You say that I'm not funny?
Wait, no, you know, you say that I'm not funny.
No, I don't.
I say that you're very funny.
I'm always on the defensive.
You're always trying to mute me.
I have said on this broadcast that I think that you're one of the funniest like YouTubers.
I've said that.
I've seriously said that.
Tell them.
Okay.
I'm laughing because of the qualifier.
Jerma, Jerma, you're one of the funniest influencers I watch.
I don't like that word.
Well, you know what?
Of all of the influencers, you're probably the funniest.
Make sure to check out Star.
Wait, who's the other guy?
Trow's channel.
He's streaming right now.
Yeah, don't, you know, you don't come over here.
I got to warn you though.
Like if you're like a new viewer and you go over to his channel,
he's going to say something you're probably going to be like,
this guy sucks.
Like he's going to say he's going to have a take on something.
I'm like a gorilla song.
You got to listen to it like five times before you see where it's coming from.
Currently running Myriad, right?
Or not right now?
Well, no, I am like developing a replacement for D&D because D&D sucks.
While it's simultaneously the best game, it's also not good enough anymore.
So I've been trying to make my own D&D.
It's coming along quite well and I'm hoping to start running games again
in a few months, two or three months.
But with that last comment, I think 60 to 70% of everyone that would have come over
probably just decided they weren't.
Well, I mean, if you want me to back up the things I say,
I can back them up.
We were talking about this again.
You've got four and a half minutes in my head.
Four and a half minutes.
Why D&D sucks?
Okay.
You have the floor.
I have the floor.
I'm going to explain one mechanic in Dungeons & Dragons.
When you cast a spell on an enemy, when you are attacking an enemy with a spell
and they are defending against and they need to roll a saving throw,
they are actually attacking your spell with their defense.
And that's very significant to note because when you're attacking a spell save,
you then a tie win.
And I yield the rest of my time to the speaker.
So, you're making what you would call, in your own words, a better version of D&D.
Well, my-
Or a more refined version of D&D.
Is that what you're saying?
The more precise way to look at it.
This is an interview now for you.
This is like a me interview.
Thank you for interviewing me.
I know you're really excited about the Myriad coming soon.
The important part is that most people play D&D on the internet, like Roll20 and stuff.
But D&D is not made to be played on a computer
that can calculate things more than a person can.
So, I'm trying to make something that utilizes the fact that you're on a computer to begin with
and then make combat more interesting and have a lot more things auto-generate.
Have you guys heard of the best game Diablo 2
that automatically rolls loot for you and stuff?
Yeah, it's got all that.
Oh, what?
That's cool.
Yeah, like Diablo 2.
Now that it's like that thing you've heard of, I get it.
We probably should open the stream because here comes the conference.
Square Enix, right?
Oh, shit.
Wow, 40 minutes went by actually pretty quick.
He muted you.
Not really, only a small amount, like only just a little bit.
All right, so this is, we gotta get this back up.
What's for dinner?
Switch, the Switch gaming one's the one, yeah, that's the one.
All right, so what else are we working on here?
Brand risk stir?
I did legitimately prepare like 20 questions for an interview for you.
So, if we really need to kill time, I can just start asking things.
No, it's starting in like two minutes.
Um, what's a good one here?
All right, so they're at, okay, yeah, we're almost there.
I actually looked up some videos of like worst all-time interview questions,
so this is a real one.
They're funnier when you know they're real.
Okay.
All people are prejudiced.
Which prejudice do you have?
Probably against not liking you.
All right, so let's open it up.
Eric Hobbs.
Aaron, ready to do it?
Are you ready?
Yeah, I have it open.
All right, so wait, refresh it.
Let's make sure we're on the same thing here.
Like I just refreshed it, like right now.
Uh, refresh.
I'm on a bright white screen.
It's the schedule, right?
And it is the schedule, and it should be starting in one minute.
It's starting in one minute.
We got Square Enix.
And by the way, I am going to start muting him
because he's been talking over too many cutscenes.
How come I don't hear anything, though?
Okay.
Let's listen to these guys.
This looks like comfy.
This looks like comfortable.
I want to sit in one of those chairs.
All right, Square Enix.
What are those robots?
What's going on?
What is this?
What is that?
What was that?
That was, what the hell was that?
Those, those were like, those are robots.
But what were they doing?
The people are controlling them.
Oh, I put, wait, I put a lot of creamer in this coffee.
And I didn't stir it because I want to get back up here.
No, and it's, I just got to this part
where all the creamer is.
And I'm just drinking essentially warm cream.
It's all right.
Oh, you're allowed to talk about the warm cream you're drinking.
And I can't say when I was in elementary school,
I could bend to my, to my face on the ground.
Kind of a one-sided relationship here.
I feel like you're in the chat right now.
Like when you close your eyes at night,
you don't just like have chat scrolling.
No, this is like, like you close your eyes.
I want, I want the remainder of this conference
to be us describing video game material.
I don't want to hear,
I don't want to hear about you bending over.
I don't want to hear about you talking about
creams.
I don't want you talking about.
And I want, I want video game discussions.
Nothing else.
I don't want to hear about you bending over anymore.
No more game.
So far game of the year.
Germa 2021.
Uh, the only one I played, which is Resident Evil 8
is the only game I've played so far that's come out in 2021.
Oh, okay.
That's a lot to choose from.
What have you played this year?
What about the power washer?
Yeah, that was pretty good.
I don't even know.
I'm in that Lost Ark technical alpha.
Oh shit.
Are you really?
Yeah, pretty good.
That's like seven years in the making, apparently,
or five, whatever it is.
Well, I mean, it's been made, just not,
it wasn't made for us.
Guilty gear?
I don't like it.
All right, here we go.
Quiet.
Good afternoon, everyone.
It's Matt Mercer here,
and I'm back as your host of Square Enix Presents.
Today, we have a special E3 edition of the show for you
with new game announcements, updates,
and exciting news from our studios across the globe.
So let's kick off with the world premiere
of a brand new game from Eidos, Montreal.
We hope you enjoy the show.
I am so proud of you.
Do you know what a birthright is, Peter?
Is this Starfield again?
Or is it just another space game?
This is not supposed to be talking.
All the space games look the same.
Stop talking.
It looks the same.
It's Marvel.
On your side.
News of the galaxy?
Rocket.
So I let Groot fill out the paper.
Space games are fine if they're Marvel.
So we got to be 6,900.
Need a plan.
Crystal Dynamics didn't make this one, right?
We got this.
Put your pants on.
Push him off tracks.
Make your main questions here, right?
Maybe we can work something out.
Get him.
You had one job, Quill.
I did exactly what?
The more no killing teammates.
Says who?
It's literally in your contract.
I made no such commitments.
In less than three cycles, all would be lost.
The galaxy cannot be saved either, Quill.
We could do this together.
Licensed music has been replaced.
Good.
It means we don't have to worry about it.
What's the actual song that's supposed to be there?
Hi, my name's Olivier Poul, senior producer here at Eidos Montreal.
For the past few years, we've had the privilege to work on our version
of Marvel's Guardians of the Galaxy and reimagine it.
Okay, react.
He's just talking about it.
React.
Now.
Faster.
You don't have much time.
I would give that a...
I don't know.
Game reviewers say blah.
8 out of 10.
It was a game that looks like it's gonna...
Fans are gonna think it's cool.
Join us on this journey and you'll hear more about the game from our team behind this project.
All right, let's do this.
He's trying to find something nice to say.
I don't have anything to say because it was just like a trailer that had like...
They had like the song of the Hedgehog music playing.
And they were just shooting monsters and it was like,
look at these characters you like.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
Characters from Marvel's past.
You can't watch a trailer and go, wow, that game sucks.
I think it's a piece of shit.
I don't even know what it is.
You can.
You can't.
I don't even know what it is though.
Like I don't know.
It's just like a video game.
You're right about that.
It is a video game.
Does it look good?
I don't know.
You know, I felt as someone who isn't really a fan of the Guardians of the Galaxy,
I felt as though the vibes that it put off were quite authentic to the series
and really captured exactly what the movies were all about.
It's probably going to make you really feel like you are Star-Lord.
Well, all right.
I'm not, I haven't really seen, I'm not a big Guardians fan, okay?
I don't, I didn't, I thought the movies were cool,
but I didn't really get it.
I'm like, oh, I don't like love Guardians of the Galaxy.
It was like, cool.
It's not that I thought it was, they were bad.
I just, pretty much all the Marvel stuff.
I love Spider-Man, okay?
Okay.
That's my barometer.
Like Homecoming, Far From Home, like those Spider-Man movies are my barometer.
And like, I don't put Guardians higher than Spider-Man Homecoming.
Okay.
So your reaction to the Guardians of the Galaxy game is, I love Spider-Man.
Star-Lord is really empowering.
He's very agile on the battlefield.
He can slide.
I hate to say it, but that's actually my reaction to every game.
It's just, oh, Guardians of the Galaxy, yeah, I love Diablo 2.
You're doing the same thing, but you're not getting shit on for it.
Or I don't like it, okay?
I don't think this game looks, it's not for me.
I don't, I don't know.
Maybe it is though.
I don't know.
They've shown like a guy going like this, like a belly of an alien.
I don't know what the video game is.
It could be great.
I need more time to process it.
And no, I'm going to defend myself here, because yes, there's a reason why.
I said that I, yes, it's Guardians of the Galaxy.
I like Spider-Man, because if this was a Spider-Man game, I'd be like, oh, yup.
But it's, I put, in Marvel, I put Spider-Man over Guardians.
You understand?
That's what I mean.
Okay.
Is that relevant?
Yes, because it's a Marvel game.
It's the same universe.
That's like saying that like if Diablo had another game in the same universe,
that was the different characters, and you liked those characters more
than like Deckard Kane, which, excuse me.
Why would you say that?
But that's my point.
Like if it's different, it's the same universe, but different characters.
I am more interested in a Spider-Man game than a Guardians game.
That's my point.
That's it.
In a Guardians game.
Okay.
And I'm more interested in Diablo 2 than I am a Guardians game.
Oh, but then you can't, but all right, that's fine.
But like they're not in the same universe.
Honestly, the Marvel universe is so just like, oh my god, I gotta get rid of everything.
So who's to say it's not in the universe?
What's going on?
I feel like I'm in the, I'm playing the game.
Yeah, it was weird.
Let's play.
I was not prepared for that.
Oh, should it be playing?
All right, here we go.
All right.
We appear to be 6,963 units short.
We intend to keep our ship, Peter Quill.
I know.
We clearly need a plan.
Are these the characters from the movie?
What?
No.
I mean, they're the characters.
They are the characters as portrayed by other people.
My figurines are not knickknacks.
Is it?
I mean, I see Groot.
I will sacrifice your head.
And take us to the majestic mountains of Kakarantara.
Guys, I think we should hear out Groot for once.
I am.
Now, the only problem with your plan is that Lady Hellbender only buys monsters,
and you are not a monster.
Groot, are you really offering to-
No, no, he is not offering that, okay?
It could work.
So Groot, I guess we could bust him out after.
Absurd.
Lady Hellbender seeks the monster with him.
The small ugly one is clearly the correct choice.
He's cruel, sadistic, and his soul is filthy and filled with rage.
I vote we sell Groot.
Yeah?
I honestly think Lady Hellbender will go for it.
Yeah, well-
Yeah, this is the first 10 minutes of the game.
I also vote for the creepy little beasts.
Two votes each.
Peter?
But is this-
Well, Rocket's definitely scarier on the inside.
He's unstable and vicious and totally oblivious to the needs of us.
Are we still into dialogue trees?
I feel like that's-
All right, let's do this.
That's gone.
Let's go sell a monster.
But I think everyone learned that they don't change anything.
Because you're going to sell either one of those two characters,
arrive in the level,
and then they're going to jump through a wall and say,
I was here.
It's not Spider-Man.
No, it's not.
True?
I honestly think the dialogue, as much as I'm-
It's not for me.
They're doing a good job, like, delivered well.
I mean, it's going to be-
It's going to be like a licensed video game, right?
I don't know.
It's probably going to be 10 hours, 8 hours or something.
All your favorite characters are here.
Look, some people really do love this franchise, and that's fine.
And I hope you like it.
Okay, if this was Diablo II, right?
And like, imagine this perspective.
Imagine you're controlling the character here,
and this is a third-person perspective.
It's Diablo II and items fall down.
I'd be excited for it.
This is a really good indicator of what we're talking about.
What's your favorite movie?
My favorite movie?
There's so many movies.
You're putting me on the spot.
Whatever I pick.
What's like a top-
What's on your top 10?
I said my favorite movie was Coraline like 8 years ago,
and people quote me on that.
I don't think I can commit to this.
Okay, well, so you would put Coraline in your top 10?
No, I wouldn't.
That's why it hurts me.
So what's a movie that you think is in your top 10?
I'm going to go with the tried, the true, the classic.
You can't go wrong with Forrest Gump.
Like, I won't be upset by saying that.
Okay.
If they made a Forrest Gump video game that was nerd person,
would you play it?
If you could, like, play as Forrest Gump.
Never mind.
Yeah, like a top-down game where Forrest Gump is, like,
beating people up and, like, loops dropping, like, Diablo 2.
Yeah, I'd play that.
I concede, I would.
You would play that.
You would like it.
Gump Royale, last runner standing.
Yeah, you would play the shit out of that.
Are you kidding me?
I'd give it a try.
I'd try anything once.
I mean, if you can bend that far,
you're going to try anything once.
God, get out of here.
I have to have, like, a three-strike policy with you.
Like, when you cross two strikes,
I need to, like, send you a message to Discord
and be like, hey, you're on two strikes.
Do I get a cooldown?
No.
Okay, so are we on one strike?
No, you're on five strikes.
I'm reducing it back to two.
One more strike and you're out.
And I'm just going to have to be
the neutral planet from Futurama.
Yes.
That's me from now on.
This game looks complete.
Oh, look, okay, let's give them some credit
because they should get it.
They are showing this is the video game.
Okay, compare this to Avengers.
But this is not, like, rock music playing
and, like, a CGI cut scene of people,
like, holding their guns in the camera.
Like, this is the video game.
They're showing the game.
This is probably the first 10 minutes of the game.
That's all right.
They're doing that.
They should deserve a little bit of credit.
They should.
I also respect the bare minimum of presenting something.
Like, they're not, look,
there's a little bit of frame rate dropping.
Like, it's fine, but that's going to happen, right?
Ah.
This actually kind of looks fun.
Like, I don't hate this.
Although, like, I don't know about the character switching.
I don't know.
Maybe it would be fun for a little bit.
Look, if you're a fan of the game, a fan of the series,
I don't want to get into the uncharted territory of, like,
oh, this is stupid.
I don't like this.
Dumb game sucks.
If I was a fan of this game, I would love this shit.
Like, people, you're allowed to like things.
You know what I mean?
How should we decide?
I would love each frame.
So that's why I was like half joking, but it really is like,
it is authentically Guardians of the Galaxy.
It honestly seems like a lot of effort to put into one of the less popular series.
Who made this?
Did they say, oh, there's a Square Enix, but like a publisher.
Eidos Montreal.
Oh, that's what my shot was complaining about.
They said Deus Ex died for this.
Now I understand.
Oh, wait, is that Eidos Montreal?
Fairly certain.
I only got one face quote.
Are you sure about this, Peter?
Look at him.
Oh, isn't it super popular?
I don't know.
I'm a boomer.
I only like Spider-Man.
Guardians is really popular, yeah.
I mean, Disney knows.
They're making a bunch of rides, aren't they?
Aren't they changing Guardians to like a bunch of rides at Disney?
But when the time comes, it's definitely popular enough to do that.
True.
I think I'm still stuck like really.
It really is like a boomer thing.
I'm stuck when Guardians of the Galaxy only existed in Marvel's versus Capcom
and nobody knew who the characters were.
That's where my like brain ages.
Wait, what they they were.
Yeah, they were in the game.
That's right.
Holy shit.
I completely forgot about that.
Yeah, they also had a lot of the Doctor Strange characters in it.
And then Doctor Strange didn't have a movie either for like five years after Marvel.
So like everyone's like, who's Dormammu?
The heck is a dagger of Denon?
Isn't Dormammu like a playable character?
No, he's a boss, right?
No, he's playable.
The boss is Galactus.
Oh, right.
Yeah, Dormammu is in the game.
You're unlocking a part of my memory I did not think was going to get unlocked.
Dormammu, I'm here to bargain.
Yeah, I think they were working on all these movies
and didn't realize how long they would take to finish.
And then Marvel came out with all these characters
for like upcoming movies 10 years later.
This is a very long earlier.
Well, what else is this work?
What else are they going to show?
Hitman, I would assume.
There's a new Hitman like every month.
How could they?
No, no, no.
But Hitman is, I mean, I did hate one of the levels.
But didn't they just come out with like a new one?
Yeah.
And I hated one of the levels.
I thought it was the worst game.
I thought it was the worst level they've ever put in a Hitman game.
Germa speaks out.
But it was great.
Never mind.
But yeah, maybe they wouldn't be doing Hitman.
I don't know.
Tomb Raider, that's true.
Probably another Tomb Raider.
October, that's coming out like this way in like a couple months.
What year is it?
I'm not playing it until the Snyder cut.
That's only four months from now.
Going to revisit two iconic brands that are being remastered for modern platforms.
Oh.
First up, relive the classic games in the Final Fantasy series.
And then get one more peek at Legend of Mana ahead of its June 24th launch.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm interested in that.
Am I pretending to like that?
Let's find out.
Are you what?
I might be pretending to like that.
I don't know why, but I think I like that.
Legends of Mana?
Yeah.
Mana?
What are they remastering?
All of them?
Wait, that's a lot.
Yeah, we're going to remaster every Final Fantasy ever.
Okay.
Do you like this?
I mean, that was...
I guess that's kind of cool.
Do you think that the last Final Fantasy is going to be called The Final Fantasy?
When they decide to stop?
I don't think they'll know it's the final one until it's too late.
Next, Earth's mightiest heroes continue their fight to defend the world in Marvel's Avengers.
The team at Crystal Dynamics is excited to share the latest updates with you.
Including new missions...
Oh, nice.
I've been wondering about this.
Yeah.
Please, God, come back to our game.
Please, for the love of God, play it again.
We swear.
We swear it's worth it.
Please, more than eight of you.
...secure that super weapon at all costs.
Cosmic energy...
Is that...
Was that normal guy Thor?
...counts, people.
Keep it moving.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Marvel.
Yeah, it is like Marvel.
No music.
Yeah, they didn't even try on this one.
This is like when you put on like Big Bang Theory without the laugh track.
I will save it.
There you go.
Cool.
They're fucking up that cube.
You don't understand what that cube is capable of.
Cosmic cube.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, this feels really weird.
I feel like I...
I feel like I have like...
In like, Premiere.
Like I forgot to put the music track on it.
If you were gonna forget to put music on a game, it would be this one.
Oh, here we go.
So is every...
When did Square Enix get like all this Marvel license?
It's like the first two games are shown.
But when you get it, you run with it.
The sound of his like leather daddy suit as he walks to his throne.
I love it.
There needs to be music.
No, there doesn't.
It's way better without it.
How would you hear Black Panther's thighs grinding with music?
Can I just play this game?
I don't want like the Avenger...
All the Avengers Avengers crystal nightmare.
It does just have like a bunch of replayable enemy spawn games.
So what you're asking...
Okay, Jerma, what you're asking for is the Guardians of the Galaxy game.
This looks like way cooler than everything they just showed.
Yeah, because it's not in-game footage.
Did you get confused again and think that it was gameplay?
Fuck!
No, I'm not that stupid.
Okay.
Oh shoot!
Hitman!
I keep just turning on my webcam for four seconds.
Like, why do I even have it?
You're looking good today.
Wait, are we gonna get to play a mobile Hitman?
Oh, it's a sniper.
Like, they keep making the sniper game.
Yeah, they put snipers in it.
Earth, space, sniper, the trifecta.
Oh, they're not even trying.
There's no music.
At least make it funny and put crickets here, you know what I mean?
But I guess that'd be kind of rude to the developer, right?
Well, I don't know if it's Twitch that did this or they that did this.
Or they that did this.
So, there's definitely a voiceover here that is part of this.
Yeah, I mean, it must be Twitch because it's not like Square Enix had Sonic music.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
They listened, they heard us.
No, this is like old movies back in the olden days.
You probably remember when they would have to have
someone actually do the sound effects behind the projector.
Like, Twitch is doing this live.
What is this?
Is this Final Fantasy?
Yeah, I think there's a Final Fantasy Battle Royale.
Oh, wait.
No, that's the...
Catsith is going to be in that one, right?
Cats?
Catsith.
Today, the team at Platinum Games is giving you an exclusive look at the epic world of Babylon's Fall.
Final Fantasy VII.
Powerful weapons and a unique art style.
Yes, he has six strikes now.
And he hasn't given me any more.
I should have, twice at least.
Well, then you got to stay on it.
Catsith?
No, Catsith.
One with the dice.
That's my favorite character in any...
That's the only Final Fantasy character I even care about.
Does the savior of Neo Babylon stand among us?
Let's find out without further ado.
I like this game, though.
I knew you would.
I knew that'd sell you.
I'm sold already.
What Jerva voice was that?
If I'm to die, then I'll die for hope.
For what little hope?
This...
This does not look good.
I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna be blunt about it.
I feel like they announced this game like four or five years ago.
I don't understand, but it has...
Doesn't mean it's gonna be good.
It has 10 out of 10 voice acting and music choice.
Not muted music.
This voiceover reminds me of a lot of rock songs in the 80s.
It would kind of just like talk really weirdly over the music for a second,
and then they'd go into it.
It looks like they didn't finish the graphics.
They put a watercolor filter over everything to like hide it.
They just like smudged it all together.
I can't say I'm not interested, though.
I think I'm interested for a bunch of different reasons.
Well, because you're in it.
Did you play any of the near games?
I played near automata.
I thought it was fun.
What is it again?
I played near automata.
It's not automata?
Near automata.
Near automata?
Oh, well, all right.
Anyways.
Automata.
Yeah, I played near automata.
And it was fun.
But then everyone will tell you that you have to beat the game six times to actually enjoy it.
To which I say, nah.
It always looked fun.
I just never played it.
Should I play that?
Should I like stream near automata?
You're not going to do anything like weird while you play it, are you?
You're not going to, like, try and look up her skirt.
It's strike three.
He's gone.
Strike three.
He's out of here.
I'm voting him.
No, they built that into the...
He's beautiful.
He's gone.
It's strike three.
All right, you can come back if you apologize for getting a third strike.
I'd like to apologize to the German985 community about the remarks I made
in relation to German985 looking up a skirt.
He would never do that.
And I'd like to apologize for anyone that I offended that
enjoys even casually 2B fan art.
Highbrow 2B fan art.
You're the worst.
Now let's check out the next major entry in the popular Life is Strange series.
True Colors.
The team at Deck Nine is ready to give you a deeper look at Alex Chen's psychic power.
All right.
Did you play Life is Strange 1?
Yes.
Oh, you want to know how...
Like, okay.
I just...
I have every opinion that no one likes.
I think Life is Strange 1 is great and I think the ending is perfect
and exactly how it had to happen.
And everyone hates the ending.
So I'm just always wrong.
I thought it was good, yeah.
I thought it was really, really cool.
But I don't like...
I played Life is Strange.
I was like, oh, that was pretty cool.
I liked that.
That didn't look like much of a difference.
That doesn't look like it's very much of a change at all.
Oh, I didn't even notice.
This is a remaster.
Didn't this come out like...
That looked like...
That looked like when they do like the PS4 versus Xbox One graphic changes.
Like differences.
And I kind of felt like the splotchy characters was on purpose.
It was kind of the way it looked.
No, I liked Life is Strange.
I thought it was like really interesting.
I'm trying to remember...
Okay, obviously don't spoil the whole game.
I'm trying to remember the ending of Life is Strange.
Oh, my...
Well, there...
Oh, well...
Can't spoil that.
But wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
This is...
Wait a minute.
I want to watch this.
No, this is not...
Life is Strange is like...
No, this is a remake.
I already know what's going on.
It's spoiling everything.
I guess they just assumed that you like already played it.
People didn't like the ending to Life is Strange.
Yeah, it was one of those like reddit opinions.
So it was probably a small minority of very vocal angry people.
I think it kind of fell in line with like none of your choices matter.
But that's...
I mean, that's just true of life because life is deterministic
and the simulation won't let you escape the bounds predetermined for you.
So like how is that not realistic?
Hey, you want me to go off on this?
You can see what he said.
What are you talking about?
It sucks.
This is...
You know what this reminds me of?
That reminds me of like those old infomercials for the HD sunglasses.
Remember those?
Put on the HD sunglasses and look at what the world looks like.
Brighten up your day.
Oh, this road sure does look boring, but with our HD technology.
And it does that little...
Oh, wow.
Look at how much different it looks.
Is this like a little bit better?
Of Hayden Springs.
Today, we have a first look at Alex's unique power in action.
Here's game director, Zach Harris, for more.
Haha.
Laugh my ass off, you're cringe.
Whoa.
Can we not bring up Kringa?
Alex's psychic power of empathy is integral to the story of Life is Strange True Colors.
Okay.
Quiet actually, because I'm interested in this.
Every relationship she builds and every decision she makes.
Never thought I'd have a freaky and bad friend.
For years, Alex has been unable to shut out the strong feelings of others.
The fear, sadness, and anger of those around her.
Leading her to believe her power is a curse.
In the wake of Gabe's death,
Alex realizes the only way she can find the truth is to embrace her power.
Is this part of the remaster or no?
This is a new game, right?
No, this is the new game.
And the only way to understand is to feel what he's feeling.
From the very start, you can use Alex's power to focus on brightly colored auras,
to gain an insight into people's emotions.
Gabe was too young.
Just too young.
These valuable insights deepen Alex's relationships with the folk of Haven Springs,
as well as sparking new dialogue options and events.
As here, from a scene very early on in the game.
You're gonna lose her.
You're gonna lose her and it's all your fault.
Alex has uncovered a secret that Mac wants to keep hidden from his long-term girlfriend.
And now he is terrified that Alex will reveal it before he can talk to Riley.
She is the best thing that's ever happened to me.
Please.
Wait, do they know she's in their head?
Mac's telling you a whole lot of bullshit.
Thanks for telling me the truth, Alex.
Do they know?
I think they were implying that you confronted him or he caught you.
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
That would be really weird if they could know.
Honestly, that's actually kind of an interesting idea.
Being able to read people's minds and have to make decisions based on knowing what they know.
They don't know that you know.
That's kind of weird.
I think what this really just comes down to is that people should just talk.
They should tell everyone how they're feeling.
Um, and they should open up.
And, you know, let's just let it out, Jerma.
What have you been hiding?
Scream Disco Elsion.
Oh, it's a long game.
The only emotion she can't feel are her own.
That's not that far away.
Somebody said acting.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, they're actors acting as characters in a game.
Oh, fuck it.
Oh, actors.
What?
Somebody said, well, fucking acting.
Yeah, but why did you pick that comment out?
I don't know.
Like, make a point.
Like, everyone else are you guys.
It's interesting.
We are excited to...
Anyone who missed out, these are actors.
I thought it was funny.
I thought it was interesting.
To kill Chaos.
That's my mission.
I just want...
At one point...
Oh, wait, quiet.
Looks like Chaos has been waiting for us.
You gonna make us go in there and find you?
Guess we'll just show ourselves here.
I only know one thing.
We want to kill Chaos.
We need to.
It's not a hope or a dream.
It's like a hunger, a thirst.
I'm pretending Andy right now.
I've not played one Devil May Cry game.
I'm not even sure I've put a Team Ninja disc into the tray of any console I've ever owned.
I'm serious.
Why am I pretending to be excited for this?
This is the shrine of Chaos.
He's here.
Is that rhetorical?
Maybe it's because I think everyone's really excited for this.
So if I say like, oh, whoa, Team Ninja, people will think I'm cool and like me.
This is it.
Yeah.
No, you know.
Like, I know they make good games and I know the games usually are pretty good.
You know that other people care about it and you're receptive.
You have the empathy power to know what empathies other people are feeling and you respect their
feelings and you want to not have me talking over their favorite games so they don't say comments
like shut up, star shot, I'm listening.
I needed him.
Let's strike five.
I think this plot of this game has something to do with killing Chaos.
Stranger of Paradise.
Final Fantasy Origin.
No, see, they didn't call it the Final Fantasy.
They didn't.
They called it.
Well, that's the first one.
This is this is Final Fantasy zero.
Well, isn't the first one also the Final Fantasy?
No others have happened yet.
I mean, it's Final Fantasy one, essentially.
Like what?
Oh, Final Fantasy seven.
I actually okay.
I talked a lot of shit about this game.
When we remember the original trailer that like three or four years ago.
I was I talked about Final Fantasy seven's remake.
I talked a bunch of shit and it I mean it looked actually kind of looks kind of fun.
Okay, is that it?
Is it no more?
Who could say?
Well, it was just like a couple of Marvel games and I guess they did show.
I mean, Square Enix is not like fucking Microsoft.
Just a couple of Marvel games.
Fuck you.
Thank you for joining us.
That's it.
Keep an eye out for news about our next Square.
Thank you for joining us.
All they showed was just a couple of Marvel games and some Final Fantasies.
Like thank you for joining us.
Our entire fucking budget of like 700 million dollars went to getting the licensed characters
for Guardians of the Galaxy and the Avengers.
So we had no leftover for the licensing for the music we used in that same trailer.
Well, all right.
No, I guess they have it.
Twitch doesn't have it.
Never mind.
I'm just wrong.
And no, Spider-Man.
We are definitely not going to sit around and let stir become a brand risk for an hour
and a half to wait for the PC show.
So that's not going to happen.
What did you think?
Um, none of that was for me.
I gotta get a haircut.
Hey, talk about the game.
This guy's coming to here talking about haircuts.
Look, we're trying to talk about the games.
I'm hiding it very well, aren't I?
No, honestly, if Square Enix were going to show anything,
I don't understand why they wouldn't show the new Final Fantasy that they've been working on,
which seemed mostly complete.
So you would think they would have gameplay or some more.
Because what I've I've never really cared about a Final Fantasy before,
but that one looked really pretty and had like garbage swamp monsters.
So I wanted to see more and I don't know where it was.
Do you think I would count all off?
You're still talking about your hair.
Um, Square Enix.
Well, we're just giving free advertisements here.
Turn it off.
Um, what is, um, oh, no, I don't know.
What is it?
So Square, I guess the Final Fantasy thing is pretty cool, right?
That actually is probably the biggest thing.
Which one?
The final fantasy origins thing, the actual like the team ninja game.
That's kind of a big deal.
Okay, I agree.
That game probably be fun.
Yep.
What else are you supposed to do on?
You know what I mean?
That's the thing.
Like, okay, I just.
Exactly, Jerma.
If you're just excited about everything, you can't say anything.
You need to let your hate out.
You have so much within you.
Just give it.
Yes, chaos.
I, but I've, I've, I've said my pieces about how I don't like certain things.
We've already, we've gone over them today.
We've talked about things that I didn't like.
This is mostly me, but there wasn't much.
I know what you're talking about.
You're, I, you, I really like you.
I just keep getting attacked lately.
My wife keeps attacking me.
Well, I don't, that's between you and your wife.
I don't know what you're talking about.
So he hates Capcom.
Wait, Capcom?
What, what?
I said fuck Capcom like two, three weeks ago because.
All right, let me ask you this.
The only game you've played in like the last year was the Resident Evil one, which is Capcom.
Listen, so I said I've opened up Resident Evil 8 on PC
and the game's not 90 FOV.
It's locked at like 81 and you can't change it.
So I freaked out.
I've said, I said, fuck Capcom.
Fuck this whole company.
And people were like, whoa, dude, fucking relax.
People were like actually like selling, saying, hey, dude, relax.
Like it's not that big of a deal.
And I was like, I, I didn't even backpedal.
I just doubled down and was like, no, fuck that.
That's fucking bullshit.
And I went off on how like surprised that 81 FOV.
Cause it's like, it makes me sick.
It doesn't, it makes me.
And they're like, yeah, I got used to it after like three hours.
But like, what, how do you feel about that?
Don't you feel like it?
I feel that you shouldn't have to get used to it.
They should get used to developing games
that you can play without feeling nauseous.
Thank you.
Yes.
But when you come, see, you're, you're, you put a foot into my world.
When you complain about a game, it's your fault for complaining.
And then a whole bunch of people show up to like praise the corporation
who created this for me.
And you're just satisfied with it.
But if you're satisfied, they just keep shitting on you.
So in reality, you want.
No, no, no, no, no.
Resident Evil 2 is like one of my favorite games
the last like five years.
Don't say that.
Resident Evil 2.
The remake.
Doesn't that make you sad that your favorite game is a remake of an old game?
It was very good.
Like, look, I know, I understand the sentiment of like remake.
Oh, it was so good.
Mr. X is like one of my favorite things and, and five years at least.
But no, so what you're saying is you're, you just want it.
You want things to be better, right?
You want the world, you want things to be better.
You want the game to be better.
Okay.
Yeah, I can say I can sit there and listen to that.
The remake is so different from the original.
That's also true.
It's very different than the original.
So I don't know.
Is it an entire I've never played.
I played like half of Resident Evil 1.
Remake 2 is a great example of a good remake.
Yeah, it is.
It's fantastic.
I think by compact, like I think they gave people so much hope
for how good Resident Evil 2 was because I actually I didn't play it.
But I watched a lot of speed runs and a lot of people were really enjoying it.
And I watched playthroughs and all that.
But what was the one that came out after that?
The next remake that was like, yeah, that in comparison was like severely lacking.
And that's what you that's what I'm saying.
You get complacent.
You let Capcom take a fucking inch.
I don't think the same team.
I don't think Resident Evil 3.
The remake was made by the same people that made the second one.
Am I wrong?
You make an excuses for him.
No, I'm just saying I don't.
I think it was a different team that made Resident Evil 2.
He's making excuses for our remake.
It was a different team.
Yeah, no, it was a different team entirely.
Made the third remake versus the second remake.
So there you go.
There's your answer.
Okay.
You're a Capcom shill.
Okay, let's be honest besides Resident Evil 3's remake.
The last the last like four or five major Capcom releases have been very good.
Haven't they?
Monster Hunter World was really fun.
I like how I liked it.
They have been doing a redemption story.
Resident Evil 7 was really fun except the boat sequence was like a fucking zero out of 10.
So the game the first like three hours of Resident Evil 7 were like a 9.0.
And then I've said this a million times.
The last like third of Resident Evil 7 is like a two.
So it averages out.
But Resident Evil 8 was really fun too.
I really liked Resident Evil 8.
I thought it was great.
Did you play 7?
I did.
Yeah.
Did you just not listen to a single thing I just said for the last two minutes?
I'm just checking and make sure no chatter left behind.
There were some people asking.
Do you like 7 more than 8 or which one more?
I had that debate here in this chat.
I don't know.
I think 8 is a better video game.
But I think 7's potentially like more interesting setting.
8 is probably a better video game to me.
7 is like a more interesting place I think.
I like them.
I like the idea.
From my perspective of again I haven't played either of them.
I just watched people play them.
I thought 7 was much much better.
But to say like yeah I could see how you could enjoy the gameplay of 8 more.
And I'm like I'm not even playing it.
Did you play 7 and 8?
Did you play both of them or no?
No.
Like I just said are you even listening to me?
I watched people play both of them.
We don't even listen to each other.
We just wait for the opportunity for the next person to talk.
Fucking political argument right here.
This is ridiculous.
This is like a case study.
We both just did not comprehend completely the last sentence both of us just said to each other.
That just happened in real time.
I'm just going to space out until it's time to make my point.
I'm going to space it out until I'm going to say yeah Resident Evil 8 was fun.
I liked it.
I think because here's the thing.
There's like this this period of Resident Evil before 6 and Resident Evil after 6.
They like there was like an absolute like catastrophe around Resident Evil 6.
Because Resident Evil 4 was incredible.
I don't even remember what 6 was.
Was that the like action-y co-op like I don't even know.
It was awful.
It was just like you shoot machine guns at other guys with machine guns.
The game was awful awful awful.
So before 6 they had this kind of idea of like oh yeah we'll do like the third person stuff.
And like well yeah 4 was incredible.
5 was really good.
There was some issues with 5 but it was very very very fun.
I love 5.
And then they just went full-blown like third person shooter.
And it was just like well this is kind of stupid.
So then then we're like oh like we gotta fucking get out of here.
We gotta we gotta change this completely.
They go back to 7 which is first person.
More scary kind of scary shit.
And then they go to 8 which is more kind of scary shit but more gameplay.
I am terrified of Resident Evil 9.
Because they might just go full first person like shooter and ruin it.
When they do the third one in a new set.
That's why you have to be careful.
Did Capcom show stuff?
I don't know I don't think so.
5 was good yeah no 5 was good.
But I'm concerned if they continue the first person shit with Resident Evil.
If 9 is going to be like the one that everybody goes oh I don't know about this one.
They they have a tendency to do that.
Capcom's tomorrow they're spreading this out to Monday?
I guess so yeah.
They usually it's four days.
Okay oh I can we just show all the games on one day.
Then have all the bad ones like not be upvoted on Reddit.
And everyone like misses the announcement.
Well you can't do everything in one day.
Because if you do everything in one day.
Then it would be there would be no time to even digest what happened.
I guess I'm looking forward to see if Dragon's Dogma 2 gets announced.
That's the stir game.
That is the stir game.
I remember you loved that game.
You played Resident Evil 4 on stream.
No I I played Resident Evil 4 like five times across five consoles.
So I don't think you'll ever see it here.
I beat the Resident Evil 4 Wii port three times.
That was so good.
The Wii version of that game was I remember playing it and going.
This is what the Wii is for.
This is this is exactly what the Wii is for.
So I love that version.
It was great.
Yep.
But yeah.
Any final thoughts stir before you get a seventh or eighth strike.
I am I'm not getting a seventh strike.
I'm being a good boy.
I don't know.
Are you waiting for the PC gaming show?
Are you doing that?
Are we going to like reconnect?
You got to get another coffee.
I mean that's in that's in like an hour and 12 minutes.
There's no way we're going to sit here and burn an hour and a half.
I'll watch it.
I'll watch it on my big screen.
Big screen.
You know I've had the same TV for like probably 10 years.
I don't know why I get another TV.
You know what I mean.
If it's a flat screen it's fine.
It's 1080.
What's the problem?
I don't know what's the problem.
I think my TV that I have I bought because YouTube gave me a gift card
for getting like 20,000 subscribers.
Wait what?
So they gave a gift card to like some electronics store.
It was like 500 bucks.
They did?
And I bought a $500 TV and I still have it and it's really it's really aging.
Where's my $500 gift card?
That is really weird that they did too.
Thinking back and I was like wow that what?
I didn't get a $500 gift card to go get a new cool TV.
Yeah well all right well I don't know what to say.
Well what's the next video game you want to play?
I think I think I would like to I would like to if you would agree to it.
I would like to get in I would like to do VR with you again because that was a lot of fun
and I have a lot of good memories a lot of fun times
during that VR stream that we did together.
Would you would you do VR again multiplayer stuff?
Let's do VR.
Are there any VR like Half-Life Alex mods that are multiplayer?
It might be well if we can look into it.
I feel like I feel like someone and not Valve I wouldn't I wouldn't put this on Valve.
Someone else has to make that.
Have we even talked since Alex even came out?
Like have we even like what have we talked about that?
Uh I think so.
Oh Game of the Year was Half-Life Alex right it wasn't Hades it was Half-Life Alex I forgot.
I I bought it when it came out instantly I still have not played it.
You would yeah we definitely have talked about it because
I was talking about it with you and saying how I didn't
you didn't like how it looked like the game had a lot of downtime
and like puzzles in between shooting.
That part and you were like it sucks but it's all right.
Yeah there's a lot of like just hold the globe
and like turn it awkwardly while you press like four buttons.
Yeah that happens a lot but you got to play that game.
You have to that's that that game is for all like the tiny little
like turn the globe puzzles.
They put like there's probably realistically like 50 of those in the game.
People are saying there are multiplayer mods.
Is it just of the campaign or I don't know.
I think it would be pretty funny actually if you backseat at me through Half-Life Alex in VR.
You having played it and me not having you make you make me the uh the
I turn into Dinklebot.
I just like float around with you and just tell you things.
Yeah.
So I would just be like experiencing the whole game again without doing anything.
Well now you can like play I don't know.
I would just have to play the whole game again.
Well it's your game of the year is that like is that so bad.
Yeah but I look I listen to me.
I was that one game that we played the one YouTube video the Groundhog Day
where like I was the cameraman and you were running in every single time.
Damned of something.
It was a motorcycle where you were you like Burger Boy.
No there was no motorcycle.
Yeah no it was it was the Pop-Tart joke.
They're going through the glass.
No that's a totally different game.
No it's not.
Yes it is.
Where I kept what you kept jumping into like frame through the glass.
That was the that was like the you Burger Boy puked on yourself.
That's not what I was talking.
I was talking about the game where I was like the hacker and you were the person in the world.
Like clandestine clandestine clandestine something clandestine.
Yeah that's the game that was really fun.
You can clandestine me.
Don't you think that like Half-Life Alex.
Do you ever just want to go back and like delete all the your old YouTube videos so
we could like play those like games and do it again on stream.
So they never look we're doing it it's like fun.
Hey you know what uh blood packed if you delete your YouTube channel I'll delete mine.
No that's not happening.
I'm not deleting my YouTube channel.
And then we'll go back and try and remember our videos and try and remake them
and then you can watch them at the remastered German.
Holy shit that sounds like a fucking brilliant goddamn idea.
It actually does.
We we should pick out like three of everybody's favorite videos we've ever done
and try to remake.
Oh yeah that sounds fucking incredible.
And then we'll we'll like we'll premiere them on stream
and see if they're as good as the original.
Yeah I bet we could do that with that damned one.
I can't even remember the name of it.
Breakfast time with goofus and doofus or something whatever the title was.
You want to try to remaster an old video.
That's actually weird enough to be funny.
Let's do it.
All right write that down.
We'll we'll we'll get that.
I'm writing that down.
I'll put it right underneath among us.
All right that's that sounds like fun.
Uh I'm gonna get going.
I don't know if you're sticking around but if you are then are you gonna keep going?
Uh I may play like Guilty Gear until the PC gaming show.
Okay.
But just fill time.
Well we're just gonna raid you.
So okay where you'll everyone uh that has hated everything you've said tonight.
Probably won't go but people may have loved what you said today and we'll join you.
I'm gonna get going.
If if you just fair warning if you send people over here we might I don't know.
I don't know.
I like honestly just like just hang out and be the last time you hang out.
I said this too it's something about being hosted.
The expectation that everyone brings over to you makes me very uncomfortable.
All right so we won't raid you.
We'll we'll say goodbye.
But you have to raid me.
You said you were like no no no no how about this how about this how about this.
Right now you're currently live.
Yeah.
If people would look at them directly I'm directly addressing you.
If people would like to continue to watch the show with stir this channel.
He's currently live right now.
I will we're not we're not going to put the pressure of of 23,000 people right.
Like with just no pressure.
It's not a number it's the the expectation of content.
Okay.
Coming from you to me is like I I it doesn't matter how many people there are.
I know I'm disappointing them all.
All right well then I'm not going to raid you.
I then I'm just you're giving such an extraordinary strange circumstance.
No no no no no you're giving expectations.
Life is about overcoming expectations.
So you have to do it to help me.
Okay so everybody be aware stir is not going to produce any content apparently.
But what do you mean content.
You're watching E3 and just hanging out.
That is content.
But like that's you're not expected to do anything else.
You don't have to like do a magic show for everybody.
But there's no E3 for another hour.
Am I supposed to be an entertaining person on my own.
Well all right how about this then I'll just host you in an hour.
No that's stupid.
Well what what do you what do you mean.
Well in an hour like everyone would have already like gone and ate dinner.
I'll just sit around the dinner table.
I'm just raiding you.
I'm doing it right now so I'm you're literally it's happening now.
So I'll see you later.
People can stay or they don't stay.
It doesn't whatever like who cares.
Okay I'm like I'm mentally preparing myself like okay.
German German viewers coming over German content.
Do I need to put on like a like a funny costume.
What can I do.
Just be you and hang out and watch E3.
Okay all right.
That's the last.
It's a pleasure.
I'll talk to you soon.
Well I want to I actually really do want to do that.
The remaster an old video.
Yeah we'll talk about it.
We'll figure it out.
We'll set a date.
We'll do it.
All right I'll see you guys.
I'll actually I'm going to say my I'm going to do my outro.
You know you know how it is.
YouTubers you know what I'm saying.
Yeah you know I'm going to run to the bathroom real quick.
So people they cannot show up while I'm peeing.
I will not one day.
Okay goodbye.
He's gone.
So I will see you guys.
Thanks for watching the Slime Rancher 2.
Huge pog moment.
I'm really interested in that.
That's probably the number one thing.
I'm kind of interested in the nothing else.
I don't think I can't think of anything.
Slime Rancher 2 looks really fun.
I also want to say I did say it on Twitter.
But I mean we're live right now.
I might as well address it.
I have been who cares right.
It's been 10 years as of what yesterday day before.
I've been doing this for 10 years.
I'm a 35 year old man.
Started my YouTube channel June 11th 2011.
It's been a fucking long time.
I I do people don't watch TV shows for more than five 10 years.
So it's shocking that 10 years later people still watch.
It's remarkable to me.
And especially considering that.
I'm looking at the view count number right now.
People keep coming here.
And I hope you like the stream.
I don't want to.
Here's the thing that I don't want to ever have happen.
The more that that number goes up.
I don't want to have myself be like oh shit.
20,000 30,000 okay.
What do I do?
I gotta be good.
I gotta be funny.
Like Star was just saying right.
I gotta try to keep grounded.
Because the more that I see people come in.
The more that I want to.
I just want to stay the same.
I don't want to like do anything different.
That's something that I'm concerned about.
Because when you look over and you see that it's just like oh fuck.
Why are there this many people here?
He's retiring.
Not yet.
Relax.
Yeah.
Thanks for uh thanks for sticking with this channel for this long.
It's been a very long time and I'm surprised every day.
We'll see how much further it goes.
We'll see how how it does right.
I don't have any expectations.
I never did.
So I'm just going to keep going.
Thanks a lot.
Hope I can continue to do the things you want to see.
I watch.
Thank you.
So uh very important though.
Tomorrow I am going to be live on Ms. Kip's channel.
I'm going to be on OTK Schooled.
I'm going to be a contestant on that stream.
So if you want to see me tomorrow uh potentially embarrass myself completely.
With uh not being able to answer what like 10 times like 30 is or something.
I've been practicing.
I'm hoping I can be good.
I'm ready.
That's tomorrow at 1 p.m pacific.
Ms. Kip's channel.
Two Central.
One Pacific.
I have to practice.
I can't get eliminated in kindergarten.
That would be so awful.
People make that joke but I can't get eliminated in like the first grade.
I would never live that down.
I've been panicking about it for the last like four days.
All right let's raid stir.
I'll see you guys later.
See you tomorrow if you watch that stream.
Uh we're getting a shitload of community subs but okay where are they?
Let me see.
Why do I I can't see it now.
Where'd it go?
Oh my stream's been playing the whole time in the background.
Good thank god it's muted.
Let me see who gave some subs here.
Let's take a look.
Uh but yeah I'll be there at 1 p.m pacific.
I just don't want to be the first person to get eliminated.
I really hope that like everybody's like as stupid as I could be.
You know what I mean?
I don't want to be the first person out.
All right we had a lot of subs.
Capra man thanks for five subs.
A straight pub thanks for 10 subs.
Onymos thanks for 20 community subs.
Uh Mr. Generic Man thanks for five.
And Keaton KTW thanks for 10 community subs.
Thanks guys.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
Well that was a very interesting stream.
There's a lot of um it's always interesting when stirs around uh for better or for worse.
As you have probably come to see over the last three and a half hours.
Uh we're gonna raid them.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Have a great rest of your day.
Uh at this point I need to wash my hands of any strange shit he might say.
So have a great night everybody.
We'll see you soon.
See you tomorrow if you go watch.
Again it's Ms. Kiff's channel at 1 p.m pacific.
See you later.