Stream is gonna, uh, get kind of killed here because I'm about to download this.
By the way, if you notice that no drop frames at all, it's been a perfect stream.
Uh, I'm not streaming to the server that I- I did- I did a server hopscotch and then found one.
So, we're good. But it's gonna be a little slow for a sec. I think we're good.
Alright, Soul Stone Surv- Wait, did this actually- did this win?
I forgot again. It's the third time I've asked. What won the poll?
Okay, I gotta close out of this.
That was Pac-Man World. Pretty cool.
Can I use the controller for this?
Soul Stone Survivors. Give it a shot.
Is this game good? Okay.
Fight. Character. I can do Barbarian.
Pyromancer. Houndmaster.
Alright. 15% crit damage.
Armor power. Attack speed multiplier.
Movement speed multiplier. Alright. Crit damage. Damage multiplier.
Alright, let's do this one.
Blacksmith. Uh, whatever. I don't care.
I'll figure it out as I go here.
Skill tree? Oh, cool. That's alright.
Alright, cool. Let's just play.
Fight. Wait. Alright.
The Scorching Valley. Yeah, let's go.
Oh, the title says Pac-Man Party. Oops.
This is- this is not- this is not sponsored.
Hold on. Gotta change the title.
Um, trying this new game. What is that?
There we go. Trying this new game.
So how does this work? So I can- I can aim?
I don't think it matters if I aim, right?
I do have something I want to change.
That's fine. This has to come down.
General, uh, alright. Yeah. Graphics. Make sure they're good.
Looks good. Alright, we're good.
That's one of the- I just didn't want the- it was kind of the music was loud.
Alright, let's go.
So just like Vampire Survivors, you pick up this stuff.
This- this feels pretty- kind of fun.
Let's see. We'll- we'll give it a shot.
Alright, just leveled up.
Do I have to press a button? Oh, R.
Oh, it pauses. Okay.
Multicast. Increases the chance of activating all your skills multiple times by 16%.
Increases your block power.
Creates four fiery orbs that rotate around you, causing 40 damage and applying burn.
Probably this.
But these are- this is epic.
Should I do it?
Uh, I guess I'll just turn that on.
So there's a 16% chance- chance- chance- I'd spe-
There's a- there's a 16% chance that I will do this twice.
Like, back whack.
What the hell is- wait, is that it?
Am I- is that me doing that?
There it is.
Okay, yeah, so that's what it is.
That's pretty cool.
Can that be upgraded?
Oh my god, dude, it proc.
Okay, fire bolt.
Shoots a fire projectile and I think I need more damage moves.
Oh, I can see the- at the cooldown.
Oh, I'm gonna die.
Oh, I got level- I got two levels up.
This is a- this looks like roblox.
It doesn't- it does not look like roblox or stuff.
Ooh, that's pretty huge.
Yep, that's gonna make my fireball bigger.
Yep.
Um, let me alone, please.
You need- you can dash?
Oh, I can dash.
All right, that's good to know.
Thank you without so many crunchies over here.
All right, I hit the ground in front of you calling a thunderstrike,
dealing 350 damage and applying stun.
Skeletal Warth Rust.
Are you gonna play Nokia Snake?
That game was awesome.
Which one of these should I do?
Which one's good?
Skeletons?
Okay.
Here's the damage of units summoned by the Skeletal Warrior skill by 20%.
Let's do it.
Here's the attack speed of the firebolt skill.
That's pretty good.
That's probably better.
That means it can happen.
Yeah, let's do this one.
Wait, this left one.
All right, let's go.
Skeletons seem very good.
Eliminate Columeth, the avatar of ice.
Okay.
Meteor?
Yeah.
Wait, this one's probably better.
Yeah, because it does my, uh, summons too, right?
Hell yeah.
Eliminate more monsters.
Okay, I got five lords.
Ooh.
All right, hold on.
What is the blue thing that's going to be?
Is that, see like the blue shards?
Is that, that's pretty good.
Is this like Vampire Survivors where I could only have six weapons and six items?
I don't know.
Maybe?
Yeah.
This one?
All right, let's go.
I love this game.
Is it good?
I mean, I, it feels pretty, it feels pretty good for a game that, you know, is
very obviously directly inspired by, you know,
this type of game, right?
I don't know, you know, Vampire Survivors is a really popular one, but it,
was there anything before Vampire Survivors?
But Vampire Survivors kind of, uh, pull a, um, like a genre creator.
Yeah, I feel like I've seen games like this before.
They just weren't as good as Vampire Survivors.
They just weren't even close for me.
Crit.
You and your nearby allies, all damage done by 40%.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Doom.
How about just, no, let's go with attack speed.
20 minutes till dawn does it best.
I never heard of that.
Is it good?
What happened to Pac-Man?
Oh, really weird.
We got to the end and, uh, mechanical evil Pac-Man, uh,
eats regular Pac-Man and like chews him up and like bone crunching sounds happen.
It was really fucked up.
I think somebody wrote, AKA, it sucked.
It did not suck.
That's unfair to Pac-Man.
It wasn't, I am being genuine.
It was a very nice game.
It was polished.
It was fun.
It was fine.
It was okay.
All right.
What do I have?
There's so many moves.
Thunder.
Oh, wait a minute.
Cancel.
Replace.
Wait, do I have any of these?
Um, oh shit.
Okay.
Should I, this one looks pretty good.
Chain Lightning looks kind of good.
Uh, I'm going to replace, I don't know.
What should I replace?
Can I just skip?
That's too many words.
Just click the coolest image.
Okay.
This one.
I'll get rid of this.
This thing sucks.
I don't think it was actually, that thing was actually the only thing killing anything.
No, the skeleton's still.
Look at all the synergies I have with the skeletons.
I think it's pretty good.
Is this sponsored?
No, it was, you guys voted for this.
Chat, we got complainers in the chat.
Wait, we got, we got, we got chat complainer randies.
I mean, you guys, you guys voted for this.
It's fun.
What are you, what are you on about?
I mean, just like in Vampire Survivors, if I knew what kind of was good with what,
that's how you figure it out.
You just play and you lose and you come back and you try again.
All right.
Um, there's even more.
Should I do?
I want this.
Um, shit.
I have so many items down here.
I just don't know what you want to do.
That's definitely awesome.
That's good too.
That's good.
How do you feel about hard seltzer?
It's okay.
Skeletal archers.
Oh shit.
All right.
I definitely need to replace this.
Uh, this one.
We're going full skeletons here.
That's very frustrated.
Um, oh, go get the, get Taco Bell.
The guy that asked that question an hour ago.
Right now he's just sitting there in a bite of his, of his McDonald's burger going.
Fuck an asshole.
He's starved.
All right.
What's this boss?
I can get him.
I'm going to die.
Well, there's so much shit going on.
All right.
I got it.
Crit damage.
Skeletal mage.
We're going to replace this with this.
Six percent more damage.
I'm just looking at all this stuff.
Um, attack speed.
Um, do I, do I have any of these?
No.
You don't have an attack.
That's fine.
I got these skeletons.
The skeletons are wiping up.
I don't need to have an attack myself.
Skeletons are doing it for me.
I got a McDonald's happy meal.
That's not enough food for me.
I could probably eat five McDonald's happy meals.
I probably, I'm, I probably could.
If you gave me 40 minutes,
I could probably eat five McDonald's happy meals.
They're going to walk the skeletons into people.
40 minutes?
Yeah, I don't think it would take.
It's one single cheeseburger, guys.
Isn't a McDonald's happy meal one single cheeseburger
and a little small fry or an apple slice or something?
Or nuggets?
Guys, I could eat 20 nuggets.
My eyes.
That would take me.
It would be so simple.
I could eat five full happy meals.
What about the drinks?
I mean, I don't think it's fair to include all the drinks
because that's just liquid that you can't.
It's not too much liquid.
I don't think I could do 10.
I know I could do five.
I think about it.
Two double cheeseburgers from McDonald's is four patties.
There's four burgers right there.
I know the bread too, but I'll be fine.
You can't.
Yes, I can.
You don't eat the toy.
What are you talking about?
Yep.
All right.
I don't think I'm lasting very long here.
I think I'm dead here.
That's it.
All right.
So now what?
Oh, actually, I have money.
Blacksmith.
Oh, I see.
What?
20 minutes till dawn.
This game was fun.
This was cool.
This is like a free demo, right?
What's 20 minutes till dawn?
Is the game any good?
I'll try this one too before leaving.
All right.
I'll try 20 minutes till dawn.
Let's try all these vampire survivor type games.