Hey, how are you? Yeah, I know, I know, I know. Listen, I don't know what it is about my body.
I don't know why my body does this or why it's like this. Well, I mean, I think I could take a guess.
At like 358 almost every day, I have to go to the bathroom. It's something the way that like my,
my pipes are in my body. It's just like, all right, okay. 355. Let's go. 356. Okay. 357. I gotta go.
It happens every day. I, you know what I have to start doing? I have to start just make, I've got
to start eating an hour earlier. At least. Yes, I, yeah, hold on. I know. My microphone is changed.
I, I'm, well, we're gonna work on it in a minute. My microphone, I fucked with a bunch of settings.
So I'm trying to figure out what, how, how, how fucked up it is. I'm, it's, I'm peaking.
You sound like the Joker. Sounds fun. How does it sound? It's really loud. Yeah. I mean, I,
I've taken the criticism. I turned myself way up and I, I made sure that I was loud as fuck now.
You know what I'm saying? He, he went from being way too quiet to really fucking loud.
Does it sound all right? We go, should I drop it a little bit? Because I have,
let me see what happens if I do this. I sound, I'm louder. Let, let me know if this is a better
place. Is this better? Dropping the gain a little bit. How does it sound? Better? Is it fine? You
sound like you're canned. I'm canned. Well, you know what I think I want to do one of these days,
maybe even today, I don't know, is just do, do a stream where I sit there and just mess with
settings until you guys give me all thumbs up emotes. And I have another dead pixel on this
monitor and it's really not making me happy. I'll tell you. What do the mods say? Do I, okay,
let me ask you this. Do I sound better or worse than I did two days ago? Better or worse than
two days ago? Better with question marks. Okay. I need to test this too, because I need to make
sure I'm not going to hurt anybody. If I like do like the patent to German on eight, five,
yell at the thing on screen. I'm going to yell and I want to see if the compressor catches it.
Cause I'm, I need to make sure that happens. Cause I don't want to hurt anybody's ears.
So turn me down a little bit and let's, let's test this to see how bad this sounds.
Okay. You ready? I'm going to make a loud sound. Just I want to, I'm warning you all right now.
What the, what is that? What is that guy? Oh, wow. Oh my God. He just killed me bad. Are we okay?
Did it, did it catch it? Did it not? It was all right. That's not all right. Cool. Yeah.
Cause when you mess with a compressor like this, or you mess with audio settings, if I yell and
the compressor doesn't catch it, it's actually going to be bad and it'll be really way too loud
and just fuck up everything. So, all right. All right. All right. Let's go. All right.
So his plan is we're doing today. Today, today we're going to be doing iron lung,
which people have been saying, you got to do that. You got to play it. I believe this is by the
dusk devs or dusk dev. So it's, but it's only an hour long. This is only like maybe an hour to two
hours long total. I loved dusk. I thought dusk was one of my, I, you know what, thinking back to dusk,
that's, I would put that probably high up on some of my favorite games I played on stream.
That game was so much fun. It was great. It was unbelievable. So, I mean, obviously if the person
that made dusk or the group that made dusk, I want to play their other game, but it's only going to
be like an hour or so. This game is not like dusk. Oh no, I know, I know. I know. I know it's a scary,
scary game. I know it's very scary. There's going to be a face cam. Well, okay. Look at the streamer.
He got really scared. So we'll do kind of like a scary game thing today. Then after that,
we're going to play Glover for the N64. They ported it to Steam and here we go again.
Glover was ported to Steam and it was voted on by pre-stream chat. So that's what we're going to do.
And then if Glover sucks, and I gotta tell you, Glove buddies, the same rules are going to apply
for Glover when I kind of, I mean, maybe, we'll see. If I love the game and I think it's like the
most fun I've ever had, I'm going to keep playing it. But after an hour or two in Glover, the
strawberry magic rules are going to apply and we're going to have to see how powerful the Glove buddies
are. You are sus. Yes. Okay, first thing is first. Wits play Iron Lung, right? Because that's what
we're doing. What about eating a glove? Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right. Let me address that.
All right. Let me address it. I'll address it. Just give me a second. I gotta tweet this. I'll
address it in a second. Be right back. Okay. So a couple of years ago, I made a comment saying,
maybe embarrassingly, that the three Stooges were going to be added to Fortnite by April 24th,
2022. And I mean, that was probably back in like 2019 or so. And I said I would bet anything.
And what I bet was, I bet that I would eat a glove on stream if they weren't in the game by
tomorrow. So, so we'll see. We'll see what happens. Well, we'll see. We'll see. You know,
we'll see what happens. They could, they could get added tomorrow. It's possible. We'll see.
So if they're not added, and look, it's probably like a licensing issue, right? They probably
were going to. It's a licensing problem, without a doubt. So I'm sure they tried to add the three
Stooges, but paramount pictures or whatever. Probably whoever owns three Stooges were like,
nah, we want to live with whatever the whatever the drama behind the scenes was to make it so
they weren't in the game. I don't know. But I'm gonna have to eat a glove eventually here.
All right. I'm gonna play around with some audio settings. You guys let me know how it sounds.
You ready? Let's do a couple of tests. You ready? Here we go. Here's the first test. Hi, guys.
This is German. Hold on. Hey, guys. It's me, German985. Coming to you from my studio.
And I'm ready to say hi. I'm ready to say what's going on. Ready to check in on how everybody's
doing. How are we? Are we good? How are we? Is it better than it just was in his studio?
Is that actually better? The mic is too hot. All right. So how about, how about now? How's
everybody doing? It's me, German985 here coming at you from my studio. Want to check in on how
everybody's doing? Want to see how crispy this sounds? How crunchy it might sound?
It's a podcast. Wait, good? You guys can't say good to everything. These are too bassy. All right.
Hold on. How about, how does this sound? Hey, guys. It's me, German. Coming at you here from
my studio. Just checking to see how crunchy and crunchy this sounds. If we've got some opinions
on how I sound, I would love to hear them. They sound the same. Test with a wheeze laugh. Okay.
Better? First one was better? Sounds like you're very ugly. Oh, dude, I don't know about this one.
You sound really ugly. The first one was, okay, wait. How about now? How about now? Hi, guys.
How's everybody doing? We having a good time here? We have, we chilling? This is shit now. Okay. How
about this? Hey, guys. How are we doing now? We chilling? Having a good time? Everybody having
a relaxing evening? I'm seeing a lot of betters. I'm seeing a lot of betters. Let me see what this
sounds like. Hey, how does it sound? Hey, guys. How are you doing? Oh, fuck. This actually sounds
like shit. Hold on. Hey, guys. Hey, guys. Hey, guys. Hey, guys. Hey, guys. Hey, guys. Hey, guys. Hey,
guys. Hey, everybody. How's everybody doing? My name is German at eight five. Hi, everybody. How
you doing? My name is German. I know this is so fucked up. Look, you can make changes. You can
change how you sound. It's so like, look at this. This is ridiculous. Okay. I actually think this
one might be the best one. If everyone wants to disagree, they can. I think this actually
might be pretty good. Are we in agreement that this one sounds better? To me, this one sounds
fine. This one sounds okay. Yeah, I think this is fine for now. I'll figure it out. You're a bad
audio quality streamer. He's trolling. No, I'm not. I'm scrolling on shit. I think this actually
sounds fine. Can I get a confirmation from the mods and the sounds fucking pog before I go?
It's still a little compressed. How about actually this actually sounds better. Oh, yeah. I think I
got it. Bingo. Got it right now. This is it. This is the one. This is absolutely the one right here.
Yep. It sure is. All right. Let me turn it up. There we go. Guys, I got it. I think I got this
the one. This is the one right here. This is the one. This is the one. Nobody move. I got it. This
is the one. Yep. I got it. This is good. Let's fucking go. I'm ready. Audio is so fucking hard
to work with. It really is like fuck audio. You know what I mean? You know, the worst thing I ever
did was I get like a fucking real microphone. I should just have a thing taped to my mouth.
The whole, who cares? You guys ready? Let's go. The biggest mistake you can ever make as a streamer
is like, Oh, I got to have like a professional microphone and I've got to have a setup where it
goes into a compressor and then it goes with the compressor into the computer. And then I go into
my audio settings or JG equalizer. No, just give me a tape fucking microphone in my mouth and who
cares? And now, now you can hear when I move. I fucked up. God damn it. Do I have the other
profile that I had saved? Of course not. Shit. Oh, I fucked it up. I fucked it up so bad.
All right. Hold on. Yep. Got it. All right. Let's go. Fucking shitty audio, Andy, whatever.
Boy, what do you see? You got to have a professional setup.
How are you doing? You're doing good. Let's play iron lung. This is loud. DJ Andy. This is really
fucking loud. All right. Is this like, is this getting, is this game going to scream at me?
Is this a screamer or am I fine? Lights off. It's, it's like four o'clock in the afternoon guys,
but it's not going to do anything. Maybe later. There you go. I just made a mess. No, I didn't.
I'm fine. It's just soap. That's all it is. Oh, it's on my hand. All right. So there you go.
I ate a glove on stream. What was I doing? I don't even know what I was just doing. What was I just
doing? What was I just doing right now? Somebody help me. Turning the lights off. Right. Okay.
They're already off. The lights are already off. They're not on. The lights are already off.
Are we ready? Okay. I know stalling, stalling, stalling. My microphone sounds like stupid.
I'm sorry. I thought I was fixing things and I just made it worse. All right. You guys ready?
Let's go. New game. That was huge. I'm ready. Let's go. Decades ago, every known star and
habitable planet vanished, leaving only those who were on space stations or starships. This event
became known as the Quiet Rapture. With supplies dwindling and infrastructure crumbling, survivors
are searching for any trace of natural resources in a universe of barren moons lit by the ghost
light of vanished stars. One such moon holds a strange anomaly, an ocean of blood. You are a
convict tasked with exploring this anomaly in a makeshift submarine nicknamed the Iron Lung.
It was not designed for this depth, so you will be welded inside and the forward window will be
closed. There was no time for training. If successful, you earn your freedom. So every
planet disappeared and got destroyed. Drink the bubble mix. You just coming up with all kinds of
stupid shit, aren't you? Like for me to do. Why would anybody do that? That's not happening.
Don't do that. Why would you? Why would anybody do that? Don't be like, take care of your bodies.
Don't drink fucking like shit that can hurt you. All right. So let me get like a, let me get a
TLDR here. I was like fucked up voice. Andy's is still reigning supreme here. So I'm a convict.
Everybody, every all life died and we like got stuck on a space station. You got it. I got a
better mic than I do. Roger, can you repeat that please? View ASD is move, interact, tabs and map.
Whoa. Briefing. Two weeks ago, we conducted an exploration of moon 85 for the first time since
the quiet rapture leading to the discovery of a fourth blood ocean. Trench beneath the ocean
surface has several points of interest. Your task is to photograph these points of interest
with the SM 13 forward camera. Photos must be taken within two units of the specified position
and 10 degrees of the specified angle. You can also use the camera to help with navigation.
Only photos taken at the specified points of interest will be saved. Since you can't navigate
by site, pay attention to your coordinates and consult the map. Proximity indicators next to
the sub controls will trigger if you're getting close to an obstacle. If they laugh, this guy
wanted to ban geometry in classrooms. Am I going to need some help? All right. So I have to go take
pictures of this stuff and I have this forward facing camera. What does, what does this do?
Can I open the, how do I take, can I, can I look at it, look through something? All right. So this
is, what, what, what, what was it? What was it? Okay. Points of interest. Okay. So X 325,
Y 741, X 325. Dude, I actually like can't see cause it's too bright in this room. I should've
played this like in two hours. I'm, I'm playing this game at the absolute worst possible time
because the sun is like, it's like four o'clock in the afternoon where the sun is like at its
fucking apex. Okay. That's a, there's so much glare on my screen. What was that? How do I change X?
All right. What was it? It was, I'll go here first. X 180, Y 576. Can I look out the window?
I'm in a submarine. Yeah. Do I know where I, okay. Hover over Y five, A 184. Where's A?
Is this A? Oh no. I'm going south. Okay. How do I change X? I'm in a submarine. Yeah. Yeah. I know.
But how do I like, oh shit. This is not an expedition. It's, it's an execution. When they
put you in here, they don't want you to return. And even if you do, and even if they keep their
promises, what freedom waits for you? A few dying ships in a sea of dead stars. How do I take a
picture? If there's still hope, it lies beyond the veil. Hoping this void is as illusionary as the
walls and dark souls and demon souls and dark souls three and Sekiro as the starlight. I will
choose to breathe my last here at the bottom of the ocean, unseen, unheard and uncontrolled. They
will get their execution. I will get my freedom. Oh, these are the buttons over here. What's this?
Ooh, this is the, okay. This is where I am. I just took this picture, right? We've got an,
we've got an anomaly. How do I move? Oh, okay. I get it. All right. So now what's,
what's like close to me right here? I need Y, I need something X in like the hundreds, right?
Am I close to anything? All right. I'm, I'm going to go for, so, okay, help me. We're talking about
an axis here. So like X, Y, right? Yes. Yeah. So like, um, when I'm talking about the X axis,
that I'm talking about like left and right, and then Y up and down. They should fucking remove
geometry from school. Teach people how to do their taxes. Not like what that line and that
line does. Okay. So I want 180X, which is pretty much there. Let's go a little bit further back
here. 180. So 180X is here. So I don't know where, where am I in Y? 178. So I'm like right here.
178. So I'm like down here. Oh, okay. So I'm like right here. So if I go to the right,
so I need 186 for 22. What am I high? What, what? I don't get it. This is X and Y, right? Isn't this
like where I am right now? Wait, what are you talking about? The numbers. Yeah, this is X,
right? X1. This is where I am right now. X180Y178. X180Y178. So I'm like right here. I'm like right
here. What are you talking about? Yeah, I'm reading this correctly. I gotta stop doing that
because people like, I look at the asshole. How many times have I like done the like, I'm like
coming into the camera. Like I'm going into the camera. Okay. So I just have to go this way. So
let's go that way. So I need to stay at 180. So if I'm here, I need to go like this. So I need X322
and I'll adjust it. What, what, what, what? What's wrong? Is that a wall? Oh shit. Um,
so I'm at X200Y. So is this, okay. Is the dark solid? This is, is this like a solid wall? Is this,
this dark area? No. Okay. So I just have to like turn. Okay. So what if I take a picture here? Is
it safe to go that way? I think so. Okay. We're good. X322. What was that? I'm not going to hit
that wall. Okay. We're good. Put the curtains down. Curtains. X322Y186. What is A? What's A?
Angle. So this is angle. Okay. Fine. All right. Almost there. X322Y186. I'm almost at 322. So I
gotta start going 322. Almost there. All right. 133. Angle 33. What the fuck are you talking about?
322. 183. Put the curtain. I can't do the curtains. 186. I'm pretty much there. I'm gonna change the
angle. 33. 322. 186. What's that? I found something. What's that thing? I gotta go down a little more,
I think. 322. I'm not quite there. Okay. No, no, no. Other way. Other way. Other 322. I gotta go
this way. 322. And then I have to go up. 322. 186. So I have to go up or down. I don't know. You don't
have to be perfect. Oh, okay. I'm almost there. 186, right? 33. The rock. Do I just go forward?
Oh, I got it. That was it? Oh, shit. All right. That was good. So we're gonna go from here to here.
So I got the picture, right? Do I have to print this? Or does it, does this count? Like, do I have
to print this out? No. Okay. All right. Counts. All right. So now I'm gonna go 378. 263. I think
I can just do this. Wait, am I gonna crash into the rocks? Oh my god. Okay. I need to turn. Just
move out of the way. 378. 263. 378. 263. Game saved. That means something happened. I'm almost
there. All right. Let's go up a little higher. 263. All right. All right. All right. 363. Let's
go more to the right here. 378. Angle 50. So what's here? Got another rock formation? Yep. Okay.
Anything here I need to see? Make sure I get a closer look. There's like a slug there. Okay. I
got it. So how, where, so I, should I, okay, I'm thinking head up this way and wrap around
and end like down here. Or go this way and wrap around and end here. I wonder. I think I'm gonna
go up this way. This way seems like a good route. Or this is, what's closer? Okay. This is 259. 406.
So I gotta go up. Yeah. 406. We gotta go up high. Hey, it's all right. No, I'm not near it. 406. Stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. What is it? What's wrong? All right. It's just a
brush. It's just a little bit of brush. 406. I gotta be careful. I gotta change this to 259. So
I gotta go 304. So I gotta go left a little bit. Hang a left. Wait, why is that? Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
That's a wall, dude. I mean, it's, it was, it was like, what does that mean? How do I increase
oxygen? Okay. Fuck. What's that? I'm not gonna, whoa. Oh my goodness. Okay. Wait. Turn, turn,
turn, turn, turn. Okay. Can I go around? How do I get oxygen? I'm almost at the right height here.
Okay. That's fine. 406. So I'm like, where am I? 2378. So I'm here. I need to just go left now,
but I have to wrap around. Oh damn. Where am I? I'm like in a cavern. Can I go this way? Am I
gonna hit this? How, how close do I have to be to hit something? All right. Pull it back a little.
Turn your lights off. I can't. Yeah. I gotta, there's something in the way here. I gotta go
all the way around it. What number I'm looking for? Looking for 259. God damn. That's far. And
then I'll have to go down. All right. And then I'm going to wrap around and go down. It's scary.
Okay. Um, should I go? I'm gonna have to go this way still. Oh, fuck. Can I make it through this?
Can I make it through this? If I just like sneak through, can I make it through that?
That's a wall. Is it a wall? Like a full wall? Shit. It's a big wall. How do I get around this?
Fuck. How do I approach this? Use the map. But I thought you guys said that the dark outline
didn't mean anything. I asked. I said, are these walls? And everyone said, no, the white is the
walls. Oh, I asked if this was important. I thought this was just like a, like pools or something. I'm
inside of this area. All right. I thought this was like, like a interesting looking map. All right.
I get it. All right. But I asked like, are these walls? Is this like solid? And everyone was like,
no, no, no. I asked if these were walls. It was the reverse. The pools is the ocean. How am I
supposed to get here then? Why did you guys tell me to go this way? I can't even go up here. This
is blocked off. All right. Okay. All right. Let's fucking go. So right now a 312, 457, 312, 457.
I'm like here, here, 457. All right. So I'm like looking at this wall right here. So if I go all
the way left and pull it this way, I should be all right, right? If I go like this, this should be
okay. Dude, the shit got real thin. All right. Here we go. You guys confused me. I thought you
all right. I had from the very beginning. All right. I'm close now. 259, 406. So I need to kind
of pull it up this way a little. There's something like, what the fuck is going on? What is this?
What's the angle? 296. What is that? What the fuck is that? Oh, did I not get a picture of it?
406. Do I have to get closer? Oh, angle 259. Okay. But it's 259 to angle 296. Oh fuck. I'm mixing
them up. I have to go this way though backwards. I navigation is like, I don't fucking do it. Like
I can't like plot land and shit. Like I give me a fucking dodge roll and I'll beat ever again.
259. All right. This is close enough. So now I need 296. All right. So what is that? Oh shit.
I have to navigate out of here. It's the worm. Okay. So now I got to go. If I keep going down
and wrap around, I'll get there because I don't, can I, can I get up here this way?
I wonder if I can go up there or should I try to just go? I have to go this way. Maybe I can.
I'll try because I'm like right here. Is there like a disconnection on the map? No, I can't.
All right. I can't. All right. All right. So I'm going to turn around and go down
because I'm like right here. I'm just going to go straight down. Use the third dimension.
That sounds like something they said in like 1995 or like 1996 or like a man, like a character.
So like you use the third dimension and it's like, oh, they turn into like
3d like Homer Simpson did. Okay. So I'm at two 56, 377. I'm three 70. I'm like here.
So I got to pull it to the right a little head this way. Uh huh. I know. I know. I'm like right
on the edge here. All right. Two, two 80, three 38, two 80, three 38. I'm like right here. So I
got to keep going down to the right. Okay. Nothing. Are you real? A CG character can't do that. Okay.
We're not at CG technology where, where like they can do this and it looks like that CG doesn't look
like that. See like skin. They don't have the technology to do skin yet. No, they don't like
hair. No, that's real hair. CG hair. It looks fucking ridiculous. All CG hair looks like the
person's underwater moving around. Sorry. I'm real. Look at this. CG can't do that yet. This
guy's jiggle physics are insane. You can't be real. You don't understand basic geometry.
I don't know how many times I have to say this. When you, okay, when you're in your thirties,
I would like for you to guys to remember what you did in high school. I have not.
Okay. When you, when you're out of like high school, you're out of college, you've been out
of a classroom for like fucking 15 years. There is no, there was no thing that I am ever doing
in my life that needs me to plot X and Y ever for any fucking reason ever. It's not like, oh,
hey, man, what are you doing today? Well, you know, plotting X, Y and angles. No, I'm cooking.
I'm doing my taxes. I'm doing fucking chores. I'm sleeping on the couch. You know what I mean?
It's there's no, there's no reason why I would ever do this. It's been like 20 years and you're,
you, I can't tell you the hard drive starts to fill in other shit and like geometry too is you
keep moving and it gets lost. The hard drive writes over it. When you're 30 fucking five, you, whoa.
When you are 35, you tell me how you do, but yeah, I got it. I could plot the fucking right
angle of a fucking acute triangle. No, you won't. No, you got more important shit to worry about.
Like, you know, like how long the grass is outside and like, is there a hummingbird that you saw?
And what's, what's the early bird special at the breakfast place? When I go to the early bird
special, the breakfast place, the, the waiter or waitress doesn't come over and give me a worksheet
and say, Hey, can you solve for X? No, they go, here you go, sir. Here's two sunny side up eggs.
Okay. Where am I? Three, six, three, two, eight, four, three, six, three, two, eight, four. I'm like
here. He's 63. All right. I gotta go up a little. Okay. Ooh, easy. Where am I? Three, seven, six,
two, nine, two, three, seven, six, two, nine, two. All right. I'm like right here. So I gotta
go up a little more. I'm not going to hit this. Right. Three, eight, six, three, 14, three, eight,
six, three, 14. Okay. I think I can just go up a little and then write a lot of people's jobs
involve geometry. So do the geometry job. Are you mad at me? What just happened? What's going on?
How do I fix this? How do I fix this? What happened? Do I have to fix that? Four? Okay.
I'm through the tunnel. I think four 38, three 22. I'm through the tunnel. All right. So I'm right
here. So I just kind of have to go like right. And then down. So we'll go like this and go
get to solve equations. So I need to hit five 60. Okay. You need to solve the math quiz.
Now these, all these math problem, Andy's, they tell me, Oh, I got to solve a math problem.
I know how to do math, math problem, Andy. I'm sorry. 500, 300. All right. I'm close. 500,
five 62 77.
I've 62 77. I gotta go up. Did I pass it? Two 77. Oh, this way. All right. I'm almost there.
Let me see. What does this person say? It should be like, I ain't never going to use the Pythagorean
theorem and then stream for a living. Like you are right. But regular people, sane people use it
sometimes. No, don't quit the game. I didn't always stream for a living. Even worse. I was
a substitute teacher. Do I need to know the Pythagorean theorem to do this? No, who cares?
Whatever. Whatever. I don't care. I win. I win. I win. All right. 43, five 60. I'm there. So I need
to turn to 43. But the Pythagorean theorem, man, like, what are you talking about? I don't need to
know the Pythagorean theorem to order from the Wendy's drive-through. Like who cares?
Like, okay. I understand. If you're like a contractor, you're like a architect or something,
right? Or you're like making blueprints or you're like doing work in like 3D design. All right.
It's specific work. That's like a big fish. Did I get it? Okay. I got it. So we got to go.
Wait, I want to see another angle of this. That was crazy. Yeah. I'm sorry. I'm a clown for a
living. Do you? Okay. When the clown blows... Do you understand what you're fucking, what you're
asking, who you're talking to? Do you understand who you're talking to right now? Like, honestly,
like if you do go to the clown show or the magician show and they do like balloon animals,
you don't like raise your hand and the clown's like, all right, yes, you. Um, can you like solve
this for X? The guy's going to be like, what do you want from me? I don't fucking do that.
I don't. I fucking make balloon animals for a living. What do you want me to do?
No, you're not going to have like the clown do like a fucking complex math problem. All right.
So we're going to go down here. This is open water too. All right. 55. Let's go here. Why is this?
What if he's a math clown? You'd get booed. A math clown would get fucking booed off the stage.
Are you serious? He comes out up there like, I can't. Oh, yeah. Oh yeah. Okay. So you see the
right angle here. What I want you kids to do is I want you to take out your pens and papers and I
want you to write down. This is 90 here. Okay. And then this is just 180 times those three angles
together. And I want you to solve, uh, what the area is. It'd be like kids start crying.
Kids would be fucking crying in the audience. You're going to make a bunch of kids cry.
The parents would leave shitty Yelp reviews. It'd be like we ordered a clown and the guy did like
math problems and like it was fucking terrible. I wish I could have gotten my money back. 613.
What's the 190? Okay. I'm on the right track. All right. I'm getting there. 197. That's literally
a family guy joke. You stole that from the show. No, I, I, guys, I don't, I didn't, I didn't, I,
no, I didn't. No, I didn't. That's not even in family guy. That's not in family guy. You're a
liar. Okay. 55. It's not. No, it's not. The thing is everybody will believe you because family guy,
like that could be a family guy joke and everyone will believe you because family guys made a bunch
of just like random references to every single thing ever. Skeleton, the rib cage or something.
I need to get a little closer. 613. One nine seven. Okay. Is that close enough?
195. All right. 55. Is that close enough? Holy shit. It's like a dinosaur. Hold on. Holy shit.
Okay. Wait a little more. Whoa. That's kind of cool. All right. This is going to be a pain in
the ass. Um, so if I go from here, I just go that way. I don't want to crash into this though.
That's kind of cool. I even checked for scurvy. I'm kind of concerned as I drink like a green
tea drink that has like vitamin C. I'm fine. All right. Let me just make sure I know where I am.
640 195. 640 195. So I'm like here. So from now just go boink. I should be fine for a little while.
I'm confused about what's happening. Uh, I am somebody that is locked in this submarine
and it's my job to go take pictures of anomalies that are on the bottom of the ocean.
All life has been removed from the planet. Uh, and I, there's like a space station that they have
created and then people that were on space stations, um, stay alive, I guess. Cause like
everything on planets died. I don't know. It's interesting. All right. I should slow down here.
Seven 10 eggs, seven 10, two 50, seven 10, two 50. I'm about right here. All right. Still on the
right path. Keep going. I'm going to, this is going to be so hard to navigate this little hole.
Okay. I think so it's seven 32, two 70, seven 32, two 70. I'm like here. All right. So this
should be all right. Now I just have to just weave through this. Yo, are you scared? Yeah,
it's kind of weird. Okay. Seven. I gotta make sure I'm in the tunnel, which I might not be.
Two seven 62 68. I'm in the tunnel. I'm like right here. Yep. All right. Easy. Seven
all right. I think I'm in seven 88, two 71, seven 88, two 70. All right. I'm like here.
So I gotta go right and then yeah. Okay. We're good. We made it through.
What the fuck is a wall right there? Where am I? Huh? Eight. Okay. Eight, two 75,
800, two 75. Where is this birth canal? I'm going to be coming out of the birth canal. Just wait.
Okay. Eight 64, two 58. Getting there. This is kind of far out of the way.
Eight 64, two 58, two oh nine eight. I'm close. What is that? Eight 64,
two 58. Eight 60. I gotta get closer. How am I gonna get closer? Eight 64, two 58.
Is it this? Should I just turn the angle a little? It's like a log in the way. Am I not in the right
spot? Eight 64, two oh nine. Eight 64, two 58, two oh nine. I mean this is like almost exactly
where it is. Oh I got it. That was weird. What is that? It's like a log. So I gotta get out of here
and go up. Oh this is gonna be a huge pain in the ass. Looked like a house. Yeah it kind of did.
It's like a building. Yeah. That was weird. All right. I gotta get out of here now.
You should crash. It's funny. All right. So I'm here. I need to go like left. Gotta be careful.
This is a little tight area too. Eight 30, 300. Eight 30, 300. Eight 30, 300. All right. I'm like
I gotta go down left here. I'm way too high up. Easy. All right. Here it is. All right. Yeah.
I think I'm in the tunnel right now. Yeah. I definitely am. What do you guys call me
facing here? What is this? I recently started watching a lot of Ludwig and watch him at night.
I fall asleep usually. I had a dream one night where I was watching myself sleeping almost like
astral projecting. Suddenly Jerma wearing a beer hat and doing his ape walk comes through the wall
above me and peeks into my brain to see if I'm dreaming about him. After seeing that he starts
after seeing that I am he starts walking through the opposite wall while he repeats
number one variety streamer. Number one variety streamer. All right. People don't minus two me.
I just read it. You didn't even comment on it. What do you how am I supposed to comment on it?
Well that was a crazy one man. That's crazy. People have fucked up dreams about me. I don't
know why. Okay. Worst one guy moment. No. No. We don't do worst one guy moment. We don't do worst.
We only do best one guy moment. I and that's not how it works. Did I just hit something?
What did I just have? What happened? I didn't hit. Nothing was on the radar. All right. Where am I
now? Five seven five sixty three fifty five sixty three fifty. I'm how did I end up up? Wait what?
Five sixty three three fifty. Okay. Right. Five sixty three three fifty. I'm here. All right. So
I just got to go up. If I see a wall be careful. All right. Is it blood? All right. Four hundred.
Why four hundred? We're about here. Five fifty six. Okay. So I just need to I'm going through here
right now. So we're going to go up and then right. What happened? What happened? What the
fuck just happened? What? What the fuck happened? Where was I? Jesus. How did I crash? I was. What?
What's going on? What the fuck's happening? I got some soft locked? How? No I'm not. It's an auto
save that. Oh shit. Oh come on. I was like halfway. I was like more than halfway through the game.
Is there a save I can pull somewhere? It's like an auto save thing. Is there an auto save that like
is in sections or something? Speed run it. Shit. That's so sad. That's so sad. Oh my god. Let me
see if I can speed run it. Fuck. That sucks. That sucks so bad. What the fuck? Okay. What happened?
I'm so. I okay. I understand the game. I'm just going to go fast and I'm going to get it done.
Go watch somebody's let's play. You can do it. See you in 20 minutes. No soft locks.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. What? It's a tweet. Someone tell Jerma I can tell them how to fix their save.
How do I do it? How do I do it? How do I do it? That's so funny. How do I fix my save? The dev
literally just tweeted this. All right. I'm going to refresh the dev's twitter and see if he gives
me a solution. It's in the game files. It's too late. Replace the newest auto save with a previous
one. Okay. Is it not too late? Did I? I didn't just do it. I didn't just fuck it up. Did I?
What did he say? He's so silly. Quick. He's reading. He's watching your tweets. Go. Oh shit.
He's playing it. Thank. Okay. All right. How do I do it? Jerma soft locking himself through the game
halfway is probably on brand. Okay. New tweet, new tweet. What do we got? Hold on Jerma. I'm typing a
solution. All right. He can DM them all. Yeah. You DM one of the mods. They'll help. Close the game.
I'm just going to close the game, right? Okay. Closing the game tech support. All right. Game is
closed. Okay. What do we do? What do I do? What should I do from here? Hold on, dude. I'm typing.
Okay. All right. All right. He said, I'm typing, laughing my ass off. That was a big one. Let me
see if I can get a huge one and catch it. The fan. Okay. I've got a fan going back here. That's
fucking this up. This fan is blowing the bubbles. I need to turn the fan off because it's too much
circulation of the air. Okay. Here we go. Oh, that went in my mouth. Fuck you. Got a new tweet.
The mod. Okay. VR Josh just said, LOL, did anyone get a DM of the jacket? No. Nope. Is he going to
tweet it? No, no, no. He's probably going to tweet out the solution. He's typing. What if he just
doesn't tweet ever again? What if he's just fucking with it and he just like, it's like,
oh yeah, I got you man. It just doesn't do it. We said it for like 40 minutes. Don't try this
on. God damn it. Tweet. Open the save folder in the install and open the progress file. Find the
data block called fake underscore sub and change the coordinates to something safe that I'm trying
to figure out. What? What? Open. Is this fake? It's making, is this a joke? He's making it up.
It's a joke. Okay. Open the save folder in the install. Okay. Let me do this right now.
Save folder in the install. So is it like this, like the steam folder, right? Like steam. Okay.
It's like steam, steam apps, right? I'm desperately trying to open the project to
figure out what the closest safe coordinates would be. Also, I don't know any of the mods
to DM. LOL. I never use Twitch. This is, I love it. This is fucking hilarious.
All right. So let me, it's in steam, like steam apps, right? Steam, steam apps, steam. Okay.
Steam, steam apps, program files, steam apps. Okay. All right. It's in steam, steam apps,
and then iron lung, right? Yep. Okay. Iron lung. Okay. Save. Progress. Open this with a text
editor, right? Notepad. All right. I got it. So I've got coordinates. Find the data block called
quote fake sub, fake sub, teleport true, no monster, fake sub. Okay. Fake underscore sub
and change the coordinates X and Y to something else. Oh shit. Okay. Where was I? I was 550
six. All right. I got it. How about like five, like 30, like three, like three, like 70 is 380.
What was it on the bud? Okay. I'm going to try five 30. Oh fuck. Oops. Okay. What should I,
what's like a safe thing to do right there? Okay. All right. All right. X I'm going to do five,
like 545. Y is Y is currently minus two. Z is 400. Solve for X. Fuck. New tweet. We got a new
tweet. What does it say? Oh, I gotta go like wash my mouth. 15 minutes ago, you said you will never
have to find a solution to X and Y. And here we are. I, but this is not, that's not even legit
though. What you're describing it. New tweet. This isn't, this is a completely, this is a complete
anomaly. Leave Y alone. I beg you. You need to leave Y alone. Oh shit. Okay. Try X five 60,
Y three 30. New tweet. No, wait. Z three 30. Oh, dev. Looks like you're having a little bit
trouble with geometry. Aren't you? Looks like the dev is having a little bit of trouble with
geometry. Just like, I'm, I'm dev. When was the last time you were in fucking high school?
When was I, I am going to get so validated right now. When was the last time? How, how,
when was the last time you were in high school? Bingo. Right. I keep this, this is perfect.
All right. X five 60, like five 60 with no decimal, just five 60, like 0.5 60.0 and Z three 30.
Okay. Three 30.0 done save. I'm opening the game right now. I suck at math.
I suck at math. I am in my thirties. I haven't had to do this for years. Go look at the tweet
right now. I'm going to fucking, I'm framing this. I'm literally going to frame that tweet
from dusk dev. Thank you so much. I'm so glad this happened. I'm so glad this happened.
Unbelievable. I'm going to frame that tweet. Okay. Let's go. Here we go. Are you ready?
Thank you so much. Oh, it worked. Oh yes. This is for like babies, right? Like this,
I'm not going to get like, please recycle where facilities exist. Do not drink bubble solution.
Avoid contact with eyes. If contact occurs, rinse with water immediately. No, I'm fine. Non-toxic
no dyes. Yeah, I'm fine. Non-toxic no dyes. I'm fine. Yeah, we're good. This is, I'm so glad.
It's just soap. I know I'm whatever. I spit it out. I put like a tiny bit right here.
So where I'm five 60, three 30, five 60, which is like right here. Three 30, which is like right
here. So I just have to go up here. Oh, dev hero. Yeah. Okay. Let me tell you something right now.
I like love, I love dusk dev games. I ain't just going to leave. No, I'm not going to play. Oh yeah.
I'm just going to go into Glover. No way. No way. No chance. I have 61, 395. So I'm like right here.
Okay. So pull it this way. So the dusk Twitter, go dust dev Twitter, go like open it right now.
He didn't tell anybody what he was doing. He's writing, try five 60, three 30. No, no, no.
Z three 30. Oh, I beg, leave me alone. I beg you. I forgot how to do math.
Somebody replied and said, are you defusing a fucking bomb? People don't know what he's talking
about. He just looks unhinged. That's so funny. Are you diffusing a bomb? I mean, we're in the
tunnel. How come you can't just have a normal play through of a game? I don't know, dude.
I feel like there's been a few Mario sunshine was a normal play through. That was a normal play
through. What happened with that one? That was fine. Okay. I think I'm through five, four 30,
five 73, four 30, five 73. I think if I spit on that, it would blow level almost. It looked like
it was really glossy. It could have been five 73, we're 28. So I'm just going to go up. I'm
right there. I'm through. Oh, geometry. I'm so fucking happy. I'm in my thirties. I haven't
done it in a lot. Yeah, I know, man. I know. And I, I'm telling you, I feel so good right now.
I feel great. I'm so happy that happened. Okay. Five 75, four 76. What was that? Five 75,
four 70. I'm like right here. So this thing is at six 23, five 20. So I got to start pulling it this
way. All right. Worms are six 23, five 20 incoming. What was that? That was like I was about to do it,
but I realized it was like not really called for 63. Whoa. It's another like dinosaur skeleton.
It's a dinosaur skeleton. I need to back up. Turn to the left. I think I'm too close. That should
be it, right? No, six 23, five 20, 63. All right. That's as close as it's going to get, man. 63.
All right. Got it. It's like another dinosaur bone. So how do I get up here? This way and up.
This is not on the map. Like, can I go this way? It looks like maybe I could. All right. I'm going
to go this way. So I just got to turn. I just have to turn. My mouth is like Sophie. I'll be right back.
Give me one second. All right. I'm back. I'm better. I'm better. Very cool. Let's go. Both
headphones have to go in. I feel better. Yeah. Now try that at home. Don't fucking do what I did. I
was trying to catch like a bubble on my like lips and like blow it back out. Didn't work. Don't do
that. Unless you're a certified professional clown like me. Well, professional in like quotes. Like I
give myself that term. All right. All right. Let's go. So where am I? I need to go just left.
I don't want to crash. He sounds kind of sad. Is he okay? Bro, I'm fine. I just ate a bunch of like
KFC. I'm good. Ah, I'd fuck an extra crispy bucket. He looks like a greasy butt. I don't care.
Whatever. All right. Five, six, five, six, one, five, 10, five, 61. So I got to go kind of left.
All right. What am I looking for? I'm looking for like four, like 350 X while staying at about 500.
Don't. Don't. Where even am I? What's going on here? I'm really close to what wall am I close to?
43514. 430. There's no wall here. What happens? Am I going to die? Okay. This bubble solution all
over my keyboard and it's like I'm sliding around it. I think I'm playing Glover with a controller.
It's soap. It's fine. It's literally soap. Like it's like I can. I got to clean the keyboard anyways.
It's probably in a while. The dev said they're going to patch the bug that I just saw in the
next update. It's fast. It's not. It's all right. Okay. Three. What am I looking for?
300 or like 350 500. All right. Keep going. Is this a wall? It's a tree. Okay. Watch out for trees.
What the? How do I get what? Five 358 519 358 519. Can I go up here? Can I actually go this way? 358
595. All right. I'm just going to go. I think I can go to the right. Can I? Am I? Is this like
not what I'm supposed to be doing? Oh shit. What is that? You're a beta male. Okay. Well,
um, correct me if I'm wrong, but a beta male is a higher version than alpha male. Beta would be
0.1. Alpha would be 0.01. So you think I fucking care? So what I get to be like a bigger, like a
more like a better version, a more complete version, not a beta male. Yeah. Yeah. You think
that's a beta? Okay. I don't know what drugs you're taking. Just wait till I get to. Yeah. Wait till
I get to release 1.0 man. All right. I think I'm through 367 619, three, wait, 619. So I'm like
right here. Let's just go up. I want Jim bro. Jerma back. Jim bro. Jerma was 10 fucking years
ago. It's never coming back. So I just got to go straight up here. This is going to be so hard to
navigate. Oh my God. So just 325 741 325 741. You just got unfazed by the fire. I mean, I saw the,
I almost said extinguisher, like fucking the pyro. I saw the extinguisher over there. So I knew it was
going to probably happen eventually. What is the baseball stream? By the way, you'll find out the
baseball stream. That's it. 741 325. What's the angle? 18. That's definitely going to get removed.
That's going to get removed from a moderator, but it was fucking crazy. Oh my God. It's a big crab
that got auto-modded. I know. I know. I know. I, but I don't get it. It was fucking weird.
It got auto-modded. All right. Whatever it was, it got auto-modded. That's all you need to know.
It was whatever. What the fuck is that? Can I get a better view?
We have to know. I have to know. What was it? Yeah. Yes. In the mod chat. That's what it was.
That's what it was. I don't, I'm not going to encourage this behavior, but I'm going to tell
you something right now. Don't fucking, this is not to be encouraged, but it was just like,
what the fuck, man? Somebody asked what the baseball stream is. And I said, whatever. And
then like, it was been like five minutes. I've been like at least five minutes.
Somebody like added that person, I think, and said he's going to shove an entire baseball up his ass
on stream. And this shit got grabbed immediately. And I read it because it's like auto-mod doesn't
delete it. It was like 20 seconds. I know. But still like, what the fuck are you talking about?
This is that, that behavior is not to be encouraged by the way. I'm just saying.
All right. So do I go left or right? I'm going to say left. So I got to go down and then right.
I don't want to encourage that kind of behavior, but like that's, it's his final stream. It's not
my, what, this person's name too. Yeah. What the fuck? The person's name was, all right, whatever.
We don't need to say the person's name because I don't, I don't want to, you can find it. I don't
know. The name was Ball Fondler. Okay. Okay. Do you want me to tell you more? Cause like, I could
tell you more. Don't encourage that behavior. That person's probably, that person's probably
timed out for like a half an hour. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
Okay. Let's see what we have to go down here. Down to at least three 50, three 50 with a side
of the one 82 free 17, six 93, six 93. I'm like right here. I'm doing the TTS boys chop. I'm doing
the TTS tick-tock voice chop up. It's like the little kid way to say shut up. Come on. Streamer
is actively making modding a challenge. My mods are going to fucking revolt. I think six 60. All
right. Keep going and then bang a kind of thing. A left. Did you watch Morbius? No dude. Why would
I, you could have told me that Morbius went straight to DVD and I would be like, okay, I don't like
so like Morbius is like the Aladdin three of the Marvel universe. I don't, what do you want me to
say? I don't, I didn't, I didn't see it. One 80. Okay. Where am I? Morbius got $1.3 billion at the
box office. I know it did not. What? How he 77 60. I'm like right here. I got to pull it up a little.
There's something behind me. What's behind me? Do you hear that? I don't see anything. All right.
Do I need to go? Where am I? Six to 68, 623, 68. I'm like right here. 623 here. I got to go up and
left. Are you going to scream your Morbius reaction review at some point? Okay. What is this? Because
it's like, Oh, okay. I got to go that way. Oh shit. All right. Where am I? All right. I got it. I got
it. I'm in, I'm in 258, 658. I'm like right here. So I got to go left in a, at, at about
at about like one 80 or so. I got to take a left. I'm going to stream today. I want to drink alcohol
in the later hours. I mean, I'm going to do this. We're going to go to Glover and then if Glover
sucks, we're going to play another game. Okay. I got to go left. 201, six 80, six, no, six 60,
201, six. Okay. I'm like right here. So I'm about to hit this wall. So I got to go left. Hey,
what's going on? What the fuck is that? I got it. There's one more. It's the leak. What leak?
Am I under water? I'm not, I'm not under water right now. I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm
going. Is this just chasing me? Is it chasing me? All right. Two 76, six 35, two 76. I'm like
six 35. Am I out? Two 76, six 35. Okay. Keep going. Now this way. You've hit something. He's 40.
Let him ask questions. I teleported. Three 10, six 44. Wait, what? What are you talking about?
Oh, teleported. Oh, okay. So I just got to go all the way to right. They changed the coordinates.
That's fucked up. This game's fucked up. All right. For X, I'm looking for,
I'm looking for like 450. I got a long way to go. He's fucked up. This game's crazy. Okay.
Stop pretending. This is going to be a pain in the ass. All right. So I'm at 445 and I'm 700.
So I'm right here. I'm like right here. I just got to go kind of hold this way.
Just navigate through here. Holy shit. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
What the fuck are you talking about, dude? Okay. Um, oh my God. Okay. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. 492, six 89. I'm like right here. Just keep going. Right. Just keep going.
And then I'm going to go up at around five, like 40. That was like a dragon. All right. Five 40,
six 90, five 40, six 90. I'm like right here. Hey, let me go. And then once I hit about seven
55, okay. What the fuck? Seven 55, five 80, seven 50, five 80, seven 50. Right after I freeze it.
Oh, thank God. It's just wood. Six 11, seven 50, six 10, seven 50, six 10, seven. Okay. So I'm
like right here. So I gotta go like this. God damn it. Is it behind me? Why is it blinking faster
when I go this way? Dude, why is it doing that? Six 30, seven 75, six 30, like right here. Seven
75. I'm like right here. Six 50, seven 80. Okay. Keep going. Okay. All right. Seven. All right.
Almost at 800 and almost 680. All right. I'm going through 670, 680, 800, 680, 800. All right. It's
just right ahead. Whatever it is. What's the angle? 828, 295, six. Okay. Don't move. 295. What is it
again? 828. I started to like look this way and this eye, this eye. I went like, I went reverse
cross. I went frog eye for a second. I went like this. I was like, I want to be like,
am I in the right spot? And it came out. I saw like this and this at the same time.
The expedition only raised more questions than answers. Satellite images showed pieces of the
SM-13 scattered all over the bottom of the ocean trench as though it had been torn apart by some
huge beast. The wreckage cannot be reached at this time. No photographs have been recovered.
The stars shine pale as bones. The moon is a lifeless corpse. It's ocean a gaping wound.
The universe, what's left of it is dying, but somewhere in the void, there must be hope.
Frog eyed. That was fucking crazy. Yeah. I didn't think it was going to, I was like about to take
the picture. I'm like, oh, is this right? It's like I, I blinked. I heard the sound and my like right
eye got to see it. It's almost like I wasn't paying attention to the horror movie because I was like,
ah, this is a horror movie. Yeah. Whatever. It's like you take a bite of your popcorn
and then you hear and it's like something happened. I'll show it here. Imagine if I was
at the movie theater and had a bowl of popcorn. Perfect. All right. So check this out.
I was looking at my phone or something and I heard the sound and then saw it.
Look at that reaction time, man. Like Jesus look over.
Oh, we're going to go slower. Man. That's these Mike and I sure are delicious.
I'm not even looking at the fucking screen.
Not even fucking paying attention. Oh, it's always like, I was like sympathy screaming,
right? Like, cause other people in the audience is screaming. Everybody else is yelling. So like,
oh my God, something must be happening that I need to be aware of. Okay. Like imagine here,
this is like what happens. You hear like, oh, I got to react. Something horrible happened.
Okay. That was iron lung. That was fun. That was cool. I've come to clean about something.
I could not watch your entire Pokemon snap. Vaughn, you kept using the item throwing joystick to move
the guy. I didn't play that. Delete that. Oh, that was fun. So now we're going to move on.
That was iron lung. That game was supposed to be like a 45 minute experience and I made it like
three hours. Well, no, it's two hours. To be fair though, I had a, I had a glitch.
There was a glitch. I had to like 15 to 20 minutes. We had to kind of figure that out.
I had soap in my mouth. I had to get rid of it. So now we're going to play Glover.
Glover for the N64. It was ported to Steam. And I have to be very honest with you. If I'm,
we're going to have to gauge how people like this and the same rules that strawberry magic had apply
to the, the glove buddies. There's a new tweet. What's it say? Oh, Jerma's biggest jump scare.
I fixed the bundle and I fixed a Jerma's stream. Anything more I need to fix tonight?
Hold on. Wait a minute. You get iron lung plus dusk plus dusk 82. How much is that?
Is it bundle on Steam? How much is it? I got to show this. How much is the bundle? 30 bucks,
20 bucks. That's pretty sick. 20, 30. I mean, that was cool. Said like one of your friends
down and be like, yeah, I'll play this and watch them scream at the end and look at their popcorn
and then, um, like sympathy yell because everybody else is. All right, give me one
second. I'm going to put Glover up. Okay. Glover incoming.