Hello, and welcome to the easy bake oven stream. I don't can you hear me? Can you guys hear me?
We're just at the beach having a good time. Wait, hold on. I can't see anything. All right
So when I was setting this up, am I even fucking live? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
I've got this elaborate setup. Hold on. Am I live? Am I even fucking live? I better be. I am!
All right, all right, all right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. How does it sound? All right, go to chat only. Oh fuck
I can't go that way. I don't I can't get the chat to work. This is a fucking disaster
Disaster I got my tools ready as you see in front of you. I can't fucking believe I'm doing this stream
Yeah, I paid for studio time to be in this spot right now to do this stream
We'll be here tomorrow to do I still can't see what you guys saying. Is it connected? What the fuck? Hold on get
In a few minutes
There we go now can see you can see you
Scary
Your mic sucks. Well, um, I lost I lost the other mic and this is the if you want to know this this truth
This is this is the microphone from if you would believe it the lifeline stream. This is the lifeline microphone
It's for the PlayStation 2
I had a panic moment here like two or three hours ago where I was like
What happened to the mic that I actually always use? Where is it do a sexy pose?
Alright, that wasn't alright. Listen to me. This is important. Is it how is it crusty?
Is it like really crusty? I don't matter is it hold on
What if I move it a little bit? Is it how crusty is it move it away from my mouth?
How's that? Is that better? Is it a little bit better? Can that can now can you hear me? Do we sound better now?
All right. Okay. Excellent. It is actually better
Yeah, it's cuz I'm speaking out directly out this way and it looks like I'm on fucking QVC
Presenting the easy vague of them, which I'm not by the way, this is I gotta make this really really clear
This is really important
They have nothing to do with this. I know it's presented in a way like they would
They have nothing to do with this. This is not I know it looks like an ad stream, but I swear to God
This is not an ad stream
This is just something that we came up with this thing hot. Okay, it is I'm like afraid of this
Have we talked about that yet?
How like I'm actually kind of terrified of this fucking thing because the old easy baked oven had a window here
Well, you could see what the fuck was going on now this new one
This is like the new age one. They've just wait did I peel the plastic off this? No, that's supposed to stay on there
Okay, the old one had a window that you could look through but this one just
Fucking it. How are you supposed to know when the food is done?
You just stuff it in here and wait like five minutes and then pull it out
How are you supposed to know because those of you guys that are like me whenever I use a real oven
I have to go up to the oven turn the oven light on and just sit there and watch
Because I don't trust anything. I don't trust myself
I don't trust the oven there if it's like 400 degrees
You have to do a pizza for like 20 minutes that oven light has to be on at all times
And I have to fucking is it burnt is it burnt is it no no is it burnt is it burnt?
So I can't really do that with this. What a loser. I mean, that's what I do. I don't I don't cook
Okay, this is gonna this first cooking stream I've ever done. So which one of these do you want to start with?
We have what do we even have now?
I'll show them into the camera so you can see how delicious that you want to do pretzel. Hold on
Well, we're gonna do them all. Here's the pizza. That's pizza. This has egg wash
Adult supervision required how do I I don't I don't see how an eight-year-old can do this eight plus
I don't I don't think I I don't think I was able to even leave the house before I was a let alone use an
Oven eight plus. All right, so you should I start might as well start with the pizza. I got my shit ready
This I got my water bowl just in case I get thirsty
I was thinking about doing a joke when this first started where I was gonna like oh I'm thirsty and do a dog
Lapping up out of the bowl joke, but then I was like, no, that's fucked up. I don't think I want to do that
I was gonna be like, oh nice water, but then I would fucking ruin the day
I would just it's just too early for that. It's it's only been like ten minutes. That's why wait
This is an adults only stream. Oh shit. That's right
Mature audience thing is on why
Mature easy bake oven stream that doesn't make any sense. I bought stained
I mean, I'm gonna say the F word a few times. All right, let's get this open
I'm gonna do the pizza first. Is this ready? So it goes in and then out. All right, so let me
Do I need to have like an egg? I didn't bring anything else nice unboxing video for all of you that will care about it
Porn stream. Oh, I need an egg. Do I need an egg? I don't think I do
Do I actually need a fucking egg? By the way, I'm not gonna eat any of this
I just wanted to make that really clear with you guys. I'm not eating any of this easy big garlic garlic herb cheese mix
Oh my god, it's in like a bag
By the way, they have nothing to do with this stream. Like if I talk about how gross this is
I just just my my opinions on the product. Okay, this is my opinions on their product. That's it
This is my opinions on the product. Nobody had any fucking note that the Hasbro had nothing to do with this
Can you see me? This is my opinions on the product. That's it. Okay, here we go
easy bake marinara mix
egg wash
Pizza dough with pizza dough mix. Okay, I'm gonna I don't think I'm capable of doing this. Where's the instructions?
I got my bowls. Hold on. This is all powdered and this is gonna turn into a pizza with that's what I'm understanding
I feel like I'm doing a presentation at a county fair with the microphone and that there's the easy bake oven as you can see
It's all powdered. So your children are gonna love it. Yeah, and there's like one person in the audience
There's like
200 empty seats
I'm telling you your kids are gonna love this and then they got that's that one guy comes up and buys it and he
The guy walked back to his car
We could fucking sad because he's got like 60 of these in his trunk and he only got rid of one poor guy
Okay cheese pizza
Pre-heat the easy bake oven for 20 minutes, which I've done before the stream turned on spray baking pan with cooking spray. I
Don't have any cooking spray guys, it's like a lick it can I just like drag my tongue up and down this oh
No, I don't have any oil. Can I just like use my like forehead? Oh
Fuck I didn't know I was gonna need oil. Oh, it did said it didn't need that said everything's in the package. It didn't say it
It's all right. We're gonna this might be a disaster. I'm gonna lick it. No, I'm not that's disgusting
All right, here we go. It'll just be a little crusty
I'll just have to like I'll just have to like fucking get up there and like
It'll be fine this thing this thing just started ticking it was like
It's like a bomb. No, what the fuck is that? That it was ticking. I don't have any butter
I'm in like I'm in a studio right now. I didn't bring any butter. Alright, let's start
Let's make the sauce pour one marinara sauce mix and one and a half teaspoons. This is a teaspoon
What is this? What is this? Is this a teaspoon or is this a tablespoon by the way?
Why can't they just be one two, three four or five? Why does that tablespoon teaspoon a pinch a dash a
Tap none of just one two, three, four or five
Why does it have to be like that just why I don't understand why teaspoon and tablespoon
Tablespoon should be two teaspoons should be one or zero. All right marinara saw. Where's that marinara's mix artificially flavored?
Oh, you really grandma didn't make this. Are you sure maybe she did? Okay
Pour one and a half pour the marinara sauce mix into a bucket. I'm gonna put it in here
Can you see what I'm doing here? All right, let's take a look. Okay in there. It looks
Looks like fun dip. Don't knock that over. All right strawberry fun strawberry mint fun dip. All right, there it is
Oh, that's a smell that I've not smelled in my life
Okay, so then pour one and a half teaspoons of water into into bowl stir the mixture with a spoon and set it aside for later
Okay, so here's one why does it have to be this hard kind of fucking spoon is flat
Alright, don't freak out. What the what's a magic trick? This is a magic trick. Whatever. I don't care one
Okay, that's one and a half. I think okay. Let's stir it up. You ready
Okay, you guys and you guys you guys doing it at home. I feel like it needs to be more than that
I need more water than this. Can you guys like hear this sounds actually doesn't even look that bad
I need more water but not that much because I don't want to be too runny. All right, I go like that
Little bit more just one more. There we go. Okay, good. Stop. Stop. Stop. I'm not gonna fucking spill it
All right. That's a good consistency. How is this gonna make a pizza? This is one
This is one spoonful of baby food. This is not a where's the pizza? This is gonna go on a pizza
How how big is this pizza? Okay. Well, this seems to be that's mixed up pretty well
No, no, no, no, no do not drop that in here. Oh can't I can't do that. That looks pretty good, right?
Would you say powdered pizza? That's what the yeah, I know guys if you ever had what is how's my hair?
I got I had a quarantine haircut. Kim gave one to me
Have you guys have had the Lunchables pizza? It's disgusting. I know remember that lunchables has nothing to do with this dream
I just give my opinions on some products. These are my personal opinions. They don't have nothing to do with this dream
I think they're gross and
This is kind of what it is. It's just looks like this. All right, this is gonna start to solidify
Okay, okay now make the cheese pour one garlic herb cheese mix and water into a bowl and stir the mix with a spoon and
Set it aside for later. Oh shit. I gotta get some more bowls. I have like five bowls. All right set that aside
We don't need that right now. Okay, make the cheese one garlap garlet the ferv. I can't even read garlic herb cheese
No, don't pour it into here. Oh, this is gonna be so bad
You guys don't understand the the bowls just keep increasing in size. This is the smallest bowl
I have the next one up is like this big
It's gonna be just like spread like a thin layer on the edges of it is it's gonna be bad use a sink
I'm not gonna make this into sink. No, this is this is like clean water and I'm not I'm not gonna make this in the sink
How am I supposed to get all this equipment into the sink? How am I supposed to do that? Use the bathtub?
No, I'm here we go garlic herb cheese mix and then just a little bit of water, right?
Okay, I gotta I gotta wipe that off. Wait, wait, did you see my jaw my jaw?
I just like snapped I pogged so hard. I took broke my jaw. What the fuck? Okay, this is what you're supposed to use
All right. All right garlic herb cheese mix
Cocaine you know what I'll be honest with you. I gotta be completely real here
This smells like the shit that they sprinkle on the Pizza Hut pizza and I kind of like it
I actually don't even think I want to I don't think I want to add water to this
I kind of think I want to keep it like this, right?
Why would I want to add water to this is it gonna turn is it gonna turn?
Okay, hold on
Is it gonna turn orange is that'll turn me off forever if it turns orange when how much water do I need?
Half one and a half teaspoons of water. Okay, I'm just gonna look this is I this there's only so much sauce
There's such a little amount of sauce that I don't want to waste it all and I don't want to eat it
I don't want I don't want to go like this. Mmm, cuz I don't I'll probably throw up by the way
And just in case I throw up. I just want everyone to know
I've got a fucking trash bag over here. So I just like put my head in the trash bag puke in here
That's the goal and it'll work
I'm just gonna like wrap it up and puke it off camera and like turn mute the microphone. Oh my god
Don't say puke. Okay, one and a half teaspoons. We're gonna do it slowly. This is not enough water
Oh, wait a minute. This is like turning into like blue cheese. Oh
That's cottage cheese. Don't say cottage cheese. Don't say cottage cheese
I think it's supposed to look like this. It's supposed to be like pretend to be cheese, right?
This is gonna be sprinkled on top. This thing's gonna burn. I think is this gonna light on fire
No, why would this thing is made for eight-year-olds? Why would it be like that? Okay, this is good. That looks pretty good
Right. What do you guys think scrambled eggs like the okay scrambled eggs
But the very end of the scrambled eggs after you scramble the fuck out of them and you're done the shit
That's left like in the pan. That's all around the sides and shit. Don't why am I saying this? Okay
Now what make the cheese make the glaze
Pour one egg wash mix and two tablespoons of water into a bowl stir the mixture with a spoon and set it aside
How much bullshit am I gonna have to fucking to use all this just for this tiny little like iPhone case?
Hold on get that out of the way. I'm gonna have to fucking wipe that down
All right. Next is the is the glaze egg wash. I gotta get the balls
Just are gonna keep getting more and more comically oversized
I'm the only fucking idiot on earth that gets a children's toy
And gets bulls designed to make food for like 10 people keep getting bigger burn out of room
All right, I don't need the lids then he's gonna go rotten or what?
How come I do an egg wash? Oh, I gotta make sure these eggs stay fresh
I got it. All right clean as you clean as you go, right clean as you go
I'm not gonna make a fucking mess. You know, I mean clean as you go
my puke bag
And the best thing about this is like if I want to spit something up if I want to like spit out what I have
Like I said, I just I just wrap my head around this
You don't even know what happened and I just like let it feel like just worm out of my mouth
You won't even know what happened
Like I can literally just go like that and just go and you won't even know what's next egg wash
Egg wash and two tablespoons of water. This is egg wash, right? This is yellow
I hate the smell of eggs like a raw egg is
Enough to drive me crazy
Do you guys hate that too us of raw egg has a very distinct gross smell and I don't I don't like it
So what I was saying before, you know
When like when I was setting this all up and I was like, you know
Getting the cameras ready and getting like getting you know
Going to the beach and getting to the fucking beach
I was just like looking at the table and over the other setup and everything
I just said kind of under my breath. What the fuck am I doing this eating sand?
It does kind of look like sand. All right, I got a this is just broke
It's just fucking broke and it just broke. How am I supposed to I'm just gonna use my hands
It actually just broke it actually did look at look at this. It's a that's like a clean weird break
Can I put just push it back together? Okay. No, that's all right. I gotta get this
Okay, we're almost at the part where I make the dough get this out of my way
I need to like where's my where's my towels? Thank you
You know, I got to fill another one of these with water and just cuz this is not gonna work
Actually, it kind of is. Yeah, it's good. It's a really fucking matter. I should have got like ten to these tools
Somebody said this is cursed. Why it's it's an easy bake oven. What's wrong with this? What is it? Nothing wrong
It's contaminated it's not
Contaminated guys all this came from the same fucking factory. What do you mean contaminated?
This all came from the same conveyor belt in between in between like pushing out glue. This is the same factory
This is my opinion. There's a joke
I just want to make sure that you know that Hasbro had nothing to do with this and this is me making up a satire on
What could possibly be going on in a weird factory?
There's nothing to do with they'd have nothing to do with this and I have nothing to do with them
These are just my comedic opinions on things that aren't even real to joke and it's the satire
It's a parody of moment. Okay, what do I do water? How much water two tablespoons of water?
This is actually like fun though. Can I be honest? Is that too much water? What is this supposed to be?
What cut what kind of what do you do? What Pete's what do you do with pizza? This is what is this?
How is this a pizza? This is this is like dog puke
This is not I have to use the spoon. I know just get rid of the handle
Just get rid of the I get rid of the handle whatever if this still works. It's just annoying. Okay, what's what is that?
What's the FDA or the what FTC say about food being out for how long there's 20 minutes, right?
They use it like food can be sitting out before it starts to be like poison. What is it? Somebody knows it
That's this is this is not I don't like that. This is just to like make the dough look like it's cooked two minutes
I can't believe that thing just broke in my hand. That's unbelievable. Best part about this is because there's so little stuff
I've realistically just have to like wipe
Wipe wipe wipe and then just like to be ready for the next one because this is barely anything
All right, make them now. It's time to make the pizza. We need one pizza dough and one
Nothing like in there, right? Okay, we need one pizza dough mix and one tablespoon of water
There are two pizza dough mix is why spit spit you want me to spit in this no
I'm not spitting in this are you guys fucking crazy? Why are there two? Why are there two of these? Okay ports?
I'm whatever. I don't know why there's two you make two pizzas spit in it. I'm not gonna spit in this bowl
I'm not even I think I think that's like not even allowed on twitch. Can you spit on twitch is spitting allowed on twitch?
Can I like spit is that allowed?
Spit switch. Am I gonna get like banned for like spitting in this bowl? Oh water
I've been looking no, that's not a good transition there. Okay. Okay. I'm almost ready
How long does it take to cook six pizzas six split the dough into six pieces and what a small balls
How am I supposed to me? How do you what do you mean? Are they supposed to be like bagel bites? What is the oh?
Shit, they're supposed to be little bagel bites. I thought it was gonna be like a like a like a I don't know
I don't like like it's like a Sicilian style like a like a square or something. I don't know. Okay, let's go
This I have to start using my hands. Oh boy, how much?
One tablespoon of water that's way more than a tablespoon shit. It's okay. Okay use your hands
Stir and press the mixture together until you get dough with my hands. Where's that shitty little thing? This is not pizza dough
How is this pizza dough? It's ruined. I need more water. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
There's a hair in this. I can't use this anymore. I have to go to a new one
There's hair in here. Look, there's like a speck of something in there. Can you guys see in there?
Do you see the one speck of some kind of foreign debris? I can't even use this now. I hate that shit
I hate it. Okay, that's enough water. Put this book put this back down
Why did I have to do the complicated one first? This is definitely like the most complicated one
Why couldn't I just dump the brownie packet into the fucking ground and then just stir it up with my finger and put it in there?
That's what the next one's gonna be. This is not this is not pizza. This is not pizza dough. This is gonna be
Like crackers. This is the bottom of the Lay's potato chip bag
This is not this is the shit that you like dump out because it's not even edible
Yeah, and you think you get all cute you dump the fucking bag up and it goes half in here and like
75% go around and you crunch it it hits the floor and you like cut all around your teeth
I need more do I need more water somebody help him what use my hands
I'm not putting my fucking hands in this disgusting. I have to do I have to use my hands
I have to knead the dough. Okay, hold on. I
Okay, that thing started making weird noise
Where do I put this um
That's this just dough. Hold on. I need a like this, right? You go like like stand up for this
Why don't I just make one big pizza? Why do I have to make six more?
I need to you didn't have to do it. Just do it somebody somebody call OSHA. He didn't wash his hands
Okay, this is as good as it's gonna get like that. Okay. How are you supposed to make six?
This you don't make six out of this this is one this is smaller
I don't have to make a pizza. What does it say flatten each ball of dough?
Like a pancake and shape it into a circle. Okay, here we go. Is this too big? Holy fucking shit
Okay, but I gotta make it nice. All right, I'm doing like three
This is I feel like this is gonna bake into the pan and never come up like this is gonna be part of the pan
Okay, let's do another one. You don't have any oil. I
Didn't say I needed oil. I don't need oil. Do I use CBD oil?
I don't have CBD oil just spit on it. It's gotta be something I can butter
I do I thought it was all gonna be inside of the packages. I think it'll be alright
I think it's gonna be alright. Okay, here we go. I'll just I won't put it in there for that long go to the store. I
What do you want? Just leave the stream on well, I go to like a grocery store
Alright, how about this if this is a fucking disaster?
I'm going to like just go to a store and I'll put on like if the fucking I don't know put on like
Spongebob Squarepants OST. I'll be back unironically. Yes. Okay, here we go. Okay, I'm gonna do like two cuz this is just this is ridiculous
Take us with you. I know what taking you with me. How many fucking people are here?
I didn't they're like eleven fucking thousand people here. What are you doing here? What the hell are you doing here?
Why are you here right now? Oh my god shit. I gotta make this I gotta do this good
Then I can't just I can't believe I don't have any fucking cooking spray
Alright, I'm doing four the one thing that I fucking couldn't eat it. I didn't bring any of it
There's two packets. There's no way you make six out of this. No fucking way
In fact, how am I gonna even put like the sauce on here? This doesn't make any sense. It doesn't make any sense
I can't even fit this one on there. How small did they want you to make these? All right. Yeah. Oh, here we go
I'm ready on the next part. Oh, I ripped it in half, right use a pastry brush
To spread some glaze on top of the dough. What the eight-year-old has a pastry brush
It's it says you can use your finger. Okay, the glaze wait. This is like oil, right? Hold on
Wait, can I put this on the bottom too? This is like oil, isn't it? It's like a glaze. No, don't don't what do you mean?
No, why it's a it's like a it's like a glaze you're gonna burn it
No, am I didn't say that doesn't say could burn careful. I think that looks alright. Why would have this much glaze?
It smells
Okay, if I could like bring you here with me right now, this smells like it's like it's like it's like it's implanting me somewhere
Like I'm going somewhere right now. I'm like on a journey. I'm going to I'm going somewhere. Where am I going?
It's summertime. It's summertime. There's a hot dog vendor sausage vendor. Not hot dog toxic fumes. What? All right
Fuck. Never mind hot dog vendor sausage vendor
It's like the air the air that's coming off of the guy that makes those sausages that at the kiosk. Okay, that's good enough
This is fucking eight-year-olds. Yeah, right more like I'm just gonna wash my hands in here
I'm not gonna need the water anymore. Yeah, that makes sense. I'm gonna that's all right sausage sweat
Okay now spread the marinara sauce on top of the pizza
Be sure to save half the sauce for your second batch of pizzas. No, thanks
I think I think it's going in the trash. This trash is gonna smell so bad. Thank God
It's one of those like double ultra ones. All right, let's put the sauce on here. This is good for now
Okay, so sauce goes on top and
Can you see I did it? Right? That's what you do. You go you go middle out
What are those? What are those pastries that have like the raspberry filling in the middle?
What are those things called? You know talking about the little the cookies with the raspberry jam in the middle
That makes me want to eat those. I think this is too thick. I think that's the problem
How hot is it gonna get in there? I'm it's like freaking me out
I don't know why I feel like I'm gonna push that in there and like just like
Burger King commercial is gonna like be up the top here. I'm afraid of this. All right, that's enough sauce. That's enough sauce
That's enough sauce. That's a good amount of sauce. I think okay. I'm gonna put that in there now. Let's put the cheese on there
I think the cheese is supposed to not be solid
They're making it look like you can squeeze it out of a bag
Spoon the cheese into a plastic sandwich bag and cut a small hole in the corner squeeze out strings of cheese
Hey, hey, this is this is like they you this is like they do in the restaurants with that big glob of mozzarella
See and this is gonna spread out there. They are that I don't like a lot of cheese on my pizzas
How does that look? Can you see?
For some reason on the back of all the Ritz crackers boxes. This is what's on the back every single time
I don't know why I don't know who the fuck does that shit
I don't know who puts like sauce and like cheese and like Dorito powder on there. It's Ritz crackers
But I don't know why that they do that. All right now it's ready time to bake. All right bake for 12 minutes
12 fucking minutes. I thought this is gonna be like give 10 5
It's a twitch 12. All right. Now I gotta which way does it go in?
Okay, you go like this like this is the way it goes like that. How does it go?
I need to I need to know how this works. Look at the picture. No, it like goes in like oh, oh, yeah
The thing on top, okay, here we go
I think it's stuck in there what if I get stuck in there and I like have to pull it out of the wall
Is it in there timer timer? What time is it? I don't know ten minutes start the time
Oh, what time is it right now? I don't even have fucking watch. What time is it? Is it in? Yeah, I think so
Yeah, it's in there and then you like push it out to the cooling side timers on the front of the oven
No, that's just it. That's a picture. That's not real. How the fuck am I gonna?
Know what I can do for 12 minutes clean up my area. Wow, that sounds like a great idea. This is perfect
It's so easy to clean
So
It's been two minutes, all right, can you guys even hear me there's a timer on the front
No, the timer on the front is a picture
Don't touch anything the timer on the front. It says 330 is a photo. It is a fake picture. It's a fake photo
Oh
Damn it. Imagine if I had somebody here with like a seagull on a stick like dropping it and trying to eat shit
This is on or not on that right there is a photo it's not real
Let me just clean up
He's lying
Degrees
I was thinking about things that I might really need. Thank God. I brought this
You needed a bunch of extra shit and that's not in the box
Sorry
Say smoke when there's no smoke, you just freaked me out
Speak up. I that's why I let it clean. All right
Is that better? Can you hear me now? I'm just trying to clean up because we have another one to do
How much time has it been? I want to take it out. It scares me oven scare me. They really do
Hey extra easy bake oven. Why would I hold on to this? It's not done
Look, it's I can just I can just jam it back in it comes out this guy. This is a glorified
Bagel toaster. Okay, it just goes in and then pushes out the other side. I can even probably put
Sesame seed bagel in here. It would be perfect on the way out. It doesn't it thinks who cares. It's not raw. Okay, okay
It's gonna be raw. You're not trying hard enough
What is anything? I don't even know that what does that mean?
I'm just trying to get my area cleaned just say the same three sentences Jeremy
Well, your brains only capable of doing one thing at a time
Cook harder. You have no passion passion for easy bake ovens. How do you have a passion for an easy bake oven?
Well, I guess somebody has to have passion for somebody has to design this and make this and shit
Did you have to be you know, there's engineers that were really into this
So yeah that you would be very passionate
I would think they give you it's your job to make this like cool device that kids can
Play with it make cupcakes, which by the way can't wait to make the fucking three layered cake
Oh, I want to bring this up too
I went way overboard with the costumes for tomorrow way overboard like something like no human should have ordered and bought this many things
this I
Don't know. It's gonna tell I don't even know what to do with it. It's seriously I bought too many things
I went overboard, but I figured it off
You're not gonna maybe not gonna do it for a while probably ever again. Who knows?
Okay, let's get a little bit of water in here so I can how long is a pin time. What's my time?
Time seven minutes. All right. All right. All right. All right. Okay, I can finish this one a BRB screen
I don't have a BRB screen on this computer. It's just gonna be like a text on the screen
rancid
Lick the paper towel. Oh my god
My I can't even tell how my hair is. All right, I'm gonna check on it. I'm gonna check it
All right, I'm gonna check on it. I'm gonna check it. I'm gonna take it out
Alright, I gotta tell I gotta take it out. I gotta take it out. I have to take it out
I get my freaking out. I have to take it up. I had to take it out
No, I have one more bowl to wipe and then I have to go and get some rinse in there
No, no, chill chill chill three more minutes. No, you never do a pizza for the time that it says
It's always overdone. I
Hate the like overdone pizza. Okay looking good. Actually wouldn't even that bad to clean up almost almost ready for round two
All right. It's gonna be it's gonna be audience's choice
For what we do for round two because as you see we've got quite a selection
I'll finish that up in a minute
Okay, I'm gonna check on it. It's time
I'm checking on it. I don't like this. I'm doing it. Okay, here we go. Let's see what we get. Don't do it yet
I'm fucking it's done. It's gonna be done
Caution supervision electronic toy unplug when not you danger to prevent electric shock. Do not immerse it in water
Wipe clean with a damp cloth immerse in water like plugged in like dropping it in the water
like a
Like a toaster don't do crazy bill
Imagine dropping an easy-bake oven into the fucking bath
What are you doing? Why are you doing that?
Bill crazy. All right, and how long has it been?
imagine
Okay, it's been alright. I'm ready. Are you ready for the moment of truth ladies and gentlemen? I'm taking it out here
Wait a minute. How do I take this out? I don't have any oven mitts. I don't oh, I don't have any oven mitts
I swear to God. I don't I don't have any oven mitts. I don't have an oven mitt. I don't have any oven mitts
This has got to be oh, this is bad. This is the so this will do this will do this will do just go
Okay, this is right. This is this is a lot of protection. Let's check it a lot of protection
Did it go in is it out here? It's out. It's out. It's out. It's out. All right, I got it
ladies and gentlemen, take a look
blocking the view take a look at this delicious
mozzarella cheese
Ladies and gentlemen, take a look at this. Oh
Ladies and gentlemen, if you could take a look
No, no, no, don't all of you leave don't all of you leave stay stay say I promise take a look at this scrumptious
cheese
Pizza all right. It's the same was wait. Did I push it through to the did this cook? Is it raw?
I think I pushed it too far the first time did I push it all the way out?
Alright, I need a plate. I didn't even what the fuck is wrong with me. Did I didn't think any of this through
This is hot. No, what am I so afraid of? This is made for five-year-olds. All right. No, it's good
It's ready and I want you to do me a favor of folks and I want you to listen to that crunch
It's like it's like it's gluing to my fucking
Canines
It's like the thing is I really I really appreciate your execution here
You used that mozzarella very well
in fact so well in fact that it is bonded with the middle of my mouth and
I do like the creativity though pretending that you're a child. That's really really nice of you to do that
You know the childlike way that you cooked in the kitchen, but I will say for those reasons
Those are the two shows that I combined chopped and shark tank. That's how fast this fucking brain goes
Now get the fuck out of here. Okay, it's like seriously not even that bad
But it is and I like I don't I have to like brush my teeth. This is seriously gonna stay I
This is not coming off. Jesus Christ. I'm not gonna eat them all no. Hey, but I made this though
Well, there's why you need the cooking spray. That's
Fantastic not really though. It's fine. That's not gonna come up. We're gonna have dough on here
I have to like scrub this with a fucking knife. Yeah, I got it. I got it. It's fine
Okay, coming up next. We're gonna make some cookies or something. I don't know, huh?
What do I mean? What are we doing? Whatever this one is? Oh, this is the cake one red velvet and strawberry cakes
Look at the image. I can't I don't have access. I have no access to like a computer right now. All right
Let me go ahead and feed this to the no, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm not I'm not gonna do that you waste
I'm sorry. I'm not I'm not eating all those I took two bites and it was too good
You're wasting the you're wasting the food guys 95% of that was flour. I didn't like it
Myself is
No, I got to drink this. No, I can't I was about to just slam that
Alright, I'll be right back with some more of this fun cooking program
Okay, stop doing the fucking jokey guy and just get it over with of my teeth
I think my teeth might be stained forever
What if I had just like two black teeth up here for the rest of my life?
I imagine I'm gonna go to the dentist and tell them like that. You need your teeth fixed. Well, what happened?
Well, you know, I ate food from an easy bake oven that I undercooked. All right. All right, give me a minute
That was in my teeth and no wonder it like it's not coming out of this either
I have to run this through a dishwasher like four times and plug the oven. Why why it's fine
It's if the things meant to be turned on and it's gonna be preheated
This hot. All right, this is
We start with you. It's gonna take equal amount of time to clean these bowls to be ready cuz I
At some point you have to say who cares and like some of your brownies gonna taste like cheese. I
Can't hear him. Hello. This one's good. This was right
Clean, right?
Be right now I'm not even here next up this one almost ready
Okay, I gotta really conserve these
Where is he? What are you talking about?
I'm right here. You know 2020 is always hindsight, right?
But I should have done this outside and just had like a hose somewhere that I could just spray into all this stuff and
To be ready to go
Okay
This is ready for round two done
this one almost I
Can't see him. I'm right here. What are you talking about?
You are outside. I'm pretend outside
All right, at some point I'm gonna have to just kind of let this thing
Like it ain't gonna happen because and I'm gonna have to just use another bowl because I have another fresh one right there
No, it's coming up it's good it's gonna take a minute see the real smart person thing to do
Like have somebody hired
To have two bowl sets and one person's cleaning the bowls while I'm doing set number two. I
Need a fucking goddamn assistant what stop wiping us. Oh
There we go, sorry about that
This stuff is fucking acid. It's still coming up
Why it's like this?
Am I wiping off the dye on the bowl or is this still the sauce? Holy shit, that's loud
Gmod Mike
All right. I can go up there and I can turn it down and I'm gonna go do that. This is almost ready
So what am I making? You guys have seen what's up there? We got pretzels. I'm not making the pretzels right now
I don't want any more disgusting smelly like savory food that'll I'll gag
We got what do we got this brown? Yeah, there's brownies there. I actually I would eat the brownies
Real food is gross when it comes to toys. Okay, real food is disgusting
It nobody wants to eat like real food coming out of something like this
Nobody does but like candy and the cookies and stuff. That's fine
It's it's it's no nobody wants to eat like a fucking hot dog in an oven like this
guys sugar flour
Salt and baking soda is like what a cookie is made out of right?
But like if there was like hamburgers in here, I wouldn't want like powdered hamburger meat
I don't want to eat like powdered cheese. I don't eat like powdered marinara sauce
This other thing is a powdered tomato, okay, no such thing to make a brownie. It's just like chocolate powder
Sugar eggs salt. It's I'm not you know, it's not powdered tomatoes like that shit was okay
This is good to go. All right, that one's ready one more and we're done
Actually, I'm gonna take a second to just get this water cleared out and then we can keep going
I'd be yeah, I don't need like this one. This this was the most complicated one. I
Ain't spending 20 minutes cleaning that just get a new one forehead
Just get a new one. This is not the garbage bowl
Good point, but all pans are gonna have some like decay on them
You know what I mean? Like you're never gonna get a pan clean. Oh, no, you're never gonna get a pan fully clean like this
My whole body is on fire I
Fuck I went like this in my nail
Nail on a chalkboard like fuck. I just screamed in your ear. Okay, fucking whatever. Don't do it again. Ah
Give me a fucking easy one. Oh
Goddamn gotta get some elbow grease in it. That's how you get it done. Mm-hmm. Look at that. Fuck his brain
You saying fuck my brain or you saying like oh, no his brain. Alrighty. Are we ready for the next delicious treat?
I have to turn the microphone down garbage bowl. You're right
Those actually those are kind of good are we good so these two chocolate brownie mixes and two this this this is gonna be so much easier
Thank God. It's actually just two or three packets not like six. Thank God. All right chocolate brownie mix
Yeah, you get two of them just in case you want to go crazy
Yeah, this is gonna be so much better vanilla frosting mix. It's just two fucking things. Thank goodness
All right, clean as you go clean as you go
Thank goodness
All right, clean as you go clean as you go clean as you go clean as you go
Clean as you go turn the oven on. Oh shit. That would have been bad
All right. This one will be nice and quick. I think I don't even do I even need should I try to do one of these
Without the instructions like fuck it. Just do that
Dump brownie mix into the fucking container and then dump vanilla frosting into the container. I need water bowl
I'm about to throw that bowl in trash. You know what I mean?
Like I'm thinking about just putting that in it's thrown in the trash, but you can't I mean, it's like plastic
I can't do that. That's terrible. Okay, here we go chocolate brownie
Surprise, what's the surprise?
marinara sauce on the bottom
Okay, here we are one and a half teaspoons of water stir until it's nice and thick. Okay. Oh, this looks nice
I actually like the way this looks. Okay, it smells like just
hot-chocolate powder, which is like I
Let me tell you something
Nesquik cocoa powder just even like chocolate milk powder
Tell me if you guys think I'm a sick fuck for doing this
I guarantee some of you guys do it too
you just you stir in a little bit just like you know, maybe one tablespoon into your milk and you get it a little bit there and
Then you sprinkle on top a layer of powder on top of the milk
So it becomes this disgusting sludge and you take a sip after you let it wait sit on the top for about 10 to 20
seconds take a little sip and you suck up the wet powder and
And it's like I'm telling you try it if you don't if you I'm telling you actually this is good to have a big
Bowl. No, I don't I did do that. Yeah, I mean I don't do this anymore. I'm a grown man. All right
Okay, where's my stirring thing? This smells very good. This smells way better than powdered tomato sauce
All right, let's get our spatula and let's uh, let's work with it here. What do you say?
Okay, I'm trying to see yeah, let's actually move this out of the way LUL poop wine. It's chocolate. Oh, I get it
It's hey. Hey, it's it's brown in there. It must be poopoo. All right guys row up
How is this only need one and a half tablespoons of water?
Can somebody explain that to me because this is not even close. I need way more water than this
I think I might even need more than that
You need like a cup of water in here. You didn't add one and a half. What? Yes, I did
I'm gonna get in there
Imagine being a parent and having your kid asked to do this on a one on a given day
This is one of those things where you just don't want to hear those words
No, can't you like go outside and just like throw shit around why I don't want to do this
Who wants to do this what parent wants to actually have to go through the trouble with this shit?
They want you to make food
Why don't you make actual brownies like why do you need this weird little fucking bagel toaster?
Just make a brownie just make brownies in your oven in your actual oven. What's this for? What is this for?
I can't I was it for I don't get it. It's for kids. Okay, you kids can cook too, but you need supervision for this
caution
Supervision required so if you need supervision to use this you need supervision to use a real oven. So what's the pro?
I don't know. What's the deal? What's the problem? This actually looks pretty this looks pretty syrupy and pretty soupy
And pretty delicious it says mix concoction until it gets all syrupy and since savory and soupy. I got it there
All right, that looks good. Damn. This looks fucking good. I did a good job
I this is from scratch isn't me doing this shit from it's too loud might be okay now
We do the frosting easy-bake vanilla frosting. We'll do it in here. Wait, was this the one with the cheese in it?
Okay. Now what is going to do water cheese frosting? We don't do this yet. Okay, roll these mixtures into balls
I need to wait what already that might light on fire. I can't okay sprinkle flour on
Okay, so wait, this is supposed to be turned into a ball. That's not gonna turn into a ball. Hold on
Just eat it out of the fucking bowl
Wow
Okay, what are you supposed to cook this? Is this like rotten boy? Do I ain't supposed to cook that is it raw?
Oh
Smells in there it fucking stinks and it smells
College dorm room in here. Oh
No, I have to go to the dentist after this one, okay
So you can't eat it raw it has to be baked cuz it's not there could be this like raw cookie dough in there
I can fix this though because there's two of these I'm gonna add this very slowly
You know, you can make a mistake. You make a mistake or two. It's fine. It's okay to make us mistake
You can fix it in post. This is this is the video editing of the cooking world
You just add a little bit more powder slowly and get it in there until it's all syrupy and soupy and thick and savory
How am I ever gonna put this into a ball? Well, um, should I just spread this on there?
What if I just spread this onto the pan and make it like just on the pan and then put the frosting on top?
So it's just a big cake. What's wrong with that? It'll still work. This is not gonna turn into a ball, right?
No, how the fuck do people cook I swear to god chefs definitely just sit there while they're doing this and going like oh my god
This is fucking wrong. This is so wrong. This is the wrongest thing I've ever done. This is not fucking right
This is wrong and then like cut to the guy
Bringing it out and being like here is your salmon, sir. The chef prepared it fresh for you
I swear to god like this is this shit's impossible. This is impossible. I'm just making a chocolate bowl
Okay, okay. This is not I'm just gonna do the thing. I said I was gonna do let's try it
More powder, but I'm not gonna be able to even move it. What do you mean more powder?
This is like one of the things I'm too tall for which how does that make any sense now?
What remember this is for kids? Yeah
More powder make balls make balls. I'm not sure I can do that with this. It's just gonna fall apart. Look at this
It's it's it's too goopy. Don't put any more powder. Are you following the recipe?
Yeah, pour one chocolate brownie mix and add one and a half teaspoons of water
I think maybe that is I think that does need to be more powder, right?
I think so because they otherwise a teaspoon. Yeah, but it was I couldn't even work with it
It was so powdery. It was impossible. God. This is annoying. Just go to Dunkin Donuts. Just get one
They have like 60 balls. All right. Hold on. It's coming together. I might be able to actually turn this into a ball now
I'm only gonna make like a couple of these I think this is so all right
This is starting to get hard to do more powder. Are you sure? Yes. All right, I'm not putting any more
I'm not doing any more powder after this. This is it terrible. Oh my god
What is this even supposed to do? How do you fuck up to a one ingredient bag? I don't understand
I think I need the other tool. This is gonna be impossible
I think I gotta get in there with my hands, but I can't get in there with my oh, there we go
Look at that. I can scrape like I can scrape the bottom. All right. What do you think? Is it ready?
What do you think that looks a little frothy?
Maybe a little maybe a little bit more powder just a little bit spinning it you're making a lot of dad noises
Fuck and whatever. Okay. This is definitely ready. Maybe a little bit more powder. I don't know
I've never made brownies before guys. I don't know what it's supposed to look like
I was hoping that there would be pictures in here to show me. I think this is good
It's very it's very stringy. All right
I'm just gonna try to get a bunch of it and then I got a have it be a ball
Okay, and then and then what make it if that defeat? Oh, these are whoopie pies. These are not brownies
Why are you guys saying brownies whether whoopie pies? They're not supposed to be brownies
Okay, so we need to make two we're gonna make one. I'm only doing four
I'm doing one two and one two. Okay, how am I gonna do this turn on the oven?
The oven's on the oven is on the ovens powered on
Okay before I do this I gotta get this prepared. I gotta be ready for this. This is gonna be a disaster
I gotta be ready with this just right here waiting for me. I can't turn this into a ball into a ball
This is just how a child eats dessert. Okay, it's almost a ball
It's it's getting there and then I have to spread it out on here. Oh shit
Hershey's kisses instead. Okay, there's one
No, no the baby got on the counter and it's just eating the chocolate out of the bowl
This is the baby. This is the baby is on the counter Jared my husband. Where the fuck are you? What are you doing?
Why are you letting him do that? You're gonna let the baby eat on the counter. What are you fucking stupid? I don't oh, right
Sorry, hey get off that counter. I can make one you supposed to make a ball. Hold on
There we go. Sometimes he's gonna get in there. All right, I'm gonna make one. I'm gonna make one whoopie pie
This is bad. This is bad. I feel like people are gonna people are gonna share this clip. Oh damn it
I can't make a ball needs more powder. I think there's no way I can do this
Barf it said use your hands
I have to like spend an hour cleaning this up. Okay, I have we're gonna do an open-faced turkey sandwich type
Bye here
Whoopie pie open face. I have one on there. It's it's starting to solidify on my hands
I don't know what to do. I don't know what I'm doing. I'll try as hard as I can to get one other ball
Smoke wait get that out of there. Okay, this is new plan new plan new plan new plan
I got one. This is it's solid now. Yeah, this one's this one's trashed. This one's trashed eating
What there's only one way out of this I to eat my way out
There's only one way out of this don't laugh if I laugh it's gonna go fucking everywhere. Don't fucking laugh focus
Focus I could have to move you guys. I can't fucking I just stop eating this what I'm stuck
I'm actually stuck. I can't move. I can't go anywhere. I can't turn. I can't like turn the stream off
I can't go anywhere. I literally can't move. I'm gonna have to sit here for the rest of my life
Is there an easy one in here just save scum I wish is there an answer an easy one
I okay. I'm making this I'm gonna do the frosting. I'm not giving up on this one
I still I got a dollop on there. We're gonna make a fucking brownie with extra frosting on it
I just have to not have this all over me. I'm I'm like in trouble
I have to pick this up with my mouth. Why did I pick this up with my fucking hands? What a joke?
What an idiot dope this thing this thing's like preheated
Well, hope you like a guy that is 35 years old almost that is stuck in his chair
Because he couldn't figure out how to do the brownies on the easy bake oven and now he is actually
Fucked because he can't move and now I have to like go wash my body. I have to go take a shower
They're not brownies. Whatever. We'll see what they are when they come out of the oven
I need a cupcake pan that doesn't say that on there. It says put them on the tray click the link
Oh, yeah, click the link. Let me just reach for my mouse and grab it. Yeah, I can't do that right now
I told you I'm stuck forever. All right. I'm good. Here we go. I'll be right back. Okay now
I'm now I'm at that point where I can literally clean myself up disaster
Why would I fucking do this with my hands? I should have I should have now that's a thought
No, that's a thought in this guy right here
I can wake a ball in my mouth and then just like off-camera just put it on there. No, what do you mean?
What I'm gonna like form it in my mouth like and then just spit it out. I'll don't do that
Don't there's an audio delay. How is there an audio delay? I have one. I'll like here
I'll just I just we have one we have a whoopie pie. It's done. All right, I have to get okay
This is gonna be weird. I can't grab this but this is gonna be
This it's gonna be loud
So just turn your volume down because I'm gonna literally just like wily coyote yank this off my head
This is why cooking sucks
Okay, because it's just a shitload of cleaning you clean for like six times more than you cook you cook for like six minutes
And you clean for like two hours. This is my cooking sucks. All right, I'm gonna make the frosting time for the frosting
Okay, cool. I think preheated nice very very nice
I'm gonna have to put them all in the same bowl. I
I'll click it. I'll click it. Give me I'll fix the volume too. Just give me one sec
You know, it's like kind of remarkable I've not gotten a single damn thing
Anywhere anywhere, but right here. That's that's remarkable. Okay frosting time after I click on the link
I'll take a break
Hold on a second. Like this is through the cookies. Hi, where's the link? You got a link for me?
Whoa, I can't you doing it too fast. You're doing it way too fast. I can't even click it. Holy shit
Oh my god, that looks horrible. No, it looks like I got like an a hockey fight. Oh
How many more of these are there? That's that's the wrong one. What do you mean wrong one?
I can't spray the cupcakes that doesn't that's not on my book. That's not on my book. Read that. That's not a cupcake pan
Oh, I'd special pan place the six flat cakes on the sprayed baking pan. I got scammed. Whatever. Whatever. Whatever
That's fine. Any more pictures you want me to look at before I go fucking ruin my reputation as an adult human being
Yeah, I saw that one. I'm back to it. You bought home on you're going too fast
You bought the easy bake up instead of the easy cupcake oven. That's a lie easy fake oven. Whatever
So I got I got sorry. It's a so it's fucked up. Who cares? All right, I'm going back over there any scraps for me
Could you see me? Could you see my face? Yeah. Okay. Hey wish I had the cupcake pan. Don't you?
That was disgusting just leave just go go trust me just go yeah, that's that's the end this
See you later. That was back there. You're free to go. You are I need my instructions. No, I don't even need my instructions
It's water that I don't have any water
Yeah, cuz I just pretended to blow a snot into the food like I would have left I would have been like, okay
This who else does somebody else has to be fucking streaming. I have to do this whole thing in here
I don't know about that. This is a lot
What's next? Oh, I'm supposed to cook this sure. Okay, so just put it in
There's only one but whatever what am I gonna do about it? How long well fucking minutes in no way
It's definitely not 12 minutes not for one. I know. All right, let's make the fraud
This is gonna be the delicious part. I am excited for this one. Oh, yeah
Mm-hmm. Yep. Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah smell that smell that one. That's just like a vanilla powder
Okay, do I don't I don't need to make that much frosting for one little cake. This is too much frosting
This is gonna be the most savory I can't wait look just say words that have to do with food
And people will think you know what you're talking about. All right, that's one's done
That's food. We need some water
How much water one and a half teaspoons? I think that's it right and then mix it up
I get I gotta move the vomit ball out of the way. Okay, here we go. So I'm not gonna add any more water
I'm not gonna be a psycho about this. It's not really as you can see it's mix it faster
No, that's not how you don't mix it faster is not better. So low it's slow and slow
Time on that one time on this one. What was it? Why when did I put it in nine minutes left? Okay
I don't want to make a fucking mess faster faster. What the fuck? This is frosting
vanilla frosting
This doesn't look like frosting
Did I do too much fucking water again? I did a teaspoon. I did it this time. It had one and a half. You saw me
No, no, no, no, no. No, this is this is reducing
Hey, this is this is reducing. There's another one of those cooking words that they say on Food Network
Yeah, okay. This is no look at it. Yeah, it's thickening up time on that. You're going too fast
You know, I need to I'm fucking knock this out of the way. Should I give it a taste?
What is it? What is it? What's it? What's it supposed to taste like?
Frosting. Yeah, this is looking like a glaze
Yeah, it looks alright. It's supposed to
Span that person
Ban that person, you know who you are and you know what you said ban them
I don't want to see their face ever again. I don't want to ever even I don't want to even hear them in this chat
You know what you said and you know who you are. Now you fucking being like holy shitty and talking about me
Yeah, ban them for at least a week. Maybe you'll learn your lesson. What do we got for time on that eight more minutes?
No, it's not. It's like four. All right. This is ready. This is nice and mixed. It's got a nice honey glaze
Consistency, it's nice gonna be a nice drizzle on our cake
What else do I have here? Oh look at this shit, but I don't like have I need to like or
Wait, what about the pretzels? Should I make the pretzels? I can make a pretty so I'm gonna make a huge pretzel
Yep. No who wants to eat these? Yeah, I'm gonna make a big pretzel. It's that one right there
Okay, I have this bowl. I have one two three three clean bowls time on that. Please. There's a time. No, what do you mean?
Hold on. Are we ready to reveal it? It's six minutes back to mixing
This is gonna be gross and a lot of people are gonna be grossed out by this
I guarantee you I have diarrhea in like three hours. I guarantee you think that's just a hot 100%
Time on that up. This thing freaks me out man. This thing freaks me the fuck out. Is this glue? No, it's
It's too thin. It's a no, maybe it's not maybe it's supposed to be like a
Like a nice little drizzle or something add more powder fine
I'll add a little bit more powder fine. That's enough put it down. Actually not a bad idea
That's it's starting to really thicken up a little bit here. You want to talk about peak inefficiency, by the way an entire
Two-two full packets of chocolate powder just 80% of it gone and there's one little dollop in there
Just absolute inefficiency. There's not you can't get more inefficient than what just happened
Although hold on a minute. I did put a big spoonful of my mouth from the beginning
So that was it that was one cake
I did one full cake in my mouth in the beginning and then I did like at least two cakes full licking it off of
My hands, right? So it wasn't a total waste maybe half of it 50% in efficiency. So I got an F still enough
All right. Yeah, that's definitely what it's supposed to be like. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, there we go. Maybe even a little bit more take it out. Take it out. Take it out
How long has it been isn't it too long? All right, I'm gonna get it
I'm gonna get it out. How long has been take it out take it out. Oh shit. Hold on
I'm almost I gotta get a little thing. So it's too hot for me. It's burning. It's not fucking burning
Quit freaking me out. You guys are fucking with me. Is it out? Oh, dude
It actually looks pretty good. It actually looks kind of good. Take a look at this like I saw the bot
Okay, here it comes. Why is it such a pain in the ass to get out? Okay, hold on
I gotta get it out of there now
Get out of there get up give it to me. Oh my fucking
God
Yet it won't oh, okay. Here comes a big reveal. Take a look at that. Ah
Yep, it is puffy. It is crispy and it's ready for the frosting. It smells good. It is a little crispy
Yeah, that's alright though. You know when you
Take out your trash you take your trash out of the trash can the bag and
It's just like one item. That's always just at the very bottom of the trash can and you just look in
You know, you see it there all the time, you know, it's in there, but you don't ever fucking grab it
You don't take it out. This is the item that's just at the bottom of the trash can it's hard as a rock
You ready to hear this? It's gonna be like hard candy. Why what happened? I did I told you it was in there for too long
A yummy whoopie pie. Holy shit. This is good. This is good way better than the pizza
Oh, dude, don't go rules dude. Don't go rules, dude. Are you kidding me? It's don't go rules
It's exactly like don't go rules. I wish I made a hundred of these you get
Yeah, fuck this you buy you get one of these don't do this make a bunch of this shit
Make the frosting don't even put the frosting on don't make the whoopie pie make don't go rules break up into little crunchy pieces
Holy shit, that's perfect. Well, I wish I had more
Then the joke from the Disney
Donald's goofy and Mickey Mouse cartoon where they were sharing one single bean and slicing it off like bread
I don't know Jack and the beanstalk. What is it called? What was that? What was that? What was it called?
It was a Jack and the Beanstalk. They were slicing one bean like a bread. It was bread. Wait, was it bread?
Oh, no, they had they were slicing bread like paper thin. What was the bean? No, they did it to a bean too
Okay, let's make a pretzel. Mmm. I think I'm I got I got clean bowls here
Let's see what it takes. Let me make sure I get this ready to go. I enjoyed my I enjoyed
Yeah delicious delicious free sample at the mall now. Let's uh that for what I had though. That was really good
You know, it's suck
So bad is that's so good and the free sample of the ball is always so good
But then when you actually get the food, it's not so good when you take that free sample that they oh here free sample
And you're like, hmm, holy shit. This is I'm this is best thing I've ever had in my life
You get the actual entree that that is it's like a 7 out of 10. I hate that shit
It's so annoying like I just I want to buy the tray like I want to go up to the people that have the trays
Of the samples and be like can I order can I just buy the tray now from you?
I'll pay twice for what the actual entree is for that's a that's a psychopath test. All right. Well, then I'm a psycho
Whatever. This is gonna go. I still got water here, which is good. Probably gonna need it
I can clean that up. Let's do the pretzel. It's because the sample people don't know how to do it
What do you mean chug the frosting? No, no, I'll shit my pants
I really will I feel like I'm about to take like medicine something about it. I can't I can't do it
I can't do something about it. I can't do that something about it
So I can't do it something about how that is that I want it
If you know if you put that in a Dunkaroos container, I'll eat it. It's not a dunker
It's not in a Dunkaroos container. No, I keep trying. I keep trying to just psych myself out and do it. It's just sugar
What's the problem? It's fucking fine. It's sugar. No, it's not. Yes. It is. Just fuck up. It's fine. It's not fine
It's gross actually is kind of gross without the Dunkaroos aspect of it. All right, let's go trash container right here
We'll move this out of the way for now. I'll have to clean this up later. All right, it's time for pretzel
It's pretzel. Hopefully pretzels not that hopefully you don't need a bunch of bullshit for the pretzel turn the oven off
Okay, fine. I
Am going to try my hardest and we've been here for a couple hours for two three hours
I'm going to try as hard as I can to make this the way that it looks on the actual package
Like I'm I have to do one that look that is correct
Have to if I'm gonna prove anything here. I need to be ready
I need I want to brush my teeth so bad clean the tray
I will let me just see what the damage is here. This isn't this is an elaborate one. It's got like holy shit
This is so he's so many packets in here. Oh
boy
Okay, this is just salt. This is egg wash
nacho cheese sauce
Pretzel mix two pretzel mixes is there three? Okay. Am I ready for this?
Let me at least hold on. Let me at least get these other bowls because I'm gonna need one two
Three four one, two, three. I'm gonna need four bowls. Let me clean this one out and let me wash this tray
my mother's probably
Freaking out right now
You know, you guys like a backseat game, you know both backseat gamers on twitch. My mother is loves to bake
She's really into it. She is probably backseat gaming right now
So hard like I I did like I fell off the cliff like four times to my mother right now right now
She's just like what is he doing with his hands?
No, what do you what are you dumb?
Like he's he are you are you pretending to not know how to do this Jeremy? And she's like, oh my I just said that
All right. Do I need what do I need for pretzel nuggets? No, I'm doing the loop. All right, I can do this one
Let me clean up the area. Let me clean this out
Try as hard as I can for this like this is you think that you like me trying to beat like Jevil for the first
Take the first try. No, I'm gonna get this first try. I'm gonna try as hard as I can
I'm gonna be fucking silent try harding the whole time. I'm gonna be dead silent
quiet I
Said I'm gonna be silent try harding this because I want to be sure I get at the first try
These are just gonna have to be cleaned later because that shit ain't gonna happen right now
Speed run speed run easy big oven. That's not gonna work. You're sweating. I know I'm sweating
Wouldn't you be in this scenario? If you want me think about it
There's over 11,000 people here watching me not be able to do children's baking toy
Do you don't think that you would be sweating just a little here?
There is like a baseball stadium full of people watching me like burn cupcakes. It's good
It's just sugar Jeremy, don't worry, it's not gonna hurt you
Ego maniac and then I will return in
Two minutes I'll be back in one or two minutes to keep going we eat this we eat this shit
We eat this this we eat this we shouldn't be eating this stuff
We shouldn't be eating this just to get a juice or a juice kale
Cucumbers and like pineapples and shit. Don't eat this stuff
I still taste the marinara sauce
Even after eating like two other things I can still taste it. It's like embedded into my gums
Alright, here we go. Time to make the pretzel. I'm gonna make this one count. I'm not gonna fuck around here
Pretzel time. Let's go. I'm ready. I'm ready to give this a fucking hundred percent
Alright, let's get this thing cooking. Uh-huh. No, it's try hard time
This is gonna be the best if this is not one of the best pretzels
You've ever seen somebody make with an easy bake oven. I will give
I don't know
50 subs
I'll give you 50 community so I'll give 50 community subs
If this is not like at least like a 5 or 6 out of 10 if this is not a 5 or 6 out of 10
I will promise. Okay. Here we go. That means I'm gonna do this right one egg wash mix. Let's go
Let's fucking go. You know what?
Ah, it's too loud for me
Don't that's bad. Yeah
next is
Pretzel mix looked over there on that screen and I thought that this bowl was a fire
I looked at the preview and I thought that was a fire
If this is this one, I don't like this one. Give me another one. This one's fucked up. No too contaminated
It's like a fucking sandbag. Come on
This
Three four
To a ball
Okay, what kind of pretzel do you want to make? I don't know how to make a pretzel actually
I don't know how to make a pretzel now what it's gonna be good. I need a little I'm what I think anymore water
I don't know. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope
Bingo use a bit more water
I'm only gonna use water just get it a little wet so I can use my hands with it
Just like they do with the fucking restaurants
Here we go, is it blood in this am I bleeding? Oh shit, is it? No, I'm not. All right
It's a fish. What are you talking? I haven't even spoken
loud for me
This sucks
Get that fucking liquid in there. That's what the problem is
It's not a fucking liquid in there get it in there work it in there go
What's a pretzel do? It's very finicky. Hold on. This one's a much better piece. All right. All right. All right
This is this one's this is the one to use fuck this one sucks. This is the one we're using
Okay, here we go. How do you how do you do it?
Dad twist it. I can't
it's
That just scared me
Okay, then it goes
twisted like this
He's going crazy. All right, that's good. That's good. That's good. Look at that. What do you think?
What do you think? You're a psycho
That's pretty pogchamp. It is
It actually is
Like that's very that's good. This is well done. That's at least a five
That's a fucking five five. That's a goddamn five
Ain't that a five?
All right now shut this up. I can't fucking I just did like a monkey. Let's just cook this just because
This music doesn't it's fucking freaking me out
Bake is this on is it on? No, you don't solve you salt after salt after you don't solve yet
you salt after make the glaze make the dough glaze it and then
Make the cheese
salt it salt now
Salt it now
Should I should I actually solve the directions? Don't say anything about salt. I don't see anything about salt. Oh shit
Yeah, it does. Okay, I gotta be careful
That's that's fine. That's not none of that. That's good. That's good. That's good. That's not that's that's perfect
All right, get it in the oven
Here we go. It's too big. Come on. Don't do this to me now. All right, get it in there 12 minutes
The shits on right?
Death
The rest of these look real complicated I'm willing to open them and see we've already done this one fuck this thing
I'm giving I'm giving this thing to my niece. Anyways, she's gonna. Oh wait the cheese sauce. What about the cheese sauce, dude?
Make the cheese dip. No, I don't want to make that. You know how bad this is gonna smell
I refuse to make this just the smell alone from opening this would would probably make me gag
Dermot's the worst uncle but a free easy bake oven with some fucking cool toys and some awesome recipes
This makes me a bad uncle. What are you smoking? Keep an eye on that. That's bread in there. We're making bread tonight
All right. Well, I mean it might as well. Yep. That's exactly what I thought it was gonna be
You know the inside, you know the Kraft macaroni and cheese the cheese packet
We're gonna be eating this shit in ten years. Anyway, 20 years from now real foods are gonna be
Hard to come by like digging a powdered food is gonna be the actually what we're eating that in bugs
Fifty years from now, we're gonna be eating bugs and powdered milk. Okay, just one with two teaspoons water. That's true. Yeah
I know I'm completely aware time what we got for a time. It must be 12 minutes everything
Why is everything 12 minutes too, right? That's it. Maybe one little bit
Yeah, maybe if I didn't have such huge ass balls
This wouldn't be a problem because all I'm effectively doing is just getting it all over the place
This is supposed to be a cheese sauce
Why did I open the why did I open this package? Why did I open the package? Why did I open this package? It stinks
This is not even a sauce. This is more like a solid than it is a sauce. I just fucked it up
I just fucking ruined it. Would you eat this? Would you eat this? Would you eat it?
I mean it kind of is like a dip. It's supposed to be a cheese
I can't even fucking imagine man going to like a Super Bowl party. Well, what do you got there? Oh, well
We've got cheese dip. Yeah, we've got a little bit of gravy left from Thanksgiving last year
we've got a sour dough dough and
Water like that. This is this is not enough
What a feast
Okay, seriously
This is the type of shit you get mad when your bowl looks like this when it's still when it comes out of the
Dishwasher like that. It's like fuck man. That's not clean
Bullshit, that's unbelievable. This is post dishwasher angry not cheese dip
Speaking of post dishwasher angry. I'm gonna have a lot of fun cleaning this shit up. I don't want to eat this
What's the time cheese dick? This is oh
Can you imagine like being in line at lunch it's like nachos is on the menu Wow nachos we never have nachos
Little lunch ladies. Just like yeah
Okay, who's next for the cheese that's when you just skip and you just go to the fucking meatball sub add more water
I need time on that. You thought you thought I was gonna do it. Oh that I didn't even know how it happened
It's like I was holding a bug in my hand and I looked down and it was gone
It just freaked me out because I didn't know what the bug was four minutes cool
This is no, this is probably the Lunchables cheese. I think is probably better than this
How has it become less is what I don't understand how did it's dip it's
Disappearing should I should I go for it? No earwax. Oh now I now you know, I can't do it
I'm taking it out. Why is every single one of these?
Let me give me give you a rundown of what the last three hours has been the last three hours has been I
make this gross shit and then sit there over the course of three recipes and
Try to eat a huge amount of the gross thing. I've done it like four times. You gotta go all in still there
That was the grossest thing. I think I've done in probably the last five years. I'm not even kidding
That's probably the gross thing. I've done in the last three years
Does it taste like cheese it tastes?
Like I feel like a cat just puked in my mouth and then somebody just sprayed
Like I can't believe it's not butter up my nose. That's kind of what it feels like. Is it ready?
It's ready. Is it time one minute. I'll tell you guys a story of how I
Never in my whole life. I've ever puked from looking at food or smelling food
I really haven't I haven't but one time I did one time
there was in the so my mother made eggs and bacon and like a breakfast spread, right and
After a few hours, you know, obviously it's like, okay, like it's clean it up put it everything in the sink and
Okay, we've got like there were there were dirty plates in there because we didn't have a dishwasher
at the time, I don't think and
in the sink with all like the dirty kind of breakfast plates was this one dirty plate that had eggs on it still just
like curdled up
Scrambled eggs wet and cold and it smelled like gross eggs and I threw up like I threw up directly
Into the sink on top of the eggs is the only times ever happen. Oh shit. No, I puked from Oreos, but no
I was sick though. That's a lie. It's not a lie. I was sick though. I was not sick for this story
That's not a that's a that's not a fake story. It's a real story. All right, here we go. You ready?
That's I wish I had some cheese dip. Ah shit. Ah, fuck. It's so bad. It smells rotten
50 subs but before but I that's not fair because I had to squish it because it wasn't it couldn't fit in here
All right, 50 subs fine. All right, fine 50 subs you get it
You can have to wait till I go go home
So if you want the subs, you're gonna have to wait till tomorrow
Cuz I can't I'm not even I can't do it right now
I did like my PayPal like credit card info like hooked up here
You didn't get scammed if you we're gonna be here tomorrow, too
Oh boy, I want to take a bite of this the cheese is kind of fucking me up. Oh, why did I eat that?
Like I'm not on like a game show where I have to eat gross shit now somebody hey somebody somebody already did it
I don't have to do it anymore
Okay, that's not good. Wait, listen to my voice. Did you hear this? This is bucket. I don't move nobody move
Nobody fucking move. This is exactly what I talked about in the past. Nobody fucking move
I need to keep this as long as possible because the cheese it's gone. God damn it. That's not edible
That's not edible. It wasn't edible coward. Let's just okay. I can't eat out of the trash
I'm a grown man. No. Nope. It smells so bad
Look at how much of a mess. This is look at how much of a mess it is to have kids
Look at how much look at how fucking hard kids are to have. I don't have any kids kids suck
Alright, I threw the tray away. I'll get it. Don't worry. I'm not gonna throw metal in the trash. We think I'm dumb
No, you cycle that shit. I'll get it later
Alright, what else is here?
I I feel like I should give this to my niece and she could actually have fun with it rather than me embarrassed myself
Like I mean, yeah, these are these would be these would be fun for like my niece to do
Someone's called me a wanker. My bowls are all dirty. I don't know if I could even do another one. Your niece doesn't want this
Yeah, she does. What who wouldn't want an easy bake oven? Dirty views the dirty bowls
This actually was fun though. I had a lot of fun doing this
I don't think I can physically make another one. I was supposed to do like six we did three
Let me see. Let me see. This one looks fun. Let me see. Let me see how fun this one looks
I just like opened my niece's present devil's food cake. Oh, this is this is a lot
Put it back. Put it back. Put it back. Put it back. Put it back. Just hold on. Stop stealing it from your niece
Fine. Don't worry. You got I do. All right. I got to clean that I got like gross cheese on it break the oven
Stop saying stop saying
Just the cock thing stop saying that you're gonna get in a lot of trouble with me personally
I'm cleaning up. I'm cleaning up. This is this ain't gonna fucking happen. You know, it isn't play jump king
That's not gonna happen. Well, so here's what we're gonna do. I'm gonna clean up. We'll hang out for a little bit
I'll be back in the studio here for green screen DLC for free volume 2 tomorrow. I'm gonna be in the same exact spot
Except
Obviously won't be a beach behind me will be full screen and 60 FPS and we'll do a shitload of stuff in the green screen
I have I have
At least a few hundred things to do. I have like I have a shitload of costumes
We're doing a lot of movie and TV show shit tomorrow. It's I'm I went overboard like I said in the beginning of the stream
Hopefully you get some good footage and make some fun shit
green screen movie night
What time tomorrow?
Probably around the same time probably like 4 o'clock 3 30 Pacific. Is there any Joe there?
There are no Joe Joe's bizarre adventure moves. I can promise you that I
Think if it might limit on easy big oven, that was fun. That was fun
But this is just this is not it's just gross. This is just it's just gross
Your kids will have a lot of fun with it your kids might like it
But then you have to clean up just make sure you have fucking a spit bag over here to like spit your food into
You know what sucks about this I
Am going to think about
Why am I doing doing that a lot today? I am going to put your hand on
I'm gonna think about eating that ball of cheese
That's never gonna leave my brain. I'm gonna think about it like once or twice a week
I'm gonna be in the shower
Just thinking about how it felt going down my throat and I think I'm forever changed
I think I've forever changed because of that. I'm thinking about it right now. Ah
Mom, I'm sorry. If you're watching
I'm sorry that I don't have the capable skills to be Baker couldn't get through for easy bake oven
Tutorials, this is cooking tutorial and I failed it. I failed it mom failed the cooking tutorial
Pepe hands
All right, let me come over there I get it
I'm gonna this is gonna take like a while for me to clean and I can get this place
I don't like a shit show
I'm coming over there now. All right, this is longer than I thought it was gonna be I thought it's been three hours
I thought it was like two. No, it's been okay. It's been three hours. Damn. All right
Three hours to do one. No turn that off show you cleaning three hours in two minutes
The oven is still on
Okay, that would have been very bad do a cleaning stream
Nice if I kept that plugged in what I actually what I'm gonna do is once we get out of here
I'm gonna get all my costumes ready. I'm gonna get every object ready. I got a shitload of objects. I got a lot of
toys and
Outfits and do a preview. No, no, no, no, no. No, are you serious finish saw?
I'm not I'm I'm in a studio right now. I'm not it like I'm not at my lap
I'm not at my computer. We're gonna finish saw on Sunday till the day after tomorrow. We're gonna finish saw
Yeah, I'm at the goddamn beach. Don't you see that went out of my room? All right, I'm out of here
I'll see you guys later. I'll see you guys tomorrow
Tomorrow's stream will be a lot longer than this because we have at least five plus hours of stuff to do
So I'll see you guys tomorrow. I can't even I lit that ball. I can't even fucking look at it
I don't know what to do with that ball this one here
God damn it. It's horrible. All right, I don't like have an ending here cuz I'm I can't like I can't like hold on
Let me see. Did we get any big bits to make sure I didn't miss anything. We did
We had a couple of huge bits. Hold on a second. Let me see. I have no outro or anything
I got nothing here. Jesus Christ. Yeah, there was like a holy shit. Let me move over this way
Let me at least say thanks to people that gave like fucking hundreds of dollars. Tay Rocker gave 50 bucks
Thank you. Tay Rocker. Last year. I was struggling to keep it together
I was homeless. Holy shit, but still working late hours at a stressful job
But my hard work paid off and now I share a home with the woman. I love that's fucking awesome
That's a really good turnaround. Your streams kept me sane on very cold nights
So I thought it was only fair to add to that towering pile of cash stuffed in your garage. Stay healthy
Don't let chat bully you you beautiful compact man. Hey, thanks and thanks for the $50 and that's I'm glad to hear about the turn
That's really good to hear we had
55 fucking dollars from the chef's corner. Hey looking forward to the rest of the stream
Thank you for being the most creative E clown
Thanks for the five years of laughs appreciate you dude, and they said and love you chat. There you go
Thanks for the insane amount of money phylactery give a hundred and fifty dollars, which is insane
Here's a hundred dollars you fucking legend. Enjoy your cancer. No, don't I don't say that I this
Enriched wheat enriched bleached wheat flour bleached wheat flour
iron sugar powdered shortening coconut oil maltodextrin sodium casein eight mono and
diglycerides
diposate to potassium sulfosate
silicon dioxide
hydrogenated palm oil cocoa pressed with alkali egg whites nonfat dry milk leavening sodium bicarbonate and sodium aluminum
Phosphates soy lesion salt silicon dioxide cellulose gum xanthin gum natural artificial flavor FD and see red 40
And that's just in the cake mix. Thanks for the fucking hundred and fifty dollars ride
ride
Dicow ride Eichel think I'm saying your name, right? Thanks for 50 bucks. This is so much money tonight
Jerma, I know you're a little busy eating your meal right now
But I found this to be the best time to mention my friends Jerma dream. Oh nice. He's my favorite in my Jerma dream
He was doing a vlog esque live stream
He was touring his new house and his girlfriend kept making really funny jokes and Jerma started getting jealous and got pissed and turned
Around and said if you don't shut the hell up, I'm gonna put you in my cringe compilation dead. Seriously. It's haunted me
Why why why am I such a sick fucking everybody's dreams and they call me false gave a hundred dollars to call me?
Thanks for the hundred bucks. This is the most beautifully cursed stream. I've seen it forever. Thanks for the laughs Jerma Ramsey
I thought it was fun. Just wish I had more balls. Thanks for the 10,000 bits
I also file actor a gift at 50 community subs Freddy dread came in with 20 community subs
Thanks a lot Freddy nondescript civilian 10 subs an anonymous gift of 20 subs
emo duck 10 Fez 5 for Liddy 5 for Libby 10
Actually Fez actually 10 for Liddy 20 and Ajax the mediocre
Thanks for the fucking huge amount of subs and then out right now any sub any
Neb subs here smug five community subs. I don't know they here maybe
Dude, okay. It's starting to I smell that cheese. I got to get fucking rid of this now
Like that cheese is is a heavy cloud. That's just filling the air. I got to get rid of this now
I can't believe I fucking ate that. I'm I'm disgusted at myself. I'm disgusted and I'm gonna I'm gonna watch the clip
I'm gonna check out some of the clips from the stream people gonna send it to me and I'm gonna be fucking disgusted by the way
There are over there some mats that I can probably fucking jump on and like flip on and shit
Those are like stunt mats over there
I'm gonna ask the studio if I can use those because if I can like front flip like
Over them and like jump on them and shit diving like shots and diving catches and shit
I'm gonna see if I can use those don't strain. Well, they're like big stunt pads. I'll be alright. Don't worry
I've been preparing for this very moment, but I gotta get out of here. I have to I gotta clean this up
This is gonna just start stinking and I don't want to have their
Studio, I don't want to fuck up their studio. So I gotta get out of here right at the very end fell six
Thanks with five subs and thanks for watching. By the way, I gotta get into frame. Thanks for watching the stream everybody
We'll see you tomorrow for the green screen DLC for free volume two. See you tomorrow. I'm gonna get out of here
But can you see under? Hold on ready? That doesn't that's not right. That's does that's weird
I don't know what the fuck I'm seeing but whatever. All right. Good night. See you guys tomorrow same time same place