I'm going to be your distraction heavy. You're going to be sniper. Your goal is to don't use the machine gun. You're going to use the sniper rifle gun.
Dude, whoa, easy. Watch that hand. Watch that right hand. Watch that hit.
We're playing an RTS right now. Like I'm one of your units.
Go towards the door. Stand next to the door.
Okay, I'm one of your units. You're just like, Commander? Affirmative.
I'm going to die.
Alright, I'm doing. I'm here. I'm here. I need to be commanded.
I don't have any commands.
What am I supposed to do?
Left, left, left.
Affirmative.
Pyrot, punch him.
Distract him.
What do you think I'm doing? He's running away.
He's just trying to kill me.
Come back, come back.
I'm trying.
I think he knows you're there.
I know he knows I'm here. Is he taunting you?
No.
I heard a pyrot taunting.
We don't have players on this team that you can just walk around and do that
Yeah, come back with me. You need to like your default position as I command you is on me
So my default position position is on you
That's where that is my I'm not saying anything you need to like try and stand in me
So I'm like tethered to you and then you need to select me
Yeah, yeah select you and then I send you after someone. Okay, you've got it affirmative
Actually, excuse me
Excuse me. Yeah, stand in front of me. No this spy punch the spy punch the demo. No, don't punch the demo
You can't give me two different. I'm not
Come with me. You can't give me like that many commands bar here. I take it. I can't you can't drop it
I'm gonna get headshot. Are you not using the sandwich because I wanted extra health. I want a 350
Get a medic to heal you you'd have full health right now if you had the normal thing
Well, we don't have a medic walk in front of this heavy I okay do something you didn't do it, right
Do it right
Walk in front of this heavy. Okay, you didn't do it
Right
Let me just take my feet and like walk one after the other after the other in front of the heavy
Like how do you how do you not do that? Right?
There's a little back here. If you see him run towards him. Otherwise, you're tethered. Okay, I see the soldier run towards soldier
Going for him commanded
Excellent job distracted. It's excellent distraction excellent work. Okay. Okay
Hold it hold your position on me
I just saw that spy dude back up back up watch out watch out
Walk in this pyro, I'm not number you right now. Oh my god, you're don't worry. I'm here
I'm here
He just doesn't know I exist yet
Yeah, give me your sandwich
Say nicely. Oh
You what the fuck is this hat? I
Was getting tons of kills before we started this I can't headshot anyone right now
And I think it's all your fault. How is it my fault? Nothing's changed if anything, it's cutting easier for you
No, this is way harder. It's kind of like you understand
Where are you cuz I'm trying to keep track of my child?
Playing this game right this spy with me. You'd never like know where I am. Hey, okay. Where am I going?
Commander
All right, I have on you focus on me. What do you think I do see anything else that you think is happening?
That's important. It's not me. All right. Okay. All right, you do you a fudge faster than me
Okay, what are the coordinates go stand right?
Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Yeah. Yeah distraction heavy's giving you a hand here. Watch out for this guy
Walk towards this health kit
Okay, there's a teleporter up there is also and there's also a sentry and a dispenser. Let me give her to the century first
Let me let me excuse me. Hello. Give him uber. Give him uber. Let me give him uber. That's what you're doing
It's so hard to stop and aim and focus on what I'm supposed to do one
You desperately want like me to give you commands you would not fist fight that medic unless I gave you instruction to do it
I'm gonna take the heat from the center. There's a century in here
Do something, please
Me you and one pyro, I don't know why
Ran at the century is going on here. He's doing a germa plan. How is that century still alive?
Did you see how many people were just shooting at it? I don't know centuries
There were like nine people shooting at this century and it was still alive
How did that portal? I just expect you to know some things
Coming back coming back right behind you. How old is this lemonade? I'm gonna have to find this out
I order you to not drink
Oh, that was gross behind you please. Oh, that was disgusting, dude
I ordered you come on. Wait, you told me not to yes. Oh shit. I wouldn't have done it. All right, where am I going?
up here tether
We're gonna mission ends in 60 seconds
All right coming me what's up going under this is an ultimate strat. I really believe in this strat you believe in this one. Yeah
We're trying to get to their spawn. We're about to like lose the game. No, it doesn't matter
Doesn't matter. This is important. Uh, watch it watch it
He's distracted. He's distracted
They're both