So something you need to keep in mind is that at some point somebody thought this
coaster might have been a good idea and is charging people money for it. This
costs money. This costs money. The ride just kills you. Why did you ever fucking ride
this ride? What kind of mess of coils did I just make down here? If one person
survives this, I'll be surprised. I'll be shocked if there's one person sitting still on this rollercoaster.
It looks like you just crushed up a fucking soda can and put it on the track. Let's see what
happens. We still haven't lost it. Oh, yeah, we have. No, no, no. What is with the building?
The building is fucking collapsing. What? I didn't do that. Oh my fucking god. I can't imagine a world where this actually will work. I mean, I'm on this human blender thing really badly. But I don't think there's gonna be enough speed to make the person smoothie that I want to make. Here we go. Holy shit, it's actually working. Oh, come on, keep going. Get to the top.
Get to the top. Come on. Come on, my creation. Yes, it worked. It just like throws the people. Look at the G force, dude. That's 28 G force. Your bones would fucking probably break at that high of G force. Let's start like a fucking new bowling team. The people are the fucking pins.
Oh, well, that's OK. That's not. Oh, I can actually see this like running away screaming. Get away from the giant hamster. You don't think I know how to do a good. You don't think I know how to do a god damn good. You know, god damn good bowling. There it is. Right. Get him. It's not what I wanted. That's not what I wanted. If this ends up actually working, then I'm going to probably laugh.
Critical distraction. What a piece of crap structure. That is not safe for anyone to go near. Considering that I just tapped it with a bowling ball and it fell down. Look at these tiny little helicopters. Are you serious? There's no way I'm going to be able to hit one of these. You need to be like so precise. All right, I'm just going to do the level. There'll be more of that dumb shit later. Bang. Oh, yeah.
I took off. I like chip the building's tooth. All right, so we got a ride here. I'm going to break it down for you. Here we go. Starting on the Stegosaurus spine. That takes you all the way up to the under J. You're going to go underneath this mess. Look at, well, just barely hitting that coaster, but you don't. Over the camel hump. Down to a deptifying 90 degree super drop. And then what happens? Holy shit, we're upside down. You're going to go upside down through the shoelace. The shoelace is the most important part. That's where everybody pews.
Not one person has not thrown up at that part of the ride. You're going to go over and under down towards the Spindy Doodle. The Spindy Doodle is patented. I actually went through the patent office and got this patent. So don't fucking steal it. Down through the pretzel. Pretzel is another part of the ride that I'm very proud of because no one's ever made a pretzel roller coaster before. And that takes you to the end of the ride. That's the scent of the scent. That's the scent. Yeah, the ride stinks. Yeah, this is the best roller coaster ever. I love them. Oh my God.
I can't even tell what's happening. So I better be getting people to sign a waiver to ride this next coaster. Because, I mean, you're guaranteed to die on this coaster. There's no, you don't live. You don't go to a theme park and see this and say that's what I want to ride unless I also want to be dead.
Here we go. First, you got to go up the speed boosts. There's the first jump. I told you. I told you.
What a beautiful day. Cascading waterfalls, beautiful wildlife forestation, and the sun shining down on all of us. God, I love it out here. I especially love the silly string ride. Go for it.
Right off the bat, that guy's stuck in the coaster. That guy is seriously lodged inside of the coaster.
I can't believe this is actually working. I seriously cannot believe this works. How have we not crashed yet? Is there anybody even left in the ride? No, it's an empty ride. It's an empty ride. There are no human beings in that ride right now. They're all gone. I'm going to manually drive around my coaster to keep everybody on the ride.
I should be able to do this. I just want to get to the end. That's all I want.
When you control the coaster, it weaves around. Okay, this is difficult here. These are boosters.
No, I can't control that. I'm holding the breakdown right now. It doesn't even matter.
I put way too many boosters here. See you later. I'm gone. I'm going to fly off right now. Yeah, knew it.