Hey, my headphones aren't in. No, they are. Well, now I can hear you. Sorry, I couldn't hear you.
I can hear you now. Welcome back. How's everybody doing? Are you doing good? Cool. How do you submit
levels for tonight? I kind of think we're just gonna just take them when I request them. You
know, like, hey, let me see one. I don't really have a plan for this besides just pulling them
out. Well, I want to do endless, not on super expert, but on easy. Just to try just to start
out. I just here's the thing about easy. So it's endless mode. How would you just play forever? If
you did it on easy? Is it okay? Correct me if I'm wrong, but isn't easy? Like jump on the
turtle's head and then walk to the flag. Somebody's gonna do it. Somebody's gonna
just do endless on twitch for like seven straight days on easy. And they're gonna do like 4000
levels. There's gonna be a record to break. Is it gonna be me? I don't think I want that record.
Because first of all, you have to you have to do that. And then you are the guy that I'm the
person that beat all the levels on easy. Because it's what I was capable of. At that
point. This is gonna move. This is all screwed up. There we go. You got this man. It's all you.
No, I don't got this. But anyways, yeah, we're gonna do Mario Maker 2.
We are going to do Dark Souls randomizer tomorrow. Let me try to get it to work.
Today is Mario Maker 2. Dark Souls randomizer is tomorrow. And then I think I'm doing
something on fourth of July. I'm pretty sure Kim and I want to do something. I think
she wants to go out. So it'll probably be today, tomorrow and then Friday.
So we'll get these two days in a row here. Weapon randomizer, enemy, pretty much everything.
I want to do weapon randomizer, enemy randomizer, boss randomizer. It's just gonna
be it's a shit. It'll be a total shit show. So I have no idea in Dark Souls remaster.
I'm gonna do it solo. I'm not gonna do it co-op with anybody.
Don't forget about Resetier. I will not. We got a lot of things to play. So that's a good thing.
You never want me to turn this stream on and be like, I have no idea what I'm doing.
I've absolutely no clue. I got nothing. I got nothing. So it's a good thing that there's
at least three or four games that I can play whenever I want. That's every stream. What do
you mean that's every stream? Every stream, that's like one stream a month, maybe. I got
nothing. When have you ever heard me say that? It's been like a month or two. Yeah, I don't play
the same damn game every day. So sometimes you got to figure out what you're going to do.
What are you talking about? Me? Yeah, you. All right, let's go ahead and start it on easy.
This is the punishment. Okay, how easy is this actually going to be? All like jokes
aside, is this absolutely impossible to lose? I don't know how to fly. Yeah, I do.
Oui. Oui. Wait, it's supposed to be impossible to lose. Uh-oh, Hugh versus kicking in.
You can't lose. Happy Fourth of July, everybody. Hope you have some hot dogs and hamburgers.
I have the strangest urge to purchase a Oui now. Don't do that. That's only a minute.
That's a long time. All right, what's next? I like this. This is fun. Okay, here we go. What's
the next one? This is like a bag of really, really mild jalapeno chips. There's no habanero
in here. There's no ghost peppers in here. No, this is just mild jalapeno. This is like
the default sauce at Taco Bell. I like it. Wait, are you seriously getting a taco without
like the Diablo sauce? Sometimes you don't want Diablo sauce. Sometimes I just want to fucking
eat a taco. Look at this. This is delicious. Can I get like six extra packets of Diablo sauce,
please? No. What's wrong with you? Nice mild flavor here. Diablo sauce is mild sauce. All
right. Okay, settle down. I know that there are people that love to tout how strong they are
with their mouths and how they can eat anything in their Diablo sauce. Not even intense, man.
I gauge how much I like a hot sauce, whether or not it hurts my body. It hurts my face and my
face hurts and I sweat and it puts me in the hospital. That's how I determine if it's any
good. Uh-oh, uh-oh, slow go. Hold on a minute here. What's the middle sauce called?
That's a middle sauce right there. Mild. No, mild. Wait, mild is the middle sauce?
No, it's not. Is mild the middle one? No, it isn't. It's mild, hot, fire, and then Diablo.
Okay, right. Yeah, so hot is... Wait, what happened? Germany's supposed to go to the
right in Mario levels. To the right in Mario levels. What is going on? This is salsa.
That's not true. Some sauces can be really bad. This is V8 juice. The tomatoes can be
too acidic for people. All right, how long am I gonna do this? How am I gonna keep this up?
In a packet of frosting. Oh, RT Game Crowd coming in for the ride! What's up, man? Thank
you. Just started, too. You guys are just in time. I don't know what you were just
claiming, but hopefully it was fun. Welcome, everybody. Thank you, RT. Are you doing Mario Maker?
What's your... All right, RT, if you're here, what's your favorite... How did I... I just got,
I got tripled right there. I couldn't even move. This little salsa's got some
fucking kick to it. No, no, no, no, no. These guys, these guys, this is honest,
but there was a bone in my fucking salsa, okay? It has nothing to do with how hot it is.
I just like... I picked a fucking bone out. No, shit. God, I'll get his bones everywhere.
All right, am I gonna get bones? Not too bad. Died to vegan almond milk. I did not. That's not
what that was. That's tricky. All right, this is not even an easy level. You just have to
pick a door. This is gonna bring me all the way back to the level. No, this shit don't
count. Does it count when the waiter sneezes in your food? No. No, god damn it, I was trying
to go... I'm still eating it though. I'm still eating the food. I'm putting it in my mouth.
Just skip it. You won't let me skip it. Oh my god, what a nightmare. Same pipe joke.
All right, which... I'm trying to see which one it is. Which one's going this one?
It's both of them, doesn't it? What's wrong with you? I drank a bunch of milk earlier.
I definitely shouldn't have done that. All right, I'm not doing this anymore. I want some...
I want some better salsa. All right, let's go to... Let's... Anybody got anything fun?
What's a decent one? All right, I'm gonna pick this one. Let's see what this one is.
Yeah, when I call for them, I'm just gonna use them. So this is TXPX3G.
Okay, searching for courses. This is called Extreme Desert Bus.
All right, 0.3% people have completed this. This is a speedrun. Reach the goal in a Koopa
trooper car. Okay, but check far, far forward. Check it. No. All right. Just... All right,
here we go. Really? Was that gonna hit my head? No. What? How do you get over this?
I have to jump on top of this and then... What? It's gone. Do I get another car? How the
hell are you supposed to do this? You gotta be going fast. All right, I got... I understand
what it wants me to do here. All right, hold on. I got it. Ow. Damn it. I can't... Do I get a
second car? All right, here we go. Nice. Wait. Oh, fuck. I did it. There's a car right there.
Desert bus. Desert jog. More like it. Looks good so far. I wonder if I'm gonna get another
car. Do I need a mushroom? That's not good. That's not good. Oh, no. I have to have the car.
Well, how am I supposed to make that jump? This is just getting over it.
Damn it. You can only bump the car like three times. I'm gonna get stuck here for like a half
an hour just trying to do this one jump. Oh, I just had it. Okay, you have to go tap, tap.
Ready? Okay. Can I make the whole thing? Imagine people actually speed running this. Holy shit,
this would be ridiculous. It's gone. Gone. You gotta be perfect or it's not gonna happen.
Shit. Shit. Shit. I don't have to go fast. No. Stop bouncing off a wall.
Ooh. All right, now what? Holy shit. No! I can do it. I can do it. I just gotta be more
careful. Slow down. Don't be an idiot. Ow, my head. I used to have bunk beds with my brother
around. I used to do that all the fucking time. I might do it already. By the way,
top bunk sucks. You have a bad dream and you wake up and you end up in the fucking ER
and you smash your head against the ceiling. Just do it again. Just do it again. Do it again.
No, top bunk is not good because every time you're in the top bunk,
when you close your eyes and you fall asleep and then you wake up in the morning whenever,
your face is just three inches away from the ceiling and you're just like,
every single time you have a mini panic attack and you can't be too panicky because if you're
too panicky, you're gonna freak out and bump your face and break your nose.
All right, we're good. We're good. What about up here? Secret? Yep.
Damn it. I thought I had it clean. No, not clean. Clean it up. No, top bunk is never fun.
It really isn't. Shit. And bottom bunk is, bunk beds all suck. There is no good bunk bed
because guess what? You've got, if you're on the bottom bunk, you've got a potential fucking
landslide hazard of the person above you collapsing on top of you and crushing you.
Sometimes, I remember, I had the bottom bunk before and you'll hear the person above you
rolling around like freaking and shit and you're like, this thing's gonna fall and
pancake me. I'm dead. I don't want somebody right above me, like 300 fucking pounds above me.
That thing is gonna crush you like the Terminator. Not yet. Not to mention,
what if somebody like pisses the bed? You're gonna get sprinkled on. Pee isn't
gonna seep through that mattress and hit you right in the head. There it is. Up. No.
No, bunk beds are not. I don't like that. All right, I'm back here.
Easy. Gentle. Gentle. Gentle. Okay, here it is. I'm out. I'm dead. You gotta be going faster than
that. Oh, I'm gonna get addicted to this level and I'm gonna fucking sit here all night.
I would rather sleep in a twin bed with like four people than have to worry about somebody
like some 400 pound dude above me in a bunk bed about to collapse on me.
I don't know why I'm assuming that the person above you in your bunk bed is 400
pounds. That person would be on the bottom, but you never know. Some people like at the top bunk.
Oh my god. Okay, I need to pay attention. Let me just, let me try to beat the stupid fucking
video game. Damn it. Let me at least try to get to that spot one more time.
This level is hours long. Well, let me at least try to get to the top there.
I didn't, I didn't get that. How did I not get that? I was touching it. Go up.
Ow. Moving to the rest of the screen? No, I'm not gonna. What's with this forward movement
and bullshit? Like I'm obviously going forward. Like what's, why is it hanging like that?
It's car mechanics. They need to fucking patch it. It's broken, I think. Here we go.
No, it's car mechanics. Car mechanics is what I thought. I heard.
I was on the forums. I was on Super Mario, Nintendo forums.
There's a huge apology post from Nintendo about the car mechanics. I don't know.
Specifically it was, um, it was written in Japanese so I had to translate it. So I might
not have the whole picture, but they were saying that the car mechanics are like all messed up
and that they were working on it. God damn it. Why? This first jump is so finicky.
You're wasting time of your life playing this game. This life. This level. You're
wasting your life. Don't remind me, Bob. Oh my god. I'm gonna jump on top of it. I'm
gonna jump on top. I wonder if that's why we're reliable, right? I can get over now.
You have to jump from this one to this one. I'm gonna try it. Here we go.
Trying to get this part clean is important. It's right here. Bang. Got it. Okay. Clean.
First part is decent. Shit. No. How did it just go? All right. Back to it. I gotta make
this jump, jump, jump, and then all the way. So we gotta do it early. Stupid. It's
not gonna be fast enough. Oh! What? What do you mean? How do I get that car? What? Does
he show up behind me? Hold on. I can't. I have to park the car in front of that thing?
Are you serious? He doesn't know? Tell me. Tell me. I want to know. I don't know. I
don't know. But what do I do? What do I not know? Tell me. Is it important? Is it critical
information that I don't have? Tell me. So park it. Shit. Wait, should I just drive over
and turn left? Turn on comments. Comments aren't going to help me, I don't think.
Damn. This is the hardest jump in the level right here. Just trying to get on
top of this from here. Pixel perfect. Pixel perfect. Pixel perfect. This thing, I gotta
fucking last any longer. Did I just, what just happened there? Did I, why did I just
throw the car like it was an item? What just happened? I just ghost rid the car into the
wall. I ejected out somehow. Oh, I know why. Because I leaned forward and my trigger
button hit the desk. Gave a rage. What the fuck keeps happening? Seriously? That's so
irritating. It's, what am I bumping? Oh my, okay, something's wrong. Something's wrong
here. Something's wrong. There's actually something wrong. There's something wrong.
What's wrong? Okay. Found out what was wrong. Good. Good. Good. The controller
wasn't plugged in. No, alright, quiet, quiet, quiet. I'm gonna get it right here. This is it.
What the fuck is happening right now? Well, something's, something ain't right here.
Well, there's sub only. What the fuck was that? Turns out there's only 30 real users
in this chat. That was fucking crazy. Um, settle down. What are you, what are you doing?
That was a lot of clapping. Yeah, it was. Now hold on. Now I gotta pay, I gotta pay attention
to the game. That was like, okay, that's the equivalent of you looking down and seeing 300
ants on the ground. You're like, hold on, wait, what the fuck is happening right now?
Hold on, hold on, I gotta take, there's ants in here. Start from back here. My god.
So, we're gonna have to keep it on for a little while. Just use the dev path? I'm
not gonna use the dev path. I will only use the dev path when I, you hear me say,
no, I'm not, I'm not doing this anymore. No, I'm not, this is fucking stupid. This is
fucking dumb. This is fucking stupid, fucking stupid. Once I start doing that, then yeah.
Once I start using the F word as every other vowel, then yeah, I swear to god, I don't
understand this one. This one feels like it works 40% of the time. How do you do the
jump at the end over here? You have to turn and then jump and then turn? Oh, there's
something wrong. There's something wrong. I'm gonna give this 10 more tries and then
I'm actually done. We're gonna move on. This is not gonna be one of those streams
where I sit here for an hour and 45 minutes trying to get through. It's not gonna happen.
Wait, I got this so much more to see. There's so much more to see. It is very
addicting though, and that's the problem. All these levels are just so addicting
because they're so meticulous and, all right, don't blow it. How do I get this? I have to
turn in midair and try to not flash. I crap. I ain't going down. Desert butts.
Nine more. Yes, keep track because yeah, I want to be held accountable for that.
Why does it not work half the time? No, I'm trying to think of an effective way.
No, why won't it jump when I land on this? I'm spamming the button too.
Ten Savovsky. Thanks for the 10 community subs. Oh, don't give subs. What are you thinking?
Don't do it. Don't do that. What are you thinking? All right, I'm starting to hate this
level only because of this part. Yeah, I'm sorry. I hate it. I'm getting there. I only
got seven more levels. I don't even understand. Oh god, I don't know where to go.
I, okay, let me try this one more time. Come on, I have to get over there from here and then jump
again. Oh my fucking god. Six more. I ain't doing this all night. I don't have this figured
out either. The creator of this level is laughing at you. Hey, dude, you made these
fucking crazy awesome levels and shit, but hey, can you make one, just edit this one
and make it like 10% easier and give it to me? And then I'll be like on stream beating it.
I'll be like, what the fuck, dude, this is so hard, but like, nice, but this level's
stacked all. Which one is this one? I don't know what to do here. I have to land and then,
but if I crash, turn before landing, that's what I was trying to do, but I lost momentum
and went down the hole. I have to figure out because when you jump, you just crash into
that wall. I do it every time. No, these stupid treadmill. Come on. No, I'm getting your tube
angry. What the heck's going on here? Yikes. All right, right here, jump down. That was it,
but I didn't jump again. My controller broke. No, it's not. No, no, it's not going to,
that doesn't work. It takes so long for your car to turn around, but by the time you turn
around again, you're already down the hole. It takes like a full second and a half to turn
the car over and go forward. I'm just going to crash into the wall. You'll see. This jump,
no, fuck this jump. Give me another copy of this, except like drop this thing here by like 8%.
Okay, here it is. I'm just going to crash directly into the fucking wall
because I obviously am not capable of doing this. Okay, that's one crash. Two more crashes
allowed. My God. See, you have to perfectly land on that. Turn left and then turn right
on the dime. Eventually, when the scientists can like come together to beat this.
Now I know why it has a 0.64% completion rate. That's probably the percentage of
scientists that exist on Earth right now. I would probably say that 0.64% of all people
are probably a scientist, right? All right, this is my last try. Last try before I skipped the
level. Wait, the dev is giving advice in the chat. Dev is giving advice. Well, I can't see.
There's a million names going by. Dev, but how can the dev, is the dev a sub?
He's like, I got a sub. This motherfucker's doing this all wrong. All right, so how do I get past
this first jump? Give me the secrets. You got to land on that conveyor, turn around,
and then spam jump at the end. Fuck. That's too hard. Spam jump. It's too hard. I'm going to
try it. I'm going to try to land, but the conveyor belt is so scary. Don't backseat him.
That's not backseating. That's advice. If you were to tell me that what I was doing was
wrong, therefore do my way, and that's right, that's backseating, but saying, hey,
like, you know, if you do it this way, that is what I'm talking about. So stop backseating me,
please. I swear to God, man. No, I got to get up there and try this one more time.
I have a strict don't backseat me policy in the channel. I'm trying to spam jump up here.
It's been like an hour. I don't want to do this all day.
This is the first viewer level. I can't do it. I got to give like a time limit.
Why? Why? I keep hitting my head on the goddamn bunk that I swear to God.
I'm of the opinion that you just throw dice in the air to get that jump.
Did you get a six? You get to go. All right, here we go. Time to actually get across.
No, you mother fucker. Why? God, why does it bounce so far back?
You launch backwards, always in that hole.
Shit. Oh my God. Like, un-fucking-bearable. Un-fucking-bearable.
This level was designed to make you hate the game. That's what it's here for,
and it's not working. I'm not going to let it work. Mario Maker 2 is fucking sick.
I'm not going to let some maniacal, maniacal developer try to take the fun away from me.
How do you fast-forward a screen? Well, there's a new feature on Twitch.
What you do is you have to, never mind. Rude. I didn't say anything. I didn't even say
anything. What do you mean rude? I didn't even open my mouth. He was about to say something
rude. No, I wasn't. Okay, don't screw it up again. I screwed it up again, but it's okay.
Okay, here we go. God. No way. No way. No way. Why did you do this? Why, why did you do it like
this? Why did you, like, make that extended by, like, one block? Why does he have to, why do
you have to do it like this? Why? The dev is in the chat. He can't quit. If I quit now, then,
like, I mean, this is his master creation. This is his master creation. Okay. Holy shit!
No! Oh! It was there, but it's too, it's too perfect. It needs to be too perfect.
Nobody's perfect. It was really close, but then I have to do the whole second half of the level
and I'm not prepared to do that shit. I just looked at chat because somebody said,
no, there is no raid right now. All right, everybody relax.
Even if I get through, even if I get through this part, which I'm not going to.
You know how much, I mean, maybe I could. If I spent another two hours here, if I would do it,
I have, if I crash the car, it's over. Things are going to split.
So I'm going to crash it right now. Holy fuck. Okay. Nope.
Um, so remember when we talked about sauces and shit and how I was on mild sauce,
where I was eating, like, a tomato out of a can? This is buying pure capsaicin
from the internet and putting it in your eyes. I, yeah, I, I just,
I kind of want to just go back and eat my taco.
Fortnite. Why? Okay. Why would Fortnite be here?
Somebody gifted Fortnite a sub. Yeah. You can gift anybody a sub.
Imagine if Fortnite, the Fortnite channel rated this stream. That would be so stupid.
All right. I'm going to get it. Jump down. God damn it. How do you do this?
How are you supposed to do that? It's not possible. I understand how that's even possible.
Turn and spam and it's been an hour. It has almost been an hour.
I'm going to give it at least, but this is, I can't just like give up.
Let me just get to the end of this. Can we, can we just fucking pretend that if I get
inside that exclamation cube that I beat it? Oh my fucking God. Why do I turn around?
Because the dev told me I had to do that because if I don't turn around, I drive,
it's a conveyor boat. So I drive directly into the wall and then I bounce off into the hole.
That wasn't the dev. You have to like land right on the edge and jump immediately.
Oh my God. Okay. I'm not reading the chat right now. I got, you know, sometimes I
think about this. Why would I, why, why would I want to sit here and stick small needles into
myself? You know, this is just, this is sticking like 5,000 small needles into my skin.
This is a whole game here. There's an entire video game here. I don't need to do the,
the needle level. You need to do the needle level. No, why do we have to do needle levels?
What happened to world 1-1? Okay. What happened to world 1-1? When everyone just enjoyed themselves
and I beat 1-1. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Now the video gaming in 2019 is, that's not enough.
I need to do world 1-1 blindfolded while you stick me with pins. We're in just,
yeah, we're in constant conflict. This is the last try, last try. This is it, this is it.
Everyone's going to say, oh, you're a quitter. I can't believe that. I beat,
I beat the last boss of Sekiro. That's all I care about. I don't care about this. I'll,
I will eat those needles. I won't eat these ones. Oh God. No, no, no, no, no, don't cry.
I don't care if you call me a quitter. It doesn't matter. I already had my 2,000
calorie a year diet of needle games. Sekiro's, I beat the last boss of Sekiro. That's all
I care about. I know people that haven't done that. Personal people, I know people
personally that haven't done that. It's like, what do you got? Come on. Can't do this one?
Whatever. That game's easier than Dark Souls. Oh God. How dare you? Oh, I did it. What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do? Where's the depth? Where's the depth? Turn? What do we turn?
Go in the box. What do we turn? I don't know what you're talking about.
What's wrong? When you hit the block? What do we, I don't, does it, does it come with me?
Drive into it. Go slowly into the box. But I can't go slow. Just working fast.
180 the car into the box. Just go forward. I ca-, oh! Okay. Now what do I do? But what do I do?
If I'm hitting one more thing, I'm dead. Is there a, is there a checkpoint?
There's gotta be a checkpoint here, right? Oh shit. I have one more hit and this
fucking model T is gonna fall apart. Ooh. But now what? Hold on. Ooh! Ooh! Jesus! Oh
my God! Oh my God. It's so hard. No, it's right here. What? How the fuck are you supposed to get?
You, really? Really? Like, no. No way. Uh-uh. I ain't going over any more cakes. No,
fuck these cakes. I'm not doing it anymore. I'm not doing any fucking vanilla frosting
bullshit. I'm out. I need a fresh car going in there. Fresh car. All right. How did I do
this last time? You have to jump like up and then I don't even know. It was dumb luck.
Broken clock is right twice a day. And I can't even do this shit. Here we go. No, it was,
I, I, I can do it. I know I can. I can do it. Not if it's a digital clock. But if you,
yeah. But it's, I'm talking about an analog clock. It's been an hour, but it's all right.
This is like, this is, it's just, I'm, I'm, I'm in it. I'm getting pretty good at this
part. I just got to nail this down. You got to do it early, early. Oh, fuck me in
You got to jump high and then turn and then jump.
You fucking asshole. Oh, I just, it's like anything else. Once you get to a certain point,
your brain just refuses to let you leave because it's some cost fallacy, but it's
not even sunk cost because I've seen some, I've seen some progress. Okay. If I was driving into
this first wall over and over again, maybe, but I, I got up there. I just want to see,
I want to do it. I want to be the 0.6% of people that have done it. I can do it.
Still in Anor Londo, but we don't care. I care. This is a personal goal for me.
Yeah, slow down. Oh, it's too hard. Whatever. People are going to call me out. I don't,
doesn't matter. Doesn't matter. Hey, you know why? You know what? Hey, I'll tell you why I
don't care. This is why I don't care. Cause 0.64% of people have beaten it. So if this 3,600
people watching this, like only, only like eight of you have done this. So I don't care.
That doesn't bother me at all. I'm out. It hurts, but I can't just,
ugh. I want to beat it so bad. I'm going back to that later. What's this one? Let's try this
one. Okay. This one is 130, no, 130. VG2, M9G. The dev is proud of you? Well, he'll be,
you'll be even more proud of me when I beat it. This is called Bowser's Challenge.
I'm the first one to play this one. And it says kinda hard. All right. I'll be the judge
of that. I am the guy that got a fourth of the way through. Um, I don't even remember
the name of the level because it was still long ago. Homing missiles. Oops.
I'm so used to the car. I've only done car. I haven't done anything else but car. What,
what, what's that flame mean? Oh, no, I'm fine with cake Luigi. Oh shit. All right. So
I have to, another hour. No, this one's just says kinda hard. I see the fire now.
I gotta blow this up. I can't kill him. So we gotta blow this up.
Holy shit. Okay. This is, I'll get there. Oh, okay. Hold on. Slow down. Slow down.
Holy shit. I had it. Oh, I've had too much coffee today. I need to like, how do you get
reverse coffee? All right. Watch it. Kinda hard. This could be, this could be fire.
I don't know what's up here. Yep. I told you. So we got, all right. Uh, we got,
they go back and forth. There is a flame there. I'm going to go now and then, oh shit. Um,
go now? Go now? Now? And then what's the, what's the, what's the, wait. Up and over.
Follow the cubes. Holy fuck. Where do I go now? Oh my God.
Man. Give me another one. All right. That's not, that actually sucks. That's going to be annoying
because I just got lucky. Wait. Now I gotta go easy. Jump over the first one. Wait till
the flame comes up and then go across. No. God damn it. Let me try this again. I have plenty
of time depending on how long it is. How often does it come up? Dang. It's going to do it
again here. So like right now. And then I got hit. Okay. That's the one I got hit by.
All right. Same deal. He's going to shoot it out. Why did he not shoot it out? Why did it
take an extra second to fit? That was, that was like timed exactly from when I was going to
land and jump again. Out of my way. Let's go. I can make that. All right. Watch this.
Here comes the second fire. Ready. I have to wait one cycle here. No. Holy shit. Wouldn't
idiot. Okay. I'm fine. All right. Now this time. Here we go. He's going to pop out now.
He's going to stand on it. Got it. Now what? I'm so paranoid. Okay. Uh, homing
bombers. I see the tail of that fire thing though. Oh shit. Oh my God. Oh no.
Oh, I forgot that if you jump up that you stuck up there. Do a demon screech. Not that
I'm not going to do a demon screech. I wasn't even mean by the way. That freaked me out.
It freaked me out because I couldn't see where I was jumping. It freaked me out.
And that's what happened. I went too fast. Demon screech. No. When are they going to add
save States to Mario maker? I want them. He's kind of lost his mind folks. All right. Wait,
just do it now. Okay. I'm fine. Now here we go. This is, uh, just be careful. All right.
Oh, okay. Oh no. No, don't shoot. Don't shoot. It's going to shoot. No fall. Oh no. Oh no.
He's going to jump. He jumps right. He jumps. Does he jump again? Oh, I did it.
That was tricky. Oh, I'm so, I'm so shaky. Somebody did it in 44 seconds. Sorry. It's
4% completion rate. There's like 50 people did this bongo man's the only other person that did
it. Let's try this one. Brody and weapon. Put one in here. Let's give it a try.
Comments. Oh shit. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, back it up. Back it up. I don't
want to do that. How do I back up? How do I hit B? How do I hit B? Do I hit B? I can't
move. Is it B? Which one is make sure this doesn't happen? The big X. I can't move. I
can't hit the X in the top right corner. Should I hit? No, it's an X. Is it B or X?
Touch the X. I, I'm going to touch it. Okay. I'm going to. Okay. I got it. I got it. I got
it. I had to rip the console out. Okay. We're good. Where I can't see it now. Okay. I
didn't know. I would have been such a bad look. What a bad look. WDGQXT9PG. I was so
embarrassed right there. I thought that that was like going through. Haunted house car ride.
Okay. Here comes another car. It's probably going to be. All right. Let's go this way.
Here we go. Haunted house car ride. Do I still need the car? I think I need the.
Yeah, that was an oof moment. All right, Luigi. Can I? Yeah, you can just run people
over. How are you? Oh, that's the scary part. I get it. Oh, that it's a little trick there.
They make you jump on it. Oh, shit. Okay. It's Luigi's mansion. Luigi's car. Oh, that was the
joke. I actually hit the comedy part because he spits at you and jumps and you land on it
and it messes you up. I didn't even trigger the comedy part last time. So shoot it. Now we
go. Oh, wait. Okay. I shouldn't be jumping. Why do I die? I don't know. I guess you can't.
I thought for some reason I was going to be able to. It was just a bad car accident.
That's just. Yeah. All right. Here we go. They laughing at me again because I went.
I thought the thing that they were laughing at was the. Go on. Spit the thing.
Oh, it's a fucking yeti. Somebody found Sasquatch.
Stop laughing at me. Do I get double car? All right. I want a new car. This car is broken.
What? What was I supposed to do there? I just. You can't tell me you would have done the same
damn thing. I mean, you would not look. I'm trying to complain to chatter. You would have
done the same damn thing. Oh, shit. Here it comes. No, I'm good. I pressed it. I was jumping.
I was pressing V. Why? Damn, I fucking went. Mario. What? No, it's not even Mario.
It's the shitty green one. I forgot. Oh, I just made a lot of people angry. Do I have to take
the car in? No, let's do it. I did what I was supposed to do. Sick. Three minutes,
44 seconds. 13%. That's still pretty good. See what people have to say. I wonder how many comments
are going to be about me. Hmm. He can't reach it. That's pretty good, Jerma Hart. Plus two,
Jerma Good. That's pretty good. That was fun. That was a good one. Let's try. This is the
first one I just saw. Let's do this one. This one is one of the first ones I saw. Let's do
CDD. KHW. I do like that a lot of you guys are playing along with it. That's fun.
This is called MonkaS in 3D. Is there already a comment? Good luck. Oh, all right. I wonder.
I'll give it a try. Let's see. This is in 3D. That's right. Speedrun. What did I do?
All right, so you get a ball jump. Go get Bigfoot. No, Bigfoot's not coming out again.
All right, power block. What do I? He's just in the way. Um, I have to jump over this and then,
but how? Oh, the spikes come down. I get it. Oh, God. Speaking of spikes coming down.
Quickly. Go. Do the P. What the fuck? Oh, um, how do you get through that?
You have to let him push you to the other side? Oh, really? Oh, that's unfortunate.
Just don't die. Oops. All right. Well, let's go, go, go, go. How do I?
Ah, shit. Oh, my God. Now. Okay. You have to jump and then grab the side and then jump up
to the hole and you got to do that fast. Insanity music is playing. Yep. Come on.
Really? I'm so close. Got it. I missed a coin. It doesn't matter. It's not to try to
get every coin to try to get to the end of the level as fast as you can.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry. All right. We're good.
Cling to the side. Side. Oh, my God. Just jump up there. I would have just lost. Oh, shit.
Now what do we do? Up. Oh, no. The lava's rising. The lava's rising. Um, is it gonna
come back up? No. I thought it was gonna go the other way. Speedrun ruined, but whatever.
Mr. Spicy Dude, thanks for the five community subs. I can see them and I can still play.
Thank you, Spicy Dude. Okay. Do I need to jump? Oh, I need to jump over now. I have to go
down. So I was right the first time. You got to go over there as fast as you can because
it dips down and then comes back up. Okay. I just leaned to the mic to do that. That's like,
I'm getting to a point where I like settle down. You know what I mean? Like calm down.
Got it. That's what I wanted. Okay. Come on. Get down there and grab them.
This is how people turn into fucking animals. I'm turning into fucking Teen Wolf. This is
what it feels like to be an Animorph. Why do you always yell into your glass? Because
it muffles the sound and it doesn't peek and hurt your ears. So I scream into the mug
and nobody can hear it. How do I scream and nobody can hear it? Because it's muffled.
That's just what we call, what do you call that? A complaint in the official review.
I almost touched that. That was really close. Get up there. I swear to God, I gotta stop.
I gotta fucking, God, I'm gonna lose my mind. Can I just hold onto the edge forever? No,
you start sliding down, don't you? I had it my first time too. That shit is fucking insane.
That's actually insane. And then we got this shit. I forgot about this. All right, calm down.
I gotta make it to the other, here we go. Now we jump up and we go over now. Quickly, get up.
Is there another one? Oh, you! No, why would you do that to me? Why would you do that to
somebody? It was so, it was there. Why would you do that? Come on, that's just not fair.
This is not fair. That womp jump is so hard. Are you gonna kaizo block me?
Okay, now where was it? It was up and then, relax. Here it comes.
All right, where's the, where is it? It's like right up here. Trigger it, where is it?
Where is it? Where is it? There it is. Oh my God, you did it again. What, I can't go in
there. Can I go up? What's that even there for? Hey, hey! What? Should I, should I,
do I need the momentum to do this? I don't, oh man, oh man. I just freaked out walking
the thing. Off the spring, would a long jump go across that whole thing?
I feel like I would just hit the ceiling. Oh, come on. I'm so close. I can't just give
up now. I'm so close to these. What are you doing, Jeremy? What are you doing? All right,
kaizo blocks are up here. Go up one more. Why? Come on, I can't handle this shit.
Come on, I was trying. I was pressing it as lightly as I could. I gotta go up the right
side to follow all the way and go up the right side. Okay, why couldn't I go up there? Why
couldn't I go up? I was trying to, oh my God. You have to jump early. You have to go to the
right side early. What is happening? The Yeti game was good? What's a Yeti game? I'm the
only person that's ever died on this map. All right, well, how about this? I 100% guarantee,
this is a 100% guarantee that when I get to the end of this,
there's going to be less than 5% of people who completed it. I 100% guarantee.
So you want to talk shit or bring out the fucking Yeti. No, I'm not going to.
I can't even do this part now. And he's going to go full Yeti. He is. I stopped
that as hard as I could. Oh my God, stop it. It happened again. I was trying to stand on
the front and I fucking can't. I can't. I was trying to stand on the front,
but you have to keep moving with it. Oh my God. I'm trying to stand on the front,
but it moves faster than you can run. It just pressed it. What is the actual completion rate
on this? What is it right now? I want to know. Get the fuck out of here. Get the
fuck out of here. What am I doing? I'm like overthinking. I'm listening to chat. Crouch,
crouch, crouch. No, no, no, no, no. I'm just doing it. Progress towards the Yeti. The Yeti
is going to unleash in a minute here. The Yeti is coming. It's currently 0%. I'm bringing
out the Yeti. What happened there? What was going on there? I can feel him. I can feel
him just rowing. He's in here. He's trying to get out. He's like, I'm going to get out
a couple more times. You die in a row and then, you know, you look over chat and they call you
like a fucking idiot. I'll be out just soon enough. Don't worry about me. I'll be out soon
enough. And I'm like, no, you won't. Oh, yes, I will. Don't fuck it up. Okay. All right.
Here we go. Let's go. Let's go. We're in. We're in. I told you. I told you I'd be out
soon enough. He's no longer with us. It's just me. What the hell? I swear to God,
I jumped there. It was so obvious, but I jumped. This is what I would call that
bullshit for my neck of the woods. That looks better. All right. It's a jump. Here we go.
Oh, what happened? I'm playing still. I'm good. Oh, what happened? You couldn't fucking do it either?
Oh, you couldn't do it either, could you? He's nowhere to be found. Not going to fucking say
anything, huh? Okay. How do I make the jump with the spring? I don't get it. Do I just
not press any buttons at all? Oh, listen to my voice. This is how people lose their
fucking minds. This is how people go crazy. But how do I have to jump? How? I don't understand.
Do ZR? Like the Biahu? Do Biahu? How do you do Biahu? I tried to do it twice.
I tried to do it twice. I tried. I can't. These games. These games. This is why I don't play them
because I'm going to have to go to the doctor after this. I'm going to have to go to the
doctor to get described like time it all. PM. So I could sleep. I'm going to wake up in the
middle of the night screaming about the Yeti that's coming to get me. I'm going to have
fucking nightmares. Oh, what? Prescription for Tylenol. Do you like this? Is this what you want?
Is this what you wanted? No, I'm not going to give it to you. I'm slowing down now.
I know that that's a joke. Can you please stop dying as a joke? I know you're not serious,
but for some reason, for some reason it's infuriating me. It's making me so mad.
And I know it's bullshit. I know it's not even real, but it's like when you go to the movies and
you watch the bad guy do something bad, you're like, God, that's bad. That bad guy, he's a
mean person. You know that person's not real, but it still makes you feel bad.
Like in the movie, I don't know. I'm trying to think of a movie. I don't want to get
spoiled. No, jump. I got to jump. Fuck, stop. Fuck, stop it. Who had German loses on an easy level
on that? It's not an easy level. It's not easy level. No, it's not. No, it's not. It's not. I
can prove that. Yeah. Yeah. Twice in a row quickly. It's going to get up there first.
This is the part that sucks the most for me is just trying to stay on that first block.
What happened? You're actually watching somebody live on Twitch lose their mind. I'm
going to get to the end of this and I'm going to be one of like seven people to beat this level.
And I will be able to say that I did it. No more half skips. I'm going to beat this.
There's hair going down. I'm going to cut my hair. My hair's too long for it to play
Mario Maker because your hair gets in your face. All right. Oh, okay. Two, two, uh,
yahoos. Okay. What do I do? Should I go? I have 86 seconds, but what does this take me?
What the hell? He's coming at me. I can't fucking do it, man. It's not fair. It's not fair.
It's not fair. He's coming at me. Am I getting charged by a bull or am I playing
a Super Mario game? Am I ducking behind like a chair to get away from the bull?
Here he comes! I can't. I can't. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm hitting. I'm getting hit.
I gotta get it together. It's hitting. That stupid fire guy that just didn't let me get it.
I'm not going to be able to ever play another video game again. They're all going to be this
level. It's breaking. I did the jump so good too, and then I got LOL momented.
Okay. Excuse me. What happened to the game? Because that was very- what happened? Why would
it not stick? Sometimes it just doesn't feel like sticking. I'm gonna start drinking.
I'm gonna start drinking. I'm gonna just go grab a bottle of wine and we're gonna win.
I'm gonna drink. Let's drink. I'm gonna start drinking wine. I have to beat this level. It got
stuck. Something's going- it needs to be recalibrated or something. I don't understand.
Take a shot every time you die. How about I take a small sip? And I mean like a tiny one.
Something's wrong. Something's actually wrong here. I'm losing it. Something's wrong.
No. Something's wrong. Something's wrong. Here we go. Something's wrong.
Waited too long.
You do this to yourself. I fucking even get by this anymore because I keep hitting my head on
the ceiling. That jump sucks. Oh, unbelievable. You only got to beat it once. That's true.
That is true. This is hair in my mouth. Okay. All right. Just yahoo, yahoo, yahoo, yahoo.
Not a big deal. Just yahoo. Okay. Go! Just hold right. Go! Holy shit! What? I don't know what
to do about this! I'm now an anime fighter. I just powered up and yelled my move. But how
are you gonna deal with this? I'm gonna fucking lose my mind every time I make progress.
There's another thing I have to learn and then die because the spring is gonna launch me forward.
Oh, there's new things to memorize every time. I gotta be close to the end though. If I do this,
I get there again. Then I just jump, wall jump a few times. It's gotta be like the end,
right? It has to be. You're almost at like the bar you'll make your limit for amount of
assets, right? It has to be. All right. Let's try it again. Thank you. Okay. Wall jump.
There's just momentum was so much faster. There's so much more momentum off the spring.
Oh my god. I should probably shouldn't even use the spring. Can I just like,
80% done if I get to the wall part? Oh shit! There's more! There's 20% more!
I gotta knock it out of the park, but I gotta get that jump correct.
Spring and then over the wall and then jump over the wall. Okay, let's go. Okay, come on.
Just right off. Don't jump that high. Just jump a little. Small jump. Just a little one.
Hey! God damn it! I can go up around to the left.
There's not enough momentum. I'll jump right into the...
I'm gonna try to go around the left side. That looks like a hey. Try this way, maybe.
I just wanted to eat like mild hot dog, but this is eating. This is like the
can't you eat 50 hot wings challenge. I went in here with like my kids. I just... I just...
Hold on. I fucked it up. No, I didn't. Thank god I'm smart. I just wanted to come in here
with my children and get... Okay. Yeti's gone. No more. There's a man playing Mario Maker to
switch it up in my driveway and he... I'm not in your driveway. I'm in my house. Take the clear
pipe during the snake walk. I can't. It doesn't hug the wall. I was thinking about trying it.
It doesn't have to hug the wall. You know what I mean? Like it has to hug this wall, right?
Yeah, see? I can't grab it. I just ran into that shit. All right. I'm gonna try going to
the left side. No, I'm not. No. You just instantly get bounced and you're just dead
if you don't go forward. You just die. If you do not go forward, you are guaranteed to die.
You have to go forward. You can't like just go left. My stamina is starting to be depleted.
I don't even smoke cigarettes, but I might. My stamina's at risk. What the fuck? No,
what the fuck just happened? I... I gotta move on. I don't think I can take this anymore.
I don't... I don't think I can take this anymore. I don't think I can fucking take this
shit anymore. It's like so fucking hard. It's too much. You're so close. If it doesn't matter
how close you are, you could drive your car a hundred miles and have 90 miles worth of gas.
The car's breaking down. We're gonna start to put the damn thing in neutral and fucking
start pushing me. All right. I'm just gonna try to wall jump. I'm gonna just try. Here we go.
Here we go. Fuck. Now what? How do I go from here? How do I go from here?
Huh? What does he want me to do now? But what do I... What do you want me to do now?
I don't understand. Oh, wait, I understand. I understand. Did I make it? Did I make it?
Do I drive the car over this way? Did I make it?
Oh! This goofy falling off the cliff. Oh my god. This goofy falling off the cliff.
But he's covered in fire ants. Oh, come on. I had it. I can do it. I know what to do now.
Dude, that was about... That was probably the most embarrassing noise I've ever made
on camera. I really think so. It could be. That was really fucking embarrassingly loud
and weird and fucking strange. I'm not proud of that at all. Not at all.
Nothing about that is what I'm proud of. And I get to go around again.
And it goes faster the second time. Okay. Oh my god. I did that. I beat this part on all
adrenaline after this. And now... And now I have to do it again. Oh, I don't even know
if I'm going to be able to. No, I'm not! So defeated. I can do it. I know I can. Fuck.
But I'm sorry. I'm sorry this has taken so long. And I'm sorry that you're... Oh. Now
my proudest moment. Okay. Calm down. I can do it. It's not that bad. It's just precision
and just patience and... I can't believe it. I thought I was going to be able to move on
finally, but we're still here. That was the one. I can't believe I... But what do you
do there? I hit my head? I have to jump out of the car. I think that you hit the top
and then you jump out of the car. That makes sense to me. I'll try. All right.
Try it again. This part's the one that just rocks at me. Just don't jump. You just kind
of have to panic. Let's see what happens. I tried. I tried. I didn't jump. It didn't
jump. It didn't go forward fast enough. Oh my god. Guys. Guys. I just a little jump,
but it's just a little one. I think I've died two or three hundred times on this
level. Anyone have any idea? How many times have I died here? It's got to be at least
two or three hundred times. I've been here for at least 50 minutes at least, but this
one feels way more painful than the other car one. I don't know why. This one just is
pain. The other one was not pain. The other one was needles. Super Mario Man. Little jump.
Little jump. Little jump. Little jump. Little jump. He didn't do the little twirl. I could
guarantee after this would go. I'm doing it. I'm going. Not even mild. I'm just going to eat
ice cream on camera. I'm just going to eat ice cream on camera and I'm going to do the
easiest levels in the game. I'm going to use one hand. I fucking beat it. It's coming back.
I'm getting a flashback of that moment. Two people have beaten this level.
Oh Jesus. No. I just wasn't high enough apparently. No.
I'm going to do it. I'm going to do it. It'll be all right. Everything's going to be fine.
I just think I need to relax and just get it done. Oh, it's not okay. I'm going to get
it done. I don't think that's going to be fast enough. Somebody just said the word
jello. Don't do that right now. I'm so sorry for what I've done to your psyche.
Well, it's definitely good. Otherwise, I'm going to stop playing it. Oh shit, I forgot.
When you do something enough times in a row and then you start to just
wash over you. It just washes over you. Like for instance, I tried to wall jump,
but Super Mario Maker 2 sucks. So you can't grab on some time. What the fuck?
I swear to God, I'm going to be the third person to beat this level. I will. Can I get
like webcams of the other two people to beat this? I want to see your reaction.
Is there everyone that was telling me to jump in this pipe over here? Are you telling me
to do that? All right. I need to get a good grab onto the wall here because I've done this
twice now and I've gotten there and I've just hit that right at the edge. No, no, it wasn't
enough. I knew it. I knew it wasn't enough when I went up. I knew it wasn't enough. I knew
it wasn't enough and that's why I did it. I knew it wasn't enough. I just, it was wrong
and I knew it and I had to just accept it. It's not hesitation. I just wasn't high enough.
Even. I need to, I need to completely just like capitulate on this level and then I'll beat it.
I don't care about time. No, just step on it please.
Is it audio desync? I'll fix it later. I'll fix it when I go take my first break,
which will be in another three to four hundred attempts at this level.
No, no, no. That's gonna happen sooner. I just need to get it over with. I just
get it over with. It's all just math. It's all just math and assets. None of this is real.
There's no spikes. There's no fire. None of this shit's real. It's all math.
You just have to do it at the right second. It's just mathematics. I'm gonna do this one
mathematically and see if it works. There's no coins on the screen. There's no fire. There's
no Mario. There's no Luigi. It's just math. It's just math. It's only math. Come on.
All right, here we go. Two divided by four is two. It's three divided by five is six. Let's go!
Am I dead? Yeti bit. Hey, Durham, a good stream. PSP desert bus. I don't think I can.
My god, this level sucks.
Is that 56 minutes ago? 33, by the way. Thanks for the five community subs,
rip pepe body lotion. I know this is cheating, but I made this just for you.
You knew I was gonna come scroll down these. That was a good level. I'm probably 38 now.
All right. No, you got me. You got me. That's that. No, that's a good strategy. You got me.
TFP C7. This is cheating. C7H. Bim, bim, boi. Thanks for the five community subs.
Okay, now I have... I'm back. I'm back in action. I'm very fragile, as you guys know.
Let's do it. Okay, this is 38. I feel so happy. I don't have to do that anymore.
Oh, TFP. I can feel how red my body is. C7H. It's a one, not a seven. Oh, oh, the audio desync.
Okay. World 6-3, they're the rats. So the audio, the game audio is happening early.
Is that what somebody said? Let's see if that helps. You tell me. Ready? Should be
World 6-3, they're the rats. All right. Are they sing? Hiding in here?
Oh, this is a delicious, mild fucking run. Q-R-S-H. How do I get that? I gotta go up.
Don't kill them. I'm not killing them. I'm defeating them.
10 coins.
But yeah, so don't you know in every game that's not rated at least T,
these people are being defeated. They're not being killed.
There's a difference. What's in the door? Good thing I just touched that flag.
Defeating them kills them. No, it doesn't. It just crushes their head.
I love the rush. I told you, my stamina was deflated. My body, my soul left my body.
Like for the last 45 minutes. I'm not used to slowing down. That wasn't on the head?
I told you, there's only one level I know how to play. Oh, it's because he has spikes on his
back. I get it. That's not clear. That's not clear by the... I didn't realize that was spikes.
I thought that was just a hairstyle. Oh my god, that's kind of tricky actually.
The conveyor belts are hard to be on. I know, you're right. It's just a math problem.
You're right. What am I thinking? It's just math. I jumped too high.
That's fucking me. That's fucking me. It goes back and forwards. I'm not using it. I'm not
doing math. Why does Luigi jump like 5,000 feet in the air? Damn, this part is actually very
hard. You only have one real spot you can jump and the conveyor belts really fuck with
you. I'm just going to cross it. Like that. Damn, that's... it goes so fast. I'm gonna have to
clear him out. I'm gonna clear out the first one and then go back. Because that aggro's him.
And then I'm gonna have him jump. Kill you. And now I can just jump. Okay, got it. Although
I'm kind of screwed here. Spikes. Oh shit. Oh my god. Too fast. Too... Do I have to jump over that?
Jesus. It's so fast. And then this one goes the other way. And I can't kill those things.
Shit. Oh, I almost had it. Gonna stay here for a second. Wait.
Alright, finally. I made it with a big guy. That hasn't happened yet. Oh shit.
No. No. I'm gonna have to go back through this all again, aren't I?
Conveyor belts. I hate these things.
This is just fucking... it goes too... it's going too fast. It's going too fast.
You can't even land on the ground here. Do I just have to... I'm gonna try to just
jump over the spikes. No, don't get hit by the second rat again. The conveyor goes the other
way. It's hard. You lose so much momentum change when you jump from these things.
Let me see if I can do this. What the fuck just happened? No, fuck no. I can't even turn around.
What am I doing? Jump. Jump. Oh my god. I know the rats jump when I jump. I knew that when
I first walked in the door. You don't think I knew that? You think it's taken me this long
to figure that out? I'm turning into the fucking air conditioner from Brave Little Toaster.
I'm back. Hi, guys. You can't do that shit. You can't even go there. It just automatically...
You see what I'm fucking seeing? Just run underneath. You can't run underneath.
Did you see what just happened there, son? You can't run underneath them.
Stop telling me to run underneath that one. Son, you can't do it. I've tried it, son.
I just want to... Son, come into my office for a minute. I want to talk to you.
I don't care. I win. I guess eight minutes. Now get out of here, kid. Holy shit. How did
you draw that? Medium heat, salsa, and chips. I played my level. These are so good. Stop
acting. What a bad comment. The conveyor belt is just fucking me so bad. All right,
let's take one from chat. Let's take one from chat. P... Hold on. There's a fish there.
That means I have to use it. Let's try this one. No, no, stop, stop, stop. P-T-D-K-N-B-M-7-G.
Okay. What's this one? Mushroom and Men. Get the mushroom all the way to the end. Okay.
Reach the goal as Super Mario. All right. Sounds good. All right. No more screaming.
No more yelling. No more. I think I already lost.
Okay. I didn't know that. Okay. I got it. I got it. I got it. I'm not going to lose.
I just... Just wait. Don't make me get... Don't make me... Don't make me be dad again.
I'll turn into dad. What? Down? Oh shit.
Leslie? Um, what? I had to... I had to eat it. Come back. It'll bounce back.
And then we have to go across? Yep. Um, but then how do I get over there? Oh, down. Shit.
Yoshi, I'm sorry. Yoshi. I just like... I just like tortured Yoshi.
Okay. This is cute. I like this. What happens? Woof.
No. Oh god. I need a break. I do. I need to go like get a drink of water or something.
Hit it. Just hit the fucking thing.
You know what? Just hit it now. Hit it now where you have a shot. You don't have to...
This is just... Jeez. It's just my stimulation. I'm just stimulated is what it is.
What happened there? Stimulation's doing it to me, Peter. You fucker. You're in a simulation?
I think... I think I'm in a normal world. Why do you keep hitting the coin ones? Because
there's something wrong with me. You understand? All right. Here we go. You gotta be quick.
Oh shit. Go. What? No. What is wrong with him? Why does he do that every time? It's freaking
me out. It's making me so mad. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
Sorry. No. You're too... I'm too big. Why am I... I'm too big to do that. All right.
Yoshi can't come through there. Yoshi cannot go through there. He's too big.
So I really should just leave him. I thought I needed him for something.
Man. He forgot the coins. Easy. Easy. Fuck off, Yoshi. Yoshi, get... Yoshi, why did you... Why?
Just... Why? Get out of the way. I'm just dumping him. The second I hit, I throw,
I spit it out. You did that there. It's there on purpose. It's there on... It's on fucking
purpose that like this stupid spike is where I did a run into. Somebody just texted me.
It was like my mother saying, I'm watching you play Mario Maker and you really need to calm down.
I don't like this side of you. You were such a sweet boy. Now what? Get over there. I did it.
But is this not a puzzle anymore? There's a hard level. What's he doing? I don't like
that. I don't like this. Is he gonna go up? Uh-oh. Okay, he goes down. Wait, hold on,
but I need to... He goes across this. There's another mushroom that I have to take care of.
I have to have him go... Oh no. Okay. Hopefully I can get this... Otherwise it's the whole
thing again. Let's go. He made it. Oh shit. Now what? Oh my god, what do I do?
Oh my god. What's going on? Oh, should I have brought this with me? What the fuck is going on?
What? Wait, how is he... What happened there? The blue... Oh, fuck.
Pain in the ass. I just tried to run by that. Here we go. Oh shit. I got it.
All right, so now there's blue...
So what was I missing at first? Let me just look. So I didn't grab the blue thing to touch or
something? Okay, here we go. There we go. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. Now? Is that...
It worked! Wait, do I now take this with me? Do I take this with me?
I don't know what to do. It's gonna fall if I don't. It's probably already bounced.
Yeah, you gotta take this thing. If it's lying on there, if you use it, it's gonna just drop.
All right, well now I know what to do. See, mom, I promise. Everything's fine. It's not.
Yoshi, let's do it. You and me together. Yoshi. One, two, three.
It's a Rube Goldberg machine. Yeah, kind of. That's sort of what it looks like, yeah.
Wait till now. Grab the P and let's go. I gotta hit it now.
It was right there, but I thought it was ahead of me.
I thought I was panicking. I thought it was ahead of me. Shit. Oh well.
Well, it's right there.
That was a hair difference.
Is music making you sleepy? Wake up! All right, okay. I'm ready. I've prepared myself this.
I just have to wait till it gets across.
Let's go. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No. I beat him last time. Just relax.
What? Oh my god. But how would that... Wait a minute. Wouldn't that just fall down?
I'm just gonna walk ahead, but wouldn't that just make it fall?
I guess it would just go on top and then go forward. It wouldn't fall backwards though,
would it? This is the end of the level already.
It can do it. It's just slow. Oh, I don't know why. I figured it would just fall down.
I'll get stuck down there. Oh, Yoshi. You are the worst.
What happened there? I just, I did, I've done this part.
Stupid dog. You made me look bad. The one time my pixel jumped over his body.
You gotta be shitting me. Yoshi, move. I was gonna say, get out of here.
Too early. Too early. Too early. Too early. Okay, let's get it.
Mm. I'm so happy that I have to do this first part every single time. I love it. I am in love
with it. I call it classic pee pants. It's a classic pee pants moment coming up. No, the
fucking ice. I just have to carry. Oh my god. I just have to bring the button over,
when the stupid cannon shoots. What the fuck? Oh no, I'm so tilted that it's just that this
first half of the level, I want to just fucking tear it up and put it in a shredder. What just
happened? Holy shit, hold on. I just gave a trillion subs. Cyanide just gave 20 subs.
Thank you for the 20 community subs, cyanide. That's a lot. That's a ton. So I'm gonna do
this, but you know, I have to beat this. This is it. I'm gonna get it right here. Trigger the
cannon and then go. I'm gonna bring the pee pants all the way across. Trigger the cannon,
pee pants. Just run. Let's go. Put it down and get it. Got it? Holy shit, it's there. How do
I get it? How do I touch it? Oh my god, do I pick the coins up? No. All right, I got
eye pee pants. I was gonna say no way. Anything else happen here? What's going on
here? This looks weird. That was a fun one. That was a good one. All it took was 20 community subs.
That's all it took. See, I told you. That was clever. It was clever. It was. What the hell?
Some of you guys, I don't know how you guys do this in like 40 minutes.
Actually seven minutes. Here's an easy level.
Ha ha ha. Jerva bad. You didn't find the 10, 30, and 50 coins, but it's fine.
My turn. It's my turn. Here's one. Here's one. Report that comment. This is what the
feature's for, right? That's what the feature's for. I mean, come on. You can't, you can't do
shit like that. Nintendo's not, that's not all right. Nintendo's, that's not, that's against
Nintendo policy. And it's slander. This report will be sent to Nintendo. Hit the button. All
right. I'm doing it. I'm hitting it. It's inappropriate. All right. It's inappropriate.
Is that inappropriate? That's, that's inappropriate behavior. I'm gonna write,
I'm writing this off stream. It's too much work. No, it's not. It's just,
oh, I just almost turned the camera on. Do I, do I have to avoid comments now?
Let's try this one. Did I just lose it? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where
is it? Where is it? One WB, P, O, L, G, X, F or P zero. One WB. Wait, what was it? One WB,
P, O, L, G, X, F. Bob-omb's begin their attack. Blast a hole in the command ship.
This is the first, I think this is the first like Mario 2, Mario 3 level I've seen.
He's my favorite. I'm gonna, I always do really well on these ones.
It's down here. Missed coin, missed coin, missed coin. I know you guys are saying that.
Don't, I don't care. Missed coin, missed coin, missed coin. See that jump?
What's happening here? Oh, it's an explosion!
I thought I was gonna get the, uh, the star, the thing, the roulette, the slot machine thing.
Nice. Who cares about that? Kaizo blocked. Kaizo blocked. Careful. Careful now.
That'll be it. Got it. I do, yeah, I did well on that level. That was a second attempt.
And that's a world record. I like that one. All right, be, be nice here. I don't want to have
any other bullshit here. I'm not gonna abuse the system. That was good. Good, good level.
Let's try this one. This one has a sad face next to it because I got it. I got it. I'll
do this one. FPD TF2 with star. Searching for level. This is called Baki Baki Bone Chompers.
A lengthy challenge course of ice, bones, and infested chompers, please help. Lengthy. Lengthy
level. All right. Changes course. I'm gonna have to deal with this asshole the whole time.
You know when you sneak up behind a cat and you, the cat is really not paying attention at
all, and you get to right next to the cat's back and the cat just like freaks the fuck out
and jumps. That's what just happened. This thing's made it to ice too. Oh boy. I'm not ready for
this one. No, wrong. Wrong. Wrong. Is there one? Does it respawn? I dreamt a lot about
it. So don't change it. I'm just trying to jump on his head. Mad because bald. Wouldn't you be?
I'm almost there. If I was. What the? Get it. Get up there. I got it. That's it. That's all
it does for me. I guess there's nothing else here for me to do. Just 30 coins. 30 coins.
I gotta go over that faster. I can't just jump on that, can I? I'm gonna need a lot
of momentum for this. Oh I slipped. I have to do momentum jump, momentum jump, momentum jump.
It makes sense to me. Perfect. Slippery shit. Just stop. Please. No don't don't don't don't.
I fucked it up again. It's just been so. I did that. I can't believe I didn't get hit by that.
That was a miracle. All right. Out of the way. Out of the way. They disappear already.
The speed. It was so slow. I couldn't turn around fast enough. It's all ice.
It's all ice. This is the swamp level of fucking Mario games. Oh my god. You can't. You can't.
Holy shit. Do you see how slippery this is? It's turned up times 10 slippery. This is the most
slippery any fucking level I've ever played. I can't do it. I just slid across the whole
entire level. It's a it's a times 10 slippery. That's like when you go to McDonald's and you
order a fucking hamburger and they put a joke amount of mayonnaise on it because you say you
want extra mayonnaise and they're like okay fine and it's unedible. I definitely have to
get rid of him and then. Jeez. Oh come on. Is there another one? Thank god. Even this is
slippery. I don't go down this. Oh man. I need to break him right? Can I smash him? I'm
not gonna be able to make this. I gotta do it. I'm freaking the fuck out right now.
Go down. I can't. Down's not gonna help me. Go down. Go down. Go down. Go down. You have to
go down. What? No I don't. Oh you fucking dick. No I was wrong. I was wrong. I was wrong to do
that. I have to go back in this. How am I supposed to jump to there? I can't make that
jump from that little sliver. I need momentum to make that jump. Unless I do have to land
on that tiny little pixel. No. Fix it. Oh see it's over. I gotta get up here now.
Move please. I don't think I can make this. I'm gonna try. I can make it. Okay I made it.
Now I have to break these. I gotta just have some confidence man. Just no confidence at all.
Is there a spot? Is that land? Am I gonna die? Do I have to jump on the bones?
Holy shit. Um okay but the arrow was pointing down here. All right what is there a block that I
missed? I I guess I screwed something up. But the arrow. Yeah there was an arrow. This streamer
is yuck very boomer. Does he? Did you see that? What just happened there? That's called a cat
like reaction. I gotta jump. Oh you dickhead here. All right so now I just have to go around it or
across it. I think I'm just gonna try to jump gently here. Well if he didn't throw the damn
thing I'd be fine. Oh no I gotta bounce on his head to get up there. All right so why would
I turn that on? Secret key was the key. But so where is it? It's not just a it's a leap of
faith but well maybe just walk off the edge. But why would the arrow be pointing down there
if there's nothing there? Try trapping the fire in the blocks? That's not a bad idea.
Just barely missed that one. It's actually really hard to do this just that jump.
I guess maybe I could get him killed. But all right so how do I get the key from
me? All right let's try this. I don't think this is gonna do anything. Is there maybe a
thing to climb? Okay that just scared the fuck out of me. All right so what the hell do I
get a P block this? Go on the coins down there and then there's probably a P block down there?
I don't have any idea but I'm gonna go for it. There is and yeah okay.
All right yeah well I'm gonna get it. I'm gonna get it. Of course you put it right where you
have to jump. In both places. In both places. Fucking ice. Bakken gave 50 dollars. Bakken this
is your level isn't it? Thank you for the 50 bucks you say. I'm so sorry I sent you the
wrong code. I meant for you to play this one. I hate this level too. I'm so sorry. Wait what?
I don't I think it's pretty fun. It's tough. It's tricky. That's a seal of approval to skip
the level. I'm so close though. I gotta get that key and then be out of here.
You can't skip now. Not now. Oops that's perfect timing. That was the that was the
earliest hit box I could have had. Okay let's try it again.
Ag is gonna be patient. The P is gonna. All right this also. If that's possible.
I'm not sure it is. Okay here we go. I gotta time this right. So let's go right when it's
on the way down. You bastard! It's all slippery! Where is it? The whole thing is slippery!
Oh every surface is slippery. It's so slippery. Come on. This ice is fucking ridiculous.
Look at him go. Give me the damn thing. It's the it's the one to the left. It's not right in
the middle. It's not it's right to the left of it. All right come on. I can do this.
I just have to do it right. Look at the slipperiness.
You saw it there folks. Dude! Oh everything is slippery. You understand how slippery everything
even the blocks even these brown blocks are slippery. All right okay everybody calm down.
This is gonna kill me isn't it? What's the respawn rate on that?
Should I just dive in there and hit up? What is that? Why are you doing this?
Hahaha drop them both or at least I'm gonna wait till you're on the other side
like that. Holy shit. Okay I'm over. Everything's fine. Okay slow down. Is he gonna he's gonna
continue. I'm not gonna make it. I can't make it. I can't make it. That's gonna hit me. Okay
I can make it now. Where's the key? Where's the key? There's another key. There's another key.
Oh no. Where's the other key? Is it a hidden block? Oh no. Do I have to kill him? I don't think I can
kill him. That's gonna hit me. I don't think I can. I can't kill him. I don't think he dies.
Shit. That's a little pixel at the end. He's dead. Man. Man. MAN! I got it. Oh yes. Okay
I did it. I'm there. Thank god you have a checkpoint. Why would you have this? Thank god.
I was so mesmerized by the super escalator. What is that going to do when I touch it?
Yoshi can step on these. Right? What's with the scary music?
Why did that Yoshi just die? Okay now I need a new Yoshi. I need a new one. I thought that
was gonna kill me for a second and I was about to be very sad. Do this. Just jump.
Okay this is just freaking me out here. Way too much movement. Oh this is...
Is this... No here it is. There it is. What does this do for me? Where's it going? No. What? I need
Yoshi. Well now I have Yoshi. Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me. Okay. I have Yoshi now. Oh excuse me.
Okay. Come here. Stop getting so scared. It's not even scary. Trust me. Oh no no no no not like
this. Like that. All right. Then we go up. So then I gotta ride it up there. So where is it?
Okay I get it. Swing myself up and jump. Oh no. This is gonna take me up there. Okay.
Okay. Oh pig. So just... I did need Yoshi. It's a good thing I got him. You can't beat this
without Yoshi. Another checkpoint. Well you know let me tell you something. Thank you.
Because if there was no checkpoint here I would have quit this level. If getting to this far
and dying. Thank you for that. Two ways. I just wasted both of these. Just in case anyone's
curious though that was a complete waste. 100% waste of resources. What? I'm so confused. I just
gotta keep. Can I do it with being small? Holy shit. I'm fine. Watch out for those pixels.
Okay. That's the easiest jump I've had to do all night and I just seriously just closed my
eyes and just died. Well now I'm not gonna waste these. Try it again. Really I didn't make that.
How did I not make that? That's bullshit. I thought that was a tunnel to go into. Not tunnels
that turtles came out of. Chasing the goal until I die. What? What? Okay. Did you see that?
I want to make sure that people rewind that. Get a clip of that because why did I speed
up? Why did I go so fast? Why is it going? I don't get it. Why am I going so fast?
Well Germany because you have forward momentum. No I don't. Almost did it again but I
saved it. Okay one key. You know what? Kill that guy. How many keys do I have? Can I store
them? I don't think I can store them. Don't touch it. All right let me try to get through
this member. I can do it. No I usually go by now. I screw it up. I usually have momentum
here and I make the jump but now I'm all screwed up. Yep see? I told you and I knew
it was gonna happen because I waited too long. Watch out for this. He was about to just
tele-frag me. Am I gonna go now? Ambushed. I gotta go this way first. See when you got
that momentum you just go and you get it done. I won't get hit by anything except
for that one pixel. I told you. This bone shit's really done to piss me off.
I got- I'm itchy. I'm breaking out hives right now I think. Did I say that I was
gonna smoke a cigarette earlier? Don't do that. It's not good for you. I can't be serious
here. Good. This is gonna be hell. This is gonna be hell. Yeah I think so. I gotta
get that side done first because there is- I'm probably gonna say close to 100% no chance
that I will do the- this side last. So I gotta be confident and get this one done.
However I do. You know what I mean? What if I just don't spawn them? No they're gonna be
spawned. What if I drop their wings? I think I have to- no I can't take them up. There's
no way I can get them. Maybe if I- I guess I can like drop the wings but then he'll just
be on the ground right? I think I just made it worse.
Because those bones fill up the whole screen. You ain't gonna fucking do that.
Might as well just fucking call it quits right there if I don't make that.
I can go for a smoke right about now. No don't smoke. Why did it not jump all the way?
That was- the gas just flew up out of my body. I'm not gonna do this shit. I
have to- I'm gonna try to stand right here. Are they spawned? I don't think they're here.
The game doesn't know that they're here. Okay. It's possible. It's possible.
I'm just gonna take a buzzer to my head. This looks like this hair falling down in my mouth.
Hair clippers. Hair buzzers. Guys. Alright get over here. That bone is gonna screw me over
here. Slow down. No it just takes up too much real estate. They both gotta go. They both gotta
go. They do. If they take up too much space I gotta go right for them right in the beginning.
I can't fucking believe it. The one time that that happens. The one time that it actually is
high enough out of the fucking ground to hit me through the ground. What? And I-
This little Mega Man area boss zone is starting to get under my skin.
I'm not gonna make it. See? Sometimes you gotta pull up. Reassess the situation. Watch out.
Don't get hit by that one pixel. Okay. I gotta bait out one. Oh man. There's no way that this-
I don't- There's no way. There's no way. It takes up so much space. Why? There's no way.
You can't jump on this part of the level. There's no jumping. That guy wasn't even
throwing at anything. He just was whipping a newspaper into the wall. Do it again. I'm going
the other way. I'm gonna cry foul on that because what the- I'm crying foul on it.
It's slippery. Every single thing is fucking slippery. It's driving me mental. No it's
slippery man. I'm gonna play a normal level after this and I'm gonna be terrible.
Terrible. Terrible. I can't even jump over you. I can't jump over this. Yes I can.
It's on now motherfuckers. I'm freaking out. I got- Okay now- No!
That's what you have to do. It's sliding around. It's the sliding around that really
causes the problem for me. It's sliding the fa- You know that I'm literally shaking right now.
I'm literally shaking and crying. Alright just scratchy ass neck. I keep- Man when you have
to hold down so many buttons at the same time and you just worry about fucking- I swear man
this slipping fucking bullshit is- I'm gonna slide down my stairs. I'm gonna baseball slide
down my slates and go through the front door. I'm gonna put a slip and slide on my stairs and
just wet it and just slide down as fast as I can. Thank god there's another mushroom because
it's so- No and you fucking blew it again. I can't believe it. Why? I just wanted to
restart from the checkpoint. This is an icy motherfucker. I'm not doing it again but I'm
so close. You gotta be kidding me. Why do bad things have to happen? Why? What if I do it
in one go? I can't believe people are gonna come to the stream back from like 40 minutes ago
and they're gonna be like you're still here at the beginning. No I'm not. I'm not. It started
over. Accidentally I pressed the wrong button. Did Nintendo wish the confirmation that you
want to start from the beginning of the level without the checkpoint? Where's my confirmation?
I'm fucking over. I'm so- it's over. Come on controllers. I'm so- I'm just like mutated
right now. If you did like a scan of my brain right now the doctor would be like what the fuck
is happening? I don't understand this. How do you have a lion brain? Have you eaten potato
chips like too many? How is your DNA mutated? I don't get it. It didn't cough into his hands
right in my face. Sorry, sorry. I finally did it. That's the first time I've ever done that.
So we're gonna get it. We're gonna get it like perfect first. Remember this part? I remember
this part. Easy. Remember this part? I do. Oh press that before you click the switch.
Holy shit. It's so bad. Like that's such a bad, bad area to fall down in. But I made it.
I can get back there. Oh my god remember this part? Yep I do. It sucked. Oh it sucked.
Oh it sucked. Jeremy? Wait you gotta get the thing. Jeremy? Jeremy? Almost there.
Oh I remember this part. This sucked. No it didn't. It's just patience.
It's just patience. I'm already back here so we're good. I can beat it. I can do it.
I know I can. Forget about this. The jumpscare. It's not real. I thought.
Press that button. Jeremy? No stop that. No let me go. Let me go.
Forget it. I'm falling. I'm falling off the edge here.
Oops. I need Yoshi. I don't. I need Yoshi. I have to. I have to go jump over here. I need
Yoshi. Oops. Guys and why did I get stuck on the guy's body? I got stuck on his head.
Do you guys think that people like throw up from playing these these levels?
I swear to god people puke from these. I'm talking full on like you have to run to the
bathroom because it's. Good. Good job. I did it. What? Where did he go? Slow down. Don't.
Everything is fucking icy. Why? Just get on Yoshi. Please get on him. Get on him. No.
Just ride it over. I need to get over here. I'm not even done either.
You stupid bastard. What have you done? You're lucky. You're lucky that you didn't
just make me mad. You ever eat so much that you feel sick and you throw up?
That's called overeating and you shouldn't be doing that. Once you get to about 80 full
you should stop eating and then after about 20 to 30 minutes your hunger reflex will turn off
and you will not be hungry at all. Just a quick little tip. Oh no. Okay. Back where I was before.
Almost right? Getting there. This is it. Made it. Everything's fine. We're good. Now I just
need to complete it. Yeah I was watching Mario Maker. There was this guy that was streaming
and he was he like he sucked at the game. No way. Really? You know when athletes after they
play a tough game they sit in that like fucking ice bath? I'm gonna have to I don't think I'm
gonna do that. How much are those? Are they expensive? No it's ice. No that's not what
I'm talking about. Notice how I went backwards? Notice how I went backwards so I didn't make sure
I didn't kill him. Where really? Where did that even come from? I need this. Okay.
Didn't get the first one. I thought I could get the first one. One little
you dick. Okay I got one. One is dead. Is that enough? Might be enough. Dude dude dude
this part it takes you like six seconds to start moving. Look at this. That's a full six goddamn
seconds. I don't even care about that one. Oh that was that was really I'm really happy
about where that hitbox was. It's just I'm I'm so happy about it. I will sing about it.
I just throw things forward and there's nobody there. I throw them. I just throw
you don't. You don't throw? No no I don't and I want something to be in front of me.
No I do not. Don't bring Otto into this. That's not Otto. This is Otto.
This part is the worst. It's the worst. There's nowhere to go. You have to get that shell
in there and you have to kill them both. There's nowhere to go. There's nowhere to go.
You have to get over there with the shell and get them both. There's no other option.
Get it in there with full health like my dad used to say. Get me to the last castle with full health
with but no with eight lives and I'll beat the game and he would. We just have to get
him there. I'm sorry dad. I you have one health. Oh no really. You gotta be. That's
two. That's two. That's two. That's two. I got it. Give me out. I accidentally just
beat this. I'm the only person that's done it. That's wow. Only two completions and 749.
Wow. Don't make me fucking angry here. These are cute but careful girl. Careful.
I enjoy you but be careful. That's a beautiful Otto. Calm down bud. This one's way easier.
Jerm is a good streamer. I appreciate him. Look clear required. Should have skipped.
This fireman. I mean like come on man. What is this? You've wrote a paragraph in here.
Hey my good friend Jeremy found a hilarious level that simulates how it is to be short
as a seven-foot man. You'll love it. I can't t-c-8-9-7-v-d-y-f. That's how I write checks.
You know you get to the end you're like ah two hundred and forty-five dollars and
raising cents. You could have put that a little more legible but you know what?
For the effort I'll do it. Let's see 8-9-7-v-d-y-f. Why would I report that? How do you all make ice
levels? It's my turn. I'm gonna write this one down too. I'm gonna write this down. Okay.
He did say it was his. It was my turn so. T-A-T-K-W-H-G. Okay. 53 minutes ago. How do you
guys draw on the switch like this? Well I guess you can use a stylus right? Did we
already do this one? That's a pretty, you know, that's a good enough Mario where I'm gonna write
this one down. All right. 7-6-N-1-C-E-R-F. Let's go through these and then we're not going to do
any more from the comments. We're gonna go into the chat after these three. Let's start with
this one. T-C-9-7-v-d-y-f. Let's give it a try. Puzzle solving short and sweet. This is by
Gary the Snail. It's called Super Ball. Black and white. Original Super Nintendo. Super original
Nintendo. Black and white. Not Cake Mario or Cake Luigi but it's close. Oh I remember this thing.
The little... Oh yeah you got my attention. Game Boy. You gotta skeeball it around.
Oh this is gonna be fun. Can I do it? Nice. Yeah it's a skeeball level. This is so happy.
Now this is the kind of salad level that I'm talking about.
Yeah this is the salad level that I wanted. I remember this... What was the one... What was
the Mario Game Boy game where you flew around in that ship and you... You shot out the little
pellets. What was that? Did I get it? I hit the POW. Mario Land. That's the one. I missed
that game. That game was so much fun. I get in there. Hit the POW. It still exists? Yeah
but I remember. What I'm saying is I remember playing it and I remember being really happy.
And it is this same song. What a good song. Get up there. Ding dong. I think I have to activate
these. I'm not getting in there. Is it despawning? Okay cool. Bounce it from here I think.
Yeah like right here. Ding dong. How many more? I have to bounce it. Probably gonna have to
bounce it up. Or maybe not. I guess... No I don't. No I don't. It's gonna be hard.
All right get it. Right here. Shit. Sands. Sure. Sure thing. Sands. I know this is the
right place. Okay wait wait one two three. There we go. This one's gonna have to travel.
Bounce it up off the wall twice. One two and then yeah probably like two. One hop up the
ceiling. Two hops off the ceiling. We're right down in the middle here. Again? All right I think
this is gonna hurt me. This is gonna hurt me isn't it? I guess that's what I was supposed to do.
Think? You gotta... I think I have to grab you? Yeah you gotta grab the little gopher.
You're stuck there forever. Bring him down here. No no no no. Get him. Get him. Okay now
I'm gonna move out of the way and drag him down there. I'm gonna transfer him.
No transfer. Transfer! Dope. No put him down. I'm trying to drop him on the treadmill
but the the hand keeps getting stuck. All right grab him and then you have to put him down. Put
him down this way. No! Put him down! Get over here! No you idiot! Where are you running to?
This way! Quick! I thought maybe I could kill him. I don't have a flower. Oh damn it.
I thought I could kill him. It's all right. No! Shoot him. I didn't have any flower. Leather
belt. Leather belt. Leather belt. Leather belt. What do you mean leather belt?
Leather belt. Leather belt. What does that mean? You guys are doing like a 13 year old
World of Warcraft reference right now? Cam on. I don't think I will. Come on. Yep. You want my
webcam on? What's it gonna add? It's not gonna add anything. Tell me what it's gonna add.
My beautiful face. Very sweet of you. So we can see how sweaty you are. I mean I look like
I probably I look like shit. I can probably guarantee you that. It's gonna add my face value.
Well you guys the reason why I don't ever do face cam is because I don't want to turn
face cam on because it's I can just I can be I can look whoever however I want and I don't have
to worry about people looking at me and going like holy shit his hair looks like dog shit
today and I'm like that you don't you could I could look perfect right now your image of me
right now is me in a nice three-piece fucking suit and I got my hair gelled back got a
clean shave I look great just have that memory have that in your mind you don't even know
what I look like right now now here's the issue what the hell do I do about this
ah somebody just somebody did that for me I don't even know how that happened
here's your answer all right drag him over here no you're causing me all kinds of fucking
pain right now let him go let him go you made it stupid hey I did it what he's an idiot
he's an idiot he shouldn't be following me around running back and forth in circles
he's stupid and he had the key I hate this streamer no you don't 60 completion rate that
was a fun one let's take a look at what people had to say hell enough ice clear required all
right well we're not no more of these from the comments on what I want to do these next
two and then pull in some from chat but there's the ID that was really fun that was cool
it was like a little ski ball one this is so fun what a fun game g4t h2k w h g
red coin castle um this is apparently pretty hard very hard one it's short and sweet
but only one percent completion why do I sound so stressed out it's but I'm stressed out what
are you talking about I'm as cool as a cucumber right now red coin castle this thing's only like
30 seconds long well that's not the right way that is not the right way to go because it's
rising let me check these how much surprise all the way I just need I gotta examine
why is it normal to eat a handful of pickles and not a handful of cucumbers
why are you eating a handful of what do you mean a handful that's not abnormal to eat
a handful of cucumbers what's what's so abnormal about that
oh I didn't see that if you you never eaten a cucumber before
wrong I've eaten like two or three cucumbers before
you just they you cut them up and you put salt and pepper on them and they're perfect
what's the big deal I need that salt pepper and a little bit of olive oil that's good
it's not weird that's not strange that's a snack it's a very healthy snack
how do I do this probably should go underneath
it's this way no
drop spin jump dummy ban that guy please
shit there's a lot of explosions going on I love that old Yoshi's Island coin sound
oh come on that didn't touch the bat the top of his head
come on you're making me look bad how many coins are there three that's not terrible
I was I didn't I was trying to get that one beat that one this guy's skills are insane
thanks I have been practicing a little who's playing he's awful his name is German985
he's a youtuber for a while and he made the switch to twitch he's been doing it pretty much
regularly he's very not he's a really nice person too like I met him in real life
sign my face and
it's got a vacation here things gonna come back and haunt me I know it
that was not intentional that was not intentional the stupid button just was pressed
I would much rather that be like left or r or something like right bumper left bumper or
something just down how many times they test this why is it just down why can't that just
be like right bumper right bumper left bumper right trigger and left trigger are the same
thing that's four different buttons you can press to do the spin you gotta press down to ground
pound I just I disagree no shit fired up all right now I gotta go no what the fuck man the
stupid I'm gonna rip this thing out I'm about to give up I can feel it I can get the yeti
levels of fucking getting uncontrollable levels I just that was really redundant what I just
said you understand three no what the fuck man it was there was right there and I just like
fucking fat fingered it go I need like two I thought it was I thought it was lava and it
freaked up isn't it rise what the fuck what it just done it too but why is this not rising
that's the thing that confused the fuck out of me and I didn't even get the first one
it is rising so how far hold on how far does this go all right so you can't effectively get
down there and so you have to be really careful because the lava will just be up there and
fucking support you out of here that was dumb shit I've ever seen in my life
Nintendo what are you thinking can I unbind down I feel like not having a ground pound
would actually if I had to go in and toggle it back on it would probably be better for me
to wait till that top this one shot
I don't want to spend like an hour on this one no no thank you is it gonna fire oh what
the fuck is it doing is it still hanging out somewhere go down and then I think I have to
ground pound it the lava's up wait till the lava to go down get the third key piece and then
get the hell out of here give me a checkpoint I deserve it I did it holy fuck
yeah I did it Jerma look at chat okay I'm looking at it right now what is it some
minion Jerma don't smoke please I'm crying and shaking right now I don't smoke hi hi hi hi hi hi
mama cucumbers are a normal snack pretty cool no no god damn no man I just want to
get out of the level I don't want to report somebody I swear to god they make that really
easy to do you can really easily accidentally just press a that was good that was tricky
that was hard I was willing to put like an hour into that one all right there's one more
that I took from the and then we're gonna do chat ones after this one and six and the one
see eight are after this I'm gonna take a break I'm gonna go grab something to drink
and he's the bathroom it creates a new Mario adventure to commence fight length enjoy
12 short and sweet 25 seconds Mario's area
that's what I would do if I was in front of the cannon you know what I'm saying
any stuff in here sometimes it's like little secrets and there is
this mushroom get that too go inside yeah was a big oh this is a flying thing
how does this did you just hold b and it's like a Yoshi fly
what's that is that good or bad is there a pumpkin head costume or something see ya
I I can jump on this right with my magical foot you need that well that was cool
and go nice that's cute little level they're all cute I got news for you
oh not enough time to leave a comment on this one when can we expect germa rumble 2019
um or uh that's funny people are using the comment sections on somebody's level to ask me
a question about germa rumble see to the person that made this level if they're not here
right now that that person is asking them that question and they're gonna wake up tomorrow
and be like what the fuck is this person talking about um I don't know I don't have an answer for
you what is germa rumble do they think that's the name of this level I don't I can't give you
an answer I don't know by the end of the year for sure question dodge no I just gave you
an answer all right uh I see this one here this one looks potentially interesting
let's get this one for when I get back I'll be right back I'm gonna take a quick pee I'm gonna
grab some water see you in a minute or two oh hello again how do you I'm gonna copy this one
this is uh he has a decent looking one here too let's try this one let me say go to
mcdonald's to get a mcchicken oh I probably will you know yeah I will that's a great idea
all right um ct l2t 93 g this is apparently a single screen puzzle munchers block the way
use all the items you can to destroy the seemingly endless door of munchers
the chickens are like gum they stay in your digestive system for three years
well I would I'm probably gonna have to go get like surgery because I've eaten like 40 on
the last like year or so all right so hold on I think I already blew it
all right so wait a minute look on music
wood gold all right we get the four elements here so when I pick up one okay I just picked
coin and I just turned it off but what is it hold on what about the shell oh dear
so the right coin moves I gotta get the shell so this right what is it what is he doing
I need to get that shell on the top left so that's
on but what is what happened over here whatever I'm gonna try to get the middle one
okay so that turned on the blue
so then turn the red back on which is the middle one right I'm killing them what are
the what's the left and right ones do left I don't know if it's doing anything oh that's
blue the coin order doesn't matter oh okay wait wait wait oh wait a minute
would you look at that okay let's just jump up here
so I screwed it up so I have to go back I mean this is working
oh wow can I pick up pow wait hold on
all right so everything's dead now I can can I go up there do this
what of the time the time the time the time jump up high how high do I have to do I just
can I just use this not really all right that's gone now let's see if I can get up there
I just want to put it down I'm trying this one one more time
no one else will ever die in that spot it's easy I just gotta get up top because then
it's let's make it blue then I can go in the tunnel in the pipe give me the power now this
gets rid of the who cares about the coin I'm not gonna get it I just want to place this here
oh shit I have to switch the thing don't die by this spike don't die by that spike don't die
by that spike don't die by that spike don't die by the spike that was so so careful too
you saw how careful I was being I was trying to be so so it has to be blue but no I can't
even get up there if the blue is switched I'm so confused
so do I need to use the power how do I switch it when I try to get up there
maybe I shouldn't take the power maybe I should throw the power when I get up there
there's not even use the power but then how do I trigger this to open the door up to the
I'm gonna put it down does this blow everything up if I place it no okay so now get up there can
I get up there with this and then throw it I was trying to go put it on I guess I
I was gonna just go put the helmet on did I not understand can I not just walk up and grab
it did I touch it no I don't I don't think I can get it all right I'm I'm I'm moving on
criminal fireman playthrough spore wife filed divorce lol have you finished a level yet
no in in five hours I haven't beaten one level zero let's try this one spore meme is
still alive hd5 cg tower to the sky stairs out of order ride the elevators at your own risk
going up pretty good description I only played sport for 25 minutes yeah because it was
flashing everybody in the face it was bad that was like actually very bad to play it was
it was pretty good I was gonna hurt somebody good music choice first of all
ah mushroom come on oh that's better even better don't hear oh my goodness
going the same way kind of no what's in there who cares oh my god up up what do you mean up
oh my god ah too many too many the music really sets maybe be able to see nice fire flower
oh get it what's going on
it's not what's going up there maybe it is no it's not there's no checkpoints it's not worth it
I thought there was nothing there for a second that's pretty good
got a little chaotic at the end there but that was really pretty good only two people
have played this two out of two 100 what do the people have to say cool nothing
happy birthday thank you nothing even there did you did your comma get deleted I see one
here let's grab this one so this person says this is baby mode now I don't know if that's
an ironic statement because it's this is one of those impossible ones or if this is actually
a really easy one that's going to be very very simple for me to do time will tell I don't
know goku in smash well I I think it's it's probably going to be pretty puzzle solving
goku really goku smash this one that's funny okay we got one here goku in smash
this is y h1 c4 h q8 g land of the trees a more relaxed approach at mario maker my first level
you've already got my attention a relaxing level land of the trees what no I'm not relaxed
I didn't know they can't I just wait they look really cool
wait come on they're really shiny I love the way that those fishes look this is fun this is
actually pretty relaxing now that you mention it who would put that in the water the fishes
died to a relaxing level you can still die that's not anything to be made fun of for
the secret up here what does that say it's not even a pea pants level what are you talking
it's not a pea pants level well that was kind of a pea pants moment right there but it's all
right and you're talking and making references and doing a voice poorly
and it's distracting enough where you can't do anything else you literally cannot do anything
else when you do that so stop it you peed my pants okay those make chickens that sound
really really good right now after a long day screaming nearly crying and shit my god
I can't wait for like a chicken sandwich
well can I beat the fish I think I can beat them no I can't
you suck no I'm just drained I'm drained I've had it's a my body is drained
the fucking bug again that was that was unrealized
McChicken with uh mayo and that's it that was cool that was cool that was pretty good
it was that was fun all right should I should I take the one where somebody says
putrid level if you have that kind of description I'm not sure that's the one I want to do
well I'm gonna try okay five nine two rm no no lettuce on it not for McDonald's for some
reason I don't know what it is but sometimes you go to McDonald's and you get lettuce on
your sandwich it's this wilted hot gross disgusting filmy just tiny thin filmy hot thing
it's like a wet napkin on your chicken sandwich not very appetizing sludge surfing in space
it's like cooked spinach yeah but it doesn't taste as good as cooked spinach
it tastes like a napkin I don't think I'm supposed to do that I'm gonna get in all
right let's go sludge racing good music choice can I not go in oh sorry my pee pants
actual lizard brain saw that the arrow is pointing down this is not putrid this is pretty
good what's wrong with this one that doesn't protect you come on it doesn't give me
it should give me something that should protect me at least five percent five
percent left after talk to poison talk to this tick poison so I got a question for you guys so
this is this would be mario maker's dream technically number three you want to see this
again I'm willing to do it again in a small dose it's pretty fun I guess it's pretty
creative people are pretty creative it's fun I need to hit that I don't know what's oh
shit okay yeah actually be careful I'm scared to get with it whatever this is he's dead right
he's dead I'm gonna go get it holy shit how do they not get hurt oh fuck what is it what is
that what is it it's just a it's a bait was it worth it no I didn't I thought it may have
been something cool it's just an extra shroom what did it cost uh you know the answer to
that question no get up get up easy all right now I want to go I want to get that
bump that's up there this bump up here I'm gonna bump it
what do you mean what what do you mean why do you hate the hearthstone stream why
what was wrong with it what was wrong with it what was I too tall I was just too tall for
this oh can I thankfully the checkpoints right there I'm now I'm small so this should work out
mushroom got it I think I waited too long dead yeah
that again I don't know why I have this weird urge to like tell you very loudly what's about
to happen and that is so hard to even do even if I try to do what I just did again
I wouldn't be able to do it these are some rare deaths yeah I'm so paranoid about hitting
the edge there that's enough time right yeah oh
oh this is I'm coasting right now I really am I gotta just like stop coasting I'm getting
up I was leaning back in the chair you're the greediest streamer ever no I'm just
coasting I'm no longer coasting I'm not sure what's over here but oh god blind jumps that's
not smart what's down here duck comes another one right cut that right at the edge anything
weird I can do over here I need to know what's up there what's up there try damage boosted
I get 200 bits if I beat your level oh didn't this one I just did didn't I do this one
already it would be an honor if you could do mine you got it let's go I will pay 20
dollars if you do a McChicken stream uh what do you mean like just eat a McChicken on
camera you will pay you will pay me 20 dollars if I eat a McChicken on the stream are we
clear on that why now we don't there's no speed there's no do it in a minute it's just
simply eat it on the stream okay I'm gonna do it why like what's the problem here uh this
is Vinny's level I'm gonna put down to do next I'm just just one right I mean I'm gonna buy four
but I'm only gonna eat one on stream and I'm gonna turn stream off this is the weirdest
thing I think I've ever had requested is can I pay you 20 dollars for you to eat a McChicken
that's such a ridiculous return on investment a McChicken is a dollar all right well I got a
couple more written down here thanks for the fun level it was pretty good I'm gonna do this
one HOM this shit is so cool though it really is imagine back in the 80s telling somebody this
is going to be possible this never-ending content Mario's Vacation Tower Heist it's a day off here
and Mario would like to go robbing Bowser again would you get in a bathtub of mac and
cheese for a hundred dollars and stream it no I'd have to be way more than that because
I would destroy the bathtub the box that the amount of macaroni and cheese would take to fill
a bathtub would be like 500 bucks it wouldn't be a hundred dollars it would fuck up the whole
bathtub and how many you understand how many boxes that is oh shit yeah that would probably
take at least 50 to 100 boxes to fill a whole bathtub I was trying to do something
cheeky over there just cover the drain
uh yeah just cover the drain
look at that rat having a good time bouncing around I'm too busy looking at the rat
and I think I've died I think I've been killed left side technically you didn't say you
wouldn't do it um guys I am not going to fill a bathtub I'm gonna deny that now I'm
not going to fill a bathtub with macaroni and cheese that's not gonna happen I gotta get across
here damn all right I gotta be up top on top of that and then up to the left well I'm not
that no amount of money is gonna have me do that just dropping goombas um so then how do I
what do I do let's go
okay and then we go damn we controller switch controller down ground town bullshit it should be
one of the triggers it's so easy to accidentally press this shit all the time uh Vilemi gave 50
dollars thanks for the 50 thanks and 50 bucks for learning huge money this is this is probably
McChicken money uh if I were to take a guess I wonder I haven't read it yet so I think it's
McChicken then let me see oh my god that just freaked me out the freaking thing's fallen um
Jeremiah I'll give you another 50 bucks I'll give you 5,000 bits if you wash down the
McChicken by chugging a Mountain Dew throwback no I'm not doing that thank you for the 50
dollars but I'm not chugging a Mountain Dew throwback I will have a stomach ache
I will have a problem it's not good for my health scream and fall down
what the fuck it's not what I didn't touch the flag why is the level go so
oh I jumped over the flag no you bumped your fucking head on the goddamn ceiling and it lost
why do you not attach to the wall like 25 percent of the time it's only in this like
new Super Mario fucking Five Toads game that's what happens
oh wow oh I wonder what happened I wonder what happened
what's up Vegeta maybe I you know be careful he's gonna be up taking off all his powers
you must have accidentally pressed down on the d-pad
maybe you gave me the controller I'd be able to take care of it really it's too hard
it's too hard why am I turning into the guy from Ghostbusters 2 why am I dripping with goo
the most unbelievable man I gotta wait till it switches and then now I have to go ready
that's not what I have to do at all that's incorrect it's only a game why do you have to
be mad because it's fucking hard and it makes me upset that's why I can't even see it's not
just a game this is this is not just a video game now a task that I need to accomplish
I'm going to fucking freak out accidental ground bounce oh my god I'll ever tilt
somewhat in the direction of down you'll go straight into the ground
I think I need a big chicken I would rather eat a big chicken than press down on the d-pad
accidentally on this dumb controller turn the webcam on because I want you to see this this
is important to me down I'm down oh by the way if you want to use these my thumb covers
the whole entire thing I'm trying to press this button if you do if you use that no it's
not it's not even better you're gonna press them all get a pro controller I refuse
oh I got it get a game cube controller I refuse no I don't like the pro controller anyways
I wish I could just use a playstation 4 controller we're all talking about
working together and having all kind oh yeah let's get everybody on stage we're all in this
together microsoft have you seen banjo kazooie yeah I'm gonna be able to use the my xbox
controller on the fucking switch and now when we all play together we win except by my service
oh my god they may as well just start like shoving each other on stage no now get out of
the way it's my you should be uh we're all in this together ready get out of the fucking way
my time it's just not being able to see yeah hey play fallout 76
I just why does it have to be scrolling so slow
you can use an xbox control I refuse I can't wait to make $20 to eat a chicken
in like 10 minutes no what happened oh my god I don't ever want to play new super mario
bros 3d wheat dickhead fucking ground grab the fucking side of the building thing I am playing
this game this is the worst Mario I'm never I'm not playing this one I'm so glad I skipped
this one oh you see you see when I get the mario 3 or cake mario levels it's over give me a cake
mario level I'll beat it in two tries you've seen it I don't need to explain it you can't
even grab that shit it's over I was trying to get the you're scaring me just get a mcchicken
you'll be fine yeah mcchicken's way better than a sticker I am gonna play this one it's
so funny when I want to actually have the ground pound happen I feel like it doesn't
happen when I press the button it only happens when you accidentally turn into mr satan
I'm gonna tap this like three or four more times and I'm gonna fucking shove mcchicken
into my mouth
you can't go too fast because the scroller goes too slow that you just die
I don't even know what even killed me the camera moves up you go off
too far off screen it does not I was just up there where is it I'm gonna skip it
god this is this is I
really what the fuck is this and what are you doing what the hell are you doing
I um I'm sorry I have to get this one this is gonna make me freak the fuck out
but I've it's like it is sunk cost fallacy just rearing its ugly ass head has he beaten
the level since he skipped the bus one you're just saying this shit and kept me going
you have to press a fucking bunch of face buttons and move and tilt and control
why it's down a ground pound huh am I the only fucking person doing this out of everybody
you've seen stream this game am I the only guy that's ground pounding into the fucking dirt
tell me please tell me how am I doing this
because I'm using the baby controller well what is it with Nintendo I love them you got a great
company here but every time you make a new console we have to buy like three different
controllers can you just have the one your ship be one that's worth fucking using like
really oh boy need that
fuck I hit the stupid fucking guy that's right here
okay I got him I think that's it you don't get the mushroom it's over but you got oh my
goodness I thought you would give me a fun one I thought this is like the mild salsa one
shut shut shut it shut it up no no I needed that why did it go the other way why would
you do that to people why would you do that to somebody oh don't come over here don't come
over here where to go which way I don't know I did I went I went I went I went I get it I
get it it's not over I think it's not over what did I just do I just went in here I don't
know I'm scared it's not over there's more of this Nintendo GameCube Mario mental breakdown
I'm trying to sit on his head Mario no Mario just get out give me the car just don't drown
Mario please no no
all right I'm gonna this is where I caught up this is where I just relax this is where I'm gonna
just relax it's not even that big of a deal just do it we can get it done I'm gonna need
the car it's actually easier without the car jump idiot I'm gonna get that guy for one
unban that guy because he's right I want to throw up the meme horn just I can't okay right here
oh what the fuck knees fall too what the fuck am I doing just hold right in the car and I was
under the water it was gonna make me you know you don't just have to hold right watch what
happens I'm gonna hope I just got a tire mark on my face did you see that shit look at my eyes
I'm going fucking hollow all right here we go ready watch this I can hold right now show it to you
look it's not working I want oh right 15 fucking minutes boom no that's not fair
all right let's do Vinnie's level please play nightbot's dead it's all right looking
forward to the mixture oh yeah I forgot I just said I was doing that I'm actually eating
him a chicken on stream percent of them I got more fucking milk fat than a goddamn
grocery store I don't know whatever make something out of what I just said
you got Vinnie's right there pipe dreams and 1400 comments five percent completion
am I gonna get angry at this one cake Mario you already got me sold here nice coin placement
nice coin placement Vinnie let me just check out the earth I like you got the fishes coming
up and down I I I would have had to be a little bit lower than that but then you know
to each their own right the audio is super off again why does this keep happening with the
switch the pipe dream part oh sneaky sneaky I would have moved it a little bit over to the
right maybe two three slots but you know you do each their own you're doing it's a very
good job so far it's really gonna come out of my jet up here I know Vinnie would hide something
like this up here he's got the intelligence to throw it up cool can I go in this one oh
uh the tide is rising hurry up hurry up nice oh okay easy that almost just killed me
not good give her to this and knock into that no oh shit oh my god middle is the middle
right in the nick of time now we gotta go we have to go now this room right now
thank god this is cake Mario level oh my I shouldn't have said anything
I'm right here though this level is actually pretty good already screwed it up it's all right
I like the little jump vine to vine that's a good little skip right there good little technique
wow the mushroom bad this to keep going on
watch out yep uh-huh okay watch out yep got it almost just died from that
watch out for the one cheeto that's coming around here I don't think I can get in these
he's gonna drop on me I knew it another one's gonna drop he's gonna drop okay I'm fine
stop screaming I don't know what it is about these games guys I don't I'm sorry I'm screaming
turn it the other way oh boy that was what the star see I love this song I love I want
to hear I want to love the fucking heavy metal rock version of the song
there are a lot of those on YouTube oh no
oh
I can hear it I know what it sounds like oh no I'm not gonna go get it I'm gonna beat this
Vinny this is pretty good I know I'm talking like you're here right now but it is this is
pretty great I'm gonna beat Vinny's level gonna beat Vinny's level yeah thank god it was a cake
Mario level otherwise I'm not sure I would have been able to complete it five minutes and it's
the 54 seconds is is the um that's all right it's my first playthrough let's take a look at
the comments let's see what they're saying nice job Vinny that was great Vinny's not gonna
know what you're talking about okay I think I was not happy about this I gotta leave a
comment how do I do how do I leave a comment I beat the level did I already screw it up
I already messed it up that was a good one nice job Vinny
I want to get the true ending okay this is apparently the true ending I don't know what
that means let's give this one a shot 3q5 s42 elf l9g koopa forest collect all the pink
coins for a little bonus at the end true ending he's starving himself I'm fine
that's the true ending I gotta get all the red coins
I love I love when you jump on these guys and you grab me throwing but I feel like
they had an air freshener and a car freshener it's not like that you know what I'm saying
gotta be awesome how do I get that give it to me this is an instant death if I I'm gonna
have to jump on somebody's head here boss fight all the way through got it I got a special key
okay it should be over it is over oh oh oh there it is there's the rock music
wait a minute is there anything else over here and it's too funny very funny oh god easy
it's not safe it's not safe
oh right this game tears my soul out of my body where's that actually I need the true
ending I need one more please my children are sleeping well you better turn your volume down
because you're gonna get loud screaming man in probably five or six seconds maybe a little less
depends on how I feel
let's try this again so what am I just what am I gonna run across this shit
just die and hit damage boost and go what have I done excuse me all right oh coins there they
are and go I know what I have to do
you just ran you stupid person I could have just ran what am I thinking I could have just ran over it I forgot it
and it's oh I'll laugh my ass off I'll laugh my ass off laugh my fucking all I
dreamcast sucks I'll laugh my ass off wait no give me the true ending now what does that mean
true ending here it is the true ending is just the inside of a school cafeteria
I'm taking this quickly because I need it no I can't even get I just want to go up
all right I got the true ending that was a cute little fun level that was pretty good I liked
it that was wholesome times they're all so bad but you can play these like five or six
times in a row that's very good nice work what's next I haven't even done endless challenge yet
it's been six hours guys should I was supposed to do that I'm going for it please pick up right
we left off reclaim the temples multiplayer versus what do you mean multiplayer is somebody
in the game McChicken we got plenty of time this bullshit ran from the sky
I mean you give me cake Mario and I fucking I go I go nuts that would have had it but
hubris always ends up making it happen I don't know why when I say something
immediately it goes completely wrong why does it do that why does it happen there has to be
some magic power or something that just takes you over once you figure out that you're
doing well when you say I'm doing well you just don't do well I should talk about how
bad I am all the time and then I'll never ever mess up
I mean these are legit cake Mario plays they're terrible plays they're awful
no one should fucking emulate these plays they're terrible they're dog shit absolute trash
three keys three keys I got it okay let's say exit go over the mole people I need those
um okay I need the star to go on to go over them on the whole thing
this is my first stream and it's a fucking mess welcome hey welcome to the family son
I gotta get all those again right oh what a fucking mess what a fucking mess
what a fucking mess here we go go
why because I got it they jump and they jump and they don't ever jump they never jump and
we have to see we have to take care of the fact that they based on their programs jump
in this version I'm gonna get killed by it if you kill me I swear to god with same size
all right do it again do this how do I get up there how do I get up there
what you got that's one of the rights of babe I'm gonna reclaim the town I'll get it
you have to jump on them don't make me eat a chicken on stream I will
I'm getting 20 bucks for it by the way I don't know how I'm gonna get this
McChicken this big chicken is uh am I gonna get it I'm not gonna be one of those people that
gets McChickens delivered to their house I find myself I have this invincibility
I am indestructible what the hell was that oh you're only invincible sometimes for some
stuff is it a star or is it a star why did you tell me to do that get over eats
I'm not really gonna be one of those people that gets the
McChicken delivered you just you're an asshole at that point but you can't get yourself to
McDonald's like yeah um I'll take one McChicken please you can maybe drive all the way to
McDonald's to bring you a McChicken or two it's 20 bucks I might as well tip the delivery
guy 20 bucks I'm gonna put up with that bull
McChicken my mother would be so disappointed in me
we'll get fries too but I don't want fries I don't understand
am I gonna endless was a mistake super expert was a mistake endless was a mistake
I played levels where I could complain about the switch controller
was there a point it was got it okay this was that sucked so I don't want to do it again
what do you stop using the star in that room that's what it's for now that's what
there's two more down there what is it I don't think this one is down here that pipe right
there I'll get baited wrenches wow I didn't know that whoa wow whoa it's a huge cartoon
bulb it was like oh whoa I would have jumped over there I gotta go up
from the fire back up back back back back back back back back this is like oh I thought
that was coming at me come on stop it I can probably make that from here I can just
there it is two out of three just got to kill the hamster out I need a mushroom
I've already done this one but I don't really remember what I don't remember what's
in here I need this last one it's down here but what's down here oh no it's this one this
one was really hard r2d2 I'm sorry oh right I can wall jump is it no that's r2d2 right
I guess I gotta slow down my body's like going 5,000 miles per hour I'm not a
candidate to play these games I do better off with you know match three games and um
hidden object adventures games for old people I'm an old person I just said that that's my
preferences hidden object games match three games I don't know oh it's frustrates me to
know when did this go up I went I don't know how do I do this you want me to jump around
grab the edge and jump over I thought I was gonna have to grab the edges
you're embarrassing all of us it's such a big tower too
easy easy no no no no no why I want both of them that's not gonna work give that
shit to me get rid of the ones over here first almost almost almost
I gotta keep do I have to keep up huh keep me do I have to keep going
I'm losing my mind why I think I have to go up then I have to keep going up
shit I'm all the way down I have they have you have to uh to shoot this control out of
a cannon in space I would if Elon Musk was like hey man you want to like shoot something
into space we're doing like space shoot stuff hey yeah yeah yeah I got something what is it man
take this are you sure you want to do that I mean to shoot that out of the cannon in space
it's gonna be like six or seven million dollars worth it hey uh dude I don't want to
like sound like an idiot or an asshole here but why don't you just get a pro controller
and I just scream and storm out of the room oh god that's so it's so perfect
oh perfect that's not how Bill Gates fucking no no Miyamoto I don't know who makes these
fucking things anymore
we eat a bunch of chickens man glorious just think about the chickens it's all that matters
oh nothing else matters I tried to hit okay I pressed right trigger and he didn't
send it to space Elon get it up there now do you think if I threw it as hard as I could
into the air I did like three crow hops and threw as hard as I fucking could in the air
it was I have so much anger against this thing right now it would go into the stratosphere it
would get there and gravity would pull it up break the controller and I'll give you 30
bucks no I don't break shit I don't break my stuff I just complain about it over and
over again I talk about how I hate it like shun it this thing out of battery am I running
out of battery okay where's where's the coaxial cable that I can plug into this
controller to make sure that it's not going to run out of battery and fuck up my video
game it's really important that this is taken seriously attempt number like 300 000
to try to get up here come up okay now should I just ride it up no I don't think so
I think I do have to use them it's I'm doubling up here you gotta ride the cannons I gotta jump
from the cannon I think this is big I can't I'm gonna fucking fucking frisbee this good
chicken into space please let me just let me just talk for a second I'm gonna get it I'm
gonna submit infinite loop infinite loop infinite loop infinite loop oh you gotta be kidding me
oh it's almost time it is almost time for like just give up and eat my chicken
what I did order it I'm going to fucking scream attach to the wall Luigi I'm holding
the button the button is being held on the wall oh am I still live hello I almost
accidentally restarted my computer I'm fucking living right now I almost restarted the computer
by hitting windows and then accidentally pressing like escape three times
this is my last shot and I'm gonna skip this level
this level is really cool fuck that diarrhea cannon section
there's something wrong there's something actually wrong because it won't do it check
the battery I wonder I can't have the satisfying like throw the cartridge out of the console
there they're like as big as mini sd drive card things you're supposed to eat them
you're supposed to put it under your tongue it'll dissolve this is the last try and then I'm
moving on from this one get me back up to the cannon and then just get it over please
not enough finally let's see it nice okay here it is no it's not you can't get up there like that
you can't do that so how do I get up here if you miss you missing you it's over
bump your head on the ceiling just there
I'm getting so many one-ups that's not what I wanted to do whatever fuck all right
bye bye bye I'm not doing this one anymore fuck this one I ain't doing this shit anymore
that level can eat my asshole I'm ordering the chickens right now this dumb ass bullshit
Mario you can eat I'm not gonna say that about Mario he's a really swell swell general
I'm gonna go for like a pee break I'm glad
oh I'm getting the chickens I tried to jump off and it didn't work
like I wouldn't just do that guys understand I wouldn't just do that I'm gonna be honest I
did not see these at all they were blended into the background
they're hard to go around I can't wait to eat those chickens
to the right all the way to the left yeah why am I playing as Luigi this is the wrong
person to be playing as how do I change this let me see here toad I'm going with toad
no don't die there's no reason to die bank and cash oh I like this
I like this music finally now I'm toad everybody relax everything's gonna be just fine I'll be
taking you through a journey of just some words filler words because you don't want
dead air on stream filler words so you don't want to have any dead air on stream okay
oh it's not fucking tall enough there's secrets over here
I'm gonna I'm so uh is this is this what it looks is this what seven hours of Mario maker
spree does to you yeah I think it does you still have to not be able to form coherent
sentences anymore this level's not bad no I I've been look complaining for me if you do
the stream when I complain it's just I'm just like coping with the fact that I'm not okay
that actually was bullshit it actually was because I got the indicator on my controller
that it was being turned off because the battery's low so that is what's happening that is dog shit
toad's base stats are worse I'm just kidding the controls are fine I want like big diaper toad
I thought I could get it physics when we're going on there for that to happen whatever
this works out last time what's going on here what's over here I don't know what I don't
should go down there's an option I don't think I should go down that's the door and then got
a Bowser jr
two shells appeared out of thin air and killed me
wait really a toad statistics joke what do you mean I didn't say it I was replying
stop I'm already under enough stress out of it but you're just bullying right now it's so hard
to do without having to get it thank god it floats back down this is the chicken
this is a McChicken emergency going on here yeah I just told the guy to come in I said come in I'm
up I'm up I come upstairs he's like what's happening man I'm not up here no all right I
once these McChickens are here I'm done I'm actually done I'm gonna eat I'm gonna make my
20 dollars eating a McChicken on stream and then I'm uh I'm going to bed I'm gonna take a
bath a hot bath I'm gonna make I'm gonna take a bubble bath when was the last time you guys took
a bubble bath screen I actually thought about it would be funny to stream me in a huge bubble bath
but that's like just creepy and fucking weird and odd and I don't think that's I'm not I
don't want to do that I already got I got the award in 2016 for weirdest person on
twitch award and like I didn't really want it I didn't show up to the ceremony to accept
the award either so trying to turn up a new leaf and do some different stuff you know
what the it comes all the way down and goes oh I can feel it I can feel the time time is
it's happening yeah I'm out of steam I'm out of gas I'm running on vapors
it's been fun yeah oh yeah running on vapors we know it's bad when you get calm and quiet
really it was after this when I did the mr satan thing I was like I gotta keep it together
but I feel fucking tired it don't matter all right finally I did it without losing a mushroom
holy shit I'm so glad that exists all right let's try to get rid of them let's try this out come
on I'm so inconsolable about what just happened because what the hell
well just I tried to jump on his head and I got like the dude that shells
and then I just bounced into the spikes and then around I don't you know I don't even know
we just got a we just got a dumb like I'm gonna knock on the door funny joke that like
I'm not running fast enough give me something what did I do it I did it that's where that's
all it took I can't believe it I didn't think that was what was gonna take what time is it
right now like 1 a.m eastern I got time I got I got enough time for the McChickens to show up
here thanks for hanging out guys still a lot of people here hope you're enjoying this stream
hope you're having fun I know I am don't blow these up I need to do this is my favorite
stream ever I'm glad you can put up with my bullshit ding dong well the question is
he's coming over here um do I need another bomb or something how many McChickens are you
getting that's for me to know and you to see three um what am I supposed to do but down
there you're doing a 50 McNugget challenge now you guys ever tell you the story of how
friends of mine told me they wanted to do a big McNugget challenge where actually it was
a Wendy's chicken nugget challenge and they talked it up for a couple hours sitting around
just hanging out hey yeah who's gonna go get them I'd like I don't want to go get them
so I was like this is gonna be fucking hilarious you guys I'll go get them so they
wanted 50 Wendy's nuggets and they're gonna have a contest who could eat them fastest and
shit so I went all the way to Wendy's and I got all these nuggets and it was like a stupid
order the person was like how many do you want 50 oh okay like dick fine okay sure like this is
like a comedy order so I did it and I probably should have known there was like six people
that I was getting these nuggets for how do you do a contest with six people in 50 nuggets
that doesn't make any sense you would need like 200 for like six to eight people so
I bought them I eventually got the guy to give them to me went back to the dude's house
that we were hanging out at and they're like all right here they are okay let's open them
up and they got them all ready and they put them on a plate and then they just started eating them
normally and it was just a lie they just wanted me to go get them a bunch of chicken nuggets
and that was the way they were gonna get me to do it because I was so psyched for them to do
this they were eating them incredibly slowly in front of me so I was the asshole that went and
got 50 nuggets and speaking of um nothing that we were talking about what's to do here I
don't think I can make a jump can I jump up over this no it's gonna get eight nugget challenge
yeah that wouldn't that make any sense oh wait a minute hold on I'm talking about like
nugget challenges it's only give me a break one two three four five they just spam up
that's a fucked up jump oh man only on a derma stream would I feel bad about chicken nuggets
well I mean it was it was kind of funny a little irritated because I thought I was
going to show it was mildly irritating see a block to hit or anything
this is gonna be pain in the ass
is it gonna be safe I'm gonna go the other way let's check an update uh it'll be here soon
okay now what is that drops you in there I can climb across this right somebody
yell at me if I'm wrong I think I can though
forgetting that the thing has a hitbox five feet
I just effectively waited for the train by standing on the tracks not gonna be in my
best interest quickly quickly just like that same deal is this a Nintendo made level I don't
I don't think so I think there was a avatar on it please feed your guild members in stream
legend not yet I will very soon though all right so what I should I not is that this
is just a bad idea should I just go backwards or something because now the button I'm not
gonna make it over here round pound there's no ground pound on this one
oh that's what I need to like get under there and just wait then oh you gotta hit the switch
twice I'm gonna get three more lives before I'm gonna do like a McChicken IV let's go
going through diamond city give it all fall down point point point got it all right now
what's the deal now keep this on that means like oh yeah now I can go this way
I'm picking it out and there's a checkpoint and it all three powers boom one two one two
it shouldn't be too bad I'm gonna go now wait
shit all right how fast one is yes I gotta jump over it no that would be bad
oh why did I not get this I only have one more this is my last guy
I should be able to stand on it I have to run with it oh maybe I'm so timid it's bad get up
there that's it now grab the sprint wait what I'm just like fuck oh I almost died that was so
close that was inches this is the end this is my last shot to get through here so I gotta go
get the first one somehow climb that vine and start screwing to the right well is there a
pixel that's gonna touch me if I stand here I don't know is it gonna hurt me
is that it no I I tried and I hit my head oh that was just the one jump but like I just
bumped the heads because it's it's it's you have to be perfect to get up there
oh no oh I'm just hanging out I'll be back here for a little while
I'm gonna hang out back here I'll see you guys in a minute just gonna be chilling back here
you're gonna need me yeah you know where to find them
this one's gonna be a treat
you just threw me off right there you don't need to tell me to watch out for my
surroundings to not throw my we mode into my fucking fridge okay I know you don't why do
you have to keep telling me this I promise I'm not gonna swing and like hit my little brother
in the head I'm gonna be sure you made that same joke on the main channel years ago it's
been a long enough time I can reason can I not touch the top
damn it it didn't touch the top either
you know it the screen that tells you to collect the coins I wish would just get out of the way
this shit's just in the way
I wonder what I have to do for this level it's not like Nintendo's told me three times
before I get to play again this one looks all right
why am I doing super expert because I am a maniac
expert is just as hard except the hot garbage is rarer
yeah what would what even classifies super expert well I screwed that up
see if I can do this one come on I can do it what oh I forgot about thought I could go through
like a jump through it is my mic broken no I'm just trying to concentrate I'm just sitting here
staring with my eyes wide open why am I turning around and hit springs you actually won't beat
this now that because one guy said that I'm gonna I'm gonna go for it you bet the uber
eats guy could beat this I bet she that she couldn't
well I don't do I'm like so concerned with like the three people in out of like four thousand
that'll tell me why you're not playing super expert what you suck you fucking idiot
then I'm like I can do it I'm capable I'm so concerned about like the five people
that would come here and be like oh this is dumb no I'm not I'm not dumb I can do super expert
watch oops oops oops those people are already gone they left like five hours ago no you gotta
go fast you can't just stop don't forget it again it's just too much to think about
oh it's all right whatever well where are those chicken sandwiches why does it take
you so long did I send this person into like a giant like drive-through line that's even worse
I'm even more of a bad person this person might be sitting in like a 12 car drive-through
line with three McChickens guess what he did again guess what he did he's he guess what he
did if you want you can rewind if you want to make sure if you know what he did he didn't
do the thing where he knocked this thing down again he's not capable of doing this I think and
what probably should happen he should probably go back to simple things like counting to ten
choosing what shape a shape looks like like circles squares you can do those I'm not
we're not sure what else he's capable of doing all right give me some fun levels all
right I've got no more of this no more of this let's do fun view levels with people
that are viewer levels you know I'm not no no no no I can do let's just play this is fun let's
do this again give me one all right I know for a fact that I'm positive that you just put
horse cock there so funny but you were the first one so nice good good this one is easy
I don't think I believe you though that's the thing I don't believe the word you're saying
right now let's see I can't wait to everyone to do like the Pepe fucking like
I came up with the Pepe like you know he doesn't know it is when you got it when you take a
hard one now everybody knows that the Pepe laugh is that like it's the dog from Dick Dasterly
Kanye Kanye of wisdom okay I'll try it oh what's this what's this thing
what is this this is we sat on it did the delivery guy was he was he mad did he sit on
this shit like after yeah I'll show here to show this fucking asshole making me wait for big
chickens like stuffing under his ass did somebody sit on this why is that lettuce on
here I'm gonna make $20 right now what's on this do you see what happened let me show you
this look at this this is a piece of lettuce this is not I promise it might look like I've
ripped off a piece of tissue paper this is lettuce and let's see how it tastes very bad
desynced it shouldn't be desynced oh I'll fix that don't worry I'm not going to eat it
until it's synced up trust me what do you think I'm crazy we should be synced up see if
you can hear the bite react more this would it be react it's a mick chicken sandwich I
just showed you the the react more oh no I'm eat I'm about to eat why am I doing this
where's my 20 fucking bucks somebody said shoot 20 times
I don't know why that's making me laugh I'll try I don't think I chewed 20 times in my
whole life you're supposed that's how much you're supposed to chew 20 times right
that's impossible that's not possible it just turns into like gush it's not enough
making this not as enjoyable as it should be
no no no I'm not 33 I am hey look you get one life to be have to be 33 and have fun
I choose this life this is the life that I choose I I choose this okay oh that's a bad
choice this is a midlife crisis on stream I'm doing just fine rub it in your hair oh that's
so funny I look I'm now I feel like I'm gonna beat this level first try if I don't beat this
level first try I know that's a bad idea I was gonna say I was gonna eat this mick chicken
less than 10 seconds okay this bag of McDonald's is so huge what's even in here why are there
bacon fries in here are you sure what is that new item new item reveal what what the hell are
these oh these are the saddest disgusting look at these look at how awful this looks look at
this look at I have no there's no connection here between me and McDonald's this is a pure
opinion and a review of this item look at how shitty these look cheesy bacon fries you ready
for this that looks like somebody just blew a bloody snot rocket into fries is it chili
it's just right in the middle it's like an ice cream scoop of like bacon chili
you need a better picture of this this is terrible that's not that's a joke let's see
how they taste grocery store uh easy cheese out of the can wouldn't order again no wouldn't
order again that's been the review for the McDonald's bacon fries wouldn't order them again
put them in your nose you think that would you know all right I again I'm just like dicking
around and being like you know we're you know they notice that the streamers do that shit
oh we're like we're doing something stupid here like oh you know we're just having fun here
like Whitney I'm doing this I'm doing I'm being a fucking weirdo you guys are just like
watching and pointing the screen and laughing at it at me you know like oh we're like doing
this no we're not it's me but these are I'm gonna get McDonald's on the line man because
holy shit these are fucking not worthy these are bad did you hear that I'm done I'm done
playing game oh I'm just gonna I'm just gonna go to IRL and eat I wonder if the viewers will
go up watch me hit like 6k just sitting there eating like shitty ground bacon fries don't
have a lick your hands like that you've been touching things okay well that's it for
Mario Maker guys it was fun it was thanks for the levels thanks for participating and if you
gave me one and a lot most of them were really really good all of them were good I could hit
it big in the IRL section okay this is how you know I've like kind of lost my fucking mind
I was about to put this in here I was about to put the straw in here for some reason have I
been poisoned I don't understand here we go nobody drinks this much soda there's another
thing who the fuck is gonna drink this this is like 66 ounces of liquid this is like five
times your sugar content for the day this is not all right I had something was solid in there
I gotta change the directory I'm so self-conscious of eating on stream I fucking you I don't like
this I know people hate this I'm really sorry that you have to be subjected to this
hold on I'm going to social eating how about um what should the title be McDonald's review
I'm gonna do two out of five stars no how about two two out of five so far what do you mean so far
food and drink click the picture what picture oh god the fucking internet man
the guy all right thought that said the guy that delivered your big chickens gave you a
mario maker level hey man don't be like the food check out my level what else is in here
this is my chicken number two this is really weird and I gotta let me I gotta apologize to
people that have been watching this channel for a long time this is weird and um how am I
desynced again that make any that doesn't make any sense this is not even that weird
people do this shit every day people do what I'm doing right now every day every day this is not
even weird this is like normal for twitch isn't it I'm killing all these things this should be
fixed if I can make webcam a little smaller I don't like people looking at me there are we
better um we should be fine he's actually eating two I'm gonna I'm gonna eat three
I got three this is what people do they just like eat and collect money no but let me just
give wait I'm not gonna eat I'm not gonna chew and talk to you that's rude but let me just give a
bunch of community subs but let me also give 25 dollars right here and said I can't believe
faked eating the sandwich too do you why is this one doesn't have lettuce on it I wish I didn't
look at that this one does this one has no this does have lettuce on it it's like wood chips
that's the lettuce McDonald's what's going on here pre-recorded McChicken make me do
something I'll do it what's the flavor oh yeah I'm just reviewing this okay so we've got
the initial bite goes right through but it's hard because I'm missing like nine teeth so
when I get it back here it's I'm missing every moment so I have to like gum it like so once
it gets the initial bite down there these are spicy McChickens I don't know why but every
single time that I have ordered a McChicken in the last six months they've just given me a
spicy McChicken have they run out did McDonald's run out of regular McChickens and they're just
trying to pass it as not I don't get it show your feet are pre-recorded I would rather you
think this is pre-recorded I'm trying to click this link but chat is moving so fast
oh my god you know some streams that you just look back and you say I kind of regret
all the things I did over the last 40 minutes this is one of them just leave this up
there are spicy McChickens yeah
fucking dinosaur man like Barney Rubble
that's what your hands look like in a cartoon when Tom and Jerry come over and smash him with
a hammer oh I got something gross here yeah good thing the camera's not on because I
just bit into a solid chunk I just bit into a bone mm-hmm that was a bone oh there's
more bones in here I don't know something's in here something in here something fucked up
in here quick get this on screen something fucked up in there I don't know what that was it was
weird for fingernail don't say that I'm not saying that look I've wanted this I love McChickens
they're my favorite
the brain you're talking about a crayon don't say that when I'm eating that will laugh
oh my god invert the other picture it's like who's okay who's reacting to who here
which one of us is reacting I don't know who's the reactor who's stream what video is this
it's the council I'm not gonna lie I heard I swear to god I heard from inside of this can
I heard a there was sitting still on this desk I heard a like a bubble coming up and
popping up here like there's a fucking animal in here we got hold up we also got something
from it what is okay so we've also got I don't think I'm gonna be able to eat this
meal I'm gonna it's gonna be delicious anyways okay so um this is a no I promise you that's
not a picture of a salad that's a salad that's not a decorated plate that's a salad
I'm not gonna eat this salad I'm not gonna eat this salad and then here's the review
all right review time I gotta eat one more to find out I think yeah I gotta get one more
how's this one look let's actually unwrap this one well as we can see from the from the
unwrapping this somebody stomped on this this one's better this one what this one's a little
better fresher a little more of a zing to it although it kind of does have a little
happen something like the lettuces they're trying to get out and escape from out of the bump like
as you see the lettuce is trying to essentially get out it's crawling out to try to leave
sorry let me front page which didn't front page me right now that would be a mistake
that's no that's not real you guys with these pictures I swear this is this is not
even be eating a hamburger this is just like an old man where is it no that's not it this
is just like a regular picture of my profile and my gross beard I don't know what that's where
I just saved it where'd it go all right this this is like hold on where is it I'm just
realizing this right now these are the images that you see back to back next to each other
for the like the hair transplant commercials you know I'm saying and I do a voiceover
talking about hey you know I'm telling you it's my hair it's my hair I can do this
you know I can go swimming with this yeah I can do this now and they like go like that I just
great put it in your hair is now a thing oh I'm gonna take a bath tonight all right get this
shit out of here where's the picture I'm looking for now this is gonna sound crazy but that
looks identical and I mean identical to my grandmother identical if I had a picture of my
grandmother it would you would say the holy shit this is unbelievable why did the stream
turn into this because somebody said they would pay me 20 dollars if I don't know why I'm not
gonna put this one on stream because somebody said they were gonna give me 20 bucks if I
ate a McChicken so I mean three because I'm hungry guys oh man where is it I just saved it
so just this is just scary this is a scary picture that's scary what is this like
earth wind fire and water why do I have all these on the screen
there was this lady and her name was Brady and she had a house with a bunch of fucking kids
and they all were a big big family and they got in fights and shit no until the one day
this lady met this fellow and they knew that they were eating chicken bones because that's
what I just fucking ate again I better not I swear to god man I'm not trying to be mean about
this I got it I got this under control hold on wait a minute wait a minute you just wait right
there hold hold that thought here's the story of a lovely lady who was bringing up three
very lovely girls all of them had hair of gold like their mother the youngest one in
hell's it's a story of a man named Brady was busy with three boys of his own
that's the way we all became the brady bunch
the brady bunch the brady bunch that's the way we became the brady bunch
let me show you that I've been fucking going back to the gym in my dreams
uh does anybody want these everybody want these fucking disgusting things
anybody want a decorated plate salad I have to try it this is a review three two out of
it's probably too intense to be honest it's part of my eyes now I can't that's not a joke
I can't do that I can't fucking do that this is a comedy uh actually hold on a second here
hold on a minute here whoa hold on wait this is this is not bad this is actually pretty
fucking good this is actually a pretty good I think this somebody this is all right no it
just wait okay that's this is this is supposed to be carrots I think let me show you this
pretty good not bad but let's look at the but I don't know what these are I don't even know
these are edible are these cheez-its what are these what are those no that's horrible that's
a carrot it's a shaved carrot not they're not very it's it's not bad it's actually
pretty good I don't do dressing on myself I eat it like a fucking rabbit so uh question
I was making a joke I did we went up in viewers we did okay this is what you want
this is what you're gonna get this is the thing that you asked for this thing you ready
you can do the whole salad in your mouth at the same time I'm not doing that
fork or riot who goes to McDonald's and gets a fork they don't just hand them up they don't
just hand out those forks and what you're going to do is you're going to add two parts
of Parmesan cheese stir it up inside of that bowl chef chef John chef John from
foodwishes.com where did you come from I don't know if I want to eat one of these like
Reese's eggs surprisingly tangy so I'm I think I'm done I think I'm I think I'm gonna go to bed
watch if I saw your face in real life I would laugh what does that mean this is real this
isn't but this is not real life how is this you can laugh now salad dressing in here and
use it as shampoo like just like condition it in there but that's not gonna happen come on
yeah yeah come on this is not IRL this is food and drink but isn't that this is this
it's the same subcategory isn't it drink the dressing I don't like dressing I'm one of those
weird vampire people that doesn't like put dressing on their salads you thought about it
I don't like dressing in clothes I like dressing in clothes are we gonna see the big
chicken in the germa rumble dressing is gross you're not weird well that thank you thank
you for saying that all right I'm gonna go I'm gonna cap this up final review so it's two
out of five so far I'm gonna give it I'm gonna give it a three no I'm gonna give it
a two eight out of five and the only reason why I'm doing that is because if we start at five
these french fries actually like they could have come out of the trash like I'm just being that's
a review that's not me like that's a review that's my opinion of this what that is the
salad's actually pretty good if you want to if you got a McDonald's salad you'd probably
think it was all right so but that brought it down like a whole letter grade the McChickens
tasted really good except those bones in them like two of them had like these weird chewy
like calluses in them so that brings it down another grade but they still tasted good it's
still they're still perfect McChickens are all amazing 2.8 I think I got a five I'll see
you tomorrow I'm out of here I'm going I'm going home I'm going home I'm going I gotta
go home that's what that one just tasted like it came right out of the ground does
that mean it's fresh if it was like dirt if you taste dirt does that mean like it's
fresh and it came out of the ground if you saw a guy in the subway eating like this
you'd move like four chairs to the right guys eating a salad with his fucking hands
and no dressing whoa bye I'm gonna stand and hold on to the thing I'm gonna stand I'm not
gonna sit next to this person this is the subway of twitch yeah it kind of is all right
I've got my greens I'm like smoking a cigarette here sweat check I'm not doing that
because I've got a lot of big hair under my arms and that would be embarrassing and everyone
would laugh at me so I'm not doing that thanks for watching everybody I'll see you tomorrow
this is not even I think this is Dr Pepper it's pretty good Mario Maker is a ton of fun
I have uh I lost my mind a few times but still an amazing fun awesome experience
everybody making levels your creativity is fucking pretty sick I wouldn't classify this
as meltdown scream this was a positive meltdown you can use this two different meltdowns
there's like positive meltdown and there's negative meltdown you can go up you can have
an upwards meltdown there's a meltup yeah I still was having fun yeah that was a meltup
that's fine but let's go back we're gonna do the bits and we're gonna do the subs too
I've been sure for eight hours what the hell happened how do we get this far well all right
eight hours any who let's go back uh we had three dollars and fifty cents from
uh origin term I hear you're angry have your baby bottle it's right here I shouldn't be drinking
soda this late it's 11 o'clock at night Pacific I gotta like go to bed time flies when
you're having fun yeah it does this was a fun one I had a great time sauce bird thank you
sauce bird for the three bucks ring a ding ding banana phone oh shit you read this a
while ago you did a Larry David impression for me and I want to thank you for doing that
I thought it was great I do have another request if you are willing to try
can you do Larry David annoyed like he's telling people to go away
I didn't what get away from what get out get away from me get out of you
let me go fucking you idiot what you do you're crazy you're crazy you're crazy
fucking nailed it thank you sauce bird for the three bucks it's terrible in all caps
I don't know what this is doing why is it doing that it's fucking boiling there's something in
here thank you c4g for the 250 hi jerma I run the bot counting the plus two minus two score
in chat didn't catch the space engine stream but my friend linked me a clip afterward of
you saying that seeing the total in chat made you self-conscious didn't occur to me that
having your stream quantified like that would be stressful and I'm sorry I've turned it off oh
no no no no no it's I'm I was messing around no don't worry about that I'm just kidding around
it's funny that's why it's gone no it's okay it's fine I'm I'm mainly messing around don't
worry it was up by 2,500 by the end the flush joke really saved him that's it mainly
but don't worry about that c4g thanks for the 250 and it was fun it was a fun thing
hey Zach or Zeke thanks for the 250 sup Jeremiah just want to share with you guys that today I
got accepted to one of the top universities in Finland pretty freaking happy have a beer on me
also you're my favorite internet entertainer guy by far cheers well that's something to
celebrate congratulations on being accepted to one of the top universities in Finland I
told you guys there are smart people that are watching this stream lots of smart look at
that school kidding me but congratulations wish you luck and not drinking beer right now
but I will drink some of this soda cheers thank you and good luck no croissant thanks for the
ten dollars Mr. Champ thanks for the 25 dollars Jeremiah I'm in Vegas for a week what are some
good things to do to kill time there are so many things to do in Las Vegas that
I would not be able to even tell you anything there is a 100 shows going on
thousands of restaurants and bars and clubs the club part maybe not so much would be
that interesting but uh hash house a go-go in the link is probably my favorite restaurant in
Vegas it's get the stuffed burger get the blue cheese stuffed burger from hash house a
go-go in the link and you your life will change completely forever getting go to go to a magic
show you know there probably is a ton of those get drunk and wander around yeah as long as you
stay in you know stay on strip or stay downtown don't get too crazy but I hope you have fun
if you're of legal drinking age and you can go into the casinos there's tons of bars and
tons of stuff to do inside wasn't David David Copperfield in town probably Penn and
Teller are here I think forever I don't think they're ever gonna leave you really if you want
to see Penn and Teller they usually they have the show I think it's the Rio they have residency
there yeah I gotta go see Penn and Teller did they're awesome they've been killing it for
years strip clubs I don't I don't I don't know that's up for you to decide with research
I have no idea but thank you and I have a good trip German lied about Taco Bell thanks
to the 250 did someone say Diablo sauce they did it was me Savovsky gave 10 community subs
early there were a lot of community subs so I want to address the ones that I missed
uh but thank you Savovsky for the 10 bake me home thanks for the 250 you're gonna play the
new Pokemon games on stream no I don't think so never really was into Pokemon I respect
those games but I don't play them if that makes sense blue pundit thanks for the three
bucks breath of the wild when I feel like I need to do God of War before I do breath of the wild
does that make sense to anybody you know no no it's a very strange thing to say is it
hey I got to delete those photos of me when I was like eating yeah um I've got a war sounds
like something I would do and breath of the wild too there's endless amount of games to
play yes to follow the timeline no croissant thanks for five dollars germa is raiding chat
what I was doing but thank you for the five dollars lacronda thanks for the five dollars
believe in yourself I did a few times that I did beat some of those levels I'm so glad
I actually beat that hellish one what was it two people in the world beat it and I was number
three feels pretty good oh the controller I will that but for real though the down I
the down what I don't even need to say we already talked about it I like I put on a record
and just let it just repeat over and over again the down ground the down ground the down ground
pound like I've said that probably like a hundred times I probably could have it on a
button I could press and play it but thank you lacronda for the five dollars thank you
captain dread pirate to go for the 15 dollars okay it was funny at first but this whole I'm
bad at driving joke is getting old move on already bad at driving like that level is so hard
that level is so hard it takes precision it takes time the car is kind of hard to maneuver
I'm bad at driving joke well thank you for the 15 dollars appreciate it
yeah it was desert bus uh niall aurean thanks with four dollars hey germ I'm going
to McDonald's do you want anything this was seven hours ago I hope you got a McChicken
niall aurean hope you had fun I wonder what you had hope you enjoyed it uh mr spicy dude
thanks for the five community subs bonjour Tristan thanks for the three dollars this guy
is just kid jokes now I want adult humor e dragon thanks for the 30 dollars I missed
this earlier but thanks for the 30 bucks e dragon use this towards your therapy bills
thank you for the 30 bucks I appreciate it adult humor he literally said Mario could eat his ass
earlier yeah I know you know when you have this thing that you just want to say so bad
and you're just holding on to it and you just have your mouth shut and you just want to say
but you know you shouldn't say it you should not say this but it just happens anyways because
you can't set you can't control yourself you have to say this thing I felt it coming out and I felt
my brain said stop saying what jeez ass that's kind of how it played out
but thank you snoozing copter for the 250 dying or failing at something insanely
difficult after acing the part before it's something that defines you I want to see a
compilation of all the times this happened also you haven't played my levels yet please
do please please I think I got a couple of them we did at least one of them wait you guys convinced
him to eat McDonald's I didn't need very much convincing did you actually somebody made you
somebody just made a username German lied about breath of the wild and god of war
do you really have that non-faith in me at all that 10 seconds after I say I and maybe
I'll play those games at some point you immediately make that account wow I gotta work
on that I need some internal development here German lied accounts fall in uh bibin boy thanks
for the five subs rare pepe body lotion thanks for the five subs ferrodean weapon thanks for
the five dollars thanks for playing my level German heart I'll be sure to cook up some
better monstrosities if you stream this again I want to play the multiplayer but everyone
tells me it sucks and it's broken and laggy and all screwed up right I'll do it again
oh it was fixed okay it's too interesting to not play it a few more times I think it really is
I feel like there's still a bunch of stuff I haven't seen that are worth streaming we will
see you'll probably get at least one more Mario Maker 2 stream not this week though we've got
Dark Souls randomizer tomorrow which if you thought today was a little bit wild and weird
I would probably show up tomorrow that's probably gonna be even stranger
I just had a weird flashback of the first person abyss watchers people in the chat were actually
telling me dude like it's all right just like calm down and just stop for a while like
everything's all right don't worry about it man it wasn't the typical like oh you talk
oh no I can't believe you didn't miss that it was like hey dude just relax everything's
all right don't worry about it everything's gonna be fine that's how you can tell that like it's
you gotta stop hey just take just take a break it's all right like we can do something else
I'm rocking to do something else oh man it was all over the place for that hour and
I know it was like almost two hours three hours of the abyss watchers in first person
you get really mad when you play souls the angriest I've ever seen you was when you died
to twin princes twin princes I don't even remember twin princes dark dark souls three
oh the lawful prince okay yeah oh angry gamer yeah it's all right though it's all in good fun
the laser angel no now I remember that I hated every second of that that oh I the laser
angel from that DLC area I remember specifically almost hovering my mouse over just stop streaming
and then just pretend I had an internet outage like just just turn it off and just turn the
fucking whole thing off and yeah sorry internet fuck and just leave I was so angry doing that
you're right we're a total joke now yeah uh but thank you too thank you to uh sign out
gift 20 community subs this is shit low subs to give in one night imagine doing that but
italics is also streaming so we know you lied well I can't I can't do that that's
you've got evidence no croissant thanks for five dollars convo breaker thanks for five
dollars so the major problem here wasn't that this was just painful it was and caused my
mom to make groaning sounds but the kicker was uh hold on wait wait wait I think these
are out of order oh here we go yeah this is out of order they came in that weird um they came in
here we go hey jerma is from convo breaker 15 dolls from convo breaker uh so now they're
in the correct order when I read them like this hey jerma I'm a little late on this
but happy three years of being subbed to you on twitch thank you for that
before I get into this story I thought I'd say a couple one guy moment so you know who I
am I'm both the guy who suggested the 250 bits minimum and also the guy who you nearly killed
in his sleep what wait anyways back in the day during my mother's third trimester with me
she went to the zoo with a friend and her born kid they went to the turtle section they were
making noise which was weird you guessed it they were having turtle sex which freaked out
my mother's friend because she couldn't answer her kid to what they were doing
meanwhile my mom was dying laughing not but a few hours later early in the next morning
my mom's water broke and she started having me this was a minute you're what you are like in
six months old you are the most advanced child I've ever seen in my life uh this was a major
problem because she needed a doctor was we got to wait for the pain meds to kick in need to
try to resist the contractions this was a problem so the major problem here wasn't that
this was painful it was it caused my mom to make groaning sounds the kicker was my mom
sounded like the turtles so she was dying laughing trying to resist contractions waiting for
a see what is this like weird role play here what is going on waiting for a c-section while
i was about to take a shit in her stomach all right now i'm ending it here i'm gonna move on
also please play pyre there's a giant lady okay duly noted i just opened no no no i just
opened the stream and now i'm leaving now stay stay stay stay stay let me just explain what just
happened stay are you still here that was it's a bit message somebody was i was reading a message
somebody sent with it they can send 250 two dollars and 50 cents and i can i'll read it on
stream and i'm i'm still here all right so i was just reading a story that some person
just made up and you came in right when you heard the whole thing about like shitting in
stomach or something so i'm just reading a thing and welcome to the channel okay yeah enjoy
follow that stream if you're having a good time thank you hey trampston thanks for the five
dollars the big man is back www.thekidfrombrooklyn.com welcome back thank you trampston trampston
also gave 15 dollars right after that i'm going to come through your monitor and give you a
quick kiss on the nose i don't know what are these a reference to trampston gave six dollars again
go to macdonald get mcchicken what is this are these references is this is this other streamer
comedy here is this other youtube comedy this might be that i don't understand these references
this is this other youtube comedy or twitch uh comedy it's a weird video oh well thank
you trampston for the uh like 28 bucks more than that 26 right here thank you uh thank you to
daisy duke for the five dollars hey germa it was my birthday the other day i just want to
thank you for making me laugh every stream can't wait for the carnival stream though
every single one of your streams is just a special i love you lots have a great night you
too i'm looking forward to the carnival stream as well hopefully it is a lot of fun back in
thanks to the five dollars can't believe i had a pee pants moment sending you the wrong level
code felt really bad there but i'm glad you played it through anyway gives me insight on
what to do and not to do for challenge levels in the future have a great rest of your night
it was a good level it was a good level even if hey let me tell you something back and
if your wrong code is that then i'd like to see you write code because that was pretty damn
good so thank you thanks for the five dollars and thanks for your level pyro cat thanks for the 10
bucks i give you 10 bucks now you have to play my level and they say well ha ha ha ha just kidding
but it would make my night if you did crazy boss fight with meowser uh we'll hold on to
these i'm gonna do it again don't worry we're gonna play this at least one more time thank
you their night is ruined now no i'm gonna remember that name pyro cat i remember because
they said mua ha ha ha pyro cat mua ha ha ha that's the one i'm gonna play thank you j
diva for the 15 dollars buy a pro controller and they say pride 100 for the pro controller
i don't have a bunch of fucking switch peripherals i think i've rotten the
closet it's one controller but i got a switch controller xbox one playstation 4
pro controller game cube controller wee brick i'm not made out of peripherals just buy it you
nerd you can use the ps4 controller but that takes intelligence you are a peripheral i don't
i don't know why but that just offended me i that like if that's offending me right now
i'm i don't know why why is it offending me anyways thank you jay for the 15 dollars thank
you s10w update for the 10 dollars 10 dollars hey germy sorry you couldn't see my green screen
video limited space or something we did try to condense it so if your video did not get
through don't worry it wasn't a bad video we just want to condense it anyways the least i
can do is donate to my favorite streamer for the first time i'll help you the best and keep
being an inspiration have fun thank you so much for the 10 bucks i really appreciate it
i'm honored to be an inspiration for somebody so thank you for 10 bucks and thanks for hanging
out here hey trampston thanks for the five dollars while you're here look up quail ludes
coke quail ludes on youtube watch it while waiting for the big chicken i already ate the
big chicken no i know what i'm no youtube video i gotta go take a bath it's in chat right now
i'll give it five seconds
so the drug back there in the late 70s and 80s quail ludes the good old 14 and they changed it
to lemon i tell you i wish i had a couple of them fucking lemons now that was the best
fucking drug ever made it was so fucking good the government took them off the fucking market
but they were they were putting the fucking drug dealers out of
not addictive bring back the fucking quail ludes you could take all the fucking cocaine
marijuana
you're on a fucking
this is the big man
that it worked it was the same video what you probably will occur is i was playing the same
video yeah fucking what the hell is that oh he just was he was just screaming
okay thank you for that not addictive i've never seen that that's fucking bizarre my goodness
anyways thank you to thank you to nico cat for the five dollars hey germa usually i get
too tired and have to leave early but this mario maker stream has been one of my one of
the best and i haven't been able to put it down germa hart thank you i was wondering
have you ever heard of a game called la mulana it's a really interesting but difficult puzzle
adventure game i bet you'd enjoy it never heard of it la mulana let's look it up it is
currently on sale by an extreme margin it is five dollars is it any good let's see
like a spelunky i'm getting some spelunky vibes it's good is it good it's good all right
put it on the list put it on the list add it to the germa lied about uh guild wars guild of
god of war again germa lied about guild wars too i'm not playing that fucking game
but thank you for the five dollars velemi thanks for the 25 dollars better not fake
this one i ate three spicy McChickens on stream and it was a mistake because i can
already feel my stomach moving around but it was worth it because it was good tasted good
except the bones whatever they were but thank you for the 20 that was a huge burp and i sucked
it in you didn't hear it thank you velemi for your 25 bills maxi kaspersky thanks for the
three bucks maniac eats ass lettuce on stream future gamer thanks for the 15 dollars these
cost me 20 dollars you did it also please listen to your horrid noises so you probably
should turn your microphones down because this is going to be loud yeah that was a huge cartoon
gulp swallow because i was nervous hey but thanks for your 20 dollars in 1500 bits thank
you i did eat him pretty good syke syke spiegel thanks for the 15 oh that's not 15 it's five
it's five dollars no message but thank you appreciate it hunter peck thanks for the 20
20 dollars here you go i had to stay up until 1 a.m to pay you to eat a McChicken
it's money well spent but please me first hard level and easy level hold on to these
i'm gonna know because hunter peck said 20 dollars for the McChicken these are both these
are two McChicken levels the contract is complete hey egg scramble thanks for the 250
would you ever serve McChickens that you sat on at a family dinner if so how long would
you sit on them would you season with salt and pepper maybe a little marshmallow flop
i wouldn't sit on any food and serve it to somebody thanks for the 250 uh egg scramble
appreciate it wait why did that was okay that egg scramble said that syke spiegel said this
three bucks i'm i'm attributing messages to the wrong people that was egg scramble that
wants me to sit on food uh syke spiegel thanks to the three dollars doling out bits more slowly
so your trash bag auto mod doesn't delete me and time me out immediately fuck you bot
wait what your trash bag auto mod tweak we'll tweak it thanks to the three dollars like
velemi thanks for the 25 more dollars velemi and velemi gave 10 community subs right after
i can't believe faked eating sandwich what a scam i ate three of them like you've given
a lot of money and a lot of subs tonight so thank you for both of those things
let's get the credits to roll that was the camera usually the credits are right at the
top but this time they're not roll those credits are you gonna roll them or what
are you gonna roll them or what are you gonna roll them or what then uh you're not gonna
i'm gonna go in here and do it there you go here they go these are all the subs all the
resubs gifted subs eight and a half hours worth tonight thank you guys all of you whether
you're a new viewer an old viewer you happen to stumble upon this channel an hour ago
and follow and then after the second or third mayonnaise on my mouth you unfollowed
and you just went back to your normal day went back to whatever you were doing
thank you really appreciate it everybody but we have uh some more bits to do as they fly by
no croissant five dollars no message thank you uh velemi uh ended the night here with
another five dollar drop hey germa all joking aside i just want to say that your streams
and videos have never failed to be fucking with chickens coming up never failed to brighten
my day glad i can give something back and i wish you the best in all your future endeavors
i'm going to get you to chug mountain dew someday though i swear to god it would take
a lot because if i did that my like intestinal problems would go nuts i just looked over here
and got sick because i looked over at these bacon fries but thank you for let me more than
happy to be here but i don't think you're gonna get me to drink mountain dew throwback
because i will puke appreciate it though i'd i'd ever agree thanks to the five bucks
here's a new disgust emote am i thinking what the hell is wrong with me that's just seven
and seven and a half hours of mario maker you just kind of just don't give a shit anymore
you know thank you to dc pro for the two dollars and 85 cents hey germ funny ass
munching tonight got any life advice you seem like the person who would be able to share
some good sense also watch out for those chicken bones life advice i don't know i don't know if
this is this two um there's two avenues that this comet could be could be serious but then
could be like you're eating salad with your hands like i you could give me some good advice
you know what i mean i'm not sure which avenue this is this is my reaction to seeing
any of his new low effort streams once streamers and youtubers start making money they stop
trying what it's the imger comment i'm about to drop three or four times the amount of money
i spent on germa rumble live for a carnival stream if you think i'm dialing back i'm not
sure even paying attention if it's i it might be ironic i don't know it could be it could be
bait too if that's your opinion it's not baiting you're not fucking around then i'm
sorry i feel that way but you won't do the no i'm not gonna do the macaroni tub
uh we've been uh we've been baited pack it up this is these least these fucking low energy
streams if there's not two clowns of unsubbing just wait just give me a little bit of time
all of your dreams will come true a new car well all of your stream dreams will come true
anyways uh let's keep going thank you to nova ostra for the four dollars germa long time watcher
first time cheer happy pride and i absolutely love watching you you never fail to make me laugh and
help me feel better you're so hilarious and creative much love to you thank you for all
your hard work when they say lesbian pride transgender pride thank you so much nova ostra
long time watcher first time cheer it's never necessary but thank you
i appreciate the very kind words thank you so much i'm glad you think that also ec long thanks
to the 250 hey germa been a fan since early 2013 i'm not able to catch every stream just
because of my job but my girlfriend and i both love your content you're easily one of the
greatest content creators internet personalities have had the pleasure of seeing good night
thanks that's a long time two back-to-back long time watchers i hope you stick around
because there is way more to see thanks to the 250 thank you bro day day for the five
dollars appreciate it no message five bucks regard no way thanks for the three dollars
will you try my friend pedro really challenging and you should definitely check it out
i heard it's fun i heard it's hard to control though oh no fuck come on
what the fucking salad just hit the ground and it's everywhere god damn it
fucking fancy i was gonna eat that i was gonna eat this i still am like
uh you just have to rinse it you can just it's lettuce you just hold it
go under cold water it'll be all right five second rule it's lettuce how did that even
happen you know i'm just glad it wasn't the bacon cheese french fries because that imagine
there was um dressing all over this that's the best possible scenario of something dropping
something remember when you asked me if i was sure about eating in my office six months ago
yeah but this was different this was yeah but this was different this this was no i this was
uh all right all right all right i'm out of here i gotta i gotta get out of here
i gotta go i gotta go i gotta get the fuck out of here uh actually there's two more bits but
uh regardo gave three dollars my friend pedro there's worth a look we just got a lot of shit
to do uh bro day day thanks for the five dollars never donated before i completely
forgot to send a message but i've been a fan for years and seeing the playstation spellbook
videos in high school he's the only streamer i watch and i really appreciate everything you've
done for the community keep being awesome you're honestly the best that's a that's
fucking an incredibly nice thing to say i hope you keep watching there's a lot more to do
in this time that i have on this platform i'm gonna try it and then two right at the very end
tingy 250 fill a tub with jello and sit in it it's a waste of food i don't want to do that
i don't want to fill a tub with mac and cheese i would rather eat the mac and cheese very
slowly over the course of three years jello is not food uh dread dead regal thanks for the
250 last minute bits jerma love the stream great inspiration thanks also have you thought
about playing black and white one or two yes i have the god games they seem very fun
it's still just a ton of things to do that's why the recommended channel really is so good
if you have anything just put it there because i scroll through it all the time and i'm pulling
out stuff i have a notepad that i keep of stream ideas and games to play and stuff to
try so definitely throw if it's not in there already give a search in that discord if you're
not in the discord it's a public discord for the community and it's there have fun use it
but i will i will see you guys tomorrow i'm gonna do dark souls randomizer
see you guys tomorrow have a great night see you around three to four o'clock pacific
ta-ta and good night