Hey, what's happening everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 game play commentary.
And tonight, got a couple of clips back to back here. One as the Forcinaceous Scout and one as the Shortstop Scout.
And then later at the end of this video, there's gonna be an engineer trolling bonus clip.
I guess you could call it a bonus clip. And, you know, I never do videos like that.
I never do like trolling type videos, but we had an opportunity to do this, and it was pretty ridiculous.
I felt bad about it afterwards, but you'll see, it's quite funny.
So let's start talking about the loadout I have on right now, using the Forcinacea.
And if you are an old viewer, if you've been around for a long time, you will notice that this is the first ever Forcinacea gameplay.
This is the first time I've ever used the Forcinacea in a video.
And there's a very good reason for that. I'll explain as we go along here.
But I just wanted to make sure I covered this item and, of course, the Shortstop coming up in the next clip.
But I'll give you the reasons why I don't like this weapon. Let's start off, of course, with the Forcinacea. I'm using it right now.
The reason why I don't like this weapon is because of situations like you're about to see right here.
So this sniper, I get behind him. And if you don't know, the Forcinacea has a very large knockback when you shoot somebody.
See, take a look right there. I could have easily have gotten the kill on him right there with any other of the scatter gun choices.
But instead, I launched him five, ten feet in the air, missed a bunch of shots. I eventually got the kill on him.
But that brings up a pretty large problem. You're going to be knocking people around all over the place with this weapon.
And you're going to be knocking yourself around as well.
And if you're one of those scouts that loves to do air battles, where you're in the air most of the time, you jump around a whole lot,
this can really throw off your timing because you'll jump in the air to shoot somebody and you'll launch yourself backwards.
And it can be very tricky. And the gun does shoot more pellets than the regular scatter gun, though, so it can do more damage.
So that's why a lot of people use it, and I can understand that.
But I don't have a lot of success with it, so I typically stay away from it.
But I wanted to make sure I covered it and gave you guys my thoughts on it.
So let's move on to the next one. And this one is actually one that I enjoy using.
So right now I'm using the full Milkman set, which includes, if you don't know, the short stomp, the mad milk, the holy mackerel,
and then the special delivery hat that the scout has.
And the whole set gives you plus 25 extra health, so you end up with 150 health, which is really awesome.
And I mean, it really does give you a little bit more protection.
It gives you that extra little inch that you might need if you get hit by a rocket or a spam shot from a Demoman.
So it can really be the deciding factor if you stay alive or not.
But let's talk the short stomp. So the short stomp, it just recently got a nerf.
If you're unaware of the nerf, the nerf is a 50% extra reload time, which sort of took a lot of the spam factor down on this weapon.
before, you could just sit there and go grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr
grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr grr gr
He was kind of our point man. You'll see him right here. He was calling out over Skype where people were coming
He's like, all right left side right side. So it was just it was just ridiculous
I felt like we were doing some type of military operation like operation century down even though the century stay up the whole time
So they oh it almost goes down right there. If you just saw that it was like three stickies right there
It didn't end up going down. So here we go. I get it right in front of the spawn door this book this I
Can't tell you how bad I felt right now
I was just like oh that guy's gonna be mad and then eventually stealth comes over on the right side with his century and
They can't get out of the spawn
We have them trapped with century guns and we are essentially just really bad people
So I just thought you guys might get a kick out of this. We didn't do this again
This was kind of a one-and-done thing. We weren't gonna do this the whole time
So what you see right here is all we did. I promise so that's gonna be the end of the video guys
Thank you all so much for watching
I really do appreciate it and I will see you guys all next time. So take care everybody