Hello ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to the grandpa Christmas album. I want to be the first to welcome you to this selection of fantastic, beautiful songs for the holiday season.
And we're going to start it off with this one of my favorite. This is Deck the halls with boughs of barley.
Let me bring my grandson in here for a second. Jeremy, come on in here Jeremy.
Yeah, a little bit of a duet here. Uh, yeah. Okay, there we go. So you do the first. What song is this? You're going to do I'm going to say fire you say that I say we're going to go back and forth.
I'm just going to sing the lyrics. Okay, just just do it. Here we go.
I'll tell you.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? How long is this song?
I can't even it's hard to do this like you don't do a Christmas album. If you don't look at the lyrics, I can't do that in song is still going.
This song is still going. Do you know the rest of the lyrics? No, but you know, I don't know. Is it really like three minutes in this bullshit? Yeah. Okay, whatever.
Just didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't
love and respect and giving me grandpa free stuff so give me all the things you got hold on hold on
up whoa ho who want it go don't don't go who want it oh whoa up on the roof just click click click
comes out saint nick with my stuff just so um hold on this is the wrong page
get this cause here is a hammer lots of tacks oh so a ball and whip and it cracks oh oh oh who
would you go oh oh oh who wouldn't go up to the store to get my house down through the chimney
with your clothes i want a new sweater yeah put that on your list this is where we slow it down
a little bit on the album relax a little bit and here is a silent night
silent night
everything is bright
round yon virgin mother
sleep in heavenly peace peace sleep come on sleep in heavenly
silent night holy night shepherd's quake at the sight
glory stream from heaven
come on
all the fields we go laughing out of way bells and bobtail ring making spirits bright
what fun it is to laugh and sing in a slaying sound tonight oh jingle bells jingle bells jingle
all the way oh what fun it is to ride in a one-horse self-made sleigh hey jingle bells jingle bells
all the way oh what fun it is to ride inside of my sleigh a day or two ago i thought i'd take a ride
and soon miss fanny bright was seated by my side who the hell is that yours was lean and blank
misfortune seemed his lot well this is making sense drifted back and i want to go to store
oh jingle bells jingle bells jingle all the way oh what fun it is to ride in a one-horse open sleigh
hey jingle bells jingle bells jingle all the way oh what fun it is to ride in a one-horse open sleigh
now i want to take a second here to bring up something that's really important to the
holiday season and that's given to your local charities whether it be one dollar two dollars
ten dollars anything like the food bank or if your school is having some type of charity drive for
toys for younger kids or something then please do it because even if you give a dollar like i said
it's really important to these families so do that if you have the money then go for it baby
and that's going to end jingle bells one horse open sleigh oh holy night the stars are brightly
shining it is the day of our dear saviors birth long lay the world in sin and therapy
yes till he appeared and the spirit felt it were a thrill of hope the weary world rejoices
for yonder breaks a new and glorious morn fall on your knees oh hear the angels voice
oh night divine the night when christ was born oh night oh holy night oh night divine oh night
divine led by the light of faith serenely beaming with glowing hearts by his cradle we stand
oh the world is a star so sweetly gleaming i don't know how the song really goes so i'm
just improvising i might as well just make up my own lyrics because i i can't do this and time it
takes on by nothing you can do but cry that was pretty good somebody write that down that was a
good lyric oh holy night the stars are brightly shining it is the day of our dear saviors birth
well this album is going to come to an end now i just want to say from the bottom of my heart
thank you everybody so much for all the support you give my grandson and me on this channel and
we love you so much we really do and it's a holiday season everybody have a very safe very
happy merry christmas happy new year and any holiday you happen to celebrate and we're going
to end this one on a strong note on a good note going to bring in everybody you've ever heard on
this channel we're going to bring in anthony wimbleton we're going to bring in germa we're
going to bring in frank my friend frank we're going to bring in all these people school principal
is even going to be here so i hope you guys are ready again we love you and have a happy holidays
happy safe holidays and of course take care everybody we wish you a merry christmas we wish
you a merry christmas we wish you a merry christmas and a happy new year we wish you a merry christmas
we wish you a merry christmas we wish you a merry christmas and a happy new year tidings to you
wherever you are good tidings to christmas and a happy new year oh bring us a figgy pudding oh
bring us a figgy pudding oh bring us a pretty pudding and a cup of good cheer we won't go until
we get some we won't go until we get some we won't go until we get some so bring some out here
i'm seriously not leaving till i get some what i'm not leaving the house till i get some you
better give it to me there's nothing here what that's just a song oh whatever we wish you a
merry christmas we wish you a merry christmas we wish you a merry christmas and a happy new year
we wish you a merry christmas we wish you a merry christmas we wish you a merry christmas and a happy
new year good night everybody have a happy safe holidays from our family to yours
merry christmas happy holidays take care everybody we'll see you soon