Now you listen here, you bumped me, and my car, and my wife, and she's pissed about it, now I gotta call the insurance.
Granny wants this car, motherfucker.
You see what you did? You see what you did now? Now you're dead.
Alright, let's get out of here. Let's get the fuck out of here, quick.
No, no, no, why you?
Oh no, I've left it on.
I'm holding a loan.
I'm coming, Elizabeth, I'm coming to join you.
This lady is going the wrong way on the off-ramp.
This lady is shit-faced.
Don't you see the signs, lady?
Oh my god.
She finally stopped.
What? Is she dead?
I think this old lady just died behind the wheel. I swear.
Is she? Hold on a second.
Hold on a second.
She's dead.
That's bad news. You shouldn't be this happy.
I don't think you understand what just happened. That's never been...
No.
What is with these dying old people?
Oh my god.
Get in the car.
Hold your horses, I got a stubbed toe here. I got like a bad knee.
What are you doing?
I'm getting in.
What are you doing out here at this hour in this fog?
It's this bad in London. I don't remember it being this bad here.
This is not even London.
That's what I'm saying.
This is San Francisco, are you fucking stupid?
You're stupid. I don't know how to be stupid.
Oh no, you just fucking ran over a bunch of people.
Oh my god.
Hide the bodies.
No, you fucking idiot.
All right, pick them up.
You're not supposed to shoot me.
Do you like my old woman voice?
Yes, which one of them is it? I know. You told me to come look at the house.
I don't know which house it is.
I see one on the left.
Which further down?
Oh, okay. Yeah, I see it. I see the house.
Now, this is for sale? How much is this house?
You're going to show me.
Okay. Geez, it's a tough drive to come down.
What kind of house is this?
Hey, uh, I'm the guy you're meeting.
I'm sorry. I don't have legs, so they made me become part of a bike.
I am this bike.
You got the drugs?
I have the drugs. I'm just so excited about these drugs.
Oh, yes. I'd love some crack.
I'd also love some cocaine.
It's not worth it.
No, come back. I just need those drugs.
This is confusing me so much.
This is seriously so confusing.
I feel like I'm moving, but I'm not at all.
Can I get, like, hit?
Hold on.
I'm throwing punches.
If a car runs into me, will I bump into it?
No, I go right through it.
I mean, I guess this is a good bike.
I'm just going to get off of it, you know?
No sense in, like, you know, staying on the bike.
What would I want to stay on the bike for, you know what I mean?
All right, he looks like the main character from Katamari Damacy.
You know, Katamari.
He, like, it's too heavy.
He's just like, eh.
Why's he wearing his nuts?
Oh, it's just hard driving his bike like this.
Yeah, it's tough, you know.
You can't get any sleep on the road for crying out loud.
This is so dumb.
I'm telling you for the last time, you shouldn't divorce me.
You shouldn't do it.
I don't want to be married to any man that would grow a mustache just to spite me.
Yeah, I did.
I did grow it just to spite you.
You're right.
Because you're old.
Well, he looks ugly.
You're ugly.
Bill, you got to...
You're a bitch.
I'm supposed to talk to him about this.
You need to pipe the fuck down while I...
Hey, Bill doesn't need to know.
He just needs to sign the papers.
We're just here to tell him.
We need to sign the papers.
Bill, where are the papers?
Just let us know.
I don't think I have the papers on me right now.
He doesn't have the papers.
Look, the papers are in your office.
We'll just go over there.
You care if we go to your office?
I'm not sure you can...
We're going to your office.
Yes!
Hey, guess what?
You know why we're going to your office?
Fucking kill him.
Kill this motherfucker.
What the hell?
All right.
Jerma?
Yes.
Welcome.
I think we finally died.
This is the end of the land.
Come with me.
Come back.
No.
It's my turn.
You never hold my hand anymore.
I'm getting it.
And you're the grandmother.
You killed the guy.
I don't know how you got in there like that quickly.
It's these things on the top that are keeping me in.
You're in.
They said it couldn't be done.
Look how many cars are in the ceiling.
What did you do?
I fucked this whole thing up.